All performances have concluded!
Jeez!
Could you stop moving?
There's no point to this...
It's required!
This is a pageant, right?
You know, a beauty contest?
Or what, you think you're
too cute for makeup?
As it turned out...
her old man didn't show up
for the wrestling event.
Kushieda, Taiga's biggest supporter,
never even came to the dressing room.
Class 2-C!
Assembly begins in twenty minutes!
Yikes!
I have to get ready to MC!
Takasu-kun, how's the costume coming?
G-Good.
I'm done.
I just made some alterations
to one of Taiga's dresses.
That's really nice, Takasu-kun!
Y-You think?
I was aiming for something Juliet-esque.
An Empire silhouette.
- A flowing and graceful A-line.
- Takasu-kun is...
- Sheer organdy.
- kinda scary.
- The pinnacle of romance.
- His face isn't the only thing that's scary.
There's also a prop to go with it.
Taiga, wanna try this on?
You're still waiting for your old man?
I seriously doubt he's coming.
I'm not.
He's probably late because of work,
so I was gonna tell him to bring
a gift to make up for it.
Really, now.
Shouldn't we revise your intro, just in case?
No need.
Just do it like we practiced.
But you're...
Kawashima-san, it's almost time!
Sorry! I'm coming!
So you're really okay with this?
Drop it.
If you say so.
You're the boss.
Hey.
What was that about her intro?
Nothing important.
Time to get her dressed.
Takasu-kun, scram!
R-Right.
Come on, Aisaka-san.
I could never smile and watch while
my friend's being hurt.
Old man...
You're coming, right?
No matter how late you're running,
you'll rush straight over, won't you?
Isn't that what it means...to be a father?
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Sorry for the wait!
At long last, we bring you the
Miss Ohashi High School pageant!
Ohashi High School Culture Festival
(Part Three)
Ami-chan in fishy-fishy...
Netty-netty...
Fishnet stockings!
Please quiet down, everyone!
Or else, I'll have to punish you!
Get my drift?
Listen to me!
Shut the hell up, you worthless pigs!
A pig that can't fly is just pork!
Kidding!
Damn...
She's trying to steal the spotlight
when she's just the MC.
Okay, let's begin!
Entry number one!
Mitsui Yuriko-san from class 1-A!
W-Welcome home, M-Master!
She's such an adorable maid.
Went with the Victorian look, did you?
- Her grip on the mic is killing me!
- Y-Yes.
Thank you!
- No one's even listening.
- And now, I'll introduce our next contestant.
Here we have a maid
with a lovely smile.
- Entry number two!
- A message?
What!?
Sender: Aisaka (Dad)
Subject: A favor
This can't be real...
Could you relay a message
to Taiga for me?
I'll be gone for a while on business.
Some stuff has come up, so we
won't be able to live together.
Apologize to the princess for me.
Thanks.
Why...?
Why did I ever believe him?
I was fooling myself.
I thought this was for the better.
That I needed to support Taiga.
But...
In truth...
I was just feeling down...
about Taiga's father showing up...
and that she'd be going far away.
I was trying to ignore how pathetic I was...
What the hell do you mean?
That's crap.
She was dead right.
I was just being selfish.
I was...
- Okay! Thank you very much!
- Takasu, you okay?
- You look a little pale.
- Taka-chan...?
What do I tell Taiga?
How can I face her?
The wait is over, folks!
Welcome the girl who needs no introduction,
class 2-C's Palm-top Tiger!
Aisaka Taiga-san!
No way...
The Palm-top Tiger?
Wow...
She's cute...
Whoa...
Um...
Believe it or not, today we have...
Aisaka-san's father in the
audience to cheer her on!
The intro they were talking
about in the dressing room...
Could Mr. Aisaka please
give us a shout out?
Um...
Maybe he isn't here?
Move on to the next girl!
Tai—
U-Um...
Aisaka-san?
A-Are you okay?
Hey, Takasu the Delinquent
is cheering his partner on!
The Palm-top Tiger's actually pretty cute.
Right on!
The Palm-top Tiger rules!
Even if she's a huge klutz!
Forget your old man!
Wait...
Shut the hell up!
I...I took my deadbeat father,
chopped him up, tore him apart, and
tossed him into a m-mor...morgue!
Time for the talent portion!
Hey!
Bring it over!
C-Coming!
Zip it up!
Um...
Don't pick me up!
Unzip it!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I couldn't do a single thing for her...
This year's Miss Ohashi is...
Aisaka Taiga-san!
Way to go, tiger!
Yeah...
Now that everybody's celebrating
for her, she must feel...
No!
That's wrong!
Isn't she all alone?
Takasu?
I have to go...
- Excuse me!
- I have to go to her!
- The hell? Hey!
- I might not be much help!
But still...!
What happened?
It's totally dark!
What's going on?
Attention!
The beauty pageant's over!
It's the guys' turn now!
Here's how this'll go down!
Mr. Lucky Man!
Mister...
...Lucky Man?
What's that?
We've set up a course on campus!
Run it.
Whoever comes in first will
be declared the winner!
They're going to make us race
during the Culture Festival?
Sounds like a drag.
I should mention that
Mr. Lucky Man will be awarded...
the honor of crowning this year's
Miss Ohashi with this tiara,
and the right to ask her to dance.
Along with all my notes, and the answers
to all exams from the past three years!
The president's notes!?
A dance with the tiger!?
In their dreams.
Do want!
Taiga...
I don't need any prizes.
I don't care about being Mr. Lucky Man.
I'm just going to do whatever it takes...
- Be careful y'all don't get hurt, got it!?
- to beat every one of them...
and win!
Scary!
Scooch that way...
Whoa, it's the delinquent!
He's gonna kill us...
On your marks!
Get set!
I'll reach Taiga!
The course consists of one
lap around the school!
Run, boys, run!
Run for all you're worth!
Hell yeah!
We took out Takasu!
Sweet!
Now's our chance!
Bastards...
I won't let you beat me!
Here they come!
Hang in there!
Takasu-kun's back in action!
That's right!
I'm...
Sorry!
That hurt!
Damn...
Whose bright idea was it to make
this part of the course!?
Screw this!
Takasu-kun!?
Seriously!?
Is that even allowed!?
Why are you trying so hard!?
Shut up!
I have my reasons!
Piss off!
There's no way...
that I'm gonna lose!
Why did you move out of the way!?
Why did you!?
- They're here!
- Oh, the leaders are in sight.
Hang in there!
- Wow! It's Takasu the Delinquent!
- Ryuji...
Well...
Mi—
Kushieda!?
- A girl!? Wait, is that allowed?
- Kushieda?
It's fine!
Girls can participate too!
Takasu-kun, were you even paying
attention when you met him!?
Did you take a good look at him!?
She was right.
I wasn't paying attention!
Giving her money every month
through a bank deposit...
Dragging her along, without
considering her needs...
Apologizing for breaking his
promise by sending me a text...
He never gave a rat's ass about Taiga.
And...
I failed to see it!
I'm an idiot!
Ryuji... Minorin...
Damn it!
Track team pride!
- Hey! How dare you do that to a girl!
- Kushieda!
- And you call yourself men!?
- Kushieda-senpai!
Take this!
All riiiiiiight!
Go, Takasu-kun!
Go to Taiga!
What are you...?
Now!
Heya!
Double KO!
- What!?
- Attack!
Kushie—
Go!
Ahead of everyone else!
Ahead of me!
You don't need to worry about me.
Weren't you watching?
I don't need any help
to get back on my feet.
So...
I'll be fine.
Really, don't worry about me.
I'll be okay.
I can get back on my
feet without any help.
I can survive just fine...on my own.
Woo-hoo!
Class exhibit! Pageant! Lucky Man!
All swept...
...By our class!
The Culture Festival was a huge success.
Yes...
Your last Culture Festival...
I'm glad I had the opportunity to be
your student council president.
I'm glad I had the opportunity
to know you all.
I have some business to attend to.
You should go enjoy yourself, Kitamura.
But...
You worked the hardest to
make this festival a hit.
O-Okay...
I-I'll go!
I've never given a damn about that guy.
Really couldn't care less.
But...
Taiga, you were...
Anyway, you and Minorin
put on quite the show.
When did you two make up?
Now look here...
Oh!
Minorin!
Taiga! Here you are!
Minorin! Minorin! Minorin!
I love, love, love you!
Yes, yes. I know, I know, I know.
You look adorable, Taiga.
That tiara suits you perfectly.
It's the tiara you gave me!
Wasn't Takasu-kun part of it?
I know nothing, saw nothing,
heard nothing!
Oh, Dumb-chi's in heat again!
Ami-san, please dance with me!
Bring it on!
Hey, what are you doing!?
It was a year ago...
Taiga's father showed up out
of the blue, just like this.
I was so happy about them
living together again.
But...
Just like this time...he up and vanished.
Sorry, Takasu-kun.
Wha—?
What?
Clearly, I'm the one who should apologize.
No, I should.
I knew full well what he's like,
but I didn't tell you.
Taiga didn't say anything to me.
I...
I care about Taiga so much.
I was probably jealous of you.
Why didn't Taiga say anything?
She knew I'd get mad.
Taiga doesn't want her father
to be seen in a bad light.
That's why she hasn't breathed a word
about her family since that day.
To me, anyway.
Jeez...
Where did Dumb-chi run off to?
Honestly...
Aisaka.
Are you alone?
Would you mind dancing with me?
I guess that won't work,
since I'm not Mr. Lucky Man.
Again...
Why are you...always so...
Aisaka?
Never mind.
Thank you.
Then...
How do we do this?
We hold hands,
look into each other's eyes,
and spin around until we're tired.
I think.
Maybe I prefer girls.
I just have this feeling...
I-I kinda hope that's not the case...
Yeah.
That came out so naturally...
Whatcha up to, Taka-chan!?
Don't be a bore!
Let's party together!
After all, we're the best class!
Yeah, yeah!
Kitamura and Tiger secured!
Hey!
Taiga...
Okay!
Let's dance the Culture Festival night away!
Yeah!
This is a special night.
It's a time to put certain feelings aside,
though I feel a pain in my
chest every time I laugh.
Even once this night is over...
I'm sure, somehow...
everything will be all right.
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
BURNING LOVE
Burning love.
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
Attention, audience!
This is a duel of fate!
I will activate the ultimate spell, Legend
of the Palm-top Tiger of Happiness!
And it'll still be my turn.