Will you dress up as a girl if I win?
That's a funny joke.
Nice joke.
Will you dress up as a girl?
How did things turn out like this?
Hi mondai hitori to futari
Hi!! 問題:ひとりとふたり
Hi! A question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり?
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
assou ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日もだいすき
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you
watashi no baka
わたしのバカ…
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da!
星の数よりもバカだっ
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね…だって! 恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaette kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えって 君と？＋私＝
Answer me. What do you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Question 4
Me, True Feelings, and the Dignity of Men!
Let us go back to one hour ago.
Yuuji, how about a game of "I Doubt It"?
Oh, you sound pretty confident.
Oh, you didn't get sick of it when you had to pay for our meal last time?
Thanks for the food.
I'll get my revenge today!
Oh, will you now? We'll bleed
every last penny out of you!
Okay, are the usual rules fine?
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy Class F "I Doubt It" Rules:
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy
Place the cards face down on the table.
"I Doubt It" Rules
I'm playing an Ace.
The others ponder whether it was the truth or a lie.
If they think it's a lie, they declare:
Doubt!
Lie
If it is indeed a lie, whoever played the card picks up the entire stack.
True
However, if it's not a lie, whoever called "Doubt" picks up the stack.
The game continues until someone runs out of cards.
Doubt!
Lie
The first person to run out of cards wins.
Doubt!
True
Class F Local Rules!
The winner is whomever is the first to have only two cards remaining.
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
This means the game ends more quickly!
The key is paying attention to the suits of each card.
The key is paying attention
to the suits of each card.
The one who collects the stack can choose which card to start with.
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Vic
tory
Class F Local Rule
Be careful which one you choose, or you might get yourself into trouble.
Be careful which one you choose
or you might get yourself into trouble.
... (Yeah, yeah.)
Well then, I'll start.
Here's an Ace.
My turn, then.
A two.
Three.
Now it's my turn!
Fou—
Doubt!
I didn't even finish saying it!
It's totally obvious.
It's written all over your face.
You shouldn't be playing cards.
I never play my first few cards
honestly; it helps me out later—
Not one of them was honest!
Tick.
I need to be very careful right now.
Three.
Four.
You played a four again, Akihisa.
I call doubt.
Idiot! I've got a present for you!
Are you serious?
You still had a four from the first round, didn't you?
It was a trick!
Not bad!
I can't tell them I didn't see the four that round.
Tick.
At last, six cards left.
Hideyoshi has four.
This is a critical moment.
How will they play?
A six.
Voyeur, play a seven.
Oh, seven!
No one got to call doubt!
He's good!
It's hard not to play the card
with that kind of coercion.
Then, I'll...
Huh?
Oh, what are you all doing?
Himeji, I thought you went home?
No, a teacher asked me to help.
They gave me this as thanks!
Would you like some?
Thanks, Himeji, but can you wait
until we're done with this game?
We made a little be—
I shouldn't say "bet".
N-No, we're not betting.
There's just a penalty for losing.
There's a penalty?
That's right.
Each time you lose a hand, you
have to remove a piece of clothing.
Clothing?
Hideyoshi.
D-Don't, Akihisa!
Th-That's perverse!
Himeji, we're all men, so you don't have to get so—
Doubt!
Why are you giving me all the cards?
Even if it's just guys, it's still wrong!
Let's have some chocolate...
...and talk a little.
All right, all right.
Just this one last game, okay?
Let's get this wrapped up quick.
Huh? Himeji?
An eight, then.
Nine.
Here's a ten.
Jack.
Queen.
I call doubt, Hideyoshi.
So you do have all four...
Oh well...
...we're all guys, so stripping a little isn't—
Jeez.
What's wrong, Hideyoshi?
Oh my, Kinoshita, you should go to sleep there!
I suppose there no way around it.
I'll stand in for Kinoshita.
H-Hey, Himeji, is that handkerchief...
Kinoshita is just exhausted!
B-But Himeji, until just then, Hideyoshi was...
But that...
Voyeur?!
It seems like Tsuchiya is exhausted, too.
What on earth happened?
Himeji is acting so strangely.
There must be something...
Could it be...
Th-Those are...!
My goodness, I can't believe he
would undress in front of Akihisa.
Kinoshita most certainly is exhausted.
There's no doubt about it; Himeji has
lost control because of the chocolate!
Is there something wrong, Akihisa?
I don't think three people is enough
to continue; I think we should end—
"End"?
What are you talking about?
There are four of us!
What?
I'll do my best.
Shouko, when did you get here?!
Forcing you to strip is my responsibility as your wife.
Damn it! That is so wrong in so many ways!
Well then, why don't we play boys versus girls?
Sure, the game will end faster that way.
What should we do, Yuuji?
There's nothing we can do. Let's
beat them and get this over with.
But... making them undress would be...
No big deal.
We can call it off if things come to that.
I see!
You're right!
Akihisa, socks are cheating!
Yuuji, this is not how a man should act.
Himeji, can we end the game here—
We're just getting started!
Shouko, you've played enough, right?
Double raise.
Stripping in front of girls is
sort of awkward, you know?
It's all right, Akihisa!
If you don't want to undress...
No!
I don't see anything even remotely
resembling a girl's uniform!
It's your fault for not heeding my warning, Akihisa~
A
Aki
Akihi
This is the Emergency Code!
Akihisa
Akihisa,
Akihisa, did
Akihisa, did you
Akihisa, did you no
Akihisa, did you notice
Akihisa, did you notice that
Akihisa, did you notice that?
?
what?
Notice what?
W
We
We ne
We need
We need to
We need to use
We need to use any
We need to use any means
We need to use any means ne
We need to use any means necessa
We need to use any means necessary
We need to use any means necessary now.
?
up?
em up?
them up?
Set them up?
My bad!
Let's continue the game then.
Oops.
Good! Now's my chance!
What?!
You chose your roles poorly.
Yuuji, you never make such simple mistakes in the middle of a match.
You certainly like playing games.
Naughty little rascals.
Tick.
Seven.
This'll be the turning point of the match.
6 cards
Any mistakes will hit us hard.
Oh?
Kubo?
She
is
lying
to
you
Kubo!
You're helping me out!
Thank you.
I'll make the best use of this opportunity!
With all my heart in it...
I call doubt on that seven!
Unfortunately, it is a seven.
Kubo!
She
is
lying
to
I'm sorry, Yoshii!
is
lying
to
is
lying
to
is
lying
to
you
is
lying
to
you
is
lying
to
you
is
lying
to
you
is
lying
to
you
is
lying
to
you
is
lying
to
you
is
lying
to
you
lying
to
you
lying
to
you
lying
to
you
lying
to
you
lying
to
you
lying
to
you
lying
to
you
NOT.
What the hell are you doing, Akihisa?!
As long as you're stripping, he's our enemy!
Why?!
Tick.
I'm starting to have second thoughts.
Himeji!
Yeah, it's not a good idea to pit yourself
against your friends in a game with penalties.
You're going to be a net idol starting tomorrow!
Just a moment, Himeji!
I didn't give you permission to take and upload photos!
Yuuji, you can close your eyes
if you find it a little embarrassing.
Damn it!
I won't lose!
By the way, Akihisa...
Wh-What is it, Himeji?
Even if I were to have to strip, I wouldn't end this game early.
Shouko, I'm sure you...
I'm quite confident about my underwear today.
It's hopeless!
They've got no qualms about stripping!
Oh.
I'll call doubt on that King you're about to play.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Checkmate
D-Doubt.
Hurry it up, Akihisa! They're going to catch us!
I don't want to be a net idol!
Hey! Don't run in the halls!
Please save us!
I don't mind having supplementary lessons!
What are you guys doing dressed like that?
I'll explain later!
It's no good, Akihisa! They're here!
Please wait, Akihisa!
You need to hurry and put these on!
You can't escape.
How do they even get into situations like these?
Question 4
Answer the following question.
Write the chemical formula of benzene.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
C6H6
Teacher's Comment
Maybe it was too simple.
Tsuchiya Kouta's Answer
BEN + ZENE = BENZENE
Teacher's Comment
You're not taking chemistry seriously, are you?
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
B-E-N-Z-E-N
Teacher's Comment
Come to the faculty office with Tsuchiya later.
Eh?!
New System
Trial Run of the Summoning Exam System
A trial run of the Summoning Exam System?
Yes, I want all of you to participate.
Trial Run of the Summon
Exam System
Why us though?
You're the most appropriate choice.
If things were to go wrong, having
higher scores would only make it worse.
Flashback
I see your point.
It did go haywire last time.
Trial Run of the Summon
Exam System
I'd prefer you didn't remind me of that, but yes; that's the gist of it.
And so Himeji and those from Class A won't be participating.
But I would love to help out.
That's too bad.
I guess there's not much we can do about it.
Trial Run of the Summon
Exam System
I appreciate the sentiment.
So, will you help me test it?
Man, that sounds like a pain.
Exam System
Annoyed
Working as a Punishment Inspector is enough trouble as it is, and now this?
Exam System
Trial Run of the Summon
Who was the moron running around
the hallway in nothing but his boxers?
I'm sorry.
New System
Trial Run of the Summoning Exam System
Anyway, I'm not asking you to do it for free.
I'll give you meal vouchers and library cards in exchange for your assistance.
Fumizuki Academy
Meal Vouchers
Wow!
Well, then I'll create a field covering the
entire school building for the trial run.
Trial Run of the Summon
Exam System
The participants will be:
Tsuchiya,
Kinoshita,
Trial Run of the Summon
Shimada,
Yoshii,
and Sakamoto.
Trial Run of the Summon
Exam System
I'm counting on you guys.
Wait just a second you battleaxe.
Trial Run of the Summonin
Trial Run of the Summoning
Exam System
I should still have quite a lot of points.
I couldn't care less about what happens to you.
New System
Trial Run of the Summoning Exam System
Hey!
Why us?
I know.
It's fine!
Let's just get this over with!
Let's see.
We just need to test them out, right?
I think so.
Okay.
Well then...
Summon!
Eh?
We're in our school uniforms? Well, it is a trial run.
My weapon is missing.
This is pretty cute!
It reminds me of when I was a first year.
Huh?
The Summoned Beings are talking.
That hardy did say there'd be an
improvement in controllability.
But really,
it was such a pain this morning.
Eh? Hideyoshi?
Did something happen this morning?
I didn't say anything.
Who would've thought some middle school boy from the neighborhood would confess to me?
Eh?!
Kinoshita, have you finally become so well known
that boys from outside the school confess to you?!
O-Of course not! I'm a guy—
It's the third time this month.
The Being is blurting out its master's secrets.
It's rare to hear him talk about that sort of stuff.
Kinoshita's good at putting on a poker face.
No, listen.
I always act natur—
She praised my acting! I'm so happy!
I really am happy about it.
Hey, Voyeur.
What?
I've always got time for the erotic.
I don't mind that, but right now I'm
thinking of something a little different.
I just want to know what's under those shorts!
Smack
It certainly speaks your mind!
It's pretty funny!
Smack
It's not!
I want to see under your shorts.
Smack
Stop smacking my head.
He sure is honest.
Maybe I should play with it a little~
Would you like to know what's under the skirt?
I don't care about—
I have a limitless desire to know about skirts; the
place where romance, dreams, and hopes all collide.
Skirts such as tight, mini, long, flared,
and pleated each have their own charms.
Though, in my opinion, culottes really shouldn't be considered skirts.
No, I don't care about them.
So they do speak your thoughts, huh?
Huh? I can touch Minami's Summoned Being?
Man, this is crazy.
Aki, give her to me.
I don't wanna! I want to be on his lap!
It's even going against the will of its summoner.
They're just expressing their true feelings, like children.
I see... Children, eh?
Aki, hug me!
Don't ask him to hug you!
Get off him!
I don't wanna!
Calm down, Minami.
It's fine. I'm used to this.
Oh, what do you mean?
Kids like me for some reason.
It's because you're on their level.
Shut it, Yuuji.
Hey, you know, Aki?
What is it?
I'm always mean to you,
but actually, I—
No!
What do you think you're doing?!
Are you all right, Aki?
Does it hurt?
Listen to your master!
I'm sorry.
Let me make it clear, Aki.
I'm not hiding anything from—
Actually, yesterday, a girl in
the same grade confessed to—
No!
Th-That's cheap, Aki!
I can't believe you tried to use her to hear my secrets!
She just blurted it out.
Don't try to weasel out of it!
Summon your being and have it blurt out your feelings!
I can't afford to have my secrets let out like the others.
I need to think of something.
So, they speak your true feelings...
What's wrong, Himeji?
Oh, it's nothing!
By the way, how do you pronounce this?
kakusa mondai
(Social Inequality)
Uhh...
Kaku-sa mon-dai, I think.
Yep, that's correct!
Eh?! Why?!
kakusa    mondai
(Social Inequality)
kakusa   mondai
kakusummondai
(Social Inequality)
Damn it!
I'm sorry, Akihisa.
I just have to know your true feelings.
Nice job, Mizuki.
Now spit it out, Aki!
Who do you like?
I need to distract myself.
Damn it!
I should've guessed, that idiot's totally useless.
You're one to talk!
What?!
Hey, you two...
Be... care... ful...
Normally, I wear shorts...
but I'm not wearing them today.
What are you say—
Let me flip your skirt!
—ing, Kudou?
Yeah, it's useless to—
Hold it! I'm first!
—try to taunt us!
Aki, come here for a minute.
Akihisa, I need to talk to you.
Yuuji.
Please stand by.
That's for always thinking of perverted stuff.
Please reflect on your actions!
I'm not wearing shorts either.
I'm sorry!
I just felt like teasing you a bit.
You're so cruel, Kudou.
You've gone too far.
Oh, just so you know, I overslept today
and I didn't have time to put on a bra—
Please spare us already!
What about your bra?!
Yuuji.
It's not what you think, Shouko!
It's just a guy's instincts.
Squish
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Are you happy?
L-Like this'd make me...
Awesome!
...HAPPY!
Man, that's twisted.
Pretty sweet, Yuuji!
I'm so jealous of you!
I'm so jealous!
Well that's just my personality.
Please stand by.
What we're trying to say is that there's a proper order to these things.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Yeah, Aki.
You need to take it slowly so that both sides are in love with each other—
Aki and I love each—
Akihisa...
W-What's the matter, Himeji?
I know it's a bit sudden, but do you have a person you like, Akihisa?
Eh? Why do you ask?
I should've guessed.
You always seem to struggle with these sorts of questions.
Eh? What?
Then let me rephrase.
She won't get me!
Who do you like?
I think I like Summon from Class G.
Eh? Her name is Summon?
Now, let's continue talking
about who we like, shall we?
That's not fair, Akihisa!
Don't you have a secret or two yourself?
I-It's all right!
I don't have anything to hide—
Actually, just now...
when you were having naughty thoughts...
I couldn't help but think strange things too...
No!
How's everyone do—
How do they even...
...get into situations like these?
hirameite kagayaite
閃いて 輝いて
Flash and sparkle!
denkyuu pikkanko
電球ぴっかんこ
Light bulb goes off!
(hai)
(はいっ)
Yes
進展しないよ
I'm not making progress
shinten shinai yo
dareka jama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
Oh no, someone's in the way
zenzen tarinai
全然足りない
It's totally not enough
sore ga mondai no koubaisuu
それが問題の公倍数
That's the common multiple of the problem
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I kind of get it
nani ga hontou no koto Baby?
何が本当のこと Baby?
What is it really, baby
mitetara koko de
見てたらここで
If you're watching
zukai shite yo Baby!
図解してよ Baby!
Show it to me, baby
kotoba mo kazu mo kimi wo arawasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
Words and numbers can't express you
(chu chu chu chu)
(ちゅちゅちゅちゅっ)
(kiss kiss kiss kiss)
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to
心がビリビリするS と
The magnetic forces between S and N
(S to)
(S と)
(S)
N  no jiryoku de
N の磁力で
It electrifies me!
(S, S, Supaaku tsuite nanbaa)
(S, S, SuperくついてNumber)
(Super goes with number!)
(I say No. 1 boy)
(And you're the number one boy!)
omedetou ima kara
おめでとう 今から
Congratulations, from now on
kimi wa My, ma, my otakara
君はMy, ma, my"お宝"
You're my treasure
tokubetsu nanda dou natte mo
特別なんだ どうなっても
You're special
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I won't let you go, no matter what
watashi wa koi shitai
私は恋したい
I want to love
yume ni genkai wa iranai
夢に限界はいらない
Dreams need no bounds
tokubetsu dayo ne acchatta mo
特別だよね 会っちゃたもん
You must be special since we met!
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
Please forgive me as is
hirameite kagayaite
閃いた 輝いた
It sparkled and flashed
seikai pittanko
正解ぴったんこ
Now I have the answer!
(gyu)
(ぎゅっ)
You'd like to talk to me?
Um...
I am the rep of Class E, Nakabayashi.
I called you out to tell you my fuzzy feelings...
No, fuzzy isn't the right word.
No, fuzzy isn't the right word. Painful?
Painful? Anguished?
Anguished?
No, anyway, I can't describe it clearly...
but I have to tell you my feelings.
Are you busy right now?
No, I'm free.
Go on, tell me.
I want you to go out with me!
Why is Yoshii so innocent and adorable?
His actions, speech, and mannerisms are all so lovely!
Whoosh.
Ms. Nakabayashi.
Uh, yes?
I'm sorry.
I can't accept such an insulting rejection!
Question 5
State the correct way to deal
with someone who is burnt.
Answer the following question.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Cool with water quickly.
Teacher's Comment
Correct. As expected of you, Himeji.
For spots that can't be cooled in
running water, put a clean towel over
the affected area and pour water. In
the case of a low temperature burn or
extremely extensive or severe burns,
cover the affected area with a clean
towel and visit the hospital.
Tsuchiya Kouta's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 5:
State the correct way to deal with someone who is burnt.
Pay them off.
Not that kind of burn.
Next episode: Me, a Peeping Tom, and Training Camp!
Me, a Peeping Tom, and Training Camp!
This will be on your test.