Humans!
If you wish not for annihilation, take heed!
I bear a message from the depths!
You will surrender the surface to us,
the Clan of the Seafolk!
Thereafter you shall become
our nourishment, human scum—
Nice head! Are you related
to an octopus by any chance?
I heard it was that same guy again.
What was his name?
I forget, but he's super-strong.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
Class C?
Never seen him before.
I've got to keep up.
THE DEEP SEA KING
Help! Somebody!
We, the Clan of the Seafolk,
now rule the surface!
Resistance is futile!
You'll pay for that, human!
The A-class hero Stinger, rising in popularity
and currently 11th in the rankings, is here to help.
At your service, everyone!
It's Stinger!
We're saved!
Go for it!
Well now…
Anyone who needs a new blowhole
drilled into their torso, step right up!
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
Master…
You have moved up to rank 2 in Class C.
You are on the verge of entering Class B!
Class B, huh?
That means I won't have any more
weekly hero quotas, right?
Correct.
Oh, excuse me…
Hello?
City J? It is a bit far.
Are there no competent heroes nearby?
Busy guy…
Master!
The monster you defeated
on your way home the other day
called itself one of the "Seafolk," right?
I forget.
Several monsters calling themselves
the "Clan of the Seafolk"
have appeared in City J
and are attacking anyone in sight.
An A-class hero is fighting them
all alone and is on the brink of defeat.
His extreme fatigue and pain are apparent.
A prompt response from the
Hero Association is desperately needed.
Hang on!
The threat level is Tiger.
All citizens are asked to stay out of the area.
You've got spunk, you slimy bastards.
My beloved Bamboo Shoot here is happy to be
battling enemies with some grit for a change.
But it's time to end this.
You can quit your boasting, human!
Your foolish fan club has run off.
But your death will not be easy.
For the taking of our brothers' lives,
long will we cause you to suffer.
Four fish to go!
It's a lot easier without an audience!
Sing, Bamboo Shoot!
Gigantic Drill Stinger Quadruple Thrust!
I did it…
I did it!
These monsters were probably a God-level
threat and I defeated them all by my—
You know, when something's so annoying,
it is a pleasure to watch it die.
How much farther is City J?
We are almost there.
But I am getting no readings.
I will scout ahead.
Once I have confirmed their location,
I will let you know.
Oh… Hey!
This is an announcement
from the Hero Association.
The threat level is Tiger.
All citizens, please stay clear of the area.
CITY A - HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Was the warning issued?
The request just went out.
We'll need to update it and re-issue.
What do you mean?
Stinger is down.
Licenseless Rider here. I'm heading in.
Give me the location.
All lines are busy at this time—
Where are they?
Hey, best forget it!
C-class heroes can't handle this one.
Huh?
The word just came down.
Emergency evacuation warning.
The threat level has been
raised from Tiger to Demon.
All residents of City J,
please evacuate immediately.
See what I mean?
Hey!
I repeat. All residents of City J,
please evacuate immediately.
Evacuate?
How foolish.
As if I'd allow even one
of these apes to escape.
So that's the one that got Stinger…
But he's the last of 'em.
Should I wait for backup?
If it's one-on-one, maybe I can—
That smarts.
Why would you do this?
Dammit, how'd he get behind me?
I was so surprised my voice went all funky.
Plus, my gunpowder-charged lightning kick had zero effect!
I can't win.
Who are you?
I am…
Lightning Max, the hero…
Fight me.
Fight you?
Of course.
I'll run for it as soon as—
What happened?
I can't feel my body…
Dammit.
You arrogant…
Lightning Flying Backwards Roundhouse Kick!
S-class hero,
Co-co Convict.
I escaped from prison just to see you!
Well, well.
A hero serving time in prison?
I tagged along and was able to escape too.
My thanks.
Prisoner number 4188, Sonic, right?
Surprised I know?
You see, I check up on
all the boys who catch my eye.
I'm serving a life sentence because
I can't resist attacking beautiful men.
Oh my.
More soldiers come for me?
Goodness!
I feel the strength about to erupt out of him!
Sonic, dear, you hang back.
Class A rank 11, sweet Stinger.
Class A rank 20, Lighting Max.
I fancied them both.
And yet you ruined them!
Now that Genos has passed me,
I may be the lowest ranked one...
but I am still an S-class hero!
I am unlike either of them.
I'll begin at half-power,
to gauge how much you can take.
You made me rip the hand-knit
sweater my boyfriend made!
I will never, ever forgive you!
A delectable slab of meat, quite prime.
My appetite's up!
Huh?
Oh my…
I felt that…
just a little.
I felt that too... Just a little.
Co-co Convict is acting tough,
but he's hurting…
So this is what a fight between a demon-level
monster and an S-class hero looks like?
It's almost comical.
Neither one could defeat me.
Dammit… His punch was
stronger than I expected.
But I must not lose to him.
I can't have any more of my boys
destroyed by this monster…
I have no choice.
I'll have to transform.
Ready…
Transform!
Co-co Convict Angel Style!
He's naked.
And he's definitely no angel.
Nor is he human.
Nor do I want to watch.
I'm out.
No one has ever seen my Angel Style
and lived to tell about it.
All the more reason to leave.
Quite unsightly.
Are those your last words?
Angel Rush!
Elevated energy levels nearby.
That must be it.
Damn it! I have no way to reach Master!
It cannot be helped.
Done with your combo?
I felt that… Just a little.
Listen up.
The objective of a combination
move is to finish your opponent.
Each separate attack must be
delivered with intent to kill.
Like this.
Isn't this fun?
Just who are you?
I am the Deep Sea King.
As lord of the Clan of the Seafolk,
this world is mine to rule.
Do you dare defy me too?
You think you have the strength
to rule the surface all alone?
That's pathetic.
Oh?
Then I suppose you must die.
That's my line.
I would have let you live if you'd
shown me the respect I'm due.
I'm no hero, but I will eliminate you.
It's raining.
Too slow.
Wind Blade Leg!
Deep Sea King,
I see right through your moves.
Are you sure of that?
Once it bites, my little moray here never lets go!
Let me be clear.
There's no way I'd ever lose to you.
It's useless.
You may have power…
but you're too slow to fight me.
I'm glad, Deep Sea King!
Fighting something like you
just confirms how strong I really am!
You see, my moves are
the fastest and the strongest!
Now what, lost your mind?
He's faster!
Stronger too?!
What happened to him?
He's huge!
The air of the surface shriveled me up a bit,
but thanks to this rain, I feel like myself again.
Your attacks don't hurt me, not even a little!
At this time, the whereabouts of the
Seafolk that attacked City J are unknown.
Several heroes who tried to stop them
have been found unconscious at the scene
and remain in critical condition.
Of all the times to hit a red light…
Where'd he run off to?
Wait, you're…
Class C, rank 2.
You a hero too?
Have you seen Genos?
Genos?
Today, as our guest, we have
the top-ranked, A-class superhero
who has also been number one in
popularity rankings for 28 weeks straight.
He's also a successful model, actor, and singer.
Let's welcome the handsome Mr. Sweet Mask!
Thank you for having me.
We are currently facing a threat level of Demon.
How do you assess the situation?
That is a difficult question.
Why is that?
I'm only a hero when I confront evil.
The rest of the time,
I'm focused on my career as an artist.
I see.
I'm only here today to promote my new song.
My apologies.
In that case, let's discuss your song.
Let me just say this.
To assuage the public's fears and worries,
heroes need to be both tough and strong so that
they can defeat evil with speed, grace, and brilliance.
I find it regrettable that there were heroes
who were completely beaten by evil this time.
So that no hero ever dies in vain,
I hope each will continue to train his hardest.
My attacks have no effect.
Could I be lacking in power?
I can't kill him unarmed.
I need to retreat for now and find a weapon.
Caught you!
Crack crack, snap snap.
Huh?
Wait there.
The next time we meet will be your demise.
No matter.
The small fry can be let go.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
There were orders to evacuate.
A hero?
If you're after the Deep Sea King,
then you'd better forget it.
Deep Sea King?
You heroes could all jump him
at once and still lose.
You're fine at playing make-believe,
but against true power
you don't stand a chance.
You can't protect a thing.
Who was that pervert?
The Seafolk?!
I sense numerous life signals nearby.
With so many…
The evacuation shelter!
Daddy, are the scary monsters still outside?
Don't worry. As long as we're
in this shelter, we're safe.
Besides, if it comes down to it,
I'm sure all of us together can beat a monster or two.
I sense them…
Yes, so many!
It's coming from...
over there!
Greetings…
and goodbye.
Please wait!
We surrender!
We will comply with any demands you have.
But please do not attack. I beg you.
I'm only in Class C,
so I evacuated. Now I'm trapped.
I'm no hero. I'm a failure…
Surrender?
I've come to kill you.
Your deaths are inevitable!
And as for my demands…
How about I demand you scream
nicely as I slaughter you?
I can't win…
I know it won't amount to much,
but all I can do is buy time
for the S-class heroes to get here.
But look at this monster…
Who am I kidding?
I can't buy time just by talking to him.
I pissed my pants…
I'm pathetic.
I'll fight with you!
Heroes?
There are others in here too?
I may be the lowest ranking at 38,
but I'm still an A-class hero.
We can do this.
I-I'm a hero too!
Allback-man is here!
Heroes?
The heroes are here?
Heroes!
They'll save us!
I feel better with an A-class around.
Yeah…
Two from Class C, one from
Class B, and one from Class A…
We can do it!
We can win!
You sure this is the way?
Yes, since residents are
fleeing from this direction,
we'll find monsters further up.
Did you see a butt naked guy run past?
What?
Maybe he was taking a bath and was left behind.
I'll check it out.
Go on without me.
Got it!
Licenseless Rider here.
Yes, we're on our way.
What! The shelter?
It was the other way!
All right. When I give the signal, charge him.
One…
Two…
That's weird.
I know I saw him…
Why so quiet all of a sudden?
Are you one of the Seafolk?
Licenseless Rider went in?
Yes. I couldn't stop—
Licenseless Rider?!
What's your location?
This is beyond you.
The monster even took out a S-class hero!
We need to assemble a subjugation squad.
An S-class hero was defeated?
Who is this?
Where's Licenseless Rider?
Stand-up Peddling Mode!
Roar, Justice!
Is this the Hero Association?
Yes.
Who are you?
Give me the owner of that
cell phone right now!
This is the hero Saitama.
Saitama?
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Next
Time
Unyielding
Justice
Hey, how'd you like my Gigantic Drill Stinger?
By the way, I nailed ten of those Seafolk things!
You're pretty upbeat.
Oh, Lightning Max?
I won't ask how many Seafolk you defeated,
but I'm sure you did great.
Next time on One-Punch Man episode nine,
"Unyielding Justice."
I'm not sure who'll mete it out,
but make sure our sacrifices weren't in vain!