U-Uhm... This isn't a prank or anything!
So... as I thought... Minami likes Akihisa...
I'm seriously gonna kill you!
Hi!! Mondai: hitori to
futari docchi ga suteki?
Colorful mawari dasu watashi no shourai
Doko made hanasou ka? Minai furi?
Assou, ookina sekai
wa kibun de hirogaru
Kyou mo daisuki, hontou ni daisuki
Watashi no baka...
Hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
Sunao ni narezu ni,
kimi to aruku yume o mita
Gomen ne... Datte!
Koi to shiranakattanda
Kotaette kimi to nazo tasu
watashi wa mugen no JUMP!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
A week after the training camp, the
Year 2 guys' suspension is over and...
Yuuji...
Hm?
What is... Whoa!
You shouldn't dodge.
You were about to give me a
head-butt. Of course, I'd dodge.
It wasn't a head-butt. It was a kiss.
Okay, don't move.
Put your hands behind
your head and explain slowly.
Kissing... Joining our lips...
A natural action for you and I since
we made a promise to get married...
Wait. I know kissing.
What I wanna know is why...
When, where, and with whom did you kiss?
You got it wrong. I just know what it
means. It doesn't mean I experienced it.
Is that right? Good.
I thought I was going to die.
What's with this all of a sudden?
That... They were kissing a moment ago.
Seriously?!
Geez... Akihisa is as stupid as ever, huh?
He knew that that would
happen if he kissed a girl.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
To tell you the truth,
while you were asleep...
Here! I found another heretic!
Okay, take him.
Ah! Hey! Stop it! I didn't...
--Hey! Stop it! Ahhh!
--...although I could only kiss him on the cheek.
Guys! Where are we?
A court for passing final judgment!
And for the heretics...?
A punishment of death awaits!
Good. We will now start the inquisition.
Huh? What're you doing here, Yuuji?
You got me dragged into this!
Read out the charge.
We will call the defendant,
Akihisa Yoshii, "A,"
and Minami Shimada "Flat Chest."
A is charged with an act
of disloyalty to our doctrine.
When A was sexually assaulting
Flat Chest early this morning,
our fellow members captured him.
We will thoroughly investigate on the
relationship between A and Flat Chest
and take proper action on A as
well as watch Flat Chest in the futu--
Just state the conclusion.
We're jealous that he was kissing a girl!
The ruling is, death penalty.
Hey, Akihisa, what's going on?
Beats me.
Doesn't something ring a bell?
When'd you see Shimada
last before this morning?
I think it might've been the
last night of the training camp.
Oh, that time...
After everyone fell asleep,
she quietly came to me.
Why didn't you think it was strange?!
I just assumed that she came to kill me.
Then what'd you say to her before that?
Let's see...
"To: Minami Shimada" "There's something I wanna
talk to you about. Could you come to my room?"
"To: Akihisa Yoshii"
"Okay, but why at this late hour?"
"To: Minami Shimada"
"Isn't it obvious? I like what I like."
What's wrong, Akihisa?!
Well, nothing.
So, what'd you guys talk about?
A love confession kinda thing.
She confessed to you?
No, I confessed to her.
Ow!
It's ringing all sorts of bells!
Heretic Akihisa Yoshii...
Will you repent your sin and accept the ruling?
What's the ruling?
I'm sentencing you to
a special bungee jumping.
Just so that I know, what will I be doing?
In order not to worry you
unnecessarily, I can only give you a hint,
but it's similar to
skydiving without a parachute.
You're telling me exactly
what it is! So no cord?!
You're gonna make me
bungee jump without a cord?!
Ah! That's Himeji!
Help me, Himeji!
So... as I thought... Minami
likes Akihisa... Minami likes...
What?! You're still like that?!
Yoshii and Shimada just exchanged
words through their eye contact!
And I thought I might
have a chance with Flat Chest!
If he's taken in not just Himeji
and Kinoshita but even Shimada,
Aki is the only one
we have a chance with!
G-Good morning, Aki.
Y-Yeah, good morning.
Say, is it okay if I sit at your table?
What?
Mine is broken, so...
Then I guess it can't be helped.
Sure, it's okay.
Thanks!
Why are you clamming up?
Well... aren't we sitting too close?
But the table is small, so...
I-I guess you're right.
Say, Aki... Uhm, if you like, that is...
...why don't we have lunch together today?
I made your lun--
What're you doing, Honey?!
Sh-Shimizu!
You can't allow this damn
pig to sit so close to you, Honey!
W-What can I do? My table is broken.
Even so, it doesn't have
to be a pig that you sit with!
So as I thought, Minami likes Akihisa...
But since Mizuki studies seriously,
I don't want to bother her.
In Aki's case, even if I bother him,
his grades are already bad, so...
I somehow get the impression
you're badmouthing me.
I can't allow it! To think that
you made lunch for this damn pig!
Fried chicken marinated
with homemade sauce,
which you prepared after
getting up at four in the morning!
The hamburgers that you made
with expensive ground beef!
The potato salad made
with organic vegetables!
How do you know so much?!
On top of that, the rice
has a heart mark on it!
Ah! Miharu!
Listen, Miharu. I've been patient up until now,
but I want you to stop doing stuff like this...
...because... I'm dating Aki.
Tatami mat flip!
Tsk.
So that's how it is,
Miharu. Please understand.
No! I'll marry you and
name our daughter Mirai,
using one character from your name!
Wait, Shimizu! What're you
gonna do if a boy is born?!
Namihei is good enough if it's a boy.
Before that, Miharu and I can't make a baby!
I'm starting the class now!
What're you doing, Shimizu?
Go back to your classroom.
I'm here to deal with an important
matter! Please overlook it this once!
An important matter?
Yes! It's very important that
I annihilate the pigs in this classroom!
I'm forbidding you to enter
this classroom from now on.
Damn pig!
You're always at the center of trouble.
You have lots of stories to talk about.
Stop it... It's not my fault.
You're wrong. It looks like we're gonna
have a big problem because of you.
Huh?
There's a movement within Class D
to try and start a Summoner Test War.
Whichever class Class D is trying
to fight is none of our concern, right?
Even if that's us, Class F?
What?
But our classroom
equipment is the worst ranked.
There's no benefit for them
to attack... Don't tell me...
That's right. Shimizu is
trying to take things out on us.
In order to separate you
and Shimada's seats,
she's trying to switch our
tables back to cardboard boxes.
But it's hard to think that everyone
in Class D would agree with Shimizu.
We're the ringleaders
of the peeking incident.
All the girls think that we're their enemy.
The Class D rep is Genji Hiraga,
but he probably can't restrain
Shimizu, who's burning with jealousy,
and the girls, who're burning
with anger towards the guys.
No way...
Because of the suspension, the guys
haven't been able to recover our scores.
Even though we have Himeji,
our forces aren't enough.
There's only one way left...
We have to avoid the war.
We can do that?
It's up to you and Shimada.
There's one thing I wanna check, though.
What is it?
Are you and Shimada really dating?
As far as I remember, I don't think we are.
This is happening probably
because of an email I sent by mistake.
You sent an email by mistake?
I see. What Akihisa did was bad enough,
but Yuuji also made a blunder
with incredibly bad timing.
So that's what was going on... Sorry, Akihisa.
If that's the case, if we clear
Shimada's misunderstanding and you two
go back to a normal relationship,
Shimizu will probably cool off.
You mean...
Muttsulini, is there a wiretap
device Shimizu planted here?
There was, but I made it look
like it was broken and removed it.
What do you wanna talk about?
About the email I sent you
while we were at the training camp...
...to tell you the truth,
you got the wrong idea.
What?
Well, it's more like, I meant
to send it to someone else.
Who?
Sugawa, I think.
What?! You were going to
confess your love to Sugawa?!
Oh no...! You may not act like it,
but I thought you liked girls after all!
Well, it's not like that.
"To: Akihisa Yoshii"
"Yoshii, why are you trying so desperately to peek on girls?"
"To: Minami Shimada"
"Isn't it obvious? I like what I like."
That's terrible in many senses.
I'm sorry! Like I said, it was sent by mistake.
I see, I see... I thought it
was a little, strange, too,
but I finally understand it now.
You're careless, too, so...
Hey, I don't wanna be told that by you
when you sent it to the wrong person.
What're you gonna
do about my first kiss?!
I'm sorry! I meant no harm!
Sorry doesn't cut it, does it?!
Th-Then...
What?
I-It was my first kiss, too,
so can it be considered even?
Of course it can't.
What? I-Is that right?
Well, uhm... then thanks for the kiss.
It can?!
Say, Minami, I want you to
answer me without getting upset.
What is it?
You told Shimizu that we're dating.
Does that mean that you...
Th-That's... You know,
since Miharu was persistent,
I thought she might
give up if I had a boyfriend.
And it was good timing, so...
What a lame excuse.
She's not being honest with herself.
Oh, you should've told me then.
I thought you might like me.
N-No way!
I thought it was strange, too.
To see you acting meekly like that.
Ahh! My arm is getting dislocated!
Now the confusion has been cleared.
Now, once we tell Shimizu about
this, everything will be settled.
Thus, the war with Class D was avoided.
However...
Idiot Test.
I want you to listen to this.
The situation is now even
worse than it was this morning.
U-Uhm, is it true that you have pictures
of Akihisa in a sailor school uniform?
100 yen per pic. Redistribution is prohibited.
I'd like to have everything you have, plea--
Oops, that wasn't it.
What?! What was that?!
That conversation does
suggest a bad situation!
Shut up, Akihisa. Don't
make a fuss over trivial stuff.
It's not trivial! Why are my pictures
being sold behind the scenes like Hideyoshi's?!
Wait, Akihisa! What you just
said is a bad situation for me!
This is the real one.
How are things in Class F?
They're not aware of us at all.
Good. We'll recover our scores while we can.
If they notice, we'll declare war right away.
This is... I thought Class D
wouldn't come to attack us anymore.
No. This isn't Class D.
This conversation took place in Class B.
Tsk! That damn Nemoto! He really plays dirty!
Why does Class B
want to declare war on us?
It seems that his position was harmed
after they lost the ST War against us.
On top of that, they participated
in the peeking operation and failed.
He's probably lost his
say in matters in the class.
As a quick measure to control
the complaints in Class B,
he must be planning to create a new enemy.
By directing their anger at us,
he'll get them to stop being angry at him.
He probably wants to regain his lost ground.
What?! We haven't recovered our scores yet.
If class B comes to attack us,
it's guaranteed we'll lose!
Now that it's come to
this, we have no choice,
but to create a situation where
Class B can't declare war on us.
Can we do that?!
Yeah. All we need is for another
class to declare war on us before them.
You mean...
Having Class D declare war on us.
What?! After we had just finally
cleared up Shimizu's misunderstanding
and avoided a war!
If we fight an ST War, we're given time
to recover our scores in recovery tests.
If we fight Class D, we can
recover our scores without worries.
I see... If we take the test
and become fully prepared,
Class B wouldn't come
attack us so easily, huh?
But Yuuji, with our current scores,
we can't even defeat Class D.
For that, I've got a separate solution.
In any case, we'll provoke Class D
and have them declare war on us.
What do we do?
We'll use what happened this morning.
You and Shimada get cozy and instigate Shimizu.
What?
Definitely no!
Can't you reconsider?
No matter what you say, I won't.
Even if it's an act, there's no way I'd
become the girlfriend of such an idiot!
Shimada, you're the only one who can do this!
If Class B attacks us now, we're
gonna go back to using cardboard boxes.
If that happens, Himeji's
parents will get worried again
and could try to have her
transferred to another school.
I want you to help us, too, Himeji.
Me, too?
Yeah, Shimada's acting by
itself would be unconvincing, so...
We want you to act
jealous of their relationship.
Could you somehow do it?
U-Uhm, Minami, Akihisa...
You may not want to do it, but please do it!
Mizuki...
I'm sorry that this is
my own personal reason,
but I really don't
wanna change schools, so...
O-Okay. I just have to pretend, right?
Thank you very much.
Now that that's been
decided, let's just get right on.
This is... a script? Let's see...
I'm sorry for asking you
to come see me like this, Aki.
Listen, I'm in love with you.
I've been feeling the
same all this time, Minami.
Hey, wh-what are these lines?!
There's no way I can say lines like that!
I know we're just acting,
but it's too embarrassing.
I guess it can't be helped.
I'll show you an example.
Huh?
Wow...
I'm sorry for asking you to
come see me like this, Aki.
Listen, I'm in love with you.
What?
Ever since I met you for the
first time, I've been in love with you!
It was really hard for me to
just be a friend all this time.
The truth is, I couldn't bear staying just friends!
Aki, I know it's strange to
say this now after what I did,
I'd like to tell you again.
I'm in love with you.
Please go out with me.
So, something like that.
A-Amazing...
My heart went pitter-patter.
What's the matter, Akihisa?
Just for a bit... could you
leave me alone just for a bit?
Huh?
There are dreams that people
don't wanna wake up from.
Muttsulini, put the wiretap
device on the rooftop back in place.
Got it.
I want the three of you to go up
to the rooftop and put on a show
so that Shimizu will hear it through
the wiretap device and get the wrong idea.
The setup is that Akihisa and
Shimada are meeting secretly, okay?
Cross your arms.
Arms?!
But...
In order also to make up for
your earlier mistake, try your best.
Th-Then...
I'm gonna kill you if you
touch me in a weird place.
If you cross it so tightly, it's hard to walk.
We're dating, so this is just normal.
But, Minami... they've been
hitting my elbow for a while now.
What? Y-You naughty jerk.
Your ribs are...
Oh no! I have to keep acting.
Say, Minami...
What is it, Aki?
What do you like about me?
That's obvious, right? From head to...
From head to...?
...eyebrows.
Fore... head, huh?
What are you two doing?
Mizuki...
Being so close to each
other and even arm in arm...
It looks as if... you two are dating!
Hm? Was that line in the script?
Oh, I see! This is an adlib!
That's right, Mizuki. Aki and I are dating.
What? Is that true?
Yeah. I'm sorry for not telling you, Mizuki.
So... as I thought, you like Akihisa?
I'm sorry for not telling you that,
either... when I knew how you felt.
I'm sorry. You can't forgive me, right?
Well, I kinda knew how you felt, too, so...
I even feel better now that you've
told me about it clearly like this.
Could it be that
you're going to forgive me?
It's not a matter of
whether I'll forgive you or not.
I think you're free to like anyone.
So I can't criticize you, Minami.
Mizuki... Thank you.
But I won't forgive you
for the kiss this morning!
That was against the rules! On top
of that, that was Akihisa's first kiss!
That was because of the
email and stuff, so... I just...
Don't "I just" me! Even if God forgives
you for cheating like that, I won't!
That's... a wiretap device?!
You dummy, Minami!
Oh no! If Himeji talks without noticing
it and Shimizu figures out it's an act...
Himeji!
H-Hey, Aki! What's going on?
Don't tell me you're choosing Mizuki!
Sorry, Minami! There's something I have to do!
Aki! Stay here with me!
I...! I'm...
in love with you...
There, I said it...
Calm down, Shimada.
Don't adlib carelessly like that.
This is it. I'm done acting.
Aki likes girly girls
like Mizuki anyway, right?
Himeji...
Akihisa...
Thank you. I didn't notice it.
What's wrong, Himeji? You seem down.
What? Do I look like that?
Yeah, you somehow looked lonely.
Looked lonely... huh?
If I do look like that,
it might be because I felt sad that
the person I like was taken away...
...even if it was just an act...
Don't worry, Himeji.
That was just an act, so...
I guess you're right.
It was just an act, right?
I might be a little jealous, too.
What?
If there was a guy both you and
Minami fall in love with, even if it's an act...
If you really are in that kind
of situation, what will you do?
What? Hmm... let's see...
I guess I'll think really hard about it.
Think...?
Yeah, I'll think really
hard about it in my own way
and tell everything honestly.
I wanted to hear who you'd pick, though...
What?
No, nothing.
But I was surprised.
At what?
How you were earlier.
It didn't look like you were acting.
Could it be that you...
What...? What?!
...used to perform in plays or something?
What...?
Ah... Himeji?
You dummy...
Hirameite, kagayaite, denkyuu pikkanko
Shinten shinai yo.
Dareka jama shiteru... No, no!
Zenzen tarinai, sore
ga mondai no koubaisuu
Ryoukai sorenai. Nani ga
hontou no koto... Baby?
Mitetara koko de zukai shite yo, Baby!
Kotoba mo kazu mo kimi o arawasenai
Kokoro ga biribiri
suru S to N no jiryoku de
(S, S, Super kuttsuite
Number, I say No. 1 boy!)
Omedetou! Imakara kimi
wa My, ma-my "otakara"
Tokubetsu nanda, dou nattemo
Gyutto ne gyutto ne hanasanai
Watashi wa koi shitai.
Yume ni genkai wa iranai
Tokubetsu dayo ne, acchatta mon
Konna watashi mo yurushichae
Hirameita, kagayaita, seikai pittanko
Question 10.
Name the nutrients miso lacks
and suitable ingredients for
miso soup that can make up for them?
Vitamin C, orange, and hydrochloric acid.
Would you call that cooking?
Next episode!
"Me, Romance, and Love Skills!"
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!
Illustration: Mako Aboshi"