Here goes.
You can do it, Ruth-san.
Right.
Lottery
Drawing
Congratulations!
You've won the grand prize.
A trip to a hot spring at a seaside resort!
Tsu
zure
-
Ya
Drawing
Lottery
A voucher for a well-established inn!
dare no koto o kangaeteru no
Who is it that you're thinking of?
haato no supeesu soudatsusen
It's a game for a space in your heart!
senkyouteki ni isshin ittai de
It's an advancing and retreating invasion
yudan naranai na
I still can't let my guard down
a
no
ano ne ima no koto
ne
You see, right now,
honno suu paasento shika
I only have a few percent
aitsu no kokoro ni
tsu
of the space
ibasho ga nainda
sho
in his heart
true
intentions
peek
out
seifuku no poketto
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
true
intentions
out
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
peek
out
My
from
my
uniform's
pocket
honne o shinobasete
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
pocket
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
I
calmly fix
my collar
sotto eri o tadasu
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
my c
calmly fix
Simply revealing all the tricks up my sleeve
sonna kantan ni wa
te no uchi akasenai
would be no good
So I guess I'll just have to wait and see
akumade mada yousumi no dankai
dakedo hontou wa ne
But you see, the truth is
miyabutte hoshii no
I want you to realize it
awai kitai ni mune tokimekashite
My heart throbs from this bubbly expectation
chirachira to miteru
I shyly take a glance at you
onna no ko no daiji na mono
What girls value as important
i
ijiwaru de
a bit mean
ji
wa
ru
de
otoko no ko no daiji na koto
and what guys value as important
mukatsuku
and annoying
mu
ka
tsu
ku
hiku ni hikenai sorezore no jijou
tug back and forth with each other
hoka ni nani mo kangaerannai
My mind stutters, I can't think at all
ma
massugu de
so direct
s
su
gu
de
isshun datte yosomi dekinai
I can't take my eyes off you for a second
ni
nibui ne
yet so dull
bu
i
ne
juujitsukan afureru hodo ni
I'll fill you up with this sense of contentment
mitashite ageru yo
until you can't receive it anymore
jo
u
jouken chiratsukase
ken
Add requirements
yousu ukagatte miteru
See how things go
otagai win-win na
ga
I think we can both win here
i
win-
win
na
to
ri
torihiki shiyou yo
hi
so let's make a deal
ki
shi
yo
u
Swimming and Schemes!?
We get to go to a hot spring together!?
Yes, we can take six people in total.
It also sounds like we can go to the beach.
How do you feel about inviting everyone?
Well...
I'm not sure about these people.
Your Highness,
sometimes it's best to forget
about your problems and just relax.
Y-You're the one who won the voucher.
Do what you want.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Yay! I wanna go to the hot springs!
Don't you, Koutarou!?
Y-Yeah.
I have no objections.
Hot springs!
The beach!
Yay!
Thanks, Ruth-san!
I'm going too.
Magical girls need to rest sometimes.
But only six people can go, right?
Oh no!
I don't think we're going to have any problems with seven.
Sanae is a ghost, so no one can see her but us.
That's Sis for you!
You're so smart!
Oh yeah.
I am a ghost.
I totally forgot.
So it's settled.
We can all go.
Thank you!
It's nice to get out once in a while.
Let's call a truce for now.
We should start getting ready for the trip.
Yeah.
So these are Earth swimsuits.
There's quite a selection, huh?
There's a bargain bin!
I kind of want a new one too.
There's so many of them!
I don't know which one to choose.
Yeah, this will be difficult.
I hope I can find a swimsuit that looks good on me.
Boing, boing.
Boing, boing!
Let's go, Ruth.
How about this?
Um... The size is a bit...
With her flat chest, there's no way that'll fit.
It's imperative that a strategist know herself.
Boing, boing.
Your Highness, how about this one?
It's a little plain.
You think so?
I think simple is best.
R-Really?
No one will notice your flat chest.
I think it suits you as well.
Ruth, let's go to the dressing room.
Right now!
Okay.
Then I'll go too.
Same.
Don't leave me behind!
Girls have a lot going on.
Oh right, Sanae.
What about you?
I'm fine.
I have one from a long time ago.
Huh?
Really?
Yeah.
I see.
I definitely want to see it, then.
Huh?
You like that swimsuit, right?
Just you wait!
Quick question.
Why are we in a spaceship if we're going to a hot spring?
Impressed, Neanderthal?
Hey! If you have a ship this big,
why are you trying to invade my room!?
That has nothing to do with this!
Your Highness, the gate is ready.
Good job.
That's a gate?
Yes. If you go through here,
it'll take you straight to the inn.
Her Highness recommended it.
She said we'd be able to save some money this way.
Oh?
I wanted to show you just how
great Fortorthen technology is.
Thanks, Tulip.
I-It's not like I care about the financial status of some Neanderthal or anything.
You're acting like such an adult now!
You didn't get any taller, though.
Just get going already!
Tsuzure-Ya
Th-This is...
It's really...
"Well-established," maybe.
Try "ancient."
Definitely an antique.
Just say it's run-down.
It'll be pretty hard to fit seven people in here.
We've measured it!
It's the same size as the room at the Corona Apartments!
When you subtract the
furniture and other items,
"Other Items"
you get 11/12ths as much usable space.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault!
We're fine with hot springs and the beach!
Right, Tulip!?
Th-That's right, Ruth.
But there's someone else in this room with us.
You can't mean—
Let's go home!
It's okay!
Everyone relax!
I figured this might happen!
What's all this junk?
Someone at the Corona Apartments left all this stuff behind.
They might be kind of old, but...
Well, it's more about setting the mood.
Sorry about that.
Whoa, watch it!
Are you trying to get rid of me too!?
Get rid of you?
I couldn't get rid of you with something like this anyway.
What was that!?
Hold on a sec.
My grandma gave me these.
Don't like it? Try to haunt me or something!
Hey!
Those two are like children.
They act like they're in elementary school.
Let's head to the beach already.
Yeah. Let's go, Ruth.
Right.
There we go.
Oh? Satomi-kun, right?
Oh, the cosplayers...
Uh, you all...
aren't planning on swimming, are you?
We all decided to meet up during summer vacation.
It's almost time for summer's big event,
so we're going to focus on making our costumes.
We invited Nijino-san, but she said she had more important things to do.
Yurika?
Yes. She's new, but she shows a lot of promise.
I see.
But this is such a coincidence.
Sakuraba-san is here at the beach too.
Huh? Sakuraba-senpai's here?
She has a summer house nearby.
Rich people must have it nice.
She's cute, great at knitting...
It makes me want to get her for the Cosplay Society.
You and your schemes.
Yep.
Anyway, we have to begin fitting our outfits, so we'll catch you later.
Umm...
Take care of Yurika for me, okay?
Of course.
Give her some polishing and she'll shine.
I won't let her go.
See you.
They really care about Yurika.
That was pretty heavy.
Wow, look at them!
Are they models or something?
Hey, Koutarou, we're here!
I'm so cute that you're struck speechless, aren't you?
I'll permit your gaze for today only.
Tell me how elegant I am!
I...
Ruth, there's no reason to be embarrassed.
You should hold your chest high.
Everyone's been looking at us.
Yurika
How is it, Satomi-kun?
You get six cute girls all to yourself.
Huh?
Sakuraba-senpai...
Satomi-kun...
Are we being ignored?
How dare you, Sakuraba Harumi!
She'll be a tough opponent.
She stole the spotlight.
She looks really good!
In that case...
Um, Satomi-kun?
Oh, you guys are finally here.
Wait, what's wrong?
You Neanderthal!
JERK
How did it come to this?
It's because you don't try
to understand girls' feelings.
Um, could you help me out?
Oh, should I?
You sure are a tease today.
That's because something nice happened.
I guess you could say that I'm in a good mood.
Here it comes, Theia-chan!
Ruth!
Wonderful, Your Highness!
Finish, Sanae!
Leave it to me!
Sanae-chan Miracle Attack!
We had a lot of fun.
Wanna head back?
Yeah. I'll bet Koutarou the Jerk learned his lesson too.
I guess burying him wasn't enough.
Seems that way.
They look like they're having a great time.
Don't worry.
I've already taken extra measures.
That was heavy.
Sis got this for us!
Huh? For us?
So which will be split first,
Koutarou's head or the watermelon?
You can't be...
Now, Koutarou.
Let us partake in this entertainment together.
No!
S-So much fun...
This is going better than I expected.
Theia-dono, a little to the left.
Right there.
Go straight forward.
Swing!
Hey, you guys!
Not you too, Ruth-san!
You're trying to make her hit me, aren't you!?
Are you sure about this?
Satomi-kun's going to get...
It's fine.
Satomi-san's pretty tough.
I guess I missed.
Tulip...
If it's that bad, why don't you try to pull yourself out?
Well, it's my turn next!
Hey, behind you!
What are you saying?
You're not fooling anyone with that.
No!
There are some weirdos!
Weirdos?
Now!
Get them!
Sanae!
Your Highness!
What are you doing!?
You brutes!
We're not anyone weird.
Y-Yeah! We're just not
interested in normal girls.
That sounds suspicious to me!
So you're after little girls, then?
You perverts...
Divine punishment!
Damn it.
They're strong.
Who are they?
Bro, the tide's coming in.
Hot Spring of the Spirits
Hot Spring of the Gods
I feel better already.
I had a lot of fun today.
Sure we bumped into a couple of freaks,
but I got to see Sakuraba-senpai.
Everyone else was getting along pretty well, too.
I have to prove myself a worthy successor in order to protect my mother, the current Empress.
So you want apartment 106 to help protect your mother.
That's right.
I can't give it up.
I see.
That's not too different from my situation.
I have to wait for my mother and father in that room.
It'd be terrible if they came back and I wasn't there.
You can't back down either, then.
Me too!
I-I'm not lying.
I owe someone my life,
and that's why I need that apartment.
Why don't you tell us about it, Yurika?
I'm acting as a magical girl for that person.
They got hurt pretty badly to save me.
So I can't give up.
It's dangerous, and I'd end up causing
trouble for my family, so I can't visit them.
I'm lonely, but...
that person was also trying their best.
I can't step down because I need the people of the earth to prosper again.
Also, there was a roller coaster.
A roller coaster?
Yeah.
When I was young,
I came up to the surface once.
I didn't get to ride on it.
I've always wanted to try it out.
Talking everything over with you all...
I guess everyone has their own reasons.
Well, this is a dilemma.
Not really. I'm going to win.
I'm not going down that easily.
Me neither.
I'm glad we came here.
This is mine!
I won't let anyone have it.
S-Satomi-sama!
Satomi-sama is...
H-He can't...
I...
I found this tree first.
I won't let you have it, Makkenji!
If you want a beetle so bad, go find your own tree.
B-Beetle?
Just a little further...
Satomi-sama...
Do you think I'm a tree with a beetle on it?
I got it!
It wasn't me you wanted.
My beetle.
Satomi-sama, you jerk!
I'm sorry!
You Neanderthal.
You're the worst.
Hey, Sanae...
Huh?
You know I roll around all the time when I sleep, right?
Yeah, but...
I've never had you cling onto me before.
Well, you are a ghost, so...
You like beetles more than girls, anyway, right?
Look at it from my view!
I know I was dreaming,
but it was an eight-centimeter beetle!
I just had to catch it!
Big beetles are what men dream of.
Summer doesn't get any better than that!
A beetle...
Don't you guys agree?
Ruth-san?
Satomi-sama, do you really like beetles that much more than me!?
I don't think I'll be able to go back to that room for a while.
Kiriha-san?
You're out for a night stroll, too?
No, I kind of ran away.
Or maybe got what I deserved.
Kiriha-san, what's that card?
Doesn't really fit me, huh?
I know that, but I just can't get rid of it.
Jeez, that Koutarou.
I got this from someone I liked a long time ago.
I haven't been able to see them since, but...
You miss them?
Yeah.
I do.
I'm not sure what I'd do if I saw them again, though.
What is he doing—
All right...
I came to get you!
Sanae!
A-Are you all right!?
Why do you have that?
Huh?
Am I just a nuisance?
Sanae?
It makes sense.
I mean, who'd want a ghost haunting their home?
Nobody, right?
What are you—
It's fine.
I get it.
It's my fault for thinking you were different!
Hey!
Hey, what's wrong, Sanae!?
Sanae!
Nothing seems to go right.
Not for me, or Sanae.
We lost today because we took them too lightly.
They were really cute—
I mean, they were strong.
Yeah, they were.
But we have this trump card.
Bro, you're not planning on using these, are you?
Yeah. We're getting what we want tomorrow.
Time to eat.
Hey, Sanae.
Look, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
It's not like you to be upset so long.
I'm just an evil spirit.
It's not surprising you'd keep your grandma's charms with you at all times.
You don't have to say it like that!
I'm a ghost!
I just want to get rid of you!
We'll never get along!
You and I are—
enemies!
Yeah, I suppose we are enemies.
That's right.
You're right. We'll always be enemies!
Sanae-chan!
Koutarou, you jerk.
akogarete iru no you
I always wanted
anata to sukyandaru
to have a scandal with you
itomenai no kokoro
My heart wants to win you over
ano ko yori mo hayaku
before that other girl does
hito wa
Why do we
nande nande
Why, oh, why?
nando
- even though each and every time,
kizutsuitemo
we end up feeling hurt -
koi ni
fall in love?
koi ni ochiru
Why do we fall in love?
ikimono nano
Ah, but such is life
marude marude mirukutii
Just like milk tea
betsubetsu no tokoro de umareta futari
Our hearts lie in separate places
amai amai no mirukutii
Just like this sweet, sweet milk tea
atsu atsu yo ima sugu kyun to nomihoshite
It's steaming hot, so I want you to drink it up in one go
marude marude mirukutii
Just like milk tea
zetsumyou na kagen ga wakaranai no ne
I can't make sense of this breathtaking feeling
torotorokeru no mirukutii
It's liquid velvet, just like milk tea
saigo dake chotto dake honnori to nigai
Even though it tastes slightly bitter at the end
Men
Women
Cold
Ramen
When you play ping pong,
you're supposed to say "saa!"
"Saa," right?
Let's try it!
That was hard.
Next Episode
Precious Charms
Yeah, it was.