We hated you from the beginning--
and loved you from the beginning, too.
And so we wanted to become true
friends with you. To cross the wall...
A bear has crossed the Wall of Severance,
our only line of defense.
Sumika Izumino has lost her life to it,
and we are now unable to reach
Katyusha Akae, Konomi Yurikawa,
and several other students.
We are facing our greatest crisis
since the Day of Severance.
Happily, the bear we believe to have
been the invader was shot last night,
but we mustn't let our guard down.
Understand that the friends sitting next
to you are the keys to your protection now.
Never be alone for a moment,
even on school grounds.
You must protect each other!
I'll be the one to protect you.
Kureha?
I'm sorry.
Why? I mean, yesterday...
That's not what I intended...
Fine then, Tsubaki.
"Mitsuko Yurizono・(Yuri)"
Damn, you're rejecting me? Well, fine.
That's what I like about you anyway.
The fun's only beginning, Kureha Tsubaki.
I'll give you a good working over,
and then I'll eat you up.
Yurikumaaaaaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
"INVISIBLE STORM"
Viens avec moi
Church chimes echo in the distance
Offer up a prayer and betray today
Wander in a dark forest, then become
the morning moon at the Wall of Severance
I won't join the Invisible Storm
Once I've made you stickier
with sweet, thin honey
Please, approve me, I'll be a good girl
Picture-book pages dancing on
the breeze shake up shadowy memories
Always
I'll be waiting you-know-where,
in an empty world
Even if everything falls apart
Even if you have to gracefully writhe,
even if you have to bend space-time
Find me
Flower petals will slowly
enfold us on a starry night
Come on...
J'ai besoin de toi
How are you? Have you calmed down a bit?
Yes.
Liar.
What?
You're a bad liar.
You're just like Reia that way--earnest to a fault.
"Reia"... my mom?
Yes.
You really remind me of her.
You're so much like your mother.
You mustn't suffer in silence, Kureha.
The pain of losing a loved one grows
worse the more you try to hide it.
I know that all too well.
I lost Reia--your mother--that day.
She was my dear friend,
and I'll never have another like that again.
That's why I was so happy
when you came to this school
and brought that flowerbed back to life.
That place held special
memories for Reia and me.
I hate bears.
Yes, so do I. They stole the ones we loved.
There's another.
What?
There's one more bear here.
But surely Yurizono exterminated
the bear that attacked Izumino...
She didn't!
I saw them! There's one more bear!
I'm positive it's still in this school somewhere!
"School" really is an excellent system.
All I have to do is stay here
and wait for the time to come.
Yurizono!
I'm volunteering to fill in
for Yurikawa as chair today.
Well done, Oniyama! Class friendship
starts with individual responsibility.
The leadership you're showing is wonderful.
Strong people are beautiful.
Y-Yurizono...
You can call me Mitsuko.
The lily opens!
There's my good girl.
Now, hurry and let me eat Kureha Tsubaki.
"Lulu Yurigasaki・(Yuri)"    "Ginko Yurishiro・(Yuri)"
Growl?
There's one more bear.
I'll never forgive bears. I'll ruin bears!
Growl-brrrr...
She's totally itching to shoot a bear!
Aw, and we came here to beat
that icky Mitsuko Yurizono to it, too!
But we can't approach her in that mood!
But who knew there'd be a rival bear
at that school who saw through us?!
Delicious smell. Growl.
Geez, Ginko, you're not even listening!
Kureha Tsubaki must be a really tasty girl, huh?
In answer to Pope Urban II's call,
the armies of kings and nobles
across Western Europe gathered
to form the first army of crusaders in 1096...
And thus began a long series of wars.
"Flashback"
Here, Miss Forgetful.
All right, girls, the test will...
...not include this!
You better believe it'll include this!
Sumika... Time moves so slowly
when you're not in class with me.
What this means is that the Crusades
exposed the people of Western Europe...
Will I start to forget everything now?
Forget that day, that moment...
Will I eventually forget love
and be invisible like the others...?
Your mother's flowerbed?
"Flashback"
Yeah. Mom told me that back
when she was a student here,
she built it with her special friend.
Ah, so that's why you love it.
Yeah. I want to make it full of flowers again.
I see. You didn't give up, did you?
Nope.
Your mother's precious garden...
So that's your love.
My love?
Yes, love.
That's why I won't give up either, Kureha.
Not on my precious love...
I won't forget. I'll never forget.
I won't give up on love either, Sumika.
We must be invisible!
Let us begin the Exclusion Ceremony.
"Exclusion Ceremony・(Exclusion)"
"Friends" are more important
than anything else, agreed?
The friends here in this
classroom right now: that's us.
People who contradict our
feelings are a disgrace, agreed?
People who stick out from our crowd
are just no good, agreed?
People who refuse to fit in
with us are a nuisance, agreed?!
People like that who can't follow social cues...
...are evil.
"Can't Follow Social Cues = Evil・(Exclusion)"
Sumika Izumino got killed
by a bear because of that.
It's only natural, isn't it? Because she was evil.
We must decide who the next evil to exclude is.
Let's search evil!
"The Invisible Storm・(Exclusion)"
"5. Hinako Serina"
"6. Uchiko Ai"
"4. Saori Shimabukuro"
"3. Aoi Uezu"
"2. Karen Tanaka"
"1. Evil = Kureha Tsubaki"
"Evil = Kureha Tsubaki"
Select! The time has finally come!
I'm going to eat her--Kureha Tsubaki!
Slurp.
Grrrrrr...
Kureha, did you have fun
with your friend again today?
That's great! You really
love her, don't you, Kureha?
You know what? As long as you don't
forget love, you'll never be alone.
Remember that.
That's right. If I don't forget love,
I'm not alone.
"Flashback"
A storm and flood warning has just
been issued for the greater metro area.
We're seeing violent rain and wind.
Residents in some areas
have been advised to evacuate.
If this applies to you,
evacuate immediately in accordance
--with your township's instr--
--Oh no--the flowerbed!
"Bear Warning"
"Storm and Flood Warning"
Kureha...
Aren't you cold?
I'm fine, Kureha.
Thank you, Sumika.
Thank you for staying my friend...
Sure. Thanks for staying mine.
I won't back down on my love.
To live means to constantly forget,
back down, and cast away.
Those who cannot replace the old
with the new will eventually perish.
We beasts never live in the past.
All that exists is the present,
the emotions we feel right now.
The mood, the rhythm of
this moment is everything.
The invisible ones decide
how to run closed worlds.
Grrrrrrr.
You know, Ginko,
I'll never forget the day I met you.
You found my love. You brought it to me.
So no matter what happens,
I won't give up on love.
The time for judgment has come, growl.
"Incoming Call: Blocked Number"
Hello.
Is your love the real thing?
Absolutely.
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance.
Kureha Tsubaki,
if your love is true, go to the roof.
The bears are waiting for you.
Give yourself over to the bears,
and your love will be approved.
I'll never forgive bears. I'll ruin bears!
I've been waiting for you, Kureha Tsubaki.
Yurizono? Why are you here?
To eat you.
What?
Here's something you'll want to know:
I'm the one who ate your beloved Sumika Izumino.
Me, Mitsuko Yurizono. I'm a bear.
What are you talking about?
I suppose you can't believe it, but I'm a bear.
A bear pretending to be human,
if we're being precise.
A bear pretending to be human?
Yes. So was that bear I shot, Konomi Yurikawa.
Yurikawa? But she was your--
"Friend"? Maybe so.
While she obeyed me, anyway.
Did you know? When you're
deciding to be friends with someone,
the only important thing is that
she's just a little bit inferior to you.
That way she's easy to control.
You look so incredulous! All right, then--
I'll show you proof that I'm a bear.
Those are Sumika's...
Yes. Believe me now?
I'm telling you, she was a freak!
She was getting eaten,
and all she did was worry about you.
"I'm sorry, Kureha! I can't fix your love,
your mother's flowerbed!
Even though I promised I wouldn't back down!
I'm sorry, Kureha... I'm sorry..."
You don't have it in you to shoot me.
That's why I love you.
Right there, that rage in your eyes--
it's so good... it's getting me off...
Your blood is boiling in your veins!
You smell. You smell like I can hardly stand.
Come on, get angrier for me.
I'll never forgive bears. I'll ruin bears!
I told you: you don't have it in you to kill me!
Grawr... grawr...
Gra-ra-rawr!
No way! This can't be...!
Tee-hee. Missed me.
Missed me.
Missed me!
Grawr!
It's all right. In place of the Sumika I ate...
...I'll love you!
I want to eat her! I want to eat her right now!
Court is in session!
We now begin the Yuri Trial.
Your Honor, give us yuri approval, fast!
I want to save Kureha Tsubaki, growl!
Save Kureha Tsubaki?
What are you talking about?
You two are bears!
Growl...
We'll eat humans! If we don't eat them,
we can't protect Ginko's love!
Ha, so you admit your crime.
I'm so cool.
Objection! For a bear,
eating humans is no crime!
Sparkle, sparkle!
Hurry, rule! It has to be now!
I see. That's the sexy way.
Shaba-da-doo. So, defendant-bears...
Will you be invisible?
Or will you eat humans?
We'll eat...
...humans!
Growl!
I now declare the verdict.
Yuri approved!
Growl, growl!
Growl!
Yuri approved!
Ra-ra-rawr!
I won't back down!
Where am I?
You won't back down on your love, growl.
Growl. Only love can change the world.
My... love...
Yes, love.
Love.
--Mmm.
What is this? Their tongues
feel rough, but... warm and kind!
I've felt this somewhere before...
Smooch.
Come on, Kureha.
I can do it!
Give me the Promise Kiss!
Grawr!
Gra-ra-ra! Gra-ra-ra-ra-rawr!
I... killed her?
I killed Yurizono?
No, this can't be!
A bear in human form... No!
But...
What did you want to talk about?
If it's the Exclusion Ceremony,
you can't participate yet.
Because you can't be our friend until
you take part in the Invisible Storm.
I don't want to, growl.
Growl! So instead, we'll tell you
something you'll want to know, Oniyama!
What?
Say, where do you think
your missing friends are?
"Missing"? You mean like Akae?
Right there.
Wh-What is this?
This is where we buried the parts
of Katyusha Akae we didn't eat.
"Katyusha Akae・(Yuri)"
Muahaha! We're super nice, right?
Wh-What do you mean, you ate Akae?
Why are you telling me that?!
Grrrr.
Growl...
Because we're about to...
Shock!
Bear shock!
...eat you.
Slurp.
On the boundary that severed
ripe moon from sleeping forest
Break the law God shackles us with and smile
I turned away from the bleating flock
of shadows and howled my bloodthirsty ego
Here amidst the Invisible Storm
Overflowing honey and soul
I want to rend silk with my fangs
I'm afraid you'll vanish
like the world's last ray of hope
The savage beast inside me
tore out the throat of innocence
Come on, shoot me through the heart
with your sweet-scented Barrett of love