I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
Hello, gentlemen.
I journeyed here
in order to take your lives.
Hello, boy.
Your partner ran into
some very bad luck, Jet.
Well, he never had any
good luck in the first place.
Yeah, but this is real bad.
If you're smart,
you'll stay out of it.
I don't care,
just tell me what's up.
Listen, I'm telling you this
for your own good.
And if you get involved in this,
you're gonna make
a world of trouble for me.
You know, Bob...
You're the only one I can
turn to for help right now.
I'll make sure it doesn't
cause any problems for you.
Where have I heard that before?
You're always in trouble, Jet.
Anyone close to you gets dragged in.
All right. This is only a rumor, but...
Have you heard of
the name "Mad Pierrot?"
So the rumor's true.
We have a mummy on the ship.
I heard you got beat up
by some freaky guy, Spike.
I seem to recall you being
in this condition before.
You're not showing
a whole lot of improvement,
but not a lot I can
do about it, huh?
Let's face it. You end up like this
because you go looking for trouble.
It's called "bad behavior."
But not my problem, huh?
Well, since there's nothing
I can do about it, I'll be off.
Take care.
The victim was a
high-ranking director at ISSP.
- The seventh one to go down.
- What?
I don't blame you for being surprised.
They've kept it a tight secret.
The top guys definitely don't want
the world to know about this.
Why's that?
Your partner's in deep trouble.
This guy's a perfect killing machine.
They say that nobody who's seen
his face has lived to tell about it.
Those few that managed to get away
were hunted down relentlessly.
And they always turned up dead.
They say he appears with a smile,
and he leaves with a smile.
Yeah, he's a mystery, all right.
An assassin known as
"Mad Pierrot" Tongpu.
Faye-Faye!
Smoke-smoke, Faye-Faye!
Puff-puff, Faye-Faye!
My name's Faye.
Not Faye-Faye.
You just say it once, okay?
Faye-Faye! Some weird mail
came-came for Bebop-Bebop.
I would've been able to pay it off,
if I had just a little more time.
Would you hold still?
Hmm... "Hello, boy."
"You're invited to a wonderful party."
Wait a minute. This is...
All right, don't tell Spike about this.
It's a secret, okay?
But why?
Faye-Faye! Why keep it a secret?
If we don't, that lunkhead--
will run right out to the party?
It's secret mail-mail from Mars.
It's Space Land?
Nice place to hold a party,
don't you think?
Yeah. You gonna go like that?
It's perfect for a
masquerade, isn't it?
Maybe this is the one.
The one I won't come
back from. The end.
Just playing with your head.
Would you rescue me if it were true?
Lunkhead.
Lunkhead-lunkhead-lunkhead!
Hey, Ed.
Uh-huh?
Wake up. Where's Spike?
- He went somewhere.
- What?
Not that this is anything new, of course.
- That lunkhead...
- Lunkhead-lunkhead!
- Ed, I need a favor.
- What-what?
Hello! Welcome!
Yo.
Let's party!
You're not allowed in here!
It's dangerous in here!
Let's play outside!
You're not allowed!
Shut up!
Let's play outside!
It's dangerous in here!
Hi!
All right, Ed. First instruction.
Enter the ISSP mainframe
and do a search for Section 13.
- You follow me?
- Aye-aye!
Edward, as far as the public's concerned,
that section doesn't even exist.
It's tightly secured.
Can you hack into it?
Yes!
Hello!
I found it!
Okay, good.
Try to get in and locate a file
with the code name "Tongpu."
Tongpu-Tongpu...
Peek-a-boo, I see you.
ISSP assassination skills
enhancement experiment.
Clinical trial sample chart number 46.
Code name "Tongpu."
Confirmed, a marked
regression of the mind occurred
during the enhancement
development process.
Experiment canceled.
Sample to be permanently
maintained at quarantine facility.
In the beginning, he escaped
from the facility to seek revenge.
But now he seems to actually
enjoy the act of killing.
Apparently, his mind
is continuing to regress.
So he's like a child with
superhuman combat capabilities.
And really... there's nothing
more pure and cruel as a child.
It's showtime!
That's the last thing I need!
Hello!
Hi.
It hurts!
Mommy!
Mommy, it hurts!
Hurts me!
It hurts!
Mommy!
Momma!
Spike, listen,
we figured out what he is.
- He's a--
- Forget it.
I don't need the info anymore.
Man, I hate theme parks.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
I knew something fishy was going on.
So that's what it was.
Hm? What are you
guys talking about?
You can't really judge
a person by their looks.
Honestly disgusting.
Whoa, whoa, what are
you guys talking about?
I never thought it
would be a teenage girl.
It makes me despise him.
Who are you talking about?
Next episode:
"Boogie Woogie Feng Shui."
Aw, I didn't do anything
for the whole preview...