Faint-hearted traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
My dream!
Year 1, Class 1, Kamogawa Asumi.
My dream is to become a rocket driver!
That's because I've heard that the Earth is very
pretty when you look at it from space.
So I want to become a rocket
driver and go into space!
I want to take people to all
sorts of different planets!
And when they're on my rocket,
my dad and Lion-san will get special free rides!
The end!
Test Complete
Damn it! This is the worst!
It's going to be totally impossible to line
all these up in these last two days!
How many days do you think it took us
to line these up in the first place?!
Or so he says, Fuchuuya-kun.
Really, who do you think lined them up?
Damn monk haircut boy.
I don't want any more of this!
I've had more than enough!
I'm getting outta here!
We're just gonna fail no matter what!
I'm telling you, just hold on a second.
Calm down a little bit.
Don't mess with me!
How can I be calm?!
You know...
It's been bothering me for a while,
but what do you think that is up there?
It's a surveillance camera.
A surveillance camera?
What, you never noticed?
If you focus your eyes on it,
you can see the inner lens moving.
See? It just moved now.
Which would mean...
we were being watched this whole time?
Probably.
For what reason?
I see. We were all mistakenly letting
ourselves focus on the dominoes.
This was originally supposed to be a
closed-environment adaptation test, wasn't it?
Right. The most important thing will
be to finish out the seven days here.
It's not about how many dominoes we line up.
Right.
What do you mean by that?
Think about it.
What reason would they have for shutting up
three guys who don't know each other in a room?
That's the thing that the school
wants to see the most, right?
Say it so people can understand
what you mean, Suzuki!
I did...
In other words, the thing you're lacking most.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
Why are you always saying things
that make people uncomfortable?!
Who's doing that now?
Ah.
I thought of a wonderful way to finish lining
up the dominoes in the last two days.
What? Seriously?!
It really is tiring having a moron in here.
They must be observing everyone's
progress from somewhere...
Actually, I wonder how that
other moron is doing...
Pull yourself together, Asumi!
Come on, Asumi!
What's wrong?! Hey!
Wait!
Who's there...
It's you, Lion-san, right?
Lion-san!
Why do you look so sad?
What are you looking at?
This is...
Yuigahama
Why is Yuigahama burning?
Mom?!
She's calmed down a little bit
now that she's lying down,
but it looks like she's not going to stop shaking.
I wonder what could have happened to Asumi...
Her mind is just in turmoil from the stress
of this unfamiliar environment.
I'm sure it's a temporary thing.
That would be nice...
She's been saying some weird things, though...
Hey, what are you doing?!
You can tell by looking, can't you?
We don't have any time to waste.
If you have time to be worrying about others,
you should line some up too.
Really... Kamogawa-san is such a nuisance...
Panicking over a little thing like that...
It's proof that her spirit is weak.
What are you doing?!
You know, Asumi...
She said she wanted to be friends with
you from the bottom of her heart!
And you're more worried about
these than someone like that...
Is that supposed to be one of the astronaut
qualifications you talk about so much?!
Hey, Dad...
Why won't Mom come back home with us?
Mom, it's me.
It's me, Asumi.
I'm always right here.
Hey, Asumi!
Where are you going?
Wait right there!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
I don't want any more of this... not at all.
I really should have pressed this button sooner.
When Asumi is suffering so much...
I'm mad at myself for hesitating like this...
Passing the test while she's suffering like that...
I wouldn't be happy about that.
I'm sure I'd regret it later.
Because that just means I failed as a person!
Don't make it sound so pretty!
You're just pushing your suffering onto
Kamogawa-san, aren't you?
You just want to run away
and hide your weakness.
You're worried about Kamogawa-san?
Don't make me laugh.
You're just a simple hypocrite!
Oh, look. Resorting to violence again?
If you think you can change
what people think like that,
you're quite mistaken!
That's something that weak people do!
You...!
Stop!
Asumi!
I've always looked up at the sky,
ever since I was little.
I always, always, wanted to be closer to it.
That's all that my dream is.
It's the only dream I have.
I'm sorry for worrying you, Kei-chan, Ukita-san.
But I don't want to give up!
I want to try my best a little longer...
Ukita-san, Kei-chan, I want to
try my best with both of you!
I get it, Asumi.
Why don't you cool that off?
I hate your guts,
but I'll apologize for hitting you, at least.
The feeling is mutual.
I never want to go through this again.
What a brat!
Kei-chan!
I know... We need to get this done, right?
Yeah.
We don't have much time left.
Still, we have no choice but to get
as much done as we can, do we?
Hey...
Even after lights out, the light in the
bathroom still comes on, right?
This is your wonderful idea?!
Yeah.
It's just pulling all-nighters lining up the
dominoes with no breaks, though!
Well, sure...
Hey, the one who came up with
this plan better not be sleeping!
Right, right.
Please be a little quieter!
Even without your yelling,
everyone's on edge already!
I know that! Dammit...
I always thought these tasted chalky, but...
They're convenient for situations
like this, aren't they?
They make them just for that reason, you know.
Well, that's true, but...
Asumi, it's your turn next.
Come on, Asumi...
Right.
We're not getting any sleep,
so we need to at least eat properly.
How about your drink?
Is orange juice okay?
Yeah.
Now...
Time to eat!
Kei-chan...
You're really good at cooking.
It's delicious!
I'm honored by your compliment!
Although it tastes the same
no matter who makes it.
Now then...
Let's get these things lined up!
I smell!
Me too...
Well, of course we do...
We've been in this airtight room for two
days without washing ourselves, I guess.
No time to spare.
Yeah...
I haven't shampooed either!
I can't show myself like this to anyone!
Ah, I want to take a full shower
and really wash my hair!
You can shower as much as
you want the day after we're done.
However, I'm not sure whether
you'll be crying or laughing...
Right, right. I'm lining them up.
I just have to line them up, right?
Thanks for the food.
Just one more day of this, huh?
Yeah.
Just one more day until the exam is over...
Just one more day!
Just two rooms, huh?
So thirteen teams lasted until the final day, huh?
That's more than we expected, isn't it?
I guess it is.
But that project must have been impossible!
The dominoes?
I wonder who thought that one up.
I would have been pressing the
emergency button on the first day!
I feel the same way.
Ah, check this out.
What is it?
Look at this.
Some of the rooms got all of them lined up?!
Yes.
0350 and 2960 did.
It's over.
Now I can finally take a shower...
You know, Asumi...
She said she wanted to be friends with
you from the bottom of her heart!
There's no way she could be...
No one can understand me.
So if you think of this "river
of heaven" as a real river,
each individual little star can be
thought of as bits of sand or g...
Gravel.
...gravel in that whole. This is again part of...
As long as I can remember,
since I was a very small child,
I almost never set foot outside of that room.
If I tried to leave the room,
I would be severely scolded.
The tutors who always came at the same time...
The three meals a day that
always came at the same time...
The meals I spent alone.
That forever unchanging life...
In that unchanging room...
But still...
The stars I could see from that window
so high up were the only...
The stars were the only...
The only thing that changed a bit, day by day.
I, too...
I, too, was always looking up at the sky.
She doesn't understand.
There's no way anyone could understand.
Tokyo National Space School
Mom, look at this!
I passed!
Now, one day, I'll be able to go into space.
Kamogawa Family Grave
I'll make sure to show you how I can
become a rocket driver, okay?
Kamogawa-san?
Suzunari-sensei!
Really? So you passed the exam!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
You're not happy?
I'm happy. Very happy.
But...
When I think about things... and my father...
I start to wonder if it's really okay...
What do you think, sensei?
About my desire to go into space...
What do you really think?
Let's see...
The answer to that... is right here, I think.
What?
No matter what the people around you think,
you have to believe in your own dreams.
I'm sure many people will say
many different things to you.
And there may be times
when you feel discouraged.
When that happens,
the answer is always right here.
It's nowhere else but there inside of you.
Thank you very much!
Kamogawa-san?
My dad hasn't seen this yet!
Congratulations, little one.
So these are the successful applicants' papers?
So they'll be the first class of this new
astronaut training course, huh?
That's right. They'll be your students
starting next semester, Sano-sensei.
There sure are a lot of different kids!
I'm looking forward to it.
Though saying that, I'll still only be their lecturer.
I probably won't get too
deeply involved with them...
Kamogawa Asumi
Is there someone you know in there?
What? No, not really.
Kamogawa?
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
Preview
I've said goodbye to Lion-san and begun
my new life at the girls' dorm in Tokyo.
To Asumi:
When you get there,
open this.
- Dad
Of course I have Kei-chan and
Ukita-san with me at school!
And Fuchuuya-kun passed as well!
Tokyo National Space School
Seagull Girls Dormitory
But I'm feeling just a bit lonely in the
nooks and crannies of my heart...
Banners: Entrance Ceremony
Next time on Twin Spica:
Space School Entrance Ceremony.
Space School Entrance Ceremony
End