Lend me your strength, Asuramaru.
So this is demon possession?
No, we need to take it a step further.
Whilst in that condition, you must wound yourself
and offer your blood to the sword.
Blood?
Sounds like something a vampire would do.
Well, there's a rather rich history behind
the relationship between demons and vampires.
Would you like to hear about it?
Nope. We just need to know how it works.
Let's do this, Yuu.
Stop right there.
If you both fail, then we're really screwed.
Should things go south, the demon could go completely berserk.
That's why we came all the way out here, far beyond the walls.
Berserk?
Hm? What is it?
Nothing.
Everyone!
What's wrong?
We have Horsemen incoming.
Three...
Four...
Five of them.
That's some real shitty timing.
Well, what can you do? Let's go.
Pierce thine enemies, Gekkouin.
Protect our friends!
I did it, guys!
H-Hold up, did you just manifest your demon?
Hey, Shinoa! Explain!
You gave training to him and not us?
Of course not.
Yoichi has been exceptionally capable at
controlling his Infernal Arm from the start.
The kid ended up mastering
demon manifestation himself.
Seriously?
Um, I've been talking to my demon a lot lately, before I go to sleep,
and now it just... happens.
Drink my blood, Asuramaru!
Wait, Yuu!
Prepare to fight!
Yuu?!
What the hell was that?
Who knows?
He was able to keep it under control so far,
so there's no immediate danger.
It'll take some time before he makes contact with his demon.
We basically have to babysit him until then.
That's what we comrades are for.
War in Nagoya
zutto yume miteita kowaresou na kibou
For years I retreated to my dreams for hope
toki wo koe kousa shita sorezore no yasashisa
Our mercy survived all this time for each other
futto miageru sora ni kimi no egao egaku
I see your smile in the clouds above
ano hi kara bokutachi wa chigau sekai wo mita
We've been living in different worlds for a long time now
omoi ga afureru shinjiau koto wa
When I revisit my memories, I realize
tayasui koto da to sono kioku wa shitteru
that trusting others and opening your heart is not difficult
hikari to yami ni kakusareta kono michi wo susundeku
I walk a path veiled in light and dark
futatsu no omoi ga kirameku
Our feelings are the guide
kimi wo mamoritai
I want to protect you
kokoro ni kanjiru kizuna wo dakishimete
I embrace the bond we share
tachiagaru toki wa ima kanashimi kirisaite
Now is the time to rise and end the grief
two souls go toward the truth
Two souls go toward the truth
sono egao sagashite
I seek your smile
kono omoi ga bokura wo tsuyoku shinjitsu he to michibiku
That desire will lead us unwaveringly to the answer
Complicated
Connections
Comrades, huh?
What?
Kimizuki?
Remember when Yoichi and I
were interrogated by the Hiiragis?
They asked us what happened on the battlefield.
And what did you say?
That I didn't know anything.
Just like you ordered us to.
It was the right thing to do.
But is it right to keep Yuu in the dark?
If you're lying through your teeth about being a "comrade"
and only plan to exploit Yuu...
Then what?
Then nothing.
I'll stay for my sister's sake.
I'll put on a mask of deceit
and hope that my disgust doesn't surface.
Watch yourself, Kimizuki.
Shinoa's protecting Yuu from the upper—
It's fine, Mitsu.
And you agree, Yoichi?
Um...
I still believe that you two are doing all this for Yuu's own good, but...
You want an explanation.
We're comrades, right?
Of course.
Or so I'd like us to be, at least.
That's why...
Let's talk about everything after we're done here.
Not just about Yuu, but about us.
You guys! Pin him down!
Yuu!
Here we go.
Yes, it appears he's made contact with his demon.
Why would a child like this be born?
We must kill the Seraph of the End.
Devil.
You're a devil's child, Yuu.
D-Dad?
Come over here, Yuu.
What?
Let's go to a better place, Yuu.
You should have died here.
Everyone died because you ran away.
Succumb to me, Yuu.
You won't tip me over the edge
this easily, Asuramaru.
There's something I still have to do.
I made a promise to him.
He needs me.
Let's protect our family, Yuu.
I'm relying on you.
Yeah.
It's because you want my help
that I can come save you.
Hm?
And here I thought I'd win.
I already know how to handle your little games.
Oh, drop the big boy act already.
You're just a devil child
abandoned by his parents.
As long as Mika, Guren, Shinoa, and the others need me,
none of that matters to me.
Is that so? Well, you do seem stronger than before.
But I find that defiant attitude
of yours rather annoying.
And what are you gonna do about it?
Kill you.
What do you think you're doing?!
I don't want to hurt you.
What are you saying?
I need you, Asuramaru.
Will you save Mika with me?
What's in it for me?
I'll be your friend.
It's hard being alone.
Feeling unwanted and unloved.
I know that well.
So you're going to be my friend?
Yup!
Yuu!
Huh?
Did I put you guys through a lot of trouble?
He's back...
You're back, right?
Trouble? Sheesh, you were losing it.
Really? I had no idea.
So did you succeed?
Yup.
Then it's all good.
But really, that was seriously tiring.
We'll do Kimizuki's next week or something.
What?!
Quit messing around and do it now!
It's still a little too soon, don't you think?
What? You too?!
Nice work.
So? How'd you go?
Were you able to ward off its attacks?
Yeah.
I have you guys now, so I'm not alone anymore.
What?
Never mind.
It's nothing.
Well, to put it simply,
humans are defective creatures,
slaves to their heart's desires to the point
of indulging in forbidden experimentation.
Now, if you'll cast your eyes over this,
I'm sure you'll understand immediately.
Wait, was that...
If that was ever to be used...
Indeed!
Humans are finally succeeding in
weaponizing the Seraphs of the End.
We now have a serious situation on our hands.
B-But Queen Krul exterminated the Hyakuya sect
years ago, effectively putting an end to that experiment.
Eight years ago, to be exact.
I killed all children carrying any trace of the Seraphs of the End with my own hands.
Is that so? You killed all the test subjects?
Must I repeat myse—
If that is the case,
then how has their research come this far?
Aside from the Hyakuya Sect,
there were no other organizations with research this advanced.
Such a failure on your watch would be a major liability issue for—
Silence, Lest Karr!
You dare oppose me?
Perhaps.
If matters such as these are too much for you to handle, I'll gladly replace you as the ruler of Japan.
Don't push your luck, brat.
We're but a mere 200 years apart.
Besides, I'm stronger than—
Now, settle down, you two.
It's undeniable that the humans are making steady progress in their weaponization efforts, Queen Krul.
How will you handle that?
Our overall stance will not change.
We will send our main units to destroy the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
Do report back with results.
By the way, Ferid Bathory...
Who is the young boy behind you?
What is the meaning of this?!
For what reason did you bring Mikaela here?
And that video you played...
Are you conspiring against me?!
Ooh, scary.
But you can't kill me.
If I should die, the information I have might find its way to the Progenitor Council.
And of course, I'll be under fire too if they find out I let Yuu escape.
Oh? Wait a minute.
Could our mutual secrets bind us together as allies?
How fortunate.
Take my hand, Krul Tepes.
Just kidding.
Treat me a little nicer the next time, okay?
Krul...
Fight it, Kimizuki!
Hey, Shinoa! Was I like this too?
No. This might be trouble.
The demon may take over his body.
What?!
What the hell are we gonna do then?
Yuu!
Please prepare for the worst!
Die!
How desperate.
Yield to me, Kiseki-ou!
Not to a weakling.
Your body is mine.
Surrender yourself to me.
Big bro...
Don't worry.
How's Mirai doing?
Not good. It's progressing fast.
The thing is, we're low on food.
We won't even last three days at this rate.
Are we leaving?
Yeah.
We're planning on tomorrow morning.
Hold on.
I need time to prepare Mirai—
Leave her behind.
She'll only slow us down.
What did you say?!
Calm down!
Listen, Kimizuki.
We have responsibilities.
We have to move while
protecting those that survived.
It's a tough world. We don't have the luxury
of taking care of the sick.
You do it.
It's the best for your sister.
Don't give me that shit. I can't—
Mirai asked me herself.
She told me that she doesn't want to be a burden for you.
She doesn't have the strength to do it herself.
If you won't do it, we will.
Hey!
Wait, Kimizuki!
Open the door, Kimizuki!
Shit.
This way, from the balcony!
Bro...
Damn it!
Hey, big bro?
I don't want to slow you down.
Be quiet, Mirai.
Please kill me.
I don't want to see you in pain because of me.
Shut up!
Just shut up!
There it is.
For a moment, you wished to be free.
"I'm so sick of everything.
What did I do to deserve this?"
"I'm just a kid, too."
"If only I could kill my sister right here, right now."
No...
"It'd be so much easier if I could just leave this burden behind."
No.
Don't you think so?
No!
This is the truth, Kimizuki Shihou.
There's no need to resist. Free yourself.
Thank you for everything.
Now put me out of my misery.
I'm sorry, Mirai.
There's no need to apologize.
This is what I want.
Can I ask you one more thing?
You know, I met this weird guy recently.
He always pisses me off,
and I hate everything about him.
But he's always saying how he'd risk his life for his foster family, even though they're not related by blood.
What do you think?
He's a total idiot, right?
Yeah.
But I can't let an idiot like that outdo me.
Not when I have an actual sister of my own.
If I had to kill you, I'd sooner...
Wait, stop!
You're done for.
Not bad.
Come forth, Kiseki-ou.
Eh?
Yuu!
Chill out, guys.
We're good.
Kimizuki!
Hey!
Then what the hell was that for?!
Isn't it about time we found out which one of us was stronger?
So you did it, huh?
Yeah. And now I'm far stronger than you'll ever be.
Oh? You wanna go?
Hey, cut it out! Stop fighting!
Fine by me.
Why not? This'll be interesting.
Come, Asuramaru!
Unfold, Asura-Kannon!
Don't wet your pants, Kimizuki!
On the count of nine, unlock the Devil's Coffin:
Kiseki-ou!
One, two, three, four...
Hey! Where do you think you're going?!
Away from whatever the hell that is!
That just has "bad news" written all over it!
Tsk.
He's an idiot, but he has good intuition.
What?!
Well, I guess it did save me this time around.
Huh?
I said, it's a pain in the ass
to deal with a dropkick like you!
Eat shit. C'mere, let's settle this once and for all!
Come on, can't we all just get along?
Bring it!
Shinoa, those were...
Yes.
The special abilities that they couldn't previously use.
Yoichi succeeded in manifestation without any training, too.
How did Lieutenant Colonel Guren find those three?
Hey, what's going on?
It seems someone's gone through the database and wiped everything about them.
Someone?
It has to be Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
Is he planning to oppose the Army's superiors?
If only it were that simple.
What?
Human experimentation, war with vampires...
I get the feeling that something horrible's about to happen.
reimei ni tsuki wa korogeochite
At first light, the moon is brought low
shitataka na kirameki ni kakusareru
by a far greater power
kanjou ni kanketsu suru omoi
Our love is manifest,
dare no kokoro mo tsumugenai
but our hearts are lacking
yuuen no inori
A distant prayer
shinjiteita chitsujo ga uso naraba
The order we believed in is a lie
jibun no kokoro de sura junshoku shite
What have we left but to sacrifice our hearts
kuruitateru honoo matou
on the fiery altar of service?
umidashite wa hakai suru hakoniwa
The little we create is ruined soon after
tatoe nigiru tsurugi ga moroha demo
Our swords bite into the hand that wields them,
subete ushinau made
but you still have to resist
aragae trickster
until all is lost
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
The Demon Army's
Ambition
"The Demon Army's Ambition."
Illustrated by Satoru Isono