When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Payday!!
Seaside Camp
For seaside camp at Hakuou Academy,
they take a private jet.
With her fear of flying,
Hinagiku does not participate.
But you mustn't panic.
Don't change the channel.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
What's this? We're suddenly
on a summer break episode?
It seems, due to rotation issues,
Episode 18 and 20 were
swapped at the last minute.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
The Rare Cards Are Swimsuits
The number of participants
is small for seaside camp.
Well, now, that's because the fee
to participate is insanely expensive.
It is not for the convenience
of anime production.
And for Hayate,
this is his first plane ride.
But you know, he once rode
in a chopper, didn't he?
Oh, well...
Thank you very much, Miss.
Wow, it's so pretty!
What is?
Kumo-umi (cloud sea)!
Oh-ho!
Katsy, why don't you come look
at the kumo-umi with us?
"Unkai".
Unkai?!
Written as "sea of clouds",
it's read as "unkai".
Once summer break's over,
I'm putting it on the kanji test.
Crushed!
Unkai. Unkai. Unkai. Unkai. Unkai.
Little Master Taiga.
I am thirsty.
I-Is cola okay?
Yes.
G-Got it.
H-Himuro...
It's cold and delicious.
Seconds, please.
Oh, sure.
Nonohara, could I sit down now?
Young Master, I told you, did I not?
You did.
And what did I say?
The best way to prevent
blood clots is to run.
One more time.
The best way to prevent
blood clots is to run!
Then run, damn you!
Nonohara, keep it down.
Yes, ma'am.
Miss, thank you for paying
the fee for seaside camp...
Air Sickness Bag
Hayate, I think it'd be better
if you didn't try to thank me
for paying while you're airsick.
Pardon me...
A luxury resort island
with white sand beaches,
floating in the blue seas of the tropics.
That is Hakuou Island.
The Hakuou Academy's island used
exclusively for its seaside camp.
We're here!
Make sure you follow me!
There!
Come on, get on already.
Up we go.
And now, to your right, you will see...
I feel like we got some
irrelevant images in there...
The screen capture people certainly
won't be able to let their guards down.
Huh?
Welcome to Hakuou Island,
Hakuou Academy's island
used exclusively for its seaside camp.
Who are you?
Pardon me.
Installed here just this year,
I am Hakuou Island's in-house butler
and manager, Schmidt Offenbach.
Please call me Schmidt.
Oh, I didn't know.
Yes, and to make this
a happy summer break memory,
I shall work hard to create for you.
Then we'll place ourselves in your hands.
We're in your hands!
Then let me show you
to your rooms right away.
The Avarice Room
The Simpleton Room
It looks like we're the only
ones assigned 3 to a room.
Is that because we're underachievers?!
I doubt that, but...
Can't show you!
Say, Himuro, which bed do you want?
The Fortitude Room
Man, that was heavy!
Young Master.
Not heavy! Not heavy! Not heavy at all!
The Social Recluse Room
The main room is yours, Miss.
Klaus and I will be in the guest room.
Then, I will see you later.
I wouldn't have minded
being in the same room...
Everyone change into your swimwear!
Assemble by the pool!
SIGN: Taiga
SIGN: Nagi
SIGN: Izumi
SIGN: Risa
Before we go swim in the ocean,
we will practice swimming in this pool.
We'll start with some stretching!
Okay, then I think it's time
to get into the pool...
Thank you for waiting!
What?!
Schmidt, what the hell is that?!
A synchronized swimming puppeteer machine!
A synchronized swimming puppeteer machine?
Yay!
Then I shall waste no time...
Push.
Zambot Moon Attack!
Hey, why is he in the foreground?!
Hey, you! What do you think
you're doing to the Miss?!
Oh, no, this is one of the attractions
for creating happy memories.
Please watch for a while.
Huh?
Uh, okay...
Start the music!
The neverending blue sky
With a heart and mind fresh as can be
Schmidt! Stop this!
How is this going to make
for happy memories?!
H-Himuro!
Power of Flower
Don't worry about me!
An indomitable spirit!
Watch me from where you are!
Nonohara, h-help!
Power of Flower
Young Master,
I do not recall raising you to be so weak!
Y-Yes, sir!
Power of Flower
Miss, are you all right?!
I may be small now
Yeah, I'm managing somehow.
But that butler named Schmidt...
But I'll reach high and look at the future
He said he would have us make
happy summer break memories,
but he's the one enjoying himself!
Powerful Flower
Yes, I think so, too.
And someday, even that bud
Wh-What are you doing?!
Will bloom large right
in the middle of your heart
Please create happy summer break
memories with your mistress.
And now, for the finale... Push.
Power of Flower
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
Hakuou
Were you able to make some happy memories?
Like hell we could've!
It is noon. That was the lunch bell.
A luxurious barbeque has been prepared
at the beachside restaurant.
All right!
Katsy, you can punch Schmidt after lunch.
True.
However, before that...
Having lunch in your school
swimwear would be unfortunate,
so I have prepared
fabulous swimwear for you!
I'm taking this!
I shall go with this one.
Hmm, then I'll pick this one.
However, I shall take the liberty
of creating the selections for you.
What?
Please leave the changing to me as well.
What?!
This is not Lancelot!
As I thought, he's the one enjoying this.
He is enjoying himself far too much.
Is "daidai-iro (orange)" orange?
(Daidai-iro tte orenji?)
Think about the answer yourself.
(Jibun de kangaenasai)
Izumi Segawa.
Miki Hanabishi.
Risa Asakaze.
Yukiji Katsura.
Miss Nagi Sanzenin.
And Young Master Taiga Ohkouchi.
Hey, now, why are you finishing up with him?
No matter how you look at it,
you're panning way too much!
And so, here they are at lunch time.
This bikini...
Yes, this is eros.
Schmidt's sensibilities are a bit odd.
You think so? I rather like it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
in order to make your seaside
camp lunch a happy memory,
I have taken the liberty
of preparing this for you.
Create.
It looks like he might be up
to something again.
No, surely not...
Eating a live alligator!
Naturally, it is still alive. Create.
Right around when hell was
breaking loose on Hakuou Island,
Isumi was...
...trying to get to the seaside camp
and had gotten lost again.
Sniff, sniff.
Woof, woof.
Peter! Come over here!
There's someone buried here!
We have to let Uncle know!
Meanwhile, Hinagiku was...
...fully enjoying a day off in the city.
Tres bien.
All right! Today, let's do
a TurboGrafx challenge in Ikebukuro!
Oh, you there, miss!
Huh? Me?
Can't show you!
You're good at this, miss!
Darn you little...!
Well, this is a highly
technologically advanced program.
It's pushing the limits of the hardware.
I see.
After rampaging its heart out,
Mr. Alligator went "see
you later" back to nature.
Hayate and the others
learned how precious life is.
Humans. Alligator. Coral. Seagulls.
They are all invaluable members
and their fellows of Spaceship Earth.
I wish you well, Alligator!
Don't ever get caught by humans again!
Find a nice bride and raise
a warm alligator family!
When the families meet, make
sure to do it at your bride's home!
Yum! It was just so yum!
*This is in Tigerese.
I can't eat any more!
But I still want to have it again!
After lunch, it's free time.
Every conceivable kind of marine sport
was being created for them.
Izumi Segawa, Miki Hanabishi,
and Risa Asakaze
encountered the brilliantly
blue sea on Hakuou Island.
They encountered...
Oh, they encountered...
Oh, they so encountered...
Head!
Hinagiku Katsura in "Delineating
the Passionate World", coming up next!
Coming Up Next
Aren't you going to play around, Miss?
I enjoy spending time like this the best.
I have brought you a drink.
Thanks. Create.
Merci. Create.
He's a good butler
when he's not up to anything...
What?
Ooh! This is good stuff!
Tail Fin
Dark Meat
You Are Here
Hyakujou (stomach)
Saezuri (tongue)
What do you think?
Of what?!
I will now have you enjoy
a wonderful deep sea outing.
But we can't see anything.
Create...
Don't try to gloss it over!
This must be Diana's doing.
Little Master?
Let's walk.
Yes, Miss.
And thus, the time for supper came to pass.
Meals at hotels are apparently luxurious,
but that has nothing to do with her.
C-Camp... Ranchu goldfish...
F-First kiss?!
Dinner at the Hakuou Academy's
seaside camp was a formal affair.
To the Hakuou Academy's seaside camp!
Create!
Oh? You seem rather glum...
I don't want a seaside camp like this!
Me, neither.
I want to go home!
We're sick of this seaside camp, too.
Idiot Trio...
Idiot Trio?!
Oh, sorry.
It's just like the three girls say.
Schmidt, we don't want to be
your entertainment any longer!
Miss Katsura, with all due respect,
I am merely exerting myself so that
you may create this seaside camp
to be a happy summer break memory.
And your exertions are a nuisance.
Master Himuro.
Schmidt, your meddlesome way isn't good
for the Young Master's education.
You, too, Master Nonohara?
Miss...
If everyone wants to go home, I'll go, too.
Then, shall we go home?
Oh, put the leftovers in tupperwares,
okay? I'll be taking it with me.
Not so fast.
Schmidt.
Move aside.
When it comes to seaside camp
during summer break,
you must have a test of courage at night!
In order for this to be a happy
summer break memory for you all,
I have had these people assemble
from all over the world!
The fun is only beginning!
It's show time!
Miss!
Hayate fought valiantly to protect Nagi.
I-I'm counting on you, Nonohara!
Take that.
Nonohara had Azumamiya fight.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Taiga protected Himuro.
Freezing Killer Jet
Klaus sprayed them with insecticide!
They often appear during the summer.
Tama set up a mosquito coil!
Create happy memories!
Like hell we could!
Everyone, we're going home!
Is everyone here?
Yes!
But that sure was one
hell of a seaside camp.
That's Hakuou Academy for you...
Oh? Katsy, this plane
is flying over mountains.
Huh?
We're not heading back
to the Hakuou Academy?!
Hey, where do you think you're going?
If you do not like the seaside camp,
I shall create a school camp in the woods.
Schmidt?!
Who knows where the group is headed?
Next time, they will fight
the memories of a summer.
Maria's Room
Hello, I'm Maria.
Our guests today are Miss
Sakuya Aizawa's butlers,
Mr. Makita and Mr. Kunieda.
I'm Makita.
I'm Kunieda.
Neither of you have appeared
in the episodes recently,
but what kinds of things
do you do on your days off?
I bought a guitar a short while ago, but...
E and stuff is fine, but F is just...!
Oh, I'm Makita.
Cleaning my room, I suppose...
Oh, but when I'm cleaning,
I can't help but end up reading books.
Oh, I'm Kunieda.
Wow, I had no idea.
Thank you for joining me today.
Well, then see you again next time.
Please look forward to next time.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful,
it'll be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
SIGN: Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Hello, hello, hello! I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
Oh? We're playing your song again?
On a certain jungle-like dot-com site,
I currently rank higher than Hinagiku,
but to be extra safe,
I'm giving it one more push!
I see...
Now is the time to prove who's
the heroine of "Hayate the Combat Butler"!
That's my Miss!
Your competitiveness
is growing ever more polished.
Hayate, the word "defeat" does not
exist in Nagi Sanzenin's vocabulary!
Bye-bye!
Preview
And now, next time on
"Hayate the Combat Butler"...
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Saki's been acting strange lately.
It seems she's got
something on her mind, but...
Saki doesn't look it, but I guess her
coming-of-age ceremony is next year.
Incidentally, how was your
coming-of-age ceremony, Maria?
I'm a young and fresh
17 years old, you know.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Miss Saki's Little Preoccupation
(National Edition) 2007".
Come to think of it,
no one celebrated my birthday.
Miss Saki's Little
Preoccupation (National Edition) 2007
Well, not that it really matters.
Join Hayate again next time to "Release!"