It is indeed the time to start Kaleido Star.
When you watch Kaleido Star, I think
you should keep your room brightly lit
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Have you ever had something
important to you end?
When we had fun, when we had tough times,
when we laughed and cried,
the precious memories
that we made together...
Being thankful for many, many things.
But, we can't let it end like this. Don't
you think? Don't you think? Don't you think?
The dream everyone is looking
for must be someplace
It has to be somewhere
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Remember how I used to say
I could make it to the end?
I must have been pretending to be tough
Everything I did was reckless
and it never got me anywhere
But you alone were always beside me
The dream everyone is looking
for must be somewhere
You can start going forward
From this moment, something will start
I want to believe that
The light I haven't seen yet is
beaming toward the promised place
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Sora! It was the best!
Two weeks from opening day,
the audience's reaction started changing.
Did you read today's newspaper?
Of course I did.
Kaleido Stage's new director, Mia Guillem.
Her appearance has been more
dramatic than Halley's Comet!
Well, of course, I deserve
to get that comment.
Don't think you'll get away with this!
"Yuri's Amazing Trap."
There was concern that Kaleido Stage
would grow smaller and weaker.
However, there is plenty of possibility
that it will regain its strength.
It really could be.
It means that no matter how
Yuri tries to obstruct us,
people cannot ignore a really nice show.
I've seen all kinds of shows,
but, even setting aside favoritism,
I think this show is wonderful.
What?
Are you serious?
My dad is an old-fashioned type kind of man.
So he can't tell a lie.
Hey, Marion...
Oh, it would be nice if this show kept
on like this and became a long run.
No way.
But if the audience keeps
growing like this...
Maybe we'll even get lots
of sponsors signing on.
I don't think you should
get overexcited about this.
Anna, you missed the timing
at the very beginning.
Mia, your face is too tense sometimes.
Sora, you let yourself go,
and make your moves too fast.
If you keep doing that, the lighting
technician cannot keep up with you.
You cannot call our performance
perfect by any means.
But...
This show is not too bad.
Just now, was that...?
Praise?
Did she praise... us?
I can tell by the way she talks.
She likes the show a lot.
Miss Layla is praising us!
That makes me happier than
any other good critiques.
Aim for a long run! Yeah! Yeah!
In order to make that happen,
we should brace ourselves for the
remainder of the two weeks and perform.
Yes.
Now I'm getting motivated! Yeah!
Me, too. Yeah!
Yeah!
For the sake of Kaleido Stage's future!
Death...
The ending of things.
Excuse me, please stop it with
the inauspicious fortune-telling.
Kaleido Stage is at the critical moment
whether it can survive or perish.
So can you produce brighter futures?
Well, there is no meaning in fortune-telling.
Sora! It's happening!
Ugh... swallowed it.
It's not the time for saying
something like that.
People are filled with a practice room!
You just said something funny!
Why now? I didn't intend it to be funny!
Anyway, please come!
What's going on?
I thought everyone quit.
I'm not dreaming, right?
Maybe everyone decided to come back
after they heard about
Kaleido Stage's reputation.
As I expected... It's happening?
After all, this is the show
that Miss Layla praised.
Seriously, the revival of Kaleido
Stage may not be a dream.
I guess you need to rewrite
"Freedom" with more people, Mia.
Let me handle it.
Oh, I didn't know you were here.
Ken.
Everyone, Boss wants us to
gather in his room right away.
What?
I wonder if it means... As we thought...
Yeah!
The announcement of his decision
to make this a long run?
Come in.
Ready?
Congratulations!
Eh?
Hello...
Yuri...
Why are you here?
Kalos, why don't you explain it to them?
I have no choice, then.
I will explain the situation to them.
Well, it's simple.
Kalos will no longer be the owner
of Kaleido Stage after today.
Instead, I will be the owner.
The current Kaleido Stage will
be dissolved after today's show.
What!
Kaleido Stage will be dissolved?
It can't be...
It's true.
But, we still have two weeks to perform.
The audience is packed.
There is no reason to quit.
She's right.
If the show keeps on like this,
even a long run is a possibility.
Kalos, don't tell me you were also dreaming
a foolish dream like them. Right?
A long run?
An amateur show like this?
It will never happen.
Hey, apologize to everyone!
Get your hands off me!
As for the rest of the
tickets for after today,
we will refund them.
Ouch!
Leave Anna alone!
Let her go!
Damn!
Let her go.
Anna...
Are you all right, Anna?
Both the Kenneth Corporation and the
Hamilton Foundation backed out as investors.
Your Kaleido Stage is over.
It will not exist.
Layla, by Mr. Hamilton's request,
I can't make a contract with you.
But, if you wish, I don't
mind persuading him.
Of course, I know all of your talents.
I definitely want you to
join my Kaleido Stage.
I'll welcome all of you.
No thank you.
Me neither.
I also decline.
Really? That's too bad.
Then, consequently, I must also ask
you to get out of the dormitory.
My speech is finished.
Yes, I sold all rights.
So you should quit, too.
Why?
There is a time for everything.
The current Kaleido Stage
is practically a corpse.
Just thinking that you're still
there makes my blood run cold.
Father, Kaleido Stage is not dead yet.
Layla, you did more than enough.
I will set up the management
office for you shortly.
There are many fields where you
can make the most of your talents,
either in the movies or on the stage.
You can do whatever you want.
First, appear on the screen again.
I heard your last movie got good reviews.
I think doing movies suits you.
I don't think you understand how
much Kaleido Stage means to me now.
If that's how you feel,
do you want to participate in
Yuri's Kaleido Stage for a while?
That would be meaningless.
Layla, then what do you want to do?
Well, I wonder what I want to do.
Maybe I don't want to lose...
I don't want to lose the partner
who motivates me so much...
Partner...
If you start doing something new, you
will forget about it soon enough.
I doubt it.
In any case, the current Kaleido Stage
will not exist after tonight's show.
That is something I cannot change.
I understand.
Layla... When you look back on this later,
you'll be glad that you
did what I told you to do.
Yes.
So, this evening is the last.
I can't believe it.
Anyway, let's put everything into it.
But I'm afraid I'll start
crying while I'm on stage.
You can't help it.
Because this will be the last.
Stop crying!
Everyone,
do you think it's okay to appear in
the last show feeling like you do now?
Even if you keep crying,
nothing will change the fact
that today is the last show.
Yes.
We shouldn't appear on the stage
like the way we feel right now.
You're right, Ken.
Since this is the last performance,
I want to show the audience the
best performance more than ever.
Right?
In order to let the audience keep the memory
of our Kaleido Stage in their hearts forever!
Yes.
That's right.
We have to do our best so we don't regret.
It's not the time to be depressed.
Thank you, Ken.
Somehow, you brought me to my senses.
That's more like you, Sora.
Boss must feel the same way.
I don't know what happened in the past,
but the Kaleido Stage that he
built up with care will be gone.
I'll go to see the Boss and
tell him how we all feel.
It's Sora.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Just a moment ago, we all talked backstage.
Everyone feels the same way.
Although today is our last show...
No... Because it's the last show,
let's make it the best show.
Boss, do you have anything you
want me to tell everybody?
There is one thing I want to say.
If you're going to prepare
yourself for the stage like that,
it's better not to do it.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Since it is the last,
we want to do our best and
make it the best show.
Are you saying that's wrong?
Wanting to do our best and finish
it on a good note, that's wrong?
It seems Kaleido Stage is going
to end because it should end.
I don't understand!
What are you trying to say, Boss?
I'm disappointed in you.
What else can we do?
I don't understand.
What does he want me to do?
Sora!
Ken!
What are you doing here?
I've been looking for you.
Sorry...
What?
I see...
So the Boss said that to you...
What'll I do? It's our last show.
And I have to appear on stage
halfhearted like I feel now.
No matter what Boss told you,
everyone united because they want to do
their best since this will be the last show.
I know.
Unless you pull yourself together,
everyone will fall apart.
Sorry, Ken.
Please let me go back to the
dormitory for just a little while.
Oh... Okay.
Please don't be late for
the raising of the curtain.
Yes.
Fool! Fool?
Fool?
Hey, listen, Fool.
Please don't hide. Please come out.
Don't tell me I can't see him anymore...
Fool! Where are you?!
Hey, Fool!
I have something I want you to listen to!
Please show up.
Please don't be mean.
I don't understand what the Boss is saying!
Fool! Please answer me!
I can't believe this.
I lost the ability to see Fool.
Listen, if you can see me,
it means that you were chosen for the stage.
Once, there was a man who was able to see me.
The man I was talking about gradually
lost the ability to see me.
I lost the ability to stay at Kaleido Stage.
And I was told something
like that by the Boss.
I'm not able to see Fool, either.
Everything is gone all at once.
I don't know what I should do at all.
So much has happened since the
first day I came to Kaleido Stage.
But even when someone got angry
with me or when I made a mistake,
I never felt like this.
I see...
I'm not able to see Fool
because I can never do the legendary
great maneuver the way I am now.
It's not like I lost the feeling that
I want to be as good as Miss Layla.
That hasn't changed even now, but...
Today is the last day I can appear
on the same stage with Miss Layla.
Mia, Anna and I have been encouraging
each other all this time.
I wanted to keep doing shows
together even after this,
but our Kaleido Stage will
be gone starting tomorrow.
Then,
I thought in the end I should
perform my best for "Freedom,"
which we all created together.
And yet the Boss told me it'd be
better if we just didn't do it.
What does he mean?
Still, I have to go.
No matter how I feel, the
curtain will still be raised.
Okay! I'm going!
But when I think that today
will be the last, I...
Oh...
Thank you.
Miss Layla...
It's likely we won't see each other again.
Don't act so tough.
I will talk to Mr. Hamilton.
No matter how hard you guys try,
your Kaleido Stage will be over after today.
I'm not thinking that today is the last day.
What?
Hey, look at the reality, Layla.
Yuri, did you see our show?
"Our"?
That's not the way you usually talk.
Sorry, but I don't think it's worth seeing.
"Freedom"...
It's a story about young people
who believe in the future.
In the story,
you can see those lively young people
doing their best for tomorrow
in spite of fighting each other.
The character I'm playing
is also that kind of person.
She really believes that she can have
the future that she is hoping for.
The others are the same too.
No matter what kind of tough
circumstances they face,
they are never overcome with
sorrow while they do nothing.
All the characters have
that kind of strength.
And I like the nature of that show.
Even if Kaleido Stage closes its doors,
it can't close the door to my future.
It will not be my last
show, unless I wish it.
That's what I believe.
At least, if I couldn't believe that,
I couldn't appear on this stage.
That is such a hackneyed,
idealistic point of view.
You think that way.
Because you don't believe in your future.
Miss Layla.
Sora!
Sorry, I heard your conversation.
So, today is not the end of the show, is it?
I don't want to make it the end
of the show as of today either.
Even after this,
I want to appear on the stage
many more times with you.
Sora, hurry.
The curtain will be raised as scheduled.
Yes.
We're not going to do our
best because it is the last.
We will do our best today, tomorrow,
and the day after tomorrow.
And we're going to put on
our best show all the time.
Yes!
It's not like the audience is
interested in seeing a sad show.
It's true.
This is what the Boss meant.
Right. Right.
It seems like you're finally
back to who you are.
Anyhow, as I thought, Miss Layla is amazing.
Yes, she is.
Maybe I don't want to lose...
I don't want to lose the partner
who motivates me so much...
If you start doing something new, you
will forget about it soon enough.
There is no way I can forget...
Just remembering Miss Layla's words,
"It will not be my last
show, unless I wish it,"
makes me so emotional I could cry.
Oh, I messed up my makeup.
Sorry, can you go before me?
Miss Layla!
Where is Sora?
She messed up her makeup right now, and...
She is fixing it.
Sora...
Oh, Miss Layla.
Oh... I'm doing my best to hurry, but...
Give it to me.
What?
I will do it for you.
Oh... Miss Layla...
Don't talk. I can't do my work.
Oh...
I enjoyed co-starring on stage with you.
Miss Layla...
Why would you say something like that?
This is not the end, right?
Right?
Now it looks good.
Let's go, Sora.
Yes.
Fool...
Can you see me again?
Yes, unfortunately.
The Sun.
This card represents a hope for tomorrow.
A hope for tomorrow.
That's nice.
That's right!
Starting tomorrow, our
performance will start!
"Next Kaleido Star"
Don't say something ridiculous!
Of course I'm worried.
And so, since we were kicked
out of the dormitory,
I'm going to stay at Ken's house for a while.
But, Sora's worried parents
came to see her, and...
What's more, inside of her mother's body...
There is a new life,
my father and mother's real child.
Where is the place I can
go back to? Where? Where?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing Family Ties."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
I'm here between the sky and the
roads, and facing against the wind
And I'm facing forward so the sorrow
doesn't rain down ever again
I came all the way here after
I jumped over that wall
There are many times when
I just want to run away
But I'm still here, so,
I'm not daunted that much
The poem I scribbled down, I can just
start writing over from the beginning
Unable to write it well, I'm laughing