Another wish is being swept across the sky.
...What was that?
A wishing star I'm not aware of?
Releasing all girls who were turned into LRIGs from their cards...
There's no way Tama can grant a wish that's beyond even my powers.
And yet, Ruu is...
Kominato Ruuko is...
Uhm...
MAYU
Are you Futase Fumio-sensei?
ubaware kanatte risou wa kurikaesu geemu surinuketeku
The acts of theft and granting are entwined within the endless games
nichijou wa utarete ana darake tatteiru no ga yatto kana
You finally take a stand after your quiet life was beaten to a pulp
ketsuron no nai kuuron mienai ruuru no ue de odotteru suteppu de
Dance upon the unseen rules with endless speculation
kuzurete iku kyou tsunagitomeru saishuu beru ga naridasu
The final bell rings out to bind together this crumbling world
ukabu omoi no joukei ni wa kimi ga irun da yo
Within my memories you're always there
waretterun dayo
Simply laughing
yurushitakunai no? motometenai no?
You say you can't forgive? That you have no desires?
soredemo mada
So why can't you stop?
We cry OPEN torimodoshitai mirai kowashitai sekai
We cry "Open!" to take back tomorrow and destroy the world
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
akehanashitai negai GOT IT? ima
Do you finally know your deepest wish?
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
kurosu suru I wish you don't cry
We cross and I wish you don't cry
hikari to yami no saki kasanatte mata iro ga tsuku you
Another color lies at the point where light and darkness cross
"sono saki" wo shinjitemiyou ka
And I choose to believe in it
And... you're really...
I am.
I'm Futase Fumio.
I kinda expected an adult...
You're a high school student?
A Fuji High uniform...
I'd never be able to get in there.
So, who will be battling us first?
So you are...
...a Selector?!
Come now, let us make for the stage of our battle.
A high school girl writer and a Selector?!
Now that's an explosive twist!
You're turning me into Burning Chorizo!
W-We didn't come here to battle.
Oh?
I can't fathom any other reason why Selectors would seek out their kind if not for battling.
It's because we're Selectors that we mustn't battle.
Now that is truly incomprehensible.
Don't you girls have wishes you want to come true?
Wishes don't really come true...
They come true, and yet they don't.
Futase-san, I think you'll understand once you learn the truth!
"The truth," you say...
You're a LRIG, so you should know it!
Why yes, I do know it.
But as luck would have it...
...I know as well.
That "truth" you're talking about...
It's what's waiting for you at the end of your Selector battles.
"The ruler of White Garden,
the almighty being who
supervises all WIXOSS battles.
What passes her lips are the Laws of the Selector."
Say,
how much do you think the author knows?
You're a real moper, aren't you...
Ruu...
Wh-What did you just say?!
Fumio said she knows.
She knows what it is that's waiting for her at the end of the battles.
A Selector who loses three times will see her wish reversed and suffer a cruel fate.
Even if she continues to win battles, becoming an Eternal Girl in the process,
the one who will make her wish come true is her LRIG, now released from the card.
I'm also aware that the Selector herself is then turned into a LRIG.
Why are you still battling, then?!
Nothing good can come from it!
I see.
You're Selectors, but you reject Selector battles?
Quite an interesting development.
All Selectors who sought me out after reading my novels
were more than willing to accept the challenge to battle me.
That's only because of how you wrote about them in your novels!
Futase-san, please tell me.
Don't you know more than what's written in the novels?
Learning that must be your wish.
Then let's act like the Selectors we are.
I'll tell you everything I know
if you can defeat me in battle.
In battle...
You cannot ask for something without offering anything in return.
As an aside, Fumio hasn't lost once yet.
What about you?
Same...
The stakes are boringly low, but that also means you have no reason to hesitate.
Hey, hey!
If Ruuko-san doesn't wanna do it, I do!
H-Hey, wait a sec!
Oh geez, this girl...
Doesn't she understand she's lost twice already?
Not a bit she doesn't.
I couldn't care less who will face me.
Me, me!
It looks like you've reached a decision.
My opponent will be that small lady there.
Yahoo!
I'll do it.
Ruuko?!
Ah, uhm...
Chiyori-san, we can't let you battle with your two losses.
She nabbed my chance!
Read between the lines!
Please, Iona-san.
That LRIG...
Never mind.
Let's begin.
Open!
Let's do this in grace.
Why did it have to come to this?!
Ruuko...
I'm... right back to battling again.
Even though Tama told me not to!
Let us stage an enjoyable performance!
I go first.
Grow!
I summon Triumph and Clay!
Grow.
I banish Triumph with Fallen.
Iona-san!
Don't worry about me.
It's your turn.
O-Okay...
I banish Puri wish Slash Miracle!
Very well. I call Surrelis to my hand with Puri's ability.
I-I'm sorry...
She just can't perform without Tama by her side.
Ruuko...
Could that black LRIG be...
So you sense something different from her, too?
She's not like us.
She has something special...
But her affinity with her
Selector seems to be horrible.
Her true power isn't being utilized.
Let's make them get serious, then.
She's... strong.
Her moves are precise and effective,
and she's always one step ahead of me...
How much longer do you plan on worrying and hesitating?
I'm not hesitating!
You used to lose yourself to greed in battle,
and had a strength that overcame predictions and experience.
I-I...
As you are now, I don't see how you could help anyone.
Neither Yuzuki nor any other girl who's turned into a LRIG.
I'll save them!
I know...
I know the horrible things Hitoe went through after her wish was reversed.
Yuzuki gave her everything to have her wish
come true, only to be turned into a LRIG in return...
It's all so horrible!
I don't want anyone else to experience that!
Grow!
You're nothing but talk.
To I think I lost to someone like you, with all the nonsense you're spewing.
I lost to a fool trying her best to help others...
I lost to such foolish purity...
Iona-san...
If you really want to save everyone, don't let minor issues sway you, and show your true self!
You're nothing like you were back when Tama was your partner!
That's right, you'll never be able to save Tama like this!
Tama...
You're right.
I need to battle.
Tama, everyone...
I'll save you all!
I hate to rain on your parade,
but the real world is not so kind as to allow for unexpected comebacks like in a story.
I won't lose.
I... won't lose!
Iona-san. Grow!
What?!
No way!
She's already on level 4!
There's no level higher than that!
What's... that?
What's with that form?
This is Ruuko's power?
The power Tama felt from her?
It... It can't be!
There's nothing in the script about a level beyond 4...
A level 5 can't...
We got a level 5!
Could this be the forbidden power that awakens in a time of crisis?!
What an exciting turn of events!
Ruuko looks like she's having fun!
Yup!
But she's the good Ruuko now, isn't she?
I think so, too.
An encore... would be welcome...
This is the curtain fall.
Forgive me, Fumio...
Don't apologize.
Iona-san, thank you.
When I heard your words, I...
Why...
did I say that?
Level 5 was quite a surprise.
And your LRIG...
Huh?
How much does Iona-kun know about that girl called Mayu?
Mayu!
Just so you know, I didn't say anything about her.
Fumio knew all about her from back before we even met.
How?
Before I became Futase Fumio,
I was a LRIG.
A-A LRIG...?
Then you've become a Selector again after you returned to being a human?
But why?
It's all for a wish.
It's all to fulfill...
her wish.
Futase Fumio is not my real name.
"Fumio" was the name of a girl who had been a Selector.
You... can move?
Can't you see that?
And it looks like you can speak, too.
You do hear me, don't you?
Oh?
Come on...
Are you sane?
You're not surprised enough after hearing a card speak.
I've read a couple of stories that sorta went like that.
I guess introductions are in order.
My name is Fumio. What's yours?
I... forgot.
Just call me whatever.
Then...
from today, your name is Futase.
Yes. Futase is the name she gave me as a LRIG.
Side Story
Volume Two
Fundamentals of Writing Novels
Become a
novelist
in
a flash
Clicking and clacking, day in, day out...
That's supposed to be fun?
I wouldn't call it fun right now.
I'm irritated because I'm having a bout of writer's block.
Then just quit.
From time to time, it's really fun, though.
Like the moments when I can feel a sense of accomplishment.
Don't you have anything like that, Futase?
I...
don't care about stuff like
dreams or wishes anymore.
That sounds like you had some before.
Never mind. I won't pry.
You can tell me about them when you feel like it someday.
If you have a wish, you should just look for Selectors and battle them.
I suppose...
No matter my suggestions, she never entered a single battle...
Huh?!
What do you mean, you don't wanna do it?
There's no meaning to my dream if I don't reach it by the work of my own two hands.
Go and find someone else.
You don't have to tell me that!
She was lying at that time.
LRIGs only appear before girls with wishes they truly want to see come true.
I'm going.
Whoa?!
You're joking, right?
I'm super serious!
Ah—crap, we're supposed to be in another classroom!
Shoot! We've gotta hurry!
Is that the new card? Neat!
Isn't it?
Hey, do you want to battle me?
Sure, okay!
Hey, me too!
Didn't you buy the cards to play with other people?
I don't really fit in with school life.
Isn't it pretty hellish to not speak with anyone the whole day?
I'm used to it already.
Is your life any fun at all?
A little, ever since I met you.
R-Really?
Well now, I guess you can smile.
People smile when they're happy.
I had become a LRIG and lost everything, but...
as time passed with her...
Author
sssssssssssFutase Fumio
I began to wish in earnest for her dream to come true.
However...
You've got some nerve, staying out all night again!
I-I was working.
Liar... I bet you were with another woman!
Says the one sleeping around with other men!
The reality she was wrapped up in
slowly swallowed her up.
Date received
Pen Name
Result
Futase Fumio
Failed
And when even the last ray of hope she had gave way to rain clouds...
What is it?
I don't care about Selectors who don't want to battle.
What if I said I did want to battle?
Fumio?!
Oho...
Now you're talking.
Hey, Fumio!
You wanted to make your wish come true by your own hands, right?!
That's right.
That's right, but...
I'm at my wit's end.
There's no point to my life if I can't reach my dream.
A life with no purpose is just too miserable...
So please lend my your help, Futase...
I understand.
I'll make your wish come true, Fumio.
Thank you, Futase.
Doing that is why I'm your LRIG.
Let's begin.
Open!
She showed exceptional promise as a Selector.
For the sake of her wish, she never lost a single battle
and surely collected her wins.
And then...
I accept
the Laws of the Selector.
And now,
a new Eternal Girl will be born.
My wish is going to come true with this...
I'll make it come true.
Futase?
I'll make sure your wish will come true.
Leave it to me.
What... kind of joke is that?
The girl who dreamed of becoming a novelist
became an Eternal Girl.
The LRIG entrusted with the girl's wish
traversed the river of stars
and soon found the room where the Girl of Fate slept.
The Girl of White had a truly beautiful, good heart.
In contrast, the Girl of Black had a very unsightly, evil heart.
The Girl of Black envied and despised the
Girl of White, always cheerful and smiling,
and yearned to erase her very existence.
The Girl... of Black?
I sense something from her that
makes her unlike all other LRIGs.
Iona-kun, aren't you
the Girl of Black?
The Girl of Black?
No...
You mustn't, Iona.
The Girl of Black can't become the Girl of White.
Once you start to long for that,
you will turn
This
Irritation
is
Disillusionment
into a dirty grey.
Life
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
I walk through
this endless street maze
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
to the sound of bells
I will
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
shed the life
that I was given
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
for a brighter tomorrow
I now feel catharsis in a world
hikari to yami kowasaseru sekai de
that will allow neither dark nor light
mezamehajimeru catharsis
With fear in my heart I swore
furueteiru mune de chikatta
that I would never again
mou dare hitori
lose anybody
nakushitakunai
The morrow may be drenched in tears,
ashita namida afuretemo
but I will face the wind
kaze no naka wo
with pride
kakenukeyukou
I will do what must be done for my future
hanate eranda mirai he
I will remember my wish,
torimodosu yo
and I will never give up
kono negai wa akiramenai
Girl of Black...
Girl of Darkness...
In truth, you are...
That
Existence
is
Pitch-Black
That existence is pitch-black.