Yes, this is Hirono.
Hello?
Miyako?
Bingo.
I haven't disappeared.
Huh?
I haven't disappeared yet.
Miyako...
Chihiro, this is who you are.
Just take it slowly.
If you read it, you'll be yourself again.
Is it okay leaving her by herself?
She'll have to deal with the rest of it on her own.
That's...
I've warned you not to get too involved with Chihiro.
I've warned you to be prepared if you wanted to be with her too.
Chihiro lost four years worth of her memories.
Even though the only things that remain are a few scattered, unrecognizable memories...
If she takes some time and reads her diary again,
she should return to the most recent her.
That's...
It's just something that has happened many times.
It will happen again in the future.
And then, as time passes, the pain of her losing memories will only become worse.
Then all the more, this is the time someone should be with her.
You don't understand.
It's not about Chihiro.
The pain that will become worse will be your pain, Renji.
That's why I've warned you not to get too involved with her.
Is it hard for you?
That is...
You can still back away now, you know.
Chihiro right now doesn't know you.
If you want to disappear, then now is the time.
Something's not right.
Yes, Tsutsumi speaking.
Senpai? It's me, Shindou.
Kei-chan.
Can you meet with me for a bit?
This is... me?
Yes, that's correct.
Nothing... will change even if I read these!
I will only return to those same days again.
Repeating that same, empty daily life.
Chihiro...
Do I have to continue writing in this diary as I always have?
Writing the same things in my diary... Why do I have to keep on writing them?!
It would be better if it ended.
Being who I am, it would be better if it ended!
I just can't be calm without touching the ball.
Can't you just bring Hirono to accompany you?
Don't ask for something impossible; he is swamped with work.
Hey, Kei-chan.
What is it?
Is it going well with you and Hirono?
G-Going well?
My relationship with Hirono-senpai is more like that of siblings.
It's not what you think...
I was actually asking about it from the "siblings" relationship perspective.
When she was alive, my mother used to be an actress.
She had that bright sparkle about her...
And I wanted to make a movie with that kind of expression.
Bright sparkle?
I think Kei-chan has that bright sparkle too.
I do?
But... it's not the same sparkle I saw in you the first time we met.
I was just wondering if something had happened between you and Hirono.
I just feel like he's so distant from me.
When I realized it, he is in some place I can't reach anymore.
Everyone...
Everyone?
Not only Hirono-senpai.
You are working really hard for your dream, Tsutsumi-senpai.
And even my younger sister has started writing a novel.
And with her condition, that is almost impossible.
But yet this injury has ground me to a halt.
I can't sparkle, being like this.
But those aren't the only things that make you worry, right?
You seem to know everything.
I've told you, right?
When I look through the camera's viewfinder, I can see everything.
Yahoo!
It's been a while, Hirono-kun.
What happened to your cell phone?
I've changed it with this.
See? A telephone card.
I got it for free.
And I won't be getting strange mails or calls.
It's a good deal.
Then I won't be able to call you.
Oh, I guess that's the drawback, huh?
Sorry about standing you up last Sunday.
It's okay.
Huh? You're not angry?
It's fine now since you came to see me.
That's not like you.
Ah, you should send your future career survey in quickly.
If you don't, they'll call your parents.
What did you write on yours, Hirono-kun?
Maybe I should write "going to the university" first.
How about being a manga author?
No way I'm going to let my parents know that.
If they found out about my current work, they'd make me stop.
Your dad doesn't approve of what you want to do?
Well, I was the one who left home.
I'm envious of your freedom.
I don't want to be told that by you.
Why?
Well, you seem to show that feeling of being carefree everywhere you go, don't you?
That's not true.
My freedom is nothing but an empty shell.
For Hirono-kun, your freedom is the freedom to do something you really want.
To go through a lot of hardships and harsh times while pursuing your dream...
is a very fulfilling kind of freedom.
Yours isn't an empty one either.
Since you have to think about a lot of things, it doesn't allow you to do anything else.
Thinking about it so much just makes your head hurt.
You can just throw them all away and run if it's too hard.
You are free to choose whatever.
That's why it's also okay to just throw them away.
That's right! You want to run away together with me?
To somewhere far away where nobody knows.
Idiot.
I guess so.
I have chosen, so I have certain responsibilities.
You can't just run away when you have already chosen.
What about me?
You've gotten me involved too, so don't run away from me, okay?
I guess it's something that I'd want to say "never happened".
That's so mean!
Thanks.
Eh?
Thanks to you, now I think that I can take a break.
Hirono-kun...
Well, those were just my thoughts.
I feel at ease when I'm with you too, Hirono-kun.
But that's only during the limited time I'm together with you.
Miyako...
Hey, Hirono-kun...
Hmm?
Hey, say something.
L-Like what?
You write shoujo manga right?
Don't you have any romantic lines for such moments?
I won't be able to let you go anymore...
That was lame.
I-I love you.
Very plain.
Je t'aime.
What's that supposed to mean?
If I kill you, I will die as well!
Isn't that for another situation?
Hirono-kun, are you really a pro-
I'm bad at expressing my ad-lib...
If it's not on paper, I can't bring out those words.
Then bring me to somewhere that has your paper...
Have you ever heard of this story?
A long time ago, it was an experiment.
An experiment?
An experiment to see what a baby would first say if it was brought up without talking to anyone.
The baby wouldn't say anything, of course.
That's half correct.
Half correct?
The baby indeed wouldn't say anything, but the baby would die too.
That's a sad story.
But in my case, I didn't die and I can talk too.
Miyako, you...
Hirono-kun...
Whatever happens, will you only look at me?
Yes, I will only look at you.
I don't want to disappear from someone's heart anymore.
Is this about Chihiro?
Yes.
Alright, I'm listening.
Chihiro has talked about nothing but putting things to an end.
I'm scared for her.
Don't worry, it's just normal for you to feel like that.
Even the painful feelings?
Do you know when one feels loneliness?
When you are alone.
That's basically just a result of it.
It's something more to the source.
Because... it's enjoyable?
Right.
Learning how to enjoy life after feeling loneliness for the first time...
It's just like learning about sadness after feeling happiness for the first time.
That's...
This world is filled with things that have two sides to it.
Almost like a laughable tragedy of sorts.
That's...
Like water, you two have stepped into this realm of loneliness.
That is...
What else can I do?!
Are you satisfied after saying that?
Do you feel better now after saying that to someone?
Why... didn't you tell me about Chihiro's condition sooner?
I did give you a warning.
You should've been able to stop us from seeing each other too.
You may be right. Perhaps I just wanted to see the result.
I wanted to see if someone like me could accomplish what I had hoped to do.
Perhaps I know the answer as to what you and Chihiro should do now.
Do you want to know?
I'll give you a hint.
Go and read Chihiro's novel carefully.
And then think about why she wrote a novel like that.
"The girl started to practice painting the next day after the wedding ceremony."
"Despite the wedding ceremony, there was only one human on this side of the paintings."
"So, she started painting herself on the paintings."
"She painted everything in the pictures."
"In that painted world, there were two humans smiling at each other."
"She felt strange when she looked at herself in the pictures."
"She didn't really understand that feeling."
"However, she continued with her curiosity."
"The girl is only one in the world."
"That made her the god of this world."
Want to take a break?
I made some cookies.
I hope you like them.
Thank you for your hospitality, Renji-san.
Renji-kun.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I just thought that you were someone older than me.
I see.
Then just use whichever is easier for you.
No, please let me call you as before.
I will return...
I will definitely return to the previous me...
I wrote a novel, right?
That surprised me.
It's nearly to the end of the story, right?
I have to continue writing it.
You don't have to force yourself.
Just resume writing only when you feel like it.
Will you help me again when the time comes, Renji-kun?
Yes, of course.
Now I have read it three times.
I... can really come back to the me that you know, Renji-kun.
Yes, you will be able to capture the spirit of Chihiro once again.
I'm glad.
Now I'm just like the previous me, who loved Renji-kun a lot.
I-I see...
Eh, you didn't know?
Well, I've never had someone say, "I love you" to me before.
But in the diary, it said that I confessed...
Well, that is actually something from me...
And it's more like an accident.
It's really an "unofficial" confession...
The word "love" was written many times in the diary, so I just assumed that...
I-I see...
Did I just move ahead too fast...?
No, I don't think so...
Maybe...
Please forget what I just said.
I've already heard it...
You're mean.
These past four years...
For four years, I have been in a standstill.
I thought it would've better if I had just gone to a dead end.
I can't do anything and I have nothing to do.
I was just standing there waiting for the time to pass.
I was hoping that it would stop.
It felt so painful reading about me being like that.
But after meeting Renji-kun, everything became brighter.
Every day became happy moments and just by reading them, I felt really warm inside.
Chihiro...
Even from this page to this one, each small bit is a part of me.
Thank you, Renji-kun.
I wonder what a memory is?
What do you mean?
If memories change, does the personality change too?
Or does it stay as it is, but only what you remember changes?
The exact personality might change, but...
I think the personality of the real person will stay the same.
I'll be glad if that is so.
What do you mean?
When I lost my memories four years ago,
I was wondering if the real me died that day too.
The same way I thought that the "me" while being with Renji-kun was already gone too.
I started to think like that.
You're wrong.
Renji-kun...
It's not like that.
Whatever happens, Chihiro is Chihiro.
You neither died, nor did you turn into a different person.
Renji-kun..
Chihiro will always be the Chihiro I know.
Don't be so foolish, Chihiro.
There's no way such a thing is true.
You're right.
It's strange, isn't it?
Yeah, it is strange.
There's no way that is true.
It's impossible.
No way...
There's no way that can be true.
Why...
Why are you still here?!
Damn, damn, damn!
Chihiro has already forgotten...
Chihiro can't remember anymore...
Why are you still here?!
You're saying that Chihiro's existence is weaker than sand?
That Chihiro's memories are duller than sand?!
There's no way that it's true...
There's no way!
Chihiro is Chihiro.
She met me...
Laughed with me...
She even got angry and cried with me!
She is the Chihiro I knew!
She didn't disappear.
She is not a different person!
That is...
That is something...
I will never accept!
Hey, come here.
Hurry and come here.
This loneliness is here...
"The girl is only one in the world."
"That made her the god of this world."
I'm going to go wake up Onii-chan.
How about some sandwiches?
Perfect!
Or so I think...
So unreliable.
What's the matter, Kei-chan?!
Kei-chan, your legs!
It'll be bad if you run!
Kei-chan!
Are you all right, Kei-chan?
Kei-cha-
Kei-chan...
Look for me and bring me back with you.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
I'm here.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?