Everyone has something that they haven't seen before in this world.
They are all lies.
This thing...
What the heck, there's mold?
I just disinfected a few days ago...
It's something very kind and sweet.
If they saw it, everyone would probably want it.
That is why the world hid the thing.
So people cannot easily obtain it.
Damn it. It won't come off.
However...
One day, someone will find it.
Only that one person will obtain it.
It is something like this.
Waste not, want not... be ecological.
Inko-chan, still sleeping?
It's morning~
Caught you.
Ryuu-chan, how cold.
I told you last night I'm going to school today.
Ohh, the entrance ceremony?
Congratulations on entering.
Is this the right attitude to welcome a new school year?
Hey, this room is so dark. Draw the curtains.
It's already open.
Ah.
It's such a huge apartment.
I wonder what kind of people live in there...
Since this was built, we cannot even receive the sun's grace.
Washed things don't dry,
we get mold, mold, mold growing everyday.
Ryuu-chan's sharp eyes looks just the same as your dad's!
The same... the same...
Don't group me together with that-
Aah! So cool, you're becoming so much more like your dad!
Eh, Ryuu-chan, are you going already?
What about my breakfast?
It's in the usual place.
That...
Only that...
I absolutely do not want anyone to mention it.
Because of these eyes you adore so much...
I... I-
Oi, wait up!
Ta-ta-ta-ta Takasu-kun!
What have you done!
Eh? What is it?
I was just enjoying the day!
Take it! Forgive us!
We only have this right now!
Really! We'll make it up to you next time!
You don't have to...
SORRY!!!
Scary! These are the eyes of a killer...
I...
Again?
You sure pick up a lot of lost wallets...
Yeah...
It would be good if we were still in the same class.
There!
Great, we are in the same class!
Scary! Those are the eyes of a killer...
Crap, not again.
Yo!
We're back in the same class this year, Takasu.
Kitamura!
With that, we conclude our opening ceremony for this year.
Please return to your classes for homeroom.
A new class...
Do I have to start by clearing up the misunderstanding first?
No problem.
I understand you, so it won't be everyone.
Ah, thank you.
That's right, there are people who understand me.
Moreover, in this class.
Yo, Kitamura-kun!
We're in the same class again, eh?
Oh, Kushieda, you are in class C as well?
It's Takasu-kun, right?
Do you still remember me?
We've met a few times.
Kushieda Minori-dono, right?
Man... remembering my full name.
I'm so glad!
Then let's enjoy our lively and heartfelt youth together!
And then...
What's wrong, Takasu?
Ah, no... I need to use the toilet.
Is that so? Then I'll go to class first.
Is it a showdown between the delinquents?
The strongest cards have been drawn so suddenly!
Is a new delinquent leader about to be born?
What?
So small...
Like a doll...
But, somehow...
Feels like a troublesome person.
It feels like I'll be eaten if I'm not careful.
Erm, this is...
Ah, it's true! The delinquent and the Palmtop Tiger
Idiot!
Palmtop Tiger?
I see...
Palmtop...
What the...
Isn't it very accurate?
OK, We'll stop here today.
Students who have not yet handed in their future careers form,
please come to the staff room later.
D-did you hear me, Takasu-kun?
Y-yes.
Are you OK, Taiga?
You came pretty late today too...
I have a runny nose, and keep sneezing...
Oh, that bug going around,
That's terrible.
That Palmtop Tiger...
is she friends with Kushieda?
It's me who has to worry...
Are you alright?
Guess so.
However...
That was awesome! Aisaka and Takasu...
The Palmtop Tiger is still stronger, eh?
Takasu only looks scary, but isn't a delinquent.
Really?
It seems that the misunderstanding will be cleared very soon.
Taiga?
What's wrong?
N... nothing.
Ta-takasu-kun... you don't know what to do in your future?
Eh?
B...b...but... everyone else has already handed in their forms.
Ah, sorry, I forgot.
Sorry, sorry!
You are uncertain about the future, so you don't want anyone to say too much about it. Right, right?
I didn't know...
Ugh, already this late...
It's nearly the cutoff for leaving school...
A... are you OK?
Uhh... Bag.. bag...
At any rate, I'd better ignore her.
Oi, you... what are you doing?!
W...What?
What are you doing?
I'm only here for my bag...
Is it your bag?
Do you sit beside him?
Could it be that the let... let... let...
Let go!
Why are you trying to take my bag?
Oi, stop it already!
Hey...
Aisaka...
Oi!
Idiot!
What a mess...
As for dad, he's in heaven!
He was a really cool person!
He always hid magazines under his suit to prevent himself from being stabbed!
How charming!
Just looking like you...
Gives me a lot of trouble!
If it wasn't for this face...
...no one would be scared.
And I wouldn't have been bitten by the Palmtop Tiger.
I should have more confidence.
That way...
Ah, the future careers form.
Huh?
What the?
For Mr. Kitamura Yuusaku.
From Aisaka...
...Taiga.
I see...
It was put in the wrong bag right?
I've never seem it before, so I have no idea what it will be like.
At any rate, I'll return it to you~
Oh, crap.
Stick back!
That person...
...could she have?
Very careless.
Let's sleep.
Hmm?
Yasuko?
No, she shouldn't be back yet...
Alright! Let's drink!
OK, Mirano-chan!
Oi...
Huh?
The window...
Ouch!!!
What's with her?
Huh?
Where have I seen this size...
Aisaka?!?!
Use a tissue!
What do you want?
What do you want?!
Forget it.
Forget what...?
Ah, that lett-
er.
Now that someone knows, I can no longer live.
There's nothing to do but die!
If so, why are you trying to kill me?!
I don't want to die, so I have to kill you!
Or at least, destroy all your memories!
Impossible!
Don't worry.
Just hitting your head with this thing won't kill you.
But taking your memory away is no problem.
Stop jumping all over the place!
Listen well!
That letter...
Shut up.
Shut up! Shut up!
You saw it, right? You read it, right?
Thats why...
I won't listen.
That's why you must...
...forget about that... that...
LOVE LETTER!
It was empty!
Em...pty?
That's right. So the content...
Or should I say it was lucky Kitamura didn't receive it.
This saved you from embarrassment.
O... oi!
How long have you been starving for?
I'm sick of food from the convenience store.
Convenience store?
What, shouldn't someone at home make...
Everyone has different circumstances.
Here.
If you had handed over that bag obediently at that time...
It wouldn't have turned out like this.
Why did you have to fight me for it?
There's still rice left on your cheek.
I'm not one that is able to eat rice with garlic in it.
Hey now...
What's so embarrassing about a love letter?
Listen up, Love letters are not embarrassing!
Wait here.
Look!
What's this?
Do you know what this is?
You shouldn't right?
This is a list for my plan of a concert I intend to hold for the girl I like.
This is a MD I made to use when I go on a drive with her.
Of course, I didn't get her permission.
I have prepared for all 4 seasons.
How's this, disgusting?
I don't have the courage to confess, so I can only have my delusions.
It's a bit loser-like,
but I don't think this is shameful.
It's good that you have the self confidence.
Since you took action instead of remaining at the delusion level.
Look forwards!
Eloquent, cheerful...
"For Kushieda Minori"
Yes! Just like Kushieda Minori...
You like Minori?
Geh, how egotistic.
You don't know your limits.
Shut up! You don't have the right to tell me so!
What? I said to forget it already...
Shut up! Goosebumps!
Sorry, Inko-chan, for waking you up.
What disgusting thing are you showing me?
Calling my precious family that...
Oh, nice, Inko-chan!
A self introduction to our guest!
You can say your name today!
I-- i-- i--n... bo.
No, Inko isn't in her best shape today.
Eh, already this late?
At any rate, we're in the same boat now.
Don't tell anyone this,
promise me!
No.
Why?
I've treated you already, go home!
I mean... please return!
My sick mother is almost back!
I... Don't... want... to!
I cannot trust you.
Also...
What happened to the love letter?
It isn't fashionable anymore, right?
Being embarrassed at a time like this?
I'll think of something for you about your love.
But it's late already, so tomorrow... OK?
Really?
Will you really help me?
Yes, yes yes yes!
I'll do anything.
Anything, right?
Letting me command you like a dog,
obeying my every wish, right?
Yes, I swear.
So, let's leave it at that.
OK, OK?
How did she get in through the window?
See you.
I'll escort you home.
No need.
My home is close, and I have a wooden sword.
No, that's the danger.
Hey, about that hole...
Aah, all that needs to be done is to paste it over.
This.
If you like, use this.
If you want money, I'll pay you later.
See you, Ryuuji.
Was my name just called?
Hello, this is Takas...
Hurry up and come he-!
Hello.
You heard it, right?
Where do you mean by, "hurry up and come here"?
To the veranda...
What?
Why is this...?
You said you'll do anything like a dog right?
W.. wait...
What I said yesterday was to help you with Kitamura...
Do you know what will happen if I get angry?
I'll use this to make you understand.
No, uh...
That is...
Give me 30 minutes!
There's only 30 minutes before the rice is done!
Three?
Do you want to eat too?
Amazing...
Sorry for intruding...
It's open?
What's with this smell?
Aisaka-san...
I'm entering.
What a smell.
AISAKA!!!!!
Aisaka! Aisaka!
AISAKA!
Let me... let me...
Clean this place up properly!
What the...
Back to sleep?
She looks hand-crafted.
The sleeping Aisaka really looked like a doll.
In this home with no sense of living.
Just like a set for playing house.
But...
For a doll,
this home is a bit too big.
It's been around 15 minutes, huh?
Okay.
What's... this?
Yo.
I'm still cleaning,
but it's almost done.
It was awesome,
the sink was full of junk, what a stench.
The pipe was all sticky and full of hair, creating a scene of hell.
The room was also full of dust...
Trespassing.
Also forced cleaning.
What are you doing, you dog?
Dog?
That's insulting to a dog...
You're both dogs, but you are a stupid dog.
Stupid... dog!
What an ungrateful girl!
It was such a rare occasion...
Oi,
you have to say "Itadakimasu".
To the gods of rice, and everyone on the production line,
Itadakimasu!
Hey... you...
Oh, your runny nose is gone.
Oh come on, it's not because this place got cleaned.
Did you just say something?
Shut up.
Useless excuses.
Misunderstandings that keep happening.
The power of genes.
Taiga, your clumsiness sure amazes me.
Shut up, go die!