Be sure to watch TV in a well-lit room and a safe distance away.
FULL MOON WO
SAGASHITE
Searching for the Full Moon
The road to love is far too long for me.
There's no way for me to love you any more. Nope, Nope!
It's as if the world inside my dream is a completely different one
where I can even tell you how I really feel.
I wear my favorite clothes every day
so that person will turn his gaze towards me.
"I like you" If I could bring myself to say it out loud
I would even be able to talk about love with you.
I want to be tucked into your heart
and I will do anything to be there.
"I love you" Those are the words I want to hear from you
and my breath will quicken when we kiss.
The me who is performing for you is the cutest of them all!
Hey, someday... somehow, someday...
No matter what, no matter where,
I'm going to do whatever it takes.
There's nothing left at my disposal.
And now, everything's getting out of hand!
Everyone!
Thank you for coming today!
Well, here's the last song.
I-It can't be.
E-Eichi?
Your dream of becoming a singer finally came true, huh?
Y-Yeah.
Yours, too?
Yeah.
That's great!
Mitsuki...
I... love you.
Eichi...
Eichi!
A dream?
Eichi?
NO MATTER WHAT, I WANT TO SING!
Hey, won't you look up?
The sky tonight is so wide and spacious after all...
Right... very soon...
I'll be fine, right?
Sure.
The sky tonight is so wide and spacious after all...
Right... very soon...
It hurts...
Mitsuki.
How many times have I told you to stop doing that?
Music is such a vile thing.
It reminds me of your father, it makes me feel bad.
I'm very sorry. But I...
Don't talk back!
Okay...
Has your fever gone down?
Yes.
Is that so? That's good.
Dr. Wakaouji is here to see you.
Come out to the kitchen.
Dr. Wakaouji!
Sorry for calling you in during your vacation.
Please don't worry about it.
So, how's her health?
She seems to be doing much better this morning.
Really?
Good morning, Mitsuki.
Good morning!
It seems like it's swelled up a little.
Is it okay if I apply treatment on it?
Yes, please.
All right, all done!
Thank you very much.
Um... Dr. Wakaouji.
What is it, Mitsuki?
Can we pretend that you're taking me to the hospital today?
You need an excuse to get out of the house, huh?
So, where do you plan on going?
Ta-da!
Seed Records' Debut Artist Audition!
Notification of Passing the First Review!
I'm keeping this a secret from Grandma, so...
No way.
You just had a fever yesterday and
had to leave school early, right?
Your throat is swollen and as your doctor, I can't allow you to do that.
But, I finally managed to get past the first review...
In your current condition, you can't sing in a loud voice, can you?
You can think about auditioning
after your throat gets better.
Mitsuki.
While it's still small, let's try an operation.
I don't want any surgery.
Because... I might lose my voice, right?
We'll cross that bridge when we get there.
I can't guarantee that it won't happen.
If that's the case, I don't want to be operated on.
Doctor...
What's even more terrifying than dying is not being able to sing for the rest of my life.
That's why...
I'm sorry.
Mitsuki...
Madam... it's about Mitsuki...
Could you possibly convince her, to go through with the operation?
I've already suggested it time and time again.
...she still refuses to listen.
For heaven's sake... She's just as stubborn as my late daughter was.
She is unable to give in!
I see...
Another failure...
I wonder if I'll have to wait
until my throat gets better...
Mitsuki, let's make a promise.
Until we meet again, we'll work hard to reach our dreams.
I'll become an astronomer.
And you'll become a singer.
Okay? It's a promise.
Yes.
But... just when will that happen...
Eichi?
All right.
W-Who are you?
How'd you come out of the wall?
This one, huh?
Mitsuki Kouyama, age 12.
Why does he know my name?
Wait a minute, Takuto.
A-Another one came out!
Were you trying to lose me?
Who are these people?!
It's because you're too slow.
Hey, there.
Is that the kind of attitude you show towards your senior?
You don't have to bring up your seniority every time, you know.
What?!
E-Excuse me.
Who might... you be?
You... Can see us?
Yes.
W-Why can she see us?!
Humans who are still living shouldn't be able to see us, right?!
You're kidding!
But... I can see you.
What do we do in this kind of situation?
If it's come to this, we have no choice.
Let's do it!
Yeah!
It's absurd to remain unknown when our cover is blown...
We are the Shinigami, the ones who silence the tears of children!
Takuto!
Meroko!
Together, we are...
Negi Ramen!
Y-You call yourselves Negi Ramen!
It sounds so tasty!
Takuto...
I really can't stand our duo's name.
My stomach hurts!
Just deal with it.
Our chief chose it after all.
Bunny ears and kitty ears... So soft!
It's because we're in the Pediatrics Division.
Pediatrics?
Shinigami have kids, too?
Kids?
Now that I think about it, if you're Shinigami...
Did you come to pick me up?
That's what were here for.
You're not supposed to say that!
It's too late for that.
So I'm going to die today.
Just pretend you didn't hear that.
You're not supposed to die for one more year.
One more year?
Is it because... my cancer gets worse?
Well, that could be why.
Sorry. Please, don't cry.
She's not crying.
Well, while we have the chance...
Let's see... In times like these...
Oh, here it is.
Actually, there are people who are trying to prevent your death.
Then... I'm not going to die?
No. It doesn't work that way.
Fate cannot be altered.
I see.
If I only have one year left to live,
I can't hesitate any longer.
Hey, Takuto...
I suggest you shut up! What are you trying to accomplish?!
I'm going to report this to the chief.
It doesn't matter, does it?
Besides, we've already been seen.
So what if after a year passes, she...
Where'd she go?
Takuto, over there!
Wait, you pipsqueak!
Stop right there!
Hey, you!
Wait up!
Taxi!
Oh, man!
Just when I had almost caught up to her.
Get out of the way!
I-Idiot!
Mr. Shinigami, thank you.
I'm going to take the audition now.
If I only have a year left,
I'll definitely become a singer before then.
Is this the place?
This is it, Eichi.
The promise we made...
I'll keep it for sure!
Where'd she run off to?
We thought she was a good girl, so we let her get away.
Oh, she's over there!
Really?
What is she doing?
Does it matter?
Hey, wait.
If you just go up to her like that, she'll run away again.
Yeah, I know.
Why won't it open?
Is there a key around here somewhere?
It's open!
All right!
I'll have to get up there then!
Yep!
They're so cute!
What are these?
I wonder if they're decorations.
They seem a little... out of place.
We caught you.
M-Mr. Shinigami!
It's troublesome for us when you go running off like this.
Now, be a good girl and come
back to the house with us.
You heard her.
P-Please wait a minute!
I want to go through the audition!
I don't want to just go home like this!
Then why were you trying to go in from there?
Yeah. Why not just use the front door?
I can't because I don't look like I'm sixteen.
Do I look like I'm sixteen?
Well... no, you don't.
That's it, I'm going in through here.
Quit it, you dummy! It's dangerous!
What if you get hurt?
But if I don't hurry, the audition will be over.
I... have to become a singe-
Did something happen?
Talking... loudly...
I can't...
My throat...
Then, isn't it impossible for you to audition?
But...
Please...
If I only have one year left to live...
please, at least let me audition.
If I fail...
I'll be a good girl and do what you say.
So...
Please!
You're serious about this, huh?
I get it.
I'll make you sixteen years old.
And then, as long as you're sixteen...
I'll make it so your body is healthy, too.
Take that.
On my command, that will begin spreading inside of your body.
You'll feel weird, but you'll just have to endure it.
That's a good girl.
You can't feel the difference?
Yeah...
Check yourself out over there, then?
Wow!
I'm really sixteen years old!
Thank you, Mr. Shinigami!
It was nothing...
No problem at all...
Thank you so much!
Hey! Get away from Takuto!
Are you satisfied?
Well... I want to try dying my hair, too.
What are you doing, Takuto?
What?
You're disobeying our orders from above by letting a human know the truth.
If they find out, you'll be in for it.
Yeah...
No way... You... and her...
Say what?
No!
You belong to me!
I'll never let her have you!
Since when was I your possession?
Don't worry. It's not like that...
If she still has any regrets left, and she passes away...
If she refuses to come with us, it'll be a problem.
I guess that's true, but...
What are you going to do if she makes it?
She'll have even more to regret.
It'll be fine.
There's no way she can make it just like that.
After turning sixteen and going through an audition...
only to fail and to have to face reality...
She won't have a shred of regret left...
Wow...
All the girls here are really cute.
I wonder if I look too plain.
Everyone's staring at me.
I wonder if I look too strange.
Maybe I'm out of fashion...
Can I sit next to you?
Sure.
What agency are you from?
Agency?
You're not part of a theatrical group or a recording agency?
Yeah.
Don't tell me I won't make it if I'm not part of an agency?
It's rather unfortunate, but it's probably impossible for you.
This is just between us.
They've already chosen someone.
What?!
Then, why are we auditioning?!
I-I'm very sorry. Sorry.
Well, that surprised me.
Why is that?
This audition gets lots of coverage on the morning news and on talk shows.
Media exposure will help anyone winning the audition become overnight sensations.
In other words, it's their one and only chance.
Is that so...
You... already knew that...
Yeah. Sorry.
The judging you've all been waiting for will now begin.
Bye, then.
Please come in when your number is called.
To start, will Number 1 please come in...
So that's how it is.
I feel kinda... let down...
I thought this was a world based more on talent than anything else.
Don't say that you want to be a singer ever again!
Grandma always discouraged me.
You should wait until your throat is better before you audition.
Dr. Wakaouji tried to stop me, too.
You have one more year before you die.
One more year.
Why am I... here?
Eichi...
Number 21.
Number 21, please come in.
I'm Number 21, Mitsuki Kouyama.
Pleased to meet you.
What genre of music do you like?
I like... Japanese pop.
If you became a singer, is there anything in particular you 'd like to try?
Well...
I'd just want to sing since I like singing.
Sing for us then.
Cue the music, please.
If she's that nervous, there's no way she'll make it.
There's only one thing that will never ever change...
Wait, stop for a second. Your voice is too soft.
The dream I am--
Sing louder.
Louder?
Is something wrong with your throat?
Does it hurt?
I guess it's impossible for you to sing, then.
Impossible...
It really was... impossible...
Please excuse me!
Are you just going to run away like that?
Mr. Shinigami!
Your throat is fine, so sing.
You love to sing, right?
You really love singing, Mitsuki.
Me, too.
I love to hear you sing.
That's right...
I'm very sorry.
Can you please let me try one more time?
Uh... sure.
Cue the music.
It's fine if it's painful...
No matter how much it hurts inside...
Whether it's pain...
...or love...
They're all part of my dream!
There's till one more thing that will never ever change...
...the dream that I am always sketching.
The me that I am right now, could I possibly reflect
all of those days in these small eyes of mine?
Hey, won't you look up? The sky tonight is so wide and spacious after all...
Right... very soon...
so I can understand...
Wow! I have such a loud voice!
With all I've got, I'm going to hurry up and shine...
It doesn't hurt at all!
I can sing in a voice like this!
I'm searching for the full moon.
This is fun!
Let's sing a song!
So that we can be together forever, I'm doing everything that I can do.
Day by day...
I will embrace yesterday's fate and tomorrow's hopes inside of me.
Let's sing a song!
As long as I'm with you, I'll overcome any pain.
More and more...
I want to be even closer to you, I stand here right now and give...
She's...
Many thanks for you!
I'm done...
Call Miya!
Get Ishikawa, too!
Okay...
Nishida! Send everyone else back!
We've decided on number 21!
Okay!
Hey, what should we do about this?!
I've been chosen?!
Although previously expected...
there will not be a third judging.
Takuto!
W-What should I do, Eichi?
I made it!
There's still one more thing that will never ever change
the dream that I am always sketching.
The me that I am right now, could I possibly reflect
all of those days in these small eyes of mine?
Hey, won't you look up? The sky tonight is so wide and spacious after all
Right... very soon... so I can understand...
With all I've got, I'm going to hurry up and shine
I'm searching for the full moon.
Let's sing a song!
So that we can be together forever, I'm doing everything that I can do.
Day by day...
I will embrace yesterday's fate and tomorrow's hopes inside of me.
Let's sing a song!
As long as I'm with you, I can overcome any pain.
More and more
I want to be even closer to you, I stand here right now and give
Many thanks for you!
PREVIEW FOR THE NEXT EPISODE
What have you done, Takuto?!
That girl made it, didn't she?!
Just be quiet! I don't know what happened.
It couldn't be that...
You've fallen in love with that girl?!
I-It's nothing like that at all!
But it's no good.
That girl has someone named Eichi, whom she likes a lot.
She's becoming a singer because of a promise with Eichi!
W-What's that?!
That's just wrong!
It was because of something like that?!
Next time on Searching for the Full Moon:
THE PROMISE WITH EICHI
The Promise with Eichi.
Look forward to it!