Attention!
I shall now explain the plan to retake Trost.
Let me start off by introducing you to him.
This is Cadet Eren Jaeger.
He's the result of a top-secret project
to turn humans into Eotenas.
He'll transform into an Eoten,
pick up the giant boulder by the shattered gate,
carry it over to the hole and seal it.
Your job will be
to protect him from Eotenas while he moves the boulder!
When this mission succeeds,
Mankind will have retaken its territory from them
for the very first time!
It may seem insignificant compared to all that we have lost,
but this one small step will be a titanic leap for Mankind!
Eren!
Can't you tell it's me?!
It's me, Mikasa!
Your family!
Evade, Ackerman!
What the hell?
He's just a normal, mindless Eoten.
Change of objective.
Protect Jaeger from the Eotenas until we can retrieve him.
His mere existence holds great potential for Mankind.
We can't abandon him this easily.
Where...
My home?
Jean!
Why isn't he using his MMG?!
Don't tell me it malfunctioned?!
I'll do something!
Mikasa!
What happened to the plan?
It was a failure.
Everyone's fighting because we can't abandon Eren here.
But at this rate, they'll be overwhelmed by the Eotena's sheer numbers!
From the back of the head to the nape of the neck.
One meter long.
Ten centimeters wide!
Eren!
Answer me!
Take one step outside the Walls and you'll be in Hell.
So why did you ever want to go outside?!
"Why"?
Because I was born into this world!
Eren!
They are the prey and we are the hunters
We are the hunters
Shingeki  no  Kyojin
the eotena onslaught
We are the hunters
Shingeki  no  Kyojin
the eotena onslaught
Without knowing the name of the trampled flower
The fallen bird awaits the wind
Prayer won't change anything
What you need right now is the resolve to fight
Swine who laugh in the shadows
At the will to move forward
Are no more than livestock
In a world of false prosperity
That stifles the freedom of the hunters
The humiliation of captivity
Serves as the signal for retaliation
As we move to slaughter our prey
That wait beyond those walls
Jaeger!
We let our bodies burn in the fire
Of our raging desires
We light a flame in the twilight
With a crimson bow and arrow!
We are the hunters
Primal Desire
The Battle of Trost ( 9 )
Damn it all!
Why am I being a burden?
Can't I do anything?
Captain, we can't do any more!
We're the last ones left!
Fall back to the boulder!
Situation report?
Five Eotenas,
approaching from the gate.
If those Eotenas think I'll cower inside 'til they're gone
they've got another think coming!
Jean!
His Maneuver Gear really is busted.
What's wrong?
Fuck.
What's wrong with this thing?
Ya shittin' me?
Not now!
Jean, calm down!
Marco?
Whaddya think you doing?
Come on.
This is like taking care of a damn baby!
Fuck me. Why is this trigger so hard to pull?
Jean!
What're you trying to pull?!
Look who's talking!
Just get the hell out of there!
You are out of your mind!
You're the crazy one!
I can't even believe I survived that.
Look at that.
Eren.
Mikasa!
Armin!
Eren beat it!
Now he's trying to finish his mission!
If we can cover him until he gains the gate,
we win!
Defend him at all costs!
We may have to lay down our lives,
but Eren must reach that gate!
Don't let a single Eoten touch him!
Don't let them get in his way!
Protect Eren!
You two, head to Eren's location.
That's an order!
Got it?
Roger!
Mitabi's squad?
What is this?
The Eotenas won't follow us!
We have to get close enough to make them attack!
This way, you bastards!
I'm gonna jam my blade up your rancid asses!
That did it!
Here they come!
Run!
Into the houses!
What's this?
Staying landbound is suicide.
Without horses or fortifications, ground assault is impossible!
Suicide? No. That's the only way.
Follow Mitabi's squad!
Armin, let's go, too.
This way! Follow the leader!
My whole body feels like it's being squashed.
Mikasa? Armin?
What are you playing at?
If you stay down there, the Eotenas will get you!
Quit dragging your asses, you damn slowpokes!
Over here!
H-Hey!
Mitabi!
So why did you ever want to go outside?!
Because from the moment we are born,
we are free.
It doesn't matter how strong
those who would deny us that freedom may be.
Water that burns?
Land covered in ice?
I don't give a shit about them!
But only those with the right to see them
can truly be called free!
Fight...
I'd willingly give my life for that right!
No matter how terrifying this world is.
No matter how cruel!
Fight...
Fight.
Fight!
Another Eoten!?
I'll handle it.
Out of the way!
Go, Eren!
FIGHT!
My friends...
Your sacrifices weren't in vain!
Today, for the first time, Mankind has defeated the Eotenas!
Yellow smoke round sighted.
The operation is a success!
Deploy all reinforcements!
Bring the elite squad home!
Information available for public disclosure
History of the Human-Eoten Conflict ( 1 )
The oldest remaining sources record that
the Eotenas first emerged 107 years ago.
They devoured most of Mankind.
History of the Human-Eoten Conflict ( 1 )
The oldest remaining sources record that
the Eotenas first emerged 107 years ago.
They devoured most of Mankind.
the eotena onslaught
Information available for public disclosure
History of the Human-Eoten Conflict ( 2 )
Cannon were the first countermeasures,
but the Eotena's regenerative abilities
rendered them useless.
History of the Human-Eoten Conflict ( 2 )
Cannon were the first countermeasures,
but the Eotena's regenerative abilities
rendered them useless.
the eotena onslaught
The remaining Eotenas are on the move!
Get onto the walls!
We'll evacuate once we've retrieved Eren.
Armin?
How's Eren?
He's so hot, I can't believe he's alive!
We need to hurry up the walls...
He's still partially fused with the Eoten.
I can't pull him out!
We'll have to cut him free.
Wait!
Eren?
Armin!
Mikasa?
That's...
The Wings... of Freedom.
Hey, you shitty brats.
What the fuck is going on here?
The serendipitous return of the Reconnaissance Legion,
together with the efforts of the Garrison's engineers,
allowed Wall Rose to withstand the Eotena onslaught once again.
It took a full day to eradicate the Eotenas
now trapped within Trost.
The barrage of canon fire sounded
from the walls in ceaseless fury.
Most of the Eotenas swarming the walls
were slaughtered with explosive rounds.
The Legion dispatched the few that survived the barrage.
During this operation, soldiers succeeded
in capturing one 4-meter class and one 7-meter class alive.
However,
207 troops were dead or missing, and 897 were wounded.
Humanity had indeed brought defeat to the Eotenum,
but far too much was sacrificed to allow for celebration.
Hey...
You're—
Marco?
Cadet,
do you know this man's name?
I guess I hadn't seen him around...
But I never thought he was actually...
Marco.
What happened?
D-Did anyone...
Did anyone see how he died?
What's his name?
If you know, tell me quickly.
Don't you understand, cadet?
It's already been two days since the hole was sealed,
and we still haven't finished collecting the bodies.
If we don't hurry, the corpses could trigger an epidemic.
We must avert a second tragedy.
There is no time to mourn your friend right now.
Do you understand?
104th Cadet Corps
Captain of Squad 19, Marco Bodt.
Marco, then?
I'm glad we have a name.
Let's return to work.
What is this?
Eotenes ambergris.
They don't have fully-formed digestive organs,
so after they've eaten all they can, they spew it up like that.
That's so...
Damnit.
It's impossible to identify anyone in this!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Apologizing won't help.
Just mourn his passing.
Got a question?
The leader of the Reconnaissance Legion's strike force, Commander Erwin.
And Corporal Levi...
W-Well...
Where
is this?
As you can see, it's an underground jail cell.
The Gendarmerie has taken custody of you.
We've only just received permission
to speak with you.
That key—
Yup.
It's yours.
You can have it back later.
The basement of your house in Shiganshina—
Doctor Jaeger's house—holds the answer
to the many mysteries surrounding the Eotenas.
Is that true?
Yes.
I think so.
That's what my father said.
But you've got amnesia, and your daddy's disappeared.
Suspiciously convenient.
Levi.
We've already reached the conclusion that he has no motivation to lie.
There's still much we don't know.
But right now, we need to hear what you want to do.
What I want to do?
To reach your house,
we must retake Shiganshina and Wall Maria.
The most expedient way to seal the shattered gate
would be to use your Eotenes body.
It's likely that Eotenas will determine our fate.
The Behemoth and Armored Eotenas
seem to operate under the same principle you do.
Your decision is the key.
The key that could save Mankind from despair.
M—
My decision?
I'll exterminate them!
Every single fucking one of them!
Answer up, you little turd.
Whaddya wanna do?
I want to join the Reconnaissance Legion
and exterminate every last Eoten!
Oh?
Not bad.
Erwin,
I'll take responsibility for him.
Let the brass know.
I'm not saying I trust him.
If he betrays us or loses control, I'll slaughter him on the spot.
But I don't think Command will complain.
I mean, I'm the only one who can kill him.
Request accepted.
You may join the Reconnaissance Legion.
The dream where your heart seeks comfort
Is more fragile than your life
You can abandon it, yet always find it again
Now, sleep in peace
My pulsing rage
Defiles the wishes I harbor
Before I forget them
Only to remember once more
In this beautiful and cruel world
We keep on asking ourselves
Why it was we who survived
What will we protect
With our strength and with our weakness
If reason and logic no longer hold sway
The time for dreaming has come to an end.
Eren awakens to the dampness of a dark underground prison
and the reality of the special military tribunal that will decide his fate.
Eyes Not Yet Seen
The Night Before the Counterattack ( 1 )