Fujinuma Satoru,
you're under arrest on charges of murder
and attempted murder resulting from arson.
It's him!
I can't let it end this way.
I still have unfinished business.
There's still something I have to do.
Hey.
Go back.
Come on, go back.
Just one more time.
Please...
I beg of you!
Go back!
I'm glad I mustered up the courage to come.
Me too.
I'm really, really glad.
What are you, stupid?
Yeah.
Satoru.
Hinazuki.
Hey there!
I got done early, so here I am.
Sorry we're late.
Are we interrupting?
Of course not.
Right, Hinazuki?
Right.
I have to succeed.
Wow, Satoru's such a gentleman!
This time, for sure.
I have to make sure I leave no regrets.
Even if I have to do it alone, and even if things get ugly.
Fail, and I won't get another chance.
This is the final Revival!
Another tomorrow became today as I waited for you
I stopped and looked back at the never-ending days with a sigh
Finally I realized my memories would fade into nothing
And a small part of my heart has been grieving since
I can't let it slip away again
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
Or I'll never be able to tell you on that day
That I regret everything that's happened around me since
Another tomorrow became today as I waited for you
Each day tears another hole in me
It has to be you
ERASED
I'm starvin'.
What say we grab a bite?
I'm broke.
Oh, I just got my allowance.
Wanna go have some okonomiyaki? My treat.
Sure!
Nice one, Satoru!
Yay!
Oh yeah, Satoru.
Did you read that book I lent you a couple weeks ago?
Poe's The Swapped Man.
Not yet, sorry.
I don't even remember.
But what would you expect?
You lent it to me eighteen years ago.
Give it a try once you get home.
It's really interesting.
I'm home.
Welcome back, Satoru.
Gimme a bit.
Dinner will be done soon.
What's wrong, Satoru?
Don't just stand around—
Did you get into a fight with Kayo?
Nah. I'm good.
That so?
Well, let's eat.
Sorry, Mom, but could you keep this in mind?
You can actually take a direct train to Ueno.
What're you even talkin' about?
February 29th, 1988.
The day before Hinazuki Kayo becomes the first victim in a series of kidnappings and murders.
This is the third time I've lived this day.
You've got guts, Satoru!
He said the same thing last time,
but now it's a day early.
I can't be picky about my methods this time.
1988 National Champions
Ice Hockey Club
Kenya.
Uh, I'm sorry, but it looks like I lost that book you lent me.
Let's talk out in the hall, Satoru.
You don't have to worry about the book.
It never existed in the first place.
Let me just get this out of the way.
Lately, I've been catching glimpses of a more serious side of yours.
And that makes me happy.
Before, you pretended to care about others despite having no interest in them, right?
Not saying you weren't serious then, of course...
But I like you better as you are now.
I'd still like an answer to this question
that's been eating away at me, though.
Satoru...
Who are you?
It feels to me like you've become a different person,
or well, like there's some additional character mixed in.
I first noticed this change in you that day
when you were staring at Hinazuki in class.
I'd noticed her bruise way before.
But I couldn't do anything.
That's how I've always been.
I take a step back when dealing with people.
But right in front of me,
you dug deep and took a step toward her.
It felt as though something took control of you to rebuke me and show me how it's done.
Just who are you, Satoru?
I...
I'm...
I am...
A hero...
wannabe.
Yeah, you're Satoru, all right.
Kenya...
Hinazuki's going to be killed.
I saw her being abused.
Next time, I'll stop it for sure.
Satoru.
You don't need results to be a hero.
You're already one.
Let me help you.
I wanna be a hero too.
I always thought you hated Hinazuki.
You know, likes repel and all that.
Yeah, I did hate her.
But at the same time, I was also attracted to her.
Oh, I kinda get what you mean.
Satoru, Kenya.
Stand in the hallway with those buckets.
Heroes often get the short end of the stick, huh?
Tell me about it.
I need to stop by somewhere.
Hiromi, Kenya. Could you take Hinazuki to the children's center and wait for me there?
Sure.
Okay.
I can get through tomorrow, March 1st,
as long as I don't leave Hinazuki alone in the park.
The problem is March 2nd—
the day of our birthday party.
Mr. Yuuki needs an alibi.
Hey, is your dad's room on the ground floor?
Y-Yeah. It's at the corner facing the main street.
Why do you ask?
Oh, I was just wondering if it was noisy at night.
N-Not really, no.
All right. One more thing...
Yuuki, do you ever see Hinazuki Kayo?
Wh-Why?
She's been hanging out with our group lately.
R-Really?
No wonder I haven't seen her around for several days.
Well, if that don't beat all!
I'm so dang happy for ya, Kayo!
That's the first time Yuuki's ever let his dialect slip before me.
L-Laters, Satoru.
Laters.
Judging from that, the killer must've decided to
frame him after seeing him and Kayo together by chance.
Hold on, Yuuki. You can count on me.
I'm gonna prevent this entire case.
Shirakaba Children's Center
Hinazuki!
Kenya!
Hiromi?
Satoru,
we're at the gym next door!
- Kenya
Satoru,
we're at the gym next door!
- Kenya
Over here!
Sorry, Satoru.
We all decided to come here.
Oh, Satoru! Join us!
I guess you can't play Othello with three people.
I've got to be careful.
I have to avoid drastic changes like these until March 2nd,
or else things could get unpredictable.
I'm home.
One, two...
Satoru! Hinazuki!
Satoru
&
Kayo
Happy
birthday!
Happy birthday!
March 2nd, 1988
Wednesday
March 1st, X-Day, went just like it did last time.
From here on, I'm gonna change the future with my actions.
I forgot something at school.
You're going this late?
Do you really need it right now?
Later!
I know I'm acting unnaturally,
but this is no time to worry about appearances.
Shiratori
Foods
I'll kill you
This'll do it!
Wh-What?
Who did that?
Now the police will provide
Mr. Yuuki's alibi for tonight.
Is somebody out there?
Hey! Show yourself!
I'll get rid of her.
If I can remove her from Hinazuki's environment...
If you'd just...
disappear...
Come to your senses, Satoru.
It'd be bad if she died.
And it'd be even worse if they caught you for it and you couldn't help anyone.
Satoru,
I've been following you for the past two days or so.
Given how desperate you've been to save Hinazuki,
I knew you wouldn't think twice about your own safety.
Thanks, Kenya.
But I really think Hinazuki's in danger today.
You did something rather concerning
before coming here, too.
What was that all about?
Th-That was to call the cops to
that house for a different reason.
I've made up my mind. Help me, Kenya.
We need to get the police to stop
Hinazuki's mother from abusing her.
You sure? That could cause a huge stir.
Good.
Have you thought it through?
I only just came up with the idea.
I'll think about the fallout now.
I don't care if it becomes a major incident or if I get caught along the way.
I don't even care if I have to face the law.
Any fallout is better than Hinazuki dying.
Look, just make sure you don't get caught.
Your mom would be devastated.
Nah.
Knowing my mom, I'm sure she'd be proud of me.
Oh. Yeah, I can see that.
Okay. Let's do this.
I'm gonna go walk Hinazuki home.
Get going.
We'll clean up here.
This time I remembered to bring my coat and gloves when I left the house.
Hinazuki—
Fujinuma—
Listen...
I'm gonna kidnap you now. Okay?
What are you, stupid?
Yep.
That's why I couldn't think of anything else.
Okay.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Reckless
Episode 7
Here we are.
An out-of-use school bus.
I heard it was the club room for
Izumi Elementary's ice hockey team.
Yo. There you two are.
Yeah. Are you sure this is gonna be okay?
Yep. They got a new bus last year,
so this one's just used for storage now.
Let's open the vent before lighting the heater.
It's all rusted.
Try not to give us away.
Okay.
Wow.
Whoa.
This is a pretty cool hideout.
I kinda wanna live here myself.
Doesn't have a bath, though.
Living in a big house doesn't guarantee happiness.
But hey, I still gotta go home.
Later, Hinazuki.
I need to go home for now too,
but I'll be back late at night.
I'll knock three times, okay?
Thank you, Satoru, Kenya.
No need for thanks. We're friends, Kayo.
We'll protect you no matter what, Kayo.
"We'll protect you, Kayo"? Really, dude?
That was embarrassing for me too!
And what about your "We're friends, Kayo"?
Kinda awkward. Especially the name.
I think I'll go with "Hina" instead.
I'll leave the "Kayo" just for you.
Thanks.
Like I said, no need for thanks.
Besides, the hard part's just starting, right?
Yeah.
If this ends up becoming public, just play dumb, okay?
Okay.
You sure took your sweet time.
Sorry.
We took a detour and talked about stuff.
Did Hinazuki's mom call or something?
Nope. Not a peep.
Oh, right.
I've got an early start tomorrow,
so you don't have to stay up making me dinner.
I'll make do with this.
Come in.
You were up?
I couldn't sleep.
Figures.
Hungry?
This is great.
Late-night cup noodles sure are tasty, huh?
I've never had them this late before.
I'd be surprised if you had.
I'm planning a summer camping trip
with Kenya and the rest.
Come with us.
Dunno if I'll be able to.
Sure you will!
'Kay.
Wake up.
It's morning.
Good thing I dropped by.
Let's leave before the Izumi students come to school.
March 3rd (Thurs)
Kayo's late?
Ice Hockey Club
1988 National Champions
This is the lunch broadcast.
Please be sure to wash your hands before eating.
Nothing's happened so far.
What do you make of it?
Would Hinazuki's mom have called the police already?
I don't think she'll look for her just yet.
Last time, on March 2nd,
Hinazuki got back home before 9PM.
After that, her mother and her mother's boyfriend beat her.
By 11PM, she had disappeared from the shed they'd locked her in.
At 12:30AM, Hinazuki's mom called mine.
The culprit murdered Hinazuki before sunrise on the 3rd.
Not only have Hinazuki's actions and ours changed a lot this time,
but so have Hinazuki's mom's and the killer's.
We're in uncharted territory now.
Staff Room
I'm Yashiro Gaku, a teacher at Mikoto Elementary.
Yes, please.
Don't tell Kazu or Osamu about this.
And, uh, sorry for dragging you into this, Hiromi.
I'm just glad you leaned on me, no matter how.
Besides, even if I'd gone home,
I would've been all by myself until 8PM.
And I'm sorry for locking you up here, Kayo.
Don't be. I've never had this much fun before.
I'm glad I mustered up the courage to come.
I'm gonna drop by your place tomorrow morning.
And leave her mom with no choice but to call the cops, huh?
Yeah.
Listen, I more or less get the gist of it,
but who's gonna handle the fallout?
Don't worry. I'll take full responsibility.
What are you, stupid?
If we say it was my idea, and you guys only helped me out...
we all get away scot-free, right?
And I'm out.
She's right.
I never even considered that angle.
On the way home, Kenya said,
"I bet you hadn't thought of that."
When I told him I hadn't, he added,
"In my eyes, that's what heroes are like."
Is that Satoru?
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory