What's wrong?
Eh?
So you're headed to Mistral?
Why are you going there?
I heard that they have great food and lots of women...
It's been a few years since the war ended.
It's a good thing that we're still alive.
Here you go.
It's Glenb!
How can you do this?
How cruel!
Seems like you're awake, little missy.
Here's some of our war bounty...
Ah, it's caramel!
T-Thank you for giving me something so expensive!
Erm... Sergeant!
It's nothing.
If we treat the trumpeter well, we'll be able to hear the retreat calls better...
We don't really get a lot of new recruits due to the recall of the draft.
Did you volunteer?
Yes! So I could learn how to play instruments.
Huh?
Uhh... I mean...
It's fine to be honest.
Do your best, little missy!
Private 2nd class, what's your name?
Kanata.
My name is Sorami Kananta!
There's a festival today at Seize.
A festival?
That's why we've stopped here...
Behold!
This is the position you've been assigned, the Time-Telling Fortress.
Head in that direction...
Yes!
Order: "Private 2nd class, Sorami Kanata, will be assigned to the 1121 Platoon of Trois State, Seize."
"Helvetia Republic Army Headquarters."
Objective completed at 1320 hours.
Thank you very much!
The city of water and glass, Seize.
Wait a minute!
I'm expected to report at 1500 hours.
I can finally let you sing...
Direction check... Done!
Time check... Done!
Gear check... Done!
Advance...
...forward!
D-flat, what a beautiful sound.
Wow!
It's a fish!
10.25 yen
What a beautiful doll...
S-Sorry!
What's wrong, Rio?
A kitten that got too excited from the festival...
... It ran at full speed towards tomorrow.
That can't be helped.
Little kittens are supposed to wander...
That's why they're cute, right?
It would have been fine, if it were a stray...
What?
However, this one has an owner.
That startled me...
But once again, I'm able to find another beautiful place.
What is it?
Thank you!
Huh?
Oh? A soldier!
A girl from the fortress?
This one looks cute.
Thanks for the fire!
All right...!
Now you've done it!
Aim and... Fire!
Thank you!
Hey!
Are you an idiot?
Getting involved with this...
What are you planning to do with your uniform looking like that?
Um... well...
Bless you...
Thank....
Come with me!
How's the bath?
Yes, I like it!
That's good.
Seems like you were an easy target.
You weren't able to dodge it?
The dye will come off once it dries...
No need to worry about it.
Um... That was a festival, right?
It is a day of legend in Seize.
A legend?
What kind?
The Fire Maidens who guard the city...
I owe you one.
The repairs for that are completed as well.
Also... This.
Felicia, huh?
That nuisance...
Late...
Late! Late!
Lateeeeee!!!
And we came all the way here just to pick her up.
All right.
Let's just wait here patiently.
It was a present from your father right?
It's nice...
A-flat.
Thank you for the wonderful bath!
I don't know why, but I always get lost easily...
But because of that, I had such a wonderful meeting!
Don't mention it.
But try not to get lost around here, all right?
Eh?
Ah!
You can distinguish the notes?
It has a very clear sound, and seems to bring back memories...
That's not what I meant-
Thief!
You fool!
Thank you very much...
Jeez...
Were you going to give up your life for something like that?
But that bell...
It's all right...
It was meant to be like this...
Late.
Happiness.
Umm...
I have something to attend to, so I'll be leaving now.
Don't get lost again, okay?
That bell...
It must have been a very important item...
What should I do?
This is bad!
From there?
Advance forward!
The Fire Maidens?
Long ago...
Long before the world became the way it is now.
Under the valley of this city, there lived a winged demon.
The demon spread fire and shook the ground, causing everyone to suffer...
Eventually, it took away all the maidens living in the fortress
and trapped them inside an underground maze...
However, the maidens did not give in.
They summoned each
> other, using the golden horns given by God and escaped the maze.
With the support
> of a giant spider, they defeated the demon and beheaded it.
After they beheaded the demon, violent flames erupted forth.
At the rate the fire was spreading, the town would have burned down.
In order to stop the fire, the maidens embraced the demon's head.
From then on, the villagers continued pouring water on the maidens and the demon's head every day...
After a year, the fire was finally put out...
And so, to comfort the spirits of the maidens who have sacrificed to save the village,
the water spraying festival was created.
The new girl... didn't come after all...
That doesn't matter anymore.
Take a look Captain, it's Rio-senpai!
Seems like she fits the role perfectly.
I guess I was correct in entrusting her with this task.
Huh? But didn't we draw lots...
Seems like I got lost again...
I'm... so worthless.
Sometimes, being lost may be fun...
...because you get to meet people who you haven't met before...
I don't want... to be alone...
Are you lost?
Yes, I want to see my mommy.
It will be all right.
If you wish for it hard enough,
that feeling of wanting to see her will reach her.
Really?
Yes.
The sound will always resonate...
Always resonate...
Always resonate, and...
And so it will be heard...
This is the resting place of the Fire Maidens.
Embracing the demon, and relieving the curse...
In order to not let it awaken once more...
That's...
The sound of the golden horn...
Could it be that the demon has...
Awakened?!
Kureha!
Hear it... someone!
My sound!
It was heard...
The sound resonated, and...
Wake up already...
Private, second class Sorami Kanata!
Ah!
Huh?
This place is...
Just how long were you intending to sleep in?
This is the Time-Telling Fortress...
The station of the 1121 platoon!
About yesterday...
I-I am very sorry to have troubled you!
Seriously...
S-Sorry!
But...
Just kidding.
But don't do something so reckless again.
Just for a bell like this...
I will teach you...
A trumpet!
...why this fortress is called the Time-Telling Fortress.
The sounds of the skies!
Kazumiya Rio.
That's my name...
I will train you to become a trumpeter.
Nice to meet you Major Sergeant Rio!
Rio is fine.
It's Felicia's...
Our Captain's policy.
We do not talk about ranks here.
Umm...
In that case...
Rio-senpai!
All right then...
Let's begin.
Blow the morning call!
The trumpet girl is bad this time.
Next time, First Battle A story of the Chair