Everything went splendidly.
That was quite the pathetic trifle
you've troubled me with, Tokiomi.
I am very grateful, king of all kings...
King of Heroes, Gilgamesh.
Your actions tonight will establish
your prowess as the King of Heroes.
They will also reveal which of our foes we must hunt down.
Please stay your hand a little longer.
Very well.
For the time being, I shall amuse myself with some exploring.
This age is rather fascinating to me.
Is the modern world to your liking?
It's unspeakably ugly.
But there are ways I can enjoy it.
What's important is whether there are any treasures here that are worth adding to my collection.
If nothing in this world is worthy of my adoration,
you will pay dearly for summoning me and wasting my time, Tokiomi.
Worry not.
The Holy Grail will surely please you, King of Heroes.
That is something for me to determine.
Well, I'll play along with your cajolery for now.
Everything of value in this world belongs to me.
No matter how precious a treasure this Grail of yours may be,
I won't let those mongrels fight over it without my permission.
I'll leave the details to you, Tokiomi.
My, my.
Honestly.
Gilgamesh just had to materialize under the Archer class, which comes with the skill Independent Action.
Well, I can just let Kirei take things from here.
For now, everything is proceeding as planned.
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
And link them on to tomorrow
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Crying and embracing the night
Screaming its grief out loud
The distant ideals gently heal
These legs that've stepped forward
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
No matter where I go
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Assassin got killed?!
Hey, Rider! This is a big deal!
One of the seven's already been eliminated.
Hey.
The Imperial
Army
Hey! Don't you get it?!
Assassin got killed!
The Holy Grail War has begun!
I've been working so hard to gather information,
yet day after day after day,
you just sit around eating rice crackers and watching videos!
You're worse than a familiar! Worse than a rat!
Also, didn't I tell you to take spirit form when I don't need you?
I have to supply you with more mana otherwise, you know!
Look, nobody cares about Assassin.
He's only good at skulking in the shadows.
He could never pose a threat to me.
More importantly, boy...
This is far more amazing!
This big black thing they call a B-2.
It's magnificent!
I'm thinking of buying around ten of them. What do you think?
It'd probably be less trouble to just buy
countries outright, considering the cost.
I see.
So, the problem is where to get all that money.
Were there some affluent capital nearby, such as Persepolis, we could simply go forth and raid it.
For the moment, this Clinton man will be our biggest obstacle.
He will prove to be a more
formidable opponent than Darius III.
A-At any rate, I'm glad that Assassin was eliminated first.
You're the type to always take the enemy head-on, right?
So it's best for us that the guy who'd use sneak attacks and tricks is out.
This Tomahawk thing looks to be useful, too!
Saber, Lancer, Archer, the three great knight classes,
and Berserker, who only knows how to thrash around.
They're all small fry in the face of that Noble Phantasm of yours!
Which just leaves Caster as a potential threat.
If we can find out who Caster is, we'll—
How did Assassin fall?
Fool. I'm asking about the
Servant that defeated Assassin.
You saw him, didn't you?
I think he was Tohsaka's Servant.
His appearance, his attacks,
everything about him was gold and flashy.
It all happened so fast, I couldn't tell...
Fool!
If I must fight someone, it will be to survive and win!
Why weren't you paying close attention to him?
Well, it matters not.
Did you observe anything else of note about the flashy gold guy?
B-But it all happened in the middle of the night...
It was over in an instant...
Hey, Rider, a Servant normally only has one Noble Phantasm, right?
As a rule, yes.
However, "how many" isn't the right
way to conceptualize Noble Phantasms.
As you may know, Noble Phantasms are the
physical manifestation of a Hero's legend or tale.
It can be a specific ability or method of attack.
Is there some Noble Phantasm that consists of throwing dozens of swords at an opponent?
A sword that splits into many copies, huh?
It's possible.
That could still qualify as a single Noble Phantasm.
But those weren't copies.
Each weapon had a different shape.
Well, forget it.
We'll learn the enemy's identity when we encounter him.
A-Are you sure that's okay?
I am!
In fact, it's more fun this way!
Food, sex, sleep, and war.
Whatever you do, enjoy it to the fullest.
That is the secret of life.
Now, let us go find some entertainment outside.
We're heading out, boy! Get ready!
H-Heading out? Where?
Somewhere, anywhere.
Oh, come on!
You weren't the only one watching Tohsaka's place.
This means everyone else also knows of Assassin's death.
All the other teams will be making their move tonight.
We'll crush them as we come across them.
Crush them as we come across them, you say...
That won't be easy.
I am Rider.
My mobility far exceeds that of any other Servant.
Wait, wait, wait! Not here! You'll blow the house away!
I have lost my Servant.
I have forfeited my right as Master and can no longer participate in the Holy Grail War.
In accordance with the treaty, I, Kotomine Kirei, ask that the Church shelter and protect me.
I accept your request.
In my role as judge, I, Kotomine Risei, will guarantee your safety.
Now, come in.
Father, is anyone watching this church?
No. This place has been declared a neutral sanctuary.
The Holy Church will censure any Master who defies the decree.
It's safe here, then.
Yes.
Don't let your guard down, just in case.
Post one of you to keep watch here at all times.
Yes. Understood.
Who was watching the battle?
I detected the presence of familiars from four separate Masters.
Two days ago, the summoning of the final Servant, Caster, was confirmed.
All of the Grail War Servants
should now be present, but...
There's one missing.
I was hoping all the Masters would see it.
At this point, surveilling the estates of the Three Families is a Master's obvious course of action.
If he couldn't even think to do that, it wouldn't
occur to him to guard against us Assassins anyway.
The Masters have their backs open, believing Assassin to be dead.
We, already Heroic Spirits of the
shadows, shall become true shadow.
The battle has begun.
At last, it is time for the 4th Holy Grail War to start.
These old eyes of mine will finally see a miracle incarnate.
So this is where Kiritsugu was born.
How did you enjoy your journey in the sky, Saber?
It was nothing much to speak of.
Far less exciting than I had anticipated.
I suppose flying is nothing to a Heroic Spirit like you.
That's not it.
Servants receive knowledge of the
modern world upon materialization.
I could even pilot this aircraft if it came to it.
You could pilot it?
My Riding skill allows me to command any beast or vehicle, with the exception of divine and mythical beasts.
Once I mount the saddle and take the reins, intuition does the rest.
Mount the saddle and take the reins...
Did I say something funny?
No.
Still, you must be the only Servant who
has flown in an airplane in physical form.
I apologize for that.
If only I could take spirit form...
No, I didn't mean it like that.
Don't worry about it.
I never get tired of watching you.
Irisviel, is there something strange about me?
No, not at all.
When you laugh like that, it means
there's some hidden meaning behind it.
What is it? I want you to be frank with me.
It means that your being stuck in
physical form isn't without its merits.
It's given me many enjoyable
hours choosing outfits for you.
Irisviel, is this manner of dress actually common in this era?
I chose it to match my own outfit.
You don't like it?
No, it's fine.
It is rather easy to move in, and besides, I'm used to dressing as a man.
What a lively place!
Kiritsugu should have already arrived, yes?
Yes. Twelve hours before us.
He'll come find us, so don't worry.
We'll keep an eye on the situation for now, so we can act when the time comes.
It's rare that I get to visit Japan,
so I'd like to enjoy it before the fighting starts.
That's dangerous.
We should secure our base of operations,
meet up with Kiritsugu, and discuss our plans.
I suppose you're right...
But wouldn't it be a waste?
We've come all this way.
And...
It's my first time.
It's the first time I've ventured into the outside world.
You spent your entire life in that castle?
I am a mere puppet created for the Holy Grail War.
Of course, it's not like I don't know anything about it.
Kiritsugu told me all about the outside world using videos and pictures.
This is the first time I've seen it with my own eyes, though.
So...
Forgive me. I got carried away.
Please stop the car.
Walking in this city will also be a new experience for me.
It is a knight's duty to escort.
I shall do my very best.
Come with me.
The equipment you requested has arrived.
Madam and Saber have arrived as well and are making their way together.
That way, the other Masters will
assume Madam is Saber's Master.
Good.
There was an incident last night at the Tohsaka mansion.
Here is the recorded footage.
What do you make of this?
It looks too good to be true.
The time span between Assassin's trespassing
and the Tohsaka Servant's response is too short.
Since Assassin has a skill that masks his presence,
it's hard to believe he was detected in advance.
I think Tohsaka was expecting an intruder.
In a battle among Servants, it's critical to conceal the identities of Heroic Spirits.
Why would Tohsaka expose his Servant for all to see?
He had a reason to, I suppose.
Maiya, what became of Assassin's Master?
He escaped to the church last night.
The judge decreed him under his protection.
Assassin's Master is Kotomine Kirei.
Maiya, send a familiar to watch the Fuyuki city church.
Are you sure?
Masters are forbidden from operating in
the neutral zone surrounding the church.
Keep it as close as you can without the priest noticing.
Very well. Understood.
Where is the thing I left with you?
Here.
About two seconds.
I'm surprised.
Yes.
Illya weighs less than that Walther.
Yet...
She's already eight years old.
Focus only on what matters now.
Don't think about anything else.
It's so beautiful.
Just like a mirror reflecting the night sky.
It's so much fun to walk around a new town, accompanied by a gentleman.
Did I make an acceptable gentleman?
You were perfect.
You were a wonderful knight today.
You honor me, my princess.
Saber, do you like the sea?
I suppose I don't really know.
In my age and country, the sea
was where my enemies arrived.
I've hated it, but never once have I admired it.
I'm sorry about that.
You're a woman just like me.
Yet, when you were King Arthur, you
couldn't afford to enjoy anything like this.
And you, Irisviel?
Would you not have preferred walking
around the city with Kiritsugu instead?
I couldn't make him do that.
It would only hurt his feelings.
Does Kiritsugu not enjoy spending time with you?
He's someone who finds happiness painful.
An enemy Servant.
Yes.
He's making his presence known from the shadows, 100 meters from here.
He seems to be inviting us there.
How thoughtful.
So he wishes to choose the battlefield.
Shall we take him up on his offer?
We shall.
Rider, let's go back down.
Right now!
What? This is the perfect vantage point.
I-I'm gonna fall!
I mean, take me down!
I-I can't take this anymore...
Don't be so impatient.
Waiting is also an important part of war!
I wanna go home.
I wanna go home to England...
I already told you to stop being so impatient.
Look. It appears that things have begun to unfold.
This will be fun!
Welcome.
I have spent the entire day searching this city.
Yet, everyone simply hides away in their little holes.
You, brave one, are the only one who responded to my invitation.
That pristine valor...
You are Saber, I presume?
Indeed.
And you must be Lancer.
I regret we cannot exchange names even
though we shall be fighting to the death.
It is the fault of those unfortunate rules.
Saber, be careful.
I can use healing magic to support you,
but nothing more.
Leave Lancer to me.
It worries me more that the other Master is nowhere to be seen.
They may be plotting something.
Please be careful.
Irisviel, please cover my back.
Very well, Saber.
Bring me victory!
Yes, without fail.
Episode 3
Land of Winter Trees
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
If I can find peace in my recollections
While reminiscing about you
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
Proof of the time I spent with you
Is right here with me
You've shown me what it means
To have overflowing feelings
Even if this world were to end
I'll be right by your side
Let's see what you can do, adorable King of Knights.
The anti-magic skill of a Saber-class Servant is no fairy tale.
He's good.
That's enough fun, Lancer.
What's happening?
I'll go! Take me, you idiot!
Next Episode
Blade of the Demonic Spear