Trost District. Year 850.
Under threat from his own regiment,
Eren Jaeger invokes his ability to transform,
saving Mikasa and Armin,
but striking fear into the hearts of his fellow soldiers.
I've always been one of you.
I'm human!
Eren is not a foe of humanity!
For humanity's glory, in what
little time I have left to live,
I will advocate his strategic value!
That brave stand went unheeded,
but for the intervention of one man.
Dot Pyxis.
The highest ranking officer in the Southern Territory.
Calm yourself.
Surely, sir, we can at least do these
young soldiers the favor of hearing them out.
I'll do it! I don't know if I can, but...
I will. I swear!
Excellently said. You have the heart of a lion.
Staff officers, hup! We have a plan to flesh out!
Wait, we...? We can't actually be moving
forward with this as our linchpin strategy.
It was just something I tossed out there.
I was thinking the same thing.
'Cept, he seems like a guy who knows what he's doing.
Has it all under control,
like we can't see the forest for the
trees, but he's got a bird's eye view.
Y'think so?
I do.
Either way, though, we've got a whole other problem
to address before we can get your plan off the ground.
And my gut tells me that the
Commander's keenly aware of it.
Which would be?
Titans aren't our only foe.
Look sharp, soldiers.
The fate of mankind rests on your shoulders.
Retake Trost, are they kidding?
Someone up top's lost their marbles;
how'd they expect us to shore up the hole?
Is the brass that out of touch?
It's a damn suicide mission!
Lost cause, no doubt.
Defending Wall Rose is the only real option here.
Jackasses. Some bureaucrat's
pushing this through for the glory.
I can't... I can't go back.
We'll die! We're all gonna die!
I just want to see my family!
What the hell, Daz? Calm down!
Stop shrieking like a sniveling coward!
Are you tryin' to give me the
impression you're a liability?
Sir, please! Look at us. We're being marched
to an early grave like lambs to the slaughter!
You too good to sacrifice yourself
for the good of humanity, soldier?
Or do you prefer I cut you down right
now as an example to your comrades?
Do what you gotta do. I'll take it over
being fed to a Titan like human candy any day!
Get a hold of yourself!
Let go of me! Let go!
I'm not going back to that nightmare!
You hear that?
Not gonna lie, he's got a point.
So, uh... Who do you think's going
to have a nervous breakdown next?
I dunno. But Trost isn't the way I want to go.
Come again?
Uh. I was only kidding around, sir!
Speak up!
What?
At the top of your lungs. Make
as much noise as you can, cadet.
You think everyone else doesn't feel the
same way about this stupid idea as you do?
Now stir up a damn distraction so I can get out of here!
And where exactly to you think "out of here" is?
Look man, I just want to see my daughter!
We're all dead anyway, right?
It's thought by many that before the
Titans held sway, mankind consisted of scores
of different races, different creeds;
all scratching and biting at each other for blood.
It's not difficult to believe that second part.
Some wise man or other is reputed to have
said, though understand I'm paraphrasing here,
that humanity required an enemy
greater than itself just to survive.
What do you suppose he could have meant?
This is the first time I've ever heard it, sir.
I guess... he thought we'd all join forces?
Some wise man.
I like the way your mind works. You're
almost as twisted and cynical as me.
Well, it's obvious to me the guy didn't
have a clue what he was talking about.
C'mon. Here we are with an enemy "greater
than ourselves" bearing down and look at us.
Exactly. If our species doesn't pull it together soon,
Titans will be merely the instruments
of our demise, not the cause.
Eren?
Well I'll be damned.
Wait, what? Is he?
That little punk is telling me to get back to work.
At least I can assume Mikasa and Armin are alright,
judging by his attitude. Still, though.
Why in god's name is he with the Commander?
Care for a swig?
Uh... yes, sir.
If you're gonna kill me,
just do it and get it over with!
Shut up! Don't think I won't!
Attention!
Take note. The blueprint of the
Trost Recovery Operation is this.
Our primary objective is to reseal the hole.
Yes, you heard right.
What's more, it will be done manually.
What?
That's impossible. We just don't have the tech.
As for how the task will be done,
that's where this fellow comes in.
Allow me to introduce Cadet Eren Jaeger.
Wha... What the hell?
Don't let appearances deceive you.
This young man is in fact the
successful product of cutting-edge science.
Fantastic as this may sound,
Cadet Jaeger possesses the ability to
fabricate and control a Titan body, at will.
Uh. Somebody tell me the Commander's off his rocker,
'cause otherwise I'm just too thick to get what he means.
Will you just shut up and pay attention? Idiot.
Recall the massive boulder roughly a league from the gate.
Having assumed Titan form, Cadet Jaeger
will hoist said boulder on his back,
schlep it to the hole, and voila!
And this is where you all come in.
Your job will be to defend him.
Yes. Defend a Titan against his own kind.
What do you mean we don't actually need to fight them?
There's an easier way.
Sorry, I know it's not my place
to interrupt. I mean no disrespect.
It's alright. Just go on with what you were saying.
Right. Thank you, sir.
See, whatever else is going on around them,
Titans are generally drawn to large groups of people.
If enough of us collected in
the corner away from the breach,
we could lure the Titans out of Eren's path.
He could be discrete about moving the boulder.
He also won't have to slow his pace
while we fight the others off of him.
And since the Titans will all be in one area,
we can pick them off via cannon fire
without incurring causalities of our own.
Now I'm not suggesting we leave Eren defenseless.
That'd be too risky.
We'll need a modest band of
Elites to act as his bodyguards.
There's no way of knowing how many Titans might
come through the hole while he's trying to patch it up.
His security detail will need to be able to handle them.
Easy enough, I think. We can retool the plan around that.
The thing is, we're making a huge assumption here.
Namely that Eren even in full-on Titan
mode is strong enough to move the rock.
I mean, to be perfectly honest, there's
very little reason for us to suppose he can.
I have my doubts. Serious ones.
As do I. Sending people to their doom on a whim
isn't a tactic I'm fond of.
Uncertainty's killed too many already.
But the Commander's right. We must do this.
Agreed. We're working against the clock here.
Titans are still lumbering into Trost as we speak.
There already may be more than we can handle, frankly.
The longer we wait, the worse
our chances of success become.
And it goes without saying, the better our chances
they'll bust through Wall Rose and wreak untold havoc.
There's something else, too.
Even the bravest of us can't indefinitely bottle our fear.
Not before something gives.
The kid can lift a rock that big?
Is this real? Is he saying we finally have an advantage?
They're lying! I'm not gonna be drawn
into sacrificing myself for this crap!
We're just disposable tools to you people!
You expect us to live and die by
whatever the hell comes out of your mouth!
You mean he's a human weapon?
C'mon. They're obviously full of it.
We're being played.
This is not how I'm goin' out.
Good luck to the rest of ya.
I'm out of here!
Me too!
Yeah, screw a bunch of this!
So help me god, I'll execute you on the spot!
To hell with you!
My family gets the time I have left!
This is getting out of hand.
I know. If we don't act now,
the whole thing'll break down.
Traitors! I'll kill you where you stand!
Desertion is answered by death!
Anyone wishing to leave will by my
personal order not be charged with treason!
Those who have seen a Titan first hand will
not be expected to revisit such horror again.
Whomever this applies to, you may leave with my blessing.
Additionally, anyone with family or loved ones
they would spare from the same trauma may also leave.
The crown will continue to recognize your service.
Thank you and good luck!
Daddy!
I couldn't live with myself.
My daughter's my all.
Daddy's coming, sweetheart. Don't you worry.
Now, think back four years ago.
Namely, the operation to retake Wall Maria.
I bring it up because you all deserve
to have your suspicions confirmed.
Officially, we labeled it reconnaissance.
But in fact, as most of you probably
know, it was little more than a purge;
a thinly disguised exercise in population control.
We knew this in our hearts, of course we did.
Yet we turned a blind eye.
We supported the state-sponsored myth because the
deaths of our fellow human beings allowed us to survive.
Pure and simple.
The guilt is ours. We share the blame. All of us.
The citizens of Wall Maria sustained themselves
on the wholesale slaughter of the refugees
who'd flown to us for help.
But turnabout is fair play, is it not?
If Wall Maria succumbs, the population
will fall by a whole other order of magnitude!
The lands comprising Wall Sina wouldn't
support half the people now living.
If we're wiped off the face of the earth,
the culprits will not have been the Titans,
let me assure you.
No, no. We'll have done it to ourselves.
If the line isn't drawn now, it won't be drawn at all.
If we must die...
let us die here!
I don't know if I'll actually be strong enough
in Titan form to lift that rock in the first place.
But, I'm sure as hell going to try.
Maybe this is naïve.
Maybe we're running on false hope,
but so what? I have to power through.
For them. For all of us.
My role... No. My duty, is to make false hope real.
Good, you're all here.
You have one mission and one mission only.
Protect Eren Jaeger.
Any risks associated with this
operation are yours to eliminate.
Which, I'm sure you'll surmise, means
out of everyone, your jobs are the worst.
Our success or failure will depend on you.
In fact, it's safe to say the fate
of mankind will reflect your own.
Sir. May I ask something?
Of course.
Are you certain about this?
Pinning our hopes on Jaeger, I mean.
Rico, don't.
I'm sorry. I assume we all have our doubts.
Sir, please. With all due respect, the
kid's abilities are an unknown quantity;
we don't have the first idea what he will or won't do.
If he can't lift the rock, or worse, he goes rogue,
a lot of lives will have been lost for nothing.
You make a good point. Perhaps we ought to
just give ourselves up to the Titans willingly.
Personally, the idea makes me sick.
I'm a sore loser.
You'd think I'd be used to it. I've been
stuck on the losing side since day one.
I'm a stubborn old fool, though.
Just once I'd like to know what victory feels like.
Even if I have to resort to extreme measures.
Naturally, sir!
I'm sure we all feel the same way!
Then I suppose we'll just have to wait and see.
The boy's abilities may be an
"unknown quantity," I'll give you that...
But I'll take it over the known quantity of our options.
Sir. It's time to get the decoy operation on its feet.
Ian Dietrich.
Rico Brzenska.
Mitabi Jarnach.
You are the Garrison Regiment's best and brightest.
Win this one for humanity.
Sir!
Excellent. Ian, I'm assigning you squad leader.
On-site contingencies will be yours to deal with.
Uh. But, sir. That is...
I have no objections.
Neither do I.
Please, sir. I'm not competent enough.
Now, now.
You appreciate alcohol, do you not?
Sir?
You know a good vintage.
You know a shoddy one, as well.
So, there it is.
Sir!
I'm so sorry, Eren.
I was just talking out of my head.
It wasn't my intention for you to be pulled into all this.
Stop apologizing. The fact is you
have a gift for strategy and you know it.
I believe in you, Armin.
Eren. I really think I should...
You're not coming with me.
You're on the decoy squad. Period.
No way! I'm not leaving you alone!
I won't take another chance...
Knock it the hell off!
Get it through your head that I'm not your responsibility!
You're not my mother!
Ackerman.
I want you on the squad that'll
be providing Jaeger with backup.
We'll need your skill.
Hop to. Let's get this started.
See ya, Armin. Don't die on me, okay?
Yeah. You either.
Let's get this straight right now.
Whatever you are, all I care about
is you getting that rock in place.
Can we count on you?
Yes, sir! I won't let you down.
You're absolutely sure you're gonna be alright to do this?
I got it!
Seriously?
How many times you want me to say it?
You just go do your job and I'll do mine.
Look, now's not the time to be playing house.
Come on, it isn't like that.
I'm gonna say what we're all thinkin' here.
The fact the fate of mankind depends on a
little brat like you doesn't make me hopeful.
All of you, stop it, right now!
We're about to be in range of the giant boulder!
I'm not seeing any Titans nearby.
The decoy strategy must be doing the trick.
Don't be a hero!
Just focus on luring the Titans to our corner of town!
If you don't need to, don't engage!
Something I want you to be aware of, Jaeger.
Make no mistake.
More than a few of our comrades are
going to die today trying to pull this off.
Their blood's on your hands.
I'm talking friends. Captains. Lieutenants. Peons.
Yes, they are soldiers. They are prepared to die.
But remember, every one of
them is a flesh and blood person.
Steady.
Hold position.
Get ready.
Scatter!
Every one of them has dreams. Hopes. Fears.
Every one of them has a name.
Alyosha. Dominic. Fine. Isabel.
Ludwig. Martina. Guido. Hans.
They're not pawns. They're people.
Some have been living together
like family since their cadet years.
This may well be the end of them.
Whole families snuffed out in a moment.
Whatever you think your mission is, Jaeger,
your first and foremost concern today is
making sure their deaths mean something.
Whatever happens, you keep that lodged in your mind.
Take everything that comes with deadly seriousness.
Right!
This is happening. I'm going to do this.
Not once in this century of terror
has mankind risen above the Titans.
Their every craven, bloodthirsty advance
has left a wake of inestimable loss for us;
lives taken, territory abandoned.
However, should we succeed, we'll make history!
Today is the day.
Lands taken by our greatest enemy will be reclaimed!
This is the place! Let's do it!
For the first time, we will know what it means not to run,
but to meet the Titans head on and win!
We've got green smoke, sir.
The Elite Squad has commenced the operation in earnest.
Now, it may seem an insignificant plot of land
compared to the vast tracts
of former glory long abandoned.
But as a symbol. As an idea.
Trost regained shall stand as a
reclamation of pride and hope beyond measure!
A leap greater than we have ever taken!
Granted, in terms of proportion,
it's not easy to see how he'll manage to lift it.
But in terms of sheer will, he's got this.
I know he does.
Eren?
The Trost Recovery Operation has begun.
As his comrades fall by the dozens,
Eren's rampage goes horribly awry.
But just as it seems, the
operation has ended in failure...