This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki.
She's twelve and dreams of becoming a singer.
But unfortunately...
...she only has one year left to live.
We, the Shinigami were asked to keep an
eye on her until the inevitable fate, but...
Today, she's become an adult...
...and she performed incredibly in the audition.
Aren't we...
...changing her destiny?!
Well then...
I wonder what's going to happen today.
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
The Promise With Eichi-kun
This is all your fault, Takuto!
Didn't that girl pass the audition?!
Man.. I was surprised too.
I didn't think she would actually be chosen.
Don't talk like that about other people's lives!
You're shouting, Meroko.
It couldn't be that you've forgotten
what our job here is?
To make sure that when her one year is up...
...she won't refuse to come with us, right?
Exactly!
So then, it doesn't matter...
...whether or not she passed the audition.
Ah, I see...
...not!
She was willing to return to the house with us...
Now that she's become a singer... it'll be
troublesome to have to follow her around.
You let a human like her know the truth...
...and even turned her into a sixteen-year old!
I won't forgive you for a stunt like this!
What's so funny?
You two seem to be so close.
Huh?
I-Is that how it looks?
Well, after all...
We are...
...the ones who silence the tears of children.
The Shinigami Duo...
...Spring Onion Ramen!
I'm really grateful for everything.
Huh? Oh... It was nothing.
What is this?!
By the way...
Why am I the only one being left out?!
...that song you sang at the audition...
...what song was that?
That was...
...the song my father, a musician, wrote.
Really...
Is something wrong?
For some reason, I can't seem to remember
whether or not I've heard it before...
Hold it!
Don't think that just because you passed
the audition, you've become an adult!
W-When I'm in this body, I'm all grown up!
Hmm... so then...
Meroko!
Stop harassing her!
Oh... but...
...I can't go home like this, so...
Huh? Oh. Of course.
Amazing...
...I turned back to normal.
Yep. Your chest returned to normal, too.
P-Please don't stare at me like that.
Geez... you're so stingy.
Hey...
Eh?
Do you...
...really plan on becoming a singer?
Yeah.
I promised, after all.
Promised?
My promise... with Eichi-kun.
Eichi-kun?
Wait, who is that?!
Your sweetheart?
What the hell?!
H-He's not my sweetheart...
...yet.
So that means...
...he's the one you're longing for?
I...
...two years ago...
...entered a treatment center for the ill.
While Grandma was traveling abroad...
...I stayed there with Eichi-kun.
He told me his feelings, but before I could answer...
...due to circumstances beyond
our control, he left for America.
No, no!
Don't go, Eichi-kun!
Don't cry, Mitsuki.
America isn't that far away.
But...
Here... let's make a promise.
Until we meet again...
...we'll work hard to reach our dreams.
For me, it's to be an astronomer.
And you, a singer.
Mitsuki...
...I love you.
Even though we'll be apart...
...I'll look for the moon in the sky.
That's why... so I can find you sooner...
...shine even more brighter.
More... and more...
And since then?
Since then?
Haven't you had any contact with him since then?
For example, mail or an overseas phone call?
Well... I have no idea how
to get in touch with him.
I see...
But...
If I accomplish my dream of becoming a singer...
...my name might even reach
somewhere as far as America.
Then surely...
...surely... Eichi-kun will... notice me.
You put your whole heart into this, huh?
Somewhat, I guess.
What is it, Takuto?
You're making such a frightening face.
Scary...
What are you?
I thought you had honest
feelings of becoming a singer...
...but it was all for a guy!
Eh?
That's just wrong!
If you don't have pure intentions
of becoming a singer...
...you can't become a good singer!
You...
...quit singing immediately!
W-Why are you saying something like that?
That's right.
Isn't it great that she's doing it because of a guy?
Not at all!
Huh?
I'll... work really hard at singing, so...
No matter how hard you work, in the back
of your mind, you'll always feel like quitting.
That can't be...
I would never want to quit singing.
That's right! What part of this is immoral?!
What part of doing it for a guy is anyways?!
Besides...
...such blind faith after being neglected
for two years is anything but normal!
You've been dumped.
He's probably already with another girl over there.
E-Eichi-kun...
...would never do something like that!
Why can't you understand that?
That's because... it's Eichi-kun, after all!
That's foolish.
Hey!
Cut it out, Takuto!
Anyways...
...someone as disrespectful of singing as you...
...will never sing again!
Hmph!
W-Wait... Takuto.
Takuto!
Come on, Takuto!
Geez... why is he so mad?
More importantly...
...what kind of person gets in the way of fate...
Someone who gets in the way of a human's fate...
...may be in love with that human.
This Eichi...
...I'll have to pay special attention to him.
Just what were you thinking?
When I told you that you shouldn't audition...
...I wasn't trying to be mean.
It's impossible because your condition right now.
Stop it.
Sorry...
But...
...it's over with now, right?
Eh?
You'll be unable to sing for a while...
Ah... no, I made it.
Made it?
What should I do?
I can't tell Sensei what really happened.
But...
...I wonder if he would believe that I transformed...
and about the Shinigami as well...
Hmm?
What do you mean by "made it"?
It couldn't be that... you passed the audition?
Um... well...
It's no use.
There's no way he'd ever believe it!
Um... I meant modeling.
Oh... modeling, huh?
Well, modeling is fine, I suppose.
But from now on, don't do anything rash like this.
O-Okay!
By the way...
...what'd you do for the application?
Under guardian...
...did you write your grandmother's name?
Um... actually...
Did you put my name down?
F-Forgive me!
It's fine, it's fine.
We'll keep it a secret from your grandmother, okay?
I-Is that okay?
Sure.
I understand your feelings, after all.
It's for Eichi-kun, right?
Y-Yep!
You are not allowed to leave the house.
Leaving the house...
...and having the Doctor take
you to the amusement park...
...you should be ashamed!
Amusement park?
So that's what we did, huh?
Thank you, Sensei.
Do you understand?
I'm very sorry.
Next time...
...a simple apology will not suffice.
Yes.
That's enough.
Please excuse yourself.
Yes.
Hmm...
Wait a minute.
What is that?
What is it?
T-This is...
Um... um...
...from the crane game.
Is that so?
E-Excuse me.
Such an annoying grandmother...
She kept going on and on...
But this means that...
...you're one step closer to your dream, right?
Yeah.
Hey...
What kind of guy is Eichi-kun?
Okay? Okay?
Eh...
Okay.
Wow!
He's a pretty good-looking guy.
How old is he?
We're six years apart, so...
...right now he's eighteen.
So this is a picture of Eichi-kun when he was sixteen?
Sooo cute.
Such blind faith after being neglected
for two years is anything but normal!
You've been dumped.
Eichi-kun...
Eichi-kun couldn't possibly...
So this is where you've been, huh?
Leave me alone.
Well, that means I have nowhere left to go.
Huh?
That girl looks like she wants to be alone, too.
You upset her...
Eichi-kun...
It's all you fault, you know.
Huh?
She's upset because you told her she'd been dumped.
Well, that's what I think would have happened by now.
Am I wrong?
Besides...
...constantly thinking about a guy who's already
dumped you is strange in this day and age!
It's strange, indeed.
Right?
Always avoiding the truth...
...you haven't changed at all, Takuto.
Do you like her?
S-Stupid.
It's nothing like that!
I-Isn't this our duty?
Besides, even if I said she was dumped...
I was just saying that as a general
observation... I didn't state it very well.
Just as I thought... something is amiss.
Such a matter...
Takuto is mine!
Here you go!
Fortune telling?
Yep.
I'll read your fortune for today.
Pick a card.
Okay.
Which one is it?
Wow! That's great!
Today's your lucky day.
That's lucky?
Yep. Super Lucky.
The lucky word today is... shopping.
The lucky word today is... shopping!
Something good will definitely happen.
Come on, let's go out.
Okay.
Grandma's out today, too.
Ah, but if I don't ask Tanaka-san...
Do you need something, Mitsuki-chan?
Um...
I want to go out shopping...
But madam said that...
If Grandma learns that you listen to forbidden music...
...I wonder what she'll say?
You might get scolded...
Shall we head out?
Where are they going?
If Meroko's going along, then I'll
just leave everything up to her.
Mitsuki-chan.
Can you wait here for a little bit, please?
Sure, I understand.
Then... then... just wait a little, please!
Later!
Hey, hey.
Hmm?
There's somewhere I want to go, too...
Ah... I'm going to use the toilet, so...
...just wait for me outside.
I got it.
Shinigami have to use the restroom too, huh?
She left, right?
That girl listened to my suggestion to go out so readily, huh?
Mero-Mero Change!
It's mine!
It's mine, I tell you!
That good thing...
...I wonder what it is.
That guy is...
It's been a long time, Mitsuki-chan.
E-
Eichi-kun?
That guy is...?
T-This can't be real.
It's real, all right.
Although, it's really a lie.
Once you're with Eichi-kun...
...you'll stop wanting to be a singer...
...and Takuto will give up on you too.
It's for that reason...
I'm dreaming, aren't I?
You're not dreaming.
Even though I went to America...
...I never forgot about you, Mitsuki-chan.
That's why...
...once I heard you'd become a singer...
...I hurried back to Japan.
Eh?
My becoming a singer...
...who did you hear that from?
Who did I hear that from?
S-Someone I know in the record business.
That's how I...
That's an amazing coincidence.
It was more than a coincidence...
...it was fate.
Fate...
By the way, Eichi-kun...
...what's with that voice?
After going to America...
...I suppose that my voice probably changed like so.
America's so vast... right?
You're so funny.
R-Really?
W-What is it this time?
There's something I have to
apologize to you for, Eichi-kun.
I... I sang... for your sake...
...I thought that you might have forgotten about me.
What? It's for that?
I'm very sorry.
Mitsuki-chan...
Will you still... like me?
O-Of course.
I'm so glad.
Back then... I...
I couldn't properly answer, so...
Now... I also... about you...
L-
I'm... I'm... I'm sorry!
Eichi-kun?
Where are you going?
Ah.
Shinigami-san.
That isn't Eichi.
It's Meroko.
Eh?
You're kidding.
I'm not kidding.
We Shinigami are capable of transformation.
Is... that so..?
That's right.
Eichi-kun... has no reason to be here, right?
I've made you wait!
Is something wrong, Mitsuki-chan?
No.
There's nothing wrong.
Your face looks pale.
Come, let's go home.
That was low!
You've really done it now!
I thought it was a good idea...
How was that a good idea?!
Someone's serious matter...
...a person's pure feelings...
...you were just toying with them!
I'm sorry...
You think that apologizing will solve this?
Wait.
Huh?
Pure... didn't you just say that they were immoral?
I said that?
You sure did!
"What part of doing it for a guy
is moral?", something like that.
That...
That was about becoming a singer...
That and this are two totally unrelated matters!
Really?
I guess that I was pretty cruel...
But all that stuff about Eichi...
...being dumped and all...
What are you going to do about it, Takuto?
Don't you think that your words hurt her?
Um...
What I said about you being dumped
just me being a devil's advocate...
...I didn't mean it.
It's just a possibility.
No... that's...
I'm sorry.
No.
I was also at fault.
If I really believed in Eichi-kun...
...no matter what was said... I wouldn't be worried.
That's why I won't be confused anymore.
I... I love Eichi-kun!
But, just as much as that...
...I love singing!
If I love him...
...then I have to believe in him!
I have to do my best to believe in him!
If I don't, then my dream will never come true!
These feelings...
...will never be impure!
I guess it can't be helped.
Do whatever you want to do.
For the next year...
...I'll work to fulfill your dream.
You will?
My blood will...
...always be inside you, so...
...I'll always be able to transform you.
When I'm not with you...
...use this whistle to call me.
I'll fly to you.
Thank you, Shinigami-san!
Stop it with the "Shinigami-san".
Call me Takuto.
Okay.
Thank you, Takuto.
Anytime.
Could it be that...
...I've become the evil villain?
Ah.
(Usagi means rabbit)
Usagi-san!
I wanted to thank you.
T-Thank me?
Yep.
Because today really was my lucky day!
You changed into Eichi-kun...
...to give me courage, right?
I'm really sorry!
Eh?
Why is Usagi-san apologizing?
Who knows?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'll never do it again!
Eichi-kun...
...I made it through the audition.
I'll definitely go see you, okay?
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Zutto egaiteta yume
the dream that I have always been drawing
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
How would I, as I am right now...
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
...look to those young eyes I used to have?
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
Full Moon wo sagashite
and find the full moon
Let's sing a song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now
Day by Day
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
I hold the past fate dealt and the hope tomorrow brings here in my heart
Let's sing a song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain
More and more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
Many Thanks for You!
Preview
Takuto!
There's an emergency... an emergency!
Her manager is coming to meet her!
You can't mean that...
That's right!
Mitsuki's guardian...
...Dr. Wakaouji is going to find out.
Wait...
That person won't recognize her when she's twelve...
She came to meet her as a sixteen year old, right?
What are we gonna do, Takuto?!
Ahhhhh... I don't know anymore!
Whatever happens, happens!
Next Time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Along Came the Manager.
Along Came the Manager
Look forward to it!