It was a small incident that happened
to me, Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I accepted the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
Destiny starts to move once again,
thanks to yet another
new introduction.
A small light shining on one's feelings
while walking through
the forest of hesitation
is most likely found in one's heart.
Because I decided to believe,
and move forward,
even if I am headed towards
a shadowed sky.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
The battle between the two
has already started on-site.
The Lost Logia in the
center of it is Class A+.
Its mannerisms are quite unstable.
It's showing signs of an
indiscriminate attack.
A taboo item that meddles
with time and space...
We must hurry in its collection.
Enforcer Chrono Harlaown,
can you head out?
I have determined the
transfer coordinates.
I can go at any time, given the orders.
Then, Chrono,
stop the battle on-site immediately,
collect the Lost Logia,
and get a detailed report
from both combatants!
Roger that, Captain!
Oh, and be careful!
Okay... I'll be going now.
Episode 8:
There's a Really Big Crisis?
Stop!
Combat here is too dangerous.
Time-Space Administration
Bureau Enforcer,
Chrono Harlaown.
Would you tell me the
details of this case?
Time-Space Administration Bureau?
First off, both of you,
stow your weapons.
If you were to continue fighting...
Fate, we're going to retreat!
Step away!
Fate!
No!
Stop! Don't shoot!
We're gonna get outta here, Fate.
Hold on tight!
The fighting has stopped.
One of the two combatants
has escaped.
Pursuit?
They are fleeing using multiple
teleports. We can't keep up.
I see.
Well, the battle was stopped quickly,
and we've finished
securing the Lost Logia,
so I will say that was good enough.
And we'll be able to hear
about the situation.
Chrono, well done.
I'm sorry. I let one of them get away.
It's all right.
You know, I'd like to hear
some of the story,
so can you guide those kids
aboard the Arthra?
Roger that. I'll return immediately.
Yuuno...
Yuuno, what in the world is this?
This is inside a dimensional transport
owned by the Time-Space
Administration Bureau.
Well, to put it simply, it's a ship
that can freely move
through the many dimensions
that exist in this world.
I don't think that's really simple.
Let's see...
Other than the world
that you live in, Nanoha,
there are many other worlds,
and my world is one of them.
This ship can cross
between those worlds.
And it's them, the Time-Space
Administration Bureau,
that controls events that
affect those worlds.
I see.
You must be uncomfortable wearing
that outfit for such a long time.
You can release your
barrier jacket and device.
I see.
You're right. Then...
And you... I think it's okay for you
to return to your normal form.
Yeah... Come to think of it,
that makes sense.
I've been in this form all this time,
so I had forgotten.
It's been a while since you've
seen me in this form, Nanoha.
What?!
Nanoha?
Yuuno... Yuuno...
Um, well, what...
But... You're kidding!
Are you two having
a difference of opinion?
Hey, Nanoha?
When we first met,
wasn't I in this form?
No, no! You were a ferret all along!
That's right, that's true!
Sorry about that.
I haven't shown you this form yet!
Right? You haven't, right?
You surprised me...
Er, can I have a moment?
I am not aware of
what's going on here,
but the Captain's waiting on us,
and if it's at all possible,
we'd like to hear your story quickly.
Oh... Sure...
I'm sorry.
This way, then.
Captain, I have brought them here.
You must be tired!
Well, both of you, please,
over here. Relax!
Please.
Okay...
I see, that's how it was.
The Lost Logia...
You were the one that
unearthed the Jewel Seeds.
That's why I was trying
to collect them.
How admirable.
But, at the same time, very reckless!
Um... What exactly
are the Lost Logia?
They're legacies from
the lost worlds...
But you don't understand
that, do you?
Let's see...
In the dimensional universe,
there are many worlds.
Each a world born unto its own,
and growing on its own.
Among them, very rarely, there
are worlds that evolve too much.
Technology and science... when
their evolution proves too great,
they destroy their own world.
And what's left over afterwards
are dangerous legacies of
the lost world's technology.
We generically call
such things Lost Logia.
How to use them is unclear,
but depending on how they're used,
they can destroy a world,
or even the dimensional
universe itself.
Dangerous pieces of technology.
Items that need to be stored
in suitable locations, following
proper procedures...
The Lost Logia you are
searching for, the Jewel Seeds,
are energy crystals that
interact with the dimensions.
If you collect a few and execute them
in a certain manner,
you can create a dimensional tremor
within the spatial area,
and, in the worst case, even
a severance of dimensions.
The tremor and explosion
that occurred when you clashed
with that black-clad mage...
That was a dimensional tremor.
Just one Jewel Seed executing
at a tiny fraction, one ten thousandth,
of full strength
had that much effect on the world.
It's impossible to gauge the effect
several of them might have together.
I heard about that once.
Back in the year 462
under the old calendar,
when there was
a severance of dimensions...
Yeah, that was a horrible incident.
Many neighboring parallel
worlds fell to ruin.
A tragedy that left its mark on history.
We can't let it happen again.
From here on, the retrieval of
the Lost Logia, the Jewel Seeds,
will be performed by the
Time-Space Administration Bureau.
You guys should just
forget this incident,
return to your respective worlds,
and go back to your normal lives.
But... That's so...
This case concerns interaction
between dimensions.
It's far worse than one where
a civilian could meddle.
But...
Well, I'm sure you can't straighten
out your feelings so suddenly.
Take your time, sleep on it tonight,
talk it out between you two,
and we'll discuss it again afterwards.
I'll see you out. Is where
I found you all right?
Sure.
Should we go home for now?
Yeah.
Um... are you about my age?
Yeah, probably.
Well... you're not mad at me, are you?
I didn't mean to end up
this way, but...
It looked like I was keeping
it a secret from you.
Oh, not at all.
I was surprised, but that was it.
I'm sorry. Thanks.
But for now...
I think it's better for me to be
in this form for everyday stuff.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's have dinner, and
then think it out properly.
What to do from here...
So amazing!
Both of them are AAA class mages.
Yeah...
This girl in the white outfit is cute.
She seems like your type, Chrono.
Amy!
That stuff doesn't matter right now!
This girl's average magical
power is 1.27 million.
The girl in the black outfit
has 1.43 million.
Their maximum execution power
is more than triple that.
If it's just about magical power,
they out-power you, Chrono.
Magic is not about the quantity
of your magical power.
You need adaptation
to suit the situation,
and decision-making skills
to use them properly!
Of course, I trust you on that front.
Chrono, you're the
Arthra's trump card!
Captain...
Oh, the data for those two.
Yes.
Certainly, these are amazing girls.
If this much magical power
was poured into a Lost Logia,
I can understand why
a dimensional tremor would occur.
Now we know the reason why
those kids, Nanoha and Yuuno,
are collecting the Jewel Seeds.
But I wonder what the
black-clad girl's reasons are?
She seemed to be rather
desperate about it.
Perhaps she has a very strong motive.
Motive, huh...
She's still a young child, right?
If she has been leading a normal life,
I'm sure she's young enough to
want to be spoiled by her mom.
You can't!
If the Time-Space Administration
Bureau has stepped in,
we can't do anything about it!
Let's make a run for it.
The two of us, somewhere...
We can't do that.
But!
It would have been fine
if he was a wimp,
but that was a first-class mage!
If he starts a serious investigation,
we don't know how long we have
before he finds us here.
That old hag, your mom,
keeps muttering things
that make no sense,
and she keeps doing
horrible things to you, Fate.
Don't say bad things about Mother.
I will too!
Because I'm worried about you, Fate!
When you're sad,
my heart hurts so much that
it's like being torn apart!
When you're crying, my eyes
and the back of my nose sting,
and I can't do anything about it!
I don't like it when you're crying
or grieving over something!
Our spirits are linked together,
just a little, Aruf.
I'm sorry.
If it's hurting you,
I won't feel sad anymore,
and I won't cry again.
All I want is for you to
smile and be happy, Fate!
Why... Why won't you
understand that?
Thank you, Aruf.
But I want to fulfill Mother's wishes.
It's not just for Mother.
I'm sure it's for myself as well.
So, just a little bit longer...
It's only a little more until the end.
Will you do your best with me?
Promise me.
That you're not just
following her orders.
That you'll be doing your best
for yourself, for your sake.
If you can promise that,
I'll protect you no matter what.
And so...
Both Nanoha and I would like
to assist your operations.
Assist, huh?
Leaving me aside, I believe
that Nanoha's magical powers
can be a useful combat
force from your end.
Collecting the Jewel Seeds,
fighting those girls...
In either case, I'm sure we
can be very useful to you.
You've thought it out quite well.
In that case, I guess
it will be all right.
Moth...
Captain?!
Let's have them help us.
We would like to save our
own trump card as well.
Right, Enforcer Chrono?
Yes, ma'am...
I have two conditions.
Both of you need to be
under the custody of
the Time-Space Administration
Bureau during this period.
That, and you must obey
every order given to you.
Got it?
Understood.
Nanoha, it's been decided.
Thank you, Yuuno.
Now, then... Momoko, Nanoha,
we're going to go out to the hill
in the backyard for a little bit.
Sure. Practicing again tonight?
Yeah.
Be careful!
Right.
Okay, let's go.
Sure!
It's been a while,
so I'm going to give you a work-out!
Hey, wait!
I'm going to come watch!
If you're coming, hurry up!
Okay! Just a second...
Miyuki, you haven't changed a bit.
Okay, that should be it.
Yeah.
Now then, what is this important
thing you have to tell me about?
Yeah...
What I told Mom was basically
everything that has happened
from when I met Yuuno until today.
But I couldn't tell her about the magic
or what Yuuno looks like,
so I told her what I could,
and that I have to leave for a while
to do what I need to do.
It might be dangerous,
but it's something I started
with a dear friend,
and I want to do it until the very end.
Right.
I might make you all worry.
But of course, I'm always
worried about you!
I'm your mother, Nanoha,
so I worry about you a lot.
But...
If you were still trying to decide
on which path to take,
I would say that you shouldn't
do anything dangerous.
But you've already made up
your mind, right?
To properly finish what you
started with your friend.
To talk things out once more
with that girl you met.
Yeah.
Then take care.
So that you won't regret it.
I'll convince your father
and brother for you.
Thank you, Mom!
I can't turn back now.
This is the path I chose for myself.
This is what I really want to do.
Hurry...
Hurry up, Fate.
The promised land...
Alhazard is waiting for me.
The land of my... our... salvation.
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of cellophane
and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying inside
a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining
on the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something
I can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
The flagship of the Time-Space
Administration Bureau, the Arthra,
is now going to take care
of me and Yuuno.
An abnormal, unprecedented
reaction from the Jewel Seeds,
and the reunion of Nanoha and Fate.
What is the wish that
Fate's mother has?
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 9:
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 9:
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean
Episode 9: The Decisive Battle
Above the Ocean
Episode 9:
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean
Lyrical, magical, in hopes
that I don't lose!