How awful!
It can't be helped.
It was too much for her to handle alone.
But she knew that this might happen.
This is too awful! It shouldn't be happening!
If you give up, it'll be the end of everything.
But you have the capacity to change fate.
This unavoidable destruction, this sorrow—you can change it all. That's why you have this power.
Are you telling the truth?
Can someone like me really do something to stop this?
Can I really prevent everything from turning out this way?
Of course you can! Form a contract with me and become a magical girl!
It was a dream?
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll continue walking upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでく
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
you'll be waiting for me against the backdrop of the beautiful blue sky, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 1     It was like I met her in a dream ·  ·  ·  ·  ·
"ore no yesy wa konna ni kawaii wake ga nai"
Because no one can translate anymore... Especially you, gg.
This show is brought to you by the sponsors you see here.
Good morning, Dad.
Good morning, Madoka.
How's Mom?
Tatsuya already headed up there. Go help out.
Okay!
Mama! Mama!
It's morning! Morning!
Wake up! Mama! Mama!
Wake up!
Huh?
Mama woke up!
How's it been going lately?
Hitomi-chan got another love letter.
That makes two this month.
Pfft. Guys who don't have enough guts to tell a girl they like her in person are worthless.
How's Kazuko?
Our teacher's still at it.
She talks about him all the time in homeroom.
This week will be their three month anniversary, so it's a new record.
I'm not sure about that. This is a risky time for them.
Really?
If it's just a fluke, then problems would be showing up about now.
I guess if they can get past this, then they'll be able to make it through the first year.
I see.
All done!
I wonder which ribbons I should use.
Huh? Isn't that too flashy?
It's supposed to be flashy. We girls must always pay attention to our looks.
That looks pretty good. Now all your secret admirers won't be able to resist you.
Like I'd have any.
You have to think you do. That's the secret to being pretty.
Safe.
Anyways, eat everything all up.
'Kay!
How about another cup of coffee?
Hmm, I'm fine.
All right. I'll see you guys later.
Bye!
Madoka, you need to hurry too.
Huh? Oh, right!
Later!
Bye!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Madoka, you're late.
Oh, those are some cute ribbons.
R-Really? You don't think I'll stand out too much?
They're very nice.
So she said you shouldn't date someone who asks you out via love letter instead of directly.
Your mom's pretty cool! She's really beautiful, and she's a career woman.
If only it were that easy...
I wish I had that problem.
I wish I could get even a single love letter.
So you want to transform into a cutie like Hitomi that everyone wants? I guess that's why you started with those ribbons, huh?
No, my mom...
I bet your mom taught you the secret to being popular! You dirty, dirty girl!
A girl like you needs punishment!
H-Hey, stop! Stop!
You're cute, but I won't let you become popular with the guys.
You're going to be my wife!
I have something important to discuss with all of you today. Make sure you pay attention.
Should a sunny-side up be hard or soft?!
What do you think, Nakazawa-kun?!
I, uh... I-I guess either's fine?
That's right! Either's fine!
If you think a woman's value is decided by how she cooks her eggs, you're horribly mistaken!
You girls out there, make sure you don't associate yourselves with anyone who says they don't really think they can eat a sunny-side up that isn't fully cooked!
It didn't work out, huh?
Yeah, it didn't.
And you guys out there, make sure you don't grow up and become someone who nags about how they want their eggs cooked!
Also, I'd like to introduce all of you to a new transfer student that'll be joining us.
She left that until last?
Okay, Akemi-san, come in.
She's cute! She's cool!
Wow, she's really pretty.
No way... She can't be...
Okay, introduce yourself.
My name is Akemi Homura. Nice to meet you all.
Akemi Ho
Akemi Homura
Umm, Akemi-san?
Akemi-san, where did you go to school before?
A Christian school in Tokyo.
Were you in any clubs?
Did you do any sports? How about art?
I never joined any.
Your hair's really pretty. What shampoo do you use?
Akemi-san has a kind of mysterious aura about her.
Hey Madoka, do you know her?
She was staring at you, wasn't she?
Um...
I'm sorry... I guess I was really nervous.
I don't feel very well.
Would you mind if I went to the nurse's office?
Oh, then I'll take you there.
I'll go, too!
No, don't worry about me.
I'll ask the person in charge.
Kaname Madoka-san, you're the health officer for this class, right?
I, uh...
Could you take me to the nurse's office?
She's really cute!
Umm, how do you know I'm the health officer?
Saotome-sensei told me.
Oh, I see. The nurse's office is...
This way, right?
Huh? Yeah, but...
You... just kind of seem like you know the way.
Akemi-san?
You can call me Homura.
Homura-chan?
What is it?
I, uh... that's a unique name.
No, I didn't mean it was weird...
I-I think it's cool!
Kaname Madoka, do you value your current way of life?
Your family, your friends—do you think dearly of them?
I, uh... do.
My family, my friends—I love them. They really mean a lot to me.
Is that true?
It is. Why wouldn't it be?
I see.
If that's true, then you mustn't ever think of trying to become someone else.
If you do, you'll lose everything.
You just need to stay Kaname Madoka, just like you have so far.
An integer divided by 14 will have an integer quotient with a remainder between 0 and 13.
a is an integer with a remainder of 6 when divided by 14, b is an integer with a remainder of 1 when divided by 14.
The quadratic equation x^2-2ax+b = 0 can be solved for an integer solution.
Find the remainder when this integer solution is divided by 14.
I-I think that's a prefecture record...
Huh? What's that about?
Doesn't make any sense, does it?
I thought she was one of those smart and beautiful girls who are well-read and athletic, but instead she's one hell of a nut.
Just how big of an impression do you have to make on people?!
Is that moe? Is that what moe is?!
Madoka-san, is this really the first time you've met Akemi-san?
Hmm, I guess I'd have to say yes.
You guess? Is there some weird reason why you'd say no?
I... think I saw her in a dream I had last night.
That's great! You're trying to get some attention yourself now!
That's mean! I'm seriously worrying about this!
It's decided, then! This is all part of your karma from your last life!
You're friends, meeting each other again after having traveled through space and time!
What type of dream?
I don't really remember... I just know it was really strange.
Then maybe you really have met her before.
Huh?
You might not remember her, but subconsciously, you know her from somewhere, and that may have come out in your dream.
Isn't that just a little too convenient?
How much of a coincidence is that?
You have a point.
Oh, look at how late it is.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
What do you have today? Piano? Japanese dance?
I have tea ceremony practice.
We have entrance exams soon, but I guess I have to keep doing it.
I'm glad I was born petit-bourgeois.
Shall we go as well?
Oh hey, Madoka? Could we stop by the CD store on the way back today?
Sure.
Kamijou-kun's again?
You know how it is.
Talk to you later.
Later!
See you!
Save me.
Save me, Madoka!
Who's there?
We're currently under construction
Store areas under reconstruction are closed
Save me.
Where are you?
Who are you?
Save me.
Was that you?
Save me...
Homura-chan?
Move away from him.
B-But he's hurt.
N-No, don't hurt him!
This has nothing to do with you.
But he called for me!
I heard him telling me to save him!
I see.
Madoka, this way!
Sayaka-chan!
Out of all the times...
What is she doing this time?
Attacking people randomly while cosplaying?
Actually, what is that?
It's not a stuffed animal, is it?
Is it alive?
I don't know. I don't know, but...
I need to save him!
Huh? Where's the emergency exit? Where are we?
What is this place?
Everything keeps changing.
Darn it! What's going on?!
S-Something's there!
This can't be happening, can it?
I must be having a bad dream or something, right Madoka?
Huh? What was that...
What's going on?
That was pretty close, but it's all okay now.
You saved Kyubey, didn't you?
Thank you.
He's an important friend to me.
He called for me.
I heard his voice in my mind.
Hmm, I see.
From the look of your uniforms, I assume you're Mitakihara students, as well?
Are you juniors?
Who are you?
Oh, that's right. I should introduce myself, but before that...
Would you mind if I took care of a little something first?
W-Wow...
E-Everything's back to normal!
The witch ran away. If you want to take it down, you'll need to chase after it quickly.
I'll give the witch to you this time.
The witch isn't what I'm interested in.
You don't seem to understand what's going on here.
I'm saying I'll let you go.
I think we both would like to avoid any unnecessary trouble.
Thank you, Mami. You saved me.
Thank these girls. I was just passing by.
Thank you very much.
My name is Kyubey!
Were you the one that was calling for me?
That's right, Kaname Madoka and Miki Sayaka!
W-Why do you know our names?
I came here to ask you two to help.
To... help?
I want you to form a contract with me and become magical girls!
Illustrator Hanokage
I can grant each of you one wish.
What? Is that true?
A wish...
It can be anything.
I can make any miracle you want happen.
I thought that was really nice.
Episode 2        I thought that was really nice
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Yumi & Yuka
Editor: guymam
Timer: kozu
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Encoder: Miku
Quality Check: kozu
kixor
thedarkhaze
tux911
limitbreakingcat
rune
steak: the best fansubber
Shiron
This show was brought to you by the sponsors you see here.