It was my choice,
and my fault...
This entire situation happened
because of me.
After witnessing
the results of the path I chose,
I finally realized that
you were right all along.
You explained it to me once,
what it meant to be a responsible person.
I couldn't understand your words back then,
but I do now.
It's not about what you've experienced,
but the choices you've made.
And there are choices only you can make.
An adult's
responsibilities and obligations...
I'll trust them...and you.
Please lead the way
down this twisted path
to a different end.
Someone must make the choices
that lead us to that future.
So, Sensei...
Please.
It's a refreshing morning.
(Silent Growth: What Makes the
Momo Friends Shop So Charming?)
The General Student Council
is in chaos
after the student council president's
sudden disappearance.
(Student Council President Still Missing?) after the
student council president's sudden disappearance.
(Student Council President
Still Missing?)
(Student Council President Still Missing?) But
the Sanctum Tower lights are finally back on,
and it appears regular administrative work
is underway again.
It seems the chaos
that overtook the city of Kivotos
is finally settling down.
(Bread and Dessert Festival
Now Open)
Just this, please!
(Abydos High School)
The next stop is Abydos High School.
Oh! This is my stop!
(Abydos Foreclosure Task Force)
Are you serious, Shiroko?
You rode from the Abydos industrial district
and back on a bicycle?!
That must be hundreds of kilometers!
I didn't check how far it was.
It was a pleasant ride though. Not too long.
Shiroko sure is something.
How was your weekend, Serika?
M-Mine?! I was just...
I did some reading at the library!
You were at the library this weekend, Serika?
I was there as well!
I-Is that so? I didn't see you!!
Anyways! What were you
reading about, Ayane?
I was researching a DOHC problem
I ran into during building repairs.
Ah! Let me explain what DOHC is.
The term is short for a type of engine
called a Dual Overhead Camshaft.
I thought it'd be
useful information to have.
What about you, Hoshino?
I did what any old-timer
does over the weekend.
Somehow, I'm not surprised.
I'm glad everyone had a pleasant weekend.
What about you, Nonomi?
What did I do over the weekend?
I went shopping!
I bought some new snacks,
a few daily necessities,
as well as forty dumbbells or so!
(Abydos Foreclosure Task Force Daily
Meeting) Let's begin our daily meeting.
To start, we'll review current events.
Kivotos, the Academy City, is composed
of many different school districts.
The General Student Council,
led by the student council president,
maintains balance between the districts.
(Endless Conspiracy Theories Student Council President Missing?)
But just a few days ago, the student council president went missing.
But just a few days ago,
the student council president went missing.
(The Reason for the General Student Council's Week-Long Silent Treatment?)
But just a few days ago, the student council president went missing.
It's most likely due to
her disappearance that
so many districts have been experiencing conflict.
Speaking of the General Student Council...
...Um, what was it called again?
That peace treaty
between Trinity General School
and Gehenna Academy?
The Eden Treaty?
Yes, exactly!
Has that been signed yet?
The student council president
was the one facilitating the peace talks,
so it's unclear what will happen.
I see...
Oh, right! Ayane!
(Shiba Seki Ramen)
The owner of Shiba Seki Ramen says
that the Kata-Kata Helmet Gang
is up to no good again.
The Ramen there is delicious.
Do you go there a lot, Shiroko?!
Is that a problem?
N-No! It's nothing...
Anyway,
it's getting harder to maintain security in Abydos.
How troublesome...
We've requested aid from
the General Student Council several times now, but...
With the student council president missing,
they're likely too busy to deal with us.
It's not like we have all the time in the world either.
Thank you very much
for using Kaiser Loans.
At the current rate,
your debt will be paid off
in 309 years and 2 months!
We will see you again next month!
...309 years and 2 months?
There's truly no end to it.
Then, see you tomorrow.
- Goodbye!
- Bye-bye!
(Foreclosure Task Force
Peroro/Fish Cakes/Jellyfish)
(What./
We're listing things that are "white and cute.")
(I don't get it.../Wanna join, Serika?/
Hard no. Today was tough...)
That took long enough.
Hey, hey!
I must've heard you wrong.
Are you little girls
trying to tell me
that my hairstyle is old-fashioned?
Just bask in the coolness of my 'do!
You're the coolest, Boss!
You're so charming, Boss!
- Exactly!
- Yes, correct!
Is it wrong of us to call something
old-fashioned, old-fashioned? Huh?!
H-How dare you keep saying that word?
Minions, punish them!
Are you still talking big?
Your stupid bullets
could never
ever hurt us!
He's still alive.
Is he sunbathing?
Heatstroke?
Water...
- Please...
- Here.
It's an energy drink.
Want some?
Wow! I'm revived!
Thank you so much.
Did you abduct this man, Shiroko?!
It finally happened...
Shiroko committed a crime!
Chill out, everyone!
What's important is covering her tracks
before people find out!
It's not like that at all.
He said he was trying
to get to our school.
What?
So, he's a visitor?
Exactly.
- I see.
- Right...
I knew Abydos was a desert district,
but it was so hot I got heatstroke
while walking out in the sun,
and the next thing I knew I was passed out.
Well... If it's okay with you,
can we ask what your name is?
Oh! Of course.
I'm Sensei, from Schale,
the Federal Investigation Club.
It's nice to meet you.
Does that mean he's
from the General Student Council?
Right.
Our requests for aid have
finally been answered!
That's great, Ayane!
Yes! Our persistence
really paid off!
We'll finally be able to restock on supplies!
Okay, everyone,
let's get to business.
(Certificate of Transfer)
What's this?
It's for all of you.
Thank you so, so much!
We'll finally have more
ammunition and supplies!
Hoshino's going to want to hear about this.
She's probably napping
in her usual spot.
I'll drag her back here!
- By the way, Sensei.
- Hm?
We haven't introduced ourselves yet.
That was Kuromi Serika,
a first-year student.
My name is Izayoi Nonomi!
I'm in my second year!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Okusora Ayane,
a first-year student.
Sunaookami Shiroko.
Second-year.
Well, I met you first,
so you knew that.
Ah. Not that I think that makes me
more important than anyone else.
There's one more member.
The current president of the Foreclosure Task Force,
Takanashi Hoshino.
The five of us make up
the Abydos Foreclosure Task Force.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Oh geez, Serika.
Be more gentle with this old-timer, please.
What nonsense are you spouting?!
You're the president,
and you need to act more like one!
Oh... Takanashi Hoshino here.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Sensei, from Schale!
The pleasure's all mine.
- Hey, Sensei.
- Hm?
I'll take you on a tour.
The desertification in Abydos
is worse than I thought.
Is it?
(Cycling Club/Now Recruiting)
It's been like this
ever since I enrolled.
I haven't seen any other students here.
Is it just the five of you?
(School Office)
Yes.
The truth is,
this school is in severe debt,
and so everyone left. Except us.
The Foreclosure Task Force has been
taking on whatever jobs we can
and repaying the debt bit by bit.
That must be difficult for you.
The gym needed to be cleaned
a little while ago...
But Ayane was sick,
so the four of us had to do it.
It was pretty hard. There was
more trash than we expected.
We still finished in the end though.
And then Ayane scolded all of us.
She was mad?
What's this room for?
It's not used for anything right now.
But this is your room
from now on, Sensei.
- Really? For me?
- Mhm.
The regular office is
overrun with sand.
Is this too small for you?
It's more than enough. Thank you.
Okay.
Shiroko, why do you want
to protect this school?
Gunshots?!
A message for Abydos High School!
Today's the day we're finally
going to conquer your territory!
Huh? The Kata-Kata Helmet Gang?!
(Please Use Sparingly!)
Now? Of all times?!
Oh geez.
I really just wanted to have a nice, peaceful nap.
I'll drive them away like I always do!
Everyone! Let's go protect our school!
Stay here, Sensei.
Shiroko?!
Watch out!
Thank you, Arona.
You're welcome, Sensei!
Here, Shiroko.
Thanks.
How tiresome.
We're rather low on ammo.
What a pickle.
If only our new supplies were here...
I see no problem.
Shiroko! Wait!
Give it up already!
We know you're
low on ammunition!
Huh?! How'd they know that?
Don't worry, Ayane.
They're no match for us anyway.
- Shiroko's creating cover for us.
- Yes!
We'll never hand over Abydos High School
to the likes of you!
Shiroko?!
Shiroko! Nonomi!
Hoshino!
Everyone! Retreat for now!
We'll regroup!
They're running around
like chickens with their heads cut off!
We were right!
They're down to their last bullets!
It'll be a fight to the finish!
Just how I like it! We'll take them all down in one go!
Sensei, if this continues much longer,
the Abydos students will...
Let's go!
Is everyone okay?
We're fine. We can still fight.
We can't let them pin us down like this!
We need to spread out.
Hey, hey. Are you guys seriously still trying?
You don't stand a single chance against us!
Take this!
We can't handle
much more of this!
Damn it! How did we
get cornered by those losers?!
Everyone!
Huh? Who's that?
Why is it important to you
to protect this school?
Sensei.
Why?
Because...
this school
is where we belong.
Is that how everyone feels?
Of course!
Who the hell is this,
swooping in like some hero?!
You can call me Sensei.
Sensei?
I'm here to help my students.
Sorry, but I have to ask you to leave
this school's property.
You think you can talk down to me like that?!
I'll shoot you to pieces!
Let's go, everyone.
Nonomi, lay down suppressive fire!
Roger!
Serika, take aim!
Damn it! Where are they?!
Just stay calm!
I would've done that
even if you didn't tell me!
Nice job, Nonomi, Serika!
What's happening?!
Don't think that you-
This old-timer can't look bad
in front of her youngins!
Coordinates confirmed.
Catch, Shiroko!
Nice timing, Ayane.
Don't underestimate me!
Hey, get a grip!
Eek! How embarrassing!
Hey!
Don't come any closer!
Deliver the final blow, Shiroko!
I said stay back!
W-W-W-W-Wait! I-I surrender!
It's over.
Ow, ow! That hurts!
Please, no! Augh! It hurts!
Then leave. Now.
Okay, okay! I'm leaving! I'm gone!
We'll get revenge one day!
We won, Shiroko!
Well done!
We really managed to
turn the tide there.
All thanks to Sensei's help.
Not at all. I didn't do anything.
It's my job as a teacher
to help my students in their time of need.
Hmph. We would've beat them
on our own anyway.
Bashful as always, Serika.
Don't be so stubborn!
Sh-Shut up!
Our little Serika is so adorable.
You're putting on such a tough front!
Stop it already!
So, this is...Sensei.
(He seems like a good guy./Sensei?/
Yeah. He seemed okay./I thought so too.)
(But let's not jump to any conclusions.)
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
Strawberry milk...
Hi, Arona.
I've been waiting for you, Sensei.