[Douglas] This is the bullet
that killed Brigadier
General Hughes.
It's a forty-five caliber...
The killer used only
this one bullet...
I'd say it was a good shot,
but it was at point-blank range.
Close enough that even a poor
shot could have done it.
Now tell me,
what is the caliber
of the gun that you carry?
It's a-- a forty-five, sir.
Here we have a copy
of your requisition form
for additional ammunition.
Does this look correct?
It says here you fired
exactly one shot...
What was that round used for?
It lists the reason right
there on the form...
I fired my weapon in
defense of Edward Elric
while in the Fifth Laboratory.
But the Fifth Laboratory
is no longer operational...
It remains unmanned.
It was definitely not unmanned.
Sure... according
to your account.
Shall I send someone
to search for this bullet
you say you fired?
There was an unexplained
explosion at the site.
The Fifth Laboratory
is now a pile of rubble.
So the place where you claim
to have used your
gun was unmanned...
and if we looked
for the bullet...
all that we would be able
to find is a pile of rubble...
Is that what you're saying?
But, Lieutenant, we have
eyewitness testimony...
You were spotted leaving the
scene on the day of the murder,
at the same time
as the shooting.
That's impossible!
Calm down, Lieutenant.
Fine then. So what were
you doing at that time?
I had the day off... I was at
my parents' house, visiting...
Please, check with them...
They'll tell you.
All you can offer us
is your family's testimony?
That is not admissible
as an alibi!
Second Lieutenant Ross
is being questioned...
No one is permitted
inside to see her.
I see.
Major Armstrong!
Sergeant Brosh...
I'm glad to see you here, Major.
Is this about Second
Lieutenant Ross?
Yes, that's right, sir.
Major, I can
corroborate her story.
Lieutenant Ross and I both
fired a round from our weapons
at the Fifth Laboratory
to defend the Elric brothers.
You did?
Yes, and it's all
written in my report...
but everyone's
ignoring it, sir.
Are they trying to frame
the Second Lieutenant for this?
When you look close, you're
all scratched up, aren't you?
You're having a rough
time of it, huh?
So, what have you
got planned now?
Well, Ed?
What are we gonna do?
[Elicia] Mommy...
please don't cry.
What do you think?
What's with the face?
I'm just surprised...
You've never asked
for my advice before.
[Ed] Oh.
I'm scared, you know.
You and Al have been
off somewhere fighting
and digging up information...
Information that could get
you killed like Mr. Hughes.
Whenever I think about
that... it terrifies me.
I mean, you could die...
I'd still be here,
and you'd just suddenly...
not be there anymore.
Like my mom and dad.
It's almost more
than I can handle...
thinking about that...
Honestly, sometimes I wish
you would just give
this whole thing up.
I do want you to get
your bodies back...
but I also want you
to stay alive and safe...
It's just...
I don't know...
Sorry.
I'm not sure what
I think you should do...
I really don't know.
You're sure being nice, Winry.
Why do you sound so
surprised? I'm always nice!
[Al] Hey! Stop it!
You take that back,
Alphonse Elric.
[Al] You're going
to add more scratches!
You take it back right now,
or else! Do you hear me!?
[Al] I'm already
dinged up enough!
[66] Your move.
[Newspaper Guy] Evening edition!
Oh, it's here! Excellent!
[66] What?
The newspaper? Again?
[Lt. Falman] I'm stuck here
babysitting you all day.
This is the only
entertainment I get.
Lieutenant Falman,
calling on an outside line.
Please connect me
to Colonel Mustang...
Yes, that's right...
My code is--
[66] What's got you so excited?
...Airam, George, Oliver...
Four, six, four, nine.
This is that lady
from the laboratory.
[Ed] The Philosopher's Stone...
The people with
the Uroboros tattoos...
The Homunculi...
How are they--?
Brother!
Here.
Don't scare me like that.
The newspaper, Ed...
Read the front page!
What is it now?
What?!
"Second Lieutenant Maria Ross
convicted of Brigadier
General Hughes' murder"?!
[Al] I can't believe this!
[Ed] Maybe the
colonel or the major
will know something about this.
What about Winry?
We'll explain it to her later.
I'm not really a fan of these.
Quit your complaining...
Every stray mutt needs a collar.
All right, I'm gonna
ask you one more time...
Are you honestly
fifteen years old?
I sure am.
I don't buy it.
It's the truth, I swear!
What's that?
What's happening?
We've got an intruder!
Come on! Give us a hand!
What?!
Behave yourself, got it?!
I will!
Lame! Lame! Lame!
Are you guys even trying?
You can do better than that!
He's still coming at us!
The guns don't even dent him!
Hold it! Stay back!
Got it!
This would be a lot more fun
if I was allowed to cut 'em up.
[Ling] Hello! Strange
armor-ghost-man?!
Do you think you could
let me out of here?
Who are you?
Just an illegal
immigrant from Xing.
Oh yeah? A foreigner?
Well, have a nice trip home.
If you let me out of here,
I could help you.
I don't have time
to deal with you.
Where did you say you were from?
Xing, east of the desert.
Come with me.
I'd be happy to.
[fighting sounds]
What?
Well, hello there, sweetheart!
I've been lookin' for you!
You're from the
Fifth Laboratory!
You haven't forgotten
me! How sweet!
I remember you, too...
I think of you every
time I look at the hole
you put in my right hand...
Just like the hole you
put in that guy Hughes.
No! It wasn't me!
Oh yeah?
According to the newspapers,
you're one guilty soldier-girl.
It can't be...
Oh, but it is...
Right now it's lookin'
like you'll be facing
the firing squad for sure.
It's not true!
They're wrong! If they would
just do a proper investigat--
Here are your choices...
Stay here and be
killed for murder...
or bust outta this joint
with me. Which will it be?
How is this happening?
Isn't there anything
else I can do?!
It sure doesn't look like it.
I have no choice! Mom! Dad!
Please forgive me!
Fine, let's go...
If this is how it has to be,
I'll escape with you.
But you better know a way
out of here, metal boy.
Oooh! You've got spunk!
I'll do what I have to do!
Yes... yes... right away.
Notify every zone in the city...
Maria Ross has broken out.
It appears she's with
a violent accomplice...
They must be caught.
If she resists...
...the order is "shoot to kill."
[Lt. Ross] How much further?
[66] Just keep moving!
Lieutenant Ross?!
Edward! Alphonse!
What are you two doing here?!
[Both] Ah!! You're that guy!
[Al] And Ling, too?!
Uh, hey, guys.
What're you up to?
[Ed] I could ask
the same of you!
[66] Quit chattering...
We don't have time for this!
[Ed] Why, you--!
All right, sweetheart,
take that back alley
and run straight to
the warehouse district.
The darkness oughta hide you.
Wait, hold on!
Tell us about Hughes!
[66] Get going! If the MPs
show up, they'll shoot you!
[Ed] Lieutenant Ross!
[66] Stay back!
[Al] No, wait! Lieutenant Ross!
You're Maria Ross... right?
What was that?!
Looks like they got her.
Hold it! Get back here!
Whoops! Missed me!
Let's go, foreigner!
Okie-dokie.
Wait! Ling! What are you
doing with a guy like him?
I'll have to fill you in later!
What now?!
Hey there... Fullmetal.
What happened here?
What happened here,
Colonel? Tell me!
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Why, Colonel?
Why was Hughes murdered?
Why would Second
Lieutenant Ross...?
Why didn't you say anything?!
You threaten
a superior officer?
You forget yourself, Elric!
Brother, don't!
I'm gonna tear you apart!
No! I won't let you!
This bastard just killed Ross!
What? He did?
[Al] How could you
do that, Colonel?!
Maria Ross was a fugitive.
Our orders were "shoot
to kill." So I did.
That's all you have to say?!
About Hughes' death...
I apologize for hiding it.
But you do not argue
against orders...
or ask for explanations.
Just follow them.
That's what it means
to be a soldier!
[Douglas] Colonel Mustang...
You will explain to me
what happened here at once.
The message went out
that if she resisted,
we were permitted
to shoot to kill.
She resisted...
so I killed her.
I understand the brigadier
general was a friend.
Yeah.
He was a good man.
Perhaps, then, it
was one of your men
who aided Lieutenant
Ross's escape.
One of my men? But why?
Why, Colonel?
I'll tell you why...
So you could burn her
to death with your own hand!
I think such speculation
is best avoided.
I'm truly sorry for
not telling you about
Brigadier General
Hughes' death sooner.
It's my fault.
Don't be so hard on yourself...
His murder wasn't
your doing, Edward.
Is everyone here, then?
[Armstrong] Dr. Knox...
Her body was almost
completely destroyed.
But judging from what
little dental work remained,
I was able to conclude that
this is indeed Maria Ross.
It's an awful thing you did.
Turning a beauty like her
into a pile of charcoal.
You must have held quite
a grudge against her...
Didn't you, Colonel?
Is the vengeance as sweet
as you imagined it?
The famous hero
of the Ishvalan War,
going this far against
a little girl.
It makes me sick.
[Armstrong] Colonel...
Please allow me to apologize
for one of my own
officer's actions.
I could never have imagined
that Second Lieutenant Ross
would commit such
a heinous murder.
She was so straightforward and
earnest... compassionate...
A truly fine officer.
Fatigue seems to be getting
the best of you, Major.
Perhaps you should
take some leave.
Back east, where I was...
It's a nice place.
None of the big city noise...
and lots of beautiful women.
[Envy] After a daring escape,
the fugitive is killed
by Colonel Mustang,
eager to avenge his best friend.
And all's well that ends well.
Are you so sure about that?
The plan was supposed
to be designed
to get Mustang
to behave himself.
He took the bait...
Now he doesn't have a reason
to snoop around anymore.
Besides... we did manage
to sow some animosity...
His subordinates won't
trust him much after this.
[Mustang] What's this?
It's a request for leave.
At a time like this?
Is that a 'no'?
No... It's fine.
Request approved.
Thank you very much, sir.
What were you thinking, going
out on your own like that?!
Do you know what the Colonel
would do to me if he found out?
Oh, pipe down, will ya?
Nobody saw me.
Don't you get it?!
That isn't the point!
You're just a helpless
soldier held captive
by a big, bad criminal...
What were you supposed to do?
Huh?
Hey! What're you
up to out there?
Building a signal fire.
Signal fire?
Bringing someone back here
you know nothing about!
How could you be so stupid?
Young Lord! We've
been looking for you.
Wow... Impressive
response time.
Looks like a party.
Hello, Elizabeth...
how are you?
It's great to hear
from you, as usual...
Are you sure your assistant
won't give you grief
for blowing off work
to talk on the phone?
No, the coast is clear... she's
out of the office at the moment.
And a good thing, too, or else I
wouldn't be able to talk to you!
So how do you like
that? He's whipped.
The second the lieutenant goes
on leave, he gets like this.
You'd think Lieutenant
Hawkeye was...
...Colonel Mustang's
nanny or something.
Uh-huh, that's right...
You know I haven't had
a day off since I got here,
so I'm seriously considering
taking some leave time soon.
Oh? Where are you going to go?
I could use a nice,
relaxing fishing trip.
Care to come along?
Yeah? Who is it? What do you--
Major!? What the hell
did you do that for?
You listen to me,
Edward Elric...
Hmm, this no good.
No good at all.
Your automail seems
to be broken.
Um, okay...
Yes, this is a serious
situation indeed...
We'll have to
repair it at once.
There's no time to waste.
Allow me to escort you
to Resembool for repairs.
Um, Major... what's up?
What was that?
You're going back
home to Resembool?
I have no idea what
he's talking about, Al!
And you, Alphonse Elric...
You would stand out too much,
so you remain here in Central.
Okay...
[Armstrong] Right!
We need to make arrangements for
transportation right away...
Come along, Edward.
Cut it out, Major!
Put me down.
I'm afraid I can't do that...
These are my orders.
From him...
Okay, I got it... Roger that.
Major Armstrong
and Edward Elric
have gotten aboard
the train, sir.
Okay.
Finally... everyone's
out of the way.
I was able to locate a
witness that saw the man
who orchestrated
the break-out...
Here... This is a rough
sketch of the guy.
Oh, he's still alive, then?
Is there any direct
connection to the colonel?
Who knows... My money says he's
the one behind it, though.
Where did he run off to?
Well, he did leave
pretty suddenly...
and he's good at hiding.
In other words, you have
no idea... You're useless.
Don't blame this on me, you ugly
hag... I'm short on manpower.
Manpower?
[growls]
But you've got plenty
of manpower right here.
[growls]
It looks like you're finally
on... Barry the Chopper.
[growls]
[Narrator] The truth lies
in the ruins of Xerxes...
The survivors who remain
in the decayed, desolate city
may hold the key to
wiping away the darkness
carried by one young man.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 18: "The Arrogant
Palm of a Small Human."
At long last... the
counterattack will begin.