When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Time sure flies.
It's already the new semester.
I've got to start with a fresh mindset.
You have a wonderful attitude as always.
Good morning, Maria-san.
I'll go wake Milady up.
Ah, you don't have to worry about that.
She won't be going to school today.
Oh, okay.
EH?!
It seems she caught a fever.
Hayate... Are you there, Hayate?
Yes, Milady!
I'm going to school.
You can't!
Schools are meant to be skipped when you're in good health.
Skipping school with this level of fever won't cut it for the King of NEETs.
More of her nonsense again.
What are you doing, Hayate?
Please, rest well.
I'll skip school, also, to nurse you today.
Hayate...
No!
If you skipped school for me, it would affect your grades.
One day won't do anything.
Things are different for a genius like me and you.
One missed day is detrimental to a transfer student like you.
Milady!
Don't worry about me!
I'm...
I'm fine...
I won't die from this.
So leave this to me and-
I don't want to, Milady!
You must go! Now!
Milady!
What the heck is wrong with this anime?
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Okay, class is starting.
Sensei, I have a question.
Yes, Azumamiya-kun?
She looks good as a teacher, too!
I wonder if Milady is all right.
Good morning!
Hinagiku-san.
It's been a while.
Yes, you're right.
So, were you able to master an ultimate move?
No, I did my best, but...
No need to rush.
Thank you very much.
And is Nagi skipping school as usual?
No, she caught a fever on the very first day of the new semester.
Eh? That worries me.
Yes.
Maybe I should pay a visit.
Please! I'm sure Milady will be happy.
Then after school, I'll stop-
Hinaemon! Help me Hinaemon!
SFX: DONG!!
You're so noisy in the morning.
You're so mean, Hinaemon.
You're going to beg for money again, aren't you?
No! Your Sis has more problems than money!
Don't brag about it!
Um, what happened?
Ayasaki-kun! Thank you for asking!
Because a new teacher's coming,
I got demoted to sub-homeroom teacher!
A new teacher?
Nice to meet you. I'm Makimura.
I'll be your homeroom teacher from today.
Eh?
I look forward to spending time with you all.
Makimura-sensei, huh?
I don't have a problem if she's an easier teacher than Yukiji.
I don't care either way.
Why? Why is that nursing robot developer here?
Allow me to explain.
Seven, Eight, Nine, Ten, Eleven, and Twelve.
All of them went berserk or something similar and thus broke down and burned up.
Ah?
Makimura-kun, what do you think of these results?
Let's see...
Not enough firepower?
What do you want to cause more explosions for?
I-I'm sorry.
Do you understand what
the most important aspect of a scientist is?
The most important aspect?
Yes. What you must always keep in mind as a developer.
That's of course-
I get it! It's cake, isn't it? Cake!
Sweets are good for your brain.
Yes, the pleasure centers of your nervous system
get stimulated and endorphin is secreted in your brain.
NO!!!
It's heart!
You're lacking heart.
Makimura-kun, in order for you to learn what heart is,
I'll have you be a teacher at your old high school, Hakuou.
Do you understand the situation now?
Both Hayate and you in front of the screen?
Yes, for the most part.
On a side note, the eyes Katsura-sensei is looking at Makimura-sensei with are really scary.
Everyone, let's spend the day with a smile!
Hmph, who does she think she is?
She can't possibly get a grasp of the student heart that easily.
First, I'd like to know all your level, so I'd like to do a pop quiz.
What? Seriously?
That's just  great.
Oh my, we have whiners.
I've won.
No students will follow you to a rigorous lesson style like this.
Okay, put your pencils down.
Collect the papers in order, please.
It was pretty hard.
Yeah, give me a break.
All right, then it's about time I show
my popularity as the senior teacher.
Good work, everyone.
A test right after a vacation was harsh, wasn't it?
I understand exactly what it felt like.
So the average is 82.3%.
You're all so smart.
It looked like Segawa-san and Hanabishi-san had several minor calculation errors.
Asakaze-san's weak point is long reading comprehension.
Ayasaki-kun, you have your basics down solid.
Um, Sensei, what are you talking about?
"What?" I'm only announcing the result of the test.
Wait, do I have to actually mark these when I grade them?
That's such a bother!
Oh, I know!
Katsura-sensei, can I ask you to do it?
Huh?
Here you go.
Hey, why me?
Sensei! I have a question on problem 2!
Sensei! Tell me how to solve problem 5, please!
Sensei~
Um...
I see. She's as smart as a supercomputer.
I can understand how Katsura-chan was taken off the homeroom teacher position.
Farewell, Yukiji.
Have a good life even after you leave here.
I'm not leaving!
Good bye, Sensei!
Bye bye.
Crap... At this rate, my position in Hakuou, in this anime, will be in jeopardy.
I've got to do something immediately.
But what?
It's finally over.
Without Milady around, school's a little boring.
Hayata-kun!
Here, these are the handouts from today.
Make sure you pass them on to Nagi-chan.
Yes, thank you.
Yes, you'd better.
But why did you have these, Segawa-san?
Why? That's obvious.
It's because I'm the class rep.
Class rep?
Ah right, you were the class representative.
Hayata-kun, I'm the leader of this class.
Please don't forget.
Yes, she's red.
Class Rep Red!
And I'm Blue.
I'm Vice-Class Rep Blue!
And, I can be your enemy or ally.
Disciplinary Black!
Three of us make up-
The Student Council Members!
You guys look like you're having fun.
Hayata-kun, we specially present you with the vacant seat, Orange!
No, I'll pass on that.
But everyone, doesn't the student council keep you busy?
Not really.
Even if we do a half-assed work, the perfect Student Council President will do something for us.
Exactly.
SFX: HAHAHAHA~
Hinagiku-san must have it rough.
But being Class Rep can come with annoying tasks.
For example, this class report.
I need to hand it in by today.
Wow, there are many places to fill in.
No worries! These are the times when Red, Blue, and Black join forces and-
Orange! Let's combine our might and...
Okay. I'm not Orange, but I'll help.
Ah, there you are!
Ayasaki-kun, can you come with me for a second?
Come, hurry!
What about the report?
Ihihihi~ Ringo daisuki.
Ihihihi~ Ringo daisuki = *Giggle* I love apples.
Kisama no akuji minuitari!
Kisama no akuji minuitari! = Your evil acts are now under the light!
Sensei, what's this about?
All right.
Listen, Ayasaki-kun. Stand still here for a while.
What is this about, Sensei?
Do you want to know my well-planned strategy?
Strategy?
I'll give an explanation only to you, then.
First, that woman comes out of the staff room.
And I'll put the ***-Pura right there.
Then...
No! My precious full scratch-built Night**gale!
Look at what you've done!
But in her path waits-
And an added combo.
If I spread a picture like that around,
she'll definitely be forced to quit the school.
Do you understand this major plan?
I understand that something is wrong with your head.
What did you say?
Excuse me.
Wait!
Students are supposed to listen to what teachers say!
Let go of me!
I don't want to take part in a Ka**kabe Defense Force-like plot!
Shut up and work with me!
I don't want to!
Um, is there a problem here?
I heard something about a plan?
Eh? Um... Well... Ah...
I was telling him to stand on the PLATform when waiting for train.
Wait, that's platform, not plan!
So funny.
Come on, you cover me, too.
Go!
Heaven itself is my ally.
I never thought I'd be able to take a photo like this by accident.
I better post it up on billboards around the campus.
Hey! What's wrong with your head?!
I will be the God of the new world.
No, there's no need to rush.
All I have to do is explain clearly what happened.
Right, Makimura-sensei?
How could you do this to me...
I can't get married anymore.
That's not what happened!
At this rate, I'll shame Milady.
Did you know that Sanzenin-san's butler was...
What? No way.
I must protect Milady's honor!
Meanwhile, at the Sanzenin's,
where they don't know what's going on.
I'm glad to see that you look better than I'd thought.
Yeah, my fever's gone down.
So, how was your summer?
Eh?
I had a pretty good time.
First, I went to a fireworks show with Hayate.
Then to beach class with Hayate.
And I went to an amusement park with Hayate.
And went fishing with Hayate.
And then...
Is something wrong?
No, just watching you talk so enthusiastically.
N-No, I wasn't being so...
So? Let me hear more.
Sure. And then I played lots of games with Hayate.
Oh, and I also watched Ya**naka Seisho with Hayate.
They were sharing their summer memories.
Also-
Sensei! Please wait!
Never ever!
Bye bye.
I will take it away even if it takes force!
I couldn't see Hayate-kun even once over the summer.
Why...
Why not give up already?
You're really persistent.
Found you, Hayata-kun.
Pekopon.
"Pekopon" is a word said after finding the hidden player in a variation of hide-and-seek.
You're so mean; you said you'd help me write the report.
Segawa-san, great timing.
Please take that camera's memory card out.
What pictures are in it?
Picture of Ayasaki-kun tied up
with a rope and making a blissful face.
Don't make things up!
Hayata-kun, so you were into those kinda things.
Since you looked feminine,
I was thinking that you liked being teased.
When did I get that character setting?
Don't be so depressed, Hayata-kun.
Since, you know, I kind of like being picked on, too.
Eh?
No! Not like that!
Geez, thanks to you, Katsura-chan,
Hayata-kun now thinks I'm a strange girl!
I can't forgive you now.
Oh, then what will you do?
I will make this memory card mine.
Looks like this is the end of you.
If you take my side, I'll take full responsibility for the next three months of homework!
You can't possibly retrieve it with that.
Here you go.
It's settled.
What?
I'm sorry, Hayata-kun.
Catch me if you can.
You're...
Um...
Who are you?
Are you the one who made my sweet honey cry?
No! No! No!
I-It was him!
Huh?
Eight!
I'm sorry, Eight. I betrayed you when I already have you.
Like I said, I didn't do anything.
Wait, when did you two have that kind of a relationship?
I won't forgive you!
Interesting.
You've made me get serious now.
In any fight I get picked on,
I'll take it on even if it goes overboard.
Why go that far?
She's actually putting up a fight!
You!
Watch out!
Take...
...that!
Not bad.
You, too.
Stop this! Don't fight for my sake!
I wonder how this is going to end.
Can't wait to see. So exciting.
What can I do?
That's definitely a self-destruction button no matter how you look at it.
All right, if I press that!
But no, I can't do it.
If I press that here, a tremendous explosion will happen.
If that were to happen...
Then Segawa-san would...
Don't worry, Hayata-kun.
No, but when someone with skirt on is nearby...
Like Hina-chan, I wear sports pants underneath, so I'm fine.
Thank you sports pants!
Blown to pieces!
Eight...
How sad...
This is all too sad.
Isn't it?
Nothing is born from violence.
Sensei...
He's responsible for everything that happened here.
But please!
Please forgive him; my request as his teacher!
Boys in puberty are really bad at controlling their hearts.
And it's the teachers' job to teach and guide them.
At times, it's painful and suffocating to see how delicate they are; so much that it drives us into walls.
But I will never look away from them!
Because... Because I'm a teacher!
Because I love them!
Sensei!
I... I finally understand.
I understand how heart is important.
Makimura-san.
I respect you.
I want to become like you.
I see.
But the road to becoming a teacher isn't easy.
You have much more to learn.
I am ready for it.
Okay, if you say so.
I will hold study sessions for you starting today.
Mostly at pubs.
At the cost of the difference in the pay between
homeroom teacher and sub-homeroom teacher.
How reliable!
She fell for my plan.
And thus...
I know a nice place I go to often.
Sounds good.
...the battle came to a conclusion.
Leaving behind the debt-ridden butler who learned there is more than one way to be smart.
What was all my effort for?
Now, now. The report got done, too, so all is good.
Th-This is...
Today, I played with Hayata-kun and others. It was fun.
It's not a diary!
Cheers!
Oh yeah, please take care of the bill here, Sensei.
EH?!
Because you're older than me and my senior.
Thanks for the treat.
SFX: SMACK
What goes around comes around.
Interesting how the world works.
Next time, it's a must-see for girls.
We'll fight against moe points.
There wasn't much screentime for me this week!
Calm down. There are days like that, too.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Earth, I love you! I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
'ey there! It's Sakuya. How you doin'?
But this song is really girly, unlike Saku's image.
You think so? The powerful words fit perfectly with her image.
What's with you two's random comments?
Besides, you two haven't heard the song yet as we dub this.
Ah, she spoiled it.
The director and staff are troubled over it,
so get the song ready fast please; GENEON's-
See you next week!
Hey, what's that for?!
Hayate-sama, you look happy.
Yes. A certain person said "thank you" to me.
My.
Things haven't been going too well recently.
People glare at me, too.
So I was a little depressed.
Hayate-sama.
Yes?
I love you, Hayate-sama.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
I've Never Experienced Facing Trouble for Being Too Popular.
Yesterday, it looked like they were hugging each other.
Interesting for sure!