[KNOCS] Can you
tell me which room
Colonel Roy Mustang is in?
[RECPTIONIST]
Well...
Can I ask what your
relation to the patient is?
I'm his private practice doctor.
Just tell him Knocs
is here to see him.
[KNOCS] Ah, hey
there, young lady.
[ROSS] Well, this
is a nice surprise.
And who is this
you've brought with you?
[KNOCS] That's a
bit of a long story...
But if you need to know...
He's kind of
my secret weapon.
[KNOCS]
So how's he doin'...?
Has this whole
thing got him down?
[ROY] The farming
method that's used
in the Ishvalan region...
They mainly double crop.
[BREDA]
Nope... that's close...
But it's called
dual-cropping...
Now think...
You've gotta know
this stuff inside out.
[ROY] Yeah...
And I do know it.
[BREDA]
Is that so...?
Which two crops
are the Ishvalans
known for cultivating?
[ROY]
Wheat and cotton.
[BREDA] That's correct...
Not a bad guess.
[ROY] C'mon, give
me some credit...
I've been researching
this stuff long before now.
[ROSS] He's hoping to
make amends with Ishval...
He wants to
make things right
before becoming
the Fuhrer.
[KNOCS]
Well... ambitious.
And what makes him so sure
he'll become the Fuhrer?
[ROY] That voice...
How long have you
been in here, Dr. Knocs?
[KNOCS] Not long...
So you don't
look so bad...
How're you adjusting?
[ROY] Well...
I can't get any rest...
Thanks to these pests.
[KNOCS] No, I meant
those eyes of yours, Roy.
How are they?
[ROY]
Right.
I envisioned a better future...
and this is the price
I had to pay for it.
[KNOCS] And are
you okay with that?
[ROY] Well,
I wouldn't say okay...
but still...
I won't let it stop me
from moving forward, either.
[KNOCS]
So tell me something...
You're gonna aid in
the restructure of Ishval?
[ROY] The Ishvalan War
of Extermination...
That's where
everything went wrong.
[KNOCS]
You're right, there...
Both for our country...
And for you and me.
[ROY]
It's time to correct it.
[KNOCS]
Correct it?
[ROY] I'm calling off
the military occupation...
And then I'll
return their holy land
to the Ishvalans left
living in the slums...
There's still a
lot to be done.
[FUERY]
We owe them plenty...
We'd all be dead now
if it weren't for Scar
and the Ishvalans...
It's the very least we
can do to repay them.
[FALMAN]
Colonel...
I brought all the
materials you asked for.
[HAWKEYE] We know that
this won't erase our sins...
but it's not too
late to fix things.
[KNOCS] This room just
reeks of optimism...
Hey, Dr. Marcoh,
listen to this...
They're already one
step ahead of you in here.
[ROY] Marcoh...?
Dr. Marcoh's here?
[MARCOH]
Colonel Mustang...
[MARCOH] I've brought a
Philosopher's Stone with me.
I believe that it might be able
to return your eyesight.
[ROY]
I suppose so.
[MARCOH]
This Stone here...
I created this Stone
by sacrificing the
lives of many Ishvalans.
[MARCOH]
It might be presumptuous
of me to ask this, but...
if your... intentions are
to help their relatives...
[MARCOH]
No.
I have no right to speak for
those whose lives I've taken...
So I'm asking this as
a personal request...
Let me heal you with this
stone so you can restore Ishval.
[ROY] I know some people
who might not like this...
Especially Fullmetal.
[ROY] But I will
accept your offer.
[ROY] And I'll devote my life
to seeing Ishval restored...
But first thing's first.
[ROY]
There's someone else
who needs that Stone
even more than I do.
[ROY] You can heal
me after you heal him.
[phone ringing]
[HAVOC] From our
hearts to your home,
you've reached the
Havoc General Store!
[HAVOC]
Hey, Breda... What's up?
[HAVOC] Do what...?
Come to Central...?
You'll explain
when I get there...?
This better be worth it.
[OLIVIER] How are
you healing, Scar?
[SCAR]
Why did you save me?
[OLIVIER] The only
interest I had in saving you
was for your alkahestry...
But plans do change...
Colonel Mustang's
requested Major Miles
to assist him in dealing
with Ishvalan affairs.
[MILES]
So...
I thought you might
be able to assist me...
Not as Scar...
the killer that is...
But as a true Ishvalan.
[MILES]
How 'bout it...?
Will you help me spread
the teachings of Ishvala?
[MILES] We can't allow our
religion and culture to die out.
That would be the
death of our race.
And this is our chance...
We can rescue our people.
[SCAR] Is this why
I was saved from death...?
Have you given me
this responsibility
as my reason to
continue living, brother?
[SCAR]
I accept.
I'll join you...
From now on...
I'll follow you
wherever you see fit.
[OLIVIER] All right, Miles,
you can take it from here.
Try not to disappoint me.
[MILES]
Sir!
[OLIVIER]
Oh, Mustang...
I wish I could see
the look on your face...
when you find out
Scar's still alive.
[OLIVIER]
Scar...
Why don't you tell
us your real name?
[SCAR]
I've died twice now...
I'm neither of the
people I once was...
I don't need a name...
Call me anything.
[OLIVIER]
Fair enough.
You take care... Ishvalan.
[ED]
Are you okay?
[AL] I didn't realize
my muscles had atrophied
so much on the other side.
[ED] Do you want
me to carry you?
[AL]
No. Thanks...
I can walk around on my own.
[AL] I'll just move
at my own pace...
You can go ahead if you want.
[ED] Nope...
We left home together...
and that's how
we're gonna return.
[AL] Well...
we better get moving then.
[ED]
Yep.
[AL] So, brother...
How's the leg?
[ED]
Well... Ehh...
I haven't maintained it
in a while, so y'know...
It's stiff.
[AL]
Thank you, brother.
[ED] Huh...?
Thanks for what?
[AL]
Oh, never mind.
[ED] Whatever...
Quit acting so weird.
[AL] I wonder
how Ling is doing...
Do you think they
made it back to Xing?
[ED] It's been two
months since they left...
I'm sure they're back by now.
[AL]
I... hope May's okay.
[ED] You've got
nothing to worry about...
She's in trustworthy hands.
[AL]
May.
[MAY CHANG]
Oh, Alphonse.
[AL]
Are you okay?
[MAY CHANG]
Yes... I'm fine.
[LING]
Hey... Princess Chang.
[MAY CHANG]
Ling Yao!
[LING]
Hey c'mon...
Quit lookin' at me
like you wanna kill me,
all right?
[LING] You're about
as stupid as I am...
Getting mixed up with
this country's problems.
And you didn't even end up
with a Philosopher's Stone.
[LING] You know
what this means...
My clan won.
[LING] As far as
your clan goes...
The Yao family...
will protect
yours at all costs.
[LING]
I accepted a Homunculus
as a friend, now didn't I...?
If I did that...
Then I can accept
the Changs...
and all of the
other families too.
[LING] Whoa, careful
with the tears, there...
You're gonna drown yourself...
I didn't think I'd have
to start protecting
you this quickly.
[MAY CHANG]
Trying to accept
and protect
everyone is just...
It's too greedy!
[LING]
Ahhh...
I guess he rubbed
off on me after all.
[LING] Alright then...
Time to go home.
[ED]
You're leaving?
[LING]
Yeah...
We need to get home
so we can bury Fu.
[ED]
See ya later.
[LING]
Yeah... Count on it.
[AL] We sure have
made a lot of friends.
[ED] I know...
Especially you, Alphonse...
You got pretty close
with a certain princess...
You aiming to be the
future prince of Xing?
[AL] C'mon...
She is a nice girl, though.
But forget about that...
What about you...
and Winry?
[AL]
Den... We're home, boy.
[dog barking]
[WINRY]
What's he barking at now?
[AL] Den...
Stop, that tickles!
♪ background song ♪
[WINRY] Dummies...!
Welcome home!
[ED]
Thanks!
[AL]
Good to be back!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[ED]
Yow!
This should
not be this hard.
[clap]
[ED]
Eh... worth a shot.
It was worth it.
[AL] Brother...
What's taking so long?
[ED]
These damn chores
are testing the
limits of my courtesy.
Winry treats me like
I'm her personal slave.
[ED] And after
everything I've--
[AL] Winry said
she's making tea
to go with the
apple pie she's baking.
[ED]
Oh... okay.
[AL]
Wowww...
You can see the entire
countryside today, huh...
[ED]
Yeah.
[AL]
It's so vast.
[ED]
Yeah.
[AL]
So...
I've been thinking
about something lately.
[ED]
Me too...
And I bet we're
thinkin' the same thing.
[MRS. BRADLEY]
So tell me...
How's work been lately?
[GRUMMAN]
Exhausting!
There's a new
problem every day
and they're sending
me to an early grave.
But I've got help...
Mustang's hard at
work in the east...
And General
Armstrong's holding down
the northern front
with her iron fists...
I might be able to
remain the Fuhrer
for some time with the
two of them by my side.
[GRUMMAN]
I'm grateful to have them.
[MRS. BRADLEY]
You aren't going to turn
the throne over
to a younger man?
[GRUMMAN]
Not just yet...
Amestris needs a
man of experience.
[MRS. BRADLEY]
Oh, does it...?
That sounds a
bit like something
my late husband
might have said.
[MRS. BRADLEY]
I never met a man
more devoted to his work.
[GRUMMAN]
I remember...
I doubt that I can
compare to his...
...devotion
to our country.
[MRS. BRADLEY]
Oh, Selim, dear...
What's wrong, sweetheart?
[SELIM]
This little bird is hurt.
Can we help it?
[MRS. BRADLEY]
The poor little thing...
We'll have Gramps call
a veterinarian right away.
[SELIM]
Please do...
They can fix it, can't they?
[MRS. BRADLEY]
It'll be fine, honey...
Now go on and
take him to Gramps.
[GRUMMAN] He has certainly
grown up to be a kind boy.
[MRS. BRADLEY]
Yes...
Everyone was against
me raising him...
but he's such
a wonderful boy.
I knew that there was
nothing to worry about.
[GRUMMAN]
We're gonna keep an eye on him
a little while longer.
[GRUMMAN] If he happens to
develop any odd behaviors...
[GRUMMAN] You understand
what must be done.
[MRS. BRADLEY] I'll see to
it that never has to happen.
[GRUMMAN]
Homunculi and humans...
Is it truly possible for us
to live in peace
with one another?
[GRUMMAN] I guess it doesn't
matter how old you get...
New possibilities
are always exciting.
[GRACIA]
So is Edward bummed out
that he's stuck
with his metal leg?
[AL]
He's okay with it...
He said that it serves
as a nice reminder
to keep him in
line for the future.
[GRACIA]
Oh.
[AL]
And besides...
He thinks that Winry
would get depressed
if she had nothing to fix.
[GRACIA]
Oh, c'mon...
Now that's just silly.
[GRACIA]
It's nice to see you...
I'm so happy
you're normal again.
And I know he's
happy for you.
[AL]
We've been treated so well...
So many people have
cared for both of us...
And now...
For all this compassion...
from people like
you and Mr. Hughes...
We feel like it's our
turn to repay the happiness
that's been given to us.
[GRACIA] Isn't that like
what the alchemists believe...
Equivalent exchange?
[AL]
No...
It's equivalent
if you take ten
and then give ten back.
But if you take ten...
and then add
something of yourself...
you return eleven.
[AL]
It's not much...
but it's an all new principle
that we're trying to establish.
And now we just
have to go out
and prove that
it actually works.
[GRACIA] So I take it
you've got something in mind?
[AL] We're still
haunted by the memory
of a little girl
that we once knew...
We weren't able
to save her...
And we will
never forget that.
[WAITRESS]
Come on in!
[AL]
Mr. Gerso! Zampano!
[ZAMPANO]
Hey, Al!
[GERSO] There's plenty
of food. Dig in!
[AL]
Thanks!
Excuse me...!
Could I have
some milk here
when you get a chance?
[WAITRESS]
Coming up!
[ZAMPANO]
So then...
You've paid all your regards?
[AL]
Yes.
[ZAMPANO]
Then the time is nigh.
[GERSO]
You ready?
[AL]
I'm off to Xing!
[AL] May's gonna
teach me everything
there is to know
about Alkhahestry.
But I'm not
stopping there...
I'm gonna travel
all over the east...
and study everything
I can about their cultures.
[AL] I wanna
see all I can...
and learn all I can...
and meet new people.
[AL]
So you guys...
You're really coming along?
[ZAMPANO] Hell yes we're coming!
[GERSO] Hell yes we're coming!
[GERSO] Good things
are bound to happen
if we stick with you!
[ZAMPANO] And you
can't argue with us...
[ZAMPANO] That's based on...
[GERSO] That's based on...
[ZAMPANO] Our animal instincts!
[GERSO] Our animal instincts!
[PIG] Rhee-rhee!
[FROG] Ribbit-ribbit!
[ZAMPANO] The truth is...
[ZAMPANO]
We're gonna find a way
to get our original
bodies back...
You're the one who told us
that we should never give up.
[GERSO] You said
to act for ourselves
and not leave it to others.
[AL]
Mm-hmm.
[GERSO] So your brother
isn't going with you?
[AL]
Nope.
I'm gonna take the east...
and Brother's heading west
to learn from that region.
And if we then combine
the knowledge of
east and west...
We might be able to
prevent the tragedy
that befell Nina
from happening again.
[AL]
But that's not all.
We've got more in mind...
It's not just for research.
[AL]
It's an enormous world...
and we want to see it all.
[WINRY] Make sure
to oil it everyday.
[ED]
Right.
[WINRY] And please keep
the screws tightened.
[ED]
Yeah.
[WINRY]
Dry it off immediately
when you get
out of the tub.
[ED]
Fine.
[WINRY]
Are you even listening?
[ED]
Yeah.
[WINRY]
There's your train.
Knowing you...
You're probably gonna
break it within a month
and have to come
home for maintenance.
[ED] Yeah, yeah...
You're probably right.
[WINRY] Well, whenever
that does happen...
Just call me to
make an appointment.
[ED]
Sure.
An appointment?
[WINRY]
What's wrong?
Listen, Winry...
Well, what...?
Just come
out and say it.
Equivalent exchange!
Huh?
[ED] I'll give half
of my life to you
if you give half
of yours to me!
[WINRY]
Awww... Come on...
Do you have to treat
everything like alchemy...?
The whole equivalent
exchange thing is just nonsense.
[ED]
What'd you say?
[WINRY]
It's nonsense...!
How 'bout I just
give you my whole life?
[WINRY] Uh...
Maybe not all of it...!
Ninety, maybe
eighty percent?
Seventy...?
That's not enough...
But eighty-five... Yeah...!
Eighty-five is
a good number!
[WINRY]
What?!
Shut up!
[ED]
I'm sorry, really!
[WINRY]
Edward!
[ED]
You are so incredible...
You knocked
equivalent exchange
flat on its butt
in just a few words.
[WINRY] Uh...
And what's that mean...?
Are you making fun of me?
[ED]
Not at all!
[ED] Thanks for
cheering me up...
I'll miss you...
Goodbye for now.
[WINRY]
Come home soon.
[train whistle]
[FEMALE STATION HAND]
Ohh...
So I see Edward's doing
some traveling as well...
Why can't those boys just
settle down for a while?
[WINRY] It's good for
them to keep moving.
[WINRY] Men who sit around
doing nothing are boring.
[ED] There's no such thing
as a painless lesson...
They just don't exist.
Sacrifices are necessary...
You can't gain anything without
losing something first...
Although... If you
can endure that pain...
And walk away from it...
You'll find that you now
have a heart strong enough
to overcome any obstacle.
[ED] Yeah...
A heart made fullmetal.