- Three Days Later -
Where...
... am I?
Medical Offices (After Hours) School Infirmary
The school infirmary.
School infirmary?
You guys...
Why are you still here?
Don't push yourself.
I'm okay, Kanade-chan.
It looked like it was pretty rough even for you, Yurippe.
And you called yourself a leader?
Seriously, you guys.
What are you doing here?
There shouldn't be any Kage anymore.
There's nothing standing in the way now.
Yeah, we know.
Well then...
But you're still here, aren't you?
You're still here.
Me?
I see...
What should I say to that...
What's wrong?
This is just a guess, but...
I think the troubles that held Yuri back are fading away.
What?
Is that true, Yuri?
Huh?
Um... well, that's...
Alright.  Let's just use my hypnotism to find out-
Get away from me!
Judging by that response, it sounds like we got it right.
Huh?  Wait, that's not right at all.
I'm the leader after all.
If my problems went away that easily...
I'd be the laughingstock.
Right?
Then, let's use my hypnotism to-
You're right!
They're all gone now!
Is something wrong with that?!
Oh, she admitted it.
Kanade-chan, you're mean.
You're just antagonistic by nature, Yuri.
You...
Good comeback.
But... that kinda makes me happy.
What does?
You called me Yuri.
Why?
Because...
It makes us seem like friends.
Friends...
You're right.
Looks like our preparations weren't wasted, huh?
Right.
Preparations?
Is something gonna happen?
There's something we want to do before the end.
Something Kanade's never done before.
Huh?
What is it?
Where's everyone else?
They've all moved on.
I see.
I'm glad to hear it.
It's because everyone helped each other out.
Not without some trouble, though...
Hmph.  It was only too easy for God.
But, one way or another...
Everyone had a pretty good time living here.
I've come to understand that.
I think that's thanks to you as well, Yurippe.
I see.
Oh yeah, Takamatsu was able to move on, too.
Even though he'd turned into an NPC, he returned to normal.
Oh?  That's good.
You don't seem all that surprised...
Didn't you say people couldn't return from being NPCs?
I guess the program was made so that the strength of one's feelings could return their humanity one day.
What song is that?
You were humming it to yourself when we were working earlier, too.
What was it again...?
It's that song.
The song that Iwasawa-san sang at the very end.
"My Song".
Ahh.
That song...
That one you guys broadcast to the whole school, right?
Sheesh.
It's a nice song, huh?
Yeah!
The Gymnasium?
Yeah.
"Shinda Sekai Sensen Graduation Ceremony"
We made it ourselves.
Kanade did the writing.
Really?
Kanade-chan, you've never had a graduation?
I was wondering if it might be fun.
It's not fun at all.
It looked like you were having fun when you were writing the letters out.
The girls usually cry.
Hmph.  Girls are always like that.
Alright, shall we begin?
Huh?  Right now?
What do you think you changed for?
No, I just...
I was wondering if we'll really disappear.
I'm not sure my heart is ready for this yet.
What?
And you called yourself a leader?
What's with you?!
You know...
Now that everyone's gone, you kinda lost your leader aura.
R...really?
Yeah, something's definitely changed.
Huh?  How?
Lemme think...
Yeah, I guess you've become more girly.
Well... should I be happy about that?
Or should I be mad?
Now that the fighting's over, you're an innocent and naïve little girl again.
So Yurippe has a cute side too.
Cu-
Yuri sure is interesting.
Alright, let's start!
"Shinda Sekai Sensen Graduation Ceremony"
Opening address!
Let us begin!
For those who fought in the Afterlife...
The Shinda Sekai Sensen (Afterlife Warfront) Graduation Ceremony will begin!
Now we'll begin by singing the War Anthem!
War Anthem?!  What's that?
The song of the SSS.
Kind of like a replacement for the school song.
I don't remember writing anything like that.
Kanade also wrote it.
You wrote it?
And wait, you're not even in the SSS!
Oh, don't worry about it.
Alright, here's the lyrics.
What's the melody?
School songs usually tend to sound alike, right?
Just wing it.  You'll be fine.
Alright...
Here we go!
Osora no shinda sekai kara
お空の死んだ世界から
From the afterlife in the heavens
Okurishimasu okiraku nanbaa
送りしますお気楽ナンバー
We bring you a lighthearted number
Shinu made ni kuttoke
死ぬまでに食っとけ
Let's all eat some before we go
Maaboo doufu
マーボードウフ
Szechuan Tofu
Aa, maaboo doufu, maaboo doufu
ああ、マーボードウフ、マーボードウフ
Ahhh, Szechuan Tofu, Szechuan Tofu
What the hell is with this song?!
Someone should have checked this! I actually just sang that!
Well, Kanade-chan worked hard and seriously to write it.
There's no need to get so upset.  Right?
Seriously?
It says right here in bold characters "lighthearted number".
But... how do I say this?
It feels like it's full of Kanade's feelings.
Where?
From start to finish.
I guess you're right.
You did it, Kanade-chan!
Yeah!
What's next?
Next is...
Graduation Diploma Conferment!
Do we have those?
We made them.
Mostly Kanade again.
So, where's the principal who'll present them?
That would be me!
Uh....
That's right, I lost at Rock-Paper-Scissors!
You got a problem?!
Hmph.  The role suits you.
Why do I always end up doing crap like this?!
Alright.
Let's get started!
UTW Presents:
Graduation Diploma Conferment!
Now then...
Tachibana Kanade!
Right!
Next.
Nakamura Yuri!
Yes!
That looks good on you.
Leave me alone.
Graduation Diploma
Miss Nakamura Yuri
This certifies your
extraordinary efforts
made for the
sake of everyone
in this school.
Shinda Sekai Sensen
Idiots...
Next.
Naoi Ayato!
Yes!
Praise me.
Jeez.
Um... thank you for your efforts!
Otonashi Yuzuru!
Yes!
"Otonashi Yuzuru - Shinda Sekai Sensen Graduation Diploma"
This certifies your extraordinary efforts made
for the sake of everyone in this school.
Take that off.
Alright.
Hinata Hideki!
Huh?!
Uh.  Yes!
What do I say?  I'm at a loss.
Thanks, man.
Same here.  You've really helped me out.
"Shinda Sekai Sensen Graduation Ceremony"
A formal speech from the Graduating Class Representative!
As I look back on my time here, many things have happened.
When I came here, the first person I met was Nakamura Yuri-san.
She suddenly explained to me that I had died.
And then...
I learned that everyone who remained in this world after death...
... was unable to accept their past lives.
They were rebelling against God.
I, too, fought as a member of their group.
However...
After getting my memory back,
I was able to accept the life I had lived.
That was... an irreplaceable experience.
I wanted everybody else to be able to experience it, too.
They had fought back for so long.
It was a very difficult thing to do.
But they were all...
... able to help each other.
Believe in each other.
These people gathered together in a Warfront centered around Nakamura Yuri-san.
They turned their strength into courage,
and began to accept their past lives.
Everyone, in the end,
looked straight ahead and disappeared.
And the five of us who remain here will also graduate today.
Even if I forget the faces of the comrades I've spent my time here with,
I... will never forget these bonds etched into my soul.
The time we spent together was truly wonderful.
Thank you all so much.
Representing the graduating class...
I'm Otonashi Yuzuru!
All stand!
Sing "Aogeba Toutoshi"!
TL note: This is a traditional graduation song in Japan.
Aogeba toutoshi waga shi no on
仰げば尊し 我が師の恩
As we look with respect upon our debt to our teachers
Oshie no niwa ni mo haya ikutose
教えの庭にも はや幾年
Even in this garden of learning, how fast these years have gone by
Omoeba itotoshi kono toshitsuki
思えばいと疾し この年月
As we think upon them, these months and years have flown by too soon
Ima koso wakareme
今こそ 別れめ
For now, we must part
I-
いー
And-
You're too slow!
What?!
It's obvious you were too fast!
No way, it's your fault you were too slow!
We came together pretty well, huh?
You really are different when you're with Otonashi!
Let's go!
Iza saraba
いざ さらば
And thus, this is farewell
Closing Address!
With this...
The Shinda Sekai Sensen Graduation Ceremonies have come to an end!
Graduating students...
Dismissed!
Hmph.  I don't want to see any women crying...
I'm outta here.
Aren't you the one crying?
Otonashi-san.
If I'd never met you, Otonashi-san...
I...
I wouldn't have been able to move on...
But...
I...
I won't lose my way any more.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.  Off you go.
Thank you... so much.
Is he gone?
Now then...
Whose turn is it to cry next?
I'm not gonna cry.
Kanade-chan.
I'm sorry I always fought against you.
I wonder why we weren't friends sooner.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
You know, as the eldest daughter,
I always had to take care of my rambunctious siblings for my parents.
I learned a lot of things from you, Kanade-chan.
You seemed so ignorant about the ways of the world,
so I was really worried about you.
We could've done... so much more.
We could've done so much more, and had so much more fun.
If only we had more time...
But... this is goodbye, isn't it?
Yeah...
Goodbye.
Kanade-chan.
Yeah.
See ya.
Thanks, Yuri.
You really helped me a lot.
Good work, Leader.
Alright.  We'll meet somewhere again.
If we're going in order, I guess I'm next.
I can go first.
What are you talking about?
Don't go off and leave Kanade-chan behind.
I'll go.
Alright...
Yeah.
I'll go.
Thanks for everything.
Without you, nothing would've ever started.
We also wouldn't have an ending like this.
I'm grateful for it.
It was practically by accident.
If you think about it, I wasn't supposed to be here anyway.
What do you mean?
In the end...
I was able to find fulfillment in my previous life.
But, I lost those memories,
and ended up wandering into this world.
It's because I remembered all of that...
that I was able to experience what a fulfilling life is like.
So that's how it was.
You really were something special, weren't you?
Like I said, it was by accident that I ended helping everyone out.
I see.
Well, let's not talk forever about it.
I'm heading out now.
Yeah.
If you see Yui, give her my regards.
I should still have some luck left over, right?
I'll be sure to use it all up!
Alright!
See ya, buddy!
Um...
How did you like the ceremony?
Was it fun?
Yeah.  Very.
But the end is kinda lonely, huh?
Yeah, but it's like the start of a journey.
Everyone is looking forward to starting a new life.
Isn't that a good thing?
You're right.
Hey...
Let's go outside.
Maybe get some air...
Okay.
Hey, Kanade...
Do you want to stay here?
It just kinda hit me...
Think about it.  Just like Yuri and Hinata...
Sent off from a cruel life...
there'll be others who'll come here, right?
You're right.
Just like Yuri and everyone, they might come here,
and suffer forever.
Rebelling against their former lives.
Maybe...
But you see...
If we stay behind,
for those new guys, just like this time,
we can show them how wonderful it is to be alive.
We can help them graduate.
It's possible that I was sent here for that purpose.
So...
Will you stay here with me?
Kanade, if you were to stay with me,
even if it's in this world,
I won't ever be lonely.
I may have said this before, but...
I want to be with you.
I want to stay with you from now on.
Because I...
Because, Kanade...
I love you.
Why... aren't you saying anything?
I don't want to say it.
Why?
If I tell you my feelings,
I'll disappear.
Why?
That's because...
I came here to thank you.
What do you mean?
I...
I'm the girl who was able to live on thanks to your heart.
It's your heart that beats in my chest, even now.
I had only one regret.
I was never able to thank the person who gave me my youth.
I've always wanted to thank him.
With that one regret remaining in my heart, I wandered into this world.
That's...
But...
How did you know it was me?
I realized it when I first stabbed you.
You didn't have a heart.
Kimi ga oshiete kureta n da mou kowakunai
きみが教えてくれたんだ　もう恐くない
You taught me that there's nothing to be afraid of.
But, just from that you...
You regained the rest of your memories
because you were dreaming on my chest.
Nigitteite kureta
握っていてくれた
This hand that I've been holding,
Kono te wo hanasanakya dame da～
この手を離さなきゃだめだ～
it's time for me to let it go.
You were reminded of the sound of your own heartbeat.
That's...
Hitori demo yuku yo
一人でもゆくよ
I'll continue on alone.
Yuzuru?
Please...
Tatoe tsurakutemo
例え辛くても
Even if it might be painful.
What you said to me before...
Minna de mita yume wa kanarazu motteku yo
みんなで見た夢は　必ず持ってくよ
I'll definitely bring with me, the dream we all saw together.
Can you say it again?
I... don't want to.
If I do that, you'll disappear!
Minna to ga ii na
みんなとがいいな
I want to stay with everyone.
Yuzuru!
Please.
I can't do it!
Minna to ga yokatta
みんなとがよかった
Being with you all was so wonderful.
Yuzuru!
Demo mezameta asa dare mo inai n da yo
でも目覚めた朝　誰も居ないんだよ
But when I wake in the morning, nobody's here anymore.
All that you've come to believe...
Let me believe it, too.
That being alive is...wonderful.
Yuzuru.
Kanade...
Mou furikaettemo
もう振り返っても
Now when I turn around,
I love you so much.
Let's always be together.
Dare no kage mo nai
誰の影もない
I don't see anyone else's shadow.
Yeah.
Thank you, Yuzuru.
Mizutamari dake ga hikatta
水溜りだけが光った
Just a shining pool of water.
Together, forever and ever!
Yeah.  Thank you.
Ikiteru koto sore wa tachimukatte yuku koto
生きてること それは　立ち向かってゆくこと
Living is what we were fighting against.
I love you, Kanade.
Thank you so much.
Kanade...
Sore ga wakatta nara
それがわかったなら
Now that we understand that,
Thank you... for loving me.
Ato wa fumidasu yuuki dake～
あとは踏み出す勇気 だけ～
all that's left is the courage to advance.
Please don't disappear!
Kanade.
Kanade!
You gave me your life.
Thank you...
Hitori demo yuku yo
ひとりでもゆくよ
I'll continue on alone
... so much.
Shinitaku natte mo
死にたくなっても
Even if I want to die
Koe ga kikoeru yo
声が聞こえるよ
I can hear a voice
"Shinde wa ikenai" to
死んではいけないと
Telling me "not to"
Tatoe tsurakutemo
例え辛くても
Even if I'm suffering
Kanade!
Yami ni tozasarete mo
闇に閉ざされても
And engulfed by darkness
Kokoro no oku ni wa
心の奥には
Inside of my heart
Akari ga komotteru yo
あかりが灯ってるよ
A small light is hidden away
Megutte nagarete
巡って流れて
As things shift and change
Toki wa utsuroi da
時は移ろいだ
And time begins to fade
Mou nani ga atta ka
もう何があったか
I can't remember
Omoidasenai kedo
思い出せないけど
What happened anymore.
Me wo tojite mireba
目を閉じて見れば
But when I close my eyes
Minna no waraigoe
みんなの笑い声
I can hear everyone's soft laughter
Nazeka sore ga ima
何故かそれが今
For some reason right now
Ichiban no takaramono
一番の宝物
That's my greatest treasure in the world.
UTW Staff
Translator:
Ershin
Timer:
Kusion
TS/Karaoke:
ar
TLC/Editor/QC:
Raze