STOP
Taichi!
The sun's up! Wakey-wakey!
You'll be late for school if you don't get up now!
Yeah...
Okay, I'm up.
Hurry and come downstairs.
Man, I slept like a baby.
It wasn't a dream?
Yui, breakfast is ready.
Sorry, Iori.
I overslept again.
Don't worry about it.
I know you must be tired.
Take your time.
You can drink this before you go.
Oh, I forgot the sugar.
Thank you.
It's fine like this.
Oh, was it too hot?
No, it's okay.
Oh...
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
New Message
Yui
Was it a dream?
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
What's up, Yoshifumi?
Huh?
Talking to a friend?
I-It's nothing!
Please don't hover over me!
Are you heading out, Himeko?
No, I just like standing here.
That's ice cold.
You'll never get a boyfriend like that.
Whoa!
Morning, Taichi.
You look tired.
You're always fired up in the morning.
That's because I don't stay up late watching pro wrestling like you.
Oh.
Morning!
Yamaboshi Academy
Inaban!
Oh, you guys came to school together today?
No, no.
We just ran into each other.
Oh?
Yui and Aoki, morning!
Yamaboshi Academy
Morning.
It's way too hot for the end of September.
This is just how I like it.
Probably because you can't even feel the seasons change.
Right?
Huh?
S-Sure...
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
What if you laugh more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Likes little sisters
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
The comic I read just now was cool.
I want to eat curry now.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi High
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry, you gotta
drink more milk
Inabaaaan
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Cooks curry
Inaba Himeko
me yui
AAAAA
We should get married
I love you
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to eat a pot of curry.
Wonder if I should.
The whole world
Let's go
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
me yui
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry
I can't go out with you
It'd be bad
I don't have the homework
for tomorrow
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
like a bird of many colors
Did you hear that?
Every month
on the 25th
Deadline
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
A Story That Had Already Begun Before Anyone Realized It
At Yamaboshi Academy,
the private school we attend, every student is required to join a club.
However, every organization is bound to have a few rogue elements.
For example, take me,
a diehard pro wrestling fan
who put the Pro Wrestling Society,
which doesn't exist, as my club of choice.
Then there's the connoisseur of cute, Kiriyama Yui,
who applied for the Fancy Club, which already closed down.
There's more: Take Aoki Yoshifumi,
who tried to join the Player's Club because he believed the rumors
that such a thing existed.
But that's not all.
There's also Nagase Iori,
who figured choosing just one club would be too hard,
so she came up with the novel idea of leaving the decision to chance,
thus allowing her homeroom teacher to pick for her.
Last but not least...
there's Inaba Himeko, who joined the Computer Club
but immediately got in a scuff with the president,
so she chose to take a different path.
Huh?
You're the only one here, Inaba?
You have eyes, dumbass.
Student Cultural Society
Long story short,
five freshmen with nowhere else to go
Student Cultural Society
joined forces to create
the Student Cultural Society.
Student Cultural Society
SCS for short.
Taichi, do you have a topic for the next edition of the SCS paper?
You bet!
Get this: "The History of Brainbuster Drop Methods in Pro Wrestling."
Most people believe the Brainbuster involves
dropping the opponent on his back,
but originally, it was about dropping the opponent on his head...
Zip it.
Uh, you're the one who asked.
I only wanted to know if you had a topic.
I don't recall asking for any elaboration on said topic.
I don't want to hear it either.
You never mince words.
'Sup?
Sorry about being late!
Oh, it's just Taichi and Inaban?
Yeah, Kiriyama and Aoki haven't shown up yet.
Lame.
I sprinted up the stairs for nothing.
Iori...
Hm?
Problem?
I'm here too, you know.
120 yen per peek.
You're charging money?
That's a pretty reasonable price, though.
What's your next topic, Nagase?
Well, I've been thinking about
what's missing from the SCS paper,
and I concluded that we need to add a sexy and dangerous element!
Nobody's reading our paper for the thrills.
It can't hurt to spice things up once in a while.
So Inaban, go for a sexy angle this time.
You can't expect an innocent high school girl to write something erotic.
I'll write the article.
You just have to model for a couple sexy shots.
Over my dead body!
Besides, you're the pretty one.
Wouldn't this be right up your alley?
Nuh-uh!
I'm more like the idol who must remain pure.
When we need something more sensual,
we turn to you.
Sensual?
I don't think high school boys are into that.
Oh.
You think they might prefer a little maturity?
How about we ask one of those high school boys?
M-Me?
Yep.
Which one of us would you rather see naked?
Y-You want me to pick?
Well...
Since I'm representing every high school guy,
the answer would be both.
3:55 PM.
Yaegashi Taichi demands that two female club members strip.
Huh?
Did you get all that, Inaban?
Of course.
This'll go in the editorial notes.
I-I know I just said it, so I can't exactly take it back,
but can you at least leave my name out of it?
Uh, please leave my name out.
Um...
What's wrong?
Well, we figured it'd be a good idea to talk to someone else.
I guess...
But now that we're here, it's like...
It's going to take a lot of courage to say this.
Spit it out!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
You see, last night...
Our souls traded places!
Huh?
I'm saying Yui and I switched places!
Like in one of those comics!
Oh, nice head shot.
The punchline wasn't worth the setup.
That wasn't a joke!
I'm being totally serious!
I'm more surprised
that Inaba hits people for making bad jokes.
Did you escape to the world of dreams
after getting shot down by Yui too many times?
That would make sense,
since you keep asking Yui out and she just ignores you.
That's not what this is about!
The same thing happened to Yui.
Right?
Yeah.
Yesterday, I woke up in the middle of the night
and found myself in a completely unfamiliar room.
When I looked in the mirror, I saw Yui's face and panicked.
Next thing I knew, I was myself again.
That's what happened to me.
I thought it was just a bad dream,
so I hid under the covers.
When I opened my eyes again, everything was back to normal.
That couldn't've been real!
Huh?
Yeah, it definitely wasn't real!
Aoki!
Don't make me part of your creepy fantasies!
You're turning on me?!
That had to be a nightmare!
So we had the same nightmare
in which we happened to switch bodies at the same time,
and everything that was moved around in your room when I panicked
was also moved around in the real world?
That's what they call a string of coincidences!
Did that make sense to you?
More or less.
It was a string of coincidences!
Besides, why would it be you and me?!
Well, you could chalk it up to fate or karma from a past life.
Q.E.D. We should start going out!
How did he arrive at that conclusion?
This is why I can't stand you!
Iori!
That creep is making stuff up!
Right. There, there.
You don't have to be so mean about it.
God, this is making no sense at all!
The two of you need to cool off a bit!
Okay, but...
It doesn't make any sense to us either.
Ah!
I left my notebook in the classroom!
Don't interrupt my train of thought!
It's no biggie.
Can I go grab it?
You're in charge here.
You don't have to ask for permission.
We can continue this later!
Iori is the only person who can get under Inaba's skin.
Iori was trying to be considerate, I guess?
Or maybe she's just clueless?
The problem is that you never know when she's doing it on purpose.
Well, why don't we have tea now?
I'll make some for Nagase.
Yeah, you're...
Huh?
I was...
My voice?
No way...
This is...
Th-These are...
Are these... those?
It's my first time touching them.
But these are a girl's...
A woman's you-know-whats?
Nagase, what are you doing?
Nagase?
U-Um...
Want me to help?
Huh?
It's more effective when someone else fondles them for you.
In many ways.
N-No, thanks.
I'll be fine.
No need to be shy.
I've got magic hands.
L-Let's take a step back, Fujishima.
We can talk this through.
Yes, let's talk...
...with our bodies!
B-Bodies?!
Taichi!
Me?!
Yaegashi?!
Fujishima, I need Taichi...
Er, scratch that.
I need me...
That's not it either.
Sorry, but I need Nagase Iori for something.
This is an emergency, so we're leaving.
We're busy right now!
I can't deny that it was about to get busy,
but please let me go, Fujishima!
See? Taichi says, I mean...
Nagase says to let her go!
The two of you sound kind of strange.
Anyway, you need to give me a good reason
before I let you take Nagase!
Just let go!
Fine then!
Stop!
N-Not my sides!
H-Hey, Nagase.
You're Nagase, right?
You're in my body right now, so don't do anything weird!
Let's just run away!
That was spooky.
I was looking for my notebook,
when all of a sudden, I was back in the club room.
Everyone was calling me Taichi.
I freaked out and ran away.
So Aoki and Kiriyama
were telling the truth.
Student Cultural Society
What is it this time?
Looks like Taichi and I traded places.
Isn't it rare to see a genuine laugh from Taichi?
Usually, there's an edge of some sort.
True.
He's pretty good looking.
He'd be popular with the girls if only he laughed more often.
Is my normal laugh really that bad?
Who gives a damn about your laugh?!
You just hurt your hand, didn't you?
Why you...
Shut up!
Inaban's really enjoying herself.
I got it.
What probably happened
was that Taichi mumbled one of his signature one-liners,
so she was going to respond with violence like usual,
but he looks like Iori now!
Which is why she stopped herself.
Pretty sad when Aoki gets to sound condescending.
But I've never seen Inaba look so happy.
Don't think I'll forget this, Tai—
Inaban, you were about to call Nagase Iori "Taichi."
That's because you guys are putting on such a weird act.
Do you really think that Taichi's capable of imitating me so well?
Inaba, I know that it's hard to believe, but you have to trust me.
I'm Yaegashi Taichi.
Yui, Aoki, what do you think?
I'm positive that Taichi and Iori have switched places.
Don't you agree, Yui?
I hate to admit it, but yes.
Oh?
Which means you're admitting that we also traded places?
Yes.
I mean, after seeing Iori and Taichi like this...
Still, shouldn't you be a little more skeptical?
Well, once you've experienced the switch, it's like, "So that's it?"
I'm getting a headache.
I'll ask you one more time.
You guys aren't fooling around or anything like that?
Iori and Taichi have really switched bodies?
Yeah.
Which means you should know information only Taichi would know, right?
Yeah,
you can ask me anything.
I expect an answer right away.
Of course.
What's the title of the last adult film that Taichi borrowed from Aoki?!
"Big Boobed High School Gir..."
Wait!
How could you ask that question?!
You don't even know the answer!
That doesn't matter.
Aoki can verify your answer.
Well, Taichi?
What's the answer?
Uh...
Big boobs, huh?
Uh, Inaba?
Could you let me whisper the answer in Aoki's ear?
Well, Aoki?
That was the correct answer, Captain Inaba!
And I also got to hear Iori talk dirty in the process!
Wait.
Did I just get hosed?
Now that we've established that both male club members like big boobs,
I'll find out if this is really Iori.
I-Is Inaba using this verification process
to get revenge for making fun of her?
I need to make sure I never get on Inaba's bad side.
Wait!
I-Inaba!
Is that true?!
It's true.
But I guess that's what it means to grow up.
What did Inaba just tell her?
So you've switched bodies.
I guess it's true.
If I compare the likelihood of Taichi reacting in such an animated fashion
to the likelihood of two people swapping bodies,
the latter is easier to swallow.
How am I supposed to interpret that assessment?
So, what are you going to do next?
Hm, what to do?
Aoki, Kiriyama, how long were you in each other's bodies?
Thirty or forty minutes, I think.
Is time a factor?
Or mayb—
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
We're back to normal!
Seriously?
I have a feeling that it was all a dream.
Well, let's just say it's been a strange day.
I don't get it.
Was this a one-day thing?
Or something that only happens to the four of you?
Anyway, we probably don't want to mention this to anyone else.
No point in making our families worry.
Yeah, I doubt anyone would believe us.
Was this really a one-day thing?
Hey, welcome home.
I'm home.
Hey, Himeko.
You're home?
You've got the wrong house.
What's wrong?
You look out of it.
Nothing's wrong.
This is how I always look.
Hey, are you okay?
You didn't look too good this morning.
Oh, I'm fine.
I just didn't get enough sleep.
Nothing you need to worry about.
Hello?
Oh, Mom?
Oh, you're gonna be late?
It's fine.
I already ate.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Bye.
Taichi!
Oh, are you on your way home?
Yeah, I had a meeting that ran late.
I'm exhausted now.
Sounds like you had a rough day.
Want some ice cream?
Taichi, you should quit spoiling me.
I'm in fifth grade now!
You don't want any?
Oh, I do.
Some Fascinating Humans
Next Time
Did three people switch bodies this time?
What does a little-known plant have to do with anything?
We can't wait until something goes wrong!
That's not who I am.
My daily life, gone with the flow of time
seemed like a dream beyond what my senses could appreciate
I don't understand, I don't understand
So I mumble, still little more than a child, and dream
Maybe I'm a coward
It shouldn't matter
I wish I could be stronger
Onto that sort of facade,
my weak cries,
scattered feelings,
and changing intentions
the sun shone
You were the only one that mattered to me
I knew that
Maybe
.              .
hi       to
ra        n
do      m
.               .
.              .
If we do our best
me yui
I love my sister
Tune in next time!
Inaba
Let's go!
I wanna eat curry