Absent-Choinded
Absent-Choinded!
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
#2
High-brow
Choi
Are you doing well, my prince?
Tamaya
I'm fine.
I've had many new experiences since I've come here.
Tamaya
And tonight'll be another first for me: a ladies-only sleepover!
Let's party!
You're supposed to wear sleepwear to parties over here, is it?
Nah, this is called a pajama party.
It's a party where we talk till we drop.
And what are you supposed to talk about?
Anything goes!
No mochi allowed.
What?
No carpentry allowed either.
How could you reject who I am?
Is my fortune-telling banned too?
Nah, we'd actually like you to tell some fortunes.
Dela isn't around, so I'll use my sixth sense!
Sense?!
She's likely to have a really sharp one!
What fortune would you like me to tell?
Luck with money, I guess?
Luck with money...
You have it, Kanna.
Loads of it!
Yay!
I can smell money all over you.
I think that's probably the smell of hammers and nails.
Luck with metals, huh?
Hmm...
Not that I mind.
What fortune will you have told, Midori?
I'll—
Love fortune.
Huh?
You'll be lucky with love, Midori.
I can see you covered head-to-toe in love and romance.
What exactly is it that you can see, Choi?!
She just said she saw you covered head-to-toe in love and romance.
So you'll be popular forever, huh?
That doesn't make me all that happy...
And you, Tamako?
You can ask for anything!
Let's see...
Oh, there are these bagels, right?
Yeah.
Aren't they all, like, sticky?
So I think the texture itself can make it all over the globe.
Tell me if mochi bagels will be a huge hit in, let's say, the US.
I said no mochi allowed!
What?!
Let's talk about more girly things.
Such as?
Such as fashion or makeup!
That sounds wonderful.
I found a stick of lip in a really mature and cute color!
Lip?
She's talking about lip cream. You smear it on your lips.
This is a metallic purplish red.
Oh wow, it looks like red bean paste! Do want!
Why don't you just put red bean paste on your lips, then?
Metallic?
That means it's shiny.
Shiny lips? That sounds great!
Uh, I think you're all a bit off...
A-Also, this here's a skin-whitening pack!
I hear it's great.
Will just my face turn white if I use that?
Nope.
Oh, right. This had nothing to do with Choi.
I figured we could get some nail art done.
Nail art? What's that?
You paint them a different color or draw things on them.
Or you could just stick these things on.
Wow, they're so shiny!
Oh, these are supposed to make you look all high-brow, huh?
Go ahead and use them.
Can I?!
I made myself all high-brow!
Choi...
That's the wrong kinda brow...
Absent-Choinded!
Absent-Choinded