[narrator] February 15th.
[calm music playing]
[Komi sighing]
[Komi grunting]
[Komi] Those chocolates I gave you
are the ones that turned out the best.
Oh, you shouldn't have!
- Thank you so much!
- [Komi gasping]
POOF
DASH
[Hitohito] K-Komi?!
REALIZATION
BALL
[Komi shuddering]
[Shuko] Shoko?
Don't you have to leave soon?
[Komi shuddering]
[Shuko] What's wrong? Are you sick?
Are you pretending to be a pork bun?
Are you cold?
Something happen at school yesterday?
Oh.
Oh, I get it.
[Komi grunting]
Shoko! You need to rise and shine
and go to school, honey!
Aww. If you stay home from school today,
you'll miss out on getting an award
for perfect attendance!
Is that what you want?
[Komi grunting]
[Shuko] Ah. She came out.
[dramatic music playing]
[railroad crossing warning blaring]
[narrator] When a person
has extreme social anxiety,
otherwise known as social phobia,
they struggle to communicate with others.
But take this into consideration.
It doesn't mean that they don't want
to form long-lasting connections
or friendships.
[opening theme music playing]
[music fades]
[whimsical music playing]
[Komi grunting]
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey, good morning!
-[Komi gasping]
[Onemine] Thanks for the chocolates
yesterday. They were good!
[Komi grunting]
YOURS WERE GOOD TOO.
[Onemine laughs] Thanks!
The ones I gave out were baked,
so you don't have
to finish them in a hurry.
You got lots of chocolates,
didn't you, Komi?
- Don't get fat.
- [Komi gasping]
Hey! Hello there!
[Komi grunting]
Your chocolates were good, Komi!
A sweet offering made by a sworn ally.
[Komi grunting]
[chuckling] Not bad at all. Not bad.
K-K-K-K... Uh, Komi!
The... The chocolates
you made were delicious!
You increased the cacao percentage
for the chocolate on the outside
of this truffle to create
a perfect harmony with the sweet flavor...
- [speaking indecipherably fast]
- [students gasping]
[Makeru seething]
[Makeru] I... I lost!
[announcer] You lose.
[Komi gasping]
[indistinct chatter]
[Komi sighing]
SLIDE
What's wrong, Komi?
Oh, hey! Good morning, Komi.
PRESSURE
[Hitohito] Huh? Um...
- [Komi gasping]
- [Hitohito] Why are you?
CREAK
[Hitohito] Uh, never mind. It's nothing.
I haven't seen that look on Komi's face
in a really long time.
[narrator] Tadano felt
like it wasn't a bad thing.
[Komi breathing intensely]
[Hitohito] I wonder what's wrong.
She doesn't look like she's angry.
Oh. Maybe it's because
I ran after her last night?
Or maybe I said something weird.
No. The more likely scenario is
that I didn't do anything in particular
in the first place.
[Hitohito moaning]
[narrator] She's straining her face
so no one notices she's embarrassed.
[Hitohito] Oh. I should tell her
what I thought about the chocolates.
Oh, about those chocolates.
They tasted so delicious.
Thanks for giving me that gift last night.
- [Komi gasping]
- [Hitohito] Komi?
[intense music playing]
MISSION 71
"IT'S JUST RIPPED TIGHTS."
Okay, everyone. Return your lab equipment
from the experiment.
[students] Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
[fabric tearing]
[Yamai] Hello! I'm Ren Yamai!
Today, like I do every day,
I'm sitting in the seat that gives me
the best view of Komi's beautiful legs.
[Yamai gasping] Komi's beauty
is first-class today, as always.
She's so dazzling.
The energy contained in her light is going
to evaporate the moisture from my eyes.
Or maybe it's gonna coagulate
all of my proteins!
[Yamai gasping]
[Yamai] A snag?
[Yamai gasping, squealing]
[Yamai] N-No!
This is terrible! It's just scandalous!
I... I've gotta get a video.
A video just for me!
No! I can't let anyone else
in the class see this!
I know what to do!
You're gonna just have to hide
behind me, Komi!
I... I've gotta hide it and make it
look natural so that no one notices!
It's gotta look natural!
[Yamai grunting wildly]
[Hitohito] Uh, Yamai?
[Yamai] If I tell her now,
Komi's gonna be so embarrassed!
But if I don't tell her,
she'll be embarrassed when she gets home!
[Yamai gasping]
I'm going to protect her on her way home!
What... what should I do?
[Yamai yelling] No! No, Ren Yamai!
You were about to touch
Komi's snag just now.
You were subconsciously trying
to make the snag bigger!
I... I want to rip it.
-I want to rip her tights to shreds.
- [Hitohito] Um...
[Yamai] I wanna see Komi
with her clothes falling off!
- [Hitohito] Yamai? Um...
- [Yamai] I can't! No, Ren Yamai!
[Yamai groaning, gasping]
- [Yamai] I got it!
- Yamai?
[indistinct chatter]
- [Yamai] Komi?
- [Komi grunts]
Komi, there's a snag in your tights
on your upper-left thigh.
[Komi gasping]
[Yamai] It's okay. Don't worry.
I always carry around an extra pair
of 80 denier tights.
And it's the exact same brand you wear!
[Komi gasping]
[Komi shuddering]
Come on. We can change in the bathroom.
- Let's both go!
- [Hitohito] Uh...
[dramatic music playing]
[Yamai] Did the snag get bigger?
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
[Komi grunting]
[Yamai] I should have told you sooner.
But I was worried
you'd be embarrassed if I told you.
But it would be more embarrassing
if everyone sees it. Sorry.
[Komi sighing]
[pencil scratching]
[Yamai] Uh...
"I'm glad that you told me."
[Yamai gasping]
Komi.
[Yamai crying]
[Yamai whimpering, crying]
[Yamai] Here you go.
I'll hold the old ones for you.
[bag rustling]
[Yamai giggling]
[Yamai sighing]
[Komi gasping]
[door slamming]
[upbeat music playing]
[both grunting, panting]
- [Yamai chortling]
- [Komi gasping]
[Hitohito] Huh?
- [Yamai roaring]
- [Komi shrieking]
What's going on here?
Should... Should I stop her?
- [narrator] Komi... uniform... bare legs...
- [Yamai screaming]
[Komi panting, gasping]
[narrator] He got a good look at them.
[Yamai panting]
MISSION 72
"IT'S JUST AN ONI AND HER CLUB."
[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] Akako Onigashima
is one of the girls in Yamai's group.
She's also friends with Komi.
She always has a smile on her face.
She's an energetic girl
with a good personality.
Everyone likes her.
[Akako] Oh! Hey, Tadano!
Good morning!
Oh! Hey, Onigashima. Good morning.
Sorry. I'm in a hurry right now.
See you later!
She always has so much energy.
[narrator] She even greets Tadano
with a smile on her face.
She's fun to be around. I like her.
She's ranked the number one person
who everyone wishes they had
as a childhood friend.
[Hitohito] Huh?
[Akako groaning, seething]
[narrator] But sometimes,
even she gets angry.
IRRITATED
[narrator] Onigashima is a monster
when she's mad.
Never mind. It's nothing.
[Akako] Come on!
Why are all the traffic lights red?
[dramatic music playing]
[Akako sighing] All right. Hmph.
[Akako grunting]
CAN'T GET PAST THIS GUY
[Akako seething]
[both grunting]
- [Hitohito] She's waiting again.
- [Akako seething]
[Akako muttering angrily]
[Hitohito] And her earbuds
are all tangled up!
[Akako gasping]
UNRAVEL
[Akako seething]
[Akako gasping]
TIE
[Akako seething]
[Akako gasping]
[Akako moaning]
- [narrator] A square knot.
- [Akako screaming]
[indistinct chatter]
[Akako seething]
[Hitohito gasping] Yamai's here!
Uh, uh, good.
Yamai is good friends with Onigashima.
Maybe Yamai can help her calm down.
[Akako growling]
[Hitohito gasping] Huh?
Uh, hey. Why did you turn away just now?
Oh. I didn't notice you there, Tadano.
Why did I turn away? Oh.
[dramatic music playing]
I have known her for a long time.
Ever since elementary school,
I've known about it.
When she gets mad,
no one can predict what she'll do.
[Hitohito] Huh?
[Yamai] The only way
for her to relieve stress
is eating, sleeping,
taking baths, or a batting cage.
So, you should be careful, Tadano.
Just let sleeping dogs lie. You got it?
[Hitohito] Yamai is saying something
that makes sense!
[scary music playing]
GROWL
[Hitohito] Her earbuds
are tangled up again.
[Akako grunting]
BOUNCE
[narrator] Monster meter.
When it fills up,
she turns into a monster.
[Akako seething]
[Akako gasping]
BEEP BEEP
[Akako seething]
[school bell ringing]
[Najimi] Ta-da! [laughing]
[Yamai] Finally, it's lunchtime.
I'm sure she'll calm down a bit
once she's had lunch.
- ORANGE JUICE
- SLURP
BEW BEW
[Akako moaning]
DROP
[Akako screaming, seething]
[Akako growling, snarling]
- [Akako] Hmm?
- [Komi grunting]
[tense music playing]
[Akako] Huh?
Oh. Uh, thank you so much, Komi.
[Komi grunting]
Huh? What's the matter, Komi?
[narrator] "She didn't tie this, right?
It's just tangled."
[faucet handle squeaking]
WIND WIND
[Komi grunting]
[whimsical music playing]
[Akako gasping]
[Akako whimpering]
[Akako crying]
- [Komi gasping]
- [Akako sobbing]
[narrator]
"Was I not supposed to untangle it?"
You're so nice to me.
Let's go to the batting cages together.
[Komi gasping]
KOMI LAND BATTING CENTER
We're at the batting cages!
Tadano! Tadano!
I'm gonna hit a home run! Watch!
[Najimi grunting]
MISS
[Komi grunting]
Whoa! You hit the ball, Komi!
- [Hitohito grunting]
- You're just average!
[Hitohito] Oh! She's really good!
[Komi gasps]
Komi, did you see that? I hit a home run!
NOD
[laughing] That was great, right?
[narrator] Now Onigashima and Komi
are even better friends.
MISSION 73
"IT'S JUST A PUSHOVER."
SQUEAK
[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] Amami Sato
is a first-year student in Class One.
From the teacher's view,
she sits on Komi's left.
She's one of Komi's classmates.
[Amami] Mm-hmm.
CLEAN
All right.
We're all set now.
Everyone can feel comfortable
in class today.
[narrator] Sato is nice to others.
[Amami] Oh, it's almost time!
[Amami giggling]
- RATTLE
- CLACK
[Amami] I gotta let her enjoy the feeling
of being the first one
to arrive at school.
[narrator] Sato is nice to others.
Sorry, Sato.
Can you pick up my pencil for me?
Oh, sure. No problem.
[narrator] Sato is nice to others.
Sato! Can you buy me the limited edition
chicken katsu bread at the bakery?
- Yeah, sure.
- [narrator] Sato is nice to--
[Shigeo] Sato, sorry.
Can you scratch my back!
- Yeah, sure.
- [narrator] Sato is--
Yeah, sure!
[Hitohito] Huh?
I didn't ask you anything yet.
SOCIAL AND CULTURAL RESEARCH CLUB
So do I do
what everyone asks of me too much?
- Wait. You're asking us now?
- [Amami] Wha...?
You're right.
You would do almost anything, Sato.
So, can you give me your panties?
[Ushiroda] You're horrible.
Your mom's panties.
[Ushiroda] Her mom's panties?
That's worse.
- Uh, yeah, sure!
- [Ushiroda] Are you sure?
You have got to learn to say no.
Ugh. But, really,
it's just my mom's panties.
- I can do that.
- [Ushiroda] No, you can't!
Ugh.
So let me help you practice saying no.
I'm going to ask you to do something,
and you say no. Okay?
Yeah, sure.
[Ushiroda] You know,
my parents are in serious debt.
Can I borrow 100,000 yen?
What? Yes! I'll try to get you that!
I'd do that for you, Eiko!
[Ushiroda] I told you to say no!
Then how about your grandmother's panties?
You're still hung up on that?
You're a disgusting pervert!
- Yeah, sure.
- Say no!
[Ushiroda breathing heavily]
Oh, it's just that being nice to others
feels really good, you know?
That's why
I can't turn down people's requests.
So is your great-grandmother still alive?
[grunting]
If you keep doing
what everyone asks you to do,
someone's going
to seriously trick you someday.
And if you keep spoiling people,
they won't function on their own.
Sato, sorry.
Can you hand me that ball over there?
- [Amami] Yeah, sure!
- We're not done yet!
[whimsical music playing]
[Amami] Hmm.
Am I really being too nice?
- Hey, Sato? Can you help me hold this up?
- [Amami] Hmm?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, sure!
I wonder why I ever started to question
whether I'm being too nice
to others in the first place?
[all] Thank you very much!
Oh.
[Hitohito straining]
[Amami] Whoa!
Are you all right there?
- Oh, thank you.
- [Komi shuddering]
Are you taking
that big stack to the staff room?
I could carry it.
Huh? I'm fine.
This stack is actually heavier
than it looks.
No problem! No prob! I'll be fine!
Uh, wait. Hold on!
[straining] Komi,
if there's anything you want, just ask.
[Komi gasping]
[Amami straining]
SLIDE
[Amami gasping]
[Komi] S-Sato,
you too.
[Amami] "Do not hesitate to ask."
[Amami] Huh.
You can't take them all yourself.
Let me take half of them.
If you two could just take the other half?
[Amami] Oh.
[uplifting music playing]
[Hitohito laughing]
You've left me no choice.
I'll carry some for you too.
[Hitohito] You should've carried them
from the start.
Thanks, Sato! You too, Komi!
You were both a big help to me!
- [Najimi] What about me?
- [Hitohito] Of course. Thank you too.
[Amami] Hmm.
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING, JUST ASK.
[Amami] Now that I think about it,
I've never asked someone else
to do something for me.
[Amami grunting]
[Amami] Um, Komi?
[Komi grunting]
Um, I... I come early every morning
and clean the entire classroom, actually.
It's just that... Well, I suppose
I just like wiping down all of our desks
and organizing everything
before class for everyone.
And so then, as I think about it,
no one has ever...
Well, I didn't know that asking people
to do something was so nerve-racking.
[Komi grunting]
[Amami grunting]
[Amami] Uh, if you don't mind,
could you maybe help me out?
[Komi grunting]
Oh! No! What am I asking you?
I shouldn't be doing it in the first place
if I have to ask for help!
Sorry to ask you something so weird
all of a sudden.
- [Komi grunting]
- [Amami grunting]
[Amami] Oh, thanks. Uh...
[Najimi] I'll help too!
I didn't know you did that!
Please allow me to help you out.
[Amami gasping]
[narrator] From that day on,
the Class One first-year students
made it their daily task
to clean the classroom in the morning.
[Komi grunting]
[Najimi snoring]
MISSION 74
"IT'S JUST A FIGHT."
[Komi grunting]
[indistinct chatter]
[narrator] Komi wants to ask her
what she's reading, but she can't.
Is something the matter, Komi?
Oh, what am I reading?
- It's a book about tsume shogi.
- [Komi gasping]
Wait. Do you wanna try playing?
[Komi grunting]
[Mikuni] I can't believe
she's so interested in tsume shogi!
She's so cute!
Huh? Hey, Tadano! Wanna play shogi?
[narrator] Kato is acting
like a busy-body old woman.
PUZZLES
BY SETSUJITSU FUKUI
All right. So I'm the one who made
these tsume shogi puzzles here.
I won't tell you
how many moves you need to solve them.
[upbeat music playing]
[Komi grunting]
Ah. You're right about the first move,
but for the next move...
[Mikuni] Oh, how wonderful!
Communication through shogi!
Miracles happen on the shogi board,
connecting men and women of all ages!
Shogi is wonderful!
Wait. Hold on there.
Why are you using a pawn to capture?
You should use your rook instead.
[Komi grunting]
If you move the pawn,
it's going to come back anyway, right?
Do you see my thinking?
That would be pointless.
[Komi grunting]
[Mikuni] Uh... huh?
Like I told you, if you move the rook,
you can do it in five moves.
- [Mikuni] Uh...
- Don't you think?
We've gotta move this piece
right over here.
I told you that's the wrong move.
- [gasping] Uh, um... Well, I guess...
- [school bell ringing]
Oh, how about that?
It's time for class to begin!
[pencils scratching]
[whimsical music playing]
[Komi sighing]
GLOOMY
[narrator] They were in a bad mood.
[school bell ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Najimi] Hey, listen to this!
At the construction site by my house,
there was this guy, and he was...
[Najimi giggling]
Oh, boy. What's wrong?
- Nothing's wrong.
- [Komi grunts]
[Najimi] Huh? [laughing]
What's going on, you two?
When did you become so close to each other
you started to fight?
- [Hitohito] Hmm?
- [Komi gasps]
[Hitohito] Uh...
[both groaning]
[narrator] They blushed.
[ending theme music playing]
[music fades]
[narrator] Something extra.
The way Tadano thinks,
the game will go like this and then this.
The gold general's going
to block the path.
Oh, I gotcha.
All I was thinking about
at that point was moving the king.
[Mikuni chuckling]
I'm sorry, Komi.
I guess I did jump the gun.
SMUG
[narrator] Komi is cute
when she has a smug look on her face too.
Something even more extra?
Look who's here!
I brought Komi and Tadano!
Hey, you three! It's good to see you.
[Amami] I'm sure you already know
each other. This is Ushiroda.
I sat in class behind you,
but we never got the chance to talk much.
[Amami] And this is Maeda.
He sat in front of you.
Komi, is your grandmother
still alive... [grunting]
[narrator] Seventy-three friends
left to go until one hundred.