Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Kaleido Stage.
It is a wondrous stage created
by illusory light and sound.
It is the best entertainment
show in the world,
and it moves and excites all who see it.
There was a girl who aspired
to be a part of this Kaleido Stage.
Help! Help! Help!
Help...
I'm sorry.
My name is Fool.
I am the spirit of the stage which
can only be seen by the chosen ones.
Today, I would like to present to you
the many dramas which have
developed at Kaleido Stage so far.
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
The girl who came from Japan
aspiring to be a part of Kaleido Stage:
--Sora Naegino, 16 years old.
--I'm finally here!
I'm going to pass today's
audition no matter what
and become a member of Kaleido Stage!
I will! I will! I will!
She came with high hopes,
but awaiting her was a
series of unexpected occurrences.
Stop right there!
However, she cleared all those
hurdles with her natural willpower
and unrivaled athletic prowess.
And finally...
...she arrived at the Kaleido Stage
that she dreamed of. However...
Shoot! I'm really late!
Is it over here?
Oh, thank goodness! This is the place!
Um, who are you?
Sora! My name is Sora Naegino!
I am very sorry for being late.
Oh, the auditions ended just now.
What?!
But I came all this way
from Japan for this audition.
What? Really? Okay,
then come up on the stage.
Oh, thank you very much...
No.
Oh, Miss Layla.
The auditions are over.
Layla Hamilton... It's really her!
Oh, there's a reason for
why I was late and...
No matter what happens,
a stage production begins on time.
But...
Go home.
I can't just go home like this!
Please!
I absolutely, desperately
want to join Kaleido Stage!
Miss Layla!
Ever since I was a child,
it's been my dream to
perform in Kaleido Stage.
It was the Kaleido Stage that she dreamed of.
But she was unable to audition,
and her dream to appear on stage was gone.
The show is going to start soon.
If you want, you can stay and watch.
What? Is it okay?
That's about all I can do for you right now.
Really?
Yeah.
So she was able to watch the show.
Then, suddenly...
Watch out!
My arm got twisted!
She ended up injuring a cast
member due to a misunderstanding.
--Hey! What the heck are you doing here?!
--Then, an unexpected person showed up.
Boss...
Boss?!
You fill the spot.
Huh?
What?!
She got a sudden chance to
appear on stage for the first time.
The show started while she was
full of anxiety and expectations.
Oh! A flip! Right!
Oh, man...
Oh, no!
I can't do it!
I can't perform at all!
Miss Rabbit, hang in there!
That's right...
I can't say that I can't do it.
I have to do it right now.
I have to do it!
Miss Rabbit!
I can't see below...
No!
Sora!
-Out of the way!
Mr. Yuri?!
Keep smiling until the end.
Yes, sir!
The show finished.
Sora was touched, appearing on stage
for the first time as she had dreamed, but...
You understand just how
naïve you were now, don't you?
Yes...
There is no place for you here.
Oh, Sora!
--Leave her alone!
--She'd dreamed of Kaleido Stage
since she was very young.
Was this the end of Sora's dream?
Sora!
You passed!
What?!
You're passing a girl who
didn't even audition.
Someday, the audience
will come here just to see her.
Having had her talent recognized by the boss,
she was officially allowed
to join Kaleido Stage.
However, it was also the beginning
of many excruciating ordeals.
The fateful Golden Phoenix.
Oh, everyone, good morning!
If you like cleaning that much,
can you do our share too?
What?
--Sora was admitted under
special circumstances,
--We want to go to our lessons early.
--and the other trainees
gave her a hard time for it.
What?
--So take care of it for us.
--Furthermore, the top star,
--I feel a little better now.
--Layla, made an outrageous demand.
Well, I didn't mean like that.
Why don't you show us your Golden Phoenix?
Golden Phoenix.
--A great maneuver that only Layla could do.
--Oh, no... Well...
Just so you know, I don't
acknowledge your existence here.
All right then. I'll do it!
I'll show you that I can
do the Golden Phoenix!
Really? I'll be looking forward to it.
But if you can't do it after
stating so boldly that you would,
you will leave this place.
All right.
And thus began the hard training
which determined Sora's survival.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
If you fall, make sure you
land on your back. Okay?
You don't have enough
momentum! One more time!
I never knew just swinging
would be this hard.
But I will do it no matter what!
--Thus, in order to gain the muscle strength
--During the day, she studied the stage.
--At night, she stayed late and trained hard.
--to perform various tricks,
--Sora's mental and physical exhaustion
--you have to eat a low-fat
and high-protein diet.
--neared their peak due
to this harsh schedule.
--Could it be...
She's working really hard?
Sora!
We brought you something to eat!
I know you haven't eaten anything yet.
Sora's earnest attitude
won her new friendships.
I can't believe she managed to
do all this in such a short time.
If she can just grab the bar now...
No, she still can't maintain
a beautiful pose in the air.
Before she catches the bar,
what she's doing can't be
called the Golden Phoenix.
Go, Sora!
By tomorrow...
I have to perfect it by tomorrow.
Finally, the date that
determined Sora's fate arrived.
I can't wait to see what kind of
Golden Phoenix she'll show us.
Yeah.
I've got to do it. I need
to believe in myself.
Sora's challenge was almost reckless.
Could Sora perfect the big
maneuver, the Golden Phoenix?
Under pressure that she had to immediately
withdraw from Kaleido Stage if she failed,
could Sora perfect the big
maneuver, the Golden Phoenix?
Sora's big once-in-a-lifetime gamble began.
The bar should not be my aim.
My aim should be my love, Romeo.
And then, I can be Juliet.
The Golden Phoenix!
She did it!
Sora, are you all right?
Yes. Thank you.
You're really something.
Oh, Miss Layla.
You didn't get the last part right,
but that was definitely the Golden Phoenix.
Huh?!
I guess I have to acknowledge you this time.
What?
Yuri, let's go.
Sora, you can stay at Kaleido Stage now!
So Sora became a real
member of Kaleido Stage.
And after that, she made the show successful
with Mia and Anna, who'd
become very close friends of hers.
And she kept giving hopes
and dreams to all kinds of people
during the course of her success.
Lonely Rosetta.
Rosetta?
The French diabolo prodigy
performer is finally here.
That's right. She's really a genius!
Shhh!
See you later then.
I'll be looking forward to it.
--Um, well, I'm your fan...
--Rosetta was a proud prodigy.
On the stage,
she put on a show that was nothing less
than you would expect from a world champion.
She showed a high level
of performance, but...
She's amazing.
But I wonder why? It's not that fun to watch.
She's like a well-oiled diabolo machine.
Mom, I'm bored.
Today is your last performance.
What?
As for the pay, I will pay you one
week's worth as agreed in the contract.
But you don't need to
appear on stage anymore.
Rosetta's pride was hurt.
--Wanting to do something for her, Sora...
--Rosetta!
She may be able to change.
I wouldn't mind bringing
Rosetta back on stage, but...
Oh, really?
You have to be with her.
What?
--Excuse me?
--See you later.
Oh, wait.
--Oh, no! Let's hurry, Sora!
--I've never done diabolo before.
Would Sora be able to
appear on stage with Rosetta?
Why does Kalos want me to pair up with you?
We should always expect
ourselves to perform flawlessly.
It's better not to do it
than to make mistakes.
That's all.
Rosetta's words were harsh.
But Sora never gave up.
Ken, I'm going to give it a try.
Then, on the outdoor stage...
Go, Jonathan!
Catch! What is this?!
Sora, jump in!
I did it!
Sora, you're awful!
Sora, go for it!
Sora!
Isn't it strange?
Huh?
When I'm watching Sora's
show, it makes me nervous,
because I'm worried she's
going to make a mistake.
Here!
She does, in fact, make mistakes,
--but once in a while,
--Oh, where are you, Jonathan?
--she can be incredibly wonderful.
Unbelievable, like magic.
Please watch Sora's performance today.
Sora's performance?
Yeah!
Rosetta saw Sora's
performance for the first time.
There, she saw the audience's smiling
faces as she had never seen them before.
Amazing...
It's completely different from my show.
Sora.
Rosetta! You came to see my show!
I want to see what our diabolo
performance might look like together.
Me too.
Okay.
Now, at last, it's time for the
first diabolo battle in history!
The world diabolo champion, Rosetta!
Now, let's see the long-awaited
outcome of this battle!
Start!
Doing good! Go, Sora!
Rosetta, don't lose!
Winner, Rosetta!
The applause and cheers didn't stop.
"The stage exists to entertain the audience."
Both of them etched that important
fact in their minds once again.
Thanks to your magic, Sora.
And thus, Sora climbed up
another rung towards being a star.
And, when she performed The Little Mermaid,
she overcame all sorts of ordeals
with her efforts and inborn spirit.
And she won the lead role that
she had dreamed of at Kaleido Stage.
Wonderful!
Sora played an important part admirably.
You're a new Kaleido Star.
Layla, who had been
watching how Sora progressed,
finally acknowledged her as a
full-fledged performer as well.
I look forward to working with you as well.
--You're too slow!
--And finally,
--Sora got an opportunity to perform
on the same stage with Layla,
--Yes. Sorry.
whom she had aspired to be like.
However, the difference in
their skill levels was obvious.
No matter how hard they tried,
their timing never matched.
Sorry.
So, Layla took unexpected action.
Yes?
Whoa...
Whoa!
Miss Layla... Excuse me...
Well, bye, Layla.
Thank you.
Thanks... Um... I...
I'm going to stay here for a while.
What?
I came here so I can study
your rhythms and pauses.
So, please try to learn
my moves and rhythms too.
Your moves and rhythms...
Yes.
Sora!
Let's go to the dining hall!
--Bowwow!
--Meow!
Thus, their life together suddenly started.
Sora tried hard to adjust to Layla's pace
even though she was unsure of herself.
However...
There weren't many days left
until the opening date of the show.
Their performance was far from perfect.
And around this time...
Jump!
Oh, we're too close....
I think it's better if we lower
the difficulty of the climax a little.
Are you saying you want to
make the climax scene easy?
Yes.
I will not accept it!
What?!
But, Miss Layla...
I cannot allow you to make the climax easy.
Please give us tomorrow, one more day!
They had one more day left.
At this time, they took unexpected action.
Excuse me...
We're going to start special training.
What?!
No matter how many times I repeat
the same things like I've been doing,
the final product will
be a safe and boring show.
Miss Layla...
This is a real fight between us.
A real fight with Miss Layla?
So, will you accept this challenge?
Yes.
Then their real fight
without a lifeline began.
She has such amazing spirit.
If I lose my nerve even a little,
she really is going to knock me in the sea.
If you drop your guard, you'll be shark bait.
The fate that awaited the
two of them after this was...
One more day left until opening.
The intensity of their training increased,
continuing on, even through the storm.
Amazing...
Are you reaching your limit?
No...
Really?
Miss Layla!
I think we'll be all right.
Yes... Yes!
Then came the opening day.
Would their first
co-performance be a success?
Sora!
Thank you.
I've not received this kind of
pleasant applause for a long time.
Miss Layla, I'm happy.
I'm happy and I don't know what to say.
Through this co-performance with Layla,
Sora had grown up a lot again.
But she had only just begun
walking the path to stardom.
After this, what kind of ordeals awaited her?
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation,
I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell
phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
"Next Kaleido Star"
Kaleido Stage is going
to be taken over by Yuri?
It was their last time on stage,
which they never expected to see.
Whatever will happen to Sora's dream?
Then, Sora flew to the Grand Canyon and
endured excruciating practice with Layla
in order to perfect the
legendary great maneuver.
The legendary great maneuver which
comes with a chance of losing one's life.
What will happen to her?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing Prologue To Stardom (Part 2)."
Furu, Fool!
C'mon!