Run!
Morning.
Nagi-chan, Yuuko-chan! Morning!
Why were you just standing there?
Look, look! This was stuck to my forehead!
Until now?
Yeah!
Guess that's just like you, Run.
You think?
Run-chan, morning.
Morning!
Run-chan!
Did you watch last night's episode?
Yeah! Yeah! It was so good!
Run-chan has a lot of guy friends, huh?
She sure does.
T-Tooru?!
Always working so hard.
Something up, Tooru?
Run-chan.
Slowly, quietly, floating by
Gently fading into the distant bright sky
More fickle than the wind,
my goal is beyond it
Let's go together
Take a breath and skip along,
the world's spring breath
The sun brings all our smiles together
Between "good morning" and "good bye" it's just us
We can do whatever we want
The sunlight shining down,
a brand new sky
The morning arch we promised to meet at
Waving your hand at me,
let me make today a special day
Let's start by talking
Love
Morning, Tooru!
You're as small as ever!
Don't pet me!
Why are you covered in dirt?!
Did you fall?!
Run-chan.
And then, you know what? It was completely flat!
Has Run been bullying her?!
She was almost hit by a car while chasing a butterfly.
You've got quite a job.
See you, Tooru.
Later.
See you at lunch, Tooru.
Morning!
Hi!
Hello, Run-chan?
Tooru! Long time no see!
Yeah.
Um... Can I come over now?
Yeah! Come over!
Thanks. See you soon.
Long time no see...
I haven't seen her since I started studying for the exam.
Coming!
Oh, Tooru-chan! I haven't seen you in ages!
Sorry I haven't come by recently.
Run is upstairs.
Okay.
Sorry to bother you.
I wonder if Run-chan will be happy.
Run-chan!
I got into the same high school as you!
Oh, Tooru!
Wha—
Ow!
Run! Who is this kid?!
Run-chan! Who is this?!
What was that?!
You got in? Congratulations!
Who cares if I got in!
So this is Tooru?
She really is small!
You wanted to introduce us to her?
Introduce?
Oh, that's right.
I thought you might be coming since they posted admissions today, so I called them over.
My friends from school, Yuuko-chan and Nagi-chan.
Nice to meet you.
Friends.
You'll be seeing a lot more of each other in the spring!
She's staring me down like I don't know what...
You left a pretty bad first impression.
You should explain what you were doing.
Um... It's a misunderstanding.
Run started tickling me.
We weren't doing anything weird.
We were just playing around.
What's all this about?
No!
Looks like they're already getting along really well!
Don't!
Shouldn't you stop her?
Now I'll pass out the forms for your electives.
You filled them out last year. You know the drill.
Here.
This year's homeroom teacher looks completely irresponsible...
And this is how you fill out the elective selection forms.
Does anyone have any questions?
As first year students, you might not have many choices, but you will have more as second and third years.
They have some bearing on your futures, so think them over carefully.
If anyone has any private questions about them, feel free to ask me.
I wonder if Run will be okay.
What is she doing?
Lunch, lunch!
Tooru, let's eat!
You're getting ahead of yourself there. Tooru isn't here yet.
Oh, you're right. Whoops!
She's here, Nagi-chan! That's my Tooru!
Did she... hear her call?
Oh! Those squirrel pins are cute!
Right?
They're my favorite!
I love animals.
Really? Then what's your favorite animal?
I guess I like birds.
Oh, like parakeets?
They are pretty cute.
Speaking of which...
Your hair kind of looks like one.
And they're tasty too.
What? That kind?!
Eating parakeets?! That's so cruel!
That's not the question!
Run-chan likes chicken.
Oh, that's what you meant.
You meant chicken is your favorite thing to eat.
Right! But I like any kind of meat!
Then why don't we go out for Korean barbecue sometime?
I feel like eating some galbi and dwaeji.
Now I really want to eat some...
I can almost hear the sound of meat cooking right now...
Sorry, that was me.
A ringtone?!
Your lunch looks really good.
Mind if I take some?
Sure! Here!
Thanks!
It's good!
Did you make it?
Again?!
Those two get along really well, don't they?
That doesn't look like "getting along"...
That was a good lunch, right, Tooru?
Yeah.
Run, where are you going?
Our classroom is over here.
Oh, that's right.
We were first years until just the other day. Whoops!
Come on, Run.
You might not make it in time if you don't hurry, Tooru.
See you later.
Tooru!
Run, you didn't fall asleep this afternoon.
Yup! I'm fine in the afternoon.
Are you sure you didn't wake up when you almost fell out the window?
You really need to be more careful.
Okay.
On the other hand, I get sleepy after lunch.
Oh, then how about some candy to wake you up?
Here.
Thanks.
Here. One for you too, Run.
Thanks!
That's the last one.
Oh, really?
Then I'll save it for Tooru.
Then you won't have any, Run.
We'll split it in half.
Run, you're so kind!
How will you split that candy?
Oh, I know! A cutter!
Maybe I can cut it with this!
Don't go crazy.
You'd be an idiot to get hurt over a piece of candy.
Don't worry!
Is it working?
It fell on the floor!
I told you.
I thought it would work out!
Tooru!
Thanks for waiting!
Let's go home.
What's wrong, Tooru?
I smell candy.
Do you still have some?
Candy! Candy! Candy! Candy! Candy!
No...
I forgot to throw away the bag.
That's amazing, Tooru! You can even sniff out empty bags!
Tooru loves sweet things a lot!
Sorry. We just ate the last ones.
I'll bring more tomorrow.
I want tortoiseshell candy!
Can't we make it something not sweet?
Or something with less calories...
But it's only candy if it's sweet!
Okay, okay. I'll bring more tomorrow.
What did you pick for your electives?
What are those again?
Kamade-sensei gave a talk about them.
Run was sleeping then.
Oh, that's right!
Then, why did you fall over, Yuuko?
Run looked like she would fall over, so I tried to catch her,
but then Run stopped and I lost my balance.
Hey, Tooru. What did you choose for your first elective?
Tooru?
I want to take
the same class as you.
With you.
Don't worry.
We haven't changed at all.
Yeah.
Tooru is just so cute!
Stop! Stop!
Hey, Tooru. How about we all go for something to drink?
Let go of me!
No fair, Yuuko! Let me hug her too!
Oh, she's so soft!
What are you—
Let's go, Tooru!
The chemistry of dreams and the spring wind,
doesn't feel like it'll stop
Lucky Happy, gather around here!
After always bustling around, what's next?
I don't know, but that's why it's exciting
Let's start
Wild, my pace, a master artist during class
With a plan in the corner
Where should we go? Right now is a paradise
The unease of being too tightly wound
I made it late for our date,
but we got here at the same time
This stage of wearing skirts
Just how will life be?
The chemistry of dreams and the spring wind, doesn't feel like it'll stop
Lucky Happy, gather around here!
After always bustling around, what's next?
I don't know, but that's why it's exciting
Let's start
Hey, hey.
Run really has a lot of guy friends.
I wonder what they talk about.
Tell us Yuuko-chan's three sizes, Run-chan!
Keep it a secret, okay? From the top: 88, 56, 87.
Whoa! That's nice!
Or something like that.
How do you know my sizes, Nagi?!
Later then, Run-chan.
Later.
Bye.
Oh?
They all left.
I see.
Oh, Tooru!
Run-chan.
Working hard as always, huh, Tooru?
Tooru, I brought candy just as promised.
Let's all have some later.
Why?
No!
Those two get along really well, don't they?
They sure do.
Next to me in the sunset, a silhouette tall as me
It's the end of another fun day
I've still got so much unending stuff to talk about
But it's time for us to go home
Bye, see you tomorrow, I'll text you later
Today's page is about all our smiles
Bye, see you tomorrow, thanks as always
I'm happy we could be together today too
Humhumhum, the wind and my heart are humming
At the next corner, I'll turn around and say "Bye bye"
Next Episode
Speaking of rain, there are all sorts of different kinds.
Drizzle, light rain, tears in rain.
Oh wow, you know more than I thought.
Here's a question for you, Mihorin!
What?
Yes, who are we?
Wait, you just told everyone my name.
Oh dear, Yutaka has just failed miserably.
On the next A Channel: Rainy Days are for Baths.
Wait, if we're doing the preview, then are we appearing next—
That's a secret.