It sounds ridiculous.
But once ya see it...
A shadow taking over a person.
We gotta warn Shiori!
The shadows are coming to kill, and it ain't a superstition!
She's in danger!
Kobayakawa Shiori also saw her shadow.
She's definitely in danger.
Let's go to her place now!
But...
that's precisely why I can't let Mio get anywhere near that danger.
I'm going alone.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Drifting Ashore
Koba Mart
The store's closed.
This is bad. Nothing's changed.
Hey there!
Is that you, Shinpei?
Mrs. Shiomi!
I'm so sorry for yer loss.
Th-Thank you. Uh... Good morning.
We don't got any convenience stores here.
It's ain't like Tokyo, right?
Well, I like this store.
They have green tea soft serve.
A little taste of home?
It looks closed today, though.
That's odd. They never said they'd be closed.
Class 3-1 Kobayakawa Shiori
Hey, Koba? Are ya in there?
That's strange. Are they not home?
They left it open.
Koba? You there?
Is it okay to just go in?
Ain't no problem.
Koba?
Huh? They even left the TV on.
This is weird.
Koba!
Shadows.
Shadows did this.
Totsumura's shadow did the same to him.
Didn't you anticipate this?
You coulda done something.
You coulda saved 'em.
Stop it!
They're monsters!
I refuse to get killed again.
All I can do is warn people and closely observe the results.
So, what'd ya find out from yer observation?
The food is untouched and cold.
They were probably attacked yesterday at dinnertime.
There are marks on the floor as if
someone punched it with great force.
What happened here?
Mrs. Shiomi, I'm going to look upstairs.
Okay! Thanks!
Judging from the size of the two dark stains,
they must've been adults.
Probably Shiori's parents.
Then where is she?
Hey.
So that's it.
Did you see a girl who looked just like you?
Why'd you ask me that yesterday?
It's something I didn't do last time.
You keep staring.
Is there something on my face?
Or is there something weird about my body?
No doubt about it.
Shiori.
The shadow at the funeral was Kobayakawa Shiori.
Y-You got your voice back. Are you feeling better?
That was such a stupid question.
Oh...
Mommy and Daddy told me not to say anything.
Are you going to answer...
Never mind.
No need to answer.
I'll find out later.
I caught the shadow sickness.
No...
I had it from the beginning!
Shinpei!
Well? Anyone up here?
What is it? Got a stomachache?
No.
I guess Mrs. Shiomi just saved my life.
After she called the police, I left the Kobayakawa home.
If I do nothing until noon, the same thing will happen.
That woman who I met on the ferry knows something.
Maybe I can save her.
I haven't seen her this time because the day started at the port.
She had too much luggage for a day trip.
I'll check the hotels on the island.
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Anmin-ya Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Tomarora
Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
A suit?
Yes. She was wearing a suit and had long, black hair.
61st Annual Hito Summer Festival
Well...
She had glasses.
Have you seen her?
Can't be sure. So many guests come this season.
Also...
She had huge... well...
Oh! Her!
I remember her! She came here.
Ya said so this morning.
You were looking fer this woman
with glasses and huge titties.
Huh?
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
But she didn't stay the night.
She just came to the cafe late in the day.
You should check it out too.
In the end, that woman didn't stay anywhere.
I couldn't find a trace of her.
Maybe there's not much I can do alone.
Bistro Kofune
Lunch Specials
Pork Cutlet
Fried Fish
Spaghetti Napolitan
Welcome...
Shin, how'd it go? Is Shiori okay?
Oh... yeah.
Man!
Welcome!
Totsumura.
It's hotter than—hey!
Shinpei! What's with that call last night? Ya lied to me!
What fight were ya—
Your usual lunch special with
fried shrimp and medium rice?
Ya know me well.
Huh?
Disappeared?
The entire Kobayakawa family?
Yep.
Really, Shin?
Yeah.
I heard ya went inside with Mrs. Shiomi.
Oh... yes.
Tell me about it later.
That's odd.
I just talked to Kobayakawa yesterday.
Right?
I really can't go into details yet,
but a detective is coming on the first ferry this afternoon.
His response is different.
Good!
It's probably because I stopped his shadow from killing him.
This is the real Totsumura!
Oh yeah, I got something fer ya.
Here.
That's my sister's.
Ushio came to see me the day before she died and asked me to keep it for her.
She said to give it to you if anything happened to her.
Ushio left this for me?
It was like she knew what was gonna happen to her.
Everything is so intricately complex.
Hey, Shinpei.
Sorry. Am I early?
No, I was waiting for you.
I can trust Sou.
I'll tell him everything.
Summer Time Rendering
So that's why I think...
Ya think Shiori's shadow killed Ushio, right?
Yeah.
The ligature marks show she was strangled,
and only one person was with her at the time.
Is it after Mio next?
Yes.
Can we tell shadows apart from people just by looking at 'em?
No.
I couldn't, at least.
I see.
That's gonna be a problem.
So basically, you might be a shadow yerself.
Yeah, but the same goes for you.
What are shadows? What are they?!
Calm down, Mio.
It'll be okay.
Cameras can film them, so they're living things,
not ghosts.
If they're alive, there must be a way to kill 'em.
Right, Shinpei?
That's true.
Shin, why don't we go to Hiruko now?
Huh?
Mr. Karikiri should know lots
about the history of this island.
He might also know about shadows.
That's right.
Mio and I were trying to visit Hiruko the first time too.
But it's too dangerous!
We ran into it near the shrine.
We have to stay away!
H-How about tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
That's when the summer festival is, dude.
Oh... right.
I figured you forgot.
Tomorrow's the busiest day of the year fer the shrine.
The priest ain't gonna have the time to talk to us.
Actually, the more people, the safer it should be.
The festival is a perfect time to visit Hiruko.
I'll come to Kofune at five tomorrow.
Let's decide on a secret code so that I can tell if yer a shadow or not.
Okay.
If I say "mountain," you say...
"River"?
That's the obvious answer, dumbass.
Uh... how about "The Tigris-Euphrates river system"?
Forget rivers fer a sec, Shinpei.
"Mesopotamian civilization"?
Nice one, Mio!
"Mesopotamian civilization"!
Are these two serious?
Thanks, Sou.
I'm glad you believed me.
We're buddies.
Ya trusted me enough to tell me too.
Don't completely trust him yet.
Not until ya find a way to tell shadows apart from people.
Why am I so negative?
Right.
By the way, there's something I wanna check out.
I'll let ya know if I find anything.
Jeez! We're getting soaked!
This sure wasn't in the forecast.
61st Annual Hito Summer Festival
Shin.
How long are you gonna stay?
Oh, well...
I wanted to leave shortly after the funeral, but now...
You should stay forever.
Forever?
Never mind. I didn't mean it.
I was just kidding. Gimme yer hand.
Here, take this.
Sis was wearing this necklace when she died.
She would've wanted you to have it.
Thanks.
Her birthday.
Input password
Password incorrect
July 24th
Nope.
Mountain.
What?
Yer supposed to say "Mesopotamian civilization," remember?
Oh, is it already time?
Y-Yer such a party-pooper.
It's gotta be the real you.
Shinpei! Put on some pants!
S-Sorry, Toki!
Please change quickly.
We're all ready.
Right, Mio?
D-Do I look okay?
I've never worn a yukata before.
You look...
Ya look great!
How is it?
Tokiko dressed her.
It might help to tell us apart from the fakes.
Th-That's true.
How is it?
I haven't told Tokiko anything yet.
Right. That's probably for the best.
By the way, what were ya looking into yesterday?
Did ya find anything?
Oh, that?
It wasn't nothing special. Just forget about it.
Let's quit chatting and go.
Ushio must be waiting.
Sis was really looking forward to this festival.
I'm sure she'll be there somehow.
C'mon, let's go. For her soul.
Sou, didn't you want to become a doctor?
You sound so unscientific.
Hito Shrine
Welcome! We're Gyokurin-en!
Green Soft Serve     1 Cone    180 yen
Green Tea            1 Cup     100 yen
Hey, Sou.
Yeah?
It's been two years since I left the island.
I thought I'd matured a bit,
but I'm still totally helpless.
I wasn't with her when she really needed me.
I promised I'd protect her.
You fool!
It's not yer fault she's dead!
Keep it together, Shinpei!
Focus on protecting Mio now!
Yer her brother!
I-I don't need to be told that!
If you ain't up for the job, leave Mio to me.
Welcome! We're Gyokurin-en!
Sou, you still have feelings for Mio?
Do ya have a problem with that?!
Whatcha chatting about?
Oh, uh, it's...
We were debating whether we liked boobs or butts more!
Hey!
Ugh, that's creepy.
No, don't believe him!
Shinpei, your ice cream is melting.
I'm telling you, he's lying!
Actually, I'm a little curious.
I mean, you were peeping on Mio when she was in the bath the other day, Shinpei.
What?! What the hell, dude?!
Wait! It's not what it sounds like!
Shinpei, what do you really think about Mio?
Huh? Wh-What're you saying, Tokiko?!
What I think of her?
Of course, I care about her.
We're family.
Family, huh?
Stop, Tokiko! Don't ask him weird things!
Shinpei, my old man just called.
After the fireworks and the send-off, Mr. Karikiri will be available.
Okay.
So until then...
What's up, Shinpei?
Over there, I just saw...
Why don't we go onto the shrine grounds and watch the fireworks from there?
Sorry. I'll catch up with you later.
H-Hey! Shinpei!
61st Annual Hito Summer Festival
Tuesday, July 24th
Join the island
in lighting up
the Hitogashima
summer!
Join the island
in lighting up
the Hitogashima
summer!
Procession
Fireworks
Send-off
Look after Mio!
Wh-Where's he going? Taking a dump?
Excuse me. Coming through.
Sorry.
Ushio must be waiting.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Sis was really looking forward to this festival.
Take a breath, take a breath
I'm sure she'll be there somehow.
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
Hey, Shinpei.
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
Make sure to find me.
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Ushio.
Next time
Jamais Vu