New students, congratulations on your acceptance.
Here at Ounan Middle School we value student's autonomy.
Developing individuality is our motto.
At the same time, as fellow members of society,
you'll learn to be cooperative, disciplined,
and responsible.
Excuse me, are you feeling alright?
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
I'm fine.
Next, we would like to call upon our new student representative...
Hayama Nayu-san.
Y-Yes!
Adult?
The Girl with Adult Panties
I'm starting to get nervous.
So you get nervous too, Haruka?
Well, yeah.
What about you, Yako-chan? Don't you get nervous?
Not really.
I understand how you feel, though.
It's that girl with the adult panties.
What are you talking about?
You didn't see it?
That girl...
Hayama Nayu.
She was wearing outrageous panties today, too.
I bet she wears them for work.
I heard she's a prostitute.
S-She's been engaging herself in criminal activities since elementary school?
She doesn't seem like the type to do that.
Well, to tell you the truth, she only thinks of money and erotic stuff.
But if she was chosen as the new student representative,
it means she must have the best grades, right?
It's more than just a rumor that she's a prostitute.
What?!
I'm telling you...
The area near the crotch needs to be bigger,
so that it doesn't dig into my delicate parts.
Huh? What does it dig into?
You know...
Come on, hurry up.
My...
My crotch!
You don't have to yell. I can hear you.
Keigo-san!
Hey.
You did a good job on your new student representative speech.
D-Didn't you go home?
Here you go.
Sorry, sorry.
It's more than just rumors that she's a prostitute.
Umm... I can't hear anything.
Let's see.
Those must be the panties she wore, from the last time she spent the night there.
"Wash them before returning them."
"You idiot."
Bye, Keigo-san.
Her young boy friend,
her crotch outburst,
delivery of bra and panties for her...
She is...
undeniably guilty!
You think so?
We have to confirm it!
See ya, Mizuno-Sensei.
See you at our next club meeting, Sensei.
Good bye.
Don't be late.
You too, Sensei.
I won't be late!
The new seventh graders have revitalized our school.
Takato-Sensei...
I've got to work hard to keep up.
Mizuno-Sensei, the size of that suit...
What? Is it really too tight?
I wonder if I ate too much when I went home for spring break?
You didn't bike to school in that outfit, did you?
What? You think I shouldn't?
She doesn't leave a lot to the imagination.
Good bye!
Well, I need to go back and change.
Be careful...
in many ways.
I'll get a shot of Mizuno-Sensei's-
The suspect hasn't even realized that she's being followed.
They must have agreed to meet somewhere around here.
You think so?
Her movements have become faster.
Maybe she just came to buy some underwear.
She's really excited about choosing underwear.
They've got to be for some guy.
What's so great about looking at underwear?
Every time I found an underwear...
I felt as if people were teasing me.
What's so fun about underwear?
When we were kids, boys and girls wore the same kind of underwear.
It's not like we suddenly became adults in middle school.
Our bodies keep changing every day...
but our hearts can't keep up.
I can't even talk to my mother about wearing new underwear.
Isn't there a kind-hearted person who can teach us all about it?
Nevertheless,
she looks so happy.
Aren't we in the same class?
I-It's just a coincidence!
We weren't following you or anything!
They've already made friends.
Or maybe they're from the same elementary school.
I hope I can make lots of friends, too.
Any volunteers?
A-As the assistant homeroom teacher, should I say something?
What about nominations?
Yes!
I'd like to nominate Nayu Hayama-san as our female Class Rep!
Yeah, she's so smart.
I agree!
Hayama-san scored highest in the entrance exam.
I think she'd be perfect.
You're right.
Those in favor, raise your hands.
W-Wait, are you okay with this, Hayama-san?
Something didn't feel right about that, Yako-chan.
About what?
Our homeroom meeting.
You mean about the Class Rep?
Hayama-san was forced into it.
Well, think about it.
She may still be a prostitute.
If those rumors turn out to be true, we can't call them out.
With huge breasts like yours, she'll surely target you.
Yeah, right. You're just over thinking stuff.
Hayama-san!
Umm, you're...
Shiraishi-san and Jinguji-san?
Y-Yeah.
That smells great!
Are we having sweet and sour pork today?
I-It's almost time for lunch.
What are you carrying?
Oh, this?
They're materials for the next class.
Forced into being the Class Rep must be difficult.
Ah. No, I'm fine.
I'm fine...
Ouch.
Now's our chance, Haruka. Let's run for it!
Shiraishi-san's breasts...
They're...
W-What's wrong with you, Yako-chan?
Didn't you notice?!
She was assessing you!
Huh?
She was appraising your breasts, Haruka!
Which means...
you've been scouted for her prostitute ring!
Let's turn those breasts into money!
But rumors are just rumors!
That may be true, but still...
Either way, we should keep our distance.
Shiraishi-sa-
Um...
Class Rep...
The teacher asked us to take this to the faculty office.
Take care of it.
Sure.
Huh?
I thought the officer of the day was supposed to take these.
I guess they'll keep running from me.
But, I need to tell them soon.
Besides...
I thought we could be friends.
Have you heard about the new student Hayama-san?
Who is that?
The girl who tripped at the entrance ceremony...
Oh the girl with the black panties?
Girls Locker Room
I was so shocked.
A seventh grader with black panties?
I can't say I wouldn't want to wear them.
No way!
You won't believe what I heard.
What?
I heard she's a prostitute.
And she has all kinds of crazy underwear.
Like what?
G-string?
See-through?
I bet she doesn't wear anything some days.
What?! No way!
I can't believe we're in her class in middle school too.
Wai- What is that?
String panties?
That's so dirty.
A-Are you okay, Hayama?
Are you hurt?
Thank you.
W-Watch your step.
O-Okay.
So that's why she was wearing that underwear...
Huh? What do you mean?
She's picking up men by flashing them her panties.
But what does she do after that?
Your clothes are dirty.
She performs lewd acts for money.
P-Paid dating?!
Hayama-san, let me copy your homework.
Please?
Oh, sure.
Here.
Wai-
Haruka!
But...
Did you forget? She's...
Hayama-san doesn't seem like a bad girl to me.
She's always so cheerful. I can't believe she's a prostitute.
Fine.
Huh?
If you're still unconvinced, then we shall find the evidence today that she's guilty!
What?!
The perfect shot!
Wai- Yako-chan!
Secretly photographing is a crime!
B-But she's a criminal.
This is nothing compared to her crimes.
Besides, I want to see the adult panties I missed at the entrance ceremony.
Yako-chan!
Good. This is the best position.
Yako-chan, your panties!
Distract her with some conversation!
Uh, you're Hayama-san, right?
You must be amazing to be chosen as our Class Rep.
I bet you're really smart.
N-Not really...
Okay.
Just a little more.
Yako-chan!
I can't do it.
I'm slipping.
I can't hold on.
Hayama-san?
W-What was that?
Ouch.
U-Um...
Aren't those Claire's teen's line panties from the "Clover" series?
They're low-rises from last fall and winter.
Low-rise?
That's what you call panties with a low waist.
They're great panties to wear with jeans because they won't stick out.
Stop saying "panties!"
They're so cute.
M-My mother bought them for me. I don't...
Let's see...
Excuse me.
You could probably start wearing adult panties.
Panties for children are designed to fit a child's body line, so the hips are narrow...
but adults have thinner waists and wider hips.
So their underwear is designed differently.
A person with womanly curves like yourself,
would be better off wearing adult panties.
You sure know a lot.
I'm an underwear monitor.
I just got absorbed.
Is that why you wear those outrageous panties?
Huh?
Let me see.
An acquaintance designed these.
I monitor new products.
The other day...
Thanks for all the hard work.
Go ahead and change.
I thought they were great...
but it seems like they're hard to wear.
You can have these back.
It's good to collect negative data as well.
If you take that information and fix them up, I'm sure they'll be happy, too.
You really are an underwear maniac, Nayu.
So that's the real story.
I-I'm sorry.
Huh? For what?
What? You thought I was a prostitute?
I-I-I don't do anything like that!
Then where does that rumor come from?
I don't know if this is relevant, but...
in sixth grade, everyone started avoiding me.
I was so happy for wearing a new black lace garter that day.
That's probably the cause of the rumor.
Oh yeah, Hayama-san.
Wasn't there something you wanted to tell us?
Oh, yeah.
Well, excuse me.
I knew it.
You've got skin bulging out of your bra.
If you leave things the way they are, it'll hurt your skin on your back.
It happens when you force yourself into a bra that's too small.
It has been a bit tight lately.
You mean you've grown that much?!
But how did you know?
It was easy to tell just be looking at your clothes.
I could hear your breasts suffocating.
I'm suffocating!
It's too tight!
Breasts are especially delicate at our age.
So you should wear something that gently envelops them.
I see.
So let's measure you!
You don't need to do that.
No need to be shy. You too, Yako-chan.
Someone's still here.
It sounds like that girl.
I thought I heard something that sounded like a string.
Hayama Nayu, it's not too late!
Calm down! Consider your position!
Calm down, Nayu!
Stop! Let go!
Oh, no.
First it was prostitution.
Now they think you're a lesbian.
With me to boot...
I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Well, we can't do anything about it.
But to make up for it...
buy me ice cream for a week.
We won't let you go home alone!
Okay!
They suspected you of paid dating and you ended up comparing panties?
I wish I could have been there.
I-It was better that you weren't, Keigo-san.
Either way, I'm glad you found friends.
I-I guess.
I hope I did.
Preview
Do you know how to choose the right size bra cup?
Nope.
I don't know.
It's determined by the difference between your top bust and under bust.
A-cup is 10 cm, B-cup is 12.5 cm...
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!
This Swelling Chest