When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
It's nice to wake up early once in a while; I met an interesting person.
Nonohara!
Come over here, Nonohara.
Your opponent is this combat butler, Nonohara Kaede.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Yes! Today will be a kendo showdown!
Your opponent will be my butler, Nonohara Kaede.
Butler?
So hello, I'm Nonohara Kaede.
I'm a butler of the Azumamiya family.
He's a butler, too?
It's him, Nonohara.
Knock him out right now!
As you order.
But before that...
Down, diagonal left down, left, kick.
It's not a Hurri**** Kick!
N-Nonohara, what are you...
Sir, did I not teach you?
If you are a man, put up a fight even if you know you would lose.
Yet, you rely on others without fighting, and you don't do anything.
I don't recall...
...raising you to be such a weakling!
Y-You wouldn't go that far, would you, Himuro?
Nonohara-kun is strict as always.
But is it all right?
He's a butler, yet he's...
What are you talking about?
We butlers aren't our masters' tools.
Just doing what they tell us to do isn't everything.
"Butler" used to be a highly honorable position that only the first born of a noble family could become.
In other words, there's that much responsibility involved in the position.
The responsibility to guide one's master along the right course.
Isn't that why you wanted to teach her the pleasure of sports?
To your hikikomori, weak, spineless, manga nerd of a master?
Who are you calling a hikikomori, weak, spineless manga nerd of a master?
I-I'm sorry, Nonohara!
I got it! I got it!
No. I won't forgive you today.
I will amend your rotten mind...
...starting with your spine!
NO!!!
Please don't make too much commotion in the dojo, Nonohara-san.
Katsura-san.
This is our educational style, so would you please not interfere?
I'm sorry, but I really can't do that.
I'm the Student Council President,
so I can't stop myself from helping a student in need.
Katsura-san...
Even if Azumamiya-kun is a weak and pathetic crybaby, I have to help him.
Huh?
Wonderful, President.
Way to strike directly at the opponent's vital point.
I didn't hit his vital point!
Okay, I get it, Nonohara.
I can't be weak anymore!
Sir!
A man must fight and open his own path!
Sir! So you understand!
Therefore!
Fight me, Sanzenin!
EHH?!
Um, Azumamiya-kun. May I ask the reason?
I promise I won't get angry.
I understand what my mistake was.
It's weird for the master and the butler to fight.
Or rather, there's no chance.
Then the correct answer is for master to fight master, and butler to fight butler!
Is he right in the head?
No, I don't think so.
Looks like it's hard for butlers to lead their master down the correct course.
Master! That's wonderful!
So you finally understand that.
So you're fine with that...
So they say, Nagi. What are you going to do?
Don't ask me.
Oh, fine.
Then I'll fight against Azumamiya-kun.
Hey, Hinagiku?
If you start swinging swords all of a sudden,
your body's going to break,
since you haven't practiced at all.
And, even though Azumamiya-kun is the weakest on the team,
because he's the least professional,
his strikes are all random and dangerous.
It'd be terrible if two people who don't know how to use a sword fought and got injured.
Huh? Azumamiya-kun?
It's fine... Looks like a match with you is an unavoidable fate.
Wow, Hinagiku-san... She keeps on hitting him right at the vital point without even trying.
Then all I have to do is to prove
I'm stronger than you with this sword!
Let's go, Nonohara!
Yes, sir!
So that's how it is. Let's do this, Hayate-kun.
Y-Yes!
I must win this match and have Milady continue with kendo!
Win or lose, I don't have any intention of returning to the Kendo Club.
Yotsuba no clobber miitsuketa.
I found a four-leafed clover.
Tama tama nandesu. Tasukete Nonohara!
It was an accident. Help me Nonohara!
Dear audience, for your reference, when you have a kendo match, make sure to put protectors on for your safety.
In anime, they don't put them on due to troubles involving redrawing cels and other adult issues.
Entering the Road to the Devil and Hell.
Does he have an acceleration device in his back teeth?
H-He's fast. Reacting is all I can do.
Here I go!
I didn't think I'd end up fighting you.
This is a wall that I have to face for the sake of my love.
But I will defeat you and prove that I'm a man!
Azumamiya-kun, I have no clue what you're talking about.
But if you talk too much, you'll bite your tongue.
Men!
Nice strike, President.
The Azumamiya boy had no chance.
Of course. Hinagiku wouldn't lose to someone like him.
But I wonder how the butler side of things will turn out.
I wonder if he's good enough to beat Nonohara-kun.
Don't joke with me! Are you saying that Hayate will lose to that guy's butler?
All right.
Hayate-kun, how is it going there?
Safety Shutter!
Hayate!
What was that about?
"What"? It was his ultimate move, of course.
Huh?
Any professional butler should possess one or two ultimate moves.
In fact, it's strange not to have them.
Something similar to Ryu*** Rambu and Hyakki *******ken, where the commands are unnecessarily complicated?
That's only inside games!
I had heard the Sanzenin's butler is strong,
but this is all you have?
He's unbelievable.
An ultimate move?
So this is what professional butlers are like.
But if I lose here, Milady will never practice kendo again.
Are you all right, Hayate?
I'll end this match with the next move.
But what can I do?
A move to deflect his ultimate move...
It's impossible.
Besides, it usually takes a full episode to gain an ultimate move.
It's impossible to learn an ultimate move in this short a time.
Hayate, I have faith in you!
I know you can come up with a counter, like how Buf****man made a comeback against Kinniku ***ter!
I'm happy that you have faith in me, but I'm not superhuman.
Believe in yourself!
A butler...
A butler is not fulfilling his responsibilities when he cannot see the trash on the floor while cleaning the room.
"You find only caterpillars on leaves!"
That's a completely wrong usage of the reference.
Ready?
Ultimate move...
Trash on the floor...
Trash?
I get it!
Safety Shutter!
Hayate!
No, he's...
Sir!
Hayate!
Men!
We lost. As expected from the butler of Sanzenin.
It was nothing. I only took advantage of your moment of shock.
It was a wonderful tactic that used my ingrained inability to use my ultimate move when I see his pathetic face.
I only used the ninja move where you use a substitute.
And you can use that ninja move?
Excuse us now.
I'd be happy if you had an ultimate move ready by the next time we meet.
Then I can put up a more serious fight.
So?
Do you feel like doing kendo now?
W-Well, watching you and Hayate fight,
it did make me think that you two are cool.
Milady...
But I have no intention of returning to the Kendo Club.
Because kendo head protectors stink.
I don't understand how people feel like exercising with that thing on.
Besides, in kendo manga, the protector gets in the way,
so you can't tell one character from another, and you can't see their expressions either.
Don't mock kendo!
What was that for?!
Looks like it's impossible for Nagi to come to the Kendo Club, but how about you?
As a butler, you need to learn an ultimate move, right?
I don't mind helping you train.
I'm thinking that I'd have to train in order to come up with an ultimate move, but...
Hayate, get over here already.
Ah, yes!
Then, I'm sure you'll have to go through a lot of training,
but when you come up with one, make sure you show it to me.
Your special ultimate move.
Yes.
Was Hinagiku still angry?
Why was she so angry?
There are things you're not supposed to comment on.
Her awakening for sports is still far away.
Thank you very much, Maria-san.
What's the formality for?
Thanks to you, I was able to experience the high school life
I thought I'd never be able to experience again.
I see. I'm happy for you.
So how was your first day?
I thought high school life isn't necessary to become a professional butler,
but I learned a lot about what it takes to become a professional.
I-I see.
Hayate, come here a second.
Yes.
How may I help you, Milady?
I-I was happy when you fought for me.
I only did what every butler should.
Besides, I found out that I need
an ultimate move as a butler, too.
Yes, that!
I gave it some thought, too, but how about getting yourself a ma***tic coating,
or starting black *****, or get a ****let from a **der.
I'm not sure about that.
I'm not a white demon, nor a gagged eyebrow boy.
And I don't have a friend who watches the stars.
Yes, therefore I realized the best way is to learn an ultimate move the correct way.
Huh?
So I made this for you as a thank you for today.
Um, is this...
Yes. Ultimate moves comes from training in the Tiger's Den.
Give it your best shot!
That's something only a 40+ year-old would understand.
I knew it'd be you.
I'm not dressed like this by choice, either!
Why should I bother with this?
Let's get your training started.
Hey, stop it! Don't become realistic all of a sudden!
I see he started to train right away.
He must have liked it.
At times, a master's kindness is unnecessary.
Anyways, the debt-ridden butler's first day at school ends like this.
Next time, we'll fight against housekeeping, laundry, and cooking.
Ultimate move, Frying Pan Flip!
Perfect.
Ramen daisuki. Koike-san no uta.
I love Ramen. Sung by Koike-san.
Tama tama Tama ni attara "Tama" tte yonndene!
If you see Tama in the streets, make sure you shout, "Tama!"
Klaus-kun's Glutton! Wonderful!
I'm hungry.
Okay, I'll imitate a few people.
Imitation of Jack ***er.
"It's Season 5!"
Imitation of Co***y.
Note: Convoy is the Japanese name for Optimus Prime.
"********, tran****m and roll out!"
Imitation of a golden hour movie channel.
"Next week's ***** movie is..."
Imitation of a bo***g story.
"Bo***g story..."
And now...
Ah, single shiritori.
Klaus...
Super car keshigomu...
Super car keshigomu = Super car eraser.
Muruwakka...
Muruwakka = ????????
Ka-
From the Windows of Trains Around the World.
Are we at Rio de Janeiro yet?
Next time will be on Marunouchi Line,
between Ogikubo and South Asagaya Station.
****y's Puppy.
Today's puppy is from Tokyo Nerima Ward and is sunbathing.
A White Tiger Cat, his name is Tama.
No. No matter how you see, that's not a puppy.
Hayate!
Let's play, Hayate!
What do we want to play with?
Stop it!
How about "Face the Way I Point"?
Tama loves to play with his master, who is a butler.
The house we explore today is the Sanzenin villa.
The family members consist of the Lady, who enjoys her NEET life.
The maid, Maria-san, who enjoys flower arrangement.
Now let's go check the house out.
The pillar's nice.
I see.
It really is a thorough job.
Uses only the genuine material.
The sense of security you feel the moment you enter.
The craftsmanship you can let your eyes enjoy.
And this is!
A well-lit sunroom.
And the foliage set around the room.
I have a fetish for foliage.
This makes me happy.
After going through the bright arch of the sun,
you reach the LDK apartments.
Note: LDK stands for "Living room, Dining room, Kitchen"
Next time, we'll show the house where you can enjoy the slivers of light.
Look forward to it.
That was good.
See you next week.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Sorry for the wait. I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
We have Hinagiku-san with us today, too.
I'm Katsura Hinagiku. Hi folks!
You look happy, Hayate.
Well, having Hinagiku-san show up makes the anime itself wilder.
I don't sleep while hugging a doll like that.
Hayate, you're making a mistake.
Eh?
The heroine of this anime is...
Hayate, it's you!
EH?!
Bye bye.
What's wrong, Milady?
I, apparently, don't have enough experience in life.
The reason I can't win anything from the manga I draw is because I don't have enough experience in life.
H-Huh...
Then I'll do things I usually don't do and gain experience points!
What?!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
For Your Sake, I'll Give My Best Blasting Through Everything.
I will give you VIP service.
You better be ready for this.
Come get us if you dare!