Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
The Circus Festival will be held soon.
The Circus Festival is a big
competition held every three years
in which the world's top
artists compete against each other
doing their really amazing techniques.
Everyone has been training very hard for
this date, betting everything they've got.
Miss Layla won the last
competition with the Golden Phoenix!
In order to be the real Kaleido Star
Miss Layla charged me with becoming,
I'll fly all the way to where
you are. I'll do it! I'll do it! I'll do it!
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa
aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Oh, they've announced it,
they've announced it!
Oh, really?
I wonder if my name is
listed, by any chance...
Let me see. Let me see.
If they listed your name,
it would be something else.
Just being nominated here
itself is very hard.
Sora... Sora...
It's not listed.
Of course not.
My name isn't listed either.
Come to think of it...
May's name hasn't come up either.
That's what you'd expect from the International
Circus Festival held once every three years.
I heard it was tough to get in, but...
Oh, there's a webpage for the
competition they did three years ago.
Miss Layla and Yuri.
They won admirably in this
competition three years ago, didn't they?
And the performance they did at
that time was the Golden Phoenix.
Winning at this festival was my dream.
I believe this trophy will
give me new strength.
The strength to jump higher and farther.
Oh... I wish I could say something
cool like that. I wish! I wish!
But, in order to do that,
I have to be in the festival.
Let's work hard and enter the
festival together three years from now.
Yeah.
In order to surpass Miss Layla,
I want to participate
in the Circus Festival too.
That's right, this is a part of my dream.
What?
What is it?
Mr. Leon's name is not listed either.
What?
But with Leon's abilities,
he'd definitely have been chosen...
"Amazing Training With Leon."
Come in.
Miss Layla!
Um, when I was in New York--
Thank you for all you did for me! Don't you--
Don't you need to appear on the stage?
"Salome in Vegas" is suspended.
Cathy, the director, caused
trouble with the producer again.
Oh, really?
Anyway, the reason
I came here today is for this.
What is it?
Invitations to participate
in the Circus Festival.
They're known as Phoenix Tickets.
Phoenix Tickets?
Since Layla won three years ago,
she has an unconditional "seed"
right to participate in the competition.
So she's saying that she wants to
recommend one of you in her place.
Recommend...
You mean one of us can enter the Festival?
If you're prepared for that.
Yes!
I will absolutely work hard.
So, please recommend me.
Well, I'll work my hardest too!
What are you going to work hard on?
What...
The Circus Festival is not just a festival.
It's a place where participants
seriously compete with each other.
It's a place where they
compete; win or lose, live or die.
All participants compete,
betting everything they've got.
The requirement is not only working
hard, but also the preparedness to win.
Participating in this
with Layla's recommendation
means you'll be expected to produce
the high-level results that implies.
And as members of Kaleido Stage,
if people see you making a
clumsy performance at the festival
it will affect the size of
our audiences afterwards.
Leon...
You decide which of the two it will be.
What?
The trapeze acts have
to be performed in pairs.
Since you'll be the other half of the pair,
you have the right to choose your own partner.
Who told you I would
participate in something like that?
If you're not ready to definitely win,
you don't have to participate.
If that's the case,
I'm the one who's refusing you.
I wonder, maybe, if you don't have the
confidence to win in the Circus Festival,
where you have so many enemies.
What?
I heard there are many on the
selection committee who hate you.
They say the reason why you
were not selected for this event
is because you've ended the
careers of countless partners.
Ended their careers?
I'm sure there are some committee members
who will want to keep the trophy from you,
even if only out of stubbornness.
This is a duel between you and your fate.
Participate and win, or run
away now. One or the other.
You're the one who decides, Leon.
A duel with fate...
Three years ago, I had no choice but to win.
And I won my duel with fate.
You ran away then, if I remember.
Ran away, you say?
You'd entered, but you never
showed up at the festival site.
I don't know what reasons you had, but...
It's not that I ran away.
If I'm going to aim for winning,
whichever one will end up
participating, I'll have to train her more.
That's true.
Both of you may be destroyed. You're
prepared to take that chance, I assume?
If they don't satisfy me,
I don't care how many people are destroyed.
If they're destroyed, it means
they weren't good enough.
All right.
Wait, Leon.
Miss Layla...
What are you doing?
The stage is waiting for you. Go.
Yes...
It seems you already know
what everybody calls Leon.
The God of Death. Right?
So you're doing this, knowing
full well what may come of it...
In order to win in the Circus Festival,
we need that much preparedness.
You're the one who taught me that, Kalos.
I believe.
I'm sure you're going to choose me.
I'll work hard.
I'll work hard so you don't feel
ashamed of me as a partner in the festival.
I will create a chance for you to show off.
What?
I will create a perfect chance
for you to show off in today's show.
Thank you so much. I... I will do my best!
So, as I thought, Leon likes May better...
No... I still should have a chance.
Saying he's destroyed countless
partners... I wonder what that meant.
May!
I don't believe this!
Leon!
Are you okay, May?!
What?
Are you saying I screwed up something?!
May...
To think you can't
handle a little ad lib like that.
Ad lib...
You don't mean you did it on purpose?!
You're terrible! Why would
you do something like that?!
If someone has not reached the level
I expect, that person is going to be destroyed.
It's that simple.
I can't believe...
I see you're not called
the God of Death for nothing.
Miss Layla...
The God of Death...
May, you failed.
Give up on the festival and
heal that shoulder quickly.
Because I'm useless...
Did you destroy me because I was an eyesore?
May...
If you want to blame something,
blame your lack of skills.
May!
You shouldn't have time to
worry about somebody else!
Miss Layla...
If you don't want to be
destroyed by Leon as well,
you should put forth more
effort than you have in the past.
Sora...
Yes...
Starting tomorrow, you will
have special training. Be ready.
Why...
I believed...
I believed the whole time, and he...
So, how was May?
It's like we thought.
Apparently the ligament
in her right shoulder is torn.
It seems she was told that
it would take a while to heal.
I guess we have to suspend the
performances of Dracula for a while.
"The God of Death." I heard it before too.
Whoever is paired with
Leon always leaves the stage.
Sora, are you sure pairing
with Leon is a good idea after all?
She's right. If Sora is destroyed
too, the Kaleido Stage will...
Sora...
Where are you going, Sora?
You're going to play Mina Murray.
I will create a chance for you to show off.
I will create a perfect chance
for you to show off in today's show.
May...
May... I wonder if she'll be all right.
What's wrong?
Aren't you happy because
your rival dropped out?
Of course not!
Why not?
May worked so hard playing
Mina Murray as Mr. Leon's partner,
and then he did something like that to her...
Not only that, if she finds out
I'm taking special training while
she's suffering from her injuries,
I don't know what she'll think of me.
Are you worrying about May?
Or are you worried that you might be hated?
As someone aiming to be a real Kaleido Star,
is that so important to be troubled with?
I know.
The things I have to do right now are
to participate in the festival and win.
Three years ago, I had no choice but to win.
And I won my duel with fate.
There's no other path for me, either.
In order to surpass Miss Layla...
In order to be a true Kaleido Star...
No matter what kind of special
training it is, I'll withstand it.
I won't be destroyed.
The training that you'll go
through will be very difficult for you.
I'll withstand it.
Then...
Until I say you can stop, stand there.
What?
But stand there with only your right foot.
That's all? That's the special training?
That's right.
I don't know what the special training
for the legendary great maneuver was like,
but you will find out how
easy that was in comparison.
If it gets to be too much for you,
run away whenever you want.
I will not stop you.
I won't run away! I'll show you;
I'll be your partner for sure!
It's almost three hours now.
And here I was wondering just how
amazing the special training was...
But he's just telling her to stand there...
Isn't this just harassment?
It could be. After all,
Leon is called the God of Death.
Do it one more time from the beginning.
What?!
Ouch...
What was wrong?
Don't ask questions.
You have only two options: do it or quit.
I'll do it!
Don't switch your foot.
Yes.
Today it's the left foot?
What purpose is this going to serve?
Leon is probably trying
to hammer the basics home.
The basics?
If I remember right, you used
to say she lacks the basics.
Yeah.
For Sora, standing in the same position
for a long time should be very tough.
And that's hindering the
range of her performance.
I think Leon sees her weakness
and is trying to correct it.
But, if he overdoes it, he may
well also kill her good points,
like her flexibility or the muscle power
she can put forth starting from a standstill.
You don't think he's just
trying to destroy Sora...
Hi, everybody...
Looks like we're having
another nice day today, huh?
You don't need to do small talk.
Sora, can you perform at Kids Stage today?
Of... course, I can...
But even yesterday, your timing was off...
It's because of this special
training, isn't it?
Sorry. I'll do my best. So don't worry.
Sora, the more I think about it, the more
I think you should stop this special training.
It's just too much.
But...
I'll talk to Leon.
Ken...
In short, you're going to quit now?
That's faster than I thought.
Mr. Leon, I can't allow you to
keep doing things like this anymore.
If you want to build up her basics,
I will make a training menu.
You've nothing to do with this.
I do. Because, Sora is...
Ken. It's okay.
Sora...
It's okay, I won't lose.
I'll see this through to the end, for sure.
I will not let him say that the special training
for the legendary great maneuver was easy.
Isn't she the girl from Kaleido Stage?
I wonder if she made some kind
of mistake, and is being punished.
Even if she did, it's just too much.
What is Leon thinking?
It's been more than two hours
since she started standing
on one foot on the bus.
Is that really doing anything for Sora?
Go, Sora!
What is this girl?
She's the first to ever endure this much.
Sagittarius's bow is drawn
to its utmost limit.
Unless she can shoot an arrow,
the bowstring will snap, and
everything will be over.
Ready? Jump!
Smile, smile.
Oh!
Oops!
She's reached her limit.
It must be painful for you to
even stand normally on those legs.
How can you keep smiling?
What... is this?
This...
At this point, this isn't
basic training or anything.
I can't think this is
for the festival either.
The only way I can see it is that he's just trying
to destroy Sora even if only out of stubbornness.
Leon, why are you overreacting so much?
I'm just doing this because it's necessary.
I don't think it is.
It looks like you're afraid of Sora.
What are you thinking?
You don't acknowledge May's skills,
yet you chose her as a partner
and you're still at Kaleido Stage. Why?
What are you seeking from Sora?
That girl is my dream, you know.
If you destroy her out of petty
stubbornness, I won't forgive you.
Where are you going?
The special training is finished.
You mean, she passed?
That's right.
Sora, you passed!
--You don't need to do it anymore!
--Sora! It's finished! It's finished!
Sora passed?
You did excellent, Sora. You passed.
Passed?
That's right.
Really?
Yeah. Congratulations, Sora.
Leon...
No...
I can't stay here anymore.
Hang in there, Sora.
Thanks.
May...
What's wrong?
Oh, no... It's nothing.
It's fine.
This is fine.
Afraid of her? Me? Impossible.
That's ridiculous.
I can't stand it!
I really, really can't stand it!
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (Here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
You talk pretty, but
aren't you just running away?
And so, I passed! Or that's what
I thought. Then, the final test?!
And it's a very cruel one.
I remember now. I'll show
you who I really am!
Face it, I'm prepared on a
different level than you are!
This is a challenge to the God of Death!
What shall I do?
What shall I do? What shall I do?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Two Amazing Demons."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...