[door opening and closing]
[Envy] Oh, no, not again...
We've told you,
you're an important
candidate for sacrifice.
We need you to keep your
strength up.. Understand?
So.. dig in, Dr. Marcoh.
You know what?... I've been
sitting here awhile...
trying to decide what
you mean by 'sacrifice'...
trying to figure
out why I'm here...
and what it is exactly
you want me to do.
[Marcoh] I'm fairly certain that
what you're doing right now
is using this land
and its people
to form a giant
transmutation circle.
And your hope is that the end
result will be the creation of
a Philosopher's Stone.
Am I wrong?
So close... Not quite... But
you're on the right track.
Then what is it?
The question is.. are you going
to cooperate with us or not?...
If not, the village is history.
[gasp]
Lust told me about
your arrangement...
If we agree to leave
the village alone...
then you'll do whatever we ask.
Which is it?...
Agree to work with us, and kill
everyone in this country...
Or refuse to work with us...
and watch everyone in your
beloved village die.
[Envy] Fool. You just have to
forsake one little village
to save an entire country...
Too bad you don't
have the stomach
to do the logical thing.
I shouldn't be surprised. That's
just how all you humans are.
[Envy] You put emotions
before common sense.
I killed a man who
was like that once.
All I had to do was make
myself look like his wife,
and he was helpless. He
couldn't even fight me.
Humans are so easy to take
advantage of... Lucky us.
[crickets chirping]
[Pride] The humans seem to
be giving you quite a bit
of trouble lately, don't
they... Wrath. Hm?
First Scar gets away from you,
then those others make off with
Gluttony. It's not like you.
Yes... you are
right about that.
[Pride] And yet, you seem happy.
Yes, I won't deny it.
This has been... enjoyable.
[Bradley] I've been
alive for sixty years...
And now, here I am, in the
ultimate position of power.
All has gone exactly as
Father had planned it would.
[Pride] There's more though...
Roy Mustang and
his underlings...
The enterprising
Elric brothers...
And these foreigners who
suddenly appeared from Xing...
As good as we are,
they've still got us
scrambling in circles.
Things are changing.
The time may be approaching
when we have to move over
for the younger generation...
Don't you see?
[Pride] Listen to
yourself, Wrath...
You've been around these
humans for far too long.
[Bradley] You may
be right, Pride.
[Pride] I hope you will
stop this foolishness
and remember who we are
and what we must do.
I won't tell Father what
you've said tonight...
He might be inclined
to see it as treason.
Anyway, about Gluttony...
Don't worry about that...
I have access to military
information, after all.
I know where he is.
[Hawkeye] What was that?!
Colonel! What's going on?
[Roy] Hawkeye, stop!
[transmutation sounds]
[rattling, wood breaking]
[roaring]
[Hawkeye] Colonel!
[muffled] Lieutenant...
Don't provoke him!
I'm the one he wants!
[roaring] Mustang!
[Ling] Come on... We're
getting out of here.
What is it?...
What's happening?
The Homunculus...
He had another monster
hidden inside his belly.
[Ling] He's swallowing
up everything in sight!
[Ed] Alchemy can produce
something like that?
How disgusting.
Let's go.. We have
to bring him down.
[Al] But we worked so hard to
catch one of the Homunculi.
[Roy] Survival is our
first priority...
Besides... he knows our
names and faces now...
It would be foolish to let
him leave here alive!
[explosion]
[Gluttony screaming]
[fire whooshing]
[burp]
He swallowed it?
[Al] Uh-oh.
[Gluttony roaring]
Hey, that worked well!
Think you can do better?
Be my guest!
[Al] Or we could just leave
you behind, Colonel...
You're the one he really wants.
Those trees over there.
Spread out!
[gunshots]
[Gluttony screaming,
transmutation sounds]
[wincing in pain]
[Roy] Damn it... Not now.
Hurry up and get in the car.
Come on, we haven't got all
night. We need to get moving!
But Ed and the others...
No way! I'm a civilian,
not military...
I'm not about to die in
the middle of a battle
with some crazed monster.
[Knox] Damn it! What's taking
those idiots so long?!
[Gluttony grunting]
Mustang!
[Gluttony screaming]
[Gluttony] Noooo!
Perfect. He fell for
the Mustang decoy.
[Al] Doesn't sound like
he's very happy about it.
All right... Now get in
the car... invalid.
[Al] Lieutenant.. please
take care of Lan Fan.
You expect me to run away and
leave this to you, Elric?!
If you stay you'll
just get in our way!
[Al] Yeah! Leave!
They're right. You won't
be any use here... Sorry.
[Ed] How did ths
idiot make Colonel?!
[Ed] Right now you need to
go and do your job...
The head of the military
is a Homunculus.
Don't you think you should
do something about that?
The head of the military?...
You aren't talking about
Fuhrer Bradley, are you?!
We can talk about it
later... Now..get in!
The car looks full...
You go ahead.
You dumbasses!
You can't really
believe we'll let
a couple children fight
this battle for us!
With the senior staff
involved in this,
you're gonna need all
the help you can get.
And that would include getting
whatever information we can
out of this Gluttony
guy, wouldn't you say?
[Al] We'll stay here and
find out what we can...
I don't think it matters
much that we're children.
This was our mission
to begin with,
and we're going to
see it through.
[Ed] We appreciate your
help up 'till now, though.
[Hawkeye] Here Edward...
I want you to take this...
You do know how to
use it, don't you?
[Al] That's a weapon...
for killing people.
Yes. But it's also a weapon
for protecting your lives.
It's your hands... They
weren't meant to kill.
And no dying, okay?
I'll take it.
[alchemical explosions]
Look after Lan Fan.
Wait... My lord!
Let's go... I said go!
Damn! What're they thinking?!
[Knox] Those three are gonna
get themselves killed!
[engine revving]
[alchemical explosions]
[Gluttony] Mustang...
Where are you, Mustang?!...
You killed Lust!...
You will pay!
I know we said we'd
stay and all...
but that's seriously freaky.
He seems to be a bit angry.
[Al] How are we
gonna catch him?
[rustling bushes]
[Al] What was that?
[Al] A dog?
Stop it... Now, Gluttony!
[Ed] A..a talking dog?!
Hey.. long time no see.
[transmutation sounds]
How are ya, Fullmetal pipsqueak?
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Ed] Dammit, I told you before:
don't call me short...!
Hey, calm down...
I'm just here to get Gluttony
back, nothing more than that...
I don't want to fight
you, pipsqueak.
[Ed] That's five now!
[Envy] What are
you talking about?
That's five times.... You called
me 'pipsqueak' twice here...
and three times in
the laboratory!
And don't tell me you've
forgotten already!
Impressive. You've got a
sharp memory there.
[Ed] Hold it!
You're becoming bothersome.
[Gluttony] Mustang was
here... Must avenge Lust!...
Swallow.. swallow...
swallow him up!
You don't get the colonel...
Or the Elric brothers.
[Gluttony] Why not?!
I've sensed this
multiplicity before.
How many people're
inside you... Homunculus?
I know you...
You're the kid who crossed
swords with Wrath, aren't you?
What do you mean, 'kid'?!...
I happen to be the twelfth
son of the emperor of Xing.
My name i-
[Envy] Eat him.
[sirens] No no no no noooo!
[Ling screaming]
You thinkin' what I'm thinkin'?
[Al] Looks like they
really aren't allowed
to do anything to
the two of us.
In which case...
[clap, transmutation sounds]
[Ed] Ling.. you get that one!
Very well... Let's
see how good you are.
You held off Wrath, but how
will you do against me?
[Bradley] Oh... did he, now?
[Bradley's wife] Yes. It was
the best paper in the class...
He chose to write an essay
all about you, actually.
[Selim] Mom.. can I read
it to you guys now?
Not at the table. Mind
your manners, dear.
Oh, don't be silly...
Why not?...
Go ahead and read, son.
I'd like to hear it.
Great! "Essay on my dad"...
He's the Fuhrer of the
nation of Amestris...
He works hard all the time,
and everything he does
is for our country.
[Selim] The people of Amestris
are always in his heart.
He dedicates his life
to making them happy.
He deals with all sorts
of problems each day
so everyone in our country
can live a good life.
But no matter how busy
he gets doing his job,
my dad never forgets
his family...
He loves me and my
mother very much.
He always looks out for us.
My dad's a good man...
He always listens to me when I
talk to him. He's always kind...
and protects our family...
And that is why... I
love my dad. The end.
Thank you for that,
Selim... very much.
You really know how
to use that thing.
Aww, thank you for the
compliment... really!
You fell for it!
[Envy] Good, isn't it?...
And you humans can't do anything
like it... So, what'll it be?
Strangled to death?...
bitten to death?
Or just carved up
into little pieces?
None of the above.
[transmutation sounds]
[Envy groaning in pain]
[Envy] That was
a dirty trick...
Blinding me. That's
not playing fair.
[Ling] People have been
trying to assassinate me
since I was a kid...
Under the circumstances,
you can't blame a guy for
learning how to fight dirty.
So, have you had enough yet?
Are you going to come
with me quietly now?...
I just want whatever
information you can give me
on becoming immortal.
[Ling] Or shall we go again?
You scum!... A mere human like
you can't condescend to me!
You seem to underestimate
humans... And that's a mistake!
[transmutation sounds]
[Ed] Nice! Got 'im!
Whew!.. That was a close one.
[Ed] I've had enough of you!
[Gluttony] Get away.
I can't eat you!
Just let me take a bite
out of the other guy!
[Al] Not today!
[Al screaming, crashing]
Stay out of my way,
guys. I'm busy.
[Envy screaming]
[Envy] Another foolish human.
Go for it, Gluttony!
[Ed] Ling!
What?!
[Envy] Dammit!.., I can't let
him eat a sacrifice!
[Al] Brother!
[explosion,
transmutation sounds]
[trees breaking and falling]
[disintegrating noise]
[Gluttony] Swallowed them?
[Al] Brother!.. Ling!... You!...
Spit them out!...
Spit them out now!
I can't... I
swallowed them.
[transmutation sounds]
[Al] Impossible... it
can't be... Brother!
[Al screaming]
[Knox] I do have another room
that my kid used to sleep in.
But people will get suspicious
if I keep all the lights on...
You'll have to make
do with my bed.
My lord. I have to go to him!
Idiot girl! What can you
do in your condition?!
[sobbing]
[Roy] He isn't home
yet?... I see...
I'll head straight to the
command center then...
Right... Goodbye.
[phone hanging up]
Let's go.
[Hawkeye] Right.
Go where?
I think now would be a
good time to find out
who we can trust
and who we can't.
What is it with you idiots?
You got a death wish?...
Your wounds haven't
begun to heal yet,
and you're already going out
looking for more trouble?
[Roy] For all we know, the
Fuhrer is a Homunculus.
I can't very well
ignore that. Besides...
We just left children out on a
battlefield to do our fighting.
If they're brave
enough to fight...
how can I just sit
here and wait?!
[car engine]
[Roy] What's so funny?
Oh... It's nothing, really.
I was just thinking...
Can you imagine the
look on Edward's face
if he heard you
talking back there?
I was only repeating
what you already said.
I have to admit,
this is unexpected...
Given the situation,
this is fairly bold action
for you to take, Colonel.
Like hell it is... I'm just
getting the ball rolling,
nothing more... Besides...
[Hughes] You need as
many people on your side
as you can get your
hands on now, Colonel.
It's taken long enough...
but I think I might finally
begin heeding his advice.
[car engine]
[Roy] Well, these are
either the gates to glory,
or the entrance way to Hell.
Wait here, Lieutenant...
If anything happens to me,
then at least you'll have a
chance of getting out alive.
[Hawkeye] No, sir.
[suprised grunt]
That was an order.
One that I cannot obey.
You're a stubborn one.
That's something you've
always known, sir.
All right... Will you stay here
if I promise to come back?
Yes... Happy hunting, sir.
[Raven] So you're Colonel
Roy Mustang, are you?
I got a call from my wife
about you a while ago.
Lieutenant General
Raven... I'm sorry ...
I haven't had time to
introduce myself...
I've been... very busy
since my transfer.
It's not a problem...
Tell me...
How is that old fox Grumman
doing these days, anyway?
The same as always sir.
[Grumman] Check.
[Roy, sighing] That's eleven
losses in a row for me.
Twelve, actually... But...
at least you put up a decent
fight this time around...
You were fine until you
were sure you'd won,
then you blew it.
So, I finished too weak.
Yes... You can't be
ruthless enough...
You're a lot like
Raven that way.
[Roy] Lieutenant General
Raven? From Central?
He's an exceptional soldier,
but too sentimental...
From what I've
heard, he'll even
tend to his wounded
men himself...
which leaves his whole
line of command in disarray...
You don't deploy your king to
tend to the pawns, do you?
How dare he say something
like that about me!
I was transferred to Central
because of the compassion
I showed my men in
the line of duty!
That border-dwelling old coot
should keep his trap shut!
Oh, uh.. sorry.
No, General, it's fine...
Actually, General
Grumman told me
that if that story
made you angry,
it meant you were still
a good and just man...
and that you were the officer
one could come to for support...
in case of an emergency.
I can't believe it... That old
fox got me again, didn't he?
[laughter]
[Raven] Oh, it's time
for my meeting.
Come on. You can walk with me.
[Raven] Have you
adjusted to Central yet?
No... I find conversing
with the citizens
around here quite
difficult, actually.
It's a mistake to
dismiss the value
of the word on the
street, Colonel.
[Roy] I know... But most of
it's just mindless drivel...
Like "Scar was seen
feeding a stray cat",
or "immortality has
been discovered."
Or maybe even that "Fuhrer
Bradley is a Homunculus."
Who knows?
[laughter]
I see.. You've got no
sense of humor, do you?
Are you certain you were
one of Grumman's men?
His sense of humor didn't
rub off on me much, sir.
[Raven] Well, At least
that bit of gossip
will give us something
to talk about over tea.
[Roy] Huh?...
I couldn't possibly
attend something like...
[door closing]
[Raven] Go on... Tell
your little joke.
You know, the one about the
Fuhrer being a Homunculus...
Please, go ahead.
[Bradley] What, Colonel
Mustang?.. Cat got your tongue?
Let's suppose for a moment that
I was actually a Homunculus,
as you say. Well now...
would that be so bad?
[Roy] Ah... I understand
now, Hughes...
When you said that
we were in trouble,
you didn't mean that danger
was closing in on us...
No... you meant the
danger was coming from us.
[Roy] Well, Fullmetal,
it looks like we've landed
ourselves in the pit of hell.
Where am I?
Blood?! What the--
What is this place?!
Al! Hey!... Is
anybody out there?!
[heavy breathing]
Where in the hell am I?!
Do you feel driven to keep
searching for someone
who is lost because you
fear to be left alone?
Or because you
have no choice?...
Because, even if you
cannot see them...
you cannot believe
they are gone.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 25...
Doorway of Darkness.
The fight continues... inside
the belly of the beast.