Beware
11 Years Ago
HISTORY
Such a pleasant scent. What do you think?
Everything is set up.
Let's give a nice, big smile.
And cheese!
From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
That's why we wanted to become true friends.
We crossed that barrier,
so that I could have you all to myself.
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Storm!
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shite
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so give me your approval
kaze ni notte ehon no page ga
As pages from a picture book flutter in the wind
kagirinaku kioku wo yurasu no
so sway my countless memories along with them
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
kurai kono sekai no naka
in this dark world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
Deliciousmell.
Slurp.
Kureha.
Good morning, growl.
Ginko, good morning!
Growl.
Slurp!
Kureha, you're so close...
What do you think you're doing?
Huh?
I asked why you're in my home!
We moved in.
Move, success!
To a long...
...and entangled stay!
Move-in soba!
To a long...
...and entangled stay!
Move-in soba!
G-Ge...
Get out!
Didn't your mother teach you to ask before moving in?
I'll have you packing by today's end!
But Kurechin, you ate the move-in soba too.
Th-This and that are different issues.
Look, it's her.
Oh, the girl who brings misfortune to her friends?
It doesn't just end with that! I heard that girls in her class
keep disappearing, one right after the other!
You should understand by now.
Misfortune befalls those around me.
It's the truth.
You'll be swept up by the Invisible Storm.
The Invisible Storm...
That's right. If you try to become
my friends, you'll just be excluded.
That's the rule of this flock. If you get it,
then stay away from me.
Kurechin's the one who doesn't get it!
Why does she think we came all this way to be her friends?
I'll protect Kureha from the Invisible Storm.
We won't back down on love, growl.
I'm not lying! She was a bear disguised as a human!
That's absurd.
Please believe me!
I saw Yurizono-san transform into a bear.
Yurizono-san ate Sumika—Izumino-san.
She told me so herself!
That's why I...
Flashback
I'm the one who killed...
Kureha-chan.
That's enough.
Sensei!
Poor thing. You must've been so shocked that you started seeing things.
No, I really did—
It doesn't have to be immediately.
However, one day you must open your eyes to reality.
I know! Your birthday is this coming Sunday, is it not?
Yes...
To think that yesterday's darling little
Kureha-chan is turning seventeen...
Time certainly does fly.
How would you like to celebrate?
A nice dinner? Or perhaps a present?
I don't feel up to anything...
This all reminds me of your mother's pendant.
I gave her that pendant for her seventeenth birthday.
I wasn't aware.
Yes, it was our promise of friendship.
Proof of our vow that we wouldn't forget love.
You wouldn't... forget love.
That's right. So long as you don't
forget love, you will never be alone.
So long as I don't forget love,
even if I were to lose something,
I won't become invisible.
Yet at times, love serves only to make us suffer.
It reminds us of our loss.
Our loss...
Flashback
Sumika.
At times like this, you must take a small step back and look elsewhere.
Kureha-chan, what you need right now is a new friend.
A new... friend?
Yes. Someone other than Izumino-san.
That's unnecessary.
What?
I don't need a new friend.
My only friend is Sumika.
I won't back down on my love!
Another fish tube pastry like Kurechin?
Is it really that deliciousmell?
It's the taste that Kureha loves.
Lovely taste?
Yes.
Something that will not yield to any storm, bear, or man.
Huh? Something like that really exists?
Yes, it does...
Flashback
11 Years Ago
HISTORY
Don't worry. You're not alone.
I'm your friend.
I love you.
Kumaria-sama...
Grind grind grind grind...
The memory of receiving someone's love.
That's why I crossed the barrier to come here.
Kureha, I want you.
I want to have you all to myself!
Tsubaki-san.
Do you have a minute?
Harishima Kaoru
LILY
We all talked it over this morning.
We made a mistake.
We realized what a horrible thing we had done.
Let us make it up to you!
To both you and Izumino-san.
Don't even start.
You have no right to say anything after excluding Sumika.
What do you want now? You started this "game", so see it through until the end.
I won't lose to the lot of you.
You can't turn me invisible!
I-I'm so sorry!
What have we done...
I'm sorry!
Only we will become Kureha's friends.
If you're a pest pest pest...
You'll be eaten by bears, growl.
Lily
Store
What's this? "Step one: The fastest way to a girl's heart is through her stomach."
Got it! Now all we need to do is make something she loves more than fish tube pastries!
Yuri Beef
Then she's ours!
I'm such a genius!
Deliciousmell, growl.
Ginko! I don't care how much your tummy is grumbling—you can't transform here.
The only meat we're allowed to eat is that of invisible girls.
So, what's Kurechin's favorite food?
Salted fish and Naporitan pasta.
Is she an old man at heart?
They've been her favorites since she was a little girl.
Then for tonight's dinner...
For Kureha
Welcome home, Kurechin!
What... are you doing?
Making dinner, growl.
We're whipping up the food you love.
The food... I love?
Yep! Your two favorites!
I-It couldn't be!
Yes! It's salted fish Naporitan!
Deliciousmell, growl!
I-Incredible!
It's a miraculous marriage!
Here, Ginko. A cherry tomato.
Open wide.
Here, Ginko. Mouth-watering honey pudding.
Here, Ginko. Mouth-watering salted salmon.
Open wide.
Now it's your turn, Kureha.
Open wide!
I'm not touching that.
Huh?
But aren't salted fish and
Naporitan pasta your favorites?
How do you know that?
W-Well...
The only person I've ever told was Sumika.
You're transfer students,
so you couldn't possibly know!
U-Um, good point...
I thought I told you to leave me alone!
But me and Ginko just want to become your friend—
Enough!
Friend this, friend that... why is everybody trying to make me back down on my love?
I don't need any new friends.
My only friend is Sumika.
My only love is Sumika! I don't need anything else!
Who are you really?
What do you even want from me?
You had me on pins and needles back there.
One more minute and I thought you'd tell her everything.
If you did that, we wouldn't be able to stay as human girls any more.
Those are the rules.
Aw man, if only Kurechin would
hurry up and remember you already.
Forgive my tardiness, Ginko.
I apologize for earlier.
In truth, I was overjoyed.
I have trouble expressing my feelings.
You don't need to worry about that, growl.
I thought that if we were to wash each other's nooks and crannies,
we could come to a greater
understanding of one another!
Gorgeousmell!
Say, Ginko. Does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
Say, Ginko. Does it feel good... here?
Yeah, that feels really good.
Say, Ginko. Does this place feel really good?
That place... feels so...
good!
There, all rinsed out.
Kureha-chan
From Sumika
Kureha-chan, here.
Flashback
Kureha-chan
I'll give this to you early.
One Month Earlier
HISTORY
My birthday isn't for a while though.
Yeah, I know.
But I need to give you this today.
You're strange, Sumika.
Wait! Don't open it up now.
I want you to read this here on your birthday.
Why?
It goes with your present.
A present?
You'll be spoiled if you read it. Please wait.
Okay?
Sure, I will.
Kureha-chan.
I want you to always be smiling just like a flower.
That is my love, so please.
I'm happy enough just watching you from afar.
What are you saying? I'll always be by your side.
That's right.
Kureha-chan, you didn't back down on your love for me.
I'll never, ever forget that.
Sumika?
They'll bloom before long.
Yeah...
Sumika... you're my only friend.
The garden...
We petitioned the school board to fix it
so that flowers could be planted once more.
I apologize for yesterday, but still...
I want to reverse the damage that the Invisible Storm caused.
If only we could fill it with flowers, then we might be able to grant Izumino-san's final wish.
Sumika's... final wish?
Yes. Your birthday is next Sunday, right?
What... about it?
I just so happened to hear about it.
It was right before Izumino-san's incident.
She wanted to celebrate your birthday by filling this garden with flowers, Tsubaki-san.
It goes with your present.
Sumika...
Please allow us to celebrate your birthday.
It was Izumino-san's wish.
Please, for Izumino-san!
As if! The two of us are Kurechin's friends!
Right, Ginko?
There's hardly any time left until Tsubaki-san's birthday.
Let's begin work today.
Agreed.
Girls, I commend your efforts over these past few days.
Ritual of Exclusion
EXCLUSION
Thanks to your dedication, Tsubaki Kureha has now begun to believe that we are her friends.
You need only endure it for a while longer.
Let us confirm our feelings once and for all.
Who is the evil we must exclude?
Let's search evil!
Ai Gekiko
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Ai Gekiko
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Tanaka Karen
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Tanaka Karen
Evil
Tsubaki Kureha
She's been selected.
Evil
Tsubaki Kureha
Tsubaki Kureha-san is confirmed as evil.
Evil
Tsubaki Kureha
Grind grind grind grind...
It's just like you said, Ginko.
That girl really was invisible.
Now we can eat her.
The time of judgement has come, growl.
Lily Court in Session
TRIAL
The Lily Court is now in session.
Bearfendant
Yurigasaki Lulu
Yurishiro Ginko
BEAR
I want to eat that girl. I'll protect Kureha from the Invisible Storm, growl!
That again?
Isn't it natural to want to protect someone you care about?
Shiny shine!
I wonder about that.
Bearfendants, you proclaim that you wish to protect Tsubaki Kureha,
and have consumed several members of the Invisible Storm, have you not?
Correct.
Then you are guilty!
Yurishiro Ginko, honestly answer my question.
What is your desire?
You say you wish to protect Tsubaki Kureha,
but that's simply pretext.
In truth, do you not simply want to become Tsubaki Kureha's only friend?
Objection!
The prosecution is relying on a sadistic presumption!
That's right! Ginko just wants to return the love Kurechin gave her.
She just wants a promised kiss!
Order in the court.
Objection overruled.
Yurishiro Ginko. Please answer the prosecution's inquiry.
He's right. I want to have Kureha all to myself.
Ginko?
I want to become Kureha's friend once more.
I want Kureha's love!
For that, I've crossed the barrier and even dragged Lulu with me.
You're wrong! I did that because I wanted to—
Even so, I won't back down on love!
I'll do anything for love!
Anything at all. I can no longer turn back.
I committed a grave sin.
Ginko, what do you mean by "grave sin"?
That's—
You don't need to say anything else, okay?
Your Honor, we have just bore witness to a confession of sin.
Please deliver your verdict of guilty to the bearfendants!
Yurishiro Ginko, is your love true?
It's true!
Even if that love is just to satisfy yourself?
Even if your pride will lead to your downfall?
I don't care. I'm a crimibear.
Understood.
Bearfendants, will you become invisible?
Or will you eat humans?
We will eat...
...humans!
Growl!
I shall hand down my sentence.
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
What do you want with me this late at night?
Me and Ginko are going to be Kurechin's friends.
Huh? What are you talking about?
We'll stop your plans right in their tracks.
Basically, we're gonna make you go away.
Shock!
Bear Shock!
Wh-What are you two?
I-It couldn't be!
We're bears!
We're going to eat you, growl!
No! H-Help me!
Ginko!
You fell right into our bear trap!
We already knew exactly who you were!
Kureha...
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger