When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Sh-She's dead!
But I have already narrowed down who the culprit is.
That is one of those dying messages.
I bet not.
Who's there?
You were behind all of this?
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
This week's Hayate is filled with suspense.
But please enjoy it with your entire family like you normally do.
The autumn wind really feels good.
Yes it does, Milady.
The foliage looks beautiful, too.
It was good to come all the way to a hot spring.
Yeah, really.
By the way Milady, which one is the inn we'll be staying at?
That one!
That?!
Wow, it's so classical.
The best way to enjoy a hot spring is to waste time at a rotting inn.
But I get this portentous feeling from there.
What?
It's emitting an untouchable vibe.
You just heard a scream from the inn, right?
Yes.
What's the matter here?
What happened?
Um, you look different from the opening.
Shut up! That situation would make me unable to get married!
I can smell a crime.
You just committed it.
I didn't expect to get caught up
in a murder case at a hot spring.
How entertaining.
I mean, we're in trouble.
We must contact the police.
R-Right.
We have a problem. We have a problem.
There is no need for that.
Will always come to the absolute truth.
Appears to be a tsundere and has the brain of a NEET.
Her name is Detective Nagi!
That bag for grade schoolers fits you surprisingly well.
That's not what you're supposed to jab at!!!
Onee-chan!
I always thought of you as a hopeless sister, but who knew this would happen...
I'm sorry for you, but please hold yourself together.
Yes, I know.
Actually, I have something I want you all to see.
What?
A video tape?
Yes. This just arrived for me by motorbike delivery.
I think it's something my sister took.
I wonder if it's recording okay.
This is this room, right?
Yes, it looks like it.
Hina. By the time you watch this,
I might already have become a star in the sky.
I guess the saying that pretty people die young was true.
Unbelievable what she can say.
Um, the background has...
To tell you the truth, I've been told to come
to this inn by an unknown individual through a letter.
It sounds like the person holds a grudge against me.
But I still don't have a clue who it is.
I think the person should be coming to this room soon, but...
I'm starting to lose interest.
Hina! If I die, then the person who killed me
will be the next person who appears on this screen.
Make sure you catch that person and get all the reparations you can for me.
Do you hear?
She's here!
It ends there?
No way, it stopped at the most crucial point.
This is horrible.
It's as bad as a mother who tricks her children by calling a honey-coated cucumber a melon.
No, it's as bad as saying pudding with soy sauce is sea urchin.
No, no.
It's as bad as calling an orange with seaweed and soy sauce a salmon roe.
This tape... The criminal must have physically cut him or herself out of the tape, then sent it.
So, this is a challenge letter to me from the criminal.
But I have already narrowed down who the culprit is.
Really?
Yes. The criminal is...
The criminal is?
You!!!
Me?
I'm only a guest staying next door.
As well as a super side character
that hasn't shown up since episode 23.
I can tell everything that happened.
I was in episode 25, too!
You called the victim out and...
Don't come any closer!
You try and touch me,
and I'll have you pay all my pub bills that have piled up!
Using a polka-dot snake that just happened to pass by...
That's what happened. So, isn't it a perfect deduction?
Well...
You just copied the most famous trick.
Apologize to Mr. Doyle.
You are under arrest.
No, it wasn't me.
I will hear no words from you. Give it up.
No.
Grab.
Break.
Don't treat my honey as a criminal.
Watch out, Milady.
Nice one, Hayate.
Milady, the criminal seems to be someone else.
Yes, to be honest, I had that feeling, too.
I see...
Then the next most suspicious ones are you three.
Wh-Where am I?
You called the victim out,
and using a polka-dot octopus that passed by...
There you have it.
What is this polka-dot octopus?
We weren't even in that scene!
Stop resisting and be arrested!
There is someone else who's likely to have a motive, isn't there?!
Right, a motive.
Yes, you have a point.
An individual who probably holds
the biggest grudge against the victim is...
Who else other than the debt-ridden butler?
Wait, what are you saying?
Glare~
All of you, please don't glare at me with those suspecting eyes.
You're the one person I trusted.
I said it's not me.
I told you it's not me!
Using a polka-dot elephant that passed by...
You look as if you wouldn't even kill an insect, and yet...
Milady, your deductions are only taking place in the wilderness.
Ah, is this Yama-san?
I have the criminal in hand,
but the victim won't be coming back.
Besides, the setting has changed from the inn to Africa all of a sudden.
How about we go to the roof top
for another chat under the sunset?
And who are you talking to, anyway?
Hey!
How many times do you have to kill me?
The story isn't progressing at all!
Mind you, it's really embarrassing to play dead in this outfit.
Hinagiku!
Ah, yes!
You better do it properly as the script says.
Yes...
Collapse.
Hey, what's that?
Blood: Hibiya
That has to be one of those dying messages.
What's a dying message?
You don't even know that?
Allow me to explain.
A dying message is a hint the victim leaves behind on purpose to aid later deduction.
Tama's Last Words: Cheney
I see.
But, what's "Hibiya"?
Allow me to explain again.
Hibiya is an area in Tokyo made up of
the Choyoda ward and Yuuraku-chou, close to Ginza.
As a bit of trivia, this is where
the very first street light in Japan was installed.
We don't need to know that kind of trivia.
Anyway, if we can decode this dying message, we can figure out who the criminal is, right?
It's starting to become like a real detective story.
Yeah.
But this is very hard.
Hard?
No, not yet.
This is nowhere close to the mystery behind the pyramids and UFOs!
What did she say?!
Um, I'm not sure about using that other glasses character.
Exactly!
You, indeed, are my assistant. You have good instincts.
D-Do I?
As he suggests, this crime was committed by a character that's not here.
Another character?
Yes. The criminal must be hiding somewhere after committing the murder.
And the location is?
You're not going to say Hibiya, are you?
Take a good second look at it.
It says Hibiya no matter how you read it.
No, the ********* seeds around it are part of the message, too.
Look, the written part is the right side of kanji.
And if you treat the ********* seeds as radicals,
Words: Coed Bath
You can read "coed bath" from it.
Isn't it amazing?
Unbelievable deduction.
And, at this inn, there happens to be a coed bath, too.
The criminal has to be here.
I really don't think that's possible.
There!
Who could the criminal be?
Continue to the second part.
Kaneme no mono wo! Hayaku!
Kaneme no mono wo! Hayaku! = Grab the valuables! Fast!
Kuminzei, haratta?
Kuminzei, haratta? = Did you pay your taxes?
Drop Out Trio's Glutton Dreamy Mood!
Hey.
What?
How about we make things clear. Are we to eat or provide a service shot in the hot spring?
Eh?
The potency of this spring is-
Risa-chin, you're supposed to do that after we eat!
It's a merry-go-round of flavor!
No, you haven't eaten one yet!
Gilgamesh.
That's the wrong show!
This tastes so good.
Who's there?
Don't say that it looks different from before.
M-Maria-san. When did you get here?
And, you are the criminal, Maria-san?
I'm not!
Then why?
Don't worry about the details.
Sexy shots have to happen in a suspense story.
We are using a towel for the sake of broadcasting restrictions,
but in reality, please do not use a bath towel in the bath.
Gosh!
Let's keep this going and let the second "must have" happen!
Gourmet food scene!
There it is.
Please enjoy the fresh seafood!
Afterwards, we have a magic show scheduled.
Here's your lukewarm gasoline.
Good stuff~
On to the third "must have"!
Inquiry at a bar!
So, what do you want?
Does this person ring a bell?
Ring a bell?
A loud one!
That girl is my older sister's friend's cousin
and the burglar that took my boyfriend away!
Rather than a suspense show,
it's becoming an afternoon soap opera.
Here's the fourth "must have".
Mada mada dane!
Yay!
Advantage, Makimura-Izumi.
Yes, it's getting exciting.
It's all messed up.
We have trouble!
Maria-san! You were in the hot spring until now?
Yes.
I went back to our room once, and I found this terrifying thing.
What is it, Maria? Stop beating around the bush and tell us.
The corpse is gone!
She's right.
It is gone.
A disappearing body. The most suspenseful moment in a suspense story.
Oh no. The case is about to become forever wrapped in mystery.
But, who hid it?
The criminal, of course.
The criminal?
Yes, must be trying to cause confusion in me to disrupt the investigation.
In that case...
Wh-What is this all of a sudden?
I'm sure they can find the key clue.
And here's something under the table.
Th-This is-
It looks like a voice recorder.
Show it to me.
Is this the scream we originally heard?
It sounds like it.
But why?
What's the significance behind it?
It's here━━━━━━(ﾟ∀ﾟ)━━━━━━!
The mystery is solved, my dear Watson.
"M-My dear Watson"...
Next Nagi's hint.
Video.
So, have you figured out the criminal and the trick behind it?
Um...
Give me a snack.
Oh, I mean, Trick or Treat.
Trick or Treat.
W-Wait, give me candy!
Halloween isn't celebrated around Japan well at all.
This is a different kind of trick.
Why are we at a place like this all of a sudden?
It can't be helped. Climax scenes by a cliff are the greatest "must have" in a suspense show.
Everything is perfect if we have Funa**** Jirou.
Allow me to explain the truth behind this case now.
Hey!
The scene of the crime was not that room.
If we assume the crime took place in a completely different room at a completely different inn, everything makes sense.
What do you mean? Explain one piece at a time so it makes sense.
Sure.
First, the criminal met the victim at a certain inn.
Recorded the victim's voice during the incident.
After that, took the victim to a room at a separate inn that looks similar,
Wait, wait, wait, it'll show! It'll show! It'll show!
in other words, carried her into that room we were in, and...
Be gentler with me! No, stop!
Gentler!
...made others hear the scream using a timer to think that the crime had just happened.
You just heard a scream from the inn, right?
Yes.
Everything was planned to create an alibi.
Here! Here, here! I have a question!
What is it?
Where's the proof?
I think the voice recorder alone is pushing it a little.
The greatest proof is on the video we watched.
In here!
Play.
I wonder if it's recording fine.
Stop!
I don't see anything suspicious.
Don't you notice something about that wall scroll?
It's completely different from the one in that room.
Exactly.
The criminal wasn't able to keep an eye open for the wall scroll.
There are four other mistakes, as well.
Those who get them correct will get-
Coming this far, you all know who the criminal is, right?
I remember one person coming late!
And that individual brought the video, right?
She said something about
a motorbike delivering it and what not.
But if she is the criminal, then everything does make sense.
Then...
M-Me?
Hinagiku-san, we never thought you'd be the criminal.
But it was so convincing.
Yes. She's the least suspicious of us.
Therefore she becomes suspicious.
Yeah, yeah.
That was a wonderful deduction.
I never thought you'd figure it out.
Yes, she's right.
I am the criminal.
No, that's wrong.
The criminal is not Hinagiku.
Hey, don't take my scene away!
You surprised me so much, the anesthesia burned out in me.
From the developments, only I can be the criminal.
But that would make this all too simple and boring.
Um, that's making it hard
to figure out who's speaking, so can you stop it?
You've all forgotten something!
There is one more very suspicious person!
One more person?
Yes! And that individual is...
That individual is?
The person doing the voice in the sky!
Me?
Milady, isn't that getting too absurd?
No, this is good.
But I don't think the viewers will accept it.
It's a suspense story produced and enacted by me.
I won't let anyone complain.
Hey!
A tidal wave!
Let's get out of here!
Hold it!
Onee-chan?
I can't take this! Why do I not get
to come out halfway into the show?!
You're a corpse, so stop coming back to life!
I can't possibly play dead forever!
You screwed up my script I wrote without sleep!
You leave me without a choice but to use my last resort!
Here comes the service time!
The best thing to do in autumn is to enjoy the hot spring while enjoying the foliage.
Really, it's so soothing.
All of you, too, hope you have a good ****** dreamy mood.
This is heaven.
Wh-Why is the men's bath so small?
Did you say something?
Don't move! It got pinched in!
What's pinched?
Don't move!
And so, Glutton Dreamy Mood.
It was a twenty-minute long special.
Next time, we'll fight against siblings.
Right, I forgot about you.
We don't have much time left.
Come, Mysterious Dark Butler Two!
Defeat the butler Ayasaki Hayate and bring him to us!
Bring him to us!
Go!
B-Fire!
Take this.
This is...
B-Fire!
Go! Hayate Blaster!
You better remember this!
Come whenever you like, Mysterious Butlers!
Oh. What the heck am I doing...
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Whee! Bounce! Bounce! This is Sanzenin Nagi.
This is Ayasaki Hayate.
I'm your idol, Katsura Yukiji.
Katsura-sensei, what are you here for?
Aren't you kind, Ayasaki-kun?
But forget that! When the heck
is my character song going to be finished?
We can't expect many sales from you.
Yes. It might be best to duo with Tama.
Ayasaki-kun, you can talk big now, huh?
Next week's guest will be the Hamster!
See you!
So you used to call Sakuya-san
"Saku-neechan" when you were little, Milady?
It's a horrid past.
Nagi never took care of little kids,
so she's a brat no matter how much she grows.
Don't make fun of me.
If I had younger siblings, then I could take care of them better than Saku.
Are you sure? Then prove it.
You got it.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Do You Like Rich, Pretty Ladies?
Did you know? Of the Wright brothers,
Orville, the younger brother, is the first one that flew.