We're finally back...
Hey, Waver.
Where are you looking? Over here, over here.
G-Grandpa!
What are you doing?
Aw, who cares? Come up here.
Let's talk for a while.
Talk?
Why do we have to talk on the roof?
Grandpa, can't it wait?
Oh, don't be like that.
They really like you, kid.
Listen, they're just under my spell—
Well, go up anyway.
It appears he has something important to tell you.
I'll wander about and patrol, so it will be safe.
Don't worry.
Worrying isn't the problem...
You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
So that nobody would have to cry ever again
we all scream and pray on fields stained red with blood
yet our pleas reach no one
I will be able to leave my solace behind
The moon's beautiful light
shines on all that makes up
the beginning
With eyes kept barely open I still see you far away
and trust your grief
This is the best place
to catch a few rays from the rising sun.
Sit down.
Here, I got you some coffee.
It'll warm you up.
Grandpa,
how long have you been up here?
When I woke up this morning, you weren't back yet.
So I thought I'd watch the sun come up, while I waited for my grandson to come home.
When you were little,
we used to come up here and gaze at the stars all the time...
Do you remember?
Yeah, sure.
When Martha and I decided to live in Japan,
we made sure to build our house here, on Miyama Hill,
so that we could watch the skylight from the roof.
We dreamed of sitting out here, on the roof,
alongside our grandson,
to watch the stars.
We never thought we'd have the chance, though.
Our real grandchildren never once came out here.
Whenever I watched the stars, I was always alone.
Hey, Waver...
You aren't our grandson, are you?
It's so strange, the way we really believed you were.
To be honest,
you were a little too nice to be our grandson...
You aren't mad?
Well, maybe I should be angry.
But lately, Martha's been so happy...
Before, I wouldn't have imagined it.
Really, I'm grateful to you two.
It doesn't seem to me
that you're here because you desire to do us any harm.
Actually, what do you think about it?
If possible, I'd like for you to stay a while longer.
I'm sorry...
But I can't promise that.
I can't even guarantee I'll make it back here safely.
So you two are risking your lives?
Yes.
Well, I don't know how important
what you're doing is to you...
But when you look back, after a long life,
you'll realize that there is nothing
that's really worth risking that life for.
Ensouzan
Roughly forty hours since I last slept...
To win the battle and summon the Grail,
one must perform the ritual
at one of the four Fuyuki ley lines.
Kotomine Kirei was neither at the church nor at the Tohsaka estate.
Which leaves the other two.
Here, at Enzousan,
and the Fuyuki Citizen's Building.
Given the ley lines' relative power, he is more likely to pick this one.
Even if he's chosen the Citizen's Building,
I can launch a frontal assault there.
If Maiya were still alive,
I would have sent her to secure it.
Once again, I'm alone...
Come to think of it,
I never considered relying on her.
Since last night,
I've been searching the entire city for Irisviel.
But I have found nothing.
I am deeply sorry.
Well, then...
Should it be necessary, use the Command Seal
and summon me, as before.
Woman.
Can you hear me, woman?
Kotomine...
Kirei.
This is where Caster's Master once hid.
Emiya Kiritsugu never was able to find it.
Soon, the Holy Grail War will end.
It's quite likely that I shall be the one
to grant the Einzbern clan's wish.
Are you unhappy that it would be me?
There is but one man to whom I would entrust the Grail.
And it is not you,
Executor.
Emiya Kiritsugu has already seen right through you.
He recognizes you as his greatest enemy.
Prepare yourself.
To me, your words are a gospel.
Emiya Kiritsugu is exactly as I imagined him, after all.
How laughable.
You are further from him than anyone!
What?
While Kiritsugu can see through you, the reverse is impossible...
You have none of the things
that he carries in his heart.
Why do you speak of me?
I'll admit it..
I am an empty man.
However...
How do he and I differ?
Devoting himself to war, without gain, for all these years...
Senseless slaughter...
Utter recklessness.
Wasted effort!
If he does not doubt, as I do, then what is he?!
Answer me.
What does Emiya Kiritsugu desire from the Holy Grail?
What prayer would he entrust to the wish-granting device?
Very well..
I'll tell you.
Emiya Kiritsugu's wish
is for humanity's salvation;
to end war and bloodshed.
Forever.
Peace on Earth.
What was that?
You can never understand.
That is the difference between him and you...
He has something to believe in.
Conflict is humanity's basest instinct.
To eliminate it would mean
humanity's own elimination.
It's futile as an ideal.
Childish nonsense!
And that is why
his only hope is for a miracle...
Many times, he has been forced
to sacrifice those he loves for his beliefs.
Yes...
He is too kind to chase ideals.
He must love,
even knowing it will mean losing that love...
I understand...
I understand very well.
So that is Emiya Kiritsugu.
At last, I see it...
My reason for fighting.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
I shall destroy
your ideals before your very eyes.
The Holy Grail shall follow suit.
Oh, you're up, boy?
I said to wake me when it got to be night.
What are you doing?
Sorry, sorry.
But I thought it might be good to take our time with preparations.
Tonight, there is no reason to rush.
Why?
Well, it's merely an instinct.
But it feels like things will end tonight.
The night air seems too still.
Does that mean that fewer participants remain?
From here on, only the strong are left.
Wh-What was that?
A strange prana surge...
I've felt something similar before.
That pattern...
What?
Is it some code?
Four and seven, in different colors.
"Victory" and "success."
If the church is sending up that signal,
does that mean the Grail War is over?
No...
It doesn't seem to be coming from the church.
Then they aren't the ones who sent the message?
In essence, someone is getting ahead of themselves.
Saying, "If you object, come and get me."
It's a challenge.
Tonight will decide things!
I see.
This is it, then...
Quite right!
And now that our battlefield is known,
I must go forth in such a way as to bring honor to the Rider class!
Come forth...
my partner!
Now, kid...
It may not be as smooth a ride as by chariot...
What are you doing?
Come on.
From this point,
only the strong can continue, right?
My Servant...
By this Command Seal, I, Waver Velvet, order you...
Rider, fight until you gain victory.
By this Command Seal, I order you...
Rider, win the Holy Grail.
Rider, take the world for your own.
I will not allow failure.
Now, I'm not your Master anymore.
Go...
Go wherever.
I don't even want to see you...
Sure, I'll be on my way.
After all those annoying orders,
are you not ready to see this to the end?
You thrice-damned fool!
Listen...
I have no Command Seals!
I quit being your Master...
Why would you still take me?
I...
Master or not,
you are my friend.
I-I'm...
You're really okay with me?
I can stay by your side?
You've been through many battles with me.
What are you talking about?
Idiot.
Up until now, have you not faced the same enemies as I?
That means you are my friend!
So hold your chest high, and consider yourself
my equal.
All right...
I shall begin by addressing your first order.
Boy, open your eyes, and watch to the end!
Yeah, do it...
Right before my eyes!
He chose the place least suited to the ritual,
in order to gain the initiative.
In other words,
his plan is not to steal the Grail.
But to use it as bait,
to kill the other Masters and me.
That simplifies things.
If he's willing to make such a stupid move,
I'll just eliminate him quickly.
Kotomine Kirei...
You look particularly ferocious tonight,
Kirei.
Now, what will you do?
Do you wish for me to wait here?
If your powers were released at close range,
they could endanger the ceremony.
If you want to fight at full strength,
go out and meet them.
Very well.
But what if this place falls under attack while I'm away?
I'll use the Command Seal to save myself.
Is that permissible?
I shall allow it.
But I do not guarantee the Grail's safety.
Tonight, I shan't hold back.
That would be the worst outcome,
but if that ensues, it would be fate.
Kirei...
You seem to have found your reason to fight.
But have you still no prayer to offer the Grail?
I can think of nothing I want.
The only answer I can give is that I hope that nothing will interfere with this fight.
Honestly...
As I suspected, the only recourse is to let the Grail reveal what hides within your heart.
If it appears Saber will arrive before I can return,
have Berserker entertain her for a while.
Understood.
Speaking of Saber,
what happened to the doll that was so important to her?
The Holy Grail's vessel is within her, is it not?
I killed her.
I had no reason to let her live.
Are you crying,
Mother?
Hey, Mother...
I had a scary dream.
I dreamed I became a cup...
And inside me,
these seven big lumps appeared...
It's okay...
It's okay!
I won't let that happen.
That will never happen to you, Ilya.
I know that
the bonds of fate will release you.
What is this place...
Inside the Holy Grail?
That's impossible!
Then...
If I'm in here...
Who am I?
That's right...
This is inside the Holy Grail.
The omnipotent wishing device that will dispel all the world's sadness,
and dispel all suffering.
I will have the power to make that happen.
The end
is nearly at hand.
Episode 21:
All the Evil in the World
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
One enemy is the mighty King of Heroes,
a worthy opponent!
Let us demonstrate our path of conquest!
King of Conquerors, I shall show you the end of your eternal dream.
I, myself, shall show you the harsh reality.
Next Time:
The Sea at the End of the World