What's wrong?
Oh? So you're from Mistral?
Such a boring place.
But the food there sure is delicious.
And there are lots of beautiful gals too.
It's already been half a year since the truce.
Just be glad we've managed to survive in one piece.
All right! I win again!
How did you win again?
Man, that's bullshit!
Hey missy, you awake there?
Here's your share of the winnings.
Oh! Caramel!
Th-Thank you for giving me such an expensive gift...
...um...
...Sergeant!
It's nothing. They say if we treat the bugler nicely,
we'll be able to hear the calls for retreat loud and clear!
Speaking of which, there's no conscription anymore,
so it's rare to see a new recruit.
Did you volunteer?
Yup! It's because I wanted to learn music.
I mean...
Honesty is a good thing!
Work hard, missy!
Private Second Class, what's your name?
Kanata.
My name is Sorami Kanata!
kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I'll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won't be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you'll play the song of tomorrow.
The Resounding Sound
The Town of Dawn
Seize is having a festival today.
A festival?
So this is as far as I can take you.
Look!
That is your newly assigned post.
It's commonly known as the Time-Trumpeting Fort.
You are to go there yourself.
Yes!
Notice of Appointment for Private Second Class Sorami Kanata:
You are hereby assigned to the 1121st Platoon stationed in Seize, Trois State.
As ordered by the Republic of Helvetia's Central Command.
Mission accomplished at 1320!
Thank you, sir!
The famous town of water and glass, Seize.
Wait a sec!
I'm supposed to report in at 1500.
I'll finally be able to make you sing.
Confirming direction... Check!
Confirming time... Check!
Confirming equipment... Check!
Forward...
...march!
G-flat... What a beautiful sound.
Whoa!
A fish!
10.25 yen.
My, what a pretty doll—
S-Sorry!
What is it, Rio?
A kitten who was too engrossed in the festival...
...ran full speed in some random direction.
These things happen.
Kittens do like to run around aimlessly.
That's what makes them cute, isn't it?
It's fine if it's just a stray.
But unfortunately, this was a house cat.
That really surprised me.
But I was able to find something else wonderful.
What's the matter?
Thank you!
Oh, it's a soldier! Are you from the fort?
This is great!
Thank you for protecting us!
You sprayed me earlier, right?
And... open fire!
Thank you.
Hey!
Are you an idiot or something?!
Actually getting involved...
What are you going to do looking like that?!
Um... I...
Bless you.
Thank—
Honestly... Come with me!
How's the temperature?
It's perfect!
That's great.
She really was an easy target.
Couldn't you even dodge?
It's fine. This kind of dye disappears on its own once you dry it.
Don't worry about it.
That was the festival event, right?
It's from a legend in Seize.
A legend...
What kind?
About the Flame Maidens who protected this town.
Sorry for troubling you.
You owe me.
It seems the repairs are finished as well.
And then there's this...
Filicia, eh?
That meddlesome girl...
She's late.
She's late! She's so late!
She's so freaking late!
And we came all the way here just to welcome her too!
I know.
But let's continue to wait, shall we?
Isn't this a gift from your father?
It's a nice one.
D-flat.
I'm done. Thank you very much for your hospitality!
I don't know why, but I'm always getting lost.
But thanks to that, I was able to meet such wonderful people!
You're quite welcome.
But don't get lost out here, all right?
Huh?
You can recognize notes?
It's a very clear and yet somehow...
...very nostalgic sound.
That wasn't what I—
You thief!
You idiot!
Th-Thank you very much.
Give me a break.
Are you going to throw your life away for that thing?
But that bell...
It's fine. It's probably meant to be.
She's late.
I'm glad.
Excuse me.
I have something to do so I'll be leaving now.
Don't get lost again.
That bell...
I'm sure it was precious to her.
What should I do?
Oh no!
That way?
Forward march!
Do you want to see things developed by your voice?
Do you want to see a purer air, a world with the changed hearts of men?
But everything on the Earth is fragile.
Nothing is meaningless.
When all is said and done, reality is not always mirrored in your eyes.
The Flame Maidens?
A very long time ago...
Which to others, see horrid and demonic things.
This is a story from before the world became the way it is now.
Deep within the bowels of the town,
No matter whose story you hear,
dwelt a winged demon.
only your eyes can tell the difference.
That demon spewed flames that made the ground tremble,
We'll sing the world's colors
and caused the people to suffer greatly.
One day, the demon snatched up all the maidens that lived in the fort,
and not forget a single one.
and imprisoned them within an underground labyrinth.
Everything has a reason,
However, the maidens did not give up.
like the stars in the symphony of life.
Using the heavenly gift they had received, they called upon each other with the golden horn...
...and finally escaped the labyrinth.
With the aid of a giant spider,
they defeated the demon and beheaded it.
Everyone makes a song of the skies.
However, the head continued to spew flames.
Everything is taught and bound.
If nothing was done,
the village below would soon turn to ash.
In order to stop the flames,
When we see each other,
the maidens took turns embracing the demon's head.
we'll become one with the stars.
As the demon's head continued to blaze in the maidens' arms...
...the villagers doused them both with water every day.
It went on for an entire year,
until the flame finally died out.
Henceforth,
in order to thank the maidens in Heaven who had sacrificed their lives,
the Water-Dousing Festival came to be.
In the end, the new girl didn't show up.
Who cares about that?
Commander, hurry up and look! It's Rio-senpai!
It really suits her well.
Giving her this job was indeed a good decision.
But didn't we draw lots to—
I got lost again.
I'm so useless.
I was able to have fun when I got lost...
But that was because I was able to meet some nice strangers.
I don't want to be alone.
Are you lost?
I want to see my mommy.
It's all right.
If you wish for it from the bottom of your heart...
...your thoughts will definitely reach her.
Really?
Yes. Sound will resound.
Will resound...
Because it will resound...
It will be conveyed.
May the Flame Maidens here be at peace.
Embracing the demon and nullifying its curse,
they offered themselves, so that the demon would never awaken again.
This is...
The sound of a golden horn...
Don't tell me the demon has awakened!
Kureha!
Please... let my sound... reach someone!
It reached.
The sound resounds... and will...
Hurry and wake up! Private Sorami Kanata!
Huh? Where am I?
When are you going to wake up?
This is the Time-Trumpeting Fort,
the post of the 1121st Platoon!
Yesterday... um... Sorry for causing you trouble!
You can say that again.
I'm really sorry!
But...
I'm just kidding.
But don't endanger yourself like that again.
Doing all that for this stupid bell...
I'll tell you...
A trumpet!
...why this place is known as the Time-Trumpeting Fort.
It's the sound of the sky.
Kazumiya Rio.
That's my name.
I will teach you how to be a good bugler.
Thank you, Sergeant Major Rio!
Just call me Rio.
It's Filicia's...
...the Commander's desire.
We don't go by rank here.
Then Rio-senpai!
Well then, let's start right now.
Play me a morning call right now!
The girl this time seems to be very lacking.
Let's remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let's move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You're just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know, you know, a little happy
let's make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you hear my precious note?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
The First Battle
The Story of the Chair
Next time: The First Battle · The Story of the Chair