I'm sorry, but I don't know what to do anymore.
I'll apologize to everyone. I don't know what else to do.
No need to apologize.
You were just in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
You've done all you
could possibly hope to do.
I'll see what I can do about this.
But no matter what I do, it won't play out the
way you intended.
Send
Message Sent
Sorry to ask you on such short notice.
really sorry, but i cant really do anything about the time or place
No, if that's how it is, there's nothing you can do.
but i hate not being able to do anything for you
Do you have any other ideas? Do you know anyone else who can?
hmm...
Senpai?
just kidding
I dont know if they'll help, but if you use them right
Senpai?
just kidding
I dont know if they'll help, but if you use them right
they might dance for you
just kidding
I dont know if they'll help, but if you use them right
they might dance for you
I think that should be fine.
Will you be available that day?
I'd love to g0!
Sorry, I meant go
If you could, that would be wonderful.
I'll tell you the time and place later.
It sounds like lots of fnu@
If you could, that would be wonderful.
I mean, fun@
I'll tell you the time and place later.
It sounds like lots of fnu@
fun!
I mean, fun@
If you could, that would be wonderful.
You may already know this,
but you don't need to fix every typo.
Anyone will know what you mean.
You may already know this,
but you don't need to fix every typo.
Anyone will know what you mean.
Relaly?
You may already know this,
but you don't need to fix every typo.
Anyone will know what you mean.
Relaly?
Really?
You may already know this,
but you don't need to fix every typo.
Anyone will know what you mean.
Relaly?
Really?
Oh, I see!
but you don't need to fix every typo.
Anyone will know what you mean.
Relaly?
Really?
Oh, I see!
So, if you could.
Anyone will know what you mean.
Really?
Oh, I see!
So, if you could.
Oh, and since you're coming,
Yes?
Feel free to bring some friends.
Maybe, say, three?
Can I really?
You're in the Classics Club, right?
If you could bring the other members, that would be wonderful.
taikutsu na madobe ni
Sitting bored by the back window,
fukikomu kaze ni
A breeze blew through the room
kao wo shikameta no wa
The reason I screwed up my eyes
terekusasa no uragaeshi
Was to hide how embarrassed I was
Mazui Presents
Hyouka
aimai ni unazuku tenohira no kyou
I gave a faint nod from the edge of my palm
egaiteru jibun wa sukoshi oogesa de
The "me" I was trying to be was a bit more than I was
nani ka kawarisou na ki ga shiteiru yo
I get the feeling that something is going to change soon
kokoro ni yobikakeru kimi no sei da ne
You reached out to touch my heart; it must be because of you
kumorizora nozoita yokan
I had a feeling, looking into the clouds
te wo nobasou itsu yori mo chikaradzuyoi yuuki de
I reached out my hand, with a stronger courage than I'd ever had
hikari mo kage mo mada tookute
The light and the dark are still so far away
sore demo bokura wa
But even though they are
yasashisa no riyuu ga shiritai
We still want to know how people could be so kind
ima wa dare no namae demo nai
Now it doesn't matter whose name it may be
kagayaki no kanata he
Beyond the horizon's light,
zenbu kako ni naru mae ni
Before it all becomes the past,
mitsuke ni ikou
Let's go and find out
Wow, I guess they made it to the finals.
Looks that way.
That's pretty amazing.
Let's Go to the Screening!
Let's Go  to the Screening!
Let's Go to theScreening!
Let's Go to the Screening!
It makes me wonder if I might have some sort of skill like that,
but in the end it would seem Fukube Satoshi is a man of no talents.
They say that great talents bloom late, but that's rather unlikely at this point.
You're a database. What's to complain about?
Well, I do take some pride in how much I know,
but even at my best I still wouldn't even qualify for "Quiz King" or anything.
Really?
Yep.
It really makes me jealous of people like that.
But it's not all flowers and sunshine for them.
What do you mean?
Geniuses can't choose to live normal lives like ours, even if they wanted to.
Is a normal life something that you wish for, Houtarou?
I see how you might.
But do you really think you'll be able to live one?
What do you mean by that?
If you ask, I would say Fukube Satoshi has no talents.
But for Oreki Houtarou, I think I'll withhold any comments.
If you think I'm not a normal person then you have terrible observational skills.
I'm just saying that I'm withholding my opinion on you for now.
Anyway, shouldn't we hurry up?
Mayaka will get mad if we're late to the meeting.
True.
Seriously. It's our summer break.
IN THE FINALS!
You're late!
There you go trying to play it off again!
Where's Chitanda?
She's still not here...
I'm a bit worried.
What's with the difference in treatment here?
It's the difference in how you live your lives.
Sorry I'm late!
A preview screening!
Let's go to the screening!
Class 2-F is going to show a movie they made.
An acquaintance of mine in that class wants to hear our opinion.
Discussing it with her took more time than I thought.
What kind of movie is it?
A mystery movie, apparently.
Sounds interesting!
Audio Visual Classroom
It should be here.
We're here, as promised!
I see. Thank you for coming.
Welcome.
I appreciate your taking the time to assist us.
This is Ibara Mayaka-san, Fukube Satoshi-san, and Oreki Houtarou-san.
They're all members of the Classics Club.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Irisu Fuyumi.
I thought so! Irisu-senpai!
I knew I'd seen you before!
Sorry, I don't remember you.
I saw you at the Cultural Festival Committee Meeting in June.
I was amazed at how well you handled the dispute between the Light Music Club and the Drama Club.
It's rare to see Satoshi hold anyone in such high regard...
I'm afraid I don't recall.
I see...
How do you know her, Chii-chan?
My family has known hers for a long time.
She helped me out a lot when I was younger.
It must be tough being part of a distinguished old family.
Now then...
This is the movie that our class made.
I'd like you to watch it and give your honest opinion of it.
Sounds fun!
You just want us to watch it and tell you what we think?
Is there something wrong?
Even if we don't like it, it's not like you're going to redo the whole thing.
Are you just trying to get us to advertise it?
No.
Then I don't understand why you want us to watch it.
A valid question.
You are correct in that there would be no point in simply having you watch it.
But I believe it would be more efficient for you to just watch it for now.
Well?
Efficient, huh?
This movie has yet to be titled.
We're calling it "Mystery" for now.
When you're finished, I have a question I'd like to ask you.
It will start shortly.
Good luck.
Good luck?
Several volunteers from class 2-F decided to produce an exhibit on the history of Narakubo at the Kanya Festival.
They went there as part of their research into it.
Aren't we there yet?
Yamanishi Midori
Sugimura Jirou
We're almost there.
It shouldn't be five minutes.
But you said that five minutes ago!
Senoue Mamiko
Kounosu Yuri
This is a tough walk.
Katsuta Takeo
It's hot, and I'm tired.
Kaitou Takeo
You're not the only one!
Come on, let's go!
Can't really expect more out of an independent film.
We can see it now.
That's Narakubo over there.
Wow.
Alright. It looks like a good place to research.
Let's find a place where we can spend the night.
We can start our research after that.
Doesn't that place over there look good?
Let's check it out.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
It's a mansion!
Mansion?
It's dusty...
It looks like the roof is intact.
It'd be dangerous to sleep here.
There's broken glass on the floor.
Let's find a place where we can sleep before it gets dark.
There's a floor map here.
A floor map!
Let's split up and look around inside.
Isn't that dangerous?
And wouldn't the rooms be locked?
That won't be a problem.
They should be here.
This is the office?
What's this key here?
I think that's the master key.
We'd be in trouble if we lost that, so we should leave it here.
I see. That makes sense.
Here.
Now we can enter the rooms.
Alright, let's look for a room we can use.
Okay!
Wouldn't you normally go look together?
What are you trying to say?
The crime is going to happen soon.
I'll bet anything on it.
He started it!
The crime occurred shortly after.
I knew it!
Find anything on your side?
Mine had shards from a mirror all over.
We won't be able to sleep there unless we clean it up.
I see. Mine was in a similar state.
Hey, Sugimura!
Find anything?
Mine was fairly clean. We might able to use it.
I'm coming down now.
Where's Kaitou-kun?
Is he still looking?
That's fine, let's go find him.
A reception room?
He's not here...
That's weird...
Try the end of the hall?
It won't open.
It's locked.
What do we do?
I'll go get the master key.
I'll go with you!
Kaitou!
B-Blood!
Wh-What's that?
That's all it takes for her to get into a movie?
Damn, who would do this?!
No way...
Is that it?
It can't be over...
That's the end of the footage.
What do you mean?
Who do you think the culprit is?
Geshi
When the sun's heat fades
and first gives way to the cool air.
Hyouka
I'll explain everything to you in a minute.
But first, let me ask you one question.
From a technical standpoint, what do you think of this video?
To be perfectly frank, it's crude.
That's what I think, too.
No amount of passion can overcome a lack of technical expertise.
But isn't that fine?
Yes. I also think it's fine.
Producing things solely for self-gratification is not necessarily bad.
Whether it's well-made or not is not particularly important.
Do you notice anything else fatal to this project?
It's not finished yet.
Correct. Thus it cannot even be called self-gratifying.
And as you saw, the location is special, so it can only be filmed during summer vacation.
But it still isn't finished.
Did the filming not go as planned?
No, every deadline was met according to schedule, and the last of the filming was supposed to be next Sunday.
Then what's the problem?
The script.
The class asked Hongou Mayu, who had once written some comics, to write a script for an hour-long film.
That's absurd!
Hongou did everything she could.
But she fell ill after writing up to this part of the script.
I hope you're not asking us to finish it...
No, I won't ask that much.
Going back to my first question, though:
Who do you think the culprit is?
Hongou fell ill just before writing the conclusion to the story.
The viewer should be able to identify the culprit from just these scenes.
But would an amateur scriptwriter put the right clues where they should be?
That shouldn't be a problem.
She has studied mystery quite intensely.
She must have obeyed the Ten Commandments, Chandler's Laws, and the Twenty Rules.
Moses's Ten Commandments?
No, Knox's Ten Commandments.
That, Chandler's Laws, and the Twenty Rules are all rules set for writing detective fiction.
Right.
So the key to the mystery should already be in our hands.
With that in mind, who do you think the culprit is?
So that's what she meant by "good luck".
I can't really say who did it.
A database can't draw any conclusions.
Yeah. I'm not sure, myself.
There were a few things I thought were fishy.
What?
I was just thinking this is your kind of thing, Houtarou.
The role of the detective.
Wow, that face says you're not interested...
I wasn't really paying attention.
How about we watch it again, then?
Can't you just leave me alone?
Who you think is suspicious is good enough.
Just tell me who you think the culprit is.
Really? Then I think it's Yamanishi-senpai.
Why?
Because of his attitude.
Oreki! Use your head!
Why don't you think about it, Irisu-senpai?
I'm not good with mysteries.
Then why didn't you stop them from making a mystery?
I wasn't initially part of the project.
I only just returned from Hokkaido and took responsibility for the project two days ago.
I would have been against it had I been there initially.
Then one more question:
Why did you choose the Classics Club for this?
First, because I had previously met Chitanda.
Second, because I heard about Hyouka.
Did you know about it?
Did Itoigawa-sensei tell her?
When I was first informed of the situation, you were the first to come to mind.
I thought you might be able to play the role of detective for us.
Don't expect too much from us.
You're right.
I understand that you'd have to go out of your way to help.
I apologize.
This ends the screening.
Thank you, and good work.
Wait a moment!
What about the conclusion?
I don't know.
I will do everything I can,
but if we must present it unfinished, then so be it.
That isn't right!
It'd be too sad to leave the movie unfinished like this!
I don't want that!
Irisu obviously doesn't want that either.
Ending it unfinished will leave a bad aftertaste.
Yeah. Especially since everyone worked so hard.
And...
And why did Hongou-san have to stop writing the script,
betraying her classmates' trust and ruining her own health?
I'm curious!
Why don't we help her, Houtarou?
It's not like you have anything better to do.
Let's do it, Oreki-san!
In memory of Hongou-san!
Hongou isn't dead.
Oh, right.
Anyway, Oreki-san!
What do you plan to do if we can't figure out who the culprit is?
Do you plan to just apologize to everyone in 2-F?
I can't accept that much responsibility.
In that case...
What if you were to simply take on the role of observers?
Observers?
You can listen to what our class's amateur detectives have to say and offer your opinions.
How about it?
I guess that's okay.
Really? Thank you.
Irisu-senpai is pretty famous.
See over there?
Her family runs that general hospital there.
So she's the princess of a large hospital?
But that's not all she's famous for.
She has a nickname.
What do you think it is?
No idea.
"The Empress".
Is she a sadist?
That'd be "The Queen".
I salute your dedication to playing the straight man.
What are you doing?
There are her good looks, of course, but apparently she's good at working people hard, too.
I heard that those around her just end up being her pawns.
That's quite something.
Anyhow, since The Empress herself has graced us with her presence,
how about we come up with archetypes for ourselves, too?
Archetypes?
For starters, Mayaka can be Justice.
I kind of wanted to go with Judgement, though.
What are you talking about?
Tarot cards.
What are you, then?
I'd say The Fool.
Actually, maybe The Magician.
I'll let Chitanda-san be The Fool.
I see...
Now that you mention it, I suppose I am The Fool.
Though it might not be a very good thing.
I don't get it...
Me neither.
What about Oreki-san?
He'd be Strength, of course.
Oh, really?
I think The Star would suit him.
No, definitely Strength.
It fits him perfectly.
I'm guessing that's not a compliment.
You could be wrong about that.
What an annoying guy.
Not happening.
Yes?
Good morning!
I came to meet you.
This young lady is unbelievable.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Morning.
Today we're meeting someone who will take us to see the detectives and hear what they have to say.
How did you arrange that?
Online.
There's a chat room for students on the Kamiyama High home page.
Wow, there is?
Can you show me later?
Of course.
Come in.
Is this the Classics Club room?
Yes. Are you from class 2-F?
I'm Eba Kurako.
Pleased to meet you.
As you've already heard from Irisu, I'll be introducing you to the detectives.
If you would follow me.
Are those snacks, Chii-chan?
Yes. Today I brought some chocolates I was given.
I thought we could share them during the discussion.
Sounds good!
It's hard to think on an empty stomach, after all.
I'm looking forward to hearing your line of thought on this, Houtarou.
Well, aren't you guys just having a blast.
Senpai, mind if I ask something?
Go ahead.
Who will we be talking to?
The assistant director, the props master, and the publicity manager.
And what were you in charge of, Eba-san?
I didn't take part in the project.
It didn't interest me.
I like that answer.
Were you close to Hongou-san?
Why do you ask?
I was just curious as to what kind of person wrote that script.
Hongou is...
diligent, careful,
has a strong sense of responsibility,
ridiculously kind, and easily moved.
She's my best friend.
I see.
We're here.
Since production is on hiatus, nobody should interrupt you.
These three are our class's amateur detectives.
konya koi ni kawaru
Tonight’s the night we fall in love
shiawase na yume de aou
Let’s meet in our sweet dreams
kitto ne mitsukete ne
Please come and find me
madoromi no yakusoku
A promise for when we sleep
mebaeteta nukumori atatakakute tomadou
I felt a growing warmth; it felt so nice that I couldn’t think
konna kimochi wo mada anata wa wakaranai no
But these feelings I have, you still don’t know they’re here
sono shisen ni wa imi nante betsu ni nai hazu
I don’t think there’s anything special in how you look at me
datte tomodachi ni shiteru no to onaji
It’s the same way you look at your friends
akegata ni kieteku chiisana negaiboshi
Fading into the dawn, my tiny wishing star
yoru no aida de no mahou
Magic that lasts only the night
konya koi ni kawaru
Tonight’s the night we fall in love
shiawase na yume de aou
Let’s meet in our sweet dreams
kitto ne mitsukete ne
Please come and find me
madoromi no yakusoku
A promise for when we sleep
Next episode: The Furuoka Deserted Village Murder Case.
The Furuoka Deserted Village Murder Case