Akihisa Yoshii was studying.
I must win tomorrow's Summoner
Test Tournament no matter what.
For Himeji's sake, too,
I absolutely cannot lose!
Okay! I'll start with Japanese History,
a subject I'm relatively good at!
You're studying hard... Aki...
Sis...
I made you a late-evening snack.
I wanted to make something
homemade, but I didn't have much time.
So please settle with this instant ramen.
Th-This is...
"Good Luck"
I wrote it with mayo.
I put my heart into it so
that you can study hard.
I-Is that right?
Well, I should accept any challenge.
Thanks for the food!
This bright red soup, reminiscent
of Szechuan-style super-spicy ramen,
looks spicy but it actually isn't.
It's also mysteriously sour
and has a flavor that could be
from either a vegetable or fruit.
The déjà vu taste
produced by those flavors is...
Hey! What's this?
I first wrote it with
ketchup, but it got dissolved.
Instant food is good as-is, so why...
I made some rice balls, too.
Oh, these might taste normal.
Yep! It's wrapped with a piece
of nori that smells of the ocean.
It's strongly flavored with unrefined
salt, which stimulates my appetite.
The rice is cooked
slightly sweet and fluffily soft
and this crunchy texture is...
Sis... this texture is different
from the rice balls I'm used to.
Aki, I know what you're trying to say.
They have a food called "paella" in Spain, right?
That's my favorite food.
To make tasty paella, they cook the
rice al dente, which keeps the rice firm.
I put my heart into cooking
the rice so that you'll enjoy it.
And voilà! Maybe my wish came true.
The rice was cooked al dente!
Rice balls don't have to be al dente!
Before that, just how did you manage
to cook rice like this in a rice cooker?!
The world is still full of mysteries.
Kongaragatta akai ito wa
Isso gouin datte choucho musubi kyu
Mune ni hazumu kimi tono
mirai hodoicha dame! Yakusoku ne
Haato kintore
Rippa ni jouju shite misemasu
LOVE dame na koi no CRY deeta wa mou
TRASH yaku ni tatanai no atarimae
SO kimi no mae ja itsudemo
Hatsukoi reberu dana... Kawaii?
Wakatta you na koto itte wai wai wai
Oshaberi na tomodachi
Dakedo minna shiritaino
wa jibun no koi no hensachi
Arere heikinten ja rongai? Uwate na daarin
Jissai wa tonda kataomoi
Reberu agete ikou High! High! High!
Kongaragatta akai ito wa
Isso gouin datte choucho musubi kyu
Mure renda panikku kimi to kyuu tenkai
Acchi muicha dame! Tsuite kite
Haato kintore
Angai tafu ni kyou mo moumoku
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Day 2"
"Idiots, Fireworks and the Summoner Tournament"
The second day of the Refreshing Festival...
These are the sales from yesterday.
Whoa!
With this much money, we can buy
some incredible equipment, can't we?
But there's one condition we need
to meet to replace the equipment.
We have to win the Summoner Test Tournament.
It's a random tournament
that's fought by two-person teams.
Himeji and Shimada are
forming our main force team.
Akihisa and I will also
participate as a backup team.
We don't have to participate?
I'd like to give you and
Muttsulini separate missions.
Got it. Just leave it to us!
If we try hard and fight well, we
can promote the merit of Class F, too.
We definitely have to win in order also
to prevent Himeji from changing schools.
So, Akihisa, you did study hard, right?
Unless you get good scores in the
replenish test before the tournament,
you can't compete.
Don't worry! I studied with a
particular focus on Japanese History!
I see. Well done, Akihisa.
Hm?
What's this?
Japanese History isn't in the list
of subjects for today's tournament.
Seriously?! No one told me that!
Well then, we're now starting
the Summoner Test Tournament!
"Summoner Test Tournament"
The main event of the Fumizuki
Academy Refreshing Festival
has now started.
What do you think, Ms. Takahashi?
I'd like to see our students try their best.
In the blue corner, from Year 2,
Class F, Yuuji Sakamoto and Akihisa Yoshii!
We'll brace ourselves and fight!
Yeah...
Geez... Don't be so down
just because you miscalculated.
In the red corner...
Look. We're fighting Class E people first.
So long as we stay focused, we can win.
Yeah. We fought them once in an ST War.
...from Year 2, Class B,
Ritsuko Iwashita and Mayumi Kikuiri!
What?! It got changed?!
We're fighting Class B from the start?!
Hey, what's going on?!
I thought our opponent was going to be Class E.
Well, it's out of my control.
What's the matter?!
There seems to be mechanical problems.
There're more battles to
come. Get on it right away!
I guess it can't be helped. Mayumi!
Yeah. Let's do it, Ritsuko!
This is unexpected.
What're we gonna do, Yuuji?
Of course, we have no choice but to fight!
What do you think of this battle, Ms. Takahashi?
Class F vs. Class B may not be much of a fight.
Since this is the first round, there're
probably many un-balanced battles.
The fighting subject is...
Math! Start!
Summon!
Not bad... Just as you'd
expect from Class B. But...!
Summon!
That's amazing, Yuuji!
How come you have such a high score?
I've been continuously studying
to beat Class A this time for sure.
To beat Class A...?
Yuuji, you'd go that far...
Shouko asked me...
Asked you what?
--Yuuji...
--...where I want to have the wedding.
I have to beat Class A...
in order to protect my life!
Yuuji, you'd go that far...
You're in the same boat
as me! Don't act unsightly!
I know. I've studied, too. Summon!
You're hopeless.
What can I do?!
Looks like they're no match for us.
Let's take care of them quickly
and get ready for the next battle.
Ritsuko!
Mayumi!
Here we come!
I see. At least you seem well-coordinated.
For girls pretending to be friends,
you're doing well in your own way.
Well then, we'll show you some real teamwork!
Right, Akihisa.
Yuuji!
I'll leave the rest to you!
What good is leaving it
to each other going to do?!
That's my line, you idiot!
Humph. Looks like our teamwork is about even.
Huh?!
Okay, Akihisa. We'll use that strategy!
Strategy?
Yeah. While Akihisa attracts
one of the enemies' attention,
Yeah...?
you defeat the other enemy.
Both of them are me!
I guess it can't be helped.
We'll fight together.
Err, it can't be helped?
I'll be in charge of attacking.
You'll be the shield.
"Flesh Shield"
I'm the only one who'll get beaten!
It hurts when I get hit, you know!
Now that it's come to this,
no blatant trick is necessary!
Each of us will defeat one!
We'll fight head to head!
"Fight Head to Head"
What about the strategy?
Hiya!
Shoot!
Take this!
My attack isn't hitting him?!
Since Akihisa is a probationary student,
he's used to using his Avatar for chores,
so he's good at making his Avatar move fast.
It's my turn now!
All right! How's Yuuji doing?!
Take this, this, this, this...!
Why?!
Now!
"Video does not depict actual match."
Huh...? Isn't it kinda like... we're bad guys?
This isn't really a pleasant sight, is it?
As an educator, I want the
Sakamoto-Yoshii team to lose at any cost.
What?! That's not nice!
The winner is the
Sakamoto-Yoshii team in the blue corner!
How frustrating!
It's embarrassing to
lose against guys like them!
That's mean! How disgusting! Stupid!
Man, how harsh people are...
We did it...
Thus, battle after battle
was fought in the first round,
and those teams that lost disappeared.
In the blue corner, from Year 2, Class F,
Yuuji Sakamoto and Akihisa Yoshii!
In the red corner, from
Year 2, Class B, Kyouji Nemoto
and Year 2, Class C, Yuuka Koyama!
Class B again, Yuuji.
So those guys, this time...
Yoshii and Sakamoto?!
Y-You're our opponent?
What's the matter, Kyouji?
It's the idiot duo from Class F.
This fight is practically in the bag, right?
Y-Yeah...
The fighting subject is...
English! Start!
Summon!
Yuuji...
What is it, Akihisa?
I thought you said you'd been
studying in order to beat Class A!
It's impossible to cover
all the subjects all at once!
We both have this kind of
score! What're we gonna do?!
Don't worry. Since our opponent
is them, there's something we can do.
Muttsulini, give me that thing.
Th-That's...
Kyouji Nemoto's Personal Photo Collection.
"Please take a look at the new me!"
Kouta Tsuchiya took and
compiled the photos of Kyouji Nemoto
who had to dress as a woman
because he lost in a Summoner Test War.
This is a work that was never to be made public.
We'll use this as a negotiation material.
I see. He did a terrible thing to
Himeji then. We won't hesitate to use it.
Nemoto! If you don't want us
to pass out this photo collection...
Wait, Akihisa.
What? Why? Don't tell me you'll forgive him!
You're too soft.
Nemoto! Look at this!
Th-That's...!
O-Okay, Sakamoto! We'll surrender!
You're the winner of this battle,
so don't show those photos!
Class C rep! Do you want this?!
Okay, we lose.
The winner is the
Sakamoto-Yoshii team in the blue corner!
Please, Yuuka! Let me explain!
Kyouji...
Let's break up.
Yuuka!
--Bummed...
Thus, one battle after
another has completed smoothly.
Good job, Aki!
I'm happy for you, Akihisa.
That's amazing, Big Brother!
Thanks, Haduki. How did you guys do, Himeji?
We won, too.
Piece of cake!
Good! I hope both our teams
can advance to the final like this.
This is strange.
What's the matter, Sakamoto?
Our opponents were a little...
Didn't we just have bad luck
since it's decided randomly?
Even so, it's baffling.
Hideyoshi, Muttsulini, prepare for the strategy.
Roger.
Got it.
Strategy?
If I'm right, we can't defeat our
next opponent if we fight head to head.
Huh?
In the red corner, from Year 2, Class A,
Shouko Kirishima and Yuuko Kinoshita!
I knew it. So they're putting these
two from Class A up against us, huh?
Just as we expected.
I'm counting on you, Hideyoshi.
Way to go! Hideyoshi
trading places with Kinoshita...
That's a strategy that works only for twins!
Did you really think it would be that easy?
What? Hideyoshi...?
Hideyoshi? You mean that idiot?
Sorry, I made a blunder.
What?!
I know how you think, Yuuji.
Now that it's come to this, I have
no choice but to use our trump card.
Trump card? You have a plan?!
Sure. Yuuji, say exactly what I tell you to.
Okay. I'll leave things to you this time.
Shouko, listen to me.
Shouko, listen to me!
I want to win the tournament no matter what.
I want to win the tournament no matter what!
--If I win the tournament...
--I'll propose to you!
--I'll propose...
--I love you, Shouko.
--I'll propose--
Wait! Hey! Why would I say that, you idiot?!
Rah!
If I win the tournament, I'll propose to you!
I love you, Shouko!
I lose.
Rep!
Even if I'm fighting by myself, I won't lose!
The fighting subject is...
Health and Physical Education! Start!
Summon!
I've got another plan! Here I come!
I'll show my strongest summon!
Summon!
See that?! Killer technique!
Summoning a substitute!
Go ahead and beat that if you can!
Teacher, that's a foul play.
Oh shoot!
I love you... Shouko!
We'll withdraw.
Rep?!
Since the team in the red corner withdrew,
the winner is the
Sakamoto-Yoshii team in the blue corner!
"Chinese-style café: European"
You son of a bitch!
What the hell kind of stunt was that?!
It was your fault that she saw
through your strategy, wasn't it?!
Give me a break! To think
that you put my life in danger...!
I'm surprised that you guys won like that.
That's okay. We all advanced
to the semi finals, so...
Yeah. Both teams came
this far. Winning the tournament
is no longer a dream, is it?
This is amazing!
I'll try hard to give you my
support so that you'll win, Big Brother!
Thanks, Haduki. I'll do my best!
We're now starting the semi finals.
In the red corner, from Year 2, Class F,
Mizuki Himeji and Minami Shimada!
Oh no...
Well, that's fine. Our goal is to
produce a champion from Class F.
We don't have to push too hard to win here.
Yeah. We'll lose quickly so that Himeji
and Minami can conserve their power.
Stupid Big Brother! Go for it!
Haduki...
I'm cheering for you! So please don't lose!
Sorry, Haduki. Grown-ups have to
deal with things kids don't understand...
If you win, I'll give you a
grown-ups' kiss as a reward!
What?!
Huh?
Not just a kiss, but I'll take a bath with you!
What?!
Take a bath together...!
You'll be tired, so I'll wash off your back!
Grrrr...
After all, we should fight seriously, right?
W-Wait! Our goal is...
--Drop dead!
It's rude if you go easy on us purposely, right?
Oh no... If we fight seriously,
I'll be in pain from the feedback!
--Kill him!
What is this...?
We're all from Class F and yet,
why do I really feel like
I'm playing an away game?
Give it up, Akihisa.
We'll quickly lose and leave.
I won't forgive you if you lose on purpose.
Shouko?!
You said that you'd propose
to me if you win the tournament.
If you lose on purpose,
we'll get married immediately.
Same difference!
Wh-What're we gonna do?
Now that it's come to this, we'll
win and won't let them complain!
But how can we defeat Himeji and Minami?
The fighting subject is...
Classic Japanese! Start!
"Video does not depict actual match."
Summon!
An Avatar with only
6 points is virtually non-existent.
Of course! Let's go, Akihisa!
Okay!
Summon!
Akihisa...!
I'm honestly feeling bad.
You don't give up, do you?!
Stop fighting and get beaten!
We'll send you to the
afterlife with a single blow.
Eek! If I'm beaten with that
score, I'll really die from the pain!
Akihisa! Block Himeji's weapon!
I'll do something about her!
Okay! I'll try!
Ahh!
Eek! What're you doing?!
Let go!
Yuuji! Now! Be careful to avoid me!
Take this!
Huh?
The winner is the Sakamoto-Yoshii
team in the blue corner!
It didn't make any difference
who I got beaten by, did it?
Huh?
--Bring death to the traitor!
--H-Hey! Wait!
Why am I the only one...
Don't worry. I won't let
your useless death go in vain.
How is a useless death not in vain?!
Huh?
I obtained some information.
Information?
It was as you thought, Yuuji.
I see... I knew it.
Akihisa, we'll fight seriously in the final.
Yep.
"Final"
The final battle will finally be held
as all the academy students watch.
Believe it or not, those
who advanced to the final
are the duo from Class F,
the lowest marked class.
We may now have to
revise our perception of Class F.
Their opponent is the duo from Year 3, Class A.
Year 3, Class A?!
In the red corner, from Year 3, Class A,
Shunpei Natsukawa and Yuusaku Tsunemura!
The Toko-Natsu Duo?!
Akihisa!
Aki!
I'm surprised to see
you've advanced to the final.
But this is it for you.
We'll crush you to our heart's content!
You still have that stuff on your head?!
I can't get it off!
You're a perv!
You're the one who stuck it on!
Upperclassmen, are you
done with your cheap tricks?
What? Cheap tricks?
You guys are the ones who played
with our opponent selections, aren't you?
Tsk. We went the trouble to
make it so that you'd lose quickly
so that we could save you the
embarrassment of losing to us.
Seriously, to see you toughed it out this far...
We'll settle yesterday's
incident right here, right now!
That's fine! We'll take you on!
Just wait and see. I'll crush you
with English, my favorite subject!
"Fighting Subject"
"English"
Both teams, prepare for battle!
"Fighting Subject"
"Japanese History"
What?!
It's not English?!
"Yuuji"
Good job, Muttsulini!
That was a piece of cake.
Yuuji...
You played all sorts of cheap tricks.
This level of handicap
shouldn't be a problem.
Dammit!
Summon!
What?!
We're standing even?!
Aki normally has about 60 points!
That's amazing, Akihisa!
We're not gonna hold back!
Shut up!
I'll take you on!
What?!
How dare you! You're only a Class F student!
Now!
I'll show you... the difference in
our experiences! Thank me for it!
Take this!
I heard that you're a probationary student.
That must really hurt.
Akihisa! You son of a bitch! Show some guts!
You can still fight, can't you, partner?
Of course!
He's struggling fruitlessly.
I'll finish him off!
Go!
To think you threw your weapon...! Fine!
Got you!
What?!
Akihisa!
The winner is the team in the blue corner!
Say...
...what?!
The champions of the Summoner
Test Tournament have been decided!
The Yuuji Sakamoto-Akihisa
Yoshii team from Year 2, Class F!
We did it, Akihisa.
Yep.
Dammit! We can't accept this!
What? Do you still have complaints?
Of course we do!
You constantly cheated in your battles!
Call them battles of wits.
You guys cheated, too!
Okay, then! We'll expose everything!
This tournament is void!
What?!
They're gonna expose our
cheatings over the school PA system!
Oh no! If our victory becomes void...
Akihisa!
That's it!
Let me borrow this a bit.
Wh-What're you gonna...
I'm not gonna let them
get in the way of our victory!
We have to win the championship
and purchase new equipment!
We're not gonna let Himeji change schools!
All right!
Good job, Akihisa!
Ah...
Shoot...
You brats...!
Not there!
Are you okay, stupid Big Brother?
Seriously, there's such a
thing as going too far, you know?
But those guys were...
By paying for the repair of
the damaged school buildings,
most of the funds for replacing
the equipment disappeared.
What...?!
We have just enough to buy low tables at best.
We put the cart before the horse.
Then... what happens to
Himeji's changing schools?
Akihisa!
Himeji...
Where have you been, Mizuki?
I was with my father for a bit.
What?
So he came to see the tournament...
This is hopeless...
My father said that...
if I am to continue attending this
school, not only should I study hard,
but I should also build physical strength.
Then...!
He also said that...
...I have good friends.
Yep! He's right!
Yasumi no yokujitsu wa yasumi ni surubeki da
Yasumi no zenjitsu mo yasumi ni surubeki da
Owaritakunai! Tsuzuite hoshii!
Heya kara wa detakunai!
Shinjitakunai! Shinjirarenai!
Getsuyou wa kirai
Okinakya owaru
Sakaraenai suima ni
Ato chotto dake nebareru
Yume no naka wa shiawase!
Okitara iitomo owatta "dame kamo..."
Yume no tsuzuki wa horaa na genjitsu
Imasara jitabata shitemo jikan wa modorya shinai
Futatabi yume no sekai e daibu
We're now starting the closing party.
To students, please
gather in the school building.
There were many misunderstandings,
but they were all due to bad luck.
So let's start ov--
"Kyouji Nemoto's Photo Collection"
Please wait! Yuuka!
Yuuji, your promise... Propose...
Dammit!
The testimony gained by torture
won't work as evidence in a trial!
Uhm... Akihisa...
I-If you like... shall we...
Let's dance a folk dance!
Okay! Let's dance, Haduki!
Oh no...
Akihisa...
What complicated guys they are...
Yep.
Thus, the Refreshing Festival has ended.
Their cheeks blushing from the burning flames,
the students held their feelings in their hearts
as the night of the festival wore on.
"The end"