I can't stop myself...
from loving...
Ryuji...
I want things to work with
Minorin, but it still hurts...
It hurts...
More than anything...
I can't take it.
Taiga!
- U-Um...
- S-Sorry about that!
Career Planning
I-I was half asleep...
Th-That's okay!
Yep, it's only natural.
It must've been quite traumatic to have
your buddy Aisaka-san get lost.
Uh-huh.
But now that you've awakened
from your nightmare,
don't forget to turn that in tomorrow.
And I'll repeat this for everyone else, too.
Don't forget to bring them.
Is that clear?
Yes, ma'am!
Okay, that's all for today.
(My Silky Love)
Every time I think of you
MY SILKY LOVE nijuu yojikan zutto
(My Silky Love)
for 24 hours straight,
MY SILKY LOVE kimino koto omoutabi
(My Silky Love)
It only makes me feel
MY SILKY LOVE modokashii kono kimochi
(My Silky Love)
that much more impatient.
MY SILKY LOVE tada afure kaetteku
It's so simple just to say I love you.
But when you come close to me,
sukito ieba kantan nanoni
kimiga maeni kichauto
my own emotions go awry
and get in my way.
kyaraga sobie watashino
koto wo jamashiteru
I can bring myself to do anything.
That's who I'm supposed to be.
itsumonaraba tsuyoki de ikeru
sonna seikakunanoni
But I just can't break this
wall down no matter what.
donna ganbatte mitemo kabewa kuzusenai
Please understand these feelings for you.
sasshite hoshii kono kimoch iwo
That's why these gazes of mine,
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimini
they tell my love for you.
daisuki dayoto okuru shisen
Now gather up my courage!
saidaino yuukide
A fragile heart made of silk,
yabure souna shirukuno haato
I realized that by meeting you,
kimini atte kizuita yatto
I was so clumsy when it comes to love.
ainiwa bukiyou dattan datte
A forgotten scar left in my heart,
wasure kaketa koino kizuato
and I suddenly felt it sting deep inside.
kyuuni uzuki dashitano kyunto
I have to say that I love you someday...
itsukawa watashi rashiku sukito iwanakya
Or it'll keep making me weaker.
imayori yowaku nacchauyo
When You're Around
In the end, we suffered only minor injuries
when the search team rescued us,
and Taiga's mom came to the
lodge to pick her up after that.
Have you been in touch with her?
Kitamura...
Teach said that Aisaka isn't doing well.
She's apparently staying with
her parents to recuperate.
You hear anything about this?
No...
I can't reach her cell...
Oh.
Kitamura.
I have a favor to ask.
What's up?
I want you to act like you were the one...
...who saved Taiga that day.
If Taiga asks, say it was you.
Say she was unconscious the whole
time and never said a word.
Please.
Is this related to the wish Aisaka
asked me to grant on New Year's?
Am I right?
Gotcha.
Taka-chan!
Wanna go somewhere fun?
Somewhere fun?
Yep, yep.
Let's enjoy ourselves!
Stop dwelling on Tiger—
Never mind him!
Six Realms of Desire
Ramen
It's freaking freezing! The group
ahead of us is taking forever!
Takasu, do you still need to make dinner?
Sorry to drag you out here.
It's okay, I'm already here. I can't
leave before trying the food.
I don't wanna go home
even when we're done.
Just the thought of talking about
career plans with my parents...
Don't freak out about it yet.
This round is only for dividing
up next year's classes.
Noto-chi, you'll be in liberal arts, right?
Yep.
My plan's to major in literature somewhere,
become editor of a music magazine,
and eventually go freelance.
Huh...
At this point, I just wanna graduate.
But I'll probably end up
working for my dad...
Wow. Guess I shouldn't be surprised that
you're all thinking about your futures.
Come on...
Something wrong with that?
Must be nice to be a genius
without a care in the world.
You're going into the sciences, right?
You and Professor Kitamura will have
no trouble on the national tests.
Uh, well...
I don't know if I'm going to college...
Okay! Next person in line please!
Nice! We're finally up!
Okay! Find a place to squeeze
yourself in nice and tight!
So, what about the girls?
You keeping tabs on anyone?
Like who?
Kushieda, obviously.
- She's probably—
- Liberal arts!
Ku-Kushieda!?
Why are you here?
Because I work here.
Wh-What about practice?
Days are shorter in the winter,
so we get out early.
Now give me your orders.
I should mention that I'll poke your eyes
out if you ask for a long noodle.
Long noodle.
Sorry.
Three orders of regular ramen.
Oh, excellent choice!
- Three orders of ramen!
- You got it!
You started another new job?
Uh-huh.
The pay's good, so I'm trying
it out for a couple hours.
Why are you always working?
Hold it.
He's about to open his eyes.
Open his eyes?
Huh? What?
Secret Art of Endless Transmigration!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Six Realms of Desire
Thanks so much!
Come again!
That girl never changes...
Next!
Never would've guessed she just rejected
someone, if you hadn't told us.
Yeah...
Women are impossible to predict.
Speaking of which, did you make up
with Little Miss Maya, Noto-chi?
Nah, she's completely ignoring me.
A girl's feelings, huh...?
Is her health really what's keeping her away?
Or is her mom selfish like her dad,
refusing to let her come back?
Or is it...?
I can't stop myself...
Did she realize I heard what she said...?
...from loving...
Career plan?
Just put, "I'm going to study hard."
Even if I get into a national university
close to home, it'll cost way too much.
It'll be fine.
You don't need to worry about money.
Here you go! Natto bomb!
Whoosh! Sticky!
Don't need to worry?
Come on...
You're smart, unlike me.
I want you to have the best education!
And make the most of your talents!
And live a super happy life!
Haven't you heard the saying?
What is it again?
Polish the crown jewels...and the
crown jewels will shine?
Something like that...
A jewel must be polished
before it can shine?
That's it, yo!
You shine so brightly when you're studying!
Yeah...
If only I had a job, even 50,000 yen a month...
No!
You're not allowed to work!
That's what you say now...
The one time you worked at Inage-san's
place was an exceptional exception.
You know about that?
You won't have time to study
if you're working, right?
And if we have to eat dinner cold, separately,
I'll no longer have a reason to live!
We wouldn't be happy at all!
I'm only saying all this because
you want me to go to college!
It'll be fine!
Everything will work out!
She's always been like this...
It'll be okay!
Growing up without a daddy
doesn't mean you'll be less happy than the other kids.
Because I'm a super mommy!
We'll be completely happy, forever and ever.
Completely happy, forever and ever, huh?
Taiga's fine, you know.
Whoa!
I heard she and her mom get along fine.
I bet they're catching up on stuff.
Hope you're right.
Hey, Kushieda.
Oh, and Takasu.
Hey.
Oh, you need our budget?
Sorry!
I'll turn it in later!
Thanks! Please do, new team captain!
See you later!
Ooh, our new president is very busy.
You're the new team captain?
But weren't you already captain?
Uh-huh.
But since Kitamura-kun's so busy
with the student council,
we combined the boys' and girls' ball teams.
And I was appointed captain.
Man, woe am I for becoming
as busy as Kitamura-kun.
Th-Then why did you start a new job?
Won't that make it worse?
No, no.
Don't you know, Takasu-kun?
You're supposed to seek hardships
while you're young.
But you'll end up doing worse at both...
Not true.
I'm working hard to keep
that from happening.
Because...
This is something I can see.
Something you can see?
Oh! Hi, Amin!
Lookin' lovely today!
Er...
What's with the attitude, Kawashima?
Stay away from me.
Stupidity is contagious.
Stupid—
Well, whatever.
I guess when the kid's away, daddy will play.
Wait.
Where are you going, Kawashima!?
Well, Takasu-kun.
I must depart!
Adieu!
But class is about to start!
Oh?
Skipping first period?
Why is it you...?
Forget it.
Hey.
There's something I've been
wanting to tell you.
Really?
Still got something left after
all that screaming?
The crack you're sitting in...
is actually...
home to a ghost!
Whoa!
F-For real!?
That space between the
vending machines...
is where a heartbroken girl choked
on a bottle of soy sauce.
Why didn't you tell me sooner!?
But nothing bad's happened, right?
I believe ghosts have their
own personalities.
They show themselves only to the people
who they believe understand them.
I once thought...that I'd found a ghost.
But...
I don't want to get so caught up
in searching for what I can't see,
that I lose sight of what I can.
And that's why...!
God, you're annoying.
Don't care enough to hear you finish.
But if you'd just hear me
out, you'd understand!
Really, now?
So if I had just stood by and watched...
If I hadn't brought anything to the surface...
It would've all gone perfectly?
Forget it.
Talking to you makes me
feel like I'm on my period.
My mind is clear now!
I'll keep my head on straight
and focus on what I can see!
Seriously. Zip it.
My mind is clear!
I'm going to choose!
I'll make my own decisions!
I'll settle everything!
Shut up...
So, about your career plan...
Sorry, I didn't finish talking
it over with my mother.
Then you haven't changed your mind
from the beginning of the year?
No, I haven't...
You're an excellent student.
That gives me certain expectations,
which drives me to sound like a nag.
That's what it means to be a teacher.
Please don't waste your time on me.
My family's poor.
So it's because of finances?
If you're willing, there are
scholarships, student loans—
Is it so strange to not
want to go to college?
No.
That isn't the case.
It's just...
That's not what your career plan tells me.
I want to know how you feel—no one else.
How I feel...
Huh? It's pitch dark in here.
Yasuko!
Are you still asleep?
New part-time job! I'll be going straight
to the bar from there.   -Yasuko
What!?
A new job?
So this is what she meant when she
said everything will work out?
But didn't she also say that life has
no meaning if we can't eat together?
You shine so brightly when you're studying!
Uh...
Too late to give this to her now.
What's so embarrassing about a love letter?
Well? Are you weirded out?
Since I don't have the guts to tell her
how I feel, all I can do is fantasize.
Pathetic, sure.
But I don't feel any shame!
That's right...
There's no reason to feel ashamed
about being in love.
But I can't say that when
she's in love with me!
Hell, I couldn't tell her if I wanted to!
She won't answer her phone!
What do I...?
Yasuko?
Hey!
Why are you working a new...?
Ta-Ta-Ta-Ta—
What?
Taiga!
Where've you been!? Who were
you with!? What were you doing!?
That hurt, you idiot!
Pig! Dog! Yaksha lookalike!
Asura face! Skullduggery!
Don't try to run away!
Ouch!
Wh-What was that!?
First you try to strangle me,
now you're giving me funny looks!
Y-You surprised me, showing up like this!
Y-You never called or anything.
I-I was r-really worried...
Oh, the battery's dead.
What the heck!?
Explain yourself!
Did you not come back because you're in—
Wh-What was I about to say?
Look.
I wasn't hurt that bad.
I was lying about not feeling well.
I'm perfectly fine.
I just wanted to skip school.
R-Really?
Perfectly fine?
Then...
H-Huh?
I mean, I hadn't seen Mommy in forever.
We stayed at a hotel together...
Went shopping, ate out, watched movies...
I let her spoil me.
So, anyway.
Let me in.
You said you weren't going
to come over anymore.
I lost my key.
I'm going to enter my room
through your window.
Using the three-second rule.
C-Can you make it through
in three seconds?
Oh, forget it!
Sorry to bother you.
H-Hold on!
I mean, since you're here,
why not stay for dinner?
There's some leftover natto.
I could add green onions
and make an omelet—
No need. I already ate.
O-Oh, yeah! Inko-chan wants to say hello!
She's sound asleep.
No, she's just...
Yeah! Playing dead!
It's a new trick she learned!
Did Fugly put on weight?
Huh? You think?
Sh-She did, huh!?
Probably because you're
not around to stress her—
I mean!
She's gorging herself out of loneliness.
She's still fugly.
Boing, boing. Boing, boing.
Having Taiga next to me just feels...right...
Hey, Ryu—
Why are you crying? That's gross.
I...
I'm not crying!
I was just yawning.
Oh.
It is pretty late.
Bye, Fugly.
Gotta go.
Wh-What is it?
Uh, this is...
I just had some free time,
so I was cleaning up...
Yeah, I'm a klutz.
This whole mess makes that painfully clear.
But...
I'm still trying to do the best I can.
I can't stop thinking about it.
Tell me, were you able to find
out how Minorin really feels?
What is this?
Did you miss your chance to ask her
because of the trouble I caused?
- Why are you worrying about me?
- I'm sorry.
- I mean...
- I won't screw up again.
You're...
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
I'm sure you and Minorin
will work things out.
Taiga...
Hey, Ryuji!
Don't just stand there!
Give me a hand!
Huh?
Oh, sure...
Knew it.
I always forget to lock it.
So much for your apartment's
airtight security.
Hey, be careful.
Oh, yeah. I almost forgot.
Thanks.
You went with Kitamura-kun and
Minorin to look for me, right?
I thought you didn't remember,
since you were unconscious and all.
Uh-huh.
But...
I had a dream.
Kitamura-kun was carrying me on his back,
and I started babbling silly
things in my haze...
But it was just a dream, right?
Yeah...
Silly things, huh?
She wants to pretend it never happened?
Then...
It was just a dream.
However...
Kitamura did carry you
up the cliff on his back.
You didn't say a word, though.
You were unconscious the whole time.
Or so I heard.
Really?
That's a relief.
For a second, I was freaking
out that it actually happened!
Yeah...
Okay!
Good night!
Taiga!?
I-I'm fine...
Good night again...
Taiga...
You're such a...
klutz.
Yeah...
In those sleepless nights,
nemurenai yoruni wa
I lay there sighing all alone.
hitoride tameiki
What about everyone else?
minna wa dounano
It just feels so lonely.
nandaka samishii
A tiny little seed in this huge Earth.
hiroi daichini hitotsubu no tane
Stretch out those roots,
nekko nobashite
and bear a fruit that's still unripe.
mada aoi miwo tsuketa
The fruit that wants to hurry and turn orange.
orenji ironi hayaku naritai kajitsu
Showering in your light
kimino hikari wo abite
only nurtures bigger ideals and dreams.
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
Why won't you notice?
kizuiteyo nee
I ate the orange today but cried
because it was still too sour.
orenji kyoumo tabete mitakedo
mada suppakute naita
It reminded too much of me,
watashi mitaide nokosenai kara
so I finished the whole thing.
zenbu tabeta
I love you. It makes me cry.
sukidayo nakeruyo
I love you. I love you.
sukidayo sukidayo
Path to Take
Rock, Paper, Scissors
for thirtysomethings!
Whee! I win!
Here I go!
C-H-O-C-O-L-A-T-E!
Valentine's Day is so much fun!