“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
A student from Raira Academy got hit by the slasher!
You should throw her body's surroundings into calamity.
Haruna, did you eat your supper?
The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Right. The strongest.
If I wasn't headless, I would have died back then.
All right! I'll kill him! I'll kill him for sure!
I'll kill him in flames!
Shizuo!
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
I'm flying...
I'm flying?
I just wanted to find out more about...
Wise Words from Fools
Ikebukuro...
About the energy source that packs this town of rubbish together.
About the truth of this town where desires swell up every day.
And about the strongest man in this town.
The man I met about half a year ago while I was covering the legend
of Ikebukuro's toughest man in the special issue of Tokyo's catastrophe reporter.
The air...
the very air around the man was different.
That's the only way I can de–
You bastard, making me violent!
Are you God? Are you playing God?
Hey, Shizuo. Let's go.
Okay.
Where are we going next?
To that sexual harassment teacher.
It's amazing.
He brought me, a man who spends his days writing the gossip column for a third-rate magazine,
back to the days of my youth.
Curiosity. Yes, an intense curiosity.
I want to know everything about the strongest man.
However, because of what happened right after that,
I had to postpone the article.
I don't know the details of the incident, but the town suddenly felt a little more like it was crawling with evil spirits.
Something is about to happen in this town.
And there's no mistaking that the strongest man is going to be involved in one way or another.
Starting my investigation for the 'Bukuro special once again,
I decided to collect some information from his nearby surroundings.
Oh, Shizuo.
He my friend. Have some ikra.
I didn't order anything.
Oh. Friend of Shizuo, friend of mine, yes?
Thank you for buying.
Is he speaking Japanese like that on purpose?
Toughest? I don't know what you talking about.
Shizuo a good guy.
So you've never seen him?
Getting into fights, or that sort of thing.
Fighting is no good. Peace is good.
Watching is good. Mirugai is good?
One dish mirugai, over here!
No, wait!
It's no use, sir.
Simon's a pacifist, so don't talk about violence with him.
No, I was just asking who's the toughest in Ikebukuro.
If that's what you want to know,
you should ask a specialist in the field.
If you really  want to know...
The toughest in Ikebukuro, you say?
Yes. I heard that you are well-informed on this topic.
I'm sure you're aware that this is an era where strength is no longer the determining factor in a fight.
What we do involves using the head rather than the body.
That's right, we've gone clean.
Clean, huh?
Of course, you make one mistake and it's over, so if someone picks a fight with us,
we have to thoroughly ensure that they don't pull a blade or a gun on us, even if they're amateurs.
Although,
in reality, it isn't the pros, but the little amateur kids who're making the most noise.
The Dollars, the Kokinzoku and the like. Well, since they don't interfere with our business, we don't bother them either.
Apparently, there've been some urban legends roaming around as well, like the headless rider and the slasher.
Let's see. The toughest guy in this town has to be:
Heiwajima Shizuo.
So it is  him?
I hear he's gotten in some nice fights. Either way, there's this informant who would know more about it than we do.
Really? Please, tell me who he is.
Not that I want this in return, but if he asks about our merchandise...
You understand, right?
So, who told you about me?
W-Well, I have my sources.
Well, whatever.
A Tokyo catastrophe reporter, huh? Exposing weird incidents and gangs.
And the next issue is on Ikebukuro?
If you know that much already, I'll be brief.
I thought about writing an article deciding who the strongest person in Ikebukuro is.
The strongest, huh?
There are plenty of strong people in that town,
but in an unarmed fight it's Simon from the Russian sushi place,
or if anything goes it's Shizu-chan.
Shizu-chan?
Heiwajima Shizuo. I'll bet you've come to hear about him?
Yeah, well, who is this Shizuo?
He's unpleasant.
Just knowing about him is enough for me.
I don't understand him, so I've tried to find out more, but even that is unpleasant.
I'd rather not talk about him.
Could you at least expand on that a little?
By the way, Niekawa-san, how's your daughter?
You must be worried about her, having changed schools after what happened.
The reporter who made contact with Heiwajima Shizuo and went dancing through the air with a street light.
If you keep sniffing around, it's not unlikely that you'll interfere with my job.
What did you...
I think you already know this, but right now some chaotic things are happening there.
Does that involve a conflict between the Dollars and the Kokinzoku?
There's that too, and then there are the slasher incidents which started it all.
The slasher?
There are already plenty of urban legends around which are hard enough to control. Any more and...
That's right. If you want to hear about Heiwajima Shizuo,
I'll tell you about a good friend of his.
Orihara Izaya, the informant, told me about a surprising person.
Oh, and a word of caution before you go.
It's best not to talk about Shizuo's brother in front of him.
I wish he'd told me that half a year ago.
I didn't see the discussion about my daughter coming.
I have a daughter who's about to be a sophomore in high school.
It's been just the two of us since my wife ran off.
I honestly don't think my daughter respects me.
All for her sake, I started writing articles for money.
Hello. I'm Celty the smuggler.
Shizuo is a tolerable person, at least to me.
However, he can be scary if you make him mad.
Actually, I'm trying to find out who the number one fighter is in this town.
The magazine you work for sure likes this kind of stuff, doesn't it?
Motorcycle gang rankings and the like.
That's very kind of you.
Anyway, there are people in town who say that you're the strongest.
It's like she's laughing.
You don't say! Shizuo is much stronger than I am. He's so tough it's awe-inspiring.
How should I say this? He's not a fighter or a martial artist, but more like a werewolf or a demon.
Or an alien? No, that's not it. More like "Little Grey Trauma."
Anyway, no matter how well-trained someone is in martial arts, if they get shot with a pistol, it's over.
That's it. His strength is  like a pistol! That comparison alone doesn't do it justice.
I was moved.
This urban legend was talking so highly about Heiwajima Shizuo's strength, which I had experienced firsthand.
Yes. It was strength from another dimension.
Perhaps he was able to control extreme amounts of energy as a side effect of the adrenaline rushing to his brain.
The power he used in one instant, which was beyond human capacity, was other-worldly.
I understand now.
I'm just curious...
What is it?
If it's all right with you, can I see underneath your helmet?
You don't have to if you–
There's no way...
That's right. Celty must be a simple magician.
After regaining my composure, I continued my investigation.
I heard rumors of the conflict between the Dollars and the Kokinzoku all around me.
I was told that the leader of the Kokinzoku, the Shogun, planned to make a move on the Dollars, who were flatly ignoring them.
What kind of person is he?
We don't know, and I don't think the younger members of the Kokinzoku would know, either.
It's rumored that only the highest-ranking members have seen his face.
The true identity of the Shogun who told his men,
to not get involved with Orihara Izaya...
Could he truly be the strongest man?
Evidently the Kokinzoku think that the frequent slasher incidents are the Dollars' doing.
There's talk that a couple of days ago, some high school girls were attacked in an incident that left only one girl unhurt.
I couldn't help but think of my own daughter in her place.
And of her father protecting his daughter from the slasher with his life.
However, my daughter is now an alien whom I can't understand.
It's no use. Today, I'll face her. My daughter, whom I love.
Did you know?
Today, the phantom killer's victim,
was the guy who's writing the Tokyo Catastrophe Report for the Tokyo Warrior.
You mean the magazine reporter?
What? Is that true?
Come on, have I ever lied to you guys?
Is he all right?
Setton-san, do you know him?
Oh, no...
I'm just a fan of his column.
Maybe I should read one.
Still, this is scary.
I hope the police don't give up.
He's here!
He's cutting!
I've said it before, I'm the one who wants to cut you!
Saika-san, good evening.
It's no use, Setton-san. He won't respond to your posts.
This is just creepy, isn't it?
Saying he just cut someone...
Maybe it's the slasher...
Nice one.
Shizuo.
Heiwajima,
You know Shizuo-san?
Heiwajima, Heiwajima, Heiwajima,
Shizuo, Shizuo, Shizuo, Shizuo, Shizuo,
Love.
Heiwajima, I love Hewajima... cut.
Heiwajima, Shizuo, cut, love, Heiwajima, cut, cut.
Love Shizuo.
Mother's hope, Shizuo.
Mother's hope, Shizuo, Mother's hope, Shizuo, love.
Heiwajima, Mother's hope, cut.
Love, Shizuo,
Cut, I love Heiwajima... cut
I, cut, Heiwajima.
I, love, Mother's hope.
Mother's hope.
Shizuo.
Anri, eat as much as you like.
You'll get fat, Anri.
It's okay. I'll exercise it off.
I was kidding. Eat as much as you want.
We're going to be together from now on, right, Dad? Mom?
The girl had a dream every night. A happy family,
like you'd see in a painting.
However, that was a long-gone illusion.
Her parents had died five years prior, in a terrible incident.
As the one person who survived it, she now has this dream.
That tragic event that took away her parents, the happy family which will never again be within her reach.
That was the first time the slasher appeared.
Anri.
Are you doing all right with the preparations for the sports festival?
Y-Yes.
She thought that she was a crafty person. She could easily see her teacher's ulterior motive,
I was worried.
Why were you with those students who were attacked?
Could it be that they were bullying you again?
but she didn't want to face him; she simply closed her mind and waited for the situation to pass by.
I'm worried about you. I'm truly worried.
The slasher might target you again, so you're not safe alone.
Sexual harassment again?
That's not good, Sensei.
She was aware that she was living as a parasite.
Masaomi!
Sonohara-san!
My, what a timid entrance.
Sorry. Were you waiting?
We waited so long I thought we were gonna turn into fossils.
Three points for the route.
Route? What do you mean, route?
At least say "minus 20 points" so I can understand your comeback!
When I came to, I was laying in a hospital bed.
It's all right. As long as you take it easy, you'll get better in no time.
We'll need you to stay here for about a week, but after that...
I had lost my memories.
No, no! You can't get up yet.
I didn't have time for this.
Hey! Niekawa-san?
Later!
See you tomorrow!
"Keep an eye on her."
That's what the voice inside me said.
Niekawa-san from room five hasn't come back yet.
This is bad. I mean, as long as he doesn't reopen his wounds, he'll be okay, but...
I'll kill him, I'll kill him, I'll kill him...
Shizuo... I appreciate the thought, but you don't have to come with me if you don't want to.
This is my problem. Besides, we don't even know if the slasher will come out tonight.
Yeah, really. I'm not letting that slasher punk get away with this.
Demon sword or not, if it has a blade, it'll break if you bend it.
And if it doesn't, I'll still kill him.
I'll kill him, I'll kill him, I'll kill him...
Calm down, Shizuo! This isn't the time to be dealing with...
Whaddya want, little pillbug?
It's that cockroach friend of yours we want to talk to.
Listen. People die from being stared at.
From curses, or insight... there's a 0.0000000000000000675% chance of it happening.
What? How many, did you say?
Huh? Bartender-san... Bartender? You're not...
Now you can't complain if I clobber you to death, can you!?
Niekawa Haruna... Why did the teacher react the way he did?
Excuse me, Miss!
It's 11 o'clock already. Since you're a student, you should hurry home.
I-I'm sorry. I'll go home now.
Will you be all right? I can take you home, if it's nearby.
We have a Code 110 in East Ikebukuro Central Park. Some youths there are brawling. Proceed there immediately.
Roger that. We're on our way.
Kuzuhara-san, let's go.
Sorry, Miss.
If you wait by the police box, I can still take you home later.
Stop!
Stop thinking it's cooler to say "instant" instead of "moment" every time you get the chance!
You're at that age when people say it like that and get weird looks, aren't you, Yumacchi!
And stop thinking that if you deny something that's common sense to all the adults in the world today,
all the rebellious middle and high school kids will read your crap!
It's shallow when people think criticizing ideologies or society makes them cool, isn't it?
You don't hear Yumasaki actually speaking badly about things every day.
What are you reading?
A novel that Yumacchi used to publish.
Doesn't sound like you did what I told you to do while I was asleep.
Now get back to your investigation.
But unlike Castano, this time it's someone we don't know.
Even if it is a member of the Dollars.
At least be sensitive enough to feel sorry for someone else.
I think it's sad. I just can't express it.
I can't forgive the slasher for what he did. I just can't express it.
Anyway, what did we join the Dollars for? Do you two want to live tranquil lives?
I want to find a cute girl with green hair in a foreign country and make her my daughter,
then come back and live a peaceful life next door to three beautiful sisters. That's the modest life that I want!
"Yotsuba"? "Yotsuba"?
Speaking of which, this is it, right? The place where the slasher appeared.
Yeah. How careless. That's the kind of kid who's been getting targeted.
Yeah. This could get bad.
What's wrong?
The guy we just passed had red eyes.
It's nothing. I just remembered something traumatic.
What am I doing?
Togusa!
Got it!
Hit him.
What is it?
Hey! Where are you going, Celty!?
Is he dead?
Man, you're a terrible person, Kadota-san! Right after I tell you people want to live peaceful lives, you turn around and do this!
There's nothing else we could've done in that situation. Either way, it was a legitimate defense.
Run!
The headless rider, and... Shizuo?
Dotachin, look!
A monster?
So you're Heiwajima Shizuo?
I've been wanting to meet you, Shizuo!
I've been trying to meet you, Shizuo!
Heiwajima Shizuo.
I really, really, really, really love you, Shizuo.
I understand. I'm gonna kill you.
That's right, Heiwajima Shizuo. I have to investigate the strongest person.
If I can write that article, everything will go well.
My wife will come back, and my strained relationship with my daughter will be good again. Just like it used to be.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Mutual Love
Next time on
Durarara
The slasher incidents should have ended with that.
But they didn't.
Instead, the fate of a girl was understood.
It turned out to be a long, long night.
Next time: Mutual Love.