"Review"
Akihisa and the gang found themselves suddenly
participating in an inter-grade courage contest.
Due to the adept strategy
of the Year 3 students,
led by the Toko-Natsu Duo, the gang
found themselves in a bitter struggle.
Spin, spin, spin, spin, wham!
Ahhh, please stop, my lord! Boom!
What're we gonna do Yuuji?
Many of our forces have already
been brought down by Year 3.
Don't worry. We've got a secret weapon.
Se...
...cr...
...et...
...weapon?
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
So...
So... he meant us, huh?
Wh-What? This isn't scary at al--
A-Are you okay, Minami?
I-It's not like that. It's just that I'm
not used to seeing Japanese goblins.
If they were German goblins, then...
Ahhhhhhhh!
I-I can't breathe... M-Minami...
Ahh, I really can't take it anymore.
Let's go back, Aki.
Wh-What is this? She isn't her usual self.
Why is my heart going pitter-patter?
This is quite a physical trick.
I will eliminate the pig
jerk who seduces my honey.
Run, Minami!
What? Ah...
I'm not gonna let you get away, Honey.
I'm going to part you and the
pig jerk no matter what it takes.
Shimizu... Right now, you look
more goblin-like than an actual goblin.
I'm sure they came this way.
I guess we have no choice.
Let's go check someplace else, Shimizu.
Honey...!
Looks like we're safe now.
A-Are you sure they're really gone?
It's about time you get used
to Japanese ghosts and goblins.
Fine. I'll go live in Germany then.
But it'll be lonely.
Not at all. I have friends in Germany, too.
Well, that's not what I meant.
What?
It's us who'll be lonely if you're gone.
Ah... Wh-What? You're just
trying to get on my good side.
It's true. Since we're always together,
I can't imagine us suddenly being separated.
"Always together"?
What's the matter, Minami?
Then... what if I say
I'll always be by your side?
What? Where I sit in the
classroom is drafty so it's always cold.
That's not it! What I wanna ask you is...
What you wanna ask me is...?
I mean... I... I... I... I...!
Whoa!
Minami? What on earth--
Ah...
I'm back.
Welcome back, Akihisa. Where's Minami?
I put her in bed in the nurse's office.
Looked like she tried too hard.
Well done, Akihisa. Our plan was a success.
Huh?
"Checkpoint"
Bring my honey to me.
Ahhhh!
Monster...
Could the "secret weapon" you said be...
You got that right.
Huh? I do understand why
Shimizu is looking for Minami,
but why on earth is Kubo...
Ah! Could it be that Kubo likes Shimizu?!
Akihisa... you're so cruel.
--Huh?
--Kubo is gonna cry.
--What?
--You're too harsh.
Whaaaat?!
You sure did keep us waiting!
We let our guard down this morning,
but we'll now thoroughly show you
the real power of the Year 3 stude--
Excuse me, but did
Yoshii and Shimada come here?
You bastard! Let me finish what I'm saying!
How dare you mock us!
We'll teach you how to behave
towards your upperclassmen!
Summon!
I guess we have no choice... Summon!
What?!
They've got over 400 points?!
I can't believe it!
That's science students for you!
Dammit! Stop running around
so restlessly! Enough already!
You're next.
Take this!
"The Toko-Natsu Duo win"
To think that Kubo lost the battle...
It's about time... for us to go.
That's right. You two haven't gone yet.
It may not be a problem for Shouko,
but my physics score is 150 at most.
It'll be a very tough battle.
If only we had one more pair left...
There is one more pair left...
...right here...
Huh? Me?!
It's true that I'm not
disqualified since I came back,
but Minami is...
Oh, that's right! Akihisa,
we've got one more person...
...someone who's here
and hasn't been disqualified.
One more person?
Uhm...
Are you guys talking about me?
But she has trouble with ghosts
and goblins. We shouldn't push her to...
I'll participate!
What?
Watching Minami,
I thought I should try hard, too.
I'll enter the haunted house with Akihisa!
P-Please walk slowly, okay?
Y-Yeah.
I'm not scared. I'm not scared
at all since I'm with Akihisa.
I'm not scared at all.
Not even a bit! Not a chance!
Well... Himeji...
Y-Yes.
Thanks for participating.
Well, I'm the one who's
always depending on you.
No, not really. I'm even happy
about you depending on me.
You're cute and smart...
On top of that, you're kindhearted.
It's like I'm protecting a princess.
Well, the problem is, the one who's
with you is someone like me who is...
Himeji?
I'm not a princess.
--What?
--I'm clumsy and am a jealous person.
I faint at critical times.
I'm full of shortcomings.
That's not true.
It is true!
You don't realize it at all.
What?
You don't notice my shortcomings...
Isn't it because you
avoid getting close to me?
Avoid getting close to you...
You hold back around me
out of consideration for me.
Your eyes see me,
but do you actually see the real me?
Akihisa, do you...
Himeji...?
Idiot Test!
Himeji!
Hm? I don't remember
a wall being around here.
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
Oh, good.
Are you...
...ugly?
Can it, and let go of my hand.
Huh? Yuuji...!
Hm? Where is Himeji?
Huh?! Hey... where am I?
Himeji has probably joined Shouko by now.
What? Don't tell me...
Yeah, it's the Toko-Natsu Duo's scheme.
Both Shouko and
I don't scream so easily, so...
That's true.
So they turned off the lights
and separated us in the dark,
and switched our partners.
I see.
Well, Shouko and Himeji are
the strongest pair without doubt.
So it works out okay.
So... what're your true feelings?
When I'm in the haunted house
alone with Shouko, for some reason,
the terror I felt when Shouko attacked
me with a spike rod comes flowing back.
Ah... I see Kirishima over that corner.
Akihisa barrier!
Now I know your true feelings really well.
Mizuki, are you okay?
Y-Yes... somehow...
Hm? This voice is...
Hi...
Himeji!
"Himeji...."
I can't hear anything. I can't
hear anyone whispering at all!
--Stop it. It's having the opposite effect!
--Himeji...
If we carelessly approach them and
she screams, they'll be disqualified.
Right. Let's keep a
distance from them for now.
Tiptoe, tiptoe, tiptoe...
Hm?
Mizuki... It's not scary. It's not scary.
I'm gonna curse you!
I-I'm okay. I'm not scared.
I'm not scared!
Mizuki... Good girl. Good girl.
Himeji...
Well, you might be worried, but she's
probably trying her best in her own way.
Her best in her own way?
In order to become our close
friend who can be of help to us.
Yuuji, could what she said earlier...
She often grumbled about
always being helped by everyone.
Himeji...
It's okay. Mizuki, it's not scary.
Y-Yes. I'm not scared.
I'm not scared. I'll do my best.
Hang in there... Hang in there, Himeji!
"Last Checkpoint"
Is this place...
Ack! I thought you would've
gotten disqualified by now.
We've got a couple unexpected
interlopers. And here we thought
we'd get to trash those
scumbags Yoshii and Sakamoto first.
I bet they hightailed it out of here, right?
Well, they are scumbags, after all.
Yuuji and Yoshii aren't scumbags.
Huh?
They're not scumbags.
"They're not scumbags," you say?
They're always causing trouble.
Their grades are bad.
If they aren't scumbags,
what should we call them then?
How about this? Instead of
scumbags, it's now society's trash.
No. That's being really rude to trash.
Seriously, trash should
stay buried in a dumpsite!
That's right. Stupid, trashy,
hopeless scumbags like them should be--
Why do you say such terrible things?!
It's true that Akihisa and
Sakamoto's grades may not be good.
They may have caused much trouble.
But why is that alone a reason
for you to say such terrible things?
You don't know them!
You don't know how kind they are!
Huh? Isn't it really just that you
don't know how stupid they are?
Why is it that you judge
people based only on their grades?!
There are many things that
you can't measure with scores!
Stop shouting! Who cares
about dregs like them?!
They are neither scumbags nor dregs!
Seriously, just shut up!
You're disqualified. Beat it already!
You don't have to tell us. Let's go, Mizuki.
So she said, Yuuji. Apparently we're kind.
That's news to me.
Though I'm not at your level,
I thought I was a fine scumbag.
Me, too. Though I'm not at your level,
I sort of knew that I was hopeless.
Seriously, what a waste for Himeji
and Shouko to get disqualified like that.
All her effort went down the drain.
Yeah. This is just a game.
She didn't have to take it so seriously.
Well then, shall we go, Akihisa?
Yeah, Yuuji.
Now we're gonna get
serious, you damn bastards!
Just how long are they
going to make us wait?
Well, it is true that there's no way they'd
show up if they saw our scores, though.
Hey, upperclassmen!
What took you so long?
Let's get started already! Summon!
Before that, let's decide on the penalty game.
Penalty game?
You guys had better not
be trying to pull something!
Don't be so alarmed. It was you guys
who mentioned the penalty game first.
Humph. What kind of penalty?
How about, the losers will do
whatever the winners tell them to.
Ha! Fine by us.
Let's start already!
Summon!
What kind of scores are those?
They're no match for our scores.
Just keep running your
mouth. Let's go, Akihisa.
Okay, Yuuji.
Dash!
What?! They ran away!
We're gonna go after them, Natsukawa!
Stop!
Where did they go?
Tsunemura! That way!
Dammit! What a hassle!
Don't tell me you're tired already!
The hallway over that way!
Where are they?!
Hello there! I'm here, upperclassmen!
How dare he make a fool of us!
Oh? You guys are slower than I thought.
Hey, that's rude.
I never expected them to be this slow.
There's no way that's all they've
got, is there? Right, upperclassmen?
Yoshii! Sakamoto! Come out!
Why don't you use those proud
brains of yours and find us already?
I'm getting tired of hiding.
You guys still can't find us yet?
We can see right through...
...what you guys are pulling!
They disappeared!
Did we go out of the physics field?!
Sorry, guys.
This is a decoy.
We're the ones seeing through it.
When did they...
Mr. Hasegawa!
Please give us approval to summon!
--What?!
--I approve!
I'm summoning my Avatar! Summon!
We're in the math field now.
You guys can't fight with your
favorite subject, physics, any longer!
What a dirty trick!
There's no rule against
switching the subject at checkpoints.
Or, are you afraid of fighting
with subjects other than
physics, upperclassmen?
You fools! We're good at science and math!
There's no way we'll lose
against you with math, is there?!
Summon!
What?!
That's right!
That glasses guy and the rolled pigtails
bitch hurt our scores this morning!
So you took that into account and...
Dammit!
Stop messing around!
It's too late to struggle.
What?!
Idiots are interesting,
don't you think, upperclassmen?
When they become frantic about something,
they exhibit an incredible
ability to concentrate.
There are those who're called
karate maniacs or judo maniacs, but it's
a compliment that means "people
who focus their attention on something."
How annoying! Shut the hell up!
In other words...
His head...!
it means that this
idiot's switch got turned on.
Why...
...did we...
...lose against these idiots?
We won. You remember
the promise, don't you?
Ha! What're you gonna make us do?
It's obvious.
Himeji...
Yoshii...
Kirishima...
Mizuki is on the rooftop.
What?
Hurry up and go.
Thanks, Kirishima!
That's quite considerate of you.
Not really. I like people who try
hard even if they're scared, that's all.
I really like people like that.
I'm neither scared of anything
nor do I have the will to try hard.
If you say so...
Akihisa...
Everyone's saying we should
go have some crêpes to celebrate.
Just earlier... those upperclassmen
came here and apologized to me.
That's thanks to you, right, Akihisa?
I'm sorry for always causing trouble.
That's not true.
It's true that you're not a princess.
What?
No princess would be strong enough
to make a sharp retort
towards upperclassmen.
Ah... That's... uhm...
Thank you. It made me really happy.
Thanks to you, Yuuji and I were
able to get serious and try hard.
Th-Thank you very much for saying that.
Shall we go now?
I think they're waiting for us.
U-Uhm, there's one thing I want to ask you.
Something you want to ask?
Yes...
Uhm... When will you
start calling me "Mizuki"?
Whaaaat?!
You call Minami by her first name,
but you still haven't called
me by my first name all this time.
W-Well, there's a complicated
reason that's hard to explain!
What's that reason?
Uhm... Well... We went to the
same elementary school, right?
Yes.
So when I tried calling you by your first name,
I said "Mizuki-chan" out of habit,
and that was embarrassing, so...
You're lying!
You've never called me by my first
name since we started high school!
That's...
Uhm, you won't laugh?
I won't laugh!
Never?
Never!
Hmm... To tell you the truth...
Yes?
Well, at home I was...
Uhm... I was practicing
calling you by your first name.
Yes... Huh?
Ahh! Nothing! Nothing!
You didn't hear anything!
Then, I'll tell you a secret.
--Huh?
--To tell you the truth...
...my first love is still going.
Now, let's hurry up and go, Akihisa!
W-Wait, Himeji! Wh-What did you just...
Hey, Aki! Why'd you
disappear without telling me?!
Minami?!
You promised me that you'd
always be by my side, didn't you?!
Whaaaaaaat?!
What does that mean, Akihisa?!
Akihisa, out of my way!
Since we didn't reach the goal
together, we'll get married immediately.
No way!
--Ah! Wait, Yuuji!
--We'll reach the finish line together.
--Hey, wait!
Please explain, Akihisa!
I'm saying, wait!
Seriously, we're always like this, aren't we?
Yep, yep.
Flash! Shine! Light bulb, shiny flash!
I'm not making progress.
Someone's interfering... No, no!
The issue is, I don't have
enough common multiples
Okay, I basically get it.
What is the truth... Baby?
If you see this, draw a
diagram and explain it, Baby!
No word or number can describe you
My heart is being shocked by
the magnetic force between S and N
(S! S! Super! Sticking together,
Number! I say No.1 boy!)
Congratulations! From here on
out you're My, ma-my "treasure"
You're special to me,
no matter what happens
I'll hold you ever so
tight and never let you go
I want to be in love, in a
dream you can forget about limits
It's special, right? After all,
we came to know each other
Forgive me for being like this
Flashed! Shined! Right answer, perfect match!
Don't run in the hallway!
Geez... They really are... idiots.
"Idiots"