Tsukuyomi Juju
Oh, Madam Juju?
What might you be reading?
Postcards from Sasami that were delivered today.
They appear to be photos from a trip.
Wow, looks like fun!
Or... not.
I could say the same.
I-I'm here...
The hotel Sasami is staying at!
Paparin made it!
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Inkjet Paper (Recycled)
I'm hungry.
We were sharing senses, so it felt like I ate,
but it was Tama doing the eating, so I've had nothing.
Bon appetit!
That's right.
Guess I have to bathe on my own, too.
With this, I shall become one with the dragon veins running through this island,
since I've now finished attuning my body to become a divine idol for it.
All I need to resurrect the Nine-Headed Dragon now is the energy...
You take morning baths too, Edogawa?
You've already uncovered my plot, Sasami?
But you're too late.
The ritual has already begun!
Huh? Oh, shut it!
What other reason could there be?
She's my enemy!
By letting her be, you'll only hinder the plan!
Edogawa... it's not out right now, is it?
What difference does it make?!
It's... fine either way.
'Sup.
Lil' Tsurugi has entered the chat room.
Good morning, Tsurugi.
Hey!
What're ya doin' naked?
Don't get into a naughty scene while I'm asleep!
I get 100% completion if you do!
This isn't a game...
So, what's with you?
Where's Tama?
Wait... I know.
Did somebody call me?
tama has entered the chat room.
Nah.
Just checkin'.
Go back to sleep.
Okay.
Call me when breakfast's ready.
tama has exited the chat room.
Um... Edogawa?
Since we've got the chance, can we wash each other's backs?
What?!
some kinda trap
What should I do?
Sasami is Yagami Tama,
so she'll be consumed if I touch her carelessly!
When you touched her yesterday,
nothing happened, right?
You're overthinking it, Madam.
Then, why is she asking me to wash her back?
She must be up to something!
So, who are you guys?
Got your wires crossed?
Introduce yourself.
O-Oh, drat!
We've been posting in the wrong room!
Delete your logs and retreat!
Jou has exited the chat room.
Foxy has exited the chat room.
Babysitter has exited the chat room.
Well that was weird.
I'm goin' back to sleep.
Um...
Not good!
You wished to wash backs, did you?
Very well.
It shall be a one-on-one battle.
I have the ability to consume my enemies.
We're on even footing.
We'll wash backs to determine who's on top and who's on bottom!
Um, I don't think you need to take it so seriously...
Guess that Sasami can make friends on her own now...
Good for her...
What are you all doing so early?
Kagamin has entered the chat room.
Now, I challenge you!
Okay, I'll wash you.
She's taken the initiative!
Edogawa, you're so pretty.
You could pass for an idol.
What does my appearance matter?
What matters is strength.
It's how much power you possess.
Well, I'm not strong.
My hair's frizzy,
my chest isn't big...
Edogawa,
I'm jealous of you.
You're just being modest.
I don't like you.
Even though you threw away the gifts you were given,
you still claim you don't have enough.
I'm not sure I understand, but I guess you're right.
If I can complain, I can try harder.
I'm sure you put in a lot of effort.
I do.
I survived through a blood-stained hell to surpass you.
You're amazing, Edogawa.
I really respect you.
It is rather early for such a racket.
Good morning, Kagami!
Listen, I think I made a friend!
That is good for you.
I've never talked to someone in our class so much!
I'm so happy!
That is good for you.
I feel like my communication skills have gotten better.
Thanks, Kagami!
In other words, she is your first friend.
Of course not. You know you're my first.
I am but a stepping stone,
a practice friend.
But you seem happy, so I shall not rain on your parade.
I shall cease being a third wheel.
Kagami?
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Listen, it's a trivial matter,
but even if you don't believe it, could you act prouder and more positive?
Looking at you irritates me.
You are my nemesis.
I'd prefer it if you didn't look so pitiful.
Thank you.
You're pretty nice, Edogawa.
Wh-What part of that was nice?!
I-I'm the greatest villain of the century!
Um, if you don't mind,
can we exchange phone numbers or something later?
Huh? Why?
We don't have to if you don't want to...
but... am I being annoying?
N-No, not that much.
Thank you, Edogawa.
You see, I really want to get along with you.
These photos look fun.
While I am bestowed with the Supreme God's power,
it will do her good to relish in her youth.
What's this?
Ain't no bikini babes here,
but at least it's not packed like sardines out here.
Nothin' beats some relaxation.
Tsukuyomi shoulda come...
Sasami
So you've come, Sasami.
You aim to do battle while I wear a defenseless bathing suit.
You're a true nemesis.
Battle?
We're playing volleybally!
She's planning to lower my guard and strike while I'm open!
However,
I, Edogawa Jou, shall not fall prey to your trap!
Hey, it's Sis!
I mean, my dear sister!
Hey, can she play too?
Have you lost so much nerve that you must call reinforcements?
As you wish.
I'll simply defeat you all.
Hey Kagami,
wanna play volleyball?
I am content.
I have no desire to intrude.
You're not intruding!
It'll be fun!
I shall refrain.
I would prefer to obsess over the construction of my castle.
Okay.
Maybe later.
Its defenses are still weak.
What kind of trip is this?
I could ask the same.
High
Quality
Hang-Dried
Kelp
Oh Sasami, I missed you so much!
But now that I'm here, everything's fine!
High
Quality
Hang-Dried
Kelp
I'll handle your meals, your baths, and all the other things that nobody else can know about!
Great Tasting
Re     sta    ur     ant
Warm
Women
Sittin' on a lap!
I'm sittin' on Paparin's lap!
Hey, Tama!
It's not "Paparin," it's "Brother."
And I don't act like that when he babies me or hugs me at all!
You're supposed to act like me!
Aww, but you're always like this, Mamarin.
I love you, Bro!
Geez...
Well, you're only a kid.
You're finally up, Tsukuyomi.
We're goin' to the festival, so hurry!
Buy us a lot of octopus balls and cotton candy, okay, Bro?
There's a festival here?
Every year, I hear.
All sorts of gods live in this country.
And what better way to worship one than with food and fun?
So let's grab a bite and see the sights!
You'll be my wallet!
Oh yeah, ask Edogawa if she wants to join us.
What is the meaning of this?
What is she plotting?
Calm down a bit.
Edogawa!
What did you call me for?
I'm already proceeding to the final phase of the ritual.
I see.
You think that if you can throw a wrench into my formula,
you can bring it all down.
All this time you spent not making a move was spent plotting the best moment to bring my plans to ruin!
You are a fearsome nemesis, Tsukuyomi Sasami!
Umm...
I don't really understand,
but are you just having delusions of grandeur?
Delusions?
She says it's embarrassing to have a nemesis after middle school.
She says you'll be on about past lives and superpowers and evil organizations before you know it.
You've discerned the existence of our organization as well?!
There really is one?
How much do you already know?
Anyway, Edogawa,
Wanna go to the festival with us?
Wait. Sir Awashima, you will explain what is happening this instant!
You're being too hasty.
I don't think Sasami bears any ill will.
She's honestly just asking to be closer as friends, Madam.
We're ready to go!
That's it. I see.
So, you wish to be closer to me?
Huh?
Uh, yeah!
I finally understand.
Sorry, but as one who stands above all others, I must be careful.
Sure!
So, Edogawa, let's be fri—
So, you wish to be my servant?
Huuuuuuuh?!
Didn't see that coming!
Um, I...
I was overthinking it, since you are my nemesis.
You only wanted to be my servant to butter me up.
Um, uh...
Everybody is either an enemy or a servant to you, Madam.
Why are you being so reasonable?
Sasami only wants a deeper, friendlier, and more even-handed relationship with you.
I see.
So that's what she's after.
It's all as clear as day.
You first came close to me...
when my body turned into a male's.
In other words,
you fell in love with me.
Huuuuuuuh?!
This just keeps getting better!
Huh? Huh?
I understand it all.
It's a bit annoying,
but being loved by others doesn't feel too bad.
Think clearly, Madam!
You're missing the point even further!
Oh, shut up.
After all, you like me, right?
Y-Yeah!
I like you, Edogawa! So let's be fri—
It's not just "Edogawa!"
If you truly love me, you'll call me something else!
"Queen" or "Master" will suffice.
Huh? Umm...
She says to ask if I can call you Joey.
This is absurd.
Kagami, where are you going?
We're going to the festival together!
If I am with you,
I will simply be a crutch for you.
Huh?
You have finally made a friend by yourself.
So please deepen your bonds on your own as well.
Kagami?
I wish you well,
Sasami.
Kagami?!
Sis!
What are you doing?
Well, my sister...
Sis!
You will explain at once!
Are you not my servant?
I'm really sorry, Edogawa!
But I have to go!
I'll call you later!
Wait!
Stop right there, Sasami!
Fine, do as you wish!
I don't need you!
Tama, hurry!
Found her!
Kagami?
Look away...
please.
Why?
Did something happen,
Kagami?
I am strange.
I know I should be overjoyed,
I know I should be supportive,
but when I see how friendly you are with Edogawa...
I do not understand it myself.
You finally became friends with someone you hold dear...
your wish was finally granted, and you are now free to pursue happiness...
and yet I cannot support you!
It must be a malfunction!
I am but a robot,
and a broken machine has no place with humans!
Kagami...
you're not just a robot.
You don't have to support me.
But...
stay with me.
You're a human.
More human than any girl I know.
So you were hurt.
Because I hurt you.
I'm the one who should apologize.
Don't cry, Kagami.
I'm sorry.
You should worry about Edogawa more than I.
You are an idiot. A fool.
Trust me.
Even if I someday change,
or make new friends,
or even if the world blows up,
I will always love you.
Without you around,
I'd rather die.
Sasami, you made a new friend.
I am inferior to a human in many ways,
and I could not bear that realization.
I wanted to disappear.
I am strange.
I must be malfunctioning.
I'm glad you were strange.
I'm so happy you cared enough for me to hurt you.
You are a terrible person,
you know.
Everyone looks really happy.
It'd be nice if they could all stay that way.
Right, Madam Juju?
Is that...
Tsukuyomi Shrine Activity Log.
Scribe, Mickie.
Today was my birthday.
The head gave me, apparently as a birthday gift, a collar.
I wondered if this sick old man was really thinking he would get me to wear it,
but after looking closely, I saw the head's name engraved in it.
The head was suddenly nude and bowing like a dog,
and an emotion I find difficult to describe rose within me.
I blacked out again, and when I awoke, I found the head...
My sincerest apologies!
Where is that cur?!
She's late!
What is Sasami doing?
She said she'd call later!
You did say you didn't need her.
You really are lonely, Madam.
I—
I'm not lonely one bit!
I'm simply awaiting our duel!
Right, right.
It's so yummy!
What are you doing, Tama?
Are you not supposed to be playing Sasami?
Mamarin's spirit power got low, so she took a nappy.
Sis, buy me that next!
I only treated you so well because I thought of you as Sasami...
Buy it for me!
My dear sister!
I will buy you squat!
Why?
Fireworks...
They're beautiful.
Yeah.
Beautiful.
Brother.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Good night.
Now, it's finally arrived!
A showtime of miracles!
Tonight, we'll have the super idol you all know and love, Sasami, singing here!
Sasami! Sasami! Sasami!
Go ahead and sing and get nekkid!
Mamarin, you can do it!
What's all this about?
Listen, I'm not going to sing!
You cannot have your cake and eat it too.
We will be in trouble if the higher-ups get furious over your reluctance to sing.
You could at least try once.
Okay, I'll do it, but you all sing with me!
I'm stunned when you smile and ask
to walk home together
I can hear your voice
everywhere like a resounding symphony
The light shines the color of love
Let's hold hands forever
I want to feel the osmosis grow
I'm done.
I'm not doin' a damn thing tomorrow.
Hey now, you did a great job!
Next Episode
It's time for Dull Drama.
Dull@Drama
On our last episode,
stuff happened.
Now, what does fate have in store?
We...
did a lot of stuff.
Yeah.
A lot of stuff.
To be continued.
Next time:
More Stuff Happens.
A sudden twist
will change our heroes' fates.
See you next time.
Next time, on the final episode.
Next Time, Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow.
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow