You really are looking a lot better.
Yeah.
The doctor says I'll be able to go home by the end of the month.
To think, I'll soon be able to train alongside you again...
I'm really looking forward to it!
Itsuki, I know training's fun and all, but shouldn't
you unwind with your friends every now and again?
That's right. You're on your summer vacation, after all.
Unwind... with my friends?
Heeeey!
Itsuki!
Hiya, Itsuki!
We've been looking for ya!
What are you guys doing here?!
U-U-Um...
Morning!
Itsuki!
Morning, Tsubomi!
Hey, Itsuki! Come join us at the Fashion Club camp!
Right now?!
Oh, a summer camp sounds lovely to me.
Come with us, please!
Huh? But...
Itsuki, go enjoy yourself, all right?
Okay!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Yaaaaaay! This is gonna be so much fun!
We can all go to the beach together!
There's the festival and fireworks too!
There's almost too much stuff to do!
And our Fashion Club work?
Uh.
Well, that's the most important thing, of course!
Hey, Naminami, you didn't bring your little sister with you today?
She's staying over at her nursery school.
That's a shame.
We brought her favorite plushies along and everything!
Oh! There's the sea!
Let's go to the Beach!
Itsuki's Exciting summer Camp!
The sea's right before our eyes!
It's so pretty...
It really is nice here.
Yeah!
Hey, Mom! This place is amazing!
Just be careful not to get the place dirty, all right?
It was very nice of my friend to lend us this villa, after all.
I know! Jeez...
Don't worry!
We'll keep an eye on her for you.
If you would.
No problem!
That's better.
So the student council president's a
member of the Fashion Club too, huh?
You didn't know, Naminami?
Yeah, I was kinda shocked.
Makes you kinda nervous, huh? Right?
Uh, um...
Yeah...
N-Now look, we're all in the same grade...
so just for today, let's not stand on ceremony, all right?
"Stand on ceremony"?
What's that mean?
Huh?
I've got so many ideas for great designs!
Erika?
What's wrong?
Was it really okay for me to come along?
Huh?
I don't think they'll really be able to enjoy themselves
since I'm here.
Well then, you'd better come with me!
Huh?!
Come on, come on!
Tsubomi, come give me a hand!
Okay.
Really, I'm fine how I am now.
No, you're not!
Everyone, please wait just a little longer, okay?
What are they doing to the student council president?
Hee-ya!
Thanks for waiting!
Come on, Itsuki!
W-Wait...
Stop messing around!
Ta-da!
Itsuki designed this dress herself!
Isn't it cute?!
Yeah!
This is kind of embarrassing...
You look great, really!
It's like you've gone from "the student
council president" to "Itsuki" in my mind...
Itsuki!
Then I'll call you that too, Itsuki!
Hey, that's not fair! I want to as well!
Itsuki!
Sure!
Now our hearts are united as one!
Itsuki! Rumiko! Naminami and Tokko! Tsubomi and Naomi!
And, of course, myself!
All right then! Let's make the most of our first Fashion Club camp!
All right!
A shower of sunlight covers me from head to toe
Here it comes!
All right!
Gotcha!
The warmth it brings me urges me on
The angle I placed my chopsticks and my timing both went...
just as planned.
Will this brand new town and these newfound hopes
I'm gonna get the next one!
Give birth to yet unknown feelings?
I'm not gonna hold back, you know.
You don't know what you're up against!
Among a bed of flowers, I see one that's downcast
There!
Got it!
It reminds me of my insecure self
Now hold it right there!
Aren't you forgetting I'm behind you two in line?
Oh...
Look beyond the leaves
Sorry, Tokko!
I got kinda carried away...
At the buds lying in wait
You both really hate losing, don't you?
Day by day, they grow closer to maturity
Like hearts filled with euphoria
They're going through all that when there's noodles over here too, huh?
The future flowers are starting to bloom
Yeah...
The sea's so vasht...
We get to have our own fairy summer camp here too!
We'll teach you that fairies always have to be vigilant, Potpourri!
Being able to smile always gives me courage
I want to play with Ichuki on the beach!
You can't do that!
And sometimes, even my tears seem like little blessings
It's our duty as fairies to guide the Precure!
You're far too immature to guide Itsuki, Potpourri!
You see, what lets me press on, no matter how worried I am
Got all that? 'Cause today, we're gonna
decide on the designs for our fashion show!
Is knowing that you're all here for me
A fashion show?
It's only once you truly believe in what you're capable of
Yes, we decided we were going to hold a fashion show at the school's fall festival.
That you'll be able to protect those important to you
That's right! So I thought we'd take this time to design the clothes we're going to wear for the fashion show.
I see...
Wait, am I gonna be in this show too?!
You'll look good no matter what you wear, Itsuki!
Everything born into this world
But what will the student council
members think when they see me...
Is guaranteed to bloom
They'll think you look beautiful, obviously!
Let's carry the seeds of hope in our hands
Yep! Erika's right!
Thank you, everyone.
And one day blossom into the grandest of flowers
All right then! Let me announce the theme for our fashion show!
Our theme is...
"A New Me!"
So let's make designs for all those clothes you've always wished you could wear!
Okay!
Let's break free of our shells
And bathe in the sunlight
Our hearts are home
To strength and true kindness
We are the flowers of the future
A new me?
Hmph.
The sea is truly vast...
Hrm?
The redness of the sky... it suits you well.
Listen up! At this training camp, we're going to
undergo special training to defeat the three Precure!
That damn third Precure...
I think she's going to be the biggest thorn in our side.
Hmph!
We three are the Commanders of the Desert Apostles!
If we get serious, defeating those Precure will be child's play!
Here's what you've all been waiting for. It's time to share our scary stories!
All right then, "Itsuki Interview" is now underway!
Hey, hold on! On a midsummer night, we should be sharing scary stories!
We can do that later!
Well then, I'll start.
What do you like to do on your days off?
Hmm... I enjoy my training, and I like reading books too, I guess?
How old were you when you started training?
I started when I was four.
Do you have a crush on anyone?!
Uh... well, there is someone I admire...
Who is it?!
It's your older brother, right?
Yeah...
Oh, lame...
Um, Itsuki...
All right then! Question time is over!
Jeez, Erika, you're always like this.
Forget the questions!
Let's tell scary stories!
I don't want to...
Oh, so you're scared, Tsubomi?!
Hey, guys...
I'd like it if you'd all tell me about yourselves too.
Well then, how about I start?
What would you like to know?
Well, do you have any brothers and sisters?
I have an older brother!
So you're the same as me!
And I have a younger sister!
I'm an only child, so I'm kind of jealous of you three.
My brother's kind of a loser, though.
You cacophonous dolt!
You can't sleep?
No, it's not that. It just seems such a waste.
I've never really spent time with
my friends before, just having fun.
This morning I was shocked, more than anything...
but today's been really fun!
Something as simple as meeting new people has let me find a new side of myself.
I realized that by coming here today.
The third Precure...
Not tonight, I think.
This moonlight is too beautiful to tarnish.
Keep it up, you two!
We might as well have a Precure summer camp while we have the chance!
Tsubomi, you're falling behind!
You're a cruel coach...
Come on, put your back into it, Tsubomi!
By building your stamina, you'll be even stronger as a Precure!
I'll do my best...
You're hard at work this morning, I see!
All three of them are here today?!
What are you creepsh doing here?!
Hmph! Isn't that obvious?
We've come to defeat you!
I hope you had sweet dreams, mademoiselle.
You're... the Desert Apostles?!
Hmph...
Itsuki!
Right!
Let's do it!
Sheeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
If you're foolhardy enough to
charge into our training camp...
then you'll be burned like a moth drawn to a flame!
Marine!
My apologies...
but I'll be showing you no mercy today!
You damn golden Precure!
Now I'll return the favor from the last time we met!
I'll get my revenge for all those times you've dirtied my beautiful face...
It's... showtime!
Blossom!
Take this!
Oh? You've gotten stronger, haven't you?
No more playing around!
Just what I wanted!
I'll show you the Marine Tact's power!
I did it!
The Blessed Perfume of Red Light!
A spray makes my mood speed up!
It looks like I can finally stop holding back!
Blossom Full-Body Punch!
Damn you!
Shtop bullying Sunshine!
Potpourri, don't show yourself like that!
You have to believe in your partner!
Sunshine! You can do it! I'm shure you can!
Thank you, Potpourri...
I'll be all right.
No matter how much you try to get in our way, you
can't stop us turning this world into a barren desert!
You have a most malevolent darkness within you.
And that darkness in your heart...
shall be illuminated by my light!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Stop her!
Sasorina!
This is bad!
You wretched Precure!
We'll have to settle this another time!
Have you all finished drawing?
How about this?
It's not bad, but...
I'm sure you can find a design that can bring out a new side of you.
Somehow, it's kinda ended up looking the same as all my other stuff...
I wonder what kind of dress a new me would want to wear?
You just have to find a design that excites you!
That excites me?
Finished!
Whoa, that's amazing! You did all these?
Because I met you all and had such fun together with you,
just thinking about it fills my head with all these brilliant ideas!
All right then!
We should work hard too, so Itsuki doesn't show us all up!
Right!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Our summer camp isn't over yet!
I sense a girl whose heart is being
torn apart by her subtle emotions!
She wants to become friends
with the girl she admires most...
...but all she can do is sigh wistfully!
Well, she should just say "Hey, be my friend!"
Yeah, she should.
She's suffering because she can't work up the courage!
You can be so dense, Itsuki!
Huh? I can?
HeartCatch Precure:
Be Brave!
Making Friends is Truly Amazing!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!