I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
♪ My love for you ♪
♪ Burns deep inside me ♪
♪ So strong ♪
♪ Embers of times we had ♪
♪ And now, here I stand ♪
♪ Lost in a memory ♪
The elders are making their move.
You're in danger.
Go quickly, but quietly.
♪ I see your face and smile ♪
What a foolish thing this is
that you have done.
A fortuneteller warned us.
On the night of the red moon,
the snake will slither and strike
bearing its venomous fangs.
You look so pitiful,
Vicious, and you are.
We have already informed you
of our final decision.
You cannot succeed us
as a leader of this clan.
The syndicate doesn't need
corpses that can't fight,
who've lost their taste for blood.
Nor does it need callow upstarts.
Your unbridled arrogance
has sealed your fate.
Take him to the chamber.
Kill me. Just do it now.
You cannot choose how
you will die, nor when.
You must learn humility.
When you pride is broken,
then we will send you
to the underworld.
Don't forget...
A serpent's venom poisons
slowly after the bite.
Oh man...
I've never screwed up
that bad before.
What was I thinking?
You and I were doing fine.
Then they come along
and mess up everything.
Seems like every bounty's a problem.
"Pamper me! Baby me!"
Nothing but trouble.
I understand now why you have
this attitude about women and kids.
Definitely too much vermouth.
Who are these guys?
Lin?
I'm Lin's brother.
Shin... That's right,
you were both inside.
Once you cross this line, you can
never go back to the syndicate.
What happened, Shin?
Vicious is gonna be executed.
He tried to pull off the coup,
but it backfired.
They got him in the chamber.
And you're a target now, too.
So's Julia.
Julia?
They're in Tharsis City.
I'll cover your escape.
Please, go now while you can.
- I owe you, Shin.
- Good luck.
I don't know what's going on
with the Red Dragons,
but it's really not your
problem now, right?
Vicious, Julia...
To me, those names sound ominous.
Like a magic spell that
unlocks an old door.
A door that should stay closed.
What are you gonna--
Keep it still, please.
You're not in the
syndicate anymore, Spike.
Yeah, I know.
And you, doctor.
Forget everything you've heard.
In fact, forget we were here.
What are you yowling about?
I'm just feeding stray cats
that wandered into the office.
Pesky cats I can't even get rid of.
When this is over,
I'm leaving the syndicate.
They'll kill you.
You know how they work.
Let them say I'm dead.
I'll be waiting at the graveyard.
By the graves, not in one.
Spike... I can't come with you.
Yes, you can.
We'll leave here.
We'll get out of this.
And go where? Do what?
Live. Be free.
It'll be like watching a dream.
So... you were going to betray me?
Did you really think
you could just leave?
Vicious...
Keep dreaming, Julia.
It's never gonna happen.
Are you gonna kill him?
I won't.
You're going to do it for me.
Either you kill him,
or else both of you die.
Those are your only options.
So there's no place for me after all.
Well, I won't go, and that's that.
And I don't care who
comes here to pick me up.
I don't want to live a life where
I'm always in someone's way.
Mother! I've been looking for you!
Alfredo!
Oh, I told you to wait
at the curry restaurant.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I'm just glad you're here.
Can you really take
care of me now?
It sounds too good to be true!
Yes, Mom. Don't worry,
I'll take care of everything.
Have you found a new job yet?
No, but I will.
What about your co-host,
that blonde girl?
Oh, I think she's marrying her agent.
Something about that guy...
Where are you?
What do you want?
I'm heading out to
the city of Tharsis.
- I want you to meet me there.
- Why should I?
Well, it's hard for Jet to get around
by himself with his leg all shot up.
So quit wasting time and get
your ass back to the ship!
What makes you think
I'm coming back?
You take too much for granted.
I have my own place to go back to!
What an attitude, high and mighty.
Jet is not alone.
He can take care of him.
Ed and Ein are there, too.
- You saved me.
- And you saved me back.
You're a good shot.
It's a plus when you're
chasing bounty heads.
You're a bounty hunter?
Well...
I'm taking a vacation
for personal reasons.
Looks like you're going
through a rough time yourself.
It might be good to work
with another woman.
How about it?
You wanna partner up?
I have... something to care of.
Right.
Too bad.
Do you know places where
bounty hunters hang out?
If you wanna put a bounty
on someone, I can take care of it.
I'm looking for a bounty hunter.
I'll drive you back.
I haven't even asked your name.
Faye.
- Faye?
- Faye Valentine.
It's a very common name.
And how about you?
- Julia.
- Julia?
It's also a very common name.
I'm glad I met you, Faye.
Same here.
Um... have I met you
somewhere before?
If you see Spike again...
Tell him I'll be
waiting for him there.
That's all.
He'll know what it means.
Tell him that I'll keep waiting.
But why?
See you later, Faye Valentine.
Hey, wait a minute!
How do you know I know Spike?
Are you still in pain?
Have you heard this story?
A man injures his leg during a hunt.
He's in the middle of the savanna.
No means to treat the wound.
The leg rots, and death approaches.
Last minute,
he's picked up by an airplane.
He looks down and sees a land
of pure white below him,
glistening in the light.
It's the summit of a
snow-capped mountain.
The mountain is Kilimanjaro.
As he gazes down, he feels
the life flowing out of him,
and he thinks,
"That's where I was headed."
And?
I hate stories like that.
Men only think about the past
right before their death.
As if they were searching frantically
for proof that they were alive.
Turn back.
When you and I first met,
you told me something.
You said that you had died once.
That you had seen death.
Why can't you just let it go?
Forget the past.
There was a woman.
First time I found someone
that was truly alive.
At least, that's what I thought.
She was the part of me I'd lost
somewhere along the way.
The part that was missing.
That I'd been longing for.
- She's back.
- Huh? Who?
This is not a repair shop,
all right, Faye?
Don't just come back here
when you've thrashed your ship.
- Where is he?
- Where's who?
The guy with the fuzzy hair.
Fuzzy hair, huh?
Can't you just say
you're looking for Spike?
Where is he?
Doing something in the workshop.
Wait a minute, Faye,
what are you up to?
You didn't come just to
see Spike, that's for sure.
I was asked to relay a message.
From Julia.
Hold on!
Jet, you there?
What? I don't have
any new information.
We're not really in a position to--
I'm glad you're all right.
I was worried.
It's getting pretty intense, you know.
- The Red Dragons?
- Yeah.
There was a coup
attempt two days ago.
New guard versus old.
The old guard won,
and now they're hunting down anyone
who could be connected to the coup.
They'll annihilate every single
target down to the last man.
- And your partner's on their list.
- Yeah, I know.
But why would they go after a guy
who left the syndicate years ago?
If he was ever part of the group that
staged that coup, they take him out.
- That's how they do it.
- What kinda logic is that?
Just run, Jet.
The police can't stop these guys.
Leave Mars, and do it fast.
It's too late for that, but thanks.
You got something?
You look like you
have some information.
It's gonna cost you.
Well, I don't have any cash.
You picked a bad time
to come back, Faye.
You sure you didn't call them here?
Yeah, right. Or maybe
they followed you here.
Well, it was bound to happen
sooner or later, huh?
Wait!
- Hold on!
- I don't have any money.
She said she'd be waiting there.
She said you'd know what she meant.
Well, I don't. Sorry.
Her name is Julia.
Someone's trying to kill her, Spike.
They're after her.
Hey, Jet, I'm ready to take off.
One who disturbs the
general affairs of our clan
must be executed according
to the general will of our clan.
I'm taking off too!
You can't, one of your
main thrusters is totally shot.
Same difference,
if we go down with the ship!
You may leave final words.
Or you may bequeath your possessions.
Nothing.
And you will shed tears of scarlet.
Spike, can you still fly?
Don't worry about us, just go!
Find what you lost,
and get it back.
Go!
The leadership of the Red Dragons
has now changed hands.
From this time forward,
my power is the only power.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
The past is the past, and the future is the future. A man is a man, and a woman is a woman. The present is the present. I am who I am, and you are who
There have been many things,
but the next episode is the last.
Sure was long.
No use doing this.
So how was it, Jet?
'Cause of you, I ended up...
I ended up raising Ein.
Found out I like dogs after all.
- Hey, Jet...
- I wonder where he went off to?
Come on, you're not
even listening to me.
- Oh... what's that?
- Never mind.
Next episode:
"The Real Folk Blues, Part 2."
- We'll see you again... somewhere.
- Huh? It's over?