I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
Confirmed.
To the new alliance,
and perhaps even friendship.
And to success for both of us.
I had no idea the view from
up here would be so breathtaking.
Makes me sad to leave.
The next time,
you'll have to stay for dinner.
Our chef cooks a Cantonese cuisine
that's just as superb as the scenery.
It's to die for, so to speak.
That's quite an invitation.
I never thought I'd break bread
with a capo from the Red Dragon clan.
Don't worry,
the food won't be poisoned.
No more betrayals.
Thank God, I can finally relax.
Take a little breather.
This won't do you any good.
The times have changed.
The syndicates can't survive
like this any longer.
This endless bloodletting
is tearing us all apart.
If Spike were here...
you would never have done this.
I don't feel up for this.
Huh?
I said I don't feel like doing this.
Then I have no choice.
Hold on a minute, Spike.
Hey, I don't wanna bother you.
Don't get salty, all right?
Just how much do you
know about these boys?
- Enough to get the picture.
- Well, then?
There's a fat bounty,
plenty of info on the guy,
and we have a lead.
So what are you scared of?
Spike, you're avoiding the subject,
and you know it.
What are you trying
to hide from me?
So how'd you mess up
your arm, huh, Jet?
- What does that have to do with it?
- Nothing at all.
So when are you gonna
answer my question?
When you answer mine.
Why is this door so small?
You can hardly get through.
- Uh, what's going on?
- None of your business.
Hey! We're supposed to be
a team here, you know.
Since when? You're just
walking trouble, so stay out of it.
Fine, like I care.
Who's this guy? New hit?
Ask before you look.
It's sitting right there.
Lighten up.
Spike?
Wait a minute, Spike!
- Prepared for takeoff.
- Spike!
- Shit... I'm not gonna back you up!
- Your call.
Dammit. Bullheaded.
Mao Yenrai. A 28 million bounty
for murdering a crime boss.
He's the head of a syndicate, huh?
Whoa! That's who you guys are after?
What, you have a fight?
Can it. You're being obnoxious.
- Really?
- I said can it!
He can do whatever
the hell he wants!
Oh God. Men are such babies.
Are you there, Jet?
I've got something big!
Something big?
Madam, excuse me.
I need to see your ticket
for the concert, please.
Ticket? Oh, I don't have any ticket.
Well, then, I'm afraid
I can't let you in, madam.
All right, but he's going to be
very unhappy with you.
- Huh?
- That's right, him.
Balcony, first box.
You know who.
Mao Yenr--
Can you park my zipcraft?
It's out front. Thanks.
What makes them all think they
can do whatever the hell they like?
There's an encryption on this thing.
You worried? Relax.
You haven't seen the
decryption master at work.
You see?
Now we type in "Mao Yenrai."
So I was right. The bounty's for real,
but there's a whole lot more to it.
Is this Mr. Mao Yenrai's box?
I looked all over for it.
- Actually, I--
- Yes, we've been waiting for you.
We request that you remain
quiet during the performance.
Put them back!
You're not getting away!
Get outta my way!
- Hm?
- Huh?
Hey, give it back,
you dumbass! Gimme!
Really, kids these days...
I'll hand you both
over to the police!
Oh my dear God...
Hey.
Isn't it bad for your health
to drink it all in one gulp, Annie?
What's bad for my health
is seeing you come back to life.
It's a shock to the system.
Hey, thanks a lot
for the warm welcome.
Why welcome the dead?
It's all futile.
But I'm alive.
No, you're not.
You died three years ago.
That's how things work here.
I know why you're here, Spike.
You wouldn't have come unless
you needed some information.
Something important, right?
Well, I'll help if I can,
but don't ask me too much.
- Anastasia...
- No! Don't you call me that!
There are only two people
who can use that name.
So... what do you wanna know?
Mao Yenrai.
What happened to him?
Mao-taijin, what's the reason for this?
No need to speak,
Miss... Valentine.
We've done a very thorough
background check on you.
Rest assured, you'll be held
in a very secure location.
Please, take your seat.
You're trembling.
Who are you? Tell me!
Vicious.
You know...
I don't tell you what to do,
but just don't get tangled up
with Vicious anymore, all right?
Why am I talking to you? It's useless.
Sorry.
You've never listened to
anyone in your whole life.
And on top of that,
you're a stubborn showoff.
You think it'd kill you to listen
to your elders for once?
No, that's too much to ask.
About Mao...
He had a lotta guys
out looking for you.
He was convinced you were
still alive. Said he could feel it.
No one could talk him out of it.
So now, here you are, finally back.
- And Mao is--
- Annie...
I think you've had enough.
Not yet. This one's for Mao.
If it's for Mao,
then I'll drink it myself.
All right, and what are you
planning to do with all the artillery?
Where's the girl?
When she saw the bounty figure,
she had a lapse of sanity.
I'm sure she's out somewhere
screwing up and getting in trouble.
- I see.
- Let me tell you something.
You're not gonna get any
reward money for Mao.
He's already dead. Assassinated.
Internal politics.
Between rival crime syndicates,
you understand? It's a trap!
Yeah, I know.
I know the whole sad story.
And you're still going?
Wait, does this have to do with Mao?
Yeah, I have a debt to pay off.
You wanted to know
what happened to my arm.
This is what I paid.
Yeah, for being too gung-ho
and running ahead of the game.
You get the point?
- I don't want to do this, Jet.
- Then why are you?
Let's just say my past
is catching up to me.
- I kinda got myself caught.
- Wha--
Yeah, they want you to
come and pick me up.
Either you show up at the place
they specify, or my life is over.
- Oh, the arrival time is--
- Who asked you to go off on your own?
Aw, come on, now!
We're comrades, right?
You brought this on yourself,
so deal with it yourself.
- We're busy.
- No! Wait, Jet!
Where are you?
You mean you're really
going to come for me?
Well, it's possible. I've got my reasons,
so don't take it personal.
Spike...
♪ I don't feel a thing,
and I stopped remembering ♪
♪ The days are just like
moments turned to hours ♪
♪ Mother used to say,
if you want you'll find a way ♪
♪ But Mother never danced
through fire showers ♪
♪ Walk in the rain ♪
♪ In the rain, in the rain ♪
♪ I walk in the rain, in the rain ♪
♪ Is it right, or is it wrong ♪
♪ And is it here that I belong ♪
When angels are forced out of heaven,
they become devils.
You agree, don't you, Spike?
I'm just watching a bad dream
I never wake up from.
I'll wake you up right now.
What's your rush, Vicious?
After all, it's been a long time.
Are you pleading for your life?
Hardly. Begging doesn't
work on you, remember?
Even if it's coming from the man who
took you in and made you what you are.
Perhaps, but he was a beast
who lost his fangs.
That's why he had to die, Spike.
And that's why you have to die.
Now, we'd like you
to drop the gun slowly.
What's wrong? If you don't comply...
Be careful!
Oh... I'm butchering it.
Hello?
Oh God! Jet, it's Spike, he--
Tough!
Dammit.
You should see yourself.
You have any idea what you look like
right at this moment, Spike?
- What?
- A ravenous beast.
The same blood runs through both of us.
The blood of a beast who wanders,
hunting for the blood of others.
I've bled all that kind of blood away.
Then why are you still alive?!
Just like that.
Sing for me, please.
You finally up, huh?
You slept too much.
You've been asleep three days.
Yeah, I was starting
to worry about you.
Hey, you should be grateful
to me for staying here.
You sing off-key.
- Ow!
- Huh?
Oh well.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
But you know what? This has
become a world with no integrity.
What are you talking about?
Everyone's putting a lid
on something that smells.
- Yeah?
- And we let it happen.
Could you tell me
what you're talking about?
The world. What's going on in the world.
With all these lids, the world
is gonna be buried in lids.
You lost me, bud.
- They keep us from seeing the truth.
- Truth, huh?
Yeah, it's all those lids.
I'm gonna crush them all away!
Next episode:
"Sympathy for the Devil."
Sounds smelly.