You.
Sir!
Hey!
Fire!
Shit.
What?
Yeah!
Eren!
Franz.
Armin!
Pyxis!
Quiet!
Damn it!
Move it!
Um, okay.
Why? Why?
Eren! No!
Take this!
Ahhhhhhhh!
No. Armin.
Look alive!
Oh god, no!
Eren! Eren!
Look at me.
What the...?
No, I'm not.
Strike here.
You bastard!
Is this real?
Is that true?
Son of a bitch.
How did I miss?
I'm sorry, I...
Lord Wald, Sir.
Excuse me, sir.
this is insane!
Yeah, whatever.
'Course you are!
Soldiers, charge!
Let's get moving.
Let that sink in.
It's been a while.
The Titans are in.
Please be a dream.
Jean! Get ahold...
We have to act now!
Tell me. Seriously.
If they get through,
Armin? What's wrong?
What's one more day?
Is that a challenge?
Prepare to intercept!
Sorry, I... I'm okay.
You gonna be alright?
Right! Give 'em hell!
Why are you shouting?
We're trained for this!
They die and stay dead.
They call it "The Sea!"
He took out the cannons!
One would think so, yes.
Sir. With all due re...!
You're right; I'm sorry.
There's so many of them!
I've gotta take him down!
led by the support squad.
but we're gonna finish it!
Mounted Cannon Squad Four,
Unless we seal the breach,
Preparations must be made!
Ackermann, you're with me.
It's a golden opportunity.
Wait! Stay with the group!
It does sound really neat.
The scent so like flowers.
I... Don't worry, I'm fine.
Have some damn perspective!
Look at it this way, Armin.
Oh my god. Please. Help me.
take out the Colossal Titan!
What kinda question is that?
Damn it! Shut up for second!
I beg your pardon, young man.
One man of action to another.
Better not fudge your scores.
The gate was no accident then.
Come now. Take this seriously.
Pyxis, please! I'm beggin you!
Why'd this have to happen now?
I have to see them. I have to!
All of a sudden, it's raining.
No! Not all of us are suicidal!
You can do this, Jean. Alright?
I hadn't planned on it. Thanks.
That, as you may have surmised,
We've got an Abnormal! Hold up!
The things you told me about...
As the Titan onslaught advanced,
Mankind didn't start this fight,
On your feet, Daz. Stop bawling.
Did he just vanish into thin air?
You understand what we're facing.
I promise we'll get through this.
Where are you going? Pyxis, wait!
Rear guard will go to the elites.
We're all about to be Titan chow.
The mass exodus is falling apart.
The sound is so faint. So gentle.
Time to put your training to work!
the entire city's as good as dead!
I expect you all to man your posts
Your mission is a very simple one:
Who the hell do you think you are?
They're simply in it for the kill.
No head-starts for you this round!
File through as calmly as possible!
Commander Pyxis, sir! I bring news!
I obsequiously accept it as a gift.
Please, no. Please, no. Please, no.
Five years later, in the year 850...
If they start pouring in, that's it!
Seriously, how long? Think about it.
in your approach to the game, Pyxis.
Not everyone can say that, can they?
I want you to come find me, alright?
giant rocks that take days to climb.
Your lordship, if I may speak freely.
Please don't go. Don't do this to me!
Just promise... Promise me one thing.
we'll have a repeat of five years ago.
You're safe as long as I'm beside you.
Why not remain where I can assist you?
That's enough, soldier. Good day, Sir.
The whole area is well-nigh saturated.
Come and find me so I can protect you.
We're on the verge of extinction here.
we do know something of their ecology.
we'll rise up right through the ranks.
Sounds good. I'm with you all the way.
They'll know what it's like firsthand.
I refuse to die like this, understand?
He's gone! Exactly like five years ago.
Consider this the last line of defense!
We're not gonna be the victims anymore!
Very well. Yet another victory is mine.
How can you hope to thwart the Titan...
Cadets will be taking the middle guard,
Right! Those in the vanguard, be ready!
No. I won't allow myself to get killed.
We can bypass rookie status altogether!
What's wrong with me? Why can't I move?
I expect you to take part! Report to HQ!
The Titans get held off here or nowhere!
Reports say the gate has been destroyed!
That's right; the outer gate is history.
Almost everything about them is obscure.
Don't! Please stop! I don't want to die!
He... He planned it. He has intelligence!
Commander, I'll go ready the horses, Sir.
Stuff about the outside world is illegal.
Seriously. You could go to jail for that.
Twenty percent of the human race perished.
What the hell, man? What's wrong with you?
Eren. If things take a turn for the worse,
Titans aren't motivated by hunger as such.
This is the chink in the proverbial armor.
Save some of the glory for the rest of us!
I really hope this is your idea of a joke.
Water that glows like fire; fields of ice;
This is our chance! Don't let it slip away!
Without him, the other Titans have nothing!
Defend the wall 'til the evacuation's done!
What? We're in completely different squads!
As if their size wasn't frightening enough.
There is, in fact, one way to ensure death.
The vanguard's been completely overwhelmed!
merchants would've scooped it out ages ago!
Imagine how huge the outside world must be!
knowing the Advance Team has been wiped out.
I was one day shy of shipping off to the MP!
Hell, some people actually died, but not us!
Whatever happens. Don't get yourself killed.
Thanks to the efforts of the Scout Regiment,
I thought things would be hairy, but this...
All the more reason not to waste this moment!
Pare down! Take only what you need to survive!
Just give me a second for my nerves to settle.
Ah. This vintage is worthy of your good taste.
You expect me to sing you a happy little song?
You're whole life's aspiration is to be eaten!
The MP will still be waiting for you tomorrow.
But that alone proved tragically insufficient.
and the monster is left no time to regenerate.
Operation Colossal Titan Response is in effect.
Damn it all, it's your sworn duty to defend us!
Am I right? We powered through for three years!
But, sir! I'm a cadet! I'll slow everyone down!
Though there is some variability on this score,
Out of the frying pan and into the fire, cadets!
You can't just march off! I command you to stay!
This whole situation just has me out of my head.
Just bear with me; there's a lot more than salt.
Sir! We pray the Advance Team will be victorious!
How long do you think before they take Wall Rose?
Clearly my brain is inferior to yours, Lord Wald.
All squadrons are responsible for supply-running,
You're not getting away! You're not getting away!
Like, salty for real? C'mon, you're making it up.
If it comes to it, lay down your lives! Dismissed!
You're loving this, aren't you, you little psycho?
What do you think the last three years were about?
You're not being asked for a self-evaluation here.
This is bigger than the two of us and you know it!
Squadron 34, move out! The vanguard needs support!
Believe it or not, it's about life on the outside!
our only choice was to withdrawal behind Wall Rose.
The Intercept Squadron will be taking the vanguard.
Sorry. I found a book my grandpa keeps hidden away!
Odd how it can remind you of something so horrible.
If you got close to the damn thing, we need details!
but we couldn't figure out how to hoist it in place.
We also know their body temperatures run quite high.
I mean if we prove our worth as soldiers right here,
I don't believe this. Those guys always talk so big!
Listen to me. You're focused on the past. Look ahead.
Should the commander actually face a Titan in battle,
This means the "Armored Titan" is likely to reappear.
Now, that isn't to suggest we're completely ignorant.
We survived. We stared death in the face and we lived.
a Titan's head usually regenerates within two minutes.
Are you basically saying that the Titans are immortal?
is where the flesh-paring blades you see here come in.
Before long we could even be leading our own regiment.
Now, now boys. You're not the only ones in your class.
Good luck beatin' us to the punch a second time, Eren.
Get back here! You're gonna pay for killing my friend!
Armin, listen. We're still going to the outside world.
He's here one moment and gone the next; just like that.
That huge boulder near the front gate was our best bet,
The Colossal Titan has laid siege to the city of Trost!
you can't reach the bottom! There's a name for it, too!
Don't apologize. Look at us. We were too scared to move.
Yes, well, no help for it, is there? If it's their time.
I want everyone split into four squadrons, as practiced.
You've been given a direct order! Pull it together. Now!
Even with their heads blown to bits, the Titans persist.
My friends are being devoured and all I can do is watch.
That's the thing! The Sea never runs out! It's that big!
If and when he does, the inner gate will also be history.
You've been assigned to the rear guard on special orders.
Eren! Where'd he go? Did he
get away or'd you take him out?
I have faith each of you will
be a credit to your regiment!
An astronomical number of
lives snuffed out in a twinkling.
God, what if the bastards
manage to bust through Wall Rose?
Okay, you've got to promise
on your life not to tell anyone.
In the year 845, two terrifying
new breeds of Titan appeared:
Just one more day and I'd have
been heading for the Interior!
A good, deep strike with one
of these to a Titan's weak spot,
Mankind has long possessed
cannon technology, as you're aware.
Listen up. Whoever kills the
most Titans gets bragging rights.
Some people couldn't take it
and either ran or were thrown out.
In fact, a Titan's driving
principle seems to be this appetite.
We have only to consider events
of the recent past to see this.
As they lack reproductive organs,
it's unclear how they reproduce.
he won't feel compelled to play
down his skill as he does with you.
we surmise that these creatures
do not in fact, consume us to live.
The territory couched within the
circle of Wall Maria was abandoned.
I wish you another opulently
appointed day of sloth and tranquility.
Now. Be aware, all of you, that
desertion is punishable by execution!
If something valuable like salt
was just floating around under water,
We need as many elite soldiers as
possible to get things back on track.
Not until I taste what life is like
outside of these godforsaken walls.
The terrifying vitality of these
creatures is beyond scientific dispute.
Trust me, you'd change your mind if
you knew what was actually out there!
Hey! Wallow on your own time! In case
you hadn't noticed, there's a breach.
Look. This is gonna get ugly and when
it does the plan goes out the window.
Whether Titans possess human-like
intelligence is up for debate, of course.
Assemble your troops and establish a
garrison around my estate this instant!
message relay, and enemy combat under
the command of the Garrision Regiment!
If the back of their neck takes adequate
damage, a Titan will not regenerate.
And to date there've been no reports
of high-level communication between them.
Any time the mood strikes them, they can
wipe out the human race in an afternoon!
When the dust has settled, there may
well be more graves than people to dig them.
We do know that Titan physiology is
fundamentally different than most organic life.
Apart from this, to all appearances, their
physique resembles the average human male.
Such obsequiousness from the single
highest-ranking officer in the southern territory.
Dear oh dear. One would think our monthly
rows would see at least some modest improvement
And, baffling though it is, their appetite
seems geared exclusively towards human beings.
For example, according to this book, most of
the world is covered with salty water so deep
We should do it ourselves one day. We can
have adventures like the guy who wrote this book.
What surviving historical documents we have
access to tell us nothing of the Titans' origin.
But my parents are, uh... Well, they're going
to sneak outside the walls to see for themselves.
Untold numbers of our brave comrades-in-arms are
laying down their lives in defense of Trost as we speak.
Besides, what earthly good can the presence of a man
who persistently loses to me at chess do for them now?
Given that they've subsisted for over a century without
access to their only source of nourishment, however,
the Colossal and the Armored, barreling through the
outer walls as if wholesale destruction was child's play.
This is bad, isn't it? There's a
hole in the wall eight meters wide
and we don't even remotely have
the engineering know-how to plug it.