No matter what I do,
I can't stop...
...loving Ryuuji.
I want him to be with Minorin,
but it's just too painful.
It hurts.
It really hurts.
I can't-
Taiga!
U-Uh...
Sorry.
I-I was half asleep...
It's all right.
Yeah, I guess it can't be helped.
This all must be very traumatic for you, considering you're such good friends with Aisaka-san.
Since you just had a nightmare, Takasu-kun,
let me remind you that the printout is due tomorrow.
I'll repeat it again for everyone.
Please don't forget it.
Understood?
Yes.
Let's stop here for today.
My silky love
nijuuyon jikan zutto
24時間ずっと
Every hour of the day
My silky love
kimi no koto omou tabi
キミのこと想うたび
whenever I think of you
My silky love
modokashii kono kimochi
もどかしいこの気持ち
these impatient feelings
My silky love
tada afurekaetteku
ただ溢れかえってく
simply overflow.
suki to ieba kantan na no ni
スキと言えば簡単なのに
Even though it's easy to say "I love you"
kimi ga mae ni kichau to
キミが前に来ちゃうと
when you stand in front of me
kyara ga sobie watashi no koto wo jamashiteru
個性がそびえ　私のコトを邪魔してる
my personality stands up and gets in my way.
itsumo naraba tsuyoki de ikeru
いつもならば強気でイケる
I can usually pull through with my assertiveness
sonna seikaku na no ni
そんな性格なのに
that's just how I am.
donna ganbatte mite mo kabe wa kuzusenai
どんな頑張ってみても　壁は崩せない
But no matter how hard I try, I can't break the wall that's between us.
sasshite hoshii kono kimochi wo
察して欲しい…　この気持ちを
I want you to realise… my feelings.
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimi ni
だから私は　いつもキミに
So I always send a gaze
daisuki da yo to okuru shisen
大好きだよと送る視線
of "I really love you" your way
saidai no yuuki de
最大の勇気で!
with all of my courage!
yaburesou na shiruku no haato
破れそうなシルクノハート
My flimsy silky heart.
kimi ni atte kizuita yatto
キミに逢って気づいた　やっと
After meeting you, I finally realised
ai ni wa bukiyou dattan datte
愛には不器用だったんだって
that I'm really clumsy when it comes to love.
wasurekaketa koi no kizuato
忘れかけた恋の傷跡
The scars from love that I'd almost forgotten
kyuu ni uzukidashita no kyun to
急に疼きだしたの　キュンと
have started to ache all of a sudden.
itsuka wa watashi rashiku suki to
いつかは私らしくスキと
Someday, like how I normally would...
iwanakya ima yori yowaku nacchau yo
言わなきゃ…今より弱くなっちゃうよ
I must say "I love you", or else I'll become even weaker.
The Scene With You
In the end, we weren't seriously injured, and the rescue team saved us.
Then Taiga's real mother came to pick her up at the resort.
Can you contact her?
Kitamura...
The teacher told me that Aisaka isn't doing so great,
so she's resting at her parents' place...
Did you hear anything about that?
No, I couldn't reach her cell phone.
I see.
Kitamura,
I have a favour to ask of you.
What is it?
Pretend that you're the one who saved Taiga.
If Taiga asks about it,
tell her she was unconscious the whole time and said nothing at all.
Please.
Is this related to the favour Taiga asked me on New Year's?
It is, right?
Yeah.
All right.
Taka-chan!
Want to go out somewhere nice?
Somewhere nice?
Yeah, let's eat some good food!
Don't let Taiga be the only thing on your-
It's nothing!
It's cold!
Aren't the people inside taking a bit too long?
Takasu, I'm not keeping you from cooking dinner, right?
I'm sorry for forcing you to come.
It's okay, I won't go home until I taste the food here.
I don't want to go home either.
My parents will just ask what I'm going to do with my life.
There's no need to be so nervous.
This career assessment is just so they can decide how to split up the classes.
Notocchi, you're going into liberal arts, right?
Yeah, I want to go into liberal arts and become an editor for a music magazine,
then finally become a freeloader.
I'd be happy just to graduate.
Well, I'll have to work for my dad anyway.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry for being surprised, but you guys are actually thinking about your futures...
Geez, what are you talking about?
Taka-chan, you're smart enough that you won't have any problems.
You're going into sciences, right?
It should be easy for you and Master Kitamura to pass the national testing.
Not really, I still haven't decided if I'm going to college-
All right, next!
Oh, we made it!
Come on, find a seat and sit down!
So how's it going?
Have you checked on her yet?
Who?
Kushieda, of course-
Liberal arts!
K-Kushieda, why are you here?
I'm working.
W-What about club activities?
Since daytime is shorter in winter they're already over.
So, give me your orders.
By the way, I'll poke your eyes out if you say coal noodles.
Coal noodles.
I'm sorry, three ramen please.
Okay, good choice!
Three ramen!
Another new job, huh?
Yeah, the hourly wage is pretty nice, so I'll try two hours.
Why do you have so many jo-
Stop.
He's going to open his eyes.
Open his eyes?
What?
Endless Circle of Transmigration!
Thanks, please come again!
She never changes.
Next please!
We would never have guessed that she rejected you if you hadn't told us.
Yeah...
Girls are such unpredictable creatures.
Speaking of which, how are things going with Maya-sama?
She's still ignoring me...
A girl's feelings, huh?
Is she not back because she's really not feeling well,
or is her mother being selfish like her father and not letting her come?
Or...
I can't stop...
...did she realise I heard her say that?
...loving Ryuuji.
Career assessment?
Just put something like "I'll study hard", and you'll be fine.
Even if I make it to a four year college,
how much money do you think it'll cost?
It's all right, don't worry about money.
Here, a fermented soybean bomb!
Don't worry?
You...
You're different from Ya-chan because you're smart.
After receiving a great education,
your great talents will launch!
You'll be able to live a great life!
Look, isn't there a saying?
What was it...?
Um, gold jewel... something polish...
Golden stone... shining or something?
"A jewel won't shine if it isn't polished"?
Yeah, that's it gansu!
Ryuu-chan, it's like you're shining when you study!
If I work and make around fifty thousand a month...
No, no working!
Even if you say that...
Working at Inage-san's is just an exception within an exception.
How do you know about it?
You won't be able to study if you work, right?
Also, we won't be able to have dinner together.
A life like that is pointless!
You won't be happy at all!
But you always tell me to go to college-
It's all right!
There's always a way!
She's always been like that.
It's all right, you're no different from other children, even if you don't have a father.
I'm an super mum!
You'll be perfectly happy forever!
Perfectly happy forever, huh?
Don't worry about Taiga.
Taiga previously said that she's on good terms with her real mum.
I think she's probably happy to be around her.
That'd be great.
Oh, Kushieda.
Oh, you're here too, Takasu.
Don't tell me you're here for the budget estimate.
I'm sorry, I'll turn it in later!
Yeah, I'll be counting on you, new team captain!
See you later.
My, the new student council president sure is busy.
New team captain?
Weren't you already the team captain?
Well, Kitamura's student council is really busy,
so they merged the male and the female softball team,
and I was appointed the new team captain.
I'll probably become as busy as Kitamura-kun, since I'm unlucky.
T-Then, why are you getting another job?
Won't that make you busier?
No, no.
Haven't you heard the saying that young people must endure hardship, Takasu-kun?
Wouldn't that hinder both sides-
Nope.
I'm working hard because I don't want to hinder anyone.
That's because it's something that can be seen.
Something that can be seen?
Oh, it's Amin!
You're beautiful as usual today!
What's with that attitude, Kawashima?
Don't come near me.
Stupidity is contagious, you know.
Isn't it great?
When the child is not here, the father can do anything he wants.
Where are you going, Kawashima?
Later, Takasu-kun! I'm going too!
Hey, class is about to start!
Do you plan to skip first?
Why must it be you?
Never mind.
You know...
I wanted to tell you this a long time ago.
Huh?
What's left to say after all that?
Actually, there's a...
...ghost in that gap!
S-Seriously?!
It appears between those two vending machines.
I heard it was a heartbroken girl who took her-
Why didn't you tell me earlier?!
But nothing has happened so far, right?
Huh?
I think ghosts have their own personality too.
They'll only appear in front of people who they want to see and understand them.
I think I've seen a ghost before, however...
...I don't want to yearn and get caught by something I can't see,
and then lose the things I can see.
That's why-
You talk too much, I don't want to hear the whole thing.
You'll understand after you've heard the whole thing!
Really?
You want to say that if I just watch and don't interfere,
everything will turn out fine, right?
Whatever, talking to you feels like having a period.
I won't hesitate anymore!
I will look forward and try to get what I want!
Oh, shut up already.
I won't hesitate anymore, I swear! I swear!
I definitely won't!
Shut up.
Well, this is about your career assessment.
I'm sorry, I still haven't talked to my family about it.
Then, do you still feel the same as at the beginning of this year?
Probably...
You're an overachieving student, and I expect a lot from you,
which is why I'm concerned about this.
That's how being a teacher is.
Please don't have expectations for me, my family is poor.
So the problem is financial?
If you need it, there are different scholarships and financial aids-
Is it so strange to not go to college?
No, that's not it.
It's just that I couldn't tell with just this career assessment...
Huh?
It's how you feel about it, not how others feel about it.
How I...
Huh? Why is it so dark?
Yasuko!
Still sleeping?
I found a part-time job,
so I'll be going to the
shop after work.
I found a part-time job,
so I'll be going to the
shop after work.
I found a part-time job,
so I'll be going to the
shop after work.
Love, Yasuko.
I found a part-time job,
so I'll be going to the
shop after work.
Love, Yasuko.
I found a part-time job,
so I'll be going to the
shop after work.
Love, Yasuko.
I found a part-time job,
so I'll be going to the
shop after work.
Love, Yasuko.
I found a part-time job,
so I'll be going to the
shop after work.
Love, Yasuko.
Wha-
Job?
So that's what she means by, "There's always a way"?
Didn't she also say it'd be pointless if a mother and son didn't have dinner together?
Ryuu-chan, it's like you're shining when you study!
Uh...
How can I give it to her now?
How is a love letter embarrassing?
Disgusting, right?
Since I don't have the guts to confess to her, I can only imagine like this.
It's horribly miserable, but I don't think it's embarrassing!
That's right, the feeling of liking someone is not embarrassing.
I can't say that to the person who likes me!
I just can't say it even if I want to!
What's more, she's not answering my calls!
What should I-
Yasuko?
Seriously, why are you work-
T-T-T-
What?
Taiga!
Where were you, and who were you with?!
You nearly killed me.
You idiot, pig, dog, yaksha, asura, gorilla!
No running!
W-What were you doing?
You tried to strangle me and looked at me with weird eyes...
I-I was just surprised because you appeared out of nowhere!
You didn't even call me.
I-I was really worried...
Oh, the battery died.
What was that?!
You have to explain everything to me in detail!
Don't tell me you didn't come back because you-
W-Why did I say that?
Look.
The wound isn't that bad.
The thing about me not doing so great was a lie.
I'm fine.
I just wanted to skip school.
I-I see, so you're all right...
Then...
Huh?
I hadn't seen my mum for a long time.
We stayed at a hotel,
and we went shopping, to restaurants, and movies and stuff.
I was just being a child!
So...
Anyway, let me in first.
Didn't you say you weren't going to come over anymore?
I lost my keys.
I'm going to go in through the window from your room.
I'll use the three-second rule.
C-Can you do it within three seconds?
Whatever.
Sorry for intruding.
W-Wait!
Hey, why don't you have dinner here?
There are some fermented beans left, so I'll just add some onions-
It's okay, I already had dinner.
O-Oh yeah, Inko-chan wants to say hi to you!
Isn't he sleeping?
No, this is...
Yeah, it's his new greeting! He learned it recently...
Did that ugly bird get fatter?
Really?
E-Exactly!
It's because you're not here to stress him-
Scratch that!
He's eating too much because he's so lonely.
He's as ugly as ever.
As I thought, being with Taiga is the best.
Hey, Ryuuj-
Huh?
Why are you crying?
How disgusting.
I-I wasn't crying.
I was just yawning.
I see.
It's late, right?
Bye, ugly one.
I'm leaving now.
What's wrong?
No, this is actually...
I was just cleaning out stuff because I had time...
Look, I didn't have time at the end of last year...
I see.
I'm really clumsy, but I finally understood after what happened.
Even if I'm clumsy, I can still be serious.
I can't stop thinking about it...
Hey, did you find out Minorin's true feelings yet?
Why?
Don't tell me you didn't ask her because of the fuss I caused...
Why is she worrying about me?
I promise I won't be clumsy anymore.
Because you...
It's all right, don't worry.
Things will definitely turn out fine between you and Minorin.
Taiga...
Hey, Ryuuji! Don't just stand there, come and help me!
It worked!
I always forget to lock the window.
A highly secured mansion isn't always convenient.
Hey, be careful...
Oh yeah, I nearly forgot.
Thank you.
You, Kitamura-kun, and Minorin went to look for me, right?
You don't remember, do you?
I mean, you were unconscious.
Yeah, but I had a dream.
In my dreams, Kitamura-kun was carrying me on his back,
and I muttered something stupid to him...
It was a dream, right?
Yeah.
Something stupid, huh?
Does she want to pretend she didn't say anything?
If that's the case...
It was a dream.
Kitamura-kun did carry you on his back,
but you didn't say anything because you were unconscious.
That's what I heard, at least.
Really?
Thank God!
For a second, I was worried that it had been real.
Yeah...
All right, later.
Good night...
Taiga?
I'm all right...
Once again, good night...
Taiga, you're really a...
...klutz, aren't you?
nemurenai yoru ni wa
眠れない夜には
On the nights I can’t sleep
hitori de tameiki
ひとりでため息
I sigh alone.
minna wa dou na no
みんなはどうなの？
How is everyone?
nandaka sabishii
なんだか寂しい
I feel a little lonely.
hiroi daichi ni hitotsubu no tane
広い大地に　ひと粒の種
Within the vast world, a single seed
nekko nobashite
根っこのばして
extended its roots
mada aoi mi wo tsuketa
まだ青い　実をつけた
and put out a fruit that was still unripe.
orenji iro ni hayaku
オレンジ色に　早く
The fruit that I wish would turn orange soon
naritai kajitsu
なりたい果実
kimi no hikari wo abite
キミの光を浴びて
is bathed in your light.
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
理想や夢は膨らむばかり
The ideals and dreams just swell-
kizuite yo nee
気づいてよ　ねぇ
Hey, feel it.
orenji kyou mo
オレンジ　今日も
Today, I tried eating an orange
tabete mita kedo
食べてみたけど
mada suppakute naita
まだすっぱくて　 泣いた
but it was so sour I cried.
watashi mitai de nokosenai kara
私みたいで残せないから
I couldn’t leave it behind like I have been
zenbu tabeta
ぜんぶ食べた
so I ate it all.
suki da yo nakeru yo
好きだよ 泣けるよ
I love it… I feel like crying.
suki da yo suki da yo
好きだよ 好きだよ
I love it… I love it.
Next Episode Preview
The Road We Must Advance on
Thirty-year-old rock-paper-scissors: scissors!
Yay, I won!
Here I go!
Chocolate!
Valentine's Day is awesome!