Let's go.
Reginaaaa!
This way!
You shall not escape!
Precures!
Welcome back.
Your safe return is what's most important.
Nice to be back...
We have to find a way to save the princess.
To wake a princess from her slumber,
you need a kiss from a prince, right?
Joe, if you'd please!
Huh?
You mean me?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
It didn't do anything!
I guess it doesn't work the way it does in fairy tales.
How embarrassing!
This is serious!
This isn't your ordinary ice.
Princess Ann may have frozen herself in this to protect herself from harm.
In that case, it won't be easy to get her out.
Then what should we do?
The Selfish will certainly return to snatch her away.
How about we hide her until she awakens?
Huh?
But where?
Sorry, but I'd have to keep it a secret from you.
It'd be safer that way.
Are you coming with?
Great.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Right!
Arriving In The Nick Of Time!
A New Warrior, Cure Ace!
Now then,
the princess is safe for now...
What should I do now?
Regina...
We really made Daddy mad by doing what we did.
And a "sorry" won't cut it with him.
Regina, do you love your dad?
Huh?
Yeah...
Even after what he did to you?
But he's my daddy.
I see.
Well, I love you too.
Back when you saved me,
your kindness shone through to me.
I was so happy!
I could tell how you felt, too.
Thank you for saving Mana.
Makopi!
Thank you, Regina.
I could tell as well.
See?
We all saw how much you loved us!
So I'm sure your dad can understand, too!
So, let's go home!
Huh? What home?
I can't go back to min—
To my house!
So, what I'm asking is...
please let her stay over for a while!
Pretty please!
Pretty please.
Bein' a good samaritan again?
Yeah...
You never quit...
Mana really takes after a certain someone.
You've got that right.
Regina, was it?
Yes.
You look kinda down.
Times like these call for food!
Now, bon appétit!
It's yummy!
I know, right?
Daddy's omelette rice always perks you up!
I say it's got a long way to go!
Oh?
I think it's already better than what you make, Dad.
What?!
Settle down.
We can have Regina be the judge next time!
Huh? Me?
Very well!
Regina won't play favorites for you!
It takes more than marriage to get a compliment from Ayumi!
Don't be so sure!
She got you, Daddy!
It's strange...
Watching them makes me feel warm and fuzzy.
But why...
does my heart hurt in spite of that?
Wow, you're so cute!
Aw, you think so?
Not more than me, though.
I guess...
What's up?
Well...
I was just thinking that I didn't have any memories with Daddy.
You didn't go out much with your dad?
Maybe...
You don't remember?
No.
When I try to remember,
my head just goes all fuzzy.
How weird...
Well, now's your chance to make new ones with him!
Now?
But I made him mad...
We already told you.
He'll understand how much you love him!
Maybe...
Definitely!
Your feelings shone through to us, after all!
I know your dad will understand!
Okay!
Once you're feeling better, I'll go with you!
Huh?
I'll help you tell your dad how you feel!
Sure!
Okay, lights out!
I'll sleep with you!
Just when I thought we were rid of that spoiled brat,
he tells us to go looking for her?
King Selfish is way too selfish!
But this makes it interesting.
How?
The Precures have begun showing friendship to Regina.
So, if she should once again be overcome by evil...
My, that does sound like fun!
That's our king of selfishness!
Good morning!
Morning!
I don't think I've ever been on a picnic before.
Really?
It's been forever for me, too!
Hello, beach!
And the weather's perfect!
Last one on the sand's a rotten egg!
Regina, did you like the picnic?
Yeah, it was super fun!
The sea's kind of calming...
Great!
At times when I'm at a loss and don't know what to do,
I come to the beach.
Huh? You do?
Yeah.
I look at how the sea and sky go on forever, and think about this:
The sea's connected to the sky.
The sky's connected to the infinite universe.
My problems are a tiny speck in comparison,
so I'll just take life one step at a time.
Take life... one step at a time...
Just kidding, but it sounded cool, right?
I don't mind.
You can be cool sometimes, Daddy!
That must be what Mana's mother loved about you.
Hey now....
My heart feels so warm again...
But... it hurts.
Okay, it's set!
Mana!
You all right?
Yeah, thanks.
Guess that comes from being Mana's dad.
I hope I can be that close with my daddy...
Found ya.
Regina, it's time to go home.
King Selfish is waiting for you.
Daddy?
But... I don't want to go home right now.
Shut up and come with us.
Who are you people?
Not someone humans oughta mess with!
Daddy!
Where's Princess Ann?
You expect us to tell people like you?!
Good grief.
It seems we'll need to do this the hard way.
He's all right, he just lost consciousness.
Girls, let's go!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor Selfishes who have lost their love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your hearts race once more!
Let's go.
Mana!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Look out, Mana!
Mana! Girls!
Why... does my chest hurt?
It's just like the pain earlier...
Why?
It is because you know love.
Daddy!
It can't be...
Has King Selfish been resurrected?
No...
That's...
A projection of King Selfish!
Regina!
Give Regina back!
Come back, Regina!
Daddy...
Regina...
Love has budded within your heart.
All because of your acquaintance with those Precures.
That is what pains and torments your heart so.
I have love?
Do away with such foolish emotions and return home.
No.
You said I was no daughter of yours!
I hate you, Daddy!
I apologize...
Huh?
Forgive me.
I need you.
Me?
Yes, my adorable daughter.
My one and only Regina...
Daddy...
But I...
I like Mana and her friends, too!
I don't know what to do!
You poor thing...
Worry not, Regina.
If you have more Egogy,
your pain will vanish, and you shall grow stronger.
Egogy?
Now, accept it.
It is a present from me to you.
It's true...
the pain is vanishing!
But...
I really do love you, Daddy.
But the ones who tore me from him...
are the Precures!
Regina!
I feel like a new woman!
Regina?
I'll erase you.
Whoah!
That is the strength King Selfish bestowed upon her.
Regina... what happened?
I think...
King Selfish infused her with his wicked energy!
All to keep her back in line.
That's evil...
Horrendously so!
And Regina...
loved her dad so much...
I will not...
let King Selfish have his way!
What are you talking about?
Nothing in the world matters besides me and Daddy.
That doesn't include you, so begone!
Regina...
Listen to me!
I don't need you anymore.
But I need you!
Regina...
you're one of my best friends!
Friend?
Indeed.
We are all friends!
Did you forget when Cure Heart saved you?
Back then, even I had thought...
that you truly wanted to be our friend!
You have to find those feelings again!
Regina!
But I know now.
All this mushy friendship garbage...
was part of your plan to hurt me!
No!
That's not it at all!
Too bad!
I'm not falling for that trick twice!
What should... we do?
If we use a Lovely Force Arrow,
it could cleanse the evil in her heart!
Let's try it.
Mana!
I know.
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Cure Heart?
I...
just can't do it!
You fools.
Girls...
are you all right?
Hang in there!
I think it's time to end this.
Farewell Precures, you faux-warriors of love!
Regina...
stop it!
Regina!
Kyupirappa!
Who are you?
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
I am love's trump card, Cure Ace!
Cure Ace?
A new Precure?
To be capable of nullifying Regina's attacks...
She must be powerful!
Please do not be alarmed by such trivialities.
I'm here to help you all reach the next stage as Precures!
Dokidoki Precure:
Taking Love Back!
The Precure's Five Vows!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!