Romero...
If you were born and raised in a different country,
would you...
...have this kind of peaceful face too?
Lizzie, you're still here?
You're heading to Mexico tomorrow, aren't you?
I thought I'd drop by to make sure
you will be a good girl while I'm away.
Who is he?
Don't you think he's quite handsome?
I can't really see the difference in those oriental faces, you see?
All I can say that he's got an easygoing face, I guess.
Do you think he can kill people?
That gotta be a joke.
He doesn't even seem to be able to kill a bug.
Yeah.
I guess that's true.
Good, keep up the pace.
A knife is a weapon and a shield at the same time.
That's why...
In the battle between knifes,
if you can flip your opponent's knife from his hand, the fight is over.
You were...
...holding back?
Why are you grabbing your enemy while they are still holding their knife?
An FBI investigator has been found dead while on duty in Tijuana, Mexico.
Remember all the words you see and hear.
Based on the evidence found on the crime scene, the authorities have started an investigation.
Detective Brice was investigating a terrorist group in South America,
Nothing.
Noche de Sangre, and it's relation to a US Military base.
And it is believed that Noche de Sangre does have involvement in this case.
She's gonna kill again.
How's Zwei's completion?
His techniques are almost perfect.
A good pace.
Ein, come!
Yes.
No one will see it through.
Covered completely by this white and soft skin,
lies a lethal weapon.
Take a stance!
Ein.
You are perfect.
I raised you, I created you.
A perfect material.
I want this perfection to be mine for eternity.
Complete Zwei with your own hands and make him perfect like yourself.
Understood.
This is the last thing to do to make you complete.
Ein.
Prove to me the next step of your perfection.
Yes, Master.
Ein...
You're quite late.
Come!
We need to prepare.
How long are you planning to make me wait?
You do know how important I am for your organization, don't you?
I've been through dangerous situations for a long time to sell you that military weaponry.
Your services has been paid in full, Captain Wallace.
But well, this is all too sudden.
There's nothing else I can do, is there?
I got dragged in a murder case while I'm on vacation.
Such a misfortune.
It seems that victim was an FBI investigator.
Someone you knew?
I have nothing to do with it.
I don't know why, but I'm being suspected.
I see.
If I'm being investigated, it'll be bad for you people too.
Inferno has a responsibility to take care of me.
Well, of course.
Let's just say that you will see the Caribbean's sunrise in a few hours.
That's what I want.
Choose the gun you think would fit you best.
Huh?
More training?
No, tonight...
...is your trial.
Trial?
Follow me.
Weren't we suppose to go to a runway?
What's the meaning of this?
What are you planning?
Mr. McGwire.
He is from the US. Navy, Captain Wallace.
A member of Inferno?
Probably, a large type automatic.
She's the bodyguard.
I'm asking you, what the hell is the meaning of this?
This guy...
You've done more than you can handle.
If you only had followed our agreement, there wouldn't be such an exposure.
But you went as far as selling those guns to terrorists.
And thus, you have been marked by FBI.
The utmost secrecy is Inferno's code of conduct.
You people are trying to...
Scythe.
Captain Wallace.
Inferno has prepared a relief treatment for you.
Please run.
What?
We will give you a ten minute head start.
After that, we will send someone to come after you.
If you can outrun them, it's your victory.
Is that okay?
Perfect.
There is a weapon storage inside that building.
Please choose what you like.
What are you trying to do?
I'm talking about giving you a chance to win your life and freedom with your own hands.
Isn't that fit for a military officer like you?
Is this how you return your favor after all I have done?
Even after all of that you...
Don't you have a limited time you can't waste?
Shit!
The situation is as you have heard.
Zwei, I'm giving you your first assignment.
Kill that man.
Use whatever method you wish.
Show us how you improvise.
Wait, I'm not ready...
Your training is over.
You've done well.
It was excellent.
You can use it all for the actual thing with ease.
You have been acknowledged by Inferno's Phantom to this extent,
Have some self confidence.
Confidence?
The confidence to kill someone...
Go, Zwei.
I can't.
I can't do this!
I will give you the choice one more time.
Accept everything and survive,
or refuse it and die.
Will he be all right?
His opponent is a Navy SEAL Captain who is still on active service, isn't it?
That should be no problem.
We have asked you personally to come all the way here, after all.
It is all to witness his abilities with your own eyes.
What weapon did he chose?
When you are on the hunt, think about how you would escape.
If you are trying to escape, think otherwise.
Your opponent should also think straight ahead.
That's why...
Phantom.
How do you see this?
Captain Wallace is a trained professional.
His experience should have been much greater than Zwei's.
But if he keeps his mind clear,
Zwei has a better sense of reflection and focus.
And your conclusion?
50-50.
Their own potential abilities will decide the outcome.
And what about Zwei's chance to win?
I do not know Captain Wallace's physical strength.
Wait! Please wait!
I don't carry a weapon.
Hear me out!
I don't know why they made a kid like you do something like this,
but think clearly!
We have no reason to kill each other.
Do you have a family?
I have a very young little brother.
I wanted to give my brother a life without hardship.
If you see only one rat, there are actually thirty around.
Someone who lied, lied other times as well.
I've been walking in dangerous places all of my life.
But he's finally going to enter a university.
At least I want to take care of him until he graduates.
Workers always carry more than one tool.
Killers are the same.
You and I, are just being used by Inferno.
It's all that organization's fault.
I thought two rounds would have settled things.
In case that boy loses, what about us?
All good shows need to take the same organized steps.
As a precaution, shall we wait inside the car?
Very well.
Playtime is over.
I've seen many guys like you.
A coward who can't even pull the trigger.
I will teach you how to kill people by example, you that is...
Did it hurt?
Killing people...
...is not a job everyone can do.
Don't you underestimate it.
Your lesson is still long ahead.
Zwei.
You did good for your first time.
Why?
Isn't this supposed to be a dream?
Didn't I tell you?
It'll be a long dream.
This is the continuation of that dream.
Until you die or lose your sanity.
It's a never-ending dream.
Do you want to end it?
It is up to you.
Throw away your eyes, ears, and soul.
And become "Zwei".
See everything from Zwei's eyes.
And hear with Zwei's ears.
If you do that, you will fear nothing.
You will not suffer.
And you'll be at ease.
I...
My name is not Zwei.
I see.
I guess you're right.
What do you want me to do?
Please end it...
Everything...
You are no longer yourself.
Stand, Zwei.
Zwei.
Where did you find that boy?
A recommendation from a certain affiliate in Japan.
I see.
So there is a talent buried under such a weak country. I see.
Indeed.
You have passed your trial.
Now, you are one of Inferno.
You are like the old me.
I know all about this despair...
...and suffering.