I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
Your attention, please.
We will soon be arriving on Venus.
All passengers, please be aware of the
following government health advisory.
The floating plants used
for terraforming on Venus
may cause an allergic reaction
in some people. If untreated,
this condition can lead to Venus
sickness, a potentially fatal illness.
Therefore, if symptoms appear,
please consult a doctor immediately.
Everybody quiet down!
Both hands behind your head, all of you!
I-I'll give you money!
Take the others,
but let me go, please!
Hurry, or you'll get the same.
Dammit... why did this
have to be the day?
You, over there!
Hey!
Are you listening to me?
You! Get up!
All right, put your hands behind
your head like everyone else.
Hey, look at me! Don't you go
back to sleep, you little punk!
You're dead!
Sorry about that.
Don't move!
Think again,
my precious bounty heads.
Don't be ridiculous,
that's 5,000 Woolongs!
I had to charge you
our special rate.
Special rate? That's not
written down anywhere!
You're sending this to a
special location, not a residence.
All right, then could
you do this for me?
In the middle of the desert?
I'm afraid that's our best price.
You know, your best price sucks.
But there's nothing I can do!
Make sure it gets there, or else!
Hey, wait!
Thanks for the payoff.
Hi.
- What do you want?
- My share.
- Right here?
- Why not? I need it. Now.
That's all you're gonna get, Faye.
I know, don't sweat it.
Depositing it at the casino again?
It's a lot more fun than the bank.
Girl never gives up.
I really hate dealing with pickpockets.
Amazing... you really are amazing.
All right! You're the guy
who fragged those hijackers.
You have some very
smooth moves, my friend.
Can I ask you a favor?
Can you teach a guy like me
how to make all those cool moves?
Like judo? And kung fu?
Huh?
Hey, wait a minute!
I wanna be a tough guy
like you, you know?
You are really annoying.
Now what part of "no"
didn't you understand?
Oh, come on, I can do it.
Just give me a try.
I beg you, master.
Going down.
Wait a second!
What was that guy's story?
Come on, just a few moves!
Think of it as helping me.
You know, like showing
a little mercy and compassion?
Afraid I'm fresh outta that stuff.
Have a heart, master! Come on!
It's not like it really
costs you anything.
Give it up already.
Venus has a lot of helium
in the atmosphere.
You can fix it with these
little popper pills.
Come on, that's not fair!
You brought it on yourself--
Those were just regular throat drops.
You're pushing it!
Oh! Hands-on training!
You're, uh...
The name is Roco Bonnaro.
It's an honor, master.
First reward we've
picked up in a long time.
So I got some tasty dog food for you.
This is all thanks to
the brilliant mastermind.
Now, let's see who's up next.
I'm telling you, don't tense up.
How am I gonna knock
someone out if it's all limp?
It's not about strength or power.
You gotta be fluid.
Huh?
You have to be like water.
- Hmm...
- You see what I'm saying?
Not even a little bit.
That's what I thought.
All right, come at me with a knife.
- You're gonna get hurt.
- Just do it.
Here I come!
How did you do that?
You're tense, I'm calm.
You apply excessive force,
I control that force
through fluid motion.
That means relaxing the whole body so
it can react instantly without resistance.
You know, without thought.
Do you see now?
It means becoming like clear water.
Water...
Right. Water can take any form.
It drifts without effort one moment,
then pounds down in
a torrent the very next.
Maybe I get it,
but then again, maybe not.
You young fool!
You should have a little
respect for your elders!
Hang on to this!
Meet me tonight, no, tomorrow night
at the cathedral on the edge of town.
- What? Hey, wait!
- There he is! Get him!
Casinos again?
The ones around here are
famous for stacking the deck.
Doesn't matter. It's her money.
On top of it,
she takes off like a bullet,
and we never know
when she'll be back.
Well, no use wasting time, huh?
How about taking in some pocket money?
Piccaro Calvino.
Usually a nickel-and-dime guy,
but by some miracle,
he pulled off a big hit this time.
Price is double if we
bring in the whole crew.
This is what they stole,
they're very rare.
These plants are used to make
the meds that cure Venus sickness.
They're very hard to grow.
Worth tens of millions each.
Sorry!
Shit... where'd he go?
Kid can... run...
Let's go.
Not bad, yeah.
Shh.
I say we keep it, definitely.
It's worth a lot more than those hoods.
Their rewards are chump change.
No, we can't.
Ha! You had to think about that.
Don't be a ditz. This thing is hot.
It's too dangerous to hold on to.
Sometimes you've gotta take a risk.
How much you lose at that casino?
What's that?
Piccaro's up to you. I'll get Roco.
You've got an appointment with him.
Why don't you just wait?
They say that Lady Bounty's
very fickle, you know?
It's Lady Luck, FYI.
A wrecked shuttle?
Why would that be out there?
Don't know.
There might be a few crazies living in
that godforsaken desert, but still...
Hold it right there!
Hold it right there! Both hands up!
I'm not a criminal.
Whoa, that makes me sound
more like a criminal, doesn't it.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Spit it out!
Let go.
I'm sorry, I just
came here to see Roco.
You mean... you're a friend of his?
Uh, well, not--
I'm glad.
Make sure you wash both hands, sport.
Boss, we can't find him anywhere.
Uh, h-hi...
You know, it's all because
of those floating plants.
They're only here on Venus.
Sometimes they send down spores
that look just like falling snow.
Most people aren't affected by it,
but some of us are.
I lost sight completely in both eyes.
Must be very hard for you.
It's surprising how you adapt.
And also, in a way, you understand
more when you can't see.
- Will you get better?
- If we spend a lot of money.
Truth is, I don't really mind
if I have to stay like this.
But Roco...
He cares about his little sister.
Look, Roco sent me this yesterday.
I know everyone says
bad things about him.
And I know he hangs out
with some bad people too.
But Roco has a good heart.
You know, I could be one of those
bad people he hangs around with.
Maybe... Guess you could be one.
But if you are, you're very different.
I can feel these things.
Both you and Roco have
something beautiful inside you.
It's hard for most people to see it,
but it's there. I know it is.
That's why I'm sharing
my tea with you.
Something beautiful, huh?
I'm afraid that... afraid that
I lost that a long time ago.
I want Piccaro.
Tell me where he is.
Piccaro? Well, I never heard
of the guy, sweetheart.
Now have you heard of him?
Well, as a matter of fact...
Huh? What's your question?
The price of seeds
from grey ash plants?
I'm just asking.
Well, just don't.
Those things are like gems.
You're lucky if you ever see one.
Oh. Really...
Well, it'd probably be hard
to find a buyer, but if you did,
I'd say about 8 million each?
- Why? Did you get some?
- No.
I thought so.
- Find Piccaro yet?
- We'll have him soon.
Just don't screw up your end.
So, little Roco.
You can be a nice boy
and tell us where the plant is.
But if you don't want to tell us...
I'm real sorry, but I dropped it.
Guess you're not gonna buy that, huh?
My little Roco.
You know, I heard you have
a younger sister somewhere.
- Is that true?
- She's got nothing to do with this!
And she won't, if you tell us
where you put the plant.
It's, uh...
I wanna know where Piccaro is.
A quick answer would be good.
O-Okay! You 'on't have to 'e 'o rough!
What? What'd you say?
I can't 'reathe!
Yo.
Oh, so you found the old place, huh?
And I brought it like you said.
Sorry, but I took a peek inside.
I see. So you know what it is?
Grey ash. Humble name
for such an amazing plant.
It's worth ten times the bounty on you
and all of your buddies combined.
Don't move.
So you're a bounty hunter, huh?
You're here to nab me
and take me in, aren't you?
Stella needs this.
That's the whole point, isn't it?
Get outta here quick,
or they're gonna kill you!
I got set up!
It was a stupid wild goose chase!
Jet, are you listening to me?!
W-Wait a minute, please!
He brought the plant!
That's what you wanted!
Now let him go, please!
I'm asking you!
Your patsy made a good
delivery boy, Roco.
Here's my thanks.
Get him!
Take him out, and do it quick!
Hold it right where you are!
She could be a little more
delicate about this.
Whoa! Easy, Faye!
There's no reward if
they're all dead, remember?
Shit, these guys are bounty hunters!
Get that thing back, now!
Roco!
Those stupid idiots!
You've already caused me enough trouble.
Come on, hang in there, you hear me?
Roco!
Master... you see it?
I was fluid like water.
Yeah. Don't try to talk anymore.
We'll have a doctor here in
a couple of minutes so-- Hey!
I have a favor...
In the music box at Stella's...
Leave it to me.
Stella's gonna be all right, Roco.
Thanks.
Okay, hang on.
Now, don't die. Don't die!
I-I wonder...
If I had met you
earlier in my lifetime...
Do you think that we
would have been friends?
Come in.
Roco? Is that you?
It's me instead.
Oh! Hey, you know
what Roco did? Huh?
He got me some grey ash from the
seedlings, and money for treatment!
The doctor says my eyes will be
all better now, isn't it great?
I want the first thing
I see to be Roco.
So tell him to come
and visit me right now!
Tell him I can't wait!
Oh, Spike... Is he in jail?
No.
Then why hasn't he come to see me?
He's dead, isn't he.
I see.
Stella...
It's okay. You can leave now.
He must have died...
because he was doing something
that was wrong, I'm sure.
It's better... if you leave for today.
It's just that...
I never got to see Roco
once with my own eyes.
Hey... what was he really like?
You know better than anyone,
without looking.
He was a terrific guy.
Exactly the person you thought he was.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
Starting next week,
Ed will be on the scene!
Who are you?
Uh, well, Ed will introduce Ed.
Full name, Edward Wong Hau
Pepelu Tivrusky the Fourth.
- That's a long name.
- Who the hell is this?
Ed made up that name for Ed.
Isn't it cool?
If you made it up,
how can you be the fourth?
Next episode:
"Jamming With Edward."
Does anyone know who this kid is?
Watch it!