And just like that.
Everything changed.
At that terrible moment, in our hearts, we knew.
Home was a pen; humanity, cattle.
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
Moment of truth, people! It's on us!
Either we secure this ground as mankind's
first stronghold beyond the walls, or we die!
Target approaching!
Split into five groups, now!
Group one will act as the bait!
All squadrons, engage omni-directional mobility gear!
Hit it from every angle!
Ahhhhhh!
For my brothers! For humanity!
Mikasa. Hey.
We should get back.
Um, where are we exactly?
Try asking me again when you're awake.
I'm up, I... I just... I dunno.
It's like the dream I was having went on forever.
It's gone now. What was it about?
Eren, have... Have you been crying?
Harken! These walls are a bulwark gifted by God!
Riven rock? Stone? Mortar? No, my brethren!
They are bastions of faith! The will of heaven manifest!
Do me a favor, huh? Don't let anyone know I was crying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Still, though.
You don't even remember why?
Might want have your dad look into that.
Right, 'cause tearing up is usually a medical thing.
Somebody messin' with you?
Hey Mr. Hannes.
Or you just get on Mikasa's bad side?
No! What are you even talking about?
Ugh! You smell like a tavern!
If only tears were cups of ale.
Of course.
You kids care for a swig?
Aren't you, uh, on watch?
Yup! Watchin' the ol' gate we are.
Thirsty work, playin' sentry. Pinochle
only goes so far to chase off the boredom.
Li'l nip now and then keeps us all in our
courage for a spell. Perks of being a guard, eh?
How do you expect to fight if
you're so loose on your feet?
Huh? Now why on earth would I have to fight?
Why do you think? What if they break through the walls?
We'd be sitting ducks on your watch!
Eren. Kid. Please. Use your inside voice.
The doc's kid has some fire in him!
Listen, the only thing they've done to the
wall in the past hundred years is scratch at it.
I have the feelin' if they get it in their big heads
to do somethin' else, we'll be more 'n ready for 'em.
A feeling? What have any of you
actually done to be ready for 'em?
Dad says you've gotta stay sharp!
Ah, good Doctor Jaeger. Yeah, well.
Can't argue with a man who
single-handedly spared us from the plague.
Thing is, he's talkin' about his scalpel.
What we do isn't half as important.
Hey, no disrespect to your father, but a soldier's time
beyond the wall kinda tends to put the
whole issue into a different perspective.
You see 'em groping around out there, mindless, dead-eyed.
Wait a minute. Sounds to me like you
don't even think they're all that dangerous.
Eh.
Oh great! Then at least have the decency to stop calling
yourselves a garrison; people might get the wrong idea!
Good point.
Look at it this way, huh? If a garrison's actually
doing what people think it oughta, we're up a creek.
Personally I take a lot of
stock in being called a freeloader,
it means things are good. It's
how I can measure peace of mind.
Good? We live in a cage. All we do is eat and sleep.
That's it. End of story.
We have the peace of mind of livestock.
Man, you were right about the kid havin' fire!
Careful not to cry it out.
You coming back to the game or what?
Yeah.
Hey! Where you goin'?
The mouth on that kid.
He's just a kid.
Tends to dream bigger than life really wants him to.
Eren. You should let the Scout Regiment thing go.
Seriously? Why does everybody think they're a joke?
What people think about 'em isn't really the issue.
Perfect timing! They're back!
We can make it if we hurry.
Get a move on! I want a good view!
Argh. Can't see squat.
Sure taken a hit, haven't they?
Yeah. Rest of 'em got eaten. That's what
happens when pride takes you outside the walls.
Moses? Moses?
Beg your pardon. Where is my
son? He should be with you all.
Oh, please tell me he made it!
I wish I had better news. Give it to her.
I'm sorry. It's all that was left of him.
He... He did good, yes? He was brave?
Tell me my son stood his ground to the bitter end.
That his death meant something!
Tell me his sacrifice gave us a better chance!
He was brave!
But. His sacrifice meant nothing.
So with all our losses. It's ever the same.
The day was lost! We have nothing!
Your son died because of me! I sent him to his death!
I sent all of them to their deaths!
And there's nothing to show for it!
All of it amounts to nothing!
Uplifting, huh.
Oh, sure.
Nothing like seeing our hard-earned taxes go toward
keeping those bastards fat and happy on human gristle.
You little punk!
What are you doing? Let me go!
Yeah, that's right! You'd better run!
Alright, I get it! Stop already!
Oh great! Firewood everywhere! Perfect!
So. Are you still bound and determined
to become one of them? The Scouts?
Just help me pick these up.
Like there was much to begin with.
Hey, we're home.
Welcome back, kids.
Wow. Somebody worked hard to keep
us in fuel for the next several days.
Eh. Whatever.
What was that for?
Your earlobe's red, which means
you've got something to hide.
Mikasa helped you again, now didn't she?
Hey. Where you off to, Dad?
A patient?
Yes. Some folks in the Interior.
I should be back in about a week or so.
So, um, Eren's thinking about joining the Scouts.
Way to keep a secret, mouth!
Get that ridiculous thought out of
your head this instant, young man!
No son of mine is going to be fodder!
Do I make myself absolutely clear?
Stop yelling at me!
Don't you dare...
It's a nightmare, Eren.
The Outside. You really have no idea.
Yeah, I get it, okay? But it's
gotta be better than this life!
I'm not stupid; I know it's ugly out there,
I know there's death around every corner. But...
We can't just give up on it.
'Cause otherwise this nightmare's never gonna end!
I see.
Excuse me. I'll be late for the ferry.
Darling, wait! Scold the boy, for heaven's sake!
Scold him? Dear, please. Think this through.
Mere words won't hold back the boy's curiosity. Eren.
Behave while I'm gone and I'll let you in
on what I've been doing in the cellar. Agreed?
Yes sir, you got it!
Have a good trip!
I meant what I said.
What?
The whole idea is just irresponsible.
Huh? Irresponsible?
So, what? It's more grown up to settle for living in
fear behind some stupid wall your whole pointless life?
Eren!
Mikasa.
The boy needs to be protected from himself.
Promise me whatever happens I
can count on you to have his back!
Where's the sacrilege now, huh?
Or does your philosophy say it's wrong to fight back, too?
As a matter of fact, it does. I'd rather
take a few lumps than brawl like a beast!
Oh, so now I'm a beast?
Take a good hard look at yourself
and tell me you're not acting like one!
You resort to violence because
your brain's the size of a walnut!
So pummel me all you want! I've already won!
Yeah, well you know what? I'm a sore loser!
Back off!
It's Eren!
Hey, lookie here! Back for more?
You'd think he would have learned his lesson.
Give this one to me.
Oh crap. She's with him.
Run! Just run!
Heh-heh. That's all it takes.
One look. I'm just that scary.
Well, one of you is.
Where'd they get you, Armin?
It's alright. Thank you.
Okay.
Oh, they just heard me rattling on about
how mankind's future lay beyond the walls.
Doubt they understood half of it, but still.
Idiots.
Why's it gotta be this way?
Why can't people just let us dream?
The walls are a powerful idea.
We've survived for a hundred years because
of them. No one's keen on tempting fate.
I may not agree with that sentiment,
but I can see where they're coming from.
It's human nature, Eren.
When all's said and done, the government's
policies are a reflection of our fear.
Yeah, the rest of the herd's
maybe. I say to hell with them!
Someone's gonna hear you.
Keep it down.
What do I care? You'll rat me out either way.
What?
I never promised you anything.
Your folks know about the Scouts?
Basically. And they're not too pleased.
Yeah. Big shock.
It's sad.
What most people here are willing to settle for in
exchange for some fleeting sense of security, you know?
Momma!
And make no mistake, it absolutely is fleeting.
The walls can't hold forever.
Only a matter of time.
What was that?
I dunno!
I'm tellin' ya, it came from over there!
Armin, what are you doing?
Talk to me! What's going on? Some kinda explosion or...?
No! That's impossible!
That wall's fifty meters high!
Oh god.
It's a titan!
It... It blasted a hole. Like it was kicking a rock.
Run for your lives!
They've breeched the wall!
We have to go.
Eren! No!
Our house is in that direction! Mom's all by herself!
Mikasa!
This... This is the end.
They're inside. We... Every last
one of us is going to be devoured!
Our house is fine; our house is fine.
You'll turn the corner and it's gonna be
standing there in one piece, just like always!
Mom!
Eren, wait!
Mikasa, grab that end and hoist with everything you got!
Oh, no.
Hurry up, dammit!
I'm trying!
It's them. You've got to get out of here!
Eren! Just take Mikasa and run! Now!
I want to, more than anything!
But first I need you on your feet!
Sweetie, listen to me. My legs have been crushed.
Even if you could get me out of here, I can't run.
There's no time.
Whatever! I can carry you!
Will you just shut up and
listen to me for once in your life?
One thing I'm asking you! One thing!
Mikasa, make him!
I can't.
You want all three of us to die?
Hannes!
Take the children and get them out of here!
Come on, Carla; that's not our only option.
Hey, I'm a trained soldier.
My skill set is killin' Titans and saving lives!
No, wait! Don't do this! Please!
Nothing fancy. Just take it down.
Get all three of 'em out of harm's way.
Make good on the debt you owe!
No! What are you doing? Put me down, you bastard!
Thank you, Hannes.
Wait! No!
We can't just leave her!
I love you! You hear me?
Stay alive!
Don't leave me.
Stop it! Nooooo!
And just like that. Everything changed.
At that terrible moment, in our hearts, we knew.
Home was a pen. Humanity, cattle.
Shiganshina crumbles. Prayers are useless.
Tears are absurd. Death agonies are nothing.
When total ruin is your reality, all
that's left of any value is revenge.