From yesterday's me to tomorrow's me:
Don't mind about the lost diary pages.
I just tore out and threw away the pages on which I made writing mistakes.
I didn't have any unhappy experiences.
Rather, I was happy.
It was a happiness I didn't really deserve.
That's why it was just a writing mistake.
Something that never happened from the very beginning.
Therefore, I tore them out and threw them away.
Please don't worry about it, and continue living your days as before.
And... please don't get involved with a person called Asou Renji-san from now on.
It will bring unhappiness to both you and him.
To: tomorrow's me. From: yesterday's me.
A
Note: The furigana in this episode all have the same meaning as the kanji unless specified.
It has already been a long thirteen hours since Chihiro and I broke up.
I bet Chihiro has already forgotten what happened yesterday.
Not just what happened yesterday, but everything since the day we met.
Everything about me...
Chihiro is the same as usual.
She's the same as the Chihiro from before she met you.
Do you know why she wrote a novel like that?
I'll listen if you've got something to say.
I see. It's painful, isn't it?
Please don't be so nice to me.
If you do, it will look like it's really over, won't it?
It's really over.
Strictly speaking, Chihiro's problem isn't that she forgets what has happened.
She can't remember it in her brain.
It's a result of repeatedly losing thirteen hours of memories.
Present-day medicine can't make Chihiro better.
Even if a miracle occurs and her illness is cured, her lost memories will never come back.
Besides, miracles don't exist in this world.
There are only inevitabilities and accidents, and what you're going to do. That's it.
It's painful to be unable to reach the person you love.
But if you keep grieving over it, the burden in your heart will just get heavier.
Even so, there's no way I can forget about it!
I didn't tell you to forget about it.
Going on with your life while shouldering that burden is also a way to live.
I won't tell you to do that though.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Are you always at the church because you're shouldering a burden?
I wonder. I've already forgotten the reason.
Come in.
What?
Nothing. I was just wondering what happened to you.
Nothing.
Really? By the way, isn't it almost time to submit your career interest survey?
Yeah.
Have you decided what you want to do?
No, not yet.
I see. Take your time. It's your dream after all.
I can't do it.
I can't even think about tomorrow, let alone such a distant future.
There won't be a "tomorrow."
Renji...
It'd be nice if tomorrow never came.
You shouldn't say something like that.
Couldn't tomorrow possibly be a better day than today?
What's wrong, Renji? Where are you going?
There's no way that could be true.
What are you grieving over, young man?
Kuze-san...
Here you go.
Thank you.
Human beings are cruel.
Even though it's heartbreaking, I feel hungry.
Even though it's painful, I feel sleepy.
And, even though it's painful for me, I still eat and sleep peacefully.
I can't forgive myself, and hence it becomes even more painful.
But, that proves you're alive.
Kuze-san...
What is it?
What should I do to fulfill my dream?
Let's see. To fulfill your dream, you need to have a dream first.
To have a dream?
You might think it's obvious, but it's a very important something.
You can have an image, a desire, or a wish of what you want to become.
Wish...
This is what I wanted to become.
Don't forget about it, and keep wishing for it.
That's the first step to fulfilling your dream.
What if the dream is something impossible?
You can only wait for a miracle to happen.
Miracles don't exist in this world.
"There are only inevitabilities and accidents, and what you're going to do."
That's Himura favorite phrase, isn't it?
But sometimes the outcome of your action, which become inevitable,
will overlap with accidents, and fulfill your dream unexpectedly.
I don't know if that can be called a miracle, but there's one thing I'm certain about.
Nothing will happen if you don't wish for it.
A
The furigana next to it says "Euphoric Field."
Wish... eh?
No matter how much I wish for them, there are things I can't do anything about.
Chihiro's memories won't come back once they disappear.
The time that she spent with me has already...
I always felt like crying.
I always looked up at the sky because I felt like my tears were going to start.
Chihiro...
E-Excuse me...
Yes?
Erm, can I ask you something strange?
Have we met before?
Even though I remember.
Even though I remember everything.
Even though I can't forget.
How is that... How is that possible?!
Chihiro...
I'm going to break up with Renji-kun soon.
Even though it will be painful and lonely, I decided from the beginning that this would be the last time.
That's why I could put up with it.
Because it was the last time, we kissed many times.
Because it was the last time, we did it many times.
Even though it's sad, this memory will soon disappear too.
Even so, I think I'll be fine.
No matter how painful it is, no matter how lonely it is, I'll forget about these feelings right away.
But now I still remember them, so it's heartbreaking. It's very painful.
Renji-kun's warmth still remains in my heart.
To tell the truth, I want to be with Renji-kun just like this all the time.
I want to feel Renji-kun all the time.
I want to spend time with Renji-kun just like before.
I don't want to forget. I don't want to disappear.
I don't want to return to those empty days anymore.
Renji-kun was the knight who saved me from agony.
Renji-kun was the prince who rescued me from inside everlasting time.
Even though I'll forget, even though I'll disappear, I love Renji-kun.
No matter how much time passes, even if everything disappears from within me,
at this very moment, I love Renji-kun from the bottom my heart.
Renji-kun, thank you for everything.
And... farewell.
There's still something I can do.
It could be a waste of effort, but... but...
Even though there are still missing pages...
Even though there are still a lot of missing pages...
I'll gather them.
I'll definitely gather all of them together.
That's why... That's why, don't...
Thirteen hours is a long time.
Why are you doing that?
Chihiro...
Even though I shouldn't... Even though I should forget about you...
I've been thinking back on it over and over again.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I can't not think about you for thirteen hours.
Chihiro!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I won't let you forget anymore.
I won't let you forget no matter what happens.
I'll always be with you.
That's why... That's why...
Renji-kun!
Chihiro!
We'll definitely... always be together.
I believe everyone has prayed to God at least once.
Even though they might not believe, one day they will surely make an honest prayer.
Something that everyone is looking for.
Something that everyone is after.
Something that's created from everyone's continuous wish and the bonds between them.
The thing that's created is...
Geez, I told you guys to free some space on the hard drive, didn't I? I can't edit.
President, are you still playing with that?
You should give up and work on something new to change your mood.
It's okay. Let me do what I want.
It wouldn't end like this.
There's no way one of his movies would end like this.
Even though it's frustrating, the movie sparkles.
Shouldn't you see how it goes for a little longer?
You just heard today that your recovery is complete, right?
No, I can't stay still anymore. With my body feeling so light...
Hey, Kei-chan!
Oh, what's for breakfast?
It's dinner if you consider the time. I already finished school.
You don't need to make something complicated.
You're going to have exams soon, aren't you?
No problem, no problem.
My brain is different from yours.
On that subject, can't you do something about your lifestyle of sleeping during the day and waking up in the evening?
It's okay, isn't it?
We have enough time to be together, and we won't disturb each other's work and studies.
Isn't it all good?
Menu planning will be a problem.
Our breakfasts and dinners will be reversed, won't they?
I don't mind eating fried meat after waking up though.
My pride won't allow that.
I've decided that I'll come up with a breakfast menu when you get up.
You don't really need to take it too seriously.
I want to.
Because I want you to eat it while it's still warm.
Huh, it's from Kei.
Ah, how did it go for Kei-chan this morning?
"Completely recovered. Going to club activities right now."
So she said.
I'm glad to hear that.
Don't you think Hiro-senpai is mean?
He pretended to be a perverted and geeky student,
but his real identity is Shindou Nagi-sensei, whom I really admire.
I feel totally betrayed.
I really hate him right now. I'm extremely angry.
You don't need to be that mad, do you?
Hm, are you taking Hiro-senpai's side?
Is this the rumored friendship between guys?
Have you fallen for a man?
Is this the joyful and embarrassing boys love?
What are you talking about?
All right.
This is as far as you guys go then.
H-Here?
Because beyond here is the place where I fight.
I see. Well then, good luck.
Yeah. Say, Senpai.
What is it?
Thank you.
I can now walk on my own feet. Anywhere I go, I'll be running towards it.
Make sure to follow me closely.
Okay.
That's right. I can't keep waiting forever for someone to take my hand.
Be careful, Kei-senpai.
I got it.
Ah, come to think of it...
What is it, Renji-kun?
You said before that you were more afraid of being forgotten than of disappearing, right?
Yeah, I might've said that.
I see. Yeah, I've decided.
I liked that place.
The quiet, empty train station where nobody came was the best place for reading alone.
However, someone got here before me today.
That was an encounter that lasted less than forty-five seconds.
Oh. It's from Chihiro.
What does Chihiro-chan say?
It seems that in order to fulfill your dream, the first step is to keep wishing for it.
Yeah. I found my dream, thanks to you.
I saw the color I had always been looking for.
I haven't found my dream yet, but I've found my way of living.
Way of living?
Meaning, to be with you.
I understood what kind of movies I want to make.
Right now, I want to keep running with all my heart.
I'm already satisfied that my last dream had come true.
It's not the last one.
This is only the beginning.
I will walk down the path together with you.
My, good evening.
Yo.
I've made you wait for a very long time.
I see. Sorry about that, Yuko.
It's been a long time, Yu-kun.