When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
I will teach everyone what true culture is.
And you. Finish coloring in the dark spots.
What?
Kuzuha-sama!
I was tiring of normal culture festivals.
Besides, right now, that head-to-toe Milady boy must be...
Milady.
How could you abandon me?
Yes, I like it.
Kuzuha-sama...
Color in the dark spots on this one, too.
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
Just you watch! I will take over this world with my manga!
Are you seriously under hypnosis?
Aren't you a little too worried?
We did receive a personal call from her last night.
Still, don't you find it strange?
That Milady is actively taking part in a school event...
...and is spending the night out trying to make the culture festival more interesting in collaboration with the Superintendent!
Where in that sentence do you find an element to worry about?
Nothing if you just read the words, but...
Well, Klaus-san doesn't know the Superintendent's nature, so...
And also Nagi has a bit of a problem in her daily life.
But, to know that Superintendent's character. As expected of you.
When it comes to the ability to cause trouble to others, she beats everyone else by leagues.
Excuse me.
Hinagiku-san?
Yes? Good morning.
Hayate-kun, we don't have time for greetings.
What's the problem, Hinagiku-san?
Look.
Th-This is...
Um, this is Hakuou Academy, right?
You think it's a strange building, too, right?
I think there is more to be surprised over than the building.
This is Nagi's doing, isn't it?
Why?
I saw a lot of cars parked out front
with many anime character drawings on them.
That's what all anime lovers' cars look like, right?
I-I think it's only a fraction of them.
In any case, a view similar to the manga festival likely to happen at the end of this year at Tokyo *** Site was there.
Doujinshi everywhere.
Character goods such as body pillows.
Doujin music CDs.
Limited edition figures at corporate booths.
Limited edition DVDs with special features.
We're selling the limited edition CD.
And, over at our Rondo Robe booth, they're selling limited edition CDs.
Those who are finding this more familiar than others, don't worry.
And, parents make sure you do not check what your children buy after they come here.
It could become the reason why they start being hikikomori.
The people look like trash from here.
There aren't enough girls' bathrooms.
There are people changing outside the locker room.
Do something about the resellers.
I couldn't buy Ka**mi goods.
And there are complaints regarding changes, too.
That's enough.
Besides, those are all completely unrelated to our culture festival.
You're right.
The Superintendent, who set up an event this large scale overnight, is amazing,
but the guests who found out about it
and came are amazing, as well.
You don't have to respect them for that.
If we don't do anything, it'll become like this every year.
We'll make such large profits.
That's not my point!
If we have so many people here,
it'll get so dangerous, we might get injured people.
I have to do something about this.
Um, I'll go search for Milady.
I think the reason behind all of this is Milady assisting the Superintendent,
and the cause for that is me leaving her alone.
To cause your master to lose interest in you...
You fail as a butler.
Poem person.
We have Sanzenin Nagi in our care.
Yes, we know that. We received a call.
A call?
That's an example of being lame.
Or a doofus.
Maybe she's just stupid.
She has to be a natural airhead.
The ahoge is the proof.
Note: An "ahoge" is a lock of hair sticking out from the top of the head
Shut up!
Oh, damn it.
And I came all the way over to sneak you over to where she is.
Why?
We're facing so much trouble thanks to her.
So take her away already!
I can't believe that this is the same campus.
Kuzuha-sama is having a snack in the dining hall,
so take her away now.
Yes, it's wonderful.
This is the pinnacle of Japanese culture!
Really now. What do you think you're doing in a place like this?
Let's go home.
Milady.
Who are you guys?
Wh-What are you saying?
Please. I'm Hayate, your butler.
Don't try to lie to me.
You can't possibly be Hayate.
I bet you're a fake.
The real... The real Hayate would...
No matter how busy he might be due to the culture festival, he wouldn't...
He wouldn't leave me alone.
Milady.
Hayate-kun...
Hey, hurry up! If you take your time, Kuzuha-sama will come back.
No mischief, Shion.
I'm sorry, Kuzuha-sama.
Boy, it looks like you really made your master angry.
She's saying that she won't return to the mansion anymore.
You're joking.
Sanzenin! You're going to show everyone how great your manga is, right?
That's right. I'm going to continue drawing manga here.
You can do that at your mansion, too.
Sh-Shut up! Splitting private life and business is a basic thing to do for a manga artist!
You're a student of Hakuou before you're a manga artist!
And you, too, Superintendent, gathering so many people.
What are you going to do if any injuries occur?
Interesting.
Then why don't we have a match?!
A match?
I'm not telling you to cancel...
I'm only saying that things are dangerous as they are now.
We will now sell Sanzenin Nagi's doujinshi at the school special booth.
Ayasaki. If your doujinshi beats us in overall sales, we will return your master and fix the culture festival, as well.
What is with this development?
It's just like Co*** **rty.
So this is a doujinshi sales showdown.
That's right.
My manga can't possibly lose to a fake!
Um, Superintendent. Are you listening to me at all?
You dare to run away? You coward!
Looks like she is not and has no intention to.
Seems so.
Very well. We accept your challenge.
Eh? Hi-Hinagiku-san?
However, to make things fair,
we, the student council, will organize everything to keep things under control and fair, including this big wild party.
Go ahead.
But, if you guys lose, the student council members will run a maid cafe in really embarrassing outfits!
If you can't accept that condition,
then I have no intention of listening to you.
What'll you do?
Even so...
Even so, the safety of the guests is important!
Hinagiku-san.
You can win, right?
Or rather, you'd better win.
I won't forgive you if you lose.
Yes...
A battle between master and butler.
This is getting interesting.
I'm the one who will win.
Hinagiku-san. Our shop is a butler cafe.
How are we going to this doujinshi sales showdown?
Yes, you do have a point.
And so the battle between the two factions began.
Hayaku koi!
Hurry and come here!
Ready?
Chotto okotteruzo
I'm a little mad
Our heart is so cheerful!
Hayaku koi!
Hurry and come here!
Millennium Legend, Magical Destroy!
Mahha kousoku dazo?
Mach high speed, you here?
On sale now!
Hikikomori nichiyoubi.
Hikikomori Sunday.
Anyone who wishes to buy one, please form 3 lines.
Suguni toned konakucha
You have to come running to me
Dame~
Or else it's a no-no!
Have a taste of your impotence, Ayasaki Hayate.
Tonikaku dame dame.
It's a no-no.
And show me you crying and withering from a broken heart.
What? Is that the reason why you set this fight up?
Do your best and lose, Hayata-kun.
In fact, go and forfeit, Hayata-kun.
I want to see Hina-chan in an embarrassing maid outfit.
So you know, if he loses, you'll be wearing the same outfits.
What?
We can't let that happen.
Right?
So we all need to support Hayate-kun.
And you, too, Hayate-kun.
If you don't win this match, you can't win Nagi back.
You have to open her eyes.
Do you hear?
Yes.
Hinagiku-san is right.
I must regain Milady's smile, no matter what.
Yorumo appare
Yorumo appare = Fun at night.
Renzoku Konbo
Renzoku Konbo = Combo Chain
We win.
I can already see him crying.
W-We have a problem!
Their sales are shooting up all of a sudden!
What?
It's that time of year. Suginami ward's famous attraction, the Hakuou Academy Culture Festival.
And this year, this shop's cake set is very popular.
Let's go take a look in the kitchen.
Excuse me. May we interview you?
Yes.
What's the secret behind the taste?
I'm just making it with all my heart.
And right now, you get this doujinshi
that lists the cake's recipe with the set.
PLACEHOLDER
Wow, that's a great deal you're getting from this.
Wh-What is this?
And the cover is specially drawn by Shiraishi-sensei.
Well, Hayate-kun's ability as a cook is at a professional level.
PLACEHOLDER
I'd like to have one, too.
But, why is Hayate-kun making cake?
It's 500 yen a set.
That's so cheap.
Can we have a cake set, Ms. Butler.
Me, too.
Yes, right away, Miladies.
Can we have a cake set here, too?
Yes, right away.
Can we have one here, too?
Hey, are you listening, Mr. Butler?
Sir?
Ah, how about a seconds for your tea, Milady?
Ohh, you're calling me Milady?
PLACEHOLDER
You don't seem to be focused, Sir.
I'm surprised those two came to help.
On the other hand,
I wonder what Milady is doing now.
I-I'm sorry, Nonohara.
Hey, Hayata-kun. You can't stop your hands.
I'm sorry!
If you don't work hard, we are the ones
who have to face the terrible consequences.
We would have interfered with you if it was only Hina.
How about we have her wear a maid outfit for us as a celebration if we win?
Nice idea.
I will not!
End of break for you, too, Hayate-kun.
We need more cake.
Yes.
I'd now like to try the cake.
Cake?
No, I mustn't.
They're thinking.
But there's nothing to fear!
We will continue to increase the lead!
Y-Yes!
If they're going to add cake, then we have an idea, too.
Shion!
Y-Yes!
There... we... go.
Sorry for the wait.
Anyone who buys Sanzenin Nagi's doujinshi will get a expensive prize!
Even those who have already bought one!
How about buying another one?
Hayate...
Dokokade boku wo yondeiru
Someone's calling me from somewhere.
Near the end of the day, the battle heats up.
Yuuki yo kaze yo maki okore
Courage and wind, start blowing around me.
And...
Dokokade boku wo yondeiru
Someone's calling me from somewhere.
I wonder what Hayate-kun's doing now.
Kizudarake datte kamawanai
I don't care if I'm covered in wounds.
Dokokade boku wo yondeiru
Someone's calling me from somewhere.
Get the car! Get the car! Get the car!
Hora saikyou no hero ni naru
See, I'll become the strongest hero.
Oh, how close!
He gets the expensive home theater set as a consolation prize!
Imasugu ikukara! Datte boku ha kimi dake no mono!
I'll be there right away. Because I belong only to you.
All right!
I'm sorry for you.
Here's your prize and doujinshi.
Thank you very much!
With that, we've sold everything!
I'm amazed that we sold this manga that doesn't make any sense.
Everyone just wanted the prize.
Yeah, that had to be it.
He's not here.
Is the reason why you're acting so stubborn that the hypnosis only partially wore off?
If so, it's easy to turn back.
You're smarter than me, aren't you?
I see. I get it.
Thank you, Haruko.
Hina.
Ah, looks like we're still down by a little.
But they ran out of ammo, so we might be able to catch up.
But there aren't any customers left.
We only have a little to go, so let's work hard to the end!
Yes! Exactly as Katsura-san says!
If we lose, you get to see Hina in an embarrassing maid outfit.
Let's... not give up... and win!
He won.
He won against something inside his heart.
Okay, then let's do this!
Yeah!
Then let's go search for customers.
Yeah, let's go.
What's wrong, Hayate-kun?
I was just thinking that working hard
with everyone on one thing is very fun.
Your face doesn't really say that.
That's not it...
I wanted Milady to experience this feeling, too.
Then let's have her experience it now.
Milady.
Welcome.
You're here to have some cake, right?
Since I know I'm the winner.
So I'm only here to see your beaten faces!
That's too bad.
We still have cake left over, so I wanted you to try some.
Right, Hayate-kun?
W-Well, if you insist so much.
I did use my head a lot from drawing the manga,
and I need the sugar from something sweet to replenish my tired brain.
So...
I want to try the cake Hayate made.
Certainly!
Sorry for the wait.
This is!
It's our specialty.
It is a little out of season,
but I made it wholeheartedly for someone.
That person said "I don't care" to me.
So... So I wanted that person to remember all the time we spent together.
It's sweet.
Hayate?
Milady!
Where am I?
I remember coming to meet you and talking to a strange fortune teller.
Milady!
What's wrong, Hayate?
If someone sees us...
We're totally being watched!
Your hypnosis must be all gone now!
So what?!
Look at the clock!
The time will run out soon.
However the difference in sales is obvious.
Now, my friends in the student council.
I'd like you to serve me
in these embarrassing maid outfits I designed.
Hello?
Nagi? I thought you must be out of your hypnotic state and with Hayate-kun by now.
You're right. So what? Things look pretty serious right now.
Oh, I'm sorry. But I wanted to have Hayate-kun's cake, too.
Will you buy some, including for all of the SPs, too?
I guess for 2000 people.
Okay.
Maria said to buy enough cake for 2000 people.
Thank you very much.
To go, right?
I-It looks like we won.
And so the risky doujinshi battle ends.
Still, I wonder why Nagi's hypnosis wore off.
I wonder why, too.
It's so half-assed, don't you think?
Hurry up, Hayate!
If you don't, the closing ceremony party will end!
What? Please wait. This is embarrassing, Milady.
Hayate-kun? What's with the outfit?
It's his punishment for leaving me alone.
Doesn't he look great?
Sounds like the folk dance has started.
Let's go, Hayate!
Eh?
I can't go out in these clothes!
Hey, Hayate!
Oh boy. Looks like Hayate-kun's busy life doesn't change.
It must be hard to deal with a stubborn person.
Wh-What's with those looks?
No, nothing really.
If you have something to say, say it clearly.
Cross-dressing...
Ayasaki Hayate...
I want him.
Gosh, Kuzuha-sama.
And so, Hayate is once again targeted by the Superintendent.
Next week, we'll fight against the city for modern teenagers.
Nagi and,
Hayate and,
Nishizawa Ayumu's
Butler Network!
Twinkle twinkle little star! I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I'm Nishizawa Ayumu.
Wait! You're still here?!
The guests should be rotating every three weeks.
What? Give me a little slack, will you?
Besides, I still haven't heard what Hayate-kun thinks about my song.
So, what do you think of my song, Hayate-kun?
You scored 35 points the last time you sang, but this one deserves 100.
Besides, nowadays, everything can be fixed thanks to science.
You spilled the beans!
Next week will be Wataru-kun and Saki-san.
Bye bye!
Why? Why is it that such a prodigy as myself can't draw anymore?
What's wrong, Milady?
Nagi is working on drawing a new manga.
Therefore, Hayate, go and find me references for date spots that teenagers like to go to nowadays.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Must see! 2007 Autumn Complete Guide Book for the Latest Trendy Date Spots for Teenagers
Therefore, I will be going out with you today, Hayate-kun.
Going out?!
Did you know? A fossil of elephas namadicus was once found at Harajyuku.