[Akira's certain day, a day of elegance compilation, episode 1]
[boy]
[Question:  Answer the following problems]
[Name:  Alexander the Great]
[Good bye, my life of living alone.]
[green-raw; yellow-forgot saffron; orange-fire too strong]
[blue-with dish detergent; orange-sticky; green-too much salt]
[tastes awful]
Yoshii Akihisa
is a young man who eagerly confronts any challenge.
Here I go!
If I use sugar water as the main course and saltwater as a side dish,
there's a kind of extravagant feel to it.
His eagerness drops a bit every day.
Coming!
Long time no see, Aki-kun.
N-Nee-san...
Yoshii Akira. 23 years old. E cup.
She's Akihisa's sister who's been living in another country.
Nee-san! Don't tell me you've been dressed like this the whole time!
What's wrong? Screaming all of a sudden...
How childish.
Coming from someone who's been walking around town in a bathrobe...
Be quiet and let me finish.
I'm dressed like this for a reason.
Sorry, Nee-san.
What happened?
I walked a long way from the airport under the blazingly hot sun for an extremely long time, while carrying all that heavy luggage.
When I got on the train, I saw my reflection and realized that I was sweating like a pig.
I thought that even if I was only meeting my brother, I still should be clean.
I didn't want you to see me like that.
So to get rid of the sweat, I put on my very water-absorbent bath robe.
Hold it! That definitely isn't normal!
So that's how I managed to meet my brother in such an elegant manner.
That's even less normal!
Thankfully, there weren't many people on the train.
If there were more, it would have been bothersome to change.
Hold on, where did you change?
Sign: Omitted
Aki-kun.
I came today because I have an important thing to do.
I'm here to check up on your living habits
and then decide if I should allow you to continue living by yourself.
Eh?
I agreed to let you live by yourself on two conditions.
You didn't forget them, did you?
If I said I did, will you get mad?
No, I won't get mad.
Thank God.
I totally—
Instead of getting mad, I will kiss you.
—totally remember!
And with the passionate, fiery kiss that still won't allow me to get married.
What the hell are you trying to do to your brother?
Don't worry.
It's your sister who won't be able to get married.
How does that make me not worry?
It'll force you to live with a sense of guilt towards your sister who nobody wants to marry.
I completely remember. Please spare me.
Then say them.
Um...
Aki-kun...
Close your eyes!
Number one: no playing video games for longer than thirty minutes per day.
Number two: no seemingly impure relations with the opposite sex.
What a pity.
Did I miss one?
You answered it perfectly; no kissing for me.
How is this depressing?
It's more organized than I thought.
You thought my room would be messier?
You are at this age after all.
I thought the room would be filled with 2000 copies of ecchi books.
I wouldn't have the money to buy 2000!
So that means you have at least one, huh?
Sign: Akihisa's points
This falls under "no seemingly impure relations with the opposite sex." Minus twenty points.
What's that score for?
It's for judging whether or not I should let you continue living alone.
I'll compare it with your next test score to decide.
So if I get 20 more points on the next test, the 20 points I lost just now will be canceled out.
Just to be careful,
you're not having any impure relationships with the opposite sex, are you?
What kind of behaviors will cost me how many points?
Holding hands with a girl will cost you 100 points.
Watching movies, eating crepes,
or having a girl make you lunch or waffles will be 50,000 points.
What's wrong?
Nothing, nothing at all.
You are a man now, after all.
I can very well understand your desires.
I didn't say that...
So I will give you a bit of leeway.
Although I disallow you to have impure relations with the opposite sex,
I'll allow you to have it with the same sex.
What? What happened to your values while you were living overseas?
Stars. They're beautiful.
This is really out of my expectations.
I still worked hard despite that.
Diligence is part of progress.
No matter how outstanding your hard work was,
if you get caught up in a small step of a long trip,
you'll ultimately end up right back where you started.
Do you have to be so harsh?
If you don't want to be chastised, then at least improve your weakest subject.
Aren't you bad at something, too?
What's that?
Cooking.
That has nothing to do with academics.
But you need to have certain skills to live.
Being only good at academics and failing at everything else...
If you continue to talk...
I'll stop your lips with a kiss.
I'm sorry.
Yuuji, I want to see your cell phone.
Why?
I heard on TV last night that you can find proof of cheating in cell phones.
Show it to me.
I refuse.
Ow...
My eyes feel like they're being burned by molten lava!
If you resist...
then I'll just have to play rough.
Hey! Don't take my pants too!
I heard that all men like to walk around in just a white shirt.
That doesn't mean I like to dress like that!
I want to see, too...
Ah, I get it! I'll give it. I'll give it to you, all right?!
Oh...
Don't be so blatantly depressed!
Here!
You have a lot more texts with Yoshii than me.
So?
In other words, you're cheating on me with Yoshii.
No way!
Can I go sleep at your house?
I don't really want to go home tonight...
Hey, wait a sec, Shouko...
That should be enough.
Good morning, Akihisa.
What's wrong Akihisa? Your face looks a lot healthier than usual.
Yeah. That's because I had a great breakfast this morning.
Akihisa sold all his manga and games so he has food money.
While Nee-san is here, if I don't pretend to live properly,
I'll get points deducted.
Cool biz?
You've seen a cool biz outfit with just the lower half?
It's all because of that weird text you sent me!
What's weird about it?
Read it out loud!
Can I go sleep at your house?
I don't really want to go home tonight...
I don't understand Aki's feelings at all!
You need to wait till you grow up more to do that!
You're so lewd, Yoshii-kun!
Yoshii...
Go to the nurse's office, okay?
Is something wrong with me learning seriously?!
What happened, Aki?
Suddenly paying attention...
You're acting really funny today.
Nothing at all.
Today's bento sure is full.
Yeah, once in a while...
Amazing... Who made this?
Me.
You're lying.
Liar.
I'm not lying!
Such extravagance... Is it Sakamoto-kun or Tsuchiya-kun?
Just tell me the truth.
Who made this for you?
Who do you think...
You don't want to go home tonight, right?
Are you that libidinous, Aki?
I don't want to believe it!
I hate you, Yoshii-kun!
What are you guys thinking?
Speaking of which, why is Kubo-kun here too?!
Screw that for now, why do you want to sleep at my house?
That's because I suddenly feel like I need to be studious...
Don't lie.
Hey, you didn't even wait for me to finish!
I see. Midterms are coming up soon.
It's not bad to have a group study session.
Really?
But it has to be at Akihisa's house.
No! Not my house!
At least not today.
What are you hiding?
Let's go and confirm...
Residency search.
Not today!
My house is very messy right now.
I'll help you tidy things up!
Ah, but...
Oh right! If I say there are things that girls wouldn't be willing to handle...
The mess is the 2000 ecchi books that I have scattered around the house!
I have to help!
I'll handle all of them!
Allow me...
This is backfiring!
Is everybody really coming to my house?
What the hell are you hiding, Akihisa?
After seeing that homemade bento you brought to school...
It must have been a girlfriend who made that.
What's with that, Aki?
Explain it to me!
Um... I haven't said anything yet.
Don't worry. Yoshii-kun wouldn't secretly go out with someone else behind our backs.
Right, Yoshii-kun?
Your eyes contain no amiability.
Well, we'll all know the truth once we go in.
Akihisa, hurry and open the door.
No.
Do you want to experience the taste of wearing nothing but a white shirt?
It'll be better if you have teary eyes and looked up.
You want to sell it?!
You're selling my pureness?!
Tsuchiya-kun, don't forget to unbutton the first two buttons.
Himeji-san, you're too specific!
I got it.
I'll open it, I'll open it, all right?
Open your shirt?
The door!
Ah! Suddenly, unexplainable items appears!
No better evidence than hard evidence.
I'm so jealous that I want to kill him.
This isn't right, Yoshii-kun.
This bra size... It doesn't fit you at all.
She's unwilling to accept reality.
Ah! That is...
A cotton puff for make up.
No. That's a fish cake.
Fish cake?
Ah, this is...
A healthy bento specifically targeted for girls!
What's wrong, Himeji-san!
I can't deny it anymore!
Why were you okay with the underwear and the make up,
but not the bento?!
Ah. Are these your friends?
A more mature, beautiful woman!
A woman with huge, sexy boobs!
You're too cruel, Yoshii-kun!
Give me back my first love!
I really don't know what the hell you guys are crying about...
I got it. I'll tell you guys.
She's my nee-san.
Nee-san?
My name is Yoshii Akira.
I thank everyone for being friends with my pitiful brother.
Please continue to take care of him.
What the hell? No matter how I look at it, she's acting very normal.
Thank you, Nee-san!
I'm Sakamoto Yuuji.
Tsuchiya Kouta.
My name's Kinoshita Hideyoshi. I've often been mistaken, but I'm not a girl—
You're a boy, right?
You're the only one that could tell that I was a boy!
That's because my idiotic, hideous, weird brother
could never possibly have relations with girls.
So these two are also boys, right?
Why are you being so rude?!
The mood was so good and all...
Those three are all girls!
No, I am a boy...
Girls?
When did you start bringing girls home, Aki-kun?
Sign: Akihisa's points
Impure relations with the opposite sex, minus 200 points.
No!
Akihisa, you've had it tough too, eh?
Yuuji.
I permit impure relations with the same sex.
It's not like that!
I'll add ten points!
Sign: Akihisa's points
That's nothing to be happy about!
We barged in here without asking, so let me at least help make dinner.
All right, thank you.
I'll come.
I'll come too.
It'll be fine with just us.
Girls can rest here!
Eh? But...
Nee-san, just be their company, eh?
All right, want to see some photo albums?
Is that okay?
Well, I'll let you see some embarrassing pictures.
Anything but that!
My life's saved.
Well, what are we making?
Looking at these ingredients, I guess we can make a Paella.
I love Paella.
But anyway... Did she know we were coming?
No way. That's because Nee-san is an idiot when it comes to cooking.
So she accidentally bought extra.
It seems delicious.
Paella, is it?
Eh? Didn't you buy those ingredients because you wanted to make that?
It looks tasty, Aki.
Yoshii-kun really knows how to cook!
You saw it, everyone saw it.
Seriously. Aki is rowdy. Minus 10 points.
Sign: Akihisa's points
It's all because of you! Always messing with me!
Nee-san actually really hates me, right?
Nope. I really love you...
as a woman.
That's totally wrong!
There's a saying in Japanese: "The dumber you are, the more loved you are."
Give it up, Akihisa. This person loves you more than anyone in the world.
Does that mean she thinks I'm the dumbest person in the world?
I also think Aki is the dumbest person in the world.
I'm positive too. There's no one in the world dumber than Aki!
No more! Stop hurting my fragile heart!
He really is an idiot.
Well then, since we've filled our stomachs, let's study now.
If you don't mind, I can help you guys.
Really?
I've completed education courses at a university over there,
so I think I can be of help.
"Over there?"
Boston, America.
There? Don't tell me... Harvard University?
So that's why...
So he's the leftover.
What are you masking behind those words!
Please look at these text books.
I found six copies under the bed.
My top-secret...
I'm deducting 60 points.
Sign: Akihisa's points
So each copy is ten points?
No. It's because you don't have any with brother-sister incest.
So unreasonable!
Then please use these as Physical Education and Health textbooks.
No! Don't expose my fetishes in broad daylight!
It seems that Aki likes girls with big breasts and pony tails.
Then, let's study shall we?
Why are you tying your hair up, Mizuki!
Because it'll bother me from studying.
I'll tie it up for you!
Minami-chan, you're so mean!
Why?
Now they won't obstruct you now.
Aki-kun, minus 100 points.
Sign: Akihisa's points
Why?!
You'll learn the reason later on in life.
What's wrong, Ninja Pervert?
Where's the rest of the 1994 copies?
You really believed it...
Morning, Yoshii-kun.
Morning, Aki.
Morning, you two.
Himeji-san, you changed hair styles?
Yeah, I wanted to freshen up my image.
Minami, you changed breast styles?
No. I found out they had grown when I got out of bed this morning.
Are you serious?!
It is puberty after all, these things happen sometimes.
I won't allow you to deface traits of the secondary growth.
It sure was fun yesterday.
We reviewed a lot of things.
But I probably won't be able live alone anymore.
Nee-san, could you hurry and go back to America...
How can you say that about your own family member?
Isn't she a good sister?
What's good about her?
Suddenly kissing and then deducting points.
She's just having fun bullying me.
That's not true.
Your sister really loves you.
In other words, she thinks I'm an idiot, eh?
Your sister keenly observes you and the things around you.
I think it's because she really cares about you.
Is that so?
What should I make tonight?
She rarely comes back here.
So I guess Japanese food would be best.
I'm back.
You're back, eh? Aki-kun!
Well, I'll go buy the ingredients for dinner.
Dinner?
Wait a minute, Aki-kun!
What is it, Nee-san?
Midterms are coming up pretty soon.
Do you have time to be making dinner?
Even though I don't have much time,
it's rare that you come back.
If that's the case, you're messing up your priorities.
I'm here to observe Aki-kun's living conditions.
You can't be spending too much time on your sister.
If something bad happens because of that, it would be troublesome for me to be blamed.
No need to cook for me.
Just focus on studying.
Leaving the cooking—
What kind of crap is that?
You only see scores, don't you?
I'll study like you want!
Nee-san is an idiot!
I'll show you with a super-high score!
Morning, Yoshii-kun.
Mornin', Aki.
Don't talk to me, or else I'll forget everything I memorized.
I-Is that so?
Then we won't bother you.
Okay! We'll begin the test.
Now start!
Piece of cake. First question.
334 BC, the last emperor of the Achaemenid Empire was Alexander the Great.
Next one!
He should be starting the test now.
Then I'll start too.
Okay, I've tried my best in answering them.
All that's left is to use the remainder of the time to check over.
Okay, put down your pencils.
Last person of each row, gather up the answer sheets.
Goodbye, my life of living alone.
Good bye, my life of living alone.
Seriously, Alexander the Great...
You filled out your name as the answer to the first question
and that shifted the answers so that they would all be wrong.
Please call me by my real name.
Darius the Third.
Stop making fun of me!
If I hadn't miswritten my answers, I'd probably have gotten a pretty good score.
If you made the same mistake on a real test,
do you think you'd be forgiven?
I worked real hard...
I've said it before.
Diligence is part of progress.
Yes.
Nee-san sure is strict.
What a mess.
Eh? Nee-san usually doesn't cook.
Raw
Forgot
Saffron
Fire
Too Strong
Dish
Detergent
Sticky
Too
Much Salt
Tastes Awful...
This is...
Failed Paella?
Don't tell me she practiced because she wanted to cook my favorite dish?
Sign: You've worked hard! I have no right to be mad!
Diligence is part of progress.
If you get caught up in a small step of a long trip,
you'll ultimately end up right back where you started.
Honestly, what an idiot...
Say, Nee-san.
Yeah?
Thank you for everything.
I love you very much.
What do you mean?
I mean as family of course.
Saying that won't make me more lenient.
What a shame.
One day.
Hm?
One day, when I feel like it...
I'll cook dinner for you.
Really?
But only when I feel like it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Nee-san.
Yes?
Do you know what the best spice is?
The best spice?
I can't cook, so I don't know.
What is it?
I wonder too...
The tenth question.
Name the Japanese author who has written such titles as 'Adolescent Detective Gang' and 'The Mystery Man of Twenty Faces.'
The culprit is in here!
It's not me.
Next week:  Mock Exam, Mysterious Thief, and the Love Letter.
This will be on the test.