Oceanus.
But what's this about?
We're going into town?
It's nothing. I just want a change of pace.
You were whining about wanting to see the shopping district too, weren't you?
The joy of window-shopping in a foreign land
is every bit as great as the joy of battle.
I really feel bad for the nations that got invaded for a reason like that.
What's up, kid? You're sounding like you actually saw it happen.
Don't worry about it.
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
This is horrible!
It's just too much!
We worked so hard to create this artwork! How could they?!
Is this... are they... even human?!
Ryuunosuke... only a very select few can comprehend true beauty and harmony.
To the vast majority of Philistines,
beauty is nothing but a target for destruction.
Maybe we just had too much fun...
And maybe God punished us.
I will say this, Ryuunosuke.
God does not punish humans, ever!
He simply toys with them.
R-Right?
Once, I committed greater atrocities than the Earth had ever seen.
But each day I murdered, and I defiled, and yet no divine punishment ever came!
And the next thing I knew,
my exploration of the depths of evil had been ignored for eight whole years.
In the end, it was not God that destroyed me,
but the selfishness of humans just like me.
The Church and the State executed me not for anything I'd done wrong,
but because they coveted my wealth and land!
What brought an end to my evil deeds was the furthest possible thing from judgment.
It was simply theft!
But...
There's still... a God, right?
Why would you, a faithless man who's never known a miracle, think that?
Because the world seems like it's boring at first...
But if you look, you can find all kinds of awesome stuff!
I've always thought this way.
A world filled with so many wonderful things
could have never happened by chance.
If you just try to enjoy it,
there's no better entertainment than this world!
I'm sure there's an entertainer writing the stories of five billion people.
If you wanted to describe somebody like that...
"God" is the only thing you could call him!
Then, Ryuunosuke, do you think that God loves humans?
He's head over heels!
If he's spending every minute of every day writing the storyline of this world,
he could never do it without love!
I'm sure he's totally into it!
While he enjoys his own work...
He loves the things that make humans look good, like courage and hope!
And he loves screams and blood just as much!
If he didn't, there's no way people's guts would be so colorful!
So I'm sure the world is filled with God's love!
In an era where the people no long believe,
and the state has abandoned God's will,
I had no idea that such a new faith had taken root!
You have my admiration, Ryuunosuke.
My master!
Aww, I'm blushing.
But if that were true,
then were all my blasphemies just a farce?
Nah. You know, the best entertainers can get smiles out of playing the villain.
If you ask me, I bet God just loves playing against your acting!
So you say that both blasphemy and praise are worship to you?
Ryuunosuke! Truly, you are the bearer of a new philosophy!
A God who makes puppets of all men for his sport,
and he himself another clown!
I see.
Then his vicious ways make sense.
Very well.
Then let us paint the gardens of God
with ever more brilliant colors of despair and terror!
We will show the author in his heaven,
that God is not the only one who knows what entertainment is!
We're gonna do something awesome again, aren't we?
Cool...
Cool!
The King gave control over the lands he conquered,
as well as the rights to their taxes, to the local nobles,
and took his armies further east.
Just like what I saw in my dream.
He only wanted to reach the sea at the end of the world.
He continued his campaign so he could see Oceanus...
Hey, kid, where are you?
There you are.
You're so small that you're impossible to see in between the bookshelves.
It was hard to find you.
Normal people are smaller than bookshelves, idiot.
So? What did you buy?
Check this out.
Admirable Grand Strategy came out today!
And I got the first-run special edition!
My luck must be pretty good!
You know, there's no point in buying the software
if you don't have the game console to play it on.
I took care of it.
Come on, kid. When we get back, we're playing two-player mode.
I bought us two controllers.
I'm not interested in low-class entertainment like that.
Why do you always try to narrow your own worldview?
Don't you ever want to try anything fun?
Shut up.
If I had time to waste on that, I'd rather spend it on a search for Truth.
So, what were you looking for here, then?
This book?
Hey... this is a book about me!
You're a weird guy.
I'm right here. If you wanted to know something, you could've just asked me.
Fine, I'll ask you! I'll ask the hell out of you!
History says you were really short.
So why did you materialize in such a gigantic form?
It says I'm short?
You really can't trust books when you don't know who wrote them.
You're not mad that it's wrong?
It doesn't really bother me, no.
Is that odd?
Throughout history, people with power
usually tried everything they could to get others to remember them.
I suppose having your name recorded in the history books
is a form of immortality.
But if that just means your name gets passed down for two thousand years and nothing else,
I'd have preferred to have...
even a hundredth of that added to my life.
Then, is it true that you died in your early thirties?
Yes, that one's true.
Hey dude!
Get out there and show us something that's gonna shock even God!
Dude!
Look forward to it, Ryuunosuke!
I shall give you the greatest "cool!" you have ever seen!
Seriously?
I can't wait!
Something awesome's gonna happen!
What are you so quiet for?
Nothing. I was just thinking how boring you were.
What? So you are bored.
Stop whining and play this game with me.
No!
Even if I get the Grail for a Servant who's a guaranteed winner like you,
I can't take pride in it at all.
It would've been better if I'd contracted with Assassin!
I don't know if that would've worked.
I think you'd be dead.
That's fine!
If I'm going to die in my own battle, then I'm not going to complain.
That's why I joined the Grail War.
And now...
I don't know what to tell you.
If the wish you had for the grail was something that impressed me,
I'd be more inclined to obey you.
But if you just want to use it to get taller...
Don't put words in my mouth!
You don't need to be in such a hurry.
Nobody said that the Grail War would be the most important event of your life—
What are you talking about?
When the day comes where you find a way to live that you can be truly proud of,
you'll be forced into your own battle whether you want to or not.
You can search for your battlefield then.
I'm sure I'm not the only one unsatisfied with this contract.
You don't like it either!
Having someone like me as your master.
If you'd contracted with a different master,
you would've been able to win far more easily, right?
Probably, yeah.
Check this out, kid.
Look at the enemy I'm fighting.
Right next to this enemy,
try to point the two of us out.
So that you can compare you and I.
That's...
Impossible, huh?
Against the enemy we're about to fight, you and I are the same.
Just little dots.
What point is there in comparing our size?
That's why I am excited!
The weakest or the smallest is fine by me!
With a body smaller than a poppy seed, I will someday surpass the world!
In my chest beats the heart of the King of Conquerors!
So, you're saying it doesn't matter who your master is, right?
No matter how weak I am, it doesn't matter to you.
Where'd you get that?
That miserable nature of yours is the sign of a conqueror.
No matter what you say, you know how small you are.
And yet you still struggle to reach heights greater than you can imagine.
That's not a compliment.
You're treating me like an idiot.
Indeed, kid. You're an idiot.
Your desires lie beyond yourself.
"Glory lies beyond the horizon."
In the world I lived in, that was the most basic rule of life.
Is that why you kept rushing towards the east like a fool?
Yes. That's right.
I wanted to see Oceanus with my own eyes.
But my dream never came true.
He didn't see that sea?
Oceanus remains the place I strive for.
It's an endless dream.
That sea is what's in Rider's heart.
Laugh if you like.
I, who dreams the same dream after two thousand years, am another great fool.
So kid.
A contract with an idiot like you feels perfect for me.
The river, huh?
Caster...
This incredible outpouring of prana
makes it clear that Caster is in the process of some incredible magic.
Welcome, Holy Virgin.
I am overjoyed that we have met again.
You never learn, fiend. What are you trying to do tonight?
I'm terribly sorry, Jeanne. But you're not the guest of honor tonight.
However, if you would like to join us as well,
I would have no greater happiness.
At this banquet and decadence that I, Gilles de Rais have prepared,
everyone may eat their fill!
Now, once again, we raise the flag of salvation!
Caster... is being absorbed?
You who have been abandoned, gather here.
I shall lead you! I shall rule you!
The resentment and rage of we, the oppressed,
shall reach to God himself!
God in heaven, with words of condemnation, I praise your holy name!
That's...
Arrogant God!
Cruel God!
We shall pull you down from your throne.
Hey, King of Knights!
King of Conquerors...
Hey, stop that. We're calling a truce for the night.
We won't be able to have any kind of fight unless we deal with that thing.
I've been going around and telling everyone.
Lancer agreed.
He should be here soon.
Understood. We agree to joining forces as well.
King of Conquerors, it will be a short alliance, but I swear loyalty to you.
Einzbern, you guys got a plan?
Lancer told me that this isn't your first time fighting Caster.
We need to take him down as soon as we can.
That monster is still maintaining itself in this world with Caster's prana.
But if it gets its own food source and becomes self-sufficient, there'll be nothing we can do.
We need to stop Caster before then.
I see. So we need to settle this before it reaches the coast and starts to feed.
But Caster himself is deep inside those thick walls of flesh.
What do we do?
Drag him out. That's the only way.
If we can expose his Noble Phantasm,
then my Gae Dearg can destroy the spell with one strike.
Lancer, will you be able to throw that spear
through his Noble Phantasm from the coast?
If I can just see it, it'll be easy.
Then Rider and I will take the front lines.
Is that acceptable, King of Conquerors?
That's fine. But while my chariot needs no roads,
how are you going to attack an enemy in the river, Saber?
My body is protected by the Lady of the Lake.
No water can stop me in my path, no matter how many fathoms deep.
That's a rare skill to have.
I want you in my army even more.
You can pay for that remark later.
For now, we need to drag Caster out from inside that monster.
Indeed!
Then I shall take the lead!
Saber... good luck.
Let's finish this, Caster!
Episode 13
The Forbidden Banquet
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
Get 'em, Bluebeard!
A failure of this magnitude is unprecedented.
You want me to draw my greatest treasure, Ea, here?!
Saber!
King of Heroes, please, wait!
What a crazy guy.
Kill all of them! Every last one!
Fate/Zero Second Season Begins April 2012