Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
Hm? Shinji, are you using
a different soup stock?
Yes, that's bonito stock.
It was a present from Ms. Ritsuko.
That's too hot!
Sorry.
You always apologize instantly!
Do you really even feel sorry?!
It's like a conditioned response with you!
You do it so people won't yell at you!
-Sorry.
-See?!
You're too intropunitive! Fundamentally!
Come on now.
That's just the way Shinji is.
And you! You're too quick
to put up with his crap!
Don't you think you've been
too soft on Shinji lately?!
Really?
Just because you got back
together with Mr. Kaji,
don't try to push your happy-happy
vibe onto the rest of us!
There's nothing going on
between Kaji and me.
Hey, Katsuragi! I found a bar with
great booze. You free tonight? Later.
But what do I know? I've never been
in a sleazy adult relationship.
But here you are, acting like a paragon
of virtue! What a hypocrite!
You make me want to puke!
Type-B harmonics test, results normal.
Adjusted depth values have all been met.
You look kind of tired, Ms. Misato.
I have a lot on my plate. Personal stuff.
-Involving Ryoji?
-Don't go there!
So, how's the Third Children doing?
-Take a look at this.
-At what?
I hope this gives him a confidence boost.
Do you read me, Shinji?
How did I do on the test, Ms. Misato?
Congrats! You are number one!
Well, this stinks. He blew right past me.
He did it so effortlessly
it's a little frustrating, you know?
He's amazing! Magnificent!
Tough! Too tough!
Ooh, Shinji the Mighty!
Our jobs will be so much easier
thanks to him!
Right?
We'll have to work super-duper hard
to keep him from leaving us in the dust!
Farewell.
TOKYO-3, YUMOTO STATION
The next stop is Seisho-Kanose.
Seisho-Kanose.
The stop is next to Bashar,
the used book and video store.
Yeah!
Evacuation of Nishi ward
will take five more minutes!
Target advancing slowly.
Rate of speed, 2.5 kph.
What kept you?
Sorry! What happened? No report from
the Mt. Fuji radio observation post?
It wasn't on their scopes! It appeared
out of nowhere right on top of us!
Pattern Orange! No A.T. Field detected!
-What's that mean?
-Is it a new type of Angel?
The Magi are reserving judgment.
Damn it, what a time for
Commander Ikari to be away...
Do you all read me?
As you can see in the data we sent,
we don't have a lot to go on.
Approach the target carefully
and see how it responds.
If possible, lure it outside the city.
One of you will take point,
with the rest providing cover. Got it?
Ooh! Ms. Katsuragi! I think Shinji
is the best man to take point!
This is obviously a job for the man's man
who has the best grades, is the bravest,
and who has the number one
synchro rate, right?
Or don't you think you can do it, Shinji?
I can handle it!
I'll show you how it's done, Asuka!
What did you say to me?!
Cool your jets, kids.
You're the one who said it, Ms. Misato.
I'm number one.
Um, that was--
Fighting is a man's job!
That's so antiquated!
Unit 02, providing cover!
Unit 00, also providing cover.
Those kids just completely ignored me.
Shinji's really come around,
don't you think?
Not like this. He needs a good
talking-to when he gets back.
You know, you have the makings
of a fine foster mother.
STATE OF EMERGENCY IN EFFECT:
CLOSED TO GENERAL VEHICLES
-Ayanami, Asuka, are you in position?
-Not yet.
We can't cover that much
ground that quickly!
Where are they?
I guess I should pin down this Angel.
It disappeared!
What is it?
Pattern Blue! Angel detected!
It's right below Unit 01!
Its shadow!
What is this thing? This makes no sense!
Shinji, get out of there! Shinji!
-Shinji!
-What are you doing, you idiot?!
Ms. Misato! What's happening?! Ms. Misato!
Asuka! Ayanami! I need backup!
Ms. Misato, do you read me?!
Eject entry plug! Send the signal!
Negative! There's no response!
Ms. Misato! Ms. Misato!
Shinji!
Asuka! Rei! Rescue Unit 01, hurry!
That idiot! Perfect scores on mock tests
don't mean a thing out here!
-It vanished again!
-Asuka, be careful!
A shadow!
Oh, no!
The city, it's...
Asuka, Rei, fall back.
-Wai--
-Wait!
Unit 01 and Shinji are still in there.
That's an order. Fall back.
This must be hard on Major Katsuragi.
When they reeled in the umbilical cable,
nothing was attached to the end.
But that means...
There's not much left
in his Eva's internal batteries,
but if Shinji can refrain from moving
around and stay in life-support mode,
he can stay alive for 16 hours.
Second tank platoon in position.
Roger. Hold position and stand by.
Opening sub laser comm line. Send specs.
Link confirmed.
Transmitting over C channel.
-UN Forces have set up a perimeter.
-And the shadow?
No movement. It grew to just past
600 meters in diameter and stopped.
How are ground forces going to be
any use against that, though?
They're here as a show of strength.
Directed at us.
What a mess. He rushed in by himself
and ignored the plan.
He has no one to blame but himself.
Just because the idiot did okay
on that test yesterday,
he goes, "I'll show you how it's done!"
He got too big for his britches!
What, you don't like it when
people bad-mouth Shinji?
Do you pilot your Eva
to be praised by others?
No, not by others! I pilot it
because I want to praise myself!
That's enough, you two.
It's true, he rushed in
without permission.
That's why I have to chew him out
when he gets back.
I never thought that sleeping
could be so exhausting.
Nothing but white.
No radar or sonar returns...
This void is too big.
It's been 12 hours since
I switched to life-support mode.
I guess I only have
four or five hours to live.
I'm hungry...
You're saying that the shadow
is the Angel's actual body?
Yes. It's roughly 680 meters in diameter
and three nanometers thick.
It's supporting that super-thin space
with an inverted A.T. Field.
The interior is an imaginary numbers space
known as the Dirac sea.
It may be connected to another universe.
And the sphere?
It vanishes when the body's
imaginary numbers circuit closes.
That object floating up there
is in reality just a shadow.
So our target is the black shadow
that swallowed Unit 01.
Then there's nothing we can do about it!
The water is getting murky!
The filters are starting to fail!
It smells...
Blood! It smells like blood!
No! Let me out!
Why won't the hatch unlock?!
Open up! Let me out of here!
Ms. Misato, what's going on?! Ms. Misato!
Asuka! Ayanami!
Ms. Ritsuko!
Father...
Please... Somebody help me.
Salvage the Eva with brute force?
As things stand,
it's the only viable option.
We drop our remaining stock of
992 N2 mines on its core area.
Concurrently with this,
our other two Evas use their A.T. Fields
to disrupt the Angel's imaginary numbers
circuit for one millisecond.
At that instant,
we focus the explosive energy
to destroy the Angel,
along with the Dirac sea that forms it.
But the Eva's frame can't take...
What will happen to Shinji?!
What kind of rescue op is this?!
The top priority of this operation
is the recovery of Unit 01.
Regardless of how badly damaged
the body may become.
Now, wait just a minute!
In these circumstances,
the pilot is expendable.
It was your mistake that cost us Shinji.
Don't you dare forget that.
Why are you and Commander Ikari
so fixated on Unit 01?
What the hell are the Evas?!
The files we gave you
are everything we have.
You liar.
Misato, please trust me.
I am taking command of
all aspects of this operation.
Route air traffic to Kansai International.
Contact the ACC and the JASSDF's
Strategic Airlift Command.
The Second Impact...
The Instrumentality Project... Adam...
I'm in the dark about way too many things.
Who is it?
Who's there?
Shinji Ikari.
But that's me.
I am you.
People have another self inside them.
The self always consists of two selves.
Two?
The self that is seen by others,
and the self that observes that act.
There are even multiples of
the individual named Shinji Ikari:
The other Shinji Ikari
that's in your own heart.
The Shinji in Misato Katsuragi's heart.
The Shinji in Asuka Soryu's heart.
The Shinji in Rei Ayanami's heart.
The Shinji in Gendoh Ikari's heart.
Each is a different Shinji Ikari,
and yet they're all the real Shinji Ikari.
You're afraid of the Shinji Ikaris
that are inside others.
I'm afraid of being hated by others.
No, you're afraid of being hurt.
Whose fault is that?
It's Father's fault.
The father who abandoned me.
It's my own fault.
There you go again,
instantly assuming that you're to blame!
That's what they call intropunitive!
I'm the one that can't do anything right!
You're the one that thinks
that you can't do anything right.
Don't you have faith in your own father?
I think I hate him.
But I'm not sure anymore.
Good work, Shinji.
Father called me by name!
My father, of all people,
actually praised me!
You're going to keep nursing that tiny bit
of happiness for the rest of your life.
If I believe in those words,
I can go on living.
By deluding yourself?
Everybody does it!
Everybody does that to go on living!
Believe in yourself for who you are.
Otherwise, you won't be able to go on.
The world is full of too many
painful things for me to live in it.
Like not being able to swim?
People aren't designed
to be able to float!
-That's self-deception.
-Call it whatever you want!
You've spent your life ignoring
or avoiding anything you don't like.
In that last battle, his kid sister got...
It doesn't matter
what everybody else thinks!
Get out!
No! I don't want to hear this!
See? You're running away again.
People can't handpick a series
of pleasant events to make up their lives.
Especially not me.
I found something that I enjoy doing.
Finding something you like
and doing just that one thing...
What's wrong with that?!
The entry plug's reserve power
is almost at its theoretical limit.
His plug suit's life-support system
is also entering the danger zone.
Let's move up the schedule by 12 minutes.
While there's still a chance
that Shinji is alive.
Father... am I an unwanted child?
Father!
You're the one who chose to run away.
That's right! The man's suspected
of killing his wife!
He killed his own wife!
No! Mother was... She was smiling.
You did a fine thing today
that people will praise you for.
You shouldn't run away, Shinji.
Keep it up.
I don't like it here.
I'm tired of being...
alone.
The heater and oxygen circulation
have both stopped...
I'm so cold...
It's hopeless... My suit's about had it.
I guess this is it. I'm so tired...
Tired of everything.
Mother?
You'll be okay?
Oh? I'm glad to hear it.
-Both Evas are in position.
-A.T. Field preparations complete.
-Roger.
-T minus 60 to mine drop.
What's happening to it?!
-Give me a sit-rep!
-Unknown, ma'am!
All the meters are off the scale!
But we didn't do anything!
-Wait, could it be Shinji?!
-That's not possible!
Unit 01's energy is down to zero!
I'm... piloting one of those things?
What have we...
What kind of monster did we copy?
I know damn well that the Evas aren't
simple copies of the 1st Angel.
But what is Nerv planning to do with
the Evas after the Angels are defeated?
Shinji!
Shinji! Are you okay, Shinji?!
I just wanted to see everybody.
One more time.
Weren't you going to chew him out?
I've never felt more afraid
of the Evas than I did today.
Are they really on our side?
It's possible that they hate us.
Major Katsuragi might suspect something.
I see. That’s fine for now.
If Rei and Shinji ever learn
the secret of the Evas,
they'll probably never forgive us.
You can stay in bed today.
We’ll take care of the rest.
Thanks, but I'm okay now.
Oh, I'm glad to hear it.
It's still there. The smell of blood.
TO BE CONTINUED
NEXT EPISODE
Eva-04, under construction
in the state of Nevada in America,
vanishes along with Nerv's 2nd Branch.
This incident forces them
to select a new Eva pilot.
Next episode!
"The Fourth to be Qualified"!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming