Why can't I do it well?
Same here...
Noeru-chan?
Rainy Season Sky
Quartz Rainbow
Do you have your wallet with you?
Yes.
Your ID?
Handkerchief?
Yes.
Tissue?
Map?
Yes.
Compass?
Carry-on food?
Yes.
Helmet?
Pistol?
Hand grenade?
That was a joke, Kana-chan.
What? I was so surprised.
If you were relaxed enough to think about it, you would have understood it immediately.
That's just mean, Rio-senpai.
Recently, you two have been so friendly to each other.
Rio, you really look like a worried mom.
Here. This is your list for today.
Listen. Today's mission is to go to town and purchase the things on the list. Got it?
Yes.
Then, please drive safely.
Departure.
Pot Au Feu is French beef stew, a type of European hotpot.
Please come back early! We have "Pot Au Feu" for dinner!
Come straight home!
She really is a mother.
This will be our first visit to the town, right, Noeru-chan?
Mmhmm.
But actually, this is like my first visit to the town...
Amazing!
What is that?
It's totally different from the time at the water festival.
The town has calmed down a lot. It's quiet.
Ow ow ow ow...
The first one is Nue, the proud roof decorator of Torowa.
It serves to ward off evil.
The drinking fountain is next to it. That is the model of the 12th king of the Republic of Helvetia, King Akira Arukaria II.
Arrival.
Ah, the one just now was...!
Umm. I was told that, so we could drive safely.
Ah-huh, thank you, I got it now.
Noeru-chan, you really know a lot.
Ah, girls.
Can you decide whether you're coming in or not? You are disturbing my business.
Ah! You're the lady from the water festival!
Big sister.
Don't be ill-tempered.
You're really stubborn, as usual.
Then at least call me Naomi.
Naomi-san?
So you mean, the next shipment will be next month?
Umm.
By the way, does that girl know about it?
No.
You girls are still weird, despite being soldiers...
E-Excuse me!
W-What!?
What is that?
You were also interested in it the first time you came here.
E-Excuse me, can I touch it?
A-flat.
This is a fish, right? What is its name?
Ah...That is...
Not a fish.
Huh? But...
That's a dolphin, a type of living creature, which was closer to us humans than fishes.
It's a sea-dwelling mammal from back when there were still living things in the sea.
It...it was in the ocean?
Really...
Beautiful.
That guy is so skilled at making these.
He's the kind of person who doesn't look like an absolute romantic, but actually is.
You know him? The one who made these?
He has a large studio just outside of town.
All the glass items that we have are his products.
I really want to see where he makes all of these.
No problem.
What?
We are going there anyway.
Really? The glass factory produces parts for the Takemicaduchi.
Right. Naomi is also collecting parts from the old time for us.
But, Noeru-chan, you are really great.
You can fix such a complex machine in that way.
In that way?
Even though I can remember the secret chord of the signal horn, my head feels as if it's about to split.
It's not...that...difficult
because...a machine won't betray you.
Noeru-chan...
Here you are. Your change is 2,750,000 yen.
Huh!? We get that much back?
You got it wrong. The change should be 2.75 yen.
You're still like that, Noeru-chan.
Here's your change.
It's true.
The recent sound of the horn in the morning, was it by you?
Y-Yes.
I'm still very unskilled... I'm sorry.
It's good! I like it.
How should I say it... It completely wakes me up.
I must improve at it as soon as possible so that I don't cause trouble for the town.
Seiya, you're so cunning.
If you don't feel good, then come after me...
Kanata, my...
Ou-ou-ouch...
Ah, I'm sorr...
Yeah! You got hit!
I'm really sorry.
Huh!? You are...
The girl from the festival!
The clumsy girl!
I feel safe now.
It seems like you've recovered from your illness.
You murderer!
Seiya-san! These people have no relation to your parents, all right?
You people are all the same! I hate the military the most!
Leave town as soon as possible!
You blow your horn poorly every morning!
You are so annoying!
Come on, Seiya!
I am really very sorry. That was so rude...
N-No...
That boy is an orphan of the war.
Because of that, whenever he sees soldiers...
Noeru-chan...
It's okay. It's true; we are soldiers.
So...
Noeru-chan.
Right. We are soldiers.
When I was commissioned, I repeated the Oath of Paradores, and I thought I understood it...
What am I saying?
I understood it from the beginning, didn't I?
I shouldn't hesitate at this point.
Right. I must be prepared by getting better.
If there is no signal horn, it will bother the people.
We can see it now.
Is that the glass factory?
That's so great, Noeru-chan!
I've never seen a building that big until now!
This one isn't good either? So the problem is the aberration?
I'm sure the refractive index is correct...
I-I am Sorami Kanata, a recruit. Nice to meet you.
Then, I...
So, how was the timing before the error occured?
There is almost no change in seek time.
The distortion at the edge of the image sensor is a little smaller than the last time...
Excuse me.
When the boss is working, he won't notice anything else.
But, Karl-oyajisan is a great guy.
He is one of only five people in the nation with the Meister title. He is a great craftsman.
He won an important competition, and even presented his work to the Grand Duke.
Maria, if you have time to chat, then go ahead and work.
Yes! I'm sorry, boss.
I don't deserve to be called "Meister" at all.
I don't have any idea of how to fix this.
What is that?
The lens for Takemicaduchi's optical sensor.
That's the original copy.
In order to repair Takemicaduchi, two identical lens are needed, so I asked him to make copies of it.
But, it hasn't been going well.
But, they're so beautiful!
Besides silicon dioxide, which is the lens' main component, we still need to mix it with thorium oxide and magnesium oxide.
With those, we can do chromatic aberration and surrounding aberration. In other words, correct the distorted image.
But, we don't know the ratio.
Because this is a magic product from the old time.
I thought glass was just beautiful, but it's complicated.
Because high-quality silicates can be collected in Seize, there are a lot of small studios focusing on handicrafts.
This factory used to be one of those studios too.
But, as the war became tougher, glass products for the military became more important
and this factory expanded during the war.
Kanata, I love machines.
But, machines can also hurt people.
Takemicaduchi must have killed a lot of people in the past.
I think that a machine that killed people in the past must be scary.
But the scary ones are not the machines. It's the people that used them, right?
Because, because, like this horn. When I am blowing it, it's that bad.
But when Rio-senpai blows the horn, it sings really beautifully.
Tanks must be the same, right?
And a few days ago, Rio-senpai let me listen to Takemicaduchi's song.
It can sing so beautifully.
Takemicaduchi must have been a good tank.
Right. This time, let's...
Noeru-chan.
Let her sleep.
She must have stayed up all night again.
Noeru-chan is working really hard to repair Takemicaduchi.
I know.
This girl is a hardcore artisan.
Otherwise, I wouldn't even accept such a job of making something so troublesome.
Here you are. Put this on her.
Thank you very much!
By the way, you went to the Windmill, right?
Is Naomi-san alright?
Yes. She said your boss is absolutely romantic.
It seems so. That's good right, boss.
Shut up! Go do your work immediately!
Ah! You are angry!
Work, work...
But, was the technology of the past that great?
Right.
But, the boss has always said...
"No matter how great it was, it was still made by human beings!"
"We must be able to make it!"
You believe the same thing, right?
Yes...Even though I want to say that...
I see.
Right, Rio-san's horn is a lot different than yours.
I've been worrying all the time. How can I become like senpai?
I decided to practice hard.
See. My lips are so swollen.
But...
No matter how I blow, I can never blow out something that sounds like senpai's music.
Apparently, I don't have talent...
Girl.
Yes.
Talent is the worst excuse someone's ever come up with for quitting.
Give that to me.
Though I don't understand horns very well...
I know young people often fail here.
Girl, are you trying to force the sound to come out?
I didn't intend to make it into this kind of shape.
Glass tends to form into this shape.
Thank you very much, Karl!
Let it sound like what it wants to be!
Morning...
Yes.
It's like the sun is rising a little earlier just for her.
That girl is also hardcore. The sound is good.
Sound?
Glass is composed of different elements at different ratios. The slightest difference can change its sound.
Even though we can't hear the difference, someone with a strong auditory sense should be able to perceive it.
Let Kanata help me find the sample with the closest sound.
In this way, probably...
Here, listen to its sound for us, girl.
Yes!
Noeru-chan, it's changed a lot since you started here.
Really?
Yes!
You did it! You did it, Noeru-chan!
Thanks.
This is the first time I've seen Noeru smile.
Mountain Hiking - The End of the World
Next Time :
Mountain Hiking
The End of the World
This program is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to people, parties, or situations is purely coincidental.