So Ra No Wo To
I'll have you practice with only
the mouthpiece for a while.
Any problem with that?
No! But, umm...
I want to be able to play songs like you...
I won't make it easy for you.
I'm ready for anything!
It's breakfast time.
The mess hall is over there.
Get going.
Right!
It's rough and ragged.
Nice to meet you.
Good morning!
You suck!
First Battle -
A Chair Story
Actually, we prepared it to
welcome you last night.
A little treat for you.
Thank you!
Oh, Rio.
Did you bring in the fish
I was drying upstairs?
No, not me.
That's odd...
Come on, Noël.
You can sleep after breakfast!
I'll do my best...
That's not doing your best.
I'm doing my best...
That's Rio-sempai's...
Sit down.
Breakfast will get cold.
Let me reintroduce you to
everyone in the 1121 Platoon.
First, the captain.
Lieutenant Filicia Heidemann.
I'm a tank commander.
Let's have fun while you're here!
Nice to meet you.
This is...
Hey, Noël.
Noël Kannagi...
Corporal Kannagi.
Pilot.
She's our mechanic, too.
Nice to meet you.
And finally...
Private Kureha Suminoya.
I'm the gunner.
Listen.
I'm younger than you, but I've been here
longer, so you'd better do as I-
She collapsed.
Thank you for everything, Noël-chan.
OK, let's get to breakfast.
But...
Enough!
All right! Then let's eat.
Let's eat.
I'm so happy...
I cut the bacon myself.
Eat all you want.
OK!
Soldiers and trumpeters
both need stamina.
Eat a lot and grow strong.
I'll do my best.
Kureha.
Y-Yes?
Once breakfast is over,
show her around the base.
Roger.
Attention!
Actually, I'm really busy,
but it was an order,
so I'm showing you around
because I have to!
R-Right. Thank you, Kureha-san.
Don't be so informal, Private Sorami!
I'm sorry!
Uh, Private Suminoya-dono.
Fine.
Then first, face the platoon and national flags...
Salute!
The 1121 Platoon presently
consists of five members:
A lieutenant, a sergeant, a corporal,
and two privates. Five in total.
Yes, Private Suminoya-dono.
That's the absolute minimum
required for a platoon. So...
That means we're all elites.
Understood!
Our platoon has been given
the following armaments:
One tank,
one heavy machine gun,
two light machine guns,
four rifles,
five handguns.
Using these, our mission is to defend the
national border around Seize, Trois.
Um...
P-Private Suminoya-dono!
I have a question!
Very well.
Permission to speak granted, Private Sorami.
If, uh... If my memory is correct,
beyond Seize is...
Correct. Beyond the mountains
is a no man's land.
But the borders of Helvetia only extend this far,
so this is a national border!
The front lines!
An important base!
So we always keep watch.
The five of us,
throughout the night.
Sleeping during watch is
absolutely forbidden.
This is the only hotline in the city
that's connected to the Capitol.
Which means...
If it rings, something big
is about to happen.
If it does, everyone's woken up
and put on alert.
Got it?
Yes, Private Suminoya-dono!
The second floor contains the captain's
quarters and the briefing room.
Under normal circumstances, entry is...
Well, it's perfectly all right.
But make sure you knock first!
This is the latrine.
Bath drawing and cleaning duties
are assigned by rotation. And...
Bathing is done in order
of rank, right?
No.
It's more fun if we all
bathe together.
Captain!
What are you doing?
Cleaning the bathroom.
But it's Noël's turn!
But she seemed so tired.
You'll set a bad example
for the rookie!
I'll do it later.
You just go sit somewhere and
act captain-ish for a while!
OK, take a good look!
This is the 1121st's
main battle tank.
Vector-Type Zero Autonomous
Tank Walker, the Takemikazuchi.
It's much bigger than the one
at the training grounds!
This is one of the so-called
zero-generation tanks.
It's a relic from the past.
There are fewer than ten left in the country.
I've heard of them.
They're supposed to be really amazing.
But its legs...
It's undergoing repair.
There aren't enough parts.
O-OK, so there's no manual either,
and we can't even find most of the parts.
But Noël will take care
of it somehow, OK?
Don't you dare call it useless!
I'm sure someday it will...
Don't make fun of us...
I know we're lax.
We're lax as heck.
They call us the useless Seize squad
or say we're just for decoration.
We're a pink squad,
yet we don't even have a working tank.
But...!
Kureha-chan.
That's it for your tour!
Dismissed!
Sounds like they're getting along.
Are they?
Just like we did, when we met.
You're right.
But it's a bit of a problem.
After I sent you after Kana-chan last night...
Captain, why is she communications?
You said the new recruit was going
to be a loader or a pilot!
It's not up to us.
Command sent her.
In the army, you don't always
get what you want.
But...!
There, there. It's all right.
Rio will take care of you, too,
just as she always has.
And of course, so will I.
She's got pretty good intuition,
so she may have realized something.
You think?
We have to do something.
I saw it.
Saw what?
A ghost?
Yeah.
No way.
You were just tired
and seeing things.
I thought so.
What do you mean,
you thought so?
I saw it, too.
The ghost.
It was in the barracks, right?
Yeah.
Don't encourage her!
But there's nothing special
about ghosts, right?
Stop it, I said!
And you, too, Noël!
You're an engineer.
Go investigate like one and then report back!
No.
Why?
Scared.
What are you saying?!
There are no ghosts!
There aren't! There aren't!
I agree with you.
Yeah.
Yes. There are no ghosts.
There aren't!
Not at all!
Not a chance!
All right!
Give the place a thorough investigation.
Blow your trumpet if you
encounter the enemy.
We'll send reinforcements!
Why?
Um, Private-dono...
What is it, Kana... Private!
This is kinda fun, isn't it?
The lightning sounds like
a marching beat.
This is a mission!
It's not a game.
Listen, Kana... Private Sorami!
You're on point.
I'll back you up.
Right!
Advance!
This place has stayed the way
it was before it was a fort.
What was it before?
How am I supposed to know?
Get going!
OK.
Ideographs.
I wonder what it says.
You can't read it, so put it down.
It'd be wonderful
if I could read it.
It's probably some
junk from long ago.
Let's get going.
You're not scared?
Nope.
Idiot!
But ghosts protect us, right?
What?
In the village where I was born, we had an annual
festival to celebrate and thank the ghosts.
Where in the middle of nowhere
were you born?
You see, ghosts possess people, drink their blood,
move corpses, and lots of nasty stuff like that.
That was close.
Sometimes rats carry
bad diseases...
What?
So, you are scared...
Is it gone?
I think so.
Hey, Kureha.
Private-dono.
I was thinking...
Maybe this was a school.
What?
There's no school this size,
even in the Capitol.
But there used to be a lot
more people, right?
So I'm sure, in this school,
there were a bunch of kids our age.
They all studied together...
What? What?
What!
I'm sure they taught music here!
Outside the army?
Look!
It hasn't changed.
I can't read the words, but...
D-sharp.
The sounds don't change...
What are you standing there for?
Wh-What?!
Hey, Kureha-chan!
It's wonderful, isn't it?
What is?
All of it!
Huh?
The town of Seize, this building,
everyone in our platoon... They're all...!
We're just a useless troop
in the middle of nowhere.
Our tank doesn't work,
and they forget to supply
us a lot of the time.
We never get any real missions.
We're all so lax...
But you love it, don't you?
What? What? What?!
I-I-It's here!
Wait, Kureha!
Kanata!
Amazing.
Of course it is!
I'm the gunner of the 1121st,
and it's a wonderful place,
and I love it more than anything!
So that's our ghost, huh?
How do you mistake
this for a ghost?
Hey, you.
You look a lot like that
thief from yesterday.
Why, you... You're tonight's dinner!
You mustn't frighten her
when she's hurt, Rio.
But...
I'm sure she has no place else to go.
And what's our symbol?
It wouldn't be right to cook her.
Isn't that right, Shuko-chan?
She named it?
But I think it's wonderful.
Yesterday, you almost died,
thanks to this thing.
But today, thanks to it, I was able
to have a great adventure!
Right, Kureha-chan?
What are you talking about?
You couldn't even classify that
as a little adventure!
Sheesh. I guess majority rule wins here.
No.
Captain's orders.
But next time you steal food,
you'll be punished.
Got it?
That was Rio this morning, wasn't it?
We'd start getting complaints from the
town if Kanata did it every day.
I'm sorry.
That's your seat.
Kureha-chan?
I just happened to find
another seat like it.
I didn't do it special for you.
Thank you!
Hey!
Stop it!
What are you two doing?
It's dangerous!
Breakfast...
A Day with the Squad - Rio Runs
Next time:
A Day with the Squad.
Rio Runs.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.