Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
It's the day to gorge on chicken and cake!
You're acting strange...
Huh?
...the both of you.
You are wonderful, Miss Yoko.
Cat paws are amazing!
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
Mommy, that's a pretty Christmas tree!
It is!
It's finally the season, huh?
Yes, it is.
The season for my heating bill to be costly.
That wasn't what I meant...
It has gotten pretty cold. I couldn't
get out of bed this morning.
That's it!
Huh?
I can just wrap myself in blankets when
I am home. Then, I can save on heating!
I see...
Miss Yoko!
Ah!
I will buy a heater for you!
Excuse me...
Oh, apologies. Here you go.
Miss Yoko! Huh?
Anyway, I wanted to say that
the Christmas season is here!
Oh, I see.
Christmas is an important day!
It's the day to gorge on chicken and cake!
That's not what Christmas is for.
Then what else is it for, here in Japan?
I guess it has become a day
for chicken and cake here.
Hey, let's have a party! Come on!
My, what a wonderful idea.
All right! I'll gorge on chicken and cake!
I told you, that is not what Christmas is for...
I'm excited for the party.
"A Day to Gorge on Chicken and Cake"
Miss Yoko!
Oh, Futaba.
Morning!
Is Hayama at school already?
Yup, she had some class rep duties.
She sounds busy.
Such a good student. She's great at
looking good in front of teachers, too.
Oh yeah, about the Christmas party,
I'll be baking the cake, too.
My, how fantastic.
You'll host the party,
Hayama will bring snacks, and...
Were you talking about Christmas plans just now?
Yeah, the three of us are having a party.
I'll tell you something you might want to know.
Huh?
Christmas also happens to be...
...Teru's birthday!
Wha...
What?!
What's up with you two?
N-Nothing! Right, Miss Yoko?
Q-Quite right, Futaba!
Hayama's birthday is on Christmas.
That means...
A devil was born on a holy night?
Such contradictory occurrences!
It's fine if you're a fallen angel-- I mean,
it doesn't matter when you were born!
Quite right! All planned by God--
I mean, the Devil?
What are you both talking about?
You're acting strange...
Huh?
...the both of you.
Oh, yeah! Miss Yoko said she
had something to tell just me.
What? I said no such thing.
Come on!
Wait, F-Futaba!
I'm nervous, because I'm
thinking about it too much.
Me, too. What should we do on Christmas?
Hm... I know!
Let's throw a birthday party for Hayama,
but pretend it's a Christmas party.
Hm? What do you mean?
Let's surprise her by telling her it's a Christmas
party, but it'll actually be her birthday party.
Oh! We will set up a trap for her.
It's not supposed to be a trap...
Anyway, let's keep it a secret from Hayama.
Got it.
What are you doing, Sonobe?
Passing out Christmas cake flyers.
I told you before to stop
passing out flyers here.
That's too bad. If our sales go up,
I might give you a raise.
What?!
N-No! Go home, this instant!
Cake shops must be busy at this time of year.
That's right. We have cake orders and have
started making stollen. I have been helping.
What?! You're making cakes, too?
I help out measuring and
sprinkling things on top.
Yes, she takes twice as long as other people,
but it's helpful at this time of year.
Of course I am helpful. Who do you think I am?
You are wonderful, Miss Yoko.
Uh, what's with this conversation?
So, does that mean you'll
be working on Christmas?
I give you permission to take that day off.
What?
You have finally made friends.
For the sake of your friend's birthday party,
I am willing to work my fingers to the bone.
Sonobe...
Well, she's more useful than a cat's paw.
Of course I am!
Wait, what's with this conversation?
Wait just a minute!
Cat paws are amazing!
H-Hayama!
Why--
I'm curious. What do you two
have to say that I can't hear?
Sorry, we have been hiding something from you.
Sonobe!
Actually, I'm planning on making
bear and cat-shaped cakes.
What?!
Wow!
I kept it a secret, because
I wanted to surprise you.
You can keep as many of those
kinds of secrets as you want!
We're off the hook, somehow.
Sonobe got us out of this one.
I love Christmas. The streets
are buzzing with excitement.
And it's fun to pick out presents.
Which one is better?
Pink? The red one's good, too.
It took an hour to decide,
and I ended up getting both.
I splurged and invested all
of this month's allowance.
Yeah, that's the plan for that day.
It is the first time I am throwing
a birthday party for a friend.
Anyway, let's have a great Christmas.
It is Hayama's birthday.
What?! Hey, wait!
Nishiyama?
What did you say? What was
it about Hayama's birthday?
Oh, you overheard?
Hayama's birthday is on Christmas.
What?!
We're having a surprise birthday party
for her, so keep it a secret.
--Please do.
--I'll buy something for you.
Yay! I've been wanting the premium card game!
--I-I can't believe it.
--I'm excited.
Yeah!
Hm? Nishiyama?
What's wrong, Nishiyama?
Christmas...
Huh?
Christmas is...
Oh, you do like Christmas. This year--
I don't care...
What?
There's nothing to celebrate, anyway.
Hm? What's gotten into you? You love Christmas.
Let's have a Christmas party!
No. Maybe I'll just eat curry on Christmas.
No way! You're having a Christmas party with me!
Come on, get up! Let's go buy a cake.
"Closed for the day"
"Come back again tomorrow"
I'm leaving now.
Oh, wait, Teru!
Bring this with you. I made this
for you. I stewed it overnight!
Uh...
Have fun at the party.
"Hayama"
Hm, where should I put this?
Hurry! Hayama's coming soon!
She's here!
--Hello.
--Hayama!
Happy Birthda--
Oh, you scared me! I thought
you were going to shoot me.
Shoot you?!
You had a pretty intense
expression on your face just now!
"Happy Birthday Teru"
My sister told you, huh?
I didn't want you to feel like you had to
celebrate with me, so I didn't say anything.
Is that why you didn't tell us?
I usually celebrate along with Christmas anyway,
so I'm used to my birthday being secondary.
That's so sad.
Thanks, though. It's been years
since I've celebrated with friends.
Then, let's have some cake.
Thanks!
I helped, too! I measured
and sprinkled things on top.
Thanks, Miss Yoko!
Oh, I have something, too. My sister made this.
I will eat it!
Woah!
Don't force yourself.
M-Miss Yoko?
You can do it!
Miss Yoko?
Amazing. I feel like I could
run a whole marathon.
Miss Yoko!
Maybe she shouldn't have eaten it, huh?
Ugh.
Cheer up, now.
I can't stand that Christmas
was also Hayama's birthday.
Were you able to enjoy your Christmas?
Hayama?!
It was also the day I was
brought into this world!
Apologize! Apologize to Christmas!
But, why? The streets celebrate my advent.
--Apologize! Just, apologize!
--Hayama...
Apologize to Christmas!
It's the first snow of the winter...
...but it's piled up so much.
Unusual weather.
But the snow is really exhilarating.
We cannot open unless we clear
this snow away, though.
That's right.
How cold! My back aches, too.
How can you...
--Heave-ho, heave-ho.
--How can you make Miss Yoko shovel snow?!
Sonobe, you must have made it snow!
You're the first to accuse me of that.
It is still snowing.
It is.
I was just thinking, will the
snow stop people from coming?
Not necessarily. Blizzards and typhoons
exhilarate people and make them want to go out.
Is that what happens?
I'll have some!
See?
Futaba. You are having cake
on a snowy day like today?
Yup. When I saw the snow,
it gave me a craving for cake.
I see, one with white whipped cream?
Tiramisu, chocolate ganache,
and opera cake, please!
Has the snow around you melted?
Teru! It's snowing a lot! Let's go out!
No way.
What?! We got a nice blanket of snow.
It'd be a waste not to go out!
Staying warm indoors is the best on cold days.
Oh, come on. Just for
a little. It's really cool.
Woah, hey!
Ta-dah! I made a snow hut!
What?! You made this by yourself?
I didn't know it's possible to make one!
Isn't it amazing? It's warm
inside. Here, go inside.
I'll bring something to drink.
We can drink it inside.
It really is warm in here.
How strange. It's made out of
cold snow, but it's warm.
Teru?!
"1 New Message"
"Kou Hayama"
"Received Mail" "From: Kou Hayama"
"Subject: Help!!" "Teru's in trouble~~"
Oh, no! Kou said Teru got caught
in an avalanche in the garden!
In the garden?!
I knew I should've stayed in.
Teru! Let's play.
Teru! Let's play...
I told you...
I got an email saying that you're in trouble.
...use the doorbell.
The snow has not stopped.
Yeah, it might keep snowing
the rest of the year.
Miss Yoko, what are you doing for New Year's?
I have nothing planned.
Will you be on your own?
Yes.
That won't do! You cannot spend it alone!
I have nobody to spend it with.
Why don't the three of you spend it together?
Huh?
That is, of course, if Hayama
and Futaba agree to it.
I'm up for it.
Me, too. It's lonely spending
New Year's by yourself.
Thank you both!
If that's the case, you should
have a pajama party.
Paja-- What?
Girls are beings that have pajama parties.
At a recent conference, it was shown that
more than an eighty percent have
a pajama party by graduation.
What conference was that?
You will remain in the other twenty percent.
What? I am the daughter of the Nishikawa family!
I will execute a pajama party splendidly.
Does that sound good?
Yeah.
Well, yes.
Then, just like our Christmas party the
other day, we will cook and have cake--
Oh, pajama parties are a little different.
We just relax in bed talking
about things in our pajamas.
What? That is a party?
Do you have enough blankets
for us at your place?
Well, er...
So, what are we supposed to do?
People usually talk about
people they like, right?
Then, let us begin.
I love rice! Paired with fried
cod roe, I can eat it forever!
I love cats! And dogs!
I can't decide between them!
Pajama... party...
Oh, I forgot I made some snacks.
Oh, then I will make some tea.
Miss Yoko!
Are you oka--
This is not a pajama party. A real pajama
party has more squeals and giggles.
What are you trying to do, Sonobe?
I'm not trying to do anything. I just want Miss Yoko
to experience normal high school girl things.
What's that camcorder for?
To document the memories.
Jeez.
Oh, my.
Well, I'm glad that she will not spend
her New Year's alone, at least.
Good morning, Hayama.
You mean...
...Happy New Year.
Oh. Happy New Year.
We got worked up and
fell asleep without realizing.
Yes, we did.
Food's almost ready.
Mom!
Mother!
There, there. We'll eat soon.
All right! Let's pound some mochi.
Pound mochi?!
Er...
What's this?
Oh, it's a mochi pounding machine.
"Off" "Steam" "Pound"
You said "pound mochi," so I thought
we'd be using a mortar and pestle.
As did I...
I asked for it for my birthday!
Wow!
Let's eat it now!
After a pajama party, the high school girls
eat mochi. What a rare event.
--Why do you have the camcorder out again?!
--Uh-oh.
Yum! It's so fresh.
Yes, it is delicious.
Yeah!
Soy bean flour, spicy, pan-fried with soy sauce,
edamame paste, fermented soy bean, or walnut!
How many should we each have?
What?
How many each?
Mochi is a must-have on New Year's!
Eat as much as you want!
What?
We're not competing in a big-eater contest!
H-Hey!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is
so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
An event in February? That must be--
Yes, the Festival of Broken Needles!
An event where a memorial service is held for broken needles.
"Mainly in the Kanto region"
It's an event geared towards women.
Valenti--
Or the Bean Throwing Festival!
"Next time: A Day to Gorge on Chocolate"