Throughout Kyoto, the pants and underwear of males went missing and everybody ran around in confusion.
"Land submarine, to the Women's bath"
"~Bed Chamber Investigation Team's rose colored search~"
I, of course, haven't taken a single step out of my home.
Because it's awkward, right?
There's no way I'd do such a thing.
No!
There aren't any pants or underwear left.
Just what exactly is going on?
Whilst I sleep, my pants and underwear that I'm wearing disappear.
I can't leave the room like this.
The man with the hobby of taking people's pants is currently bedridden.
I'll drop by as a visitor.
Couldn't find them.
Gross...
It's over. I've searched all over Rakuyou, but there's no pants, and not a single pair of underwear to be found.
Hey, you.
Your underclassmen is Akashi-san, right?
Know her address?
I have a bit of business with her.
Hey now, it's not like you won't be compensated.
O-ouch...
Who are you guys?!
Nobody suspicious, don't worry.
We just want to know the address of Akashi-san.
Who would tell the address of a female underclassman after being kidnapped?!
Hey, don't be like that.
What is this?
Or rather, aren't you leaving out too much in your explanation?
I wouldn't give out the address of a maiden.
You're a man, right?
She's so innocent, we...
Anyway, this submarine will get to her place unnoticed, and then it's possible to leave at once.
And then naturally...
Are you a pervert? That's a crime!
As I thought, it's better if you don't know.
So you know then?
I don't know, really.
At last, Rihaku-shi fell ill and we were able to put this to good use.
Until now...
I've burned all the pants and underwear.
They don't wear underwear in Scotland, nor pants.
Since ancient Japan, it's been kimono or loincloth.
Originally, a man's radiator, so to speak, not having a regional function to keep under wraps is outrageous.
Then, I found an interesting book.
Creating a scrubbing brush by mixing white fiber and fern together results in something called Van der Waals interaction.
Rather, it was written matter drives into the back of primitive matter.
That's how I found this blueprint.
A quick buy at the used book market?
You can only find good books at the start of the market.
God will be angry.
For some reason, what's written in this book cannot be remembered.
There appears to be contrivances to prevent transcription.
It cannot be photocopied and pictures cannot be taken. It had to be built while keeping an eye on it.
I see, you've made up your mind.
I will create a breezy "free hanging" world!
That's an interesting and superfluous story.
It's no good, I've contracted some kind of virus after handling his underwear.
The man who claimed he wouldn't change his underwear until he reunited with the apple girl?
It was an inevitable dilemma I tried to avoid but after we had taken them, he was able to meet with her.
I was able to grant his wish.
That's a convenient way of thinking.
If the energy of his distress devised a mysterious energy,
it wouldn't be strange, but...
Now, about the submarine?
It'd be great if the Bed Chamber Investigation Team members weren't riding it around,
but they're so bothersome about putting it to "good use."
Please take care of yourself.
"Get well soon"
Was it your group who stole the pants and underwear? Perverts!
Don't say strange things, that's something Rihaku-shi made happen.
That's something I have no interest in.
Right? So Akashi-san's address!
Even with us, Akashi-san would not tell her address..
She's probably been targeted by stalkers like you before.
Akashi-san has been spotted with the sonar!
Oh, we did it?
We won't let her go this time.
Hey, stop this!
We don't need you anymore!
Akashi-san!
Hurry!
Hey, she's not here!
She's near by.
Where? Where's she hiding?
Where?! Where is she?!
What happened?
A harpoon...
Bed Chamber Investigation Team?
A club of men with the interest of collecting erotic art and secret treasures.
Can't we lure them?
Akashi-kun and Hanuki will go to Sakura Yu at eight.
We'll go too.
"To master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu to work up a sweat."
"Sakura Yu"
Welco-
Men are that way.
We have important business. It's a crime.
There's no greater crime than men going into the women's bath.
What do we do? It's not like I don't understand, but...
I can get in the women's bath, because I'm still small.
You're just going to grow soon anyway.
To think you didn't call me to a public bath.
You'll need my help.
It looks more like the women's bath is a need to you.
It's because you like taking it off.
Give back the used book.
It's necessary for used books to have a proper encounter.
Okay.
What's this about?
Rihaku-shi got a hold of a used book with a secret technique and angered God.
God?
The God of the used books market.
Men go that way.
Hanuki! Call us anytime.
Alright.
Well, how are my muscles?
The setting sun!
Thanks.
Let's get in.
Ah, moth.
Moth?!
It's here.
Wait till it gets into the bathtub.
Hanuki-san!
Alright.
It's too much.
Hold on.
"Electric bath"
Perverts!
You alright Hanuki?
Akashi-san! Aren't we able to do anything?
Clearing one's mind of all mundane thoughts makes walls like curtains.
Let's go.
It was amazing, it was a single towel showdown with Hanuki.
Still can't see, even after slowing down the video.
Akashi-san was completely naked.
It's unbelievable.
Kaori-san was so cool.
Thanks to Jougasaki, their life was forfeit.
We sure cleaned them up.
Hmm, it's unbelievable.