I ran.
I couldn't move!
The past will follow you,
wherever you go.
Why?
The Slasher attacked me.
So, yeah. Banzai!
Hurry!
Don't tell me you want
to join the Dollars...
No way!
You can't run from your past.
Don't!
A New King
Will Arise
A great man once said that the world is a myth.
30 Minutes 100 Yen
Internet, Karaoke, Ping-Pong, Billiards
I think he said it, anyway.
Even if he didn't,
I'm sure someone else said something similar.
Russian Sushi
Welcome!
How ya been?
Thanks for coming!
It's cheap!
I give you discount, President Kadota.
Who's a president?
Five of your cheapest nigiri.
Right.
So what do you want,
head of the Yellow Scarves?
To us, the realm of fiction
is as important as reality.
The two are equal.
So it's not that we dislike reality.
You'd understand if I said that the head of the
Yellow Scarves wanted to talk to the Dollars?
Fine.
Just so we're clear,
we don't know many details,
and the Slasher's taken out some of us, too.
Honestly, we'd be happy if you could
clear up this misunderstanding.
That's...
Drink tea?
Catechin's good for you.
Hot!
It's OK, President Kadota.
Still your heart, and even flame will feel cold.
Don't get mad.
It's just hot.
You don't really know what
that means, do you?
I'm amazed you can hold a teacup that hot.
You guys may be the only ones thinking that.
The Dollars have no vertical or
horizontal connections.
So there could be a group of them doing
the slashings, and you just don't know it.
And if they attack other members of
their gang, they won't be suspected.
I see.
Makes sense, I guess.
So why do it?
Why would a group,
uninterested in money and fame,
try to use the Slasher attacks
to destroy the Yellow Scarves?
I wish I knew.
It might be a personal vendetta.
A personal vendetta?
Never heard of the Dollars fighting
with the Yellow Scarves.
Not the Dollars.
Blue Square.
Kida...
I won't forget what they did to us.
After what happened,
things calmed for the moment,
but that doesn't mean people have forgotten.
That's what I think.
That's why you came to me?
You would know, right?
Tell me who the leader of the Dollars is.
And if you can, how many of your
old Blue Square friends are-
Oh, man. Kida-kun...
You can't mistake reality for your delusions.
Blue Square never existed.
Isn't that for the best?
Saki... Saki was attacked by people who don't exist,
and she's still in the hospital-
That's right.
Your ex was done in by a
group that doesn't exist.
What's wrong with that?
Karisawa-san, I'm going to lose my temper!
You've already lost it.
And Yumacchi lost his first.
So you're even.
Just like you're mad over
what happened to her,
some people are mad over what
you're saying about the Dollars.
Given that, if you can't call it even,
then you shouldn't come talk to us.
Not that we're blameless in the matter,
but if you're going to bring
up the past, when it was
Dotachin who saved her and
you who ran away...
Then we'll just treat the whole thing
like a delusion that never happened.
If reality and fiction are equal, then any reality
you don't need can just be called delusion.
That's how we do things.
You're wrong, Karisawa-san.
I'm wrong?
Even if there was a Blue Square,
Blue Square were the first ones to get the
crap kicked out of them in that episode.
But for some reason, they're getting
treated like the only bad guys here.
That's why I'm complaining.
I get it!
I'm embarrassed!
I'm so embarrassed!
I'm sorry.
No, no.
We're the ones who should apologize.
We do feel bad about what
happened with Saki-chan.
No, I should be thanking you.
You've got every right to hate us.
We did all that to a middle school kid.
But Kadota-san, you didn't do anything...
No matter how much you try to escape it,
you can't get away from what you were part of.
But let me make this perfectly clear.
I don't know who the boss is, and I ain't looking.
And one more time, the Dollars have
nothing to do with the Slasher
and no reason to pick a fight
with the Yellow Scarves.
I see.
There was one person, though,
who said they knew who the boss is...
Who?
Wait.
What are you gonna do when you find out?
Even if you get the boss's name from him,
are you gonna go have a nice
cup of tea with him?
Or are you gonna get the Yellow Scarves
together and kidnap him?
I just want to find the Slasher.
Do the rest of the Yellow
Scarves agree with you?
If you had a firm hand on them like
you did, I could trust and help you.
But while you were gone, they changed.
Don't tell me you haven't noticed.
I still think they're my friends.
You don't know what you should do, do you?
Even if it was the Dollars,
doesn't it have nothing to do with you now?
You hated fights between groups.
That's why you...
Ran.
But sometimes, the reality you thought you'd
gotten rid of, returns in a warped way.
But this time, it's not just my
friends in the Yellow Scarves.
Someone very important to me, someone with nothing to
do with my past or the Yellow Scarves, was attacked.
That's what I can't forgive.
That's your...
Yes, it's my problem and mine alone!
I'm just using them...
Using the Yellow Scarves as an excuse.
If you know that much,
then I won't say anything.
I'll let that guy who knows the boss
and the boss himself decide.
But.
If you guys do decide that we're your enemy...
If we do... Then what?
You want a fight, you'll get one.
You're ready for that, right?
I hope you realize that,
if you're doing this for revenge,
it's on a totally different level than the
kiddy fights that kids your age have.
I...
You're scaring the other customers.
If you're gonna talk like that,
do it outside.
Here you go!
Five Kremlin nigiri, Mr. President!
You fight 'cause you're hungry.
Eat and be full!
Full of dreams!
A man's stomach is a factory of dreams!
Smile.
Thank you, Simon.
Um... L-Let's eat...
Dangerous.
That chef's too dangerous!
Hey, isn't this usually attempted murder?
I didn't know you could stab
a knife that deeply.
Russian Sushi
See you, Kida.
Don't do anything you'll regret.
Man, that chef's one scary mother...
A few inches either way,
and there'd have been a body.
Sorry, I thought he was cool.
Me, too!
I saw him in my mind,
fighting sambo style
with the hero of a cooking manga
who says not to play with knives!
Thus, in our minds, the chef became
a former Russian Armed Forces martial arts
instructor, who once fought the mafia!
He might just be pretending to
be a sushi chef as a cover!
He wouldn't open a restaurant as
conspicuous as Russian Sushi.
Horada... Horada...
What, Kadota-san? Is that some new spell?
Dotachin chanted Ho Rodaho Roda!
You think it's a root spell or a summon spell?
Might be lightning.
Remember what Kida was saying?
I already told you this,
but you can investigate the Dollars all you want,
and you won't find the Slasher.
I... No, we disagree.
What?
There's a rumor that the black biker
is part of the Dollars.
Why are we talking about the
black biker all of a sudden?
Last night, we saw something unbelievable.
I see...
So the Black Rider helped someone
with a katana escape,
which means they're working with the Slasher.
And...
A guy named Horada said he was attacked
by the black biker once before.
Horada?
Horada...
Oh, so that's why you were muttering "Horada".
What's the big deal about Horada?
It's nothing big...
But yeah, I may be wrong.
Wrong about what?
Just, I think I once knew a guy with that name.
If there's a group, within the Dollars,
working with the Black Rider,
and they're attacking the Yellow Scarves,
things would make sense.
Hey, Yumacchi, that doesn't
make any sense, does it?
How so?
The black biker took out the Slasher once.
Togusa-san rammed the guy with a car.
And then Shizu-chan smashed him with a door.
But there were fifty other attacks that night.
But those guys...
Either way, there'll be no more Slasher.
They picked a fight with Heiwajima Shizuo.
You can guess what happened.
But...
This is the phone number of
the guy who knows the boss.
Do what you want with it.
Orihara Izaya
Cheer up, would you?
Gloomy faces scare away customers.
Eat that and leave the place smiling.
Thank you.
Fighting is bad!
You're happy enough. Don't
take others' happiness.
Share it!
Hey, I just learned this.
"The merciless are failed catfish."
"Mercy benefits yourself, as
well as others," you mean.
Are you a catfish, Mr. Kida?
Hey, hey. Hey!
This is good.
Bored.
Having nothing to do is really boring.
Can I punch you?
Oh, shut up. I'm paying you.
What's this chocolate you
sent to the Awakusu-Kai?
It's a handgun. Why?
Six months ago, someone ran away with some
handguns from the Awakusu-Kai, right?
Right...
The one that horrible Dullahan was after, right?
Yeah...
Celty got most of them before
they could cause a problem,
but there's still one out there.
So...
Kida Masaomi
I thought you'd be calling soon.
A bluff?
Yes, of course.
OK.
I'll be there soon.
In the end, you yourself were the only
one who couldn't run from the past.
A great man once said that
the world is symbolic.
I think he said it, anyway.
Even if he didn't, I'm sure someone
else said something similar.
I haven't seen you make that
face in a long time.
It's the same one you used to make.
You were a middle schooler,
but it was an adult's face.
While I enjoy my remembrance of things past,
let me welcome you like so...
Welcome back.
I'm sure I know what you're here to ask.
I could've told you on the phone,
but it's a bit too serious for that.
I heard your friend got slashed?
Sonohara Anri-chan, wasn't it?
Looks like she's more important to you
than the kids in the Yellow Scarves.
Once upon a time, a young boy,
influenced by manga and TV shows,
made a group called the "Yellow Scarves."
The Yellow Scarves fought
another group, with a Blue Flag,
and were in great peril.
Then a brilliant strategist appeared...
Why are they all girls?
But it wasn't Shokatsu Koumei.
It was more like Sousou?
And then the other group, now in peril itself,
kidnapped the young boy's princess.
The boy tried to save her
but got scared halfway...
If the girl you like was caught up in a Yellow
Scarves gang war and badly hurt...
I see, I see... This is just like
what happened with Saki-chan.
I bet you're thinking this.
"I thought I loved Saki,
but I was too scared to save her."
Maybe it wasn't true love.
Maybe you were just after her body.
Maybe you didn't love her
as much as you thought.
Good lord, he goes on.
And as time passed,
you actually wanted that to be the case.
Which would mean that if you really loved a girl,
you could risk your life to protect her.
And now Sonohara Anri's your
chance to find out, right?
If you believe that, that's fine.
I want to do it anyway.
Get your revenge on the Slasher?
Or destroy the Dollars?
Depending on your answer,
it might be both.
I like that resolve.
Fine.
This is to keep you going forward.
So I'll tell you the facts, the truth,
and the unvarnished reality.
The three are normally different,
but they're sometimes the same.
By the way, how's Mikado-kun doing?
You introduced me to him this spring,
your friend, Ryuugamine Mikado-kun.
Why are you mentioning him now?
I was thinking he must be
really worried about this.
He's got nothing to do with this!
I haven't told him about the Yellow Scarves.
He's the same as always - quiet,
but doing really well.
He seems like he's enjoying
every day of his life.
Are you jealous of his peaceful life?
This has nothing to do with him!
And if it did?
I see, I see...
Mikado-kun's doing well.
His friend's suffering so much, and he,
the cause of this suffering, is enjoying his life.
Wait a minute!
What do you mean, Izaya-san?
You know what I mean.
The head of the Dollars is your beloved
best friend, Ryuugamine Mikado-kun.
Though, you may be the only one of
you two who thinks you're friends.
Reality is always a pain.
I Don't Want to Die Yet!
My Engel's Coefficient
Tako no Ichiyaboshi
Fed up with it, we decided
to remake the world.
Make walls, divide things into trash
and things we care about,
leave what we loved inside and
kick the rest outside.
And when we tried it,
it really worked!
You can make a world out of nothing
but moe and tsundere and BL!
It was an amazing discovery!
That's the one good way to distinguish
between reality and fiction.
<Kanra> Did you hear?
The Dollars and Yellow Scarves
went at it again.
<Tanaka Tarou> Again?
<Setton> Scary.
<Tanaka Tarou> But it's just another
small-scale fight, right?
<Kanra> Actually, this time, they
attacked the Yellow Scarves.
<Setton> Wow, bold!
<Kanra> That Headless Rider, you know...
They say it teamed up with the Slasher
and attacked their secret base! LOL
<Setton> Ah...
<Kanra> What's wrong, Setton-san?
<Tanaka Tarou> No way.
I won't believe that, even from you, Kanra-san.
That's preposterous.
<Saika-san has joined the channel>
<Saika> What are you all talking about?
<Setton> An anime! LOL
<Kanra> No, we're not, Setton-san.
<Tanaka Tarou> It's this giant monster
movie that's coming out.
<Saika> Oh, I see.
<Kanra> Et tu, Tanaka Tarou-san?
<Setton> It's good!
I hear this one had the producers changed twice,
and they changed all the scriptwriters.
<Saika> I'll check it out.
<Kanra> By the way,
this is just a rumor.
<Tanaka Tarou> What?
I heard the general of the Yellow Scarves is gonna
challenge the boss of the Dollars to a showdown.
Really?
Masaomi!
Why are you going home without going to class?
Eh, you know...
You took yesterday off, too.
You look better.
Um, Kida-kun...
There you are!
Takeguchi?
Ryuugamine, did you tell someone
I was in the Dollars?
You, too, Kida?
What?
Didn't you hear about how they're
fighting the Yellow Scarves?
Someone was asking about me yesterday.
I didn't tell anyone.
Me, neither.
OK, thanks.
See you!
Bye.
I'll be going, too.
Go home with us.
Got something to do.
My hordes of female fans won't let me go...
Let them have their fun.
See ya!
Masaomi...
Listen, no picking fights with them!
Even if they provoke you,
don't do anything.
But General...
Don't give them any reason to come after us.
If the Slasher is part of the Dollars, get proof!
General, you said you were going to ask an acquaintance
about the Dollars' boss. Did you learn anything?
No.
Some are saying, after what happened two days ago,
they can't just sit back and take it.
If they go out of control...
I'll be ready if that happens.
I'll tell you why this is happening to you.
You don't have a color.
You thought that meant you were safe.
Idiot!
In the real world, no one will come
to save you without a color.
A group with no ties to each other...
Yeah, right!
It's just...
...a bunch of kids screwing
around on the internet!
We'll eliminate you from reality!
We,
the Yellow Scarves!
Sometimes, reality ends up like
something out of the 2D world.
Masaomi?
Takeguchi...
was hit by the Yellow Scarves.
Takeguchi-kun?
I'm going to see him in the hospital.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Everything
Covered in Fog
Why didn't I stop then?
What do I know about the Dollars?
If I stay like this, there'll be no
change in my everyday life.
But...
Next time:
Everything Covered in Fog.