You get such good grades
because you can read minds. I'm jealous.
I do that on my own!
Do you really?
Can you say with absolute certainty that you arrived at these answers yourself?
You don't think that
someone else's thoughts drifted into your head?
Maybe... But...
Lay off!
Don't pick on Kotoura just because you failed your finals!
Barely Avoided Failing
Class Rank #2
Class rank #1
Failed Most
Exams
Bound for
Remedial Classes
Plain Ol'
Good Grades
You don't get to spend summer vacation at my grandfather's house with me.
I'm sorry!
Please, don't go until my remedial classes are over!
TLC
Tobikage
Timer
Floris257
Editor
Chippo
K-time
Floris257
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Logo AFX : KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter
Floris257
Naruto-kun
QC
Robo731   Floris257
Encoder
Floris257
Summer Vacation!
Summer vacation has arrived.
I never cared about summer vacation before,
but I'm kind of excited for this summer.
Come on, Moritani-san. I was just kidding.
R-Really?
Yeah. You'd be lonely if you spent the summer by yourself, right?
Barfoura
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
You stink,
Barfoura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh~
I'm so sorry!
D-Don't worry about it...
Your grandfather's house
is where we went to get you not long ago, right?
That place was absolutely gorgeous!
Please don't get your hopes up too much.
There is a lot of nature with the sea and mountains around,
but there's not much to do...
The sea?! Sounds good to me!
Oh, ho. The sea, eh?
Now that finals are over,
I've gotta go buy a new swimsuit!
That sounds great! Let's go right now!
S-Swimsuit...
But are you sure it's okay for us to come along with you?
Oh, sure. I'd like to talk with you guys more this time,
so I really hope you'll come.
I see. We'd be glad to then.
Okay.
Swimsuit. Boobs. Butt. Swimsuit. Boobs. Butt.
Swimsuit. Boobs. Butt. Swimsuit. Boobs...
No perverts allowed.
I'm sorry! Please let me come!
Why are you giggling?
Did you see a girl in a swimsuit out there?!
We're still a long way from the beach.
How excited are you about seeing swimsuits, anyway?
But the swimsuit I'm most excited to see is yours, ya know.
What are you saying?
We're on a trip here.
Don't spend it reading. Have some fun with us.
I was having fun, actually...
Oh, yeah!
I went swimsuit shopping with the girls the other day,
and it looks like my size has changed...
You gained weight again?
What do you mean, "again"?!
I'm not getting fat! I'm growing!
Of course... Since it's four to a seat,
there's always one who gets left out...
Do you feel nothing when you see this?!
Take a better look!
Sto-o-op!
Look! Look! Look! Jiggle, jiggle! Look! Look!
Wasn't I alone before...?
Moritani-san.
Kotoura-san?
Want a chilled mandarin?
Yes, I do!
It's so cold! And sweet!
I've got candy, too.
It's delicious!
Why do you have to be like that?!
Sto-o-op!
Just look at this jiggle! Jiggle, jiggle!
Think I'll take a nap.
He should be coming to pick us up...
Hey! Nice of you to come!
You're late, Grandfather.
Sorry. Streets in Japan are so narrow...
Head Priest, I see you came as well.
Zenzou-san invited me along.
You've traveled a long way.
There's not much here, but make yourselves at home.
We appreciate it.
So, how's it going? Have you kissed her yet?
Only a matter of time, Grandfather!
Please, Grandfather!
And I believe you're a new face.
Y-Yes. I haven't introduced myself yet.
Nice to meet you. I'm Moritani Hiyori.
Ah, Moritani-san, eh?
Oh, yes... Not that it has much to do with anything,
but I hear the town you all live in is pretty dangerous.
Especially at night, where there was a random attack on the streets...
Yikes!
Come to think of it, wasn't there a martial arts dojo in that town?
I think it was called Mori... Mori... Ah, I've forgotten.
Getting old sucks.
I-I think he knows...
Don't pick on her too much.
It's okay, Moritani-san.
Kotoura-san!
Oh, we're here already?
Okay, everyone. Hurry on out.
Um... Grandfather, what is this place?
The head priest told me
that you kids are interested in psychic abilities. Correct?
Well, that's really just our president—
Of course! We're all enthusiastic members of the ESP Society!
Wait, does that mean...
Yes.
This building appears to be a hospital,
but in reality, it was a secret government lab
for the study of psychic abilities.
But then...
One day, an out-of-control
psychic ability destroyed the lab,
and everyone inside was...
I see. This certainly is perfect for the ESP Society.
Sounds interesting.
Uh, president, you don't mean...
L-Let's not! Okay?
You're such an open book.
Really, Grandfather, why did you bring us to a place like...
Huh?!
Hey! Grandfather!
You really came prepared, president.
As president of the ESP Society, it's only natural.
It feels like something could pop out at any moment.
I'm leaving! I wanna go home!
Kotoura-san... I-I can't breathe! Let go, would you?
You again?!
Seriously, you should let go, Kotoura-san.
Okay? Okay?
No! Don't abandon me!
Come on, Kotoura-san! Get off!
Yuriko, you do realize this isn't really a psychic research lab, right?
Of course I do.
What?!
Then, why are we exploring this place?!
Well, obviously, because it's funny to see Kotoura-chan freaking out so much.
Demon!
I figured as much.
B-But even if it's not a psychic research lab, it's still a hospital.
Don't you think there might be ghosts?
No way.
If you see any ghosts, it's just your mind playing tricks on you.
You believe in psychic abilities, but not in ghosts?
Well, I've never seen one.
But if there really are any lurking around here,
I wonder if the ghosts of any psychics will be among them.
I-I don't want to see them!
Don't worry. We've got a real psychic here.
All I can do is read minds!
What can I do against a ghost?!
I just heard some kind of voice!
This is an old building.
It was just the wind.
There's another voice!
It's saying "Hold on to me... Hold on to me..." in a perverted voice!
Relax. That's just Manabe-kun's thoughts.
A g-ghost!
In a swimsuit!
Relax. That's just that idiot's fantasy.
Oh, yeah!
How can you imagine things like that in a situation like this?!
Don't underestimate me!
I can fantasize about things like that in any situation!
I can't take any more!
Manabe-kun?
Wh-What is that thing?!
H-How should I know?!
It's a chupacabra.
That means "sucker of goat blood" in Spanish.
It's an unidentified mysterious animal, or UMA.
What do UMAs have to do with psychic abilities?!
There are more of them!
Now that's a psychic research lab for you!
It's got the Jersey Devil, Mothman, and even the Yeti!
I wish that "Oh, yeah" girl would show up, too!
"Oh, yeah!"
Welcome to Harukaland!
Harukaland?
This is the first time Haruka has brought friends home.
I put together this theme park to commemorate the occasion.
Look behind you!
TL Note: Sign on the wall means: ''Terror! Abandoned Hospital Do you have the guts to be admitted here...?''
Wasn't the hospital attraction fun?
I told him it was a bit much...
S-Stupid geezers...
Grandfather, you jerk!
Wait! Wait!
Mama, no!
Don't leave me!
Mama!
I should never have given birth to you.
Oh, yeah... I'm back at home...
Morning, Kotoura!
Manabe-kun... M-Morning.
You're up already? It's still early.
Yeah, you know, I always wake up really
early during summer vacation, for some reason.
Yay! I'm gonna go catch some beetles!
He's just like a little boy.
But man, your family's house is so huge!
I've been exploring all morning!
Totally, a little boy.
Sexy, sexy, sexy, sexy...
Found it!
The treasure has been found!
If you sneak into my room, I won't forgive you.
You pervert.
Gah! My manly dreams were leaking out again?!
Wait, is that where your room was?
This room is...
Wh-What are you doing?
Let's play, Kotoura!
Huh?
It's our first summer vacation together!
It'll go to waste if we don't enjoy ourselves to the fullest
Okay.
What should we do?
Wanna go visit Harukaland again?
Just forget about that theme park!
Yeah! The beach!
Took you long enough to get here.
Grandfather, what are you doing here?
Why shouldn't I be at the Kotoura family's private beach?
Yeah, but...
First a theme park, and now a private beach?
The rich are so...
Don't sweat the details.
Stop!
We were invited here.
It's only polite to enjoy ourselves.
Y-You're right.
Kotoura-san! Let's get in the water already!
Over here!
Here! Here!
Look at 'em jiggle!
Mine jiggle, too!
Senpai, it appears my psychic ability has awakened.
What a coincidence. Mine, too.
I can read Kotoura's mind.
Another coincidence. I can, too.
What do you think of my new swimsuit?
Come on, Manabe. Say something.
Okay. Try not to get sunburned.
I'll be resting over here.
I have sensitive skin...
There we go.
Jeez!
Don't you have anything else to say?!
Let's go, Moritani-san!
Yeah!
Well, at any rate...
Take that!
Ain't the beach great?!
Beaches are great.
Hey! You're still wearing your shirt!
That's improper, Haruka!
There, it's off!
Hey! Kotoura!
This feels nice.
Kotoura! Come play with me...
Hiss!
K-Kotoura-san?
Kotoura's acting like some feral cat. She won't play with me.
She's just being shy. Don't you think it's cute?
Better than a certain someone who doesn't react at all...
What should I do? At this rate...
I won't get to see Kotoura in her swimsuit.
I won't get to play with her.
She's probably picking up on your ulterior motives.
He's talking to the president about something.
Probably just raving about how jiggly her breasts are again...
Stupid Manabe-kun.
I'll have fun without you.
Huh?
President, are you hungry?
Yeah. Let's have lunch.
Hey, Kotoura-chan, come back!
Look how frantically she's waving...
What?
Kotoura!
She's caught in the current!
Manabe-kun, use the boat!
M-Manabe-kun...
Kotoura!
There you go!
M-Manabe-kun...
I was so scared!
I thought I'd never make it back!
N-No kidding! That's what you get for going off alone!
Yeah...
It's dangerous, so stay close to me.
Okay.
You guys are way too extreme.
All right, lunch is prepared.
I've been waiting for this!
After all that worrying, I'm even more hungry.
Grandfather, what do you mean lunch is prepared?
I called in a chef. Something wrong with that?
N-No, not really.
I'm going ahead, okay?
Kotoura...
Honestly, that was a perfect chance,
and you couldn't do a thing! Pathetic wimp!
I know! Next time, I swear!
I prepared a lunch...
But I have a feeling I'll never get to feed Manabe-kun one of my lunches.
Oh, did you make that lunch?
I'll have that.
M-Manabe-kun? But...
I'd rather have that.
Yummy! Your cooking is awesome, Kotoura!
They're having a much more extravagant meal over there...
You don't have to eat this.
I've been dying to eat one of Kotoura's homemade lunches!
It's good... So good!
What is it?
N-Nothing.
Yeah?
This is so good!
I'm glad I came to the beach.
It just isn't summer without fireworks.
Whoa! Don't point that at others, president!
And Muroto-senpai, you're the vice president, so stop her!
I love these.
Don't follow me!
I told you to stay away!
Are these meager fireworks really enough for you?
I had some really flashy ones prepared...
I appreciate the thought, but please, just go home!
I even had them specially made...
U-Um...
Manabe-kun, President Mifune,
Muroto-senpai, and Moritani-san...
I, um...
Thank you.
I never knew summer vacation could be so much fun.
Silly.
Summer vacation has only just begun.
Come on, Kotoura-chan. Join us.
I told you not to point that at others!
Sorry, but the black snakes are all mine.
Kotoura.
Yeah.
All right! I'm gonna enjoy this summer vacation for all it's worth!
Kotoura-chan's as clumsy as always...
Are you okay, Kotoura?
I'm fine!
J-Jiggly jiggle!
Just kidding.
Kotoura...
No! Don't give me that  consoling look!
It's okay, Kotoura! You're...
Silky smooth!
Shut up, you pervy perv!
Episode 7
In This World, I...