Kerry! Kerry!
Come on!
Jump! Jump!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Kerry!
Awesome, Kerry!
Nah...
That was nothing!
Shirley...
Shirley!
Kerry!
Were you waiting long?
Kerry, do you know the origin
of our island's name?
Nope.
Oh, Arimago is some kind of crab, right?
Right.
Long ago, people made offerings to
the sea gods here, on this island.
But one day, a little girl,
with no food for her sick mother,
stole from those offerings.
So the gods cursed her,
and turned her into a crab.
That's where the name comes from?
That's a terrible story.
You know...
The shrine where they worshipped those gods
is on top of this mountain right by your house.
That's why none of the villagers will go up there.
They think it's bad luck.
They're always warning that
if I go there too often,
I'll get cursed, just like that girl.
For real?
But everyone's always so nice to me.
Well, you don't seem like
an outsider anymore!
The villagers think of you
as my little brother.
Brother, huh?
You've adapted to life here pretty well.
You think so?
When you first got here,
everyone picked on you.
They said you had a funny name!
You—
You started it, Shirley!
You were the first one to call me Kerry.
Because it's hard to say your real name.
Kerry... Kerry...
It's Kiritsugu.
Kerrytoogoo!
Not even close.
Huh? Aw...
Okay.
Dad, is that a new one?
Yes, success number one hundred.
These flowers never wilt.
I've altered their flow of time.
They won't grow any further,
but they'll never die, either.
Wow...
The question is
if we can apply the same theory to human beings.
All done!
Shirley, you...
Look!
My first successful specimen!
Shirley's been learning by imitation,
while she helps me out.
She definitely grasps the basics of magic.
Sensei, you did practically everything...
I only jumped in at the very end.
But that's still awesome!
Hey, Dad...
Yes?
Can I try doing what Shirley did, too?
That's a good idea.
With some help, you'll definitely succeed!
Right, Sensei?
No.
You're not ready yet.
This isn't a game.
There are real risks.
In Shirley's case,
I decided that she'd amassed enough
knowledge and experience to try.
Father, why won't you understand?
Shirley...
Everyone misunderstands the sensei!
Listen, Shirley...
Please don't go back to that house.
Let's talk inside.
Dad should spend some time
with the villagers, too.
I dunno.
Father Simon and the others seems to have it out for him.
I'm always getting preached at.
They say if I keep working at that house,
I'll end up possessed by a demon.
I mean, he made me promise to keep this
with me at all times.
It's supposedly some kind
of mystical protection charm.
Shirley, aren't you at all scared of my dad?
Nope.
I realize that magical research
isn't exactly normal,
but all of Sensei's research and discoveries
are so remarkable, it really could make history.
I think he's amazing.
Um...
It's sharp and cuts really well.
See you tomorrow.
Shirley, is something wrong?
Keeping flowers in bloom forever...
It's such beautiful magic.
Hey, you did it, too.
At my level, flowers are my limit.
Sensei is so much further along.
His medicines could eliminate death itself.
I just...
I think about using his work to benefit humanity
so that they will finally understand him.
But he's given up on that.
Still, Kerry...
I know you can do it.
What?
You're his star pupil.
If it were going to be anyone, it'd be you.
Not me.
I'm not his pupil.
I'm only an assistant.
I only clean and help out.
I'm not his student or anything.
So I can't refute what Father Simon says about him,
because there's nothing I can say.
Kerry...
You're next in line, without doubt.
Everything he does, he sets up
for you to one day continue.
It's just too early.
Hey, come with me.
Kerry,
what do you want to be
when you grow up?
If you continue your father's work,
how will you use its results?
Someday, you'll have the power
to change the world.
In fact, I guarantee that you'll be able to.
I'm certain of that.
Well...
It's a secret.
Then I'll wait and see, with my own eyes,
what you do when you grow up.
Until then, I'll stay by your side.
Okay?
Wh-Whatever...
Knock it off...
Whee!
Morning, Dad.
Kiritsugu,
you didn't go into my workshop
yesterday, did you?
Huh?
No...
All right.
Kiritsugu, don't go to the village today.
Actually, don't leave the house.
What's going on?
Shirley's late.
Hey!
Have you guys seen Shirley?
Shirley?
What happened to you?
Kerry...
Shirley!
I...
I just wanted to s-show it.
Sensei's research...
But...
It...
It isn't working...
Kill me.
Use it, please...
You must kill me.
Do it now, before it's too late...
I'm begging you!
There's no time!
Do it, before I lose control!
Hurry!
It really was Shirley?
Kerry, for now, you stay put.
I'll go inform the village.
W-What is this?
Father Simon?
It seems I'm late.
H-Hey!
Who are you?
Shouldn't you be more concerned about yourself?
But if you don't get up,
you'll be one of them in no time.
What happened?
Who did this?
Setting the village on fire...
I'm guessing you've heard of
vampires, right, kiddo?
We call them Dead Apostles.
Dead Apostles?
They drink people's blood,
increasing their numbers.
By now, pretty much everyone
on the island is one.
So we're here to clean up the mess.
Actually, there are two separate groups
working to get the village under control.
One is the Holy Church's Executors.
They're zealots who believe
that they're justified
in slaughtering anyone who defies God.
Obviously, they'll show no
mercy to any Dead Apostles.
They'll kill anyone who they suspect has had their blood drunk.
Then there's the Mages Association,
which is a bit harder to explain.
They're more interested in discovering
who unleashed these loathsome creatures,
and keeping that knowledge for themselves.
"All to themselves" being their motto,
they'll kill anyone they believe to know the truth.
To cover it up, they will utterly
erase any evidence.
They're the ones who set the fire.
Which are you with?
I'm like a salesman who deals
with the Mages Association.
Now, kiddo...
I have a question for you.
I'm looking for a mage who's
been designated for sealing.
A mage...
Obviously, you have no idea what that means.
The first human to become a Dead Apostle here...
Let's say I'm looking for the medium that
changed them into a Dead Apostle.
Whatever caused the transformation.
The bad mage who made it should be hiding
somewhere on this island.
Do you know anything that might help?
Oh, Kiritsugu, you're safe.
Thank goodness.
I told you not to go to the village.
Dad, why are you researching Dead Apostles?
Kiritsugu, how do you...
Shirley used your magic on herself.
Oh...
Well, it's unfortunate.
But what's done is done.
Shirley inadvertently led me to the
answer earlier than anticipated.
Dad,
will you do the same thing to me someday?
Don't be ridiculous.
A Dead Apostle that can't suppress
its bloodlust is a failure.
The Emiya family research requires eternity.
The Root will remain forever out of reach,
so long as we have mortal flesh.
This experiment took a lot of time,
but it seems to have been a failure.
I'll have to take my theory
back to the drawing board.
Kiritsugu, we'll continue this later.
Right now, we must escape.
Can we still escape?
I hid a motorboat on the southern coast,
in case something like this happened.
Sorry, there isn't any time for you
to gather your things, Kiritsugu.
Come on.
I'll do it.
He's set up a barrier within the forest.
A really strong one.
Breaking it will take time.
However, I can get through.
I have to do it.
Kerry,
what do you want to be
when you grow up?
That barrier wasn't nearly as
tough as you made it sound.
Are you mad?
There was no guarantee you'd be in time.
If he'd gotten away,
he would've continued his
research somewhere else.
That's a poor reason for a son to kill his father.
You really are a good person.
I'll get you off the island.
After that, you must decide things for yourself.
Anything you want to take with you?
Nothing.
Episode 18:
Distant Memories
After fleeing the island,
I spent the next several years with
that woman, Natalia Kaminski.
That meant following the same path,
the path of the hunter.
Next Time:
Where Justice Dwells