Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
So I'm raising a pet dog in this one game right now.
It's just so cute that I start talking to it.
You know how when you talk to animals,
you just end up speaking to them in an affectionate tone, whether or not you try.
Even though it's just a game.
I know what you mean!
Gyopi-chan
When I talk to my goldfish,
I can't help but use baby talk.
I can understand talking to dogs or cats,
but talking to fish...
One must be really lonely to do something like that.
What was that!?
That's discrimination!
And what's with that patronizing look!?
Which reminds me,
I've always wondered,
but that command they use to make dogs stand,
"Chin-chin,"
I wonder what exactly does it mean?
Eh? U-Um...
W-Well, it would take quite a while if I went into the details,
but I am quite certain it was derived from a Chinese word.
Okay.
Everyone who just had an inappropriate thought...
...raise your hand.
2D has Substance
Observations on GuXXXM
Gun**m is ridiculously popular, even today.
Yeah, Daddy ***** it, too!
G***am has lots of variations, too.
Like V.
And W.
And X.
Yep, and I saw them all in real-time when they first aired!
One could say it was passion,
or rather, my duty as a fan!
In that case,
would you watch something like The Gu*dam Serial Murder Case...
...or Detective Gund*m, if they started airing?
As a Gun**m fan,
I suppose I have the **** to watch it, however,
**** is kind of...
But it's a kind of ***** you can't call by a letter of the alphabet.
And while we're on the subject of **ndam, it occurred to me,
while it doesn't seem like it, I'm already *** years older than *muro.
Boy, that's really *****.
And in 2 more years,
I'll be the same age as B****t-san!
I can't imagine it!
Well...
B****t-san is a pretty *** character, even in the Gun**m world.
Then again, so is Ha**n-sama...
Actually...
You're quite ***** for your age,
so I'm not too sure about using *** as a standard of comparison.
You could have at least said I look ***** for my age.
Nah.
You're so cute!
Our neighbors gave us something nice.
It's a souvenir from their vacation, apparently.
What is it?
A pot?
You grew up just how I wanted you to be!
Gosh, you're so cute!
It's hot, Dad.
More importantly, that was a dangerous statement.
Morning already...
I drank too much last night,
so I figured I'd be out till past noon...
I guess I'm younger than I thought.
"And now the morning news for Monday, July 2nd."
"Early this morning a man at a restaurant,
W-Wait...
Where's Sunday?
"Suddenly shouted out loud, 'This ramen is terrible!'"
What happened to my day off!?
I always tell myself that I'm going to study hard for my tests tonight,
but I end up getting so sleepy.
So I asked Onee-chan for some advice...
"You're not good with horror movies, right?"
"Maybe if you watched one,
it would keep you awake all night?"
"Seeing how you came crawling into my futon last time."
And so,
I didn't get sleepy after watching one.
I guess an older sister would know best.
But ever since then,
once it's night,
THUMP
even the slightest noise around the house makes me jump,
which makes it even harder to focus on studying.
And so I ended up not getting enough sleep...
I felt so sleepy during class.
But for someone who claims to dislike horror films,
you seem to watch them quite often.
It's not that I choose to watch them...
My mother's the same way...
"Hey, Miyuki."
"I rented this, so do you want to watch it together?"
"It's too scary to watch by myself."
It seems those who aren't good with horror movies,
tend to watch them more often, right?
Perhaps they want to be scared...
You're wrong, Yuki-chan!
In my case, I really can't stand them!
Iwasaki-san, do you know the answer to this one?
I worked on that problem for a while,
and I couldn't solve it,
so I was going to ask Miyuki-san.
I see!
We're really lucky to have Senpai around us to rely on in these situations.
That's what I was talking about with Iwasaki-san at school today.
Wait, what!?
She has that much faith in me!?
This girl is going to experience first hand how cruel this world can be!
Hey, Nee-san,
did you ever study for tests with Ki-neesan?
Nope.
It's a pretty common situation in games.
Get a girl and a guy who both like each other, and put them in the same room... how can they focus?
And when you can't focus anymore, you start fantasizing about stuff you like.
And your hidden side starts to show.
Onee-chan.
I need help with this part...
Oh, I'm kinda busy right now, so you should ask Yui-neesan.
Study, study...
D-Dirty trick!
I-I think it's because I went to a different school.
I don't remember learning this stuff.
I see...
I-It's painful!
Man, now I'm stuck, too...
Nee-san, do you understand this part?
Of course you don't!
If you don't expect an answer, don't ask!
Didn't you see what happened earlier?
Ah, geez!
Maybe I'll call Miyuki-san.
Might be a bother for her, though.
Well, it'd probably be a bother...
...since it's already late.
Why is it that...
...she never turns to her dad in these situations?
You can rely on me once in a while!
I'm going to fix you real good!
Izumi,
don't sleep in class.
How can you casually beat a child in this day and age...
...where laws are more strict and corporal punishment isn't allowed!
Not that I have a problem with it...
I guess you're right.
But I don't hit just anybody.
I choose my targets carefully, if you catch my drift.
Else I could get in trouble later on.
How can she just say stuff like that so brazenly?
Another amazing thing about her.
Besides, don't you think it's weird not to give a little beating here and there?
「 His life is the story of our era's most perfect man 」
Jean-Paul Sartre
John Lennon
「 Coolest man in the world 」
Che Guevara
「 Shoot, coward...
You are only going to kill a man 」
And that's it for today.
Miyuki-san, I'm sorry but...
...I didn't catch the names of these periods.
Miyuki-chan, show me how to do this one.
That's right...
All you guys say is, "Takara, Takara."
Why don't you ever ask your teacher questions?
Kuroi-sensei!
Oh! Izumi, what's up?
Well, I had a question...
What's this?
Go ahead, ask away! I won't refuse!
There's this rare item in a game I'm playing right now...
Eh, what?
Sensei?
No...
That's not what I meant...
It sure is sweltering after a typhoon.
We had quite a few instances of good weather after a typhoon.
Like they say, a storm of relatives!
That's a good one.
By the way, what was good?
Just for the record,
that was supposed to be a joke, right?
Um...
I wanted to ask you something, Onee-chan.
What's up, sounding so formal?
About this morning...
Did Kona-chan say something funny?
I couldn't tell what the joke was...
We always watch the news together,
yet why is she at the same level as Konata?
Notice for
Absent Resident
Why do you people always have such perfect timing...
"The pitcher has his eye on the runner on second."
How's the baseball game looking tonight?
At this rate, it'll probably go into extra innings.
Again!?
Geez!
I have to change the recording times on the VCR again!
Good grief...
Why didn't they just plan a larger time block for it in the first place?
Besides,
don't you think each play in pro baseball takes a lot longer than it should?
If all the players wanted to, I'm sure they could move at a brisker pace,
and then finish on time, don't you think?
Well...
Some fans like the game because of the slow pace,
and the players need to concentrate, too.
So, are you used to school life yet?
Yeah.
But there's so much homework-I'm overwhelmed.
I see.
Third-years focus on studying for entrance exams,
so they don't get much homework, right?
Konata...
You...
What is she talking about?
Man, it's hot!
Navel showing!
Konata!
How can you walk around dressed like that!?
What are you going to do if Yu-chan copies you?
But it's so hot lately.
You know,
it's kinda like that thing the Diet's doing.
Cool Biz?
Yeah, that's it!
No, that's something completely different.
What are you doing?
Eh?
Aren't you anxious to see if you've gotten any replies to your mail?
And while I was reading my book, I missed my stop.
As usual, your everyday clumsiness just adds to your cuteness.
Really?
Doesn't it just cause more trouble?
You just don't get it, do you?
It's the way she's embarrassed when she tries to fix her mess-ups that makes her moé.
It's totally cute when you have some kind of weakness like that.
What?
So at your work do you...
"Ah, I spilled it all over!"
"I'm so sorry, sir!"
...do stuff like that?
Kagami,
that looked kinda stupid.
What are you doing?
You're the one who brought this topic up!
Though I'm the one that reenacted it...
So what do you do?
Do you act clumsy to score points with the customer?
No, I don't do anything like that.
It might be a common stereotype,
but you'll get in trouble with the manager if you do stuff like that.
Really now?
I figured you'd be like, "It's so moé,"
and do it all the time.
You just don't get it, Kagami.
Certainly, klutzy girls may be cute and have the moé elements...
But in reality the damage they cause can get on people's nerves.
Even if you can just laugh it off in games.
You otaku can be pretty severe when it comes to judging others...
"For the person who gets a perfect score,
courtesy of Look JT*,
we have tickets for a one-month getaway in the tundra!"
You know, variety shows and quiz shows like these,
always give out a bunch of prizes.
"Now, let us begin the discovery!"
"I am currently at The World's Bellybutton."
"Ayers Rock!"
I'm sure that's how they get all their contestants.
And if they get a big-name celebrity on the show, the ratings shoot up.
"This week's mystery is located in magnificent Australia."
I suppose.
"Here you can find kangaroos, koalas, and other wild animals."
Though I'm not too sure.
But you know,
if they let the viewers participate and sent some prizes to them, too,
"This continent, separated long ago by tectonic movement,
wouldn't that boost the ratings even more?
has become a holy land isolated from foreign intrusion."
I see where you're going,
but that's a pretty direct way of appealing.
Good morning!
Yo!
I was playing a game yesterday when it suddenly occurred to me...
Who's our school idol?
What do you mean, school idol?
Like Miss Ryouou or something?
Yeah...
That's what you would normally think...
In games, it's the basics of the basics.
With personal bodyguards and such.
Another exhausting day at the office.
Man, that felt good!
I have to leave early tomorrow...
I better stay off the Internet tonight...
...and hit the sack.
Don't wanna be late.
I'm starting to prioritize my sleep...
Is it a sign I'm getting old?
Back when I was in school, I spent my sleep-time doing other stuff...
T-Tamura-san,
is something the matter?
You've been making a lot of faces...
Well, you know how when you're drawing...
...you tend to make the same faces as the characters?
Is that so?
So you were drawing.
I never knew that you drew manga, Tamura-san.
They're mainly doujin, though.
What kind of manga do you draw?
Um...
Normal stuff, like 4-koma...
Or a romance manga...
...between the characters in my favorite game.
So hard to answer...
The other day, I won 3,000 yen from a lottery I entered for fun.
I must have had good luck that morning.
Or at least that's what I thought...
Amazing!
But on my way to school, the tire on my bicycle burst so I had to pay for repairs.
And my lunch was ruined so I had to buy another one from a convenience store.
And the money vanished like it was never there in the first place.
My 3,000 yen...
Reality is harsher than fiction...
I suppose.
But you know...
I figured it might make a good story for my manga,
so perhaps it was okay...
She's tough!
An artist's drawing hand...
...is everything.
I must protect it, no matter the cost.
S-She's tough!
You really are skilled, Tamura-san.
Actually, I've been in a slump lately.
That's actually supposed to be scrapped.
Oh, but I think this is one of my better ones right now.
Objection
Of course...
The casual viewers aren't going to understand...
...the slight changes and the details that make a world of difference to the artist.
Of course, I knew that...
Crap!
What's wrong, Tamura-san?
My favorite mechanical pencil...
I was drawing yesterday and I left it on my desk at home.
Want to borrow mine?
No,
I'm just no good without it.
How can I put it... it just doesn't feel the same.
Of course...
Mechanical pencils are all the same, right?
I know that's true...
Of course, that's how people would react...
And I couldn't decide, so I was stuck there for over three hours.
What's wrong, Tamura-san?
H-How embarrassing...
What are they thinking, dressing like that in broad daylight?
A coat?
It's summer and yet they're dressed like that...
Aren't they hot?
I guess this is the pain that can only be experienced...
...by someone who understands...
Hold on.
I need to message a friend.
Welcome!
Sure is crowded.
I'll go write my name on the list.
So I stayed up late playing games with Onee-chan again.
Suzaku-sama!
Suzaku-sama, party of three!
Ah, they called us.
But Tamura-san, they called a different name.
At times like this,
you just want to put down the name of your favorite character.
It sort of makes you feel closer to that character... I guess.
Haruhi
Kyon
Yuki
Mikuru
Itsuki
Current Bowler :    Haruhi
Hm...
I guess you can find comrades anywhere in the world.
Thanks.
I wish I could be slender and tall like you, Iwasaki-san.
Fantasy
I admire you so much, Minami-chan...
That's why...
Yutaka...
Rely on the Nurse's Office
Reality
Kobayakawa-sama, you'll still grow...
Perhaps...
You'll grow even taller than me.
Taller than you?
Fantasy
Minami-chan!
Minami-chan...
No!
That goes against the natural world order, so no!
And that last one was clearly out of this world!
Calm down, girl!
Tamura-san, are you okay?
You look rather pale.
The truth is, today's the submission deadline for an upcoming event...
...and I just sent out the script I spent all night finishing...
Ah...
But I feel like I'm really shining...
When I look at all the hard work I put into something like this.
She's tough...
Tamura-san!
What's yaoi?
Which definition would you be looking for...
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
Believe it or not, Lucky Channel is already on it's 19th episode!
Looks like we're finally in the home stretch.
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
And I'm her assistant, Shiraishi Minoru!
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Net Darling!
That aside,
Da-Da Darling!
Akira-sama is certainly in a good mood today.
Nothing good at all about adult circumstances!
Did something good happen?
What do you think?
Eh...
N-Never mind...
Man, being on TV really puts a strain on your nerves.
The stress really builds up after nineteen episodes.
I wish I could just dip in a hot spring and ease some of this stress.
Maybe I'll win that prize they were talking about on the quiz show...
That means!
First, we have to start at the point where you appear in the quiz show, right?
Not good!
Oh yeah!
Vacations sure are nice!
I wish I could go on one, too!
Traveling to a place you've never been to...
...really makes you feel so much better.
Isn't it great?
Do you like to travel?
Of course I do!
I love to!
I've actually been to quite a few places!
I climbed Mt. Takao!
And I've been to Jougashima!
I'm definitely an outdoors type of guy!
So you like to travel...
Nothing calms your spirits more on days like these...
...than a nice hike through the great wilderness!
That sounds nice...
A hike through the great wilderness...
...must really calm the soul.
Right?
Getting away from the city...
And immersing yourself in the tranquility of nature...
It heals both the body and the soul!
Sounds good.
Nature might be nice.
Isn't nature great!?
You wanna go on a hike?
Seriously?
Can I?
Well, if I can, I'd love to!
All right!
Okay.
Minoru's Nature Hike is a go.
I-It's huge...
Take those with you.
I guess these are good to have...
Where...
Am I going with all of this...
Exactly...?
Mt. Fuji.
But I've already been to the mountains...
Sure.
It's not the mountain, but the forest.
Go to the forests of Fuji.
The forests, huh?
Who is...?
Oh, me...?
Yeah.
Uh...
What am I supposed to do when I get there?
Get me a bucket of water.
Water?
I want to drink some of that famous Fuji spring water...
...so go to the forest and get me some.
Eh!?
No way!
Don't they sell that stuff at convenience stores!?
But I want mine fresh!
I'm not going alone, right?
Alone...
Alone!?
Someone's coming along with me, right?
Don't worry, don't worry,
the director and the producer said they would sacrifice themselves and go with you.
Aren't you glad?
Oh, my savior!
Come on!
Stop wasting time!
Don't miss the deadline.
Wait!
Ah, we're already out of time!
Let me go!
Everyone!
Fine!
Next week I'm going to have a really special guest...
I'll do it myself!
Stop!
Please stop!
...here on Lucky Channel!
Look forward to it, okay?
Bye-bii.
Let go of me!
Did we really need to go through all this trouble to get rid of him?
Couldn't you have just-
Part of my body is hot! Hot!
This week, we would like you to enjoy the pleasant image of nature and two young women playing with bubbles.
Hello!
Shiraishi Minoru here!
Now, please listen to me!
How a Man Should Live!
Aitsu no you ni naritai na!
I wanna be like him.
Also, please feel free to turn off the sound.
Mae dake wo muite tsukisusume
Always looking ahead and moving forward.
Ichido kimetara doko made mo!
Once you've made up your mind, never stop.
Kuraitsuitara hanasanai!
Once you've grabbed on, never let go.
Kokoro mo karada mo supopon!
Body and soul are bare naked.
Kokoro mo karada mo
Body and soul are bare...
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star:
Nanako here.
Yui-chan here!
I've been thinking...
With summer,
we all get our hopes up for something to happen before it begins...
But before you know it, summer goes by and nothing happened, right?
Well, I guess nothing special really happens.
Besides, I doubt you're going to have a long relationship with some person you met by chance.
I'm not so sure about that...
Well, we've still got time.
So let's do our best, all right?
Yes!
So hard to answer...
「 How to Spend
Summer 」
Next time: "How To Spend Summer"
I'm available!