Going for a walk in the forest feels great!
Well, aren't you carefree!
We're here to find a clue to the princess.
We're here!
Indeed.
This is a collection of world-famous sculptures,
the Forest Sculpture Gallery!
The princess loved sculptures.
Maybe she came to see them in this world, too!
But...
whenever she looked at sculptures,
her eyes seemed so sad.
Anyway, we're gonna search this gallery together!
Right!
And perhaps...
we might find the fourth Royal Crystal.
Or so I feel.
Hi!
Regina!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Shock!
The Stolen Crystal!
Regina, why are you here?
Mana, listen!
I'll be a good girl this time!
All so we can be real friends!
It's fine for you to be friends,
but have you reflected on your actions from last time?
Last time?
You made a Selfish and hurt us all, remember?
Of course I reflected!
Really?
Totally!
Do you understand what it means to reflect on your actions?
Huh?
Nope!
Well, we can explain what that means later.
But Regina, you have to be friends with everyone, not just me.
Everyone?
Yeah, everyone!
I-I'll try!
Huh? Is she...
A bit different from before?
Yeah, you can do it!
Mana.
Makopi?
Don't tell her about our search for the princess or the Royal Crystals, okay?
S-Sure.
So, whatcha doin' here?
Well, uh, you see, um...
We came to see the sculptures, of course!
Right, right! Quite right indeed!
In that case,
there's a great sculpture over here!
Let's go see it!
W-Wait, Regina!
Stop!
What's wrong, Mana?
When you're walking,
it's best to walk together!
Aw, but I want to be alone with you!
You want to be friends with everyone, right?
But that ice cream I ate with you the other day was tasty.
Yeah, it tastes good with two,
but it'd taste even better with the five of us!
It'd be more fun, too!
I guess...
I know!
I really only want Mana, but I'll put up with them!
It's hard to get angry when she's that honest...
Are you all right?
Alice.
Yes, I'm fine.
It's calling me!
Makopi?
Makoto?
Makopi, what's up?
This statue...
looks just like the princess!
Princess?
Oh, pay no mind!
Yeah, it's nothing, really!
Ah, quite the lovely statue.
The Solitaire owner?!
Oh, hello there.
Ai too?
That's a funny hat!
And this lady is?
I'm Regina.
It's a lovely name.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Why is he here?
And right by the statue that resembles the princess, at that?
What are you here for, Mister?
This statue is a new addition, and I fell in love at first sight.
Or perhaps I should say that the statue fell for me...
He's a laugh and a half!
Hey, Regina!
Wait, do you know the model of this statue?
Huh?
Oh dear, look at the time!
I have an important business meeting to attend!
Take care of Ai, if you'd please!
Hey, wait!
He took his leave.
What was he gonna do about Ai if we weren't here?
Aiya, Ai!
Why are you crying?
Let me handle it!
At times like this...
You need this Lovies!
Yo! Checka Racka!
She's so cute asleep!
Just like Mana said.
Her smile was not a lie.
Mana, what do you think of this statue?
Well, it's a very beautiful person.
Yeah, I like it too!
Especially that jewel in her chest!
Hey, could that be a Royal Crystal?
What's that?
Well, it's...
It's a really royal looking crystal!
Hey, you're lying.
Lying's the first step towards a life of crime.
You seem to know that proverb well...
Well, Royal Crystals are very important things that we're searching for.
Then I'll give you a present!
Wait...
Here, Mana.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
Yeah, I figured.
Do you have any idea what you did?!
We're sorry!
We're extremely sorry!
Geez...
Hey, don't get so mad.
Sir...
You must be...
He's Mr. Hitomi, the artist behind the statue you broke!
We're sorry!
Don't worry.
It wasn't something little girls could break.
There must have been a crack in it somewhere.
But even I think it's strange.
I feel like it was never my work to begin with.
Huh?
When I picked that red stone up by the river,
I was struck by sudden inspiration.
It was like I made that statue by someone else's commands.
But this is just a piece of glass.
Regina!
Well, everything breaks someday.
That was the fate of this statue.
We're really very sorry!
What are you doing?
Cleaning up.
You don't have to.
He forgave you.
It's the thought that counts.
We can't put it back together,
but we can at least do this.
But I was the one who broke it.
You've got nothing to do with it.
What are you saying?
We're friends, remember?
Friends?
Because we're friends,
we want to stick together through the good times and the bad.
Well, when you're friends with someone who takes on other people's troubles as much as Mana,
expect a lot of bad.
Well, if you'd be so kind as to bear with me...
Oh well, I guess I'll hang in there.
I want it, too...
I want...
to be...
your friend!
What are you talking about?
You're already our friend.
What is this feeling?
My heart is beating out of my chest!
A Royal Crystal!
Regina, you okay?
This is a Royal Crystal!
Regina?
Those Royal Crystals...
all belong to me now.
Now hand them over.
You can't, Regina!
We told you before, they're very important—
I'm saying I want them!
Regina?
Why are you acting weird?
Not gonna?
Then I'll steal them from you!
How's the cleanup coming?
That sparkle!
I feel some more inspiration coming on!
Good timing.
I'll turn you into a splendid Selfish!
Selfishtatue!
Art is...
wreckage!
Let's go, girls!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor sculpture who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
My heart doesn't need to race.
I'll just defeat you Precures and take the Royal Crystals myself!
Sculpture!
Regina!
Wreckage!
Wreck! Wreck, wreeeeck!
Wreck, wreck... wreck!
The sculptures!
Wreckage!
Stop it!
Don't break any more of them!
Wreckage!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
It didn't work!
Heart!
Sword!
Take these!
Sword was turned into a statue?
How horrible!
Welcome to my collection!
The birth of a masterpiece!
Now, who will be my next work of art?
I'll take care of him!
Precure Diamond Shower!
It worked!
Art is...
wreckage!
The Diamond Shower didn't work?
Wreckage!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
The Rosetta Reflection, too?
Statue!
Rosetta! Diamond!
The birth of two masterpieces!
Girls...
That's my Selfish for you.
Regina, turn them all back to normal!
Sure.
But only if you give me all the Royal Crystals.
If you refuse,
I'll smash all of your precious friends to pieces!
Regina, what happened?
I thought you were getting alone with everyone today, not just me!
Back then, I was so happy that my heart skipped a beat!
Didn't yours?
What a load.
Do you listen to yourself?
Regina!
Well, since it looks like you don't care about saving your friends,
I'm done trying to cut you some lame deal.
Selfish!
Steal the Royal Crystals!
Wreckage!
Wreck, wreck, wreck!
Precure Heart Shoot!
What a moron.
Shoulda just handed them over.
Now, complete your collection of Precure statues!
Now, statue!
Mister!
Fire a Heart Shoot at your friends!
Huh?
Why?
You should be able to return your friends to normal!
Hurry!
Girls...
I'm going to save you!
I won't let you!
Hey now!
I'm your opponent.
Precure Heart Shoot!
Girls!
Selfish!
Wreckage!
Girls, let's go!
Right!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Love love loooooove!
What was I...
Now, return the Royal Crystal!
Who do you think I am?
I'm King Selfish's daughter, Regina!
Mister!
I-I'm fine.
I'll go home for today.
But remember this:
the Royal Crystals all belong to me!
See ya!
Regina...
There, there...
Just who are you?
That armor!
It's the mark of a Trump Kingdom warrior!
What were you to the princess?
My name is Jonathan Klondike.
Princess Ann's fiancé.
The princess's fiancé?
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Mister, please tell us how you and the princess fell in love!
Dokidoki Precure:
It's Appeared!
The Final Royal Crystal!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!