[Hohenheim]
Donatus... Poswell...
Reinmeir... Gianni...
Collins... Toni... Willard...
Ripley... Mechthild... Mayo...
Forgive me...
but I have to use you.
[Trisha] You can
hug them, you know.
They are your sons.
[Hohenheim] I don't want
the monster to spread.
Please... If it could
spread that way...
don't you think I would've
caught it a long time ago?
[Hohenheim grunts]
[Hohenheim]
Since I got this body,
I've seen a lot of death.
But I always tried
to think about it
as part of the flow
of the larger world...
That made it easier somehow.
And each time I encountered
something new and wondrous,
it seemed right that
I'd accepted this body
and kept on living...
For a long time,
that was enough.
But then... I met you, and
together we created two sons.
Now it's different...
I don't get any older...
but my sons age and
grow before my eyes.
And suddenly I'm terrified.
I'm realizing that I
really am a monster.
[Trisha] Dear! Dear,
come here a minute.
What is it?
Hello, sir... Good afternoon.
A photographer?
[Trisha] Yes...
Let's fix you up.
You know we don't have
a single family picture.
That's pretty short notice.
[Al laughs]
[Hohenheim sighs]
Here, you hold Ed, all right?
[Hohenheim]
U-Uh... Uh, sure...
Okay, we're ready...
You can go ahead.
This isn't good.
[Ed laughs]
[Hohenheim exhales]
Okay, look right here...
And hold still, please.
What you don't see,
dear, is that someday
I'm going to be a wrinkled
old monster myself.
So today, we're going
to take this picture,
and I'll be able to remember
us all together, smiling...
No matter what,
we're always a family.
So even if you're scared...
don't try distancing
yourself from us.
And one other thing, too...
Stop calling yourself a
monster. It's not true.
Say cheese, everyone!
He's taking it... Smile, dear.
[Hohenheim] My plan
was to take this body,
and in doing so,
to extend my life.
But things are different now.
I want to be with
Trisha and the boys.
To grow old and die with them.
That bastard...
[Hohenheim grunts]
There, that ought to do it.
[Hohenheim yells, groans]
What were you doing?
[Hohenheim]
Fixing the swing.
When did you get so handy?
I haven't ever been able
to do much for the boys...
but I can at least do this.
Trisha. I'm going away.
Wait here for me.
Okay.
Don't tell the children...
I don't want them
to know about my body.
Right... Sure you don't
want me to wake them?
I can't bear to
look at their faces.
Silly man... it's
okay for you to cry.
Uhh--
Oh! You two boys
are up early...
What're you doing out of bed?
Al said he had to go potty.
[Trisha] And of course his
big brother took care of him.
Thanks a lot, little man.
[door opens]
[fire crackles]
[Hohenheim]
Just a little while longer.
[Officer] Well?
It's no good... There's
still nothing coming through.
That's just great... So we're
cut off from all contact.
Your orders, sir...
What should we do now?
[Officer] There has to
be an exit somewhere
to dump out the rubble.
We'll keep going
a little farther...
Smith, go back and report.
Sir!
What is it?
Fan out!
[mysterious windy sound]
[mysterious crash sound]
[Officer gasps]
[multiple screams]
[Smith trembles]
[Smith pants]
[Smith screams]
[Raven] Would
you be interested
in a legion of
immortal soldiers?
He took the bait!
Never dying... or getting old.
You want it too, don't you?
[Olivier] What I
want... is to kill you!
[Raven] Hm?
Oh... it's just such
an incredible question,
I don't know what to say.
Well, are you
interested or not?
There're only two answers.
It is intriguing...
Can you tell me, General,
on the day when this
"dream" comes true...
will my men share in
this gift as well...
or is it only for me?
I can tell you
when the time comes.
[Olivier]
Does that mean there are
no guarantees until then?
If I buy into this, I'll
be forced to facilitate
whatever dirty plans
he has for Briggs.
And if I refuse, I'll
just be swapped out
for some other pawn...
probably demoted.
So... do I accept
his offer or not?
[knocking on door]
Excuse me.
Yes, what is it?
[Soldier 10]
I'm sorry to disturb you,
but the underground
tunnel advance team--
[Raven] What's this about
an underground tunnel?
Speak, soldier.
Yes, sir. Something's
happened to the advance team.
[Olivier] Very well,
I'll be right there.
[Raven] I'm coming, too.
Right... let's move.
Hold on a sec!
[Al gasps]
[Buccaneer] Hm?
It has to look convincing.
[Miles] Buccaneer,
what're you doing?
[Buccaneer]
Prisoner transfer, sir.
I'm moving the Elric brothers
from the east cells
to the west...
May I ask who this is?
This is Mr. Solf J. Kimblee.
He's General Raven's
honored guest.
[Ed] Kimblee...
The Crimson Alchemist.
Wait, did you say
the Elric Brothers?
You mean the
Fullmetal Alchemist?
I see. Now I understand
your nickname.
Oh... it's this one?
[Ed] If one more person
makes that mistake...!
Nice to meet you...
I've heard much about
the Fullmetal Alchemist.
Hello.
General...
[Olivier] What happened?
We lost all contact
with the advance team
that was sent down
to search the tunnel.
Shortly after,
Smith's horse returned.
It came back with what
we assume was his arm.
Just his arm?
Where's the rest?
It's still missing, sir.
And his horse
can't lead us back.
It's too terrified
to be of any use.
Henschel... get
a rescue party--
[Raven] I'm afraid you can't
do that, General Armstrong.
That tunnel is too dangerous.
What have you done with
the "immortal monster"
you were telling
me about earlier?
[Olivier sighs]
Put him back and seal the
tunnel's entrance... General.
But there are still men--
I am speaking to the general.
See, I know northern law...
Obey strength...
and obey the power.
Isn't that the way it works?
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
I am General Raven,
from Central. I've heard
a great deal about you
from His Excellency.
Hello.
[Raven] It appears
you've been good boys
and kept your mouths shut.
[Ed] That was the agreement.
[Raven] You don't seem happy.
[Ed] Oh no, I'm
absolutely thrilled.
Who wouldn't love to have
their friends taken hostage?
[Al] Um... Do you
think you could
release us from this cell soon?
The deal was, if we
didn't mess with you,
you would let us
continue our journey.
There's no need to worry.
I'll let you out of here soon.
[Ed] That tunnel...
is it part of whatever
you're planning, too?
If they find out...
Again, you don't need to worry.
I've already spoken
with the General.
She's going to put the
Homunculus back underground,
and seal up the
tunnel's opening.
[Ed and Al gasp]
General Armstrong's on
our side now, Fullmetal.
[Ed and Al breathe anxiously]
General! Aren't
we going to go in
and search for
the missing team?
[Olivier] Quiet, Henschel.
We can't just abandon
them down there!
They still may need our help!
[Olivier] I said, be quiet!
[Henschel grunts]
Be quiet and obey.
[Henschel sighs]
[Kimblee] Obey the one
who holds the power.
They call her "the impregnable
northern wall of Briggs"...
but even she
yields to authority...
Well, that certainly is
the wisest approach.
[Miles] Hmm.
Oh... so that's the monster.
Ngghhh...
[worried chatter]
Well, Good morning, Sloth.
Did you have a good rest?
Who're you? I'm still sleepy.
You'd best wake up...
There's still a lot of
work to be done here...
Pride explained it to
you, now didn't he?
Eh? I guess...
What a pain... oh, well...
I have no choice. Mmm...
Such a pain... but I forget,
why is it a pain, again?
Too much of a
pain to remember.
[Sloth sighs]
[Raven] Not to worry.
He's a chimera doing some
work for the Central forces.
He's helping to
make this country
even greater
than it already is.
Of course, it's still a
top-secret operation.
So, close this hole
and guard our secret...
I'm counting on
you, soldiers...
It's people like you who
make this country what it is.
[fire crackles]
Hmm...
[Marcoh] All the
important parts
are written in
ancient Ishvalan...
There's no way I can read it.
Does that mean we give up?
[Marcoh] If Scar
were here, he might
be able to read it.
He was an Ishvalan monk,
so he might know
their ancient writing.
[May sighs]
Where is he? Could something
bad have happened to him?
[Soldier 11]
We found her!
The girl with the
black-and-white cat.
[Soldier 12]
Right... let's go!
[Soldier 11] Uhh!
[Soldier 12] Huh? Gah!
[Marcoh and May
exhale happily]
[May] Mr. Scar! Mr. Yoki!
Did you find the
research notes?
Mm, yeah! They're right here!
[Scar] We need to relocate...
The Briggs soldiers
know where we are. Move.
You see, General?
We are the chosen ones,
and we will receive immortal,
near-godly bodies...
We'll rule the entire world.
The name was Smith, wasn't it?
There was nothing we could
have done to save them.
Those who aren't chosen...
will they be sacrificed
for those who are?
Yes... The survival
of the fittest...
The weak will become the
foundation of the country...
and the strong will take
their rightful place on top.
Is that what happened in Ishval?
Indeed... they were
part of the plan...
They were weak and
deserved to perish
for the good of their betters.
[Kimblee] Is that right?
No, I'll take care
of it... Okay.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[Miles] You seem to be making
rather frequent phone calls.
[Kimblee] Can you tell me
where General Raven is?
I need to speak with him.
[Kimblee] Hmm?
You were seriously
injured and near death...
and then the same
day you show up here,
totally recovered... What
sort of magic can do that?
That information is
none of your business.
Another thing:
you were imprisoned
for killing officers...
Why would they release you?
Do I have to say it again?
It's none of your business.
[Olivier] When did
all of this begin?
From what I hear, when the
country was first founded...
And now, my generation shall
preside over its completion...
I'm grateful for
your assistance...
You're a true servant
to your country.
I'll speak with my superiors
about preparing a seat for you.
Hm. There's no need.
What's that?
[Raven screams]
[several gasps]
[Olivier] Which arm
did Smith lose
in the tunnel?
The left or right?
Wait! What are you--?!
Growing old is truly
terrifying, isn't it?
You would know, General...
Before you became so afraid
of your own mortality,
I'm sure long ago
you had an earnest
love for your country.
You... You can't!
You were going to be
one of the chosen ones!
You would have been one of us!
I don't need a
new seat from you.
You're going to lose
the one your moldy ass
has clung to for too long...
right about now, Raven!
You old traitor!
[Raven screams]
But, immortality... was
right before... our eyes.
General... You are among
the weak who will become
the foundation for this
country... Literally.
I was going to...
to be immort--
Now that that's done...
get in touch with Major Miles.
Sir!
The rest of you,
we have work to do!
General...
[Olivier] Hmph.
I want that concrete
nice and level.
[Workers] Right!
[Kimblee] You're not a
fan of me, are you Major?
Is it because I was
a State Alchemist,
one of the ones who served
in the Ishvalan War
of Extermination?
What information can I give
you to make you happier?
Do you want to
know about the war?
About how your
countrymen died in it?
Shut your mouth, Kimblee.
What, you don't
want me to tell you?
I said to shut up!
Major, may I have
a moment with you?
[Soldier 13] I have a message
for you from the general.
She says, "Operation complete.
No need to buy more time."
Roger that.
[Miles] I'm just
glad I'm not stuck
talking to that guy anymore.
I don't know how much
longer I could've lasted.
Kimblee.
Apparently nobody
can find General Raven.
Do you have any idea where
he might have gone off to?
The general's missing?
Seems like it...
This is a fort,
but that doesn't mean
it's safe enough
for an outsider to
be wandering around.
If anything happens
to the general--
[Kimblee] I, for one,
would welcome it.
If anything bad should happen
to General Raven,
then I have permission
to act in whatever
way that I see fit...
That decision came down
from the Fuhrer himself.
[Miles grunts]
Now, perhaps you could
provide me with a car
to drive me down the mountain.
You should act quickly...
It's in your best
interest, I promise...
Right now, orders from me
are tantamount to
orders from the Fuhrer.
[Miles grunts]
[Henschel] Please wait,
General Armstrong!
We have to search for Smith and
the others before we seal it!
Fullmetal saw this coming...
So he made us this secret
passage into the tunnel.
Ah!
She killed him?!
[Al] General Raven?!
Yep, and that was all I
was ordered to tell you.
[Ed] Hey, wait a minute!
When're you guys
gonna let us out of
this damn place?
[Neil] Who knows? Take
it up with the general.
Dammit!
[Al] Getting angry
won't do any good, Ed...
We should just rest for now.
I can't just sit around
while all this is going on...
I need to do something!
[Al] Uh?
Hi. Afternoon, boys...
I was hoping that I might
have a word with the
Fullmetal Alchemist?
[Ed sighs]
Oh, don't tell me that
you have some reason
to dislike me, too.
You should be grateful.
I brought a visitor
with me to see you.
A visitor?
[Ed and Al gasp]
Winry?!
Why did you come here?!
Why?! Why do you think?!
You have to adjust your automail
for the north, don't you?!
And just what are you
doing in that cell?
We didn't ask you to come here!
What's with you?! I was
worried about you, idiot!
Someone from the military
contacted me, so I came--
The military?
Don't be so hard
on her, you two...
The Fuhrer was
concerned about you...
He wanted to make sure
you were taken care of.
[Ed and Al grunt]
[Mustang] Kimblee?
Yes. I heard about it
from a friend of mine
who's working as
a nurse at the base
of the mountain. She
said he was admitted
with serious injuries,
but after General Raven
came to visit, he
recovered right away.
[Mustang] Raven and Kimblee.
That's all the
information I have for now.
Thanks a lot. Tell me
if you hear anything else.
It was really nice seeing you!
[Older woman] Nice?
That's not much to go on.
A bouquet of flowers
might help you next time.
Eh, I'm better off without
her... But thanks anyway.
[Older woman]
When one woman leaves you,
another may find you.
I have a message for you
from Olivier Mira Armstrong.
Colonel Roy Mustang, right?
Hm. I'll take every flower
you have in that cart.
[Narrator]
The chains that bind us
often appear in the
most unexpected forms...
Young man, break free
of your chains...
Cast them off,
free yourself of fear,
and reveal the
identity of the enemy!
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 37: "The
First Homunculus."
Artifice and intimidation...
They may be the key
to your success.