Here at Fumizuki Academy, a school festival known as the "Refresh Festival" is coming up soon.
As the Academy adopted a special system that includes the Exam Summoning Battle,
the festival flourishes every year with many visitors.
The students were thus inspired to get themselves ready and prepare for the festival.
Meanwhile, in Class 2-F...
Come back to us!
Come back, Voyeur!
...someone was being resuscitated.
kongaragatta akai ito wa
こんがらがった赤い糸は
It's our tangled red thread of fate!
isso gouin datte choucho musubi kyu
いっそ強引だってチョウチョ結び きゅ。
I'll tie it into a butterfly knot!
mune ni hazumu kimi to no mirai
胸にはずむキミとの未来
My heart leaps at the thought of a future with you,
hodoicha dame! yakusoku ne
ほどいちゃダメ! 約束ね
so don't go untie it! It's a promise, yeah?
haato kintore
ハート筋トレ
I am training up my heart
rippa ni joujushite misemasu!
立派に成就してみせますっ
I will show you just what I can do!
Love! dame na koi no
LOVE・ダメな恋の
Love! After a failed love
Cry! deeta wa mou
CRY・データはもう
Cry! Now my data is
Trash! yaku ni tatanai no
TRASH・役に立たないの
Trash! It isn't any good at all!
atarimae
あたりまえ
I should have known
So! kimi no mae ja itsudemo
SO・キミの前じゃいつでも
So, whenever you are here, I am always
hatsukoi reberu dana kawaii
初恋レベルだな… 可愛い?
just like a beginner in love... Am I cute?
wakatta you na koto itte
わかったようなコト言って
I always act like I know it all
wai wai wai
ワイワイワイ
Why? Why? Why?
oshaberi na tomodachi
お喋りなトモダチ
Everyone is so friendly
dakedo minna
だけどみんな
But in fact, everyone
shiritai no wa jibun no
知りたいのは自分の
really wants to know how they rank
koi no hensachi
恋の偏差値
in the game of love!
arere
あれれ
Huh?
heikinten ja rongai uwate na daarin
平均点じゃ論外?うわてなダーリン
Average isn't enough? You're so great my darling!
jissai wa tonda kataomoi
実際はとんだカタオモイ
It is in fact, a crazy one-way love!
reberu ageteikou
レベルあげていこう
Let's raise our level up together!
High!
High! High! High!
kongaragatta akai ito wa
こんがらがった赤い糸は
It's our tangled red thread of fate!
isso gouin datte choucho musubi kyu
いっそ強引だってチョウチョ結び きゅ。
I'll tie it into a butterfly knot!
mune renda panikku kimi to kyuutenkai
mune renda panniku kimi to kyuutenkai
胸連打パニック キミと急展開
My heart is hit by panic! Things with you just took off!
acchi muicha dame tsuite kite
あっち向いちゃダメ! ついてきて♪
Don't go looking elsewhere! Just follow me!
haato
ハート
I am training up my heart
kintore
筋トレ
angai tafu ni kyou mo moumoku!
案外タフに今日も盲目っ
Amazingly, today was pretty tough too
FFFpeeps presents
Day 1
"Me, Maids, and A New Chapter"
Let's go back a few days.
The students had started preparing for the Refresh Festival.
Meanwhile, Class 2-F was...
Play ball!
...playing baseball.
Bring it on, Yoshii!
Let's rumble, Sugawa!
The next ball will be...
a curve ball...
to the batter's...
head!
Hang on, that's against the rules!
Don't hold back! Give it all you've got!
Of course I'd hold back!
You brats! How dare you goof off!
Oh no! It's Ironman!
Yoshii! You again?!
Why do you always go straight for me?!
The mastermind is obviously the class rep, Yuuji!
Throw a fork ball...
at Ironman's...
crotch?!
Screw you!
I'd be screwed for that!
Cut it out and return to your classroom already!
The only class which still hasn't decided on a theme is Class F!
Okay...
So,
let's decide on a theme for the school festival.
Raise your hand if you have any ideas.
Okay, Voyeur.
A photo exhibit.
And what kind of photos are we going to exhibit?
That's a secret.
A secret?
Display valuable photos that allow you to peek into the world of mysteries.
They are
priceless
erotica
It's still a suggestion. Just write it on the board.
Sure.
Photo exhibit...
Se... Sec...
Secret?
P-Peeping... room...?
Anyone else?
Yeah, Himeji.
Umm, what about a wedding café?
It's like a maid café, but the waitresses wear wedding dresses instead.
Hey, that might be cute.
The girls would be happy, and the boys would love it too, right?
Marriage is a man's grave.
Akihisa, write it down.
Wedding... man, and...
Any other ideas?
How about a Chinese café?
We'll do a Yum cha service to set ourselves apart from the other classes.
As they say, no culture is as deep as Chinese...
No matter
although European culture has been pretty pervasive lately.
where you
are
You're still flat
Akihisa, write it down.
Let's see... Chinese... European...
Come on, Akihisa. You're only writing down the words you remember-
Guys! Have you decided on a theme for the school festival yet?
We got three proposals.
WTF happened here?
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Maybe I should just give you more supplementary lessons.
Huh?! What's that supposed to mean?!
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
Geez, can't you people take this more seriously?
Don't you want to raise some money to upgrade your facilities?
You mean we can buy desks with the money we make?
Oh! I didn't think of that!
Can we really do that, teacher?
I knew you guys were idiots,
Idiots
but I didn't know things would get worse than orange boxes.
While it may be fair penalty, it would be preposterous if it affects with your studies.
Prepos
terous
I will bargain with the principal to make this a legitimate exception.
Really?
We wouldn't have to study using these drawing boards and mats anymore.
That should amaze my dad, too!
Y-Your dad?
Ah, never mind.
Anyway, doesn't it sound interesting?
Okay. Let's take a vote.
Vote for the theme you want to do.
Photo Exhibit
The secret peeping room
Wedding Cafe
A man's grave
Chinese Cafe
European
There we go.
I hope we get a lot of customers.
We have to succeed this time, so give it your best, Aki.
Hm? "This time"?
Well, I was told to keep it a secret, but Mizuki might transfer.
Himeji might....
transfer?!
Transfer
No way! I still have to make lots of sweet memories with her!
What will happen if the only sweet girl in Class F transfers?!
Everyone will lose hope, and the class will fall apart,
decaying into a hell ruled by violence and plundering!
Just like in the Legend of the Century's End Messiah, we'll all have mohawks,
spending our days in constant conflicts revolving around the sole heroine, Hideyoshi!
Akihisa's brain overheated.
He can't deal with unexpected situations.
Akihisa, wake up!
Hideyoshi, would you still love me even if I had a mohawk?
Just how did you associate that with Mizuki's transfer?
Why is Himeji transferring?
Mizuki's parents are worried about her studying in Class F.
They have a point. She's spending her day in terrible conditions with the dregs of the school.
No wonder they're worried.
If she transfers, she'll be able to study in a normal environment.
So that's what she meant just now...
Ah, I see. She might be able to convince her parents
once we improve the facilities of our class.
We can't afford to fail, Akihisa.
Yeah.
We're back!
Himeji.
Tsuchiya made a dish for our Chinese café. Will you try some?
Sesame dumplings.
I'll try one.
Oh, this is good.
Yeah! The surface is crispy and the inside is soft and chewy.
I love how it's not too sweet.
This makes me want a cup of tea.
I'll go get some.
Oh, I'll help too.
Are they that good?
I'll try one then.
Oh! The surface is crunchy and the inside is sticky.
I love how it's not too sweet, but really spicy fla-
What's wrong, Akihisa?!
Voyeur, did you really make that sesame dumpling yourself?
I certainly did...
I only made three. Why were there more?
Judging by his condition, it must have been Himeji's work.
That was dangerous! It's just Russian roulette with 50-50 odds!
Grandpa, I'm coming to you.
He sure is one unlucky guy.
o
x
Fumi
zuki
Fest
x
zuki
Aca
demy
Refr
esh
x
And so came the day of the school festival.
Welcome to Chinese Café European!
Someone! Someone save him!
We already went over this.
Akihisa!
We're short-handed. Would you mind helping in the kitchen?
Oh well. I'll have to do it myself.
Thank you for your patronage!
Welcome!
We are currently conducting a waitress popularity survey.
Please cast your vote on your way out!
Looks like the business is running fine, for now.
We got quite a few customers, too. It's working out nicely.
Hey! Just how long are you gonna make us wait?
What's with this café? Aren't you gonna take our orders?
Y-Yes, I'll be with you soon. Please give me a minute.
What?!
We've been waiting plenty long enough.
We got a lot of other stuff to see too. Don't keep us waiting forever, ya dumb jerks!
S-Sorry. Please wait a minute.
What's with their attitude?
Third graders? They're such a pain in the ass.
Jesus, we're starving here.
Oh?
Sesame Dumplings
200¥
Sample
There's good food right here!
The surface is crunchy and the inside is sticky.
I love how it's not too sweet, but really spicy fla-
Oh no! This is bad!
300 joules, charge!
300, roger!
3, 2, 1!
Thank god.
You guys are really used to this.
We live on the verge of death.
What caused this?
Th-This is...!
I can't believe they ate the display sample.
What's with the damn food here?!
You trying to kill us?
We won't let you off easy!
This is bad. I have to cover this up somehow.
Congratulations! You're the first winner today!
Winner?
Is there a prize or something?
Prize?
Well...
Here, open up!
As if we would!
You bastard! You'll pay for this!
We'll put you out of business!
No way! You're the one who ate the sample!
Shut up! Call your manag-
I am the representative, Sakamoto Yuuji.
Is there a problem?
Natsukawa was flung to the wall by your punch just now...
Well, I start my negotiations with a punch.
Stop messing with us, you son of a bitch!
And that was the follow up kick.
Man, that hurts.
Tsunemura!
Lastly, I'll finish the negotiation with a pro-wrestling move.
N-No thanks. I've had enough.
I see. Then...
And that concludes our negotiation.
He's well trained.
That's Karl Gotch style.
Orders
Item          Amount
Sesame Dumplings
Punch And Kick
German Suplex, Karl Gotch
Style
2x
1 each
1 set
FFF Squad
Recruiting
Members
Task Details
You will put your strong emotions into blunt tools
and crush your target. It's simple.
A wide selection of tools are supplied.
Of course, you may also bring your own.
Beginners need not worry.
Kind seniors will guide you with care.
Young men, step forward!!
You will put your strong emotions into blunt tools
and crush your target. It's simple.
A wide selection of tools are supplied.
Of course, you may also bring your own.
Thank you very much!
This place is empty now.
That's strange. It's lunchtime.
This is looking bad.
Welcome!
Huh?
Hello, Mr. Stupid!
Hazuki, you're here!
Yeah! I'll help you out since it's the school festival and all!
Thanks, Hazuki.
Don't worry. It's for the café of my husband-to-be after all!
You had my first kiss.
Huh?
Why am I on the ground?
Tsuchiya! Lend me some forks. Five should be enough.
Count me in too, so make that ten.
Time for an inquisition.
First off, death penalty.
Thanks for coming all the way, but as you can see...
business is going really slow.
At this rate, wild grass will start sprouting up.
We don't really need any help at the moment.
I see...
I wanted to try on a Chinese style dress.
100 meat buns. Make it quick.
Get it yourself!
It could be because of that rumor.
Rumor?
Lolicon
Yes.
First Cultural Festival -Hazuki Chapter- Episode 1
I got a little lost on my way here,
so I asked lots of people where the biggest idiot's shop is.
Everyone told me the way here right away.
It's already a landmark, eh...
Are you talking about me?!
Everyone also said I shouldn't go there since it's nasty.
No way!
We all gave this place a thorough cleaning. We even put up pretty bunting!
None of the guests complained.
They should have all been satisfied.
Except for two, that is.
That Eversummer pair must be spreading bad rumors.
Eversummer?
They are Tsunemura and Natsukawa. Take the first characters and you get Eversummer (tokonatsu).
I see.
Then I'll just have to find them and re-open negotiations.
Hazuki, where did you hear that rumor?
I heard it at a place full of pretty girls!
All right! Let's find them at all costs!
Pretty
Girls
You seem to have a different objective in mind.
Maid Cafe
So this is the place Hazuki was talking about.
I don't see anything unusual.
It's too early to tell.
Welcome home, master.
Wow! Kirishima, you look great!
Thanks, Yoshii.
Welcome home. I won't let you leave tonight, darling.
Can I leave right now?
Here is the menu.
Let's see. Get me some...
Shortcake
Mont Blanc
Panna Cotta
Gateau au Chocolate
Pumpkin Pudding
Lemon Tart
Madeleine
Cheese Tart
Cake Set ¥450
Cake Only ¥300
Please choose from
the drinks below
Coffee Blend
Cafe latte
Darjeeling
water.
Most certainly.
How about you, master?
Shouko, what's up with this menu?
Menu~
For Yuuji
Today's Recommendations
Today's recommendations:
Honeymoon with the maid
... current market price
Lovey-dovey date with the maid
Honeymoon with the maid.
... priceless
A sweet kiss with the maid
Lovey-dovey date with the maid.
... secret
A sweet kiss with the maid.
Supply is limited, so order quickly.
I won't!
Man, this place is so clean and nice!
The Chinese café at Class 2-F was terrible. This is on a whole different level!
That place was dirty, it smelled strange,
the waitresses were ugly, and it's named European when it's a Chinese café.
What dumbasses!
Those are all lies!
One is true, actually.
I won't let this slide!
Hold it.
Our reputation will only get worse if we start a fight here. Use your head a little.
Then what are we doing?
Let me see.
Shouko, I need a maid outfit.
Okay.
Time out! What are you doing?!
Yuuji, you said you need me.
Not you, the maid outfit!
I meant just lend me a spare if you've got one!
I'll bring one right away.
Stop looking so disappointed!
Yuuji, what are we going to do with the maid outfit?
We'll ask Hideyoshi to help out, of course.
I see now. That's genius.
How's this? Looking like a girl now?
Changing
Just as I'd expect from you, Hideyoshi. It looks pretty good.
This kind of makeup is my absolute specialty!
We're gonna put a bra on too?!
You gotta make it perfect if you're to play the role!
Actually, we should use panties-
Th-That's...!
Maid Cafe
Really, I don't understand why anyone would want to go to that dirty Chinese café!
It's Class F. They're nothing but trash.
What's the matter, missy?
You're pretty cute!
Whoa, what's wrong? Did you fall in-
EAT THIS!
Was it good enough?
Y-You're from Class F!
Crap!
Ahhh! This person is peeping up my skirt!
What?! H-Hold o-
How could you do such a sick thing in public, you sicko!
What are you talking about?! I'm the victim here!
Shut up! You felt up the waitress' breasts!
This man's a pervert!
Huh? What's this?
The hell?! It won't come off!
See? He's groping them so hard!
Totally not!
This is bad.
We're getting out of here, Natsukawa!
Wait!
Haunted House
Hmph.
It's well made, but these toys can only do so much.
Is there anything scarier?
Those bastards! I won't forgive them!
We'll make them pay no matter what it takes.
How?
I have an idea. Let's go!
Wh-What was that just now?
I must have anticipated scary things too much and hallucinated it.
So, if I do the opposite and anticipate beautiful things...
Wh-What a beauty!
I-I shouldn't!
I already have in my heart, my sweet honey Yoshii!
However, her beauty was out of this world!
No, that would be betraying my feelings for Yoshii!
Damn! I forgot to ask her class and name...
But I have Yoshii!
I could run after her right now...
God! What should I do?!
Do whatever you like.
Welcome!
We're getting more and more customers!
Aki's team must have done a good job.
I helped out as well!
Damn, we lost them.
What should we do, Yuuji?
They might be spreading bad rumors again.
Huh?
What's wrong, Voyeur?
This is bad! A waitress was kidnapped!
What?
Hello?
Hey, thanks for that punch earlier.
Right now we're with a really cute waitress of yours.
Your sales must've dropped by now without your top waitress!
Give Himeji and Minami back!
Calm down there. You don't want to make me angry.
Don't worry. We'll be having lots of fun with her.
I will...
never forgive them!
Voyeur, do you know where they are hiding?
It'll take some time.
Okay. Please.
Men's Changing Room
Are these video streams from the school's surveillance cameras?
The angles are too low for that.
These are my surveillance cameras.
I have 32 video monitors on campus.
I don't see them anywhere.
I have 57 audio monitors too.
Switch to audio then.
You hear that? He was so pissed!
Serves him right!
Bingo!
Where's the source?
Athletics storage.
All right!
Sorry!
I'm coming, Himeji, Minami.
What?!
Bastard, how did you find-
Himeji!
Minami!
What's wrong, Akihisa?
Those two are working at the café.
Hideyoshi, why are you here?
They dragged me here and made me play a game with them.
They were having fun, then.
And thus ended the first day of the Refresh Festival.
How do the sales look, Shimada?
It's awesome!
We have enough for system desks even after subtracting the expenses!
Really?
What's up with these amazing sales?
Hmm, lemme see... Voyeur Co. Deluxe Photo Collection Set A,
500 copies all sold out.
Refresh Festival Limited Edition.
In any case, today was a success!
Mr. Stupid, that's so great! Good for you!
Thanks, Hazuki. It's all thanks to your help.
These sales were only possible because the waitresses attracted a lot of customers!
I have the survey results.
Today's most popular waitress is...
Akichan
Did we have
a girl
this cute?
Did we have
a girl
this cute?
Akichan
Did we have
a girl
this cute?
Did we have
a girl
this cute?
Akichan
Did we have
a girl
this cute?
Did we have
a girl
this cute?
Akichan
Did we have
a girl
this cute?
I don't have to be the first, but still...
What should I do about this frustrating feeling?
Congratulations, Akihisa.
For once, you're a winner.
I'm not happy at all!
All right!
Everyone, listen. This is important.
Huh?
I talked to the principal about the classroom facilities.
She'll make this an exception so we can buy new facilities using the booth sales.
Exception
However,
there is a condition.
An Exam Summoning Contest will be held on the second day of the Refresh Festival.
She will only approve it if the winning team is from this class.
Exam Summoning Contest?
It's a randomized tournament of teams chosen from the entire student body.
It's full of strong opponents.
No way...
What will you do, Akihisa?
Of course... I'll do it!
If you want to participate, form a team and register.
That's all!
That's all
Monday! Monday! Monday!
Monday!
yasumi no yokujitsu wa yasumi ni suru beki da!
休みの翌日は休みにするべきだ!
The day after a day-off should also be a day-off!
Monday! Monday! Monday!
Monday!
yasumi no zenjitsu mo yasumi ni suru beki da!
休みの前日も休みにするべきだ!
The day before a day-off should be a day-off too!
Monday! Monday! Monday!
Monday!
owaritaku nai!
終わりたくない!
I don't want to see it end!
tsuzuite hoshii!
続いて欲しい!
I want it to go on and on!
heya kara wa detaku nai!
部屋からは出たくない!
I don't want to get out of my room!
shinjitaku nai!
信じたくない!
I don't want to believe it!
shinjirare nai!
信じられない!
I can't believe it!
getsuyou wa kirai
月曜はキライ
I really hate Mondays!
Good morning!
okinakya owaru
起きなきゃ終わる
If I don't wake up it will end.
Good morning!
sakaraenai suima ni
逆らえない睡魔に
I can't fight against this drowsiness.
Good morning!
ato chotto dake nebareru
あとちょっとだけ粘れる
I can hold out just a little longer.
Good morning!
yume no naka wa shiawase!
夢の中は幸せ!
I'm happy in my morning dream!
okitara ii tomo
起きたらいいとも
It'd be best if I got up,
owatta "dame kamo..."
オワッタ「だめかも…」
but it's over. "Maybe that's no good..."
yume no tsuzuki wa horaa na genjitsu
夢の続きはホラーな現実
After the dream comes the horror of reality.
imasara jitabata shitemo
今更ジタバタしても
Even if I struggle against it now,
jikan wa modorya shinai
時間は戻りゃしない
that time won't come back to me.
futatabi yume no sekai e daibu
再び夢の世界へダイブ
So I dive back into the world of dreams!
Hence, the dream of Class 2-F was relegated to the second day.
And here is another man in pursuit of his dreams.
Just who was that?
I have good stuff today.
Th-This is...
H-How much?
Huh? What are you guys doing?
Yoshii!
No...
This is... not what you think!
Huh?