It's really coming down now.
The forecast was off, eh?
Forecast, prediction, warning, expectation, plan, prophecy.
Things that tell of the future ain't ever been reliable.
Are ya sure it's under here?
Yes. I have a bad feeling.
Let's hope my feeling is off too.
Run!
Don't stop!
Damn!
They're only going after Ushio.
They haven't attacked me at all.
Ushio!
Does yer arm hurt?
Crap. We can't go any further.
Get outta here! Move!
Sou!
Awesome!
Is this why ya brought the bug spray?
Yeah! It's working just like I hoped!
Ain't a living thing that doesn't hate fire!
Ya okay, Ushio?! We can still go back!
I'm fine!
Let's keep going.
I hate leaving things halfway done!
Figured ya'd say that.
Shinpei, I'll open a path!
Take care of Ushio!
Way ahead of ya!
Ryuunosuke!
Tell me when yer gonna shoot!
Ya blasted my ears!
Sorry, but you'd be dead if I waited at all.
Can't believe these shadows are lurking underneath the island.
There are more of them.
Their nest is close.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
The number you have called is out of the range of...
Dinner Time
Where's Shin?
He went out to see Sou.
I can't reach Sou or Tokiko either.
Come home soon, Shin.
Shadow sickness already took Sis and Shiori.
If it gets him too...
Ain't this Shiori's hair tie?
Over here.
Shinpei is here...
What?
W-Wait!
Watch where yer—M-Mio?
Oh, Tetsu. S-Sorry.
Don't jump out like that!
What's going on? Ya look pale.
It's Shiori! Didn't ya see her?
What?
Was she found?
Where is she?!
She went running the way ya came from.
Ain't possible.
I only saw ya running toward me.
Shiori!
What?
Sh-She disappeared.
Wait!
The manhole lid is loose.
Shinpei is here.
What's that mean?
Is Shin down there?
What?
No, ain't no way! We must be mistaken!
No way a little girl would go inside this thing!
Normally, I'd agree.
But what if it was Shiori's shadow?
Tetsu—
Hell no.
I didn't even say anything!
Ya want me to check inside, right?
Ain't happening! I'm a busy man!
I'm on my way to the city fer drinks!
If I show up smelling like the sewers, Erika will hate me fer sure!
So drinks are worth more than a human life?
No, but this one?
Ya'd be a hero.
What?
A hero who finds a missing girl would be all over the news.
Ya'd be famous.
Erika would totally fall fer ya.
But I won't force ya.
I'm going with or without ya.
Follow me.
It ain't like I'm doing this because I wanna be a hero and get girls!
Don't get me wrong!
I'm an ally of justice who just wants to find Shiori!
Thanks.
Being superficial is totally better than doing nothing.
Ain't that a little harsh, Mio?
Did we escape them?
Yeah.
But what is this place?
It's starting to look even stranger.
Yeah, look.
This is impossible.
What?
These are corals.
How can sea animals live on land?
They're shadows.
What?
The corals, sea anemones, and barnacles are all shadows.
Who'd do anything like this?
I dunno, but someone printed the sea here.
It's seawater.
This must be connected to the sea.
It'd be great if we could find another way out.
This is getting too dangerous, Shinpei.
I've used up all the gas too.
It's over if we get attacked again.
H-Hey, Ushio?
I-I'm okay.
Just hungry.
How's that possible?
We just ate an hour ago!
That's not yer usual hunger.
Yer right arm hasn't healed, has it?
This is damaged data from my real body.
To heal it, I need food.
Then Shinpei can give ya another rice ball—
No, that ain't it!
I don't mean normal food.
The only way to repair this data is to rescan the original.
But Ushio was cremated.
I can't repair this wound.
A-Are ya serious?
All this time...
So it's been hurting ever since the
shadow Mio stabbed ya yesterday?
I wasn't sure until just now.
Why'd ya keep something so important from us?!
Sorry.
I'll erase my right arm fer now.
That'll take away the pain.
No way to heal it?
That can't be.
She's getting weaker.
Dammit!
I can't let her die again!
What if I loop?
What if I turn back the time?
How would that heal it?
Don't move.
Turn around slowly.
If the two of you make any sudden moves,
it'll cost you Ushio's life.
Wh-What're ya doing here?
Tokiko!
It's a dead end.
Shadows came from here.
It's a path only they can go through.
We know one thing now.
Shadows used these sewers and tunnels to move around the island.
Yeah.
The army dug a ton of 'em in this area.
Ain't anyone alive who knows their full extent.
Wouldn't surprise me if there were more of these passages.
What should we do?
We don't have tools to cut steel bars.
Should we go back up and find another way in?
Hitogashima Port
Koba Mart
Hishigata Clinic
Hitogashima Junior High
Hitogashima Elementary School
Based on the map, we're near the center of the island.
Nah.
There probably ain't an entrance that humans can use.
Take a look ahead.
This ain't no sewer.
It's a natural cave that was always here.
Hiruko's grotto really existed.
What?
My gramps told me about it when I was a kid.
There's a massive underground cave on Hitogashima.
That's Hiruko's grotto.
Until the mid-Meiji era, an entrance appeared near the port during the low tide,
but the army closed it up during the First Sino-Japanese War.
Hiruko's grotto is an island legend that I thought was a myth.
It's said that's where our guardian god Hiruko lived after drifting to Hitogashima long ago.
That's Hiruko's lore.
Sis would know more.
Should we switch?
Not right now.
We can ask the Karikiri boy,
though I wish his old man was still alive.
He might've known something.
Anyway, let's go back and get tools—
Quiet.
Hey, let's just go back. She ain't gonna be in here!
I'm sure I saw Shiori up there. And I know ya did too!
Man, I smell like the sewers now.
I gotta take a bath before I go out.
I'll tell Erika how manly ya are, okay?
Oh, ya would?
Shiori!
Hold on a sec, Mio.
How'd she get to the other side? Well?
Yuck.
No way.
Wait!
Are we dreaming?
What?
Yer going? Mio?
I have expensive shoes on, y'know!
Hey, that was...
Kofune Mio and the police officer Totsumura Tetsu.
My sister's bad feeling may've been right.
I wouldn't follow them.
It's a trap.
At least we know Mio is human.
She has immunity.
Who knows?
I guess we'll find out.
Toki?
I'm surprised ya survived this far
intruding on forbidden soil, Brother.
Answer me!
Wh-What's this all about, Tokiko?
She's too far.
She's out of range for the nail gun.
What are ya doing here?!
Dumb question.
What?
I'm recovering faulty goods.
Thank you for bringing Ushio to me.
She's tough to find since she's broken.
She's coming closer.
I can reach her in three more steps.
We'll take care of her from here.
I won't let you touch Ushio!
Please! Stop!
No, Shinpei.
Toki is...
Too bad, Shinpei.
I'm human.
You can kill shadows, but not humans.
Are ya really Tokiko?
Shall we...
chat for a bit?
Summer Time Rendering
My apologies, Negoro.
Negoro
How may I help, Doctor?
Add this to today's fodder.
It's almost nine.
Hurry and carry it over.
Yes, Doctor.
I understand.
We surrender.
No! Shinpei!
Sou!
Shinpei's right.
It sucks, but we can't win.
Don't do anything stupid,
Brother.
Grab her.
Ushio!
Dammit! Stop it, Tokiko!
Sou, calm down.
What?!
She would've killed her already if she wanted to.
She just wants to take Ushio.
Am I right, Toki?
I haven't figured anything out yet.
If I can take the silence as a "Yes,"
then it's still early.
Sorry, Ushio.
Hang in there.
It's just going to be a bit longer.
Where are ya taking her?
To yer father?
I get it.
Tokiko!
Is Dad making ya do all this?!
Yer so clueless, Brother.
I guess it's inevitable.
Dad didn't choose ya.
What?
If you've seen this much,
there isn't much point in hiding it anymore.
This could actually be a good
chance to show you everything.
Please put down your weapons.
I'll guide you if you comply.
I don't want to take drastic measures.
Please come of your own free will.
Hiruko is waiting.
You'll miss.
A little to the right. Five degrees to the right.
Shaddup!
Don't worry about me.
Fine.
Focus on yer own targets!
We lost track of Mio.
Is she okay?
We ain't got the time to worry about others.
Look around.
What the hell is this place?
It's like the bottom of the sea!
That's a Doflein sea anemone.
Dof... What?
It lives in the deep sea.
I saw it on TV before.
They can't live on land.
These must be all shadows.
Behind us!
I don't like this.
Ya killed that thing twice!
Why's it still here?!
Is it immortal?!
Oh? Yer not surprised?
It would make sense if you didn't really die.
You faked being killed and dove underground.
Right?
My sister was suspicious of the sewers.
I see. Hizuru doesn't disappoint.
Why'd ya return to get in my way?
I told ya I'd kill ya if I saw ya again.
I guess ya wouldn't know, Minakata Ryuunosuke.
Hey, how's she know yer name?!
No!
I figured out ya hid inside Hizuru
when we talked in the kids' room.
It can't be.
Are you Haine?
It's been 14 years since we saw each other.
However, I'm not interested in you.
You're only a personality and a memory.
Where is your body?
Where's the body that stole Mother's right eye?
Haine, you're playing make-believe all over again?
But this time you're using Kobayakawa Shiori's memory.
It got blocked!
That shot should've hit!
I read his memory.
Neither Hizuru nor Ryuunosuke know where the body is.
I can't read the old man.
Can I kill him?
Sure.
Let's run, Ryuunosuke.
We can't beat that.
You've got to be kidding.
Don't ya get it?!
We're the ones being hunted!
They're not shadows of humans,
but of something much more terrible!
Watch it.
He's slightly off.
He's about two seconds ahead.
Yes, I know.
Ryuunosuke!
There. One down.
Nezu!
Damn you!
Oh?
Around there?
So close.
It's hard to hit two seconds ahead.
Yer not going after him?
No need.
The blood is dark.
I hit the liver.
It's a fatal blow.
He'll die soon anyway.
Where are Ushio and Shinpei?
They're close, but don't worry.
I sent two stray shadows with Tokiko.
More importantly, I'm really hungry.
I can't wait 'til nine o'clock.
Dammit.
I have no strength.
Shinpei lost his weapon and surrendered.
He must've decided not to loop before finding out the truth.
He's gonna go as far as he can.
Ain't that right, Shinpei?
Th-That wasn't me!
It's Hiruko.
She's hungry.
I've accepted what I do.
I won't ask for forgiveness.
I just want you guys to understand it.
Dad is opposed to telling you though, Brother.
I won't warn ya not to tell anyone because ya can't.
But please don't tell Mio, Shinpei.
I don't want Mio to find out what you see and learn here.
I won't get Mio involved with this.
Good.
You're kind.
A long shadow stretches to the ceiling.
At the foot of that shadow...
Nine o'clock sharp.
It's dinner time.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Bloody Night