WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
There is no guest. MadoHomu ♥
Yuuki Aoi has a nickname for Saitou Chiwa. I don't want to spoil it in this opening text, but I'll put it in italics the first time.
Hello, everyone! Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆ Magika episode 10,
I Won't Depend On Anyone Anymore audio commentary shall begin now!
With the role of Madoka, I'm Yuuki Aoi.
And with the role of Homura, I'm Saitou Chiwa!
（ ﾟ∀ﾟ）ﾉ Uuuu—!
Just the two of us!
Refreshing, isn't it?
It's refreshing!
Right,
up until now we've always had a guest person, so~
Mm!
Yes.
That's right.
This is a bit...!
Mm!
This is a bit, a bit...!!!
What to do? When we have a guest-san, we're always asking the guest-san many questions...
Mm, mm.
We have a conversation together too, of course.
That's right, ne.
We have a whole episode to talk among ourselves!
Yes we do, and moreover, it's episode 10!
(lol)
It's this episode!
What're we going to do, Ao-chan? This is a bit...!
What to do?
This is the episode where I talk the most, though.
Ahh–Eh? Right, that's right.
What am I going to do when I'm the one talking!?
Somehow, I can't say "The acting right here, you know..."
C–Can't say it, but... To me, for Chii-sama's acting in this episode, I told everyone "This part is awesome!"
Really? For me too, when I watched episode 10, I thought there were so many wonderful parts in Ao-chan's acting!
No, no, no!
It's that kind of episode.
It's that kind of episode, it's that kind of episode.
(lol)
Nah, but... well you know, this is the opening stage. Of the time leaps.
That's right, ne.
This is another different axis.
Saying it's particularly a time axis is a little bit wrong, though.
That's right, ne.
You could say it's sort of close to something like a parallel world...
Homura constantly persists through them.
Mm.
That is, what is it... various different times.
Various different times, certainly.
This is one of those.
Really, though...
It's also a little different from rewinding time in the time you're currently in, too.
That's also different.
Really, it's very similar to clearing various scenarios in a game.
Right, right.
It was said during the time for episode 10 that "there will be reminiscence (flashbacks)," but...
Ah, that's right, ne.
"Homura's flashbacks" wasn't written, so...
(Could that be Homura? I didn't think she was a meganekko!)
メガネっ娘 (meganekko) - Glasses girl.
(Me neither!)
Didn't it surprise you?
Probably!
When we saw it the very first time, "A–Akemi Homura" wasn't added yet, so
Right, right, right, right, right!
everyone was like "Mm? Who's this?"
It was like a new program!
Right!
I thought it was probably a new chara.
I certainly thought that!
When we first heard about this, it was for the recording of the previous episode,
That's right, ne.
I was given art for this meganekko version of Homura...
"Ao-chan, come look!!!"
That's right!
It was like "But this is meganekko!"
"No way, super cute!" we said that, or something...
"No, no, but, this!" is what I was like.
Ne?
I was completely trembling with fear, I remember...
Ya~!
No, but really, Urobuchi-san also says this, really...
"Ah, really, the actor picked was for the sake of this part! It's Chii-sama~" is what is thought.
No, no, no~
It was truly frightening.
(lol)
I thought "No way!"
But ya know, it's quite, ne...
With these circumstances exposed...
Man, we really got the script at the final moments.
(lol) Is it okay to say that?
There's staff behind me, so actually what I am saying?
That's right, ne.
They're looking at me in a bit of a daze...
Daze, daze!
Looking in a daze.
'Cause, really...
"Hurry up and give it to me! Hurry up!" is what I thought...
Right (lol)
Then when I got it, she talked so much, so it was hard work, you know...
Right.
Actually, for this episode, it was written that Madoka should be cooler...
Right!
It was properly written that Ao-chan should switch up Madoka's acting a bit.
Somehow, the sound director Tsuruoka-san said to sort of...
"Do it more like a honor student with a natural high."
"Natural high...?"
That's 'cause it had a feeling of "Please act cocky," right?
Right, right!
When you get cocky in this anime, I'd say you get gonyogonyo'd.
gonyogonyo = eaten.
Direct reference to Mami-san. "GONYO" is written in Charlotte's barrier in runes.
Although that's actually there. (lol)
Ah, there are no longer any people that haven't seen all of this, right?
That's right. Right, right.
There's no one who hasn't seen this whole ep, right? I think so, so anyway,
Madoka—
If you haven't seen this yet, please go watch the original volume first, okay?
Ah, right right!
Right, right.
"Awawawawa"
They're gone now.
Right, right~
Right, Madoka actually dies quite a number of times, she's repeatedly somewhat cocky, so...
Somehow... she's extremely cocky this time.
Ne?
This.
It's come~
This part! It's become somewhat popular among us.
A secret! ★
Right, right, right.
This, you know...
Just after this, is amazing.
A secret! ★
Is said. There's a star, right?
Right!
★!
There was a star in the actual script.
Right, right, right, it was written there~
Really, I thought the line between "cool" and "annoying" would be pretty thin for that one.
Right, right.
Upon seeing that, Homura begins to aspire to be one...
Then, up until now, this has left a huge impression on me, but...
In regards to Mami-san... amazing.
She has that "Tomoe Mami" feeling, so...
That's right! Tomoe Mami.
It's just that this kind of feeling she has is amazing, ne.
Somehow... it's unexpected.
Then,
Right.
that lying thing is there, too.
That's right, he's come...
That filthy white thing.
Love filthy, though.
He's a white demon, truly.
(lol)
Right.
But somehow, this time, especially in the second half...
This is really an episode where I mostly talk to Ao-chan, isn't it?
That's right, ne~
Madoka and Homura haven't had any basic conversation yet, so...
Somehow, you know...
I really think, "Thank goodness for Ao-chan" every time.
No, but really, for the atmosphere here... Somehow, probably,
I think people who watch the audio commentary for every episode probably really understand this, but...
Well, the one who is able to set the atmosphere here, is definitely Chii-sama.
No no no, that isn't true.
(lol) Really
(lol) I can't do anything but follow your signs.
That isn't true~!
It is true.
That isn't true.
You think of so many different things. You interpose with your wide knowledge, it's so difficult.
Today you can talk as much as you want.
That's right! Today I think I can talk as much as I want.
That's why it's true for the thoughts of heart up until now, too...
Then you know, for the episode after this, episode 11...
Right! That's right!
But I think that many guest-sans will probably come, so we won't get to talk...
Ne?
Gotta use this chance now to talk! (lol)
Use this chance to talk!
So with that, everyone—
I can't say the outcome, though.
That's right, everyone who's scared of spoilers will be constantly "wawawa"'d here.
Right, right.
Anyway, for us, who are mains in this part,
Yes.
it's like "How should we do the audio commentary this time?"
That's right, ne.
What to talk about, I thought...
Earlier, when those two were at Mami-san's house... Originally, Madoka was the one who assisted Homura-chan, right?
So when I read the script, I thought "I see, so this is where Homura-chan starts."
Right, right.
It's Homura-tan, though~
How is it, really... Madoka right now is quite strong, though...
Right!
That's why, for that part in the beginning from episode 1,
Mm, mm.
"Ah, this is the conversation they had before, isn't it?"
That's right, right, that conversation took place.
This part of the show left a huge impression on me. I remember it so well...
In the end, even more than doing the actual acting.
Mm, mm.
Really,
I really thought of all the things that had accumulated up until now...
It's true for Homura too. For example, that kind of divide in acting.
There's the cool Homura from up until now, then there's the timid meganekko Homura here...
It's true for Madoka too, the somewhat cowering/hesitant Madoka from up until now, and this Madoka who has confidence.
It's just that, for the division in these acting styles, I feel that anyone could surely do it. It's easy to understand, ne?
That's right, ne.
But, for the division in the acting styles that Ao-chan pulled off,
really, the heart's... different rhythm... this is really hard to explain, but...
Your heart is in a different state, and very subtly in accordance with that, the acting you put forth changed...
That's why, it isn't particularly the conversation's content that did it,
it really felt like the whole setting of that Madoka properly changed, so...
Somehow, I had a feeling of really seeing that, so...
When watching it, I constantly thought "This is just so nice!"
Thank you so much~!!!
Truly.
Really, for me to say this... it might come off as a bit egotistical,
but if my companion for Madoka wasn't Ao-chan, I don't think I could have acted out Homura so well.
I think that for ep10.
That is... most certainly true for me, as well.
No, no, no, no, no.
Somehow, ne, when I heard you were my companion for Homura, truly, it's really true that...
What is it, um, really when I heard the kind of acting my companion did,
that filled my heart, so I was able to do my acting well.
Really, doing Madoka☆ Magika, what is it, I always felt the depth of the acting, but...
I really didn't know what kind of presentation it'd be.
Feeling that, truly... seeing episode 10, "Ah, my companion can give such an emotionally moving feeling in her performance," I'd say.
That was the feeling.
Really, I've been continuing to do this job for about 10 years. I've done many various different works, but in all those years,
I've never been so personally taken aback by the content before.
This piece of work makes me think "Ah, I'm so glad I did this job" from the bottom of my heart — Ah, uuu...
...You know?
Then... I don't know if I can say this myself, but...
Really, I sincerely think I was able to do proper acting, and that may call more people to watch...
I've said this in a previous session, but...
Yes.
Originally for these auditions, I didn't take Homura.
That's right, ne.
So it's possible I wouldn't have done her, you know?
But, one time, Urobuchi-san asked me to please try out Homura during one of the audition sessions,
and I did Homura.
That's true for Ao-chan too, though. And I think this world couldn't have been crafted without you and me, Ao-chan.
That's right, ne.
But that's true for Mami-san too...
and Sayaka, and Kyouko too...
It's also true for QB-sama!
"Without everyone, there's no way it could have been done" is something I truly understand this time.
That's right, ne.
Mm!
That's truly right, you know.
Somehow, all of the actors truly put their souls into this, I think it's truly wonderful...
Somehow, what is it, I even got to do the main role, too...
That's right, you're the chairwoman!
But somehow, a chairwoman can't do anything at all without the people around her, I think.
No...
It's fine! Because Ao-chan is the one who's the youngest, and I'm pretty close in age with everyone else around me...
Ah, right (lol)
But, really, with Ao-chan as the chairwoman, I feel like I was able to do work with a good feeling that actually created an environment.
I've talked with Tsuruoka-san and such too, but...
Up until now, I've been a relatively young one in the workplace, so I've had many senpai around me who would lend guidance,
so I could do acting that had feeling to it, but I was mostly focused on myself;
This time, for the first time, and it's truly the first time for me:
Mmm...!
Somehow, I thought "I want to be a proper senpai"...
So then Ao-chan can be the one with the best feeling, who creates an environment with her acting.
Regarding both the Madoka who tries to escape, and the Madoka who isn't shaken up at all.
Around us, so much was changing, and yet this story was still stable.
Then, I think that sort of "creating an environment" thing is important.
I really do, and then for Ao-chan...
Since Ao-chan was around for all of this, she properly knows, really knows, that "Then, please take care of it!" was said...
Because the mutual faith thing was understood...
That's why somehow, this time, the workplace was extremely...
Somehow, since everyone around you was doing good work, you could do good work, and you respected everyone...
I really felt that. Especially here, you know.
Here, you know. From here, it's like if I didn't truly trust my companion, then I couldn't show this...
From here.
Like my own heart's filthy parts...
So I was able to do acting where many various things came out.
It's acting that I really couldn't have done if I didn't trust my companions.
So... that's what I'd say.
Right, you got completely absorbed in it, I definitely understand that.
Amazing, truly.
Somehow, mou ne,
what is it, I can't explain how to do acting, so...
That's right, ne.
This is really hard, but...
Still, probably...
This...
What to call it...
To place your voice in something and put out something that holds this kind of feeling...
It was quite the performance to put on, this time!
That's right, ne.
Somehow,
Right.
Really, overall, what is it... working on things up until now,
since I thought I really wanted to see how this develops...
Somehow, that helped at the mic a little bit, because I thought I really couldn't just put in minimal effort.
Gradually, somehow... I was able to see how Madoka saw the world...
How she interacts with things and her habits...
Somehow, what is it, that really felt like it resonated with me.
Right.
Ne?
I understand, but it's impossible to explain.
Right.
Really, I have no idea how to explain this, but...
Still, within yourself... Um, in my case, Homura.
In Ao-chan's case, she can really understand Madoka, what she's thinking and how she acts.
Yes. That's right, ne.
There are so many things like this, though...
But while we understand, we can't explain, but we understand...
That's right, ne.
and Ao-chan understands the thing to understand!
(lol) Desu!
It's quite difficult, isn't it?
Right, it's difficult.
But, surely since we couldn't do the scripting or the general presentation, I believe that the shape of our acting...
I think that is our part that we left behind.
That's why we're like one portion of the scripting and general presentation!
That's right, truly!
And I think the writers were really about to die. Really.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is especially true for animated works, and this time I definitely really think this, but...
Really, our voice becomes a life.
Lately I've been thinking about this a lot, since I've had a relatively large amount of seiyuu work...
This is true for us, and everyone around us...
However, we really are the life of a work.
Because it all comes together.
That is true for this "BAANG" effect just now, and this enemy's design too...
Ne?
and the music, too.
When everything comes together, that is when the story begins to spin. Right.
Yes.
We really are one part of that. So...
We really can't joke around too much.
That's right, ne.
That would end up coming out in our feelings.
Right, somehow...
We might end up getting complacent.
Somehow, in order to achieve that completeness, everyone didn't go to a different piece of work -
instead they focused on this, and after that, this work really prospered because of it...
Right, right, right.
Right, that's why... just a little bit ago, ne? We had a launch [party]. Um...
At the launch [party] I was able to talk with many different people.
Somehow, "Ah wow, this many people love this work?"
Right!
It was moving, ne?
Ne?
Amazing.
And everyone really likes it.
Right! Since everyone loves it, so many gathered at the launch.
That's right, ne.
Everyone was really... we greeted many girls and guys, but...
At that time, everyone was making an extremely satisfied face!
Right!
I felt so extremely thankful for it! Somehow, even the words "thank you" just wouldn't come out.
Truly.
It filled my chest with a lot, ne.
Ne?
Somehow, for us to finish a single episode, it takes around five hours or so, right?
Right.
But for the people who actually make this work, and such...
They're always writing/drawing.
They're really working so hard that they'll die.
Right, right.
Ne?
I think they're amazing, truly...
I think they're amazing. That's why,
I think that this "We'll leave the art to you" thing is extremely important.
That's right, ne.
In fact, there's so much trust. Since there's trust, you can leave things to other people.
Like this scene here, which is the climax of this episode, though...
Ah, really...
Really, starting from right here, if we were like:
～（´∀｀～） It's painful, it's difficult!
Right!
（～´∀｀）～   I'm so sad!
If we overdid this part like that...
Right, right, right.
We'd have killed this scene instantly.
Well, um, Homura has given up here, but actually Madoka has not given up.
Right.
These girls' feelings are like that.
So that kind of thing where our portrayal can actually kill the art...
That's right, ne.
Somehow, it's truly amazing, ne?
Amazing, it really makes me give my full effort.
Then, the sort of sorrow in these girls' weeping - Like, this rain, too...
Ne~?
Like, this presentation in general... Truly,
somehow, you look at many different parts of this work, don't you?
Truly.
You can feel so many different people's love...
Mm...
So, when I did this piece of work, truly, how can I say it...
It isn't about yourself, but everyone around you has a harmonious affection for such a wonderful piece of work—
Ao-chan's acting right here is the best!
No, no, no.
It's magnificent.
Truly.
Then, this facial expression is also magnificent!
Ne? This—
I thought "It's this facial expression!?"
Right.
Um...
These character designs began with Ume-sensei, so these were faces that weren't even imaginable to me...
It was truly shocking.
Right.
Somehow, it's like it really hurts to see cute things suffering.
That's right.
They're making faces that are really in a struggle, so...
Ne?
Mm.
Right. Somehow, they're struggling and in pain...
"How did they draw this?" is what I think about.
Then, this request of hers is quite intensely hard, isn't it?
This request is intensely hard!
I thought this was amazing, she's behaving like a spoiled child and relying on Homura-chan's kindness.
No, no, no!
This is amazing!
I thought that.
But I sort of think that Homura is also very happy here.
Ah, because from Homura-chan's standpoint, this is sort of... I see!
Because—
Somehow, she's being depended on. For Homura, she was always the one depending on others. So now Madoka is depending on her.
I see...
That's why...
It's something that she doesn't want to do, but it also has that other aspect to it.
Ah, this part, this... this scream hurts ;_;
I actually said this during the Official Guidebook interview just a little bit ago, though...
So this might be a little bit redundant. At least, Ao-chan already knows. But really...
That "Uuu!" scream... Um, really, it's probably a scream where your voice just cannot come out...
Then, what made me really happy was that Tsuruoka-san said "Don't add any SEs here."
I was truly happy. They were completely leaving it up to my voice. In the script there was probably an SE like "Bang!" there,
for them to say "erase the sound that we added, please"...
It was like "Ah, I've trusted everyone so much, and now everyone is putting trust in me," this feeling was very happy.
It's true for Homura who will continue her fight too, though...
I think like "It really was okay to depend on other people!"
That's right, truly, um...
Because I was able to feel everyone's power, I was able to do my acting. That is wonderful, I think.
Yes, that's right.
Right. Somehow, earlier, at the part where Madoka depends on Homura-chan to do that request,
For me, I thought that Madoka trusted and loved Homura-chan, but...
it was the part where she acted most like a spoiled child depending on others.
I thought it was something like that, but...
When you told me that Homura-chan was happy to be depended on, I thought "Amazing!"
I was taken aback!
Ah, I see, I see, I see.
Right, Madoka was surely like "Ah, I'm sorry Homura-chan, I have to leave everything to you る↑"
That's what I thought myself, so...
Then, just now, when Homura-chan says she won't let Madoka fight from now on...
I thought, so...
Right, right.
Right now, I'm actually very much relieved.
Ah, really?
It's like that.
But um, the ending too, at the very end... Really...
That's right, ne.
Since Madoka had faith in herself, that made Homura quite happy.
That's what I think.
So...
I see!
Like right now, she's in the most difficult position she can possibly be in, and yet she's still concerned about Madoka.
The extent that Homura is concerned for Madoka makes her an extremely strong person, I think...
Strong.
It's wonderful to think in another person's interest so much... Really, that's
"Because they are friends!" I think.
Mm.
Somehow, it's a bond of love so strong that they just won't break and fall to nothing, so...
Right, right.
It's amazing. Probably, it's also a different thing from a feeling of ren-ai (romantic love), I think.
It's different from that, ne.
They are friends, so the fact that they think in the interest of their companion this much...
Because, if it was ren-ai they'd probably think of themselves a little bit more, like "Return her to me!"
That's right, ne.
Ah, this! Right here, Tsuruoka-san erased the SE.
During episode 1, there was a "piro!"
Right.
That was there.
That's right.
Right, right.
Ahhh. It's no good...
Truly. It's difficult, ne.
Really for me, I think this especially about Madoka☆ Magika, but...
Homura and Madoka, during the second half, the length of their long lines gradually increases...
That's right, ne.
We didn't really do very many retakes.
We didn't do many.
There are times when our emotions went into harmony [with the characters], and times when they might not've, but...
But it was a very... unedited-ish feeling.
They just let us do things with our feelings, and then made selections for lines based off of that.
That's right, ne.
Somehow, really, that... no matter how many retakes you do, it won't change how you feel, so...
The fact they didn't break our flow at all, it was like everyone was so careful, I think...
That's right, ne~
Somehow, it was amazing. I truly think of it as amazing.
Right.
That's why it really feels like... we engraved ourselves! (lol) It really has that feeling.
Ne~?
Truly!
Everything was done satisfactorily!
That's right!
Right!
And everyone was able to watch that...
Right.
That makes me the happiest, you know!
Right,
the happiest.
Really,
No matter how hard I think I try, no matter what I try to convey, if people didn't accept and appreciate it, it'd have no meaning.
Somehow, it's like it gives the powerless me some meaning in all of it.
It makes me so happy.
I'm truly happy I was able to do Homura—
(lol)
This part is amazing, huh?
I feel so extremely happy to be connected with this piece of work...
I really think that, so...
And, everything we did went directly into the normal dialogue.
That's right, ne.
It isn't something we can really say, but the fact that everyone is able to feel our acting means everything to us.
So, when various people give us their various feelings, it moves our hearts too.
Yes.
Mm.
Mou, this part, you know... Truly...
For me, this part... I really love this person.
I think it's extremely nice how everything is done for another person's circumstances.
It's really like, "Precious friends are nice, huh?"
It's nice, huh?
Mmm!
Truly... I'm so glad I was able to participate in this, I think.
I'm so glad, right.
I really think that this will have "defined" a lot of things in my life.
This is a really big fragment, I think—
Then here, they add the opening!
That's right!
For me, for the first time in ages—Or, perhaps even for the first time ever...
"I think it'd be nice to sing this!" I thought.
I even told Iwakami-san, "I want to sing Connect!"
He said, "No, that's okay, Saitou." though (lol)
(lol)
We're ClariS!
Right, right, right, "I want to sing with Ao-chan!"
We're ClariS...
Sorry about that.
Putting this here was really moving, wasn't it?
It was truly moving.
Really in the beginning I thought this song was about Madoka,
then after ep10 I thought it was about Homura-chan,
then after seeing the end I thought it was about Madoka again!
That's right, isn't it...
Yes...
Somehow, it's really deep, isn't it?
Really, when you look at the whole thing overall, there are just too many deep things...
That's right.
I think I want to watch it again.
Right, me too!
Especially when you look at the whole thing, watching from ep3 all the way until ep10-11-12...
Then the fact that everyone has watched it!
It makes me truly happy!
I'm glad this really became a true masterpiece.
Right, right.
Since I have confidence, I can really give it my all now!
Really, everyone gave it their all to craft this...
Yeah!
To receive everyone's love, I am very happy!
Mm.
That's why, please. Watch the next episode!
Watch the next episode!
Watch until episode 11.
Right!
If you do, you'll be able to see Homura-chan's feelings!
You'll be able to see another different thing!
Yes! So then...
Thank you very much!