Okay! Well then, try a self-introduction!
U–Um... I'm A–Akemi H–Homura...
Um, er... I request that you please treat me well...
Akemi-san has been hospitalized for a long time because of a heart disease.
Akemi Homura
This is the first time she's come to school in a while, so many things might be confusing.
Everyone help her out, okay?
Akemi-san, where did you go to school before?
Were you in any clubs or anything?
Sports clubs? Cultural clubs?
Your hair is really long, you know!
Isn't it troublesome to do every morning?
Um, I–I'm, er...
Akemi-san.
You have to go to the school infirmary, right?
Do you know the location?
Eh?
No...
Then, I'll lead you!
I'm the health officer, after all.
I'm sorry, everyone!
Akemi-san has to go to the school infirmary to take medication during break time.
Ah, is that so?
Sorry that we kept you.
Akemi-san, see you later, okay?
I'm sorry.
No one has bad intentions, but...
Something like a transfer student is really rare, so they're cheerful!
No, um...
Thank you very much.
You don't have to be so nervous!
We're classmates, after all!
I'm Kaname Madoka.
Call me Madoka!
That's...
It's fine!
So, may I call you Homura-chan, too?
I, um... haven't been called by my given name very often...
It's a really weird name...
Eh? Such a thing isn't true!
Somehow, you know... it has a feeling of being really fired up, and I think it's cool!
I'm losing to my name.
That sort of thing is wasteful!
After all, since you already have a wonderful name,
Homura-chan, it's fine for you to be cool too!
f(x) is defined by... Calculate:
Given that p is a prime number, and n an arbitrary natural number,
prove that (1+p)^p - n^p -1 is divisible by p.
So then, how about trying this problem?
Right, you had a leave of absence, didn't you?
You should borrow notes from a friend.
Anemia brought on just by warm-up exercises is pretty bad, you know.
After constantly sleeping in bed for half a year, there's no helping it, is there?
Homura-chan, it's fine for you to be cool too!
That's impossible... I can't do anything.
I only burden people with trouble. It's shameful.
Why is that...?
From now on, will I... always stay like this?
In that case, it's fine to just die, you know.
I wonder if it's fine to just die...
Right... it's fine if you just end up dead.
End up... dead...
W–Where is this...?
What?
What is that!?
No...
That was a close call, wasn't it?
It's all right now, Homura-chan!
Y–You two are...
Those two are magical girls.
They are those who hunt witches.
Our secret was exposed all of a sudden, wasn't it?
Keep it a secret from everyone in our class!★
Tomoe
Mami
Kaname-san...
Do you always fight with those things?
Hmm, "always"?
Well, Mami-san is a veteran, but...
As for someone like me, I just made a contract with Kyubey last week.
But the style you fought with today was much more skillful than before, Kaname-san.
You have peace of mind?
You're... not scared?
I don't have peace of mind, and I'm scared too, but...
when you beat a witch, that alone saves a lot of people.
It's worth doing, you know.
Kaname-san needs to persevere so she can grow and stand on her own before Walpurgis Night comes.
Well then, I'll come back, okay?
That's...
Tomoe-san has died, yet...
That's why.
Now, Walpurgis Night can only be stopped...
By me alone.
It's impossible! You can't win against such a thing by yourself!
Kaname-san, even you are going to die!
Still, I am a magical girl, after all.
That means that I must protect everyone.
Hey...
Let's run away...
Because there's just no helping it...
No one will resent you, Kaname-san...
Homura-chan.
You know, I'm happy I became friends with you.
When you were suddenly attacked by a witch, I made it just in time...
Even now I take pride in that.
That's why I'm truly glad I became a magical girl.
That's what I think.
Kaname-san...
Farewell, Homura-chan.
Stay well.
No!
Don't go!
Kaname-san!!!
Why...
You understood you were going to die, and yet...
Rather than save someone like me, you should have...
I wanted you to live, instead...
Are those words true? Akemi Homura.
Would you wager your soul for the sake of that prayer?
If you have a desire you want fulfilled, even if it means accepting a fate of battle...
I will give you power.
If I form a contract with you, any kind of wish can be granted?
That is correct.
You have the necessary qualifications.
Please enlighten me.
By using any prayer you desire, will you make a Soul Gem shine?
I...
I want to redo my meeting with Kaname-san.
Rather than being the me whom she will protect...
I want to become the me who will protect her!
The contract has been formed.
Your prayer has surpassed entropy.
Now, you may release it. That newfound power!
This place is...
Discharge
Mitakihara
Middle School!
I... still haven't been discharged from the hospital...
Entrance Guide
It wasn't a dream...
Okay! Well then, try a self-introduction!
I'm Akemi Homura. Please treat me well.
Akemi-san has been hospitalized for a long time—
Kaname-san, I became a magical girl too!
From now on, let's do our best together!
Eh? Um...
Well then, here I go!
What do you think, Mami-san?
Halting time, is it?
It is certainly amazing, but the problem is how to use it, you know.
how  to  create
explosives
Mami-san! Right now!
Okay!
Akemi-san, please!
Y–Yes!
Hooray?
Hooray...!
Hooray!!!
Amazing!
Well done.
That was amazing, Homura-chan!
What's wrong?
Hey, Kaname-san? Hang on!
Why...
What?
Why is... such a thing...
Discharge
Mitakihara
Middle School!
I have to tell them...
Everyone is being deceived by Kyubey!
Uh, look here...
Just how exactly would Kyubey benefit from telling us lies like that?
That is...
Do you want to cause an internal struggle by planting strange ideas in our heads?
It couldn't be that, in reality, you're an accomplice of that girl called Kyouko or whatever, right?
T–That's not it!
Sayaka-chan, what you're doing now is creating an internal struggle.
Either way, I'm opposed to forming a team with this girl.
Madoka and Mami-san use projectile weapons, so they might be fine with it, but...
Suddenly having explosions and such appear in front of my face...
I'd want a little relief from that, you know.
How many times will I get caught in the middle of them?
Akemi-san, I wonder, do you have any weapons other than explosives?
(Ltd)
I'll think about it a little bit...
What the hell are you!?
What'd you do to Sayaka!?
Sayaka-chan, stop it!
Please, remember!
You wouldn't do something like this, Sayaka-chan!
Sorry, Miki-san...
Sayaka... Damn it...
This kind of thing is...
Awful...
This sort of thing is just too much...
Tomoe-san!?
If Soul Gems give birth to witches...
Everyone has no choice but to die, right!?
You and I both!
Stop it!
No more...
No more, already...
This is just...
It's all right.
Why don't the two of us persevere?
Shall we bring down Walpurgis Night together?
We're... both finished now, aren't we?
Do you have any Grief Seeds?
I see.
Hey... If we were to stay like this, and become monsters together...
Would you like to make a mess of anything and everything in this world?
All of the unpleasant things and all of the sad things...
Until they're all wiped from existence,
we'll destroy, destroy, and destroy more...
If we did that... don't you think it'd be nice?
I lied just before.
I had a single one that I saved.
That's...
Why did you give it to me!?
Because I want to request something that I can't do but you can, Homura-chan.
Homura-chan, you can return to the past, right?
You've said you can change history so that an ending like this never happens, right?
Before Kyubey deceives my idiotic self, I wonder if you could save me...
I promise you.
I'll absolutely show you salvation.
No matter how many times I have to repeat this, I won't fail to show you protection!
I'm glad...
Could I depend on you... for just one more thing?
Yeah.
I... don't want to become a witch.
Even though there are unpleasant and sad things...
There are still so many things... in this world that I want to protect...
Madoka!
Homura-chan, you finally called me by my given name, didn't you...?
I'm happy...
No one... will believe the future.
No one... will endure and stop the future.
Then...
I will...
W–Who's there?
Madoka.
If something appears, then approaches you, promising a miracle...
You must never do as it says.
Eh?
Um...
I won't depend on anyone anymore.
It isn't necessary for me to make anyone understand anymore.
Madoka will not fight anymore.
All of the witches will be finished by me alone.
And this time...
Walpurgis Night will, by this hand...!
Awful...
It can't be helped.
It's too heavy a burden for that girl alone.
That's too much! Such a thing shouldn't happen!
Madoka, you mustn't lend your ears to its words!
If you give up, that's as far as you'll get.
But if it's you, fate can change.
This seemingly unavoidable destruction, and this grief...
It's fine for you to overturn all of it.
Because for that reason, you are endowed with power.
Is that true?
Don't be deceived! That's what it wants!
Can a person like me... really do something?
Can I change this outcome?
Of course!
So form a contract with me...
...and become a magical girl!
Don't!!!
That was quite astonishing, huh? Transformed Madoka, that is.
If it was her, then I predicted that she'd become the strongest magical girl, but...
By no means did I expect that Walpurgis Night to be defeated in one shot, you know.
The possibility of that result... surpassed your expectations?
Later or sooner, the conclusion would be the same.
As the strongest magical girl, she defeated the greatest enemy.
Of course, after that, she has no choice but to become the worst witch.
If it's the current Madoka, she's likely to annihilate this star within 10 days or so, don't you think?
Well, that's a problem for you guys, humanity.
Our energy collection quota goal is mostly complete, you know.
You're not going to fight?
No...
My battlefield is not here.
Akemi Homura...
Are you—
Repeat it.
I'll repeat it as many times as necessary.
I'll cycle through the same section of time as much as necessary, searching for the one and only exit.
The path to saving you from a fate of despair.
Madoka... the one single person... who is my friend...
Homura-chan?
For you...
If it's for your sake...
Even if I'm imprisoned in this maze for eternity...
I do not mind.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったら
なくした未来を
The future I had
lost at some point...
私ここでまた
見ることできるの？
will I be able
to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing
shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いて
この世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as
necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた
時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of
time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged
feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した
未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the
future where I'll start running
難しい道で
立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill
on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さで
いつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for
me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 10
I Won't Depend On Anyone Anymore
While watching over those girls for so long, did you feel nothing at all?
The pain everyone was going through... did you try to understand it at all?
Episode 11
The Final Guidepost Left
The final guidepost left.
Subtitle notes, runes, and extras @ http://tri4.net