Oh no!
That sound...
What's wrong?
Dela?
That's the first time I've seen a bird fall down a staircase.
Long time no see, Dela.
Earthquakes, lightning, wildfires, wild fathers...
There are many terrifying things in this world.
This girl hails from an island to the south, and she's scarier than a demon!
She makes my blood run cold.
However, what is a man if not for his courage?
Hey there, Choi.
Did you long to see me that badly?
What's this? You've gotten a lot cockier since the last time I saw you.
My apologies!
And what the hell happened to you?!
You're big enough to have your own timezone!
Indeed! I put on a little too much weight!
You're not even a bird anymore!
Dela's...
It's as you say!
...in big trouble!
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
You gave me a place to sleep and even provided me with food.
I'm terribly sorry.
Did you sleep well?
I did.
Thanks to your generosity.
We have a bunch of stuff in that room,
so it was probably a bit cramped, right?
Sorry about that.
Don't be!
I turned up on your doorstep without warning, and you still gave me a place to stay, so I'm very grateful.
What a polite gal.
Aren't you gonna eat?
The food's gonna get cold, Dela.
Well, if you insist...
Let's see—
No! I couldn't possibly!
You're gonna eat later, then?
Has Dela been rude to you at all?
Not at all!
Really?!
That's right, Lady Choi.
Is Choi your name?
Or surname?
It's my name.
What's yer surname, then?
Mochidis Gusting.
Dad...
I'm Choi Mochidis Gusting.
I guess I can live with that.
Is the bird yours?
No.
Dela's a royal pet.
Wow.
So what Dela said was true!
The island I'm from has been ruled by the Mochidis Gusting family for generations.
Oh yeah, I saw you on film.
Along with that boy.
Boy?
You mean the prince?
You're a princess?!
Hey, Anko!
Sorry.
I am but a fortune-teller.
I use the royal bird to tell fortunes during my country's festivals or important ceremonies.
I see. Augury, eh?
Indeed.
I am a royal bird.
A royal...
...bird...
I can't augur anything when you're that fat!
Forgive me!
Episode 7
She Became A Bride!
Anyway, I'm heading off.
Please take care.
What's a "club"?
Here I was, thinking he was just some strange bird,
but he really did belong to a royal family?
I thought he made it all up.
He came here from an island to the south, apparently.
Did Choi have any amazing treasures on her?
Gold, silver, jewelry...
She's not a pirate, you know.
Apparently, she's a fortune-teller.
A fortune-teller?
What about Dela?
She says she tells fortunes using Dela.
That's kinda hardcore.
She came in search of a bride for her prince, or so I hear.
All the way to this eastern country.
This is useless!
I can't augur at all like this!
I'm so sorry about everything!
I didn't come here expecting to be reunited with a miniature blimp!
Of course not! This is all... my... fault!
The prince was worried sick because you didn't contact us at all, you know!
Even though we sent you so many messages!
You did?
My communications system seems to be malfunctioning!
What?!
Did a circuit break somewhere?
What's wrong?!
Dela.
Dela!
Do you think our messages are reaching Dela, Choi?
Yes, they should be.
Wake up, Dela.
Huh?
So we can't contact you unless you're unconscious?
I wonder what's wrong.
I guess I'm a little out of whack...
It's because I suffered such rough treatment in an unfamiliar land.
Didn't you leave in search of a bride for the prince?!
Why were you lazing around in a place like this, anyway?!
That's...
They fell in love with me and wouldn't allow me to leave!
They kept saying, "You're planning on leaving after all we've done for you?"
What?
And they worked me like a horse!
Uh...
At that mochi shop!
They did?
And yet you're this fat?
Well, uh...
Oh!
They made me eat a ton of mochi!
They played the "You sayin' our mochi's not good enough fer ya?" card.
That's how I became too fat to fly.
And then I couldn't escape!
A trap, huh?
Who was it?
Huh?
Who trapped you?!
Uh...
'Twas the girl from the mochi shop.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Where's Choi?
She said she'd do some cleaning as thanks for taking care of her.
I knew it. She couldn't sleep too well.
Sorry. Did I wake you?
You can take a nap on the second floor, Choi.
I couldn't possibly!
Your father and grandfather wouldn't accept any money,
so I thought I'd repay the favor by working instead.
But that sound was much too pleasant...
And I dozed off.
Hey, Dela, wake up!
I'm so very sorry!
Oh yeah, have you eaten lunch?
Not yet.
You needn't answer!
Yes, ma'am!
I haven't either, so how about we eat together?
Oh yeah! How about some mochi?
Wrapped in seaweed, maybe?
Don't want any.
Huh?
I don't want any mochi.
Do you...
hate mochi?
I don't even know, but I do know I don't want any!
I see.
Oh yeah! Then...
Where are we headed?
I thought maybe we could get some udon noodles.
U-Udon?
Oh, Tamako!
I hear that girl is one of Dela's acquaintances.
That's right.
Isn't she cute?
What's your name?
Huh?
Uh...
Lady Ch-Choi.
My, good for you, Dela!
Someone you know came to visit!
Then, as a welcoming gift...
Here's a croquette!
It's delicious.
Try it out.
No thanks!
They fattened up Dela so much that he couldn't fly, and now they're going after me too!
Huh?
Oh no, it's nothing!
Tamako!
I heard she came from a distant island to the south?
Really?
Hello.
She smells like the south.
What kinda scent is that?
How admirable for one so small to travel so far!
Please take this, if you'd like.
Huh?
Here's a great game to kill some time with.
Try this mochi that's totally better than Tamaya's!
Heave-ho.
Thanks a lot, everyone!
Did you all ensnare Dela like this?
Ensnare?
No! Don't let it bother you, sir!
I will not be deceived!
She's been through a lot despite being so young, hasn't she?
It brings a tear to my eye!
It's all right!
The people here are all good folk.
So take it easy for a while!
Oh, Choi's apparently a fortune-teller!
My, really?
What kind of fortune-telling?
Tell a fortune for us!
Dela.
Yes, ma'am!
Huh? You're going to use the bird to tell a fortune?
That's right.
Go for it, Dela!
White...
A huge, white beast will soon descend upon this place!
White?
Beast?
Mao!
Wait!
That dog...
That's Mao, the dog who often comes here on walks, right?
A huge, white beast...
She nailed it!
Amazing!
You're quite good!
That's the first time I've seen anything like it!
All right! I'm going to practice too!
Practice some restraint instead.
It was right...
So it was right...
Usa Bath
How nice.
I want my fortune told too.
Maybe she can tell me what questions will come up in my next exam?
I normally don't tell fortunes outside a state ceremony!
Oh...
Oh, welcome!
Good evening!
Oh, right!
This is Choi. She's currently staying with us!
I heard.
I've heard your fortunes are really accurate!
You put the clothes you take off in this basket.
I'm sure you're tired.
Let's take a nice, relaxing bath!
I mustn't be deceived.
I mustn't be deceived!
I mustn't be...
I really wasn't expecting Lady Choi to come all the way here.
I do wonder how she found this place.
Choi's fortunes are terrifying.
Let the water come up to your shoulders, Anko.
Oho.
Wait!
What if Lady Choi caught me?!
Guess I should sit tight today.
Can't hurt to listen, though!
Tamako.
I'm getting out soon.
Huh?
Where's Choi?
She must've gotten out before us.
You think?
Huh? Choi's not here.
There's no way she'd go home without us, right?
Lady Choi!
What's wrong, Dela?!
Are those...
...peaches?
Nope!
Choi!
Tamako Market
I've never been so humiliated in my life!
I can't possibly apologize enough!
It's all because you decided to come here!
Yes, ma'am!
You're completely right! I understand!
Do you really understand?!
Choi?
Are you okay?
Leave me alone!
All right.
I'll leave your dinner here, okay?
Wait! This could be a trap as well!
I must be on my guard more!
Augury
Wow.
When did this turn into a fortune-telling shop?
What's wrong with that?
Everyone looks like they're having fun.
You will incur the wrath of the earth very soon.
Oh no! How frightening!
But it's not that big a deal.
Oh, that's a relief.
Thanks, Choi.
Ouch!
It's the wrath of the earth!
She was right again!
Amazing!
Lady Choi...
Should you really be telling this many fortunes?
I'm doing this to get you back in shape.
Besides...
Fortune-tellers are amazing!
I have to repay them for everything they gave me yesterday.
I'm deeply moved!
Maybe I should become one too.
Um...
Could I have my fortune told as well?
I don't mind.
Actually, um...
What is it?
No, er...
Are you in love?
No, um... er...
Oh, so he had someone he liked?
What a smooth criminal.
For real?!
But unfortunately, it'll die unrequited.
Oh, wow!
The fortune-telling's really popular!
Sayuri...
Could I get my fortune told too?
You could...
Um, can you predict compatibility?
Compatibility?
You mean with a loved one?
Huh?
What?
Did you find someone nice, Sayuri?
This is a huge shock.
I'm just kidding.
There's someone I'm thinking of marrying...
Oh!
This day has finally come!
Congrats, Sayuri!
Thanks!
We gotta have a party tonight!
Better bring some booze!
You don't get to drink!
No way...
Marriage...
I'm back!
T-T-Tamako!
What're they up to over there?
Tamako...
What do you think about m-marriage...
Hey, Tamako!
What's going on?
Sayuri's getting married.
What? Really?
Wow!
It's not that big a deal.
And to think, she used to be this tiny little kid...
I see a gentle wind and calm waves.
Huh?
A tranquil relationship.
Thank goodness.
That's great. Choi's fortunes are accurate,
right?
Right!
Choi's fortunes are incredibly accurate!
What's with you, Mochizou?
Sayuri.
I hope you'll be happy.
Thanks.
So who else is getting their fortune told?
Me! Pick me!
Wasn't it my turn next?
Yeah, after this one!
What?
Be careful not to stay in too long tonight.
Okay, Choi?
I merely let my guard down yesterday!
I remember capsizing when I was little too!
Temporarily
closed
We apologize for the inconvenience
Usa
Bath
I guess they're all still in shock.
Hey, guys!
What's wrong?
It says they're closed today.
Huh?
Sayuri's their only daughter...
Yup.
They must be feeling really lonely now.
Hm?
Guess we should just use our own bath today.
Right.
Bye.
See ya!
Choi!
Um...
Thanks for telling such a great fortune.
I'm sure Sayuri felt really relieved.
Bye.
Choi, you okay?
I'm coming in!
Choi—
Choi?!
Choi!
Prince!
Lady Choi!
Oh, Lady Choi!
What's Dela doing here?!
I'm sorry!
Apologies won't cut it! What're you—
Lady Choi?!
Lady Choi!
How's Choi?
Looks like she's got a fever.
The fatigue musta caught up with her.
Also...
She's been crying in her sleep.
She keeps mumbling about not being able to hear the waves.
Tamako.
Hm?
Don't worry about your chores.
Take good care of her.
Okay!
Um, I'm sorry about all of this.
Shh!
Can you hear it?
It's the sound of the waves.
The owner of the record store recommended this song to me.
Hey, my girl!
This isn't like my country's music at all!
It's a lot merrier and more classical—
Hey!
Shut up, Dela!
Yes, ma'am!
You lied to me, didn't you?!
You said you were ensnared in a trap!
Well, I never went as far as to call it a trap...
I'm going to report everything to the prince!
Please, anything but that!
What "trap"?
You just fattened yourself up!
No, that's not... totally incorrect, but—
You just admitted it!
I couldn't help it!
Choi...
The mochi here is just so delectable!
She got better!
Your excuses won't work!
A wind blows, heralding the onset of autumn.
The seasons come and go, always changing.
However, there are things that will forever remain unchanged.
Thank you very much!
She might become a bride,
but tofu will always be square.
It's tofu because it's square.
Choi!
Are you okay being up and about?
Yes.
I'm feeling a lot better, thanks to you.
What's this?
Oh.
This is the mochi we're going to give out at Sayuri's wedding.
We're making samples to figure out what shape we want it to be.
Red and white?
They're the colors we use for auspicious occasions here.
They're freshly made.
Want to try some?
Oh, you didn't want any mochi, did you?
No, I'll have some.
Really?
Then try this one!
H-How is it?
Mochi is... delicious!
That's it! That's perfect!
Our family may be named Mochidis Gusting, but Mochidel Icious!
Hey! Stop stuffing your face!
You stop eating!
How long can you stay here, Choi?
I'm sorry, but I was hoping I could stay here until the communications system gets fixed.
Usagiyama Market
Home-made side-dishes
What? It'd be nice if it never got fixed, then.
But then that'd get in the way of our search for the prince's bride.
A bride, huh?
Are you looking for anything in particular?
That's...
I knew it! This scent!
Choi?
Hm?
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
Looks like autumn's upon us.
Tamako here.
If you're wondering why red and white are auspicious colors in Japan, it originates from an ancient battle
where the Genji clan hoisted white flags and the Heike clan red ones.
They give off a celebratory feel, don't they?
Episode 8    I Won't Let Them Call Me a Chicken!
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?