The Black Rose Baron is...
My sister!?
It's a bit stuffy.
My, a little frog and Cat. Good afternoon.
Hiya.
Are you going to tell that today, mya?
Tell? About what?
"Should we stop it already?"
That! That!
What? What?
Oh, come on…
"Should we stop it already!?"
Remember, mya?
Tonberry!
Just now, Satsuki was saying to me...
about what "Caviar of the field" is.
I have to tell her!
How much more of an air-head can she be?
Better be afraid of her, Nekane Springfield.
Bonjerin.
Yeah, yeah...
"There are people who like to expose secrets!"
By Chisame.
Chiu Chiu is also angry!
Pun pu~n!
By Chiu.
I see. So you guys know now.
Aniki…
Oneechan is... the Baron
Evangeline-san.
Too bad it isn't your father.
Takahata-sensei, you knew it all along?
Sorry for keeping quiet about it.
I think Nekane-san has her reasons to do so, as well.
It’s the same.
So you think so too?
Eh?
Well, in fact, I made the mistake of telling everyone about it,
so it spread out through the whole class, so I asked Secchan to help me.
I've been able to ask everyone to keep quiet about this in front of Nekane-san.
I also think there is a reason to hide all this, too.
So Nekane-san herself, is not aware that everyone knows.
Yeah. I don't think she realizes it yet.
That's a relief.
Perhaps Nekane is following a chain of dark events.
She probably knows what's behind all this.
What's behind all this?
Could it be, it has something to do with the Star Crystal?
The Star Crystal? I don't know about that.
What is clear, is that she is hiding...
something that has to do with you.
It’s got something to do with Negi, but I don't know what.
She is in such disguise, because she can’t say…
If she disguises herself, she can be with Negi.
She probably worries about him, and cannot leave him alone
So, Nekane-san's true identity being revealed must have been a miscalculation.
But since she's discovered, there's no way for her to deceive anymore.
This is why all of us must continue to expect anything.
If that's the case...
What should we do from now on?
I think not doing anything would be better.
When it is time to reveal everything, Nekane will reveal it herself.
I think that whatever it is that Nekane-kun isn't telling us,
it should be left to her for now.
Well, I think that decision of hers is too kind.
I understand.
I'll wait until my sister tells me about it.
Then, I’ll tell everyone in the class.
I’ll leave that to you.
Anyway, sensei...
Hmm? What is it, Konoka-kun?
Before dinner, it's better that you don't eat ramen.
Itadakimasu!
This is good!
It's good isn't it, Hakase-san?
Uh, yeah.
I want the Black Rose Baron to try this, too...
That was close...
Luckily, you're around.
Asuna?
Oh my, Asuna-chan.
Nekane-san, is it tasty?
It is!
It’s the Japanese taste, isn’t it?
Yeah!
Do you want seconds?
I believe so!
By the way, do you like the Black Rose Baron?
Eh? The Black Rose Baron?
Yeah. The Black Rose Baron.
Yes, I like him.
I thought so!
He's cool eh?
Yeah! That's right!
Asuna!!!
HEY!! Hold it! Hold it!!!
Onee-chan, is the Oden good?
Ah, Negi! Yep! It’s good alright!
Ah, is that right? That's good.
What is it? You're being weird Negi...
In the nick of time...
That air-headed girl.
The father’s head compared to the daughter's is slightly the same?
Two points.
That's intense. Then, the father's is slightly the same?
Don't say unneccesary things, thanks.
Gosh, what were you thinking, Asuna?
Huh? What?
Don't "what" us!
What are you angry about?
Haven't you been told already?
Don't talk about the Baron in front of Nekane-san!
It’s alright now, but if she realizes it, what are we going to do?
It’s alright!
She won't notice with just that!
It’s not alright at all!
What do you want to talk to her about?
Well, I just want to get closer to her.
Closer to her?
It's okay! It's okay!
Really, it’s not okay at all!
The two of you really worry too much...
Asuna-san...
Anyway, I was in the middle of dinner so...
Hold on a second!
Asuna!
Please be quiet about it, okay?
It’s for Negi's sake, also!
Yeah. I know, I know...
She doesn't understand.
That person doesn't understand!!
Yeah true, but what can we do?
Ah! That's right!
Eh? Me and Asuna-kun?
Yeah Takahata-sensei, the only person who can stop Asuna is you!
Right now,  Negi-sensei and the rest told Asuna not to say anything unneccesary.
But, doing that never seems to work.
But, how am I going to stop her?
Asuna has the habit of forgetting about other things...
when she is in the middle of doing something.
In other words, if Asuna is interested in you, then she might stop talking about Nekane-san.
Erm, then please tell me again. Why me?
Because Asuna likes you!
Eh!?
Though, it ended around Year 2.
But she suddenly became interested in Chupacabras.
Oh yeah, Chupacabras.
Then, her attention shifted to the Bonge-Bonge, and now to Nekane-san.
Bonge-Bonge!?
A creature that occasionally roams the area. It's around 10 meters high.
Ah! Catherine, huh?
Catherine!?
That's what Evangeline and I call it.
Catherine.
I shall take a memo.
Secchan, what are you planning to do taking a memo?
Sorry, recently I've been forgetting a lot of things.
Err, that's not what I mean.
Um, don't worry about me. Please continue.
Ugh, sometimes I just don't understand you, Secchan.
Owh, darn! I accidentally used hiragana to write the letter “n”!
Anyway, Takahata-sensei.
I'll leave it to you to protect Nekane-san's secret!
The Night Duty room has been transformed into Nekane's room magically!
It’s wonderful!
Wonderful job, Nee-san!
It's the same as the room in Wales!
Isn't it nostalgic, Negi?
Yeah!
Hmm? Is that right?
Asuna-san, what are you doing?
I'm just doing a little...
A little what?
As expected, it was never meant to be easy to locate.
Stop it! Asuna-san!
What are you looking for?
Ah. Nothing. Don't worry about me.
Oh, is that right? Then I shall not worry.
Onee-chan!!
Ah! Found you!
Asuna! Negi-kun! Come here for a bit!
What are you doing? That was such a good place!
What do you mean that was such a good place?
You shouldn't go through other peoples' rooms!
Anyway, Konoka-san, you called us here for...
Ready?
Yep! All set!
Alright then, we'll leave the rest to you.
Huh?
Let’s go, Negi-kun!
U... Uh, right!
Hey, hey wait a minute! What are you doing? Hey Konoka!
Oh! Is that Asuna-kun over there?
Eh?
Hey.
Takahata-sensei.
So, thats what this is all about.
With this, if we can revive Asuna-san's thoughts about Takahata-sensei,
then it will be alright! Mission Complete!
We must complete this!
Do your best! Takahata-sensei!
Huh?
Evangeline-san! Chachamaru-san!
When did you!?
We know what's going on.
Please don't worry... in a good way.
Huh! That's my line!
Please be quiet. In a good way.
Argh! You said it not once, but twice!
What a sudden turn of events!
What could have happened anyway!?
CM!
Oh, a fly.
What the hell, that gave me a fright.
Did that hurt?
Well, it’s alright. Not.
Yeah, it’s a bit painful...
Heh. I'm sorry.
What the hell. A fly?
That frightened me...
But, the mood is still around!
Takahata-sensei! Keep going!
It's a good night isn't it, Asuna-kun?
Wow! Look over there. The moon's beautiful.
Hey, sensei...
Did you know that Nekane-san is the Black Rose Baron?
E-Err, yeah.
That was a surprise, eh?
How someone so cool got exposed?
What do you think, sensei?
Err, yeah. That's right.
That Baron costume, I wonder if she made it herself, or did she buy it?
Where is the mood, anyway?
Asuna is obsessed with the Baron.
In a good way!
This is not when you use that.
This is bad.
This is bad, Ojou-sama!
Do your best, Takamichi!
We failed.
We can't change Asuna's feelings.
Ojou-sama?
That means...
This mission has ended.
All personnel retreat!
I wonder if we should ask Nekane-san herself? Sensei?
I'm not sure about that...
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS!?
How is it, Negi-kun?
Is the Bonge-Bonge around?
No!
It doesn't look like it's here, Aniki...
Yeah...
Negative!
Is that right...?
So, the Bonge Bonge is not around.
Ojou-sama, you might be right about being able to get Asuna-san...
to get into something else when the Bonge Bonge arrives, but...
Even if we walked around like we in the Walking Club used to,
it might be impossible to find it too, de gozaru.
It's not there!
Desu!
Even the traps did not catch anything.
Desu.
That strange thing wanders about aimlessly all the time...
It was always appearing close by when we didn't really need it to be, aru.
Now when we want it to be here it just isn't here, aru.
It’s acting like someone whom you’ve just confessed to.
Huh? Am I mistaken?
No, not really...
Wow, how deep, just like an adult!
As expected from our ghost nee-san!
Plenty of experience, isn’t it?
Err, no, that’s not it...
Sayo-chan! Can I admire you?
Anyway, the Bonge-Bonge is difficult to catch isn't it? Ojou-sama?
There isn't anything else we can do.
Let’s give up on the Bonge-Bonge Mission.
Eh? Giving up already?
It would be dangerous if Asuna opens her mouth.
Let’s try and get to Nekane-san as quickly as possible, de gozaru!
I'm not finished yet.
If we can't use the Bonge-Bonge, let’s try other ways!
Eh? There are other ways to do it?
There is still one way!
Asuna's last obsession!
The Chupacabra?
Bingo!
Chupacabra!?
In this world?
Now that you mention it, we haven't seen it.
We didn't see it!
De gozaru!
It's not here, is it?
De gozaru.
Ojou-sama, how are we going to use something that isn't here?
There is a way! I made an order to Hakase-chan last night!
Order?
This is the Mechacabra.
Wow! As expected of Hakase-chan!
It looks just like it!
Really?
Hey, how do we move it?
We cannot move it at the moment.
We need someone to go inside.
Inside?
It has to be driven?
Well, to put it simply…
Who will drive it?
That's already been decided.
If it’s a chupacabra, there is only one person who can do it!
Right? Negi-kun?
EH!?
M-ME!?
Fold in, fold out. Fold in, Fold out. Fold in...
I'm done!
A crane！
Mine is a frog.
Mine is a snail.
Nekane-san, what about yours?
Here!
What?
Moss ball!
Robot! Robot!
Aah! It looks good on you after all!
You'll definitely capture Asuna's heart with this!
I won’t!
Anyway, Hakase-san, why on the roof?
We haven't tested its operation yet.
Operation test?
Isn’t it a vehicle?
Nope, it’s a mecha.
Standby!
Smoke… smoke is coming out!
Launch!
Ta-mayaaaa!
It failed.
What do you mean by failed, Hakase-san?
It's beautiful eh, Secchan...
What do you mean beautiful!? Ojou-sama!?
Chupacabra Mission Complete!
On that note, wasn’t it alright that Negi-sensei wore that after the test?
Argh... I finally got out of there...
What the hell was that prank all about?
Asuna-san! In front of you!
Asuna-san!!
Someone's in trouble!
Help me!!
Asuna-san!
Negi-kun! Transform me!
Me too!
Alright!
Partner: Konoe Konoka, Sakurazaki Setsuna.
Show me the power within you!
Contract,
Activate!
Ugh! Both are Suka cards!!
No way!
Aargh! This is useless!!
I’m ashamed...
Asuna-san!!
Honya-chan!
Try your best, Nodoka!!
All at once!!
Are you alright, Asuna-kun?
Thank you!!
Asuna-san!!
Negi-kun! Take out the darkness now!
Yeah!! Err, um Right!
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
Wait!
Oh no!
Hey...
AAH! THE CAT'S OUT OF THE BAG!
Asuna-san! Don't! Don't do it!!!
Hey, Black Rose Baron!
What is it, Asuna-kun?
That costume, can I borrow your costume?
I just want to wear it once!
Pretty please?
This?
Please, I'll give you a Chupa-Tee for it!
Co... costume?
Alright. I'll think about it.
YEAH! Looks like I've succeeded this time!! ALL RIGHT!
What the hell does she mean by "All right"...?
What the?
I think she's really interested...
But, not in either Nekane-dono or the Baron...
So it’s the costume she was interested in...
Ojou-chama!
Yeah! This was one heck of a mistake!
KAN KAN KAN!!
And so it was, Nekane-san's secret is safe, in a good way.
Copycat!!
Hello, hello!
Today, I’ve found a talking cat!
Surprising!!
As expected from a magic world, eh?
Hey, Neko-chan, say something to everyone on the net!
Tonberry!
A journalist needs boxwood、bravery and independence.
Next time,
"Wouldn’t it be great to go back and play like a child?"
"Even if you can’t go back, you can still play, right?"
By Kazumi.
Ah! One more thing!
Don’t be so quick to note something like, “ghosts do not exist”, okay?
One horizontal stick.
One vertical stick.
And while I’m at it,
We get the letter “ten”!
Was it a letter?
Just a litter…
2 points.
One horizontal stick…
She still going on…
To sa… To sa… To sa…
Chiu!!