You're awake?
Let me out.
What do you plan to do?
I will join up with Master.
Scythe betrayed the organization and ran away.
He abandoned you.
The situation is still unclear.
I will join up with Master.
If joining him is impossible, I will aid in his escape.
If I distract them, I can draw off some of his pursuers.
Pull over.
No way.
While the hunt is still in progress, you need to stay with me.
Scythe is under the protection of Phantom even as we speak.
The fear of Phantom is always with him.
It's the reason the organization can't make careless moves.
If you were to be captured here,
Scythe would be in trouble.
You've changed, Zwei.
Changed?
Yes.
You are a different person from yesterday.
That's right.
You're no longer "Zwei".
You're Azuma Reiji.
You were listening?
You have a place to return to.
There is a real you.
But...
...I have nothing.
I'm Ein.
A number.
Master is the only place I have to return to.
That's not...
I have nothing.
Master gave me...
...a name, Ein, and nothing else.
Ein...
That's me.
I'm no one.
Phan...tom.
You're wrong.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You can drink it.
You didn't think I'd be gone?
You're reckless, but you're not a fool.
The stolen van has been found.
It was empty.
So we let them all escape, huh?
Scythe is your pet dog.
Take care of this matter.
I'm fully aware of it.
KARMA
nando mo onaji koto no kurikaeshi no naka wo ochite itte wa
何度も同じことの繰り返しの中を堕ちていっては
Falling into the same endless repetition again and again.
You know this song?
Ah, sorry.
Was it too loud?
What is its name?
Don't know... I wonder.
I forgot the title, but I heard it pretty often in town.
Does everyone in Japan listen to this kind of music?
KARMA
Everyone has their own preferences when it comes to music.
kono mi wa rasen no you umare kawatte mo nao samayoi tsuzuketeru
この身は螺旋のよう 生まれ変わってもなお彷徨い続けてる
This body is like a spiral. Even if I were to be reborn, I will continue to wander.
There's no difference there between Japan and Las Vegas.
Tell me about Japan.
You remembered, didn't you?
Memories of when you were living your life as Azuma Reiji.
I guess so.
yasurakani
安らかに
Peacefully...
owari ni shiyou
終わりにしよう
Let's end it...
It's me.
The cargo is on schedule.
I wish you a safe trip.
What're you talking about?
The escape and transport route,
you took care of it down to every little detail.
I'll contact you again after things have settled down.
I hope we will be on good terms in the future.
She can't be trusted.
If we get careless, she will sell out the whole Godou clan.
So what?
We've been using her as well, eh?
It's risky.
Don't chicken out now, Shiga.
Make up your mind.
I'm gonna be big.
Azuma Reiji.
You should go back.
Go back?
Yes.
Where would I go back to?
You should know what I've done in the past half a year.
I can't go back now.
You have a past, though.
You can exist in this world as Azuma Reiji.
You're no different.
You're here right now.
You have something I don't have.
There is something to prove your identity.
Is something like this important?
Yes. That's your proof of yourself.
It's something I don't have.
What are you doing?
Reiji?!
Do you realize what you've done?
That was your...
It was just a piece of paper.
My memories make me who I am.
And you have those too...
You told me about your dreams before, didn't you?
Memories of colors.
They are bright and dazzling with a strong wind.
Those are memories of your homeland, aren't they?
They are fleeting memories.
There's no guarantee that it's my homeland.
But it's your memory.
You have a past too-
not as a number like "Ein".
You have a real name.
Why? Why are you so concerned about me?
You have nothing to gain.
I don't want you to die.
I don't want them to slaughter you.
It's not for anyone's sake.
This is my own will.
Doing this is my proof of myself.
I don't need a stamp on paper for that.
None of that.
Your driving license, please.
Where did you come from?
Las Vegas.
We were visiting a friend.
Wallace Young, 20 years old.
You look younger in the flesh.
I hear that quite often.
And your company?
My sister.
She doesn't look well.
Yeah, it's a long journey.
She's a bit carsick.
I see.
Okay, drive on.
You've become smoother.
Hmm? The act just now?
What are you saying? You taught me that.
What will you do now?
We'll keep on moving and stop from time to time to let you rest.
And when your wounds have healed, let's go someplace faraway.
Faraway?
Where?
To the very end.
That's...
I told you, didn't I?
I decided this of my own will.
I'll buy something to eat.
Ein! Ein!
I felt no fear yesterday, but...
...my finger...
...won't move.
Reiji...
Pull the trigger.
Put me at ease.
You're too selfish.
What's wrong, Ein?
You used to be much stronger than me.
That's not true.
I...
...was only doing it for Master's sake.
Just for that reason...
Even if it meant making the whole organization my enemy,
if Master commanded it...
But...
Now, I'm...
...living for what reason?
Chased by the organization and just running away.
I can't even pull the trigger.
If I had died yesterday...
...at least I could have died as Ein.
That's...
Were we fighting this whole time just to die?
No.
We fought to live.
We didn't want to die for a stupid reason like this.
We wanted to live.
That... is the only reason.
I'm being chased by Inferno.
If our pursuers found this place...
The organization or me, who would you point your gun at?
You don't need to ask.
I'll point it at the organization.
I'll pull the trigger of my own will.
Why?
Why are you trying to survive so desperately?
Are you telling me to live the same life?
Don't you want to?
But...
I'm no one...
I have nothing...
Neither a reason to live nor a role.
Ein...
No.
Let's stop calling you "Ein".
"Ein" is just a number.
It's not a name.
You need a new name.
A name?
Not like Phantom or a number.
A name for you to live your life by.
Elen.
It's Elen.
I'm going to call you Elen from now on.
Why "Elen"?
I don't need a reason.
That's my decision.
Not as an assassin or a puppet.
It's a name for you to keep on living as yourself.
Elen...
It's a bit strange.
Is that so?
Elen, let's look for it.
The past you've lost.
Once we've found your real name,
there will be plenty of reasons to live.
Even if you have to hurt someone,
keep on living.
We might suffer for now,
but let's go...
...together.
If that boy you like joins Scythe's side...
...what should be done?
Kill him.
I'm going to withdraw some money and get a new car.
I will be back in an hour.
How's your wound?
I'll be fine if I don't force myself.
Be careful, Elen.
Alright,
Reiji.
Elen...
The name Reiji gave me.
With this name, I will...
How unlike you, Ein...
Overcome your pain with willpower.
Master...
Last exit, Zwei.
Has your sweet honeymoon been fun?
Lizzie...
Looks like you've been played by Scythe.
I have no business with him.
I wonder.
We shall have a long conversation about that.
I just got an update.
My subordinate tailing Phantom has been killed.
Phantom has returned to Scythe's side.
That's a lie!
Elen.
Spill it already!
Where's Scythe headed?
I don't know. We were just...
As I thought, he knows nothing.
Leave the rest to me.
You can leave.
I'll acknowledge that stubbornness of yours, at least.
I've killed the microphone.
You can tell me anything you want.
Saving Ein and running together...
Was that your choice?
You're an idiot.
They branded you an accomplice.
People question your loyalty.
Your chance to return to Japan is gone.
However...
...there is one last option open to you.
A way to prove your innocence,
...and take Ein back.
What... is it?
You should know...
...how to use this.
I will kill Scythe.
Elen...
I'll make you smile someday.
I'll return to you a normal smile.