Got a moment?
What is it?
I want to figure out what time
we're going on Saturday.
Wait, haven't you heard?
Orimoto and I were texting each other,
and we ended up making plans to hang out.
Nah. First I've heard of it.
Wanna come with us, then?
Like hell I do.
Please. Think of it as helping me out.
You know I wouldn't be of any help.
And it's not like you'd need my help, anyway.
Most of all, I'd like to chill at home on weekends at least.
Is that so?
You. Phone.
I'm gonna sleep. Just leave it there when you're done.
O-Okay.
Hello?
Yo, 'sup!
Yukinoshita Haruno
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something real
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Are you and your little sister fighting?
Compared to your family situation, it's nothing.
Gotcha.
Anyway, I heard you got asked out.
Sure you don't wanna go?
Nobody asked me out.
Hayato invited you. Just go!
Why would I?
Y'know, Hayato usually doesn't
bow and ask for favors.
He's way too proud for that.
Yukinoshita Haruno
I'd really like to know why he wants to take you along so badly.
What's the problem? It's so romantic!
You get to go on a date with the girl you were in love with!
You don't call that love.
What do you mean?
That was just a selfish, one-sided fascination,
or, well, just a misunderstanding.
It wasn't genuine.
You're like a monster of reason.
What the heck? It's not like that.
I see.
A monster of self-consciousness, then.
Anyway, you'd better go on that date.
Yukinoshita Haruno
Don't make me come drag you out myself!
Thanks for coming along.
I'm only here cause Yukinoshita Sr.
scares the crap out of me.
If you want to thank someone, thank her.
But why change plans to a weekday just for me?
Oh, is that them?
Sorry we're late!
Shall we get going?
What first? A movie?
Yeah!
I'm down for a movie!
Let's go!
What genre?
Romance?
Of course!
I'm watching a movie with you!
If people from junior high heard about this, they'd freak out!
I bet.
I know, right?
Looking back, I get the feeling things were the same back in junior high.
Never once had the distance between us shrunk.
I'd just never realized
that Orimoto Kaori treated everyone the same way,
even if she had no interest in them.
That's just the way she is.
I feel like I've finally gotten some closure on something that'd never really got going.
Wasn't that explosion totally insane?
I'm pretty sure Hikigaya wet himself!
The look on his face had me laughing so hard.
I wasn't expecting it to be that loud.
Yeah, it surprised me a little.
But weren't you totally calm the entire time?
I know, right?
It made me jump a little,
but he acted like it was nothing.
Hikigaya, though...
Y-Yeah.
I-I hope you enjoyed my clown act.
I-If we don't hurry, we won't have time to check out the shops.
What's up, Ebina?
Haya—
Panties! Pink! Unexpected!
Y-Yumiko, you okay?
H-Hayato...
We'd better get going.
We should check out some snowboarding gear as well.
Huh? If it ain't Hayato!
Hey, Hayato!
What's wrong, Tobe?
Get a load of this!
I came here with Irohas 'cause she said she wanted a new tracksuit,
but she's been going on and on about protein!
Wh-Whoops. Are we interrupting?
My bad. We'll be outta here in a sec.
Right, Irohas?
Hikigaya!
Whoa, too fast, Irohas!
That gave me a start!
What're you doing here?
You've got some balls to be goofing off with chicks while you've got work to do
Out having fun?
...is what I think I'll get if I read between the lines.
Nah, I'm not really goofing off or—
Who is that, anyway?
Your girlfriend, maybe?
But there's two of them.
How do you know one another?
Help!
Irohas is scary as hell!
How is it even possible to sound this cold with that thousand-watt smile?
Sorry about that, Iroha.
I made him tag along.
Oh, is that so?
Well, I'm just hanging out, too.
Let's kill time together!
Come on, Irohas.
We should get going, yeah?
I know! Let's hit up Lions Sports!
Forget it. That place is mainly for baseball gear, anyway.
So Iroha shows you that side of her, too.
She tries to show off her cute side to most people.
I guess she wants to be loved.
It's rare for her to show her true self.
You know, that'd mean she showed me her true self because she doesn't want me to love her.
I heard you liked her back in junior high?
Is that your type?
I'm surprised.
Shut it.
It wasn't just Orimoto.
There was a noisier girl, a more silent one—
different as can be, yet I still fe—
still thought they were my type.
You can hardly call that a preference.
Besides, just because it was the case in the past doesn't mean it's still the same.
You're right.
In the end, I guess we've never really fallen in love.
Neither you
nor I.
You know, I kinda have the hots for Ebina.
How about you, Hayato?
Who's on your mind?
I...
Come on.
Nah, let's not do this.
That's not fair, bro!
At least give me an initial.
Y.
It was all a misconception.
Aren't you hungry?
I am!
What would you like to eat?
Anything goes.
What should we get?
How about some Saize?
Didn't you say anything goes?
What? Do you hate Saize?
Saize!
Or is it me that you hate?
Well, something too upscale would be a bad idea,
so why don't we grab a bite at that cafe?
This place has some great food.
Right? That was super delish!
I'm stuffed! That's Hayama for you.
He has the best taste.
Some people, though...
You're gonna say it out loud?
N-Nuh-uh, not saying it!
Oh, come on.
Seriously, though!
Saize of all places?
Haha, I know, right?.
It actually took me a sec to realize what he was saying.
Same, girl!
I'm glad we came here.
Yeah.
I'm not really fond of that.
R-Right?
Oh, that's not what I meant.
I'm talking about the way you two are acting.
U-Uh...
Right...
Y-Yeah...
Oh, there they are.
You guys...
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
Hikki?
What're you doing here?
I asked them to come.
Hikigaya's more than the kinda guy you make him out to be.
He's close to a pair of girls far lovelier than you could ever hope to be.
Could you stop judging books by their cover and running your mouth?
Sorry. I'm outta here.
Y-Yeah.
Sorry, me too.
I see now.
I was told this would be a meeting about the election.
You mean the student council election?
U-Uh, we were hoping to have Hayato run for president, so today, we...
Oh.
They want to make Hayato a candidate.
There's nothing strange about that choice in itself.
However...
I just wanted to do what I could.
Oh? Is that so?
Sis?
So, you won't run for president?
And here I thought it was a lock.
The way you go about forcing work on others is just like Mom.
Well, I guess you're fine that way.
You don't even have to lift a finger.
Others always get their hands dirty for you.
So, that's what this is about.
If that's all, I'll be leaving.
W-Wait, Yukinon!
Why would you antagonize her?
Do you need to ask?
It's the usual.
That seemed a bit overboard, though.
You think?
Yeah.
Well, I've got a little sister too,
so I can see where you're coming from.
You can see through everything, huh?
Why the scary face?
I really am impressed.
Gee, thanks.
You're such an amusing boy.
Always trying to read between the lines.
I quite like that, you know?
I mean, it's adorable how you're
constantly living in fear of malice.
On the other hand, people who can handle anything flawlessly are boring.
Well, then.
I got the answer I was looking for,
so I should get going.
Someone rained on my parade, anyway.
I don't need you looking out for me.
That wasn't my intention.
I just did what I wanted to.
Does that include what you said to Orimoto and Nakamachi?
Sure you should've done that?
I feel awful. I never want to do anything like that again.
You shouldn't have bothered, then.
Why don't you take a seat?
I've been thinking all along
about how to fix what I broke.
I'd pinned my hopes on you.
That's why I relied on you despite being aware of the consequences.
And because of that, you...
Hey.
You need to realize your own worth.
And not just you. The people around you, too.
What are you even talking about?
That's easier said than done, though.
I wish I could've gone about it better,
but this is all I could manage.
This is how you've always done it, right?
Don't you think it's about time you stopped sacrificing yourself?
I'm not like you.
Sacrificing myself? Please.
It's perfectly normal to me.
I'm always alone.
Other people don't factor into what I do.
The things that happen in front of me are parts of my life, and my life alone.
Don't stick your nose where it doesn't belong.
Don't you help people
because you want someone to help you?
Not at all.
Quit forcing your disgusting pity on me.
Hikigaya
For fuck's sake!
I won't let you call what I do self-sacrifice.
Who would ever want to be a
scapegoat for the likes of you?
Although I couldn't put it in words,
I had my convictions.
The one thing I shared with someone else,
and the one I've lost now.
Yukinoshita came to talk to me this morning.
Said she was going to run for
student council president.
That so?
Hikigaya, what will you do?
Nothing.
If we're going purely by qualifications, she's the obvious choice.
Yeah.
If the teachers and others hear about this, I bet they'll be overcome with joy.
You haven't told anyone else?
Nope.
Let me ask you once again.
Hikigaya,
what will you do?
Yukinoshita.
Are you planning to run for president yourself?
She didn't tell you?
N-No.
I was just about to discuss it with her.
You can hardly call that a "discussion."
Is it because of what your sister said?
That has nothing to do with it.
I'm doing it because I want to.
Yukinon, what about the club?
We'll be fine.
This club doesn't have much to do,
and I already know what student council work entails.
It won't end up being a burden.
Thinking objectively,
this is the best option.
I can beat Isshiki, no problem.
Also...
Also, I don't mind doing it.
Maybe so, but we could always solve this without an election battle.
Are you talking about your idea from before?
Yeah.
You greatly overestimate yourself if you think you can influence the entire student body alone.
Then I'll just have to come up with a method that takes that into account.
If you think everybody cares about you enough to hate you,
then you think far too much of yourself.
My methods are different from yours.
You can say that again.
Oh, so that's how Yukinon does things.
W-Wait up!
Let's walk home together!
Yukinon's gonna run for president, huh?
Yeah.
I'm thinking of giving it a shot, too.
You're going to run for president?
Why?
I've got nothing.
There's nothing I can do,
so I figured I could flip the table and use that to my advantage.
What's that even supposed to mean?
Don't just selfishly—
I'm not the one being selfish.
You guys are!
Have you thought this through?
I have.
I thought about it, and realized it was the only way.
It's my turn to carry the load.
I realized that I've been leaving it all in your hands until now.
I haven't done anything.
Really?
Yeah, so there's no need for you
to put in extra effort.
But that's not all there is to it.
If Yukinon becomes student council president,
I'm sure she'll be the best president ever,
and I'm sure it'll help improve the school.
But, like, it'll cost us our club.
No, it won't.
Yes, it will.
You saw what happened during the cultural festival.
You know how Yukinon tends to focus on one thing.
You see...
I'm in love with this club.
I'm in love.
Anyway, like,
if I become student council president, I can just half-ass things
and our club will stay the same, right?
We're talking about me here.
Nobody's expecting anything from me.
So...
I'm gonna beat Yukinon.
Yuiga—
Oh, I'll be okay from here.
Later.
Later...
Bye-bye, Hikki.
If Yukinoshita and Yuigahama truly believe
they're making the best choice, then that's fine.
It's just...
And
Yuigahama Yui Makes Her Declaration.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
The Scent of Tea No Longer Fills That Room.
Uh, I'll have a Milano Doria, a Peperoncino, and a drink—
oh, and a salted chicken, too.
You're ordering way too much.
Well, that's the best thing about Saize.
Its prices are reasonable, and so's the food.
I know, right? Viva la Saize!
Oh, I'd like a Focaccia and a drink.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Focaccia tastes amazing with gum syrup.
That sounds amazing! I'll have one, too!
Oh, and some...
Chorizo Prosciutto!
What's that, your finishing move?