They're so cool...!
What, you want a guitar?
I've never played, but...
Maybe I could start...?
Just like Momoka-san!
Give up.
You've got no experience.
Your vocals will take a dive.
She's not listening.
Well, it's no surprise after her first concert.
Geez, look at her face.
She's totally imagining it.
Screaming out everything I felt
at the top of my lungs,
with every last bit of my strength...
I've never done anything like that in my life.
It felt like I was venting my soul
without caring how people would react.
Nina!
Time for practice.
Coming!
Thanks (Surprise)
Okay, stop for a sec.
- What do you think?
- Sounded good to me.
Let's play it back.
I want to break it
I don't have the courage
Someone hurry up and teach me a reason to live
Not bad, not bad at all.
There are so many people to take my place
Can you add some modulation when you start the chorus?
Someone hurry up and teach me a reason to...
Like that?
Yeah. It feels too normal, it's dull.
Oh, and let's re-record the drums.
What, now?
I've got an early start tomorrow, you know.
Diamond Dust?
Yeah. She was looking them up.
She must be anxious about them.
But they're real bigshots now, aren't they?
Well, sure, but...
If she really was worried,
she wouldn't have grouped up with
a couple of amateurs like us.
But...
Oh no.
Oh no!
What's wrong?
Sorry, I'm calling it a day!
See you tomorrow!
I'm in front of the shop
Subaru-chan?
Everything alright?
Still no read receipt.
Must be a man.
Whaaaa?!
Gotta say, I didn't see that coming.
Maybe it's an ex that wants to get back together.
What are you talking about?!
Why are you getting so worked up?
I mean...
Is it true?
Band girls are popular with band guys.
They're like moths to a flame.
Moths?
You better be careful, too.
I'm going to call her.
No chance she'll pick up.
Just relax, we'll find out tomorrow.
When it comes to romance
or shifts at work, freedom is best.
What do you think, Momoka-san?
About the current Diamond Dust.
Nothing, really.
You really don't care?
It's not like I'm holding a grudge.
If anything, I hope they succeed.
Why did you quit, then?
Who cares about that?
Don't worry about it.
Just focus on singing.
What kind of band were they?
I told you not to worry about it.
Please tell me.
Here, catch.
We used to be in the Light Music Club
at our high school.
We were all pretty skilled though,
and passionate to boot.
We even had the same dream. It felt like fate.
"This must be a miracle."
We got so excited.
And we were right.
At the school festival in autumn of our first year,
so many people came to see us
that they couldn't fit in the gymnasium.
We were the headline act. It was the best.
"Let's turn pro! No going back!"
We quit school,
came to Tokyo, released an indie CD,
held concerts, and just when our big debut was in sight,
that's when I dropped out.
Momoka-san...
I didn't know you could smile like this.
No sir, I wasn't sleeping...
I should've just slept in bed.
A message from Subaru-chan!
Huh?
Quitting the band.
Sorry!
Say what?!
We really shouldn't.
Why not?
The three of us are meant to be a band!
How can you give up so easily?
I'm not giving up.
If she cares about the band,
she'll dump the guy and come back.
But if we try to stop her,
it could just make her more obstinate.
You think so?
Don't tell me you've never had a boyfriend?
Have you?
Excuse me...
What are you doing?
Whenever I come here,
I get a little nervous.
I'm the leader, so follow my lead.
When did you become the leader?
Oh, and Subaru-chan puts on an annoying act here,
so try not to get mad.
Oh?
Subaru...
-chan?
This way, dear Grandmother.
What ever is the matter?
- Suba-
- What's that? You've lost your way?
Grandmother, please wait a moment
while I help these poor souls.
What on earth are you doing here?
What did you expect
after sending a message like that?
I'll explain later, so just leave!
Tell us why, first!
Oh, come on!
Who are they?
Grandmother!
They're, uh, my friends.
My actress friends.
Actress?
Isn't that right?
Heavens, it's so busy here that it makes me dizzy.
It is a big city.
Subaru-chan.
- Watch your posture.
- Right!
I'm always telling you to watch your posture.
Your everyday actions and behavior
will seep into your acting.
You must always maintain a healthy body and mind.
Yes, Grandmother.
If the two of you
happen to have any advice, please do share it with her.
Now, if you'll excuse me for a moment...
Subaru-chan.
I know.
Was that Awa Tendo? The actress?
You only just realized?
Not like anyone told me. Cut me some slack.
That's right, she's my grandma.
She told me yesterday that
she was in town and wanted to see me.
Wait, you're from a showbiz family?
Not exactly.
My parents work normal jobs.
You don't want to become an actress though, right?
No! But like I said,
if I told her that now, she'd be crushed.
Then why did you say you were quitting the band?
I just panicked, and like,
you know what they say about
deceiving your friends to decieve your enemies.
You've lost me.
It means that's how serious I have to be
if I want to fool her.
She looks like a nice lady, though.
On the surface, maybe. She's from Kyoto though,
so you shouldn't take what she says at face value.
Really?
- Posture.
- Right!
We should go back.
I'd like to see how much you've improved.
Huh?
Would the two of you be so kind as to join us?
H-Huh?
W-What do you want?
I actually, uh, love you, my dear!
Don't laugh!
An etude?
Yes, a lovers scene.
You profess your love for her,
and Subaru-chan plays her former lover,
come to take her back.
Uh, right.
The hell is an etude?
What a wonderful idea, Grandmother!
It means we perform on the spot!
Ad-lib!
Let's go back to the school and give it a try.
Are you kidding me?!
How does that sound?
No way!
We can't escape
No way no how no chance
No thank you.
It seems Nina-san didn't hear you very well.
Listen to me, damnit!
Do it! Do you want me in the band or not?!
I'd rather die!
Now now, we can't have you
planning your performance over the phone.
Right!
Come now children, let's go.
Wait.
Y-You're...
I cannot deny my heart.
I love you too!
Why did you break up with me, then?
What?
I've been serious about you since we started dating.
I thought we'd be together forever.
How could you give it up so easily?
Uh, well...
How?!
Were you lying when you said this was real?
No, I was telling the truth...
Then why?!
I can't believe you used the play to pick a fight
and say whatever you want.
Got a problem with that?
Look, I know.
I don't actually want to quit the band.
And when it comes to acting,
nobody even sees me as anything more
than Awa Tendo's granddaughter.
- But still...
- What?
Something feels off.
Grandma wouldn't pay me a visit on a whim like that.
She's not the type to ever be so spontaneous.
No wonder!
Girls Band Cry.
A role in a TV show?!
It's feeding back! Don't speak into the mic!
I don't have a choice. Grandma's made up her mind.
It's just a minor role,
so it shouldn't take more than a week,
but I can't come to practice in the meantime.
Gotcha.
Are you sure?
You're not better.
You skip practice when you need to study, don't you?
That's not the same.
- Is too!
- Is not!
No fighting.
But Subaru-chan might leave!
Happens all the time with bands.
Don't say that...
Why are you so upset?
Because you're being so cold.
The way I see it, you're the cold one here, Nina.
I told you I'm coming back.
Just trust me!
But...
C'mon. Everyone's got stuff they wanna deal with on their own.
You don't like talking about why you came to Tokyo, do you?
That's...
Time's a wastin'.
We'll just re-record Subaru today.
You can go home, Nina.
The hell do you mean, I'm the cold one?
Goddamnit.
Are you free tomorrow?
No!
I lied! I am!
Where on earth are we?
This is my home.
Come on in.
THE NEXT DAY
Wow...
It gets boring fast.
- Is tea alright?
- Yeah.
Have a seat wherever you like.
The beanbag's great for gaming.
Thanks.
Watch this.
What a pretty lady.
I figured we should have a proper talk.
You'd get all emo again, otherwise.
AWA TENDO (THE RISING STAR)
SUBARU
This is where they got my name from.
My grandma chose it.
Is this...
Yep. This was her breakout role when she was young, apparently.
Not that I know, though. I wasn't born yet.
Anyway, she thought it'd be an auspicious name...
for an actress.
But you don't want to become one.
That's true.
I'm tired of getting special treatment wherever I go
just because of her.
I don't even like acting. It's embarrassing.
But you know...
Whenever I tell her I want to become an actress,
she smiles.
It's the only time she really smiles.
Not with a fake smile.
What do you think?
What would you do in my shoes?
There.
Now do you get how I feel,
you little punk?
But you can't keep this up forever.
If you don't want to become an actress,
the sooner you tell her, the better.
You're right.
Yeah.
I thought if I went to that acting school,
she'd realize I wasn't cut out for it
and give up.
- See ya.
- Mm.
- You don't have to worry. I'm not going to quit.
- You promise?
When I drummed at our concert the other day,
I felt like I might seriously enjoy all this.
I just dropped a real banger,
don't leave me hanging!
Yeah.
What's this?
I'm sorry. Nina.
If you were gonna feel bad,
you shouldn't have gotten angry in the first place.
LATER...
Detective Granny's Case Files, part 6!
Starring Awa Tendo as Granny!
It's a pleasure.
I'm her granddaughter, Subaru.
I'll be playing the store clerk.
It's a pleasure to be here.
That's some serious makeup she's got on.
It's hard to tell unless they use that much.
Bands do the same thing when they perform.
- Huh? Are we going to do it too?
- Maybe. Depends.
Quit daydreaming..
Let's begin!
Is she really going to tell her?
Yeah. That's what she said.
She'll probably have to quit school,
so she might go back to her hometown for a bit,
but she wants to continue with the band.
If it's gonna turn into such a big fuss,
she could just not tell her.
That's true.
But she feels she'll have to tell her one day.
That's a wrap!
Let's begin our checks!
Are you sure?
Yes. We're done for the day.
This was our first duo act.
That's great.
I've always dreamed of this...
Of the two of us starring in the same show.
Do you want her to become an actress?
Of course.
Subaru's name is the same as my breakout role.
My daughter really hated my work, you see.
I was never at home,
and for all my pride,
I was hopeless at household chores.
That's why I was thrilled
when Subaru told me she loved my work.
She was the only one who smiled for me.
She was the only one who loved what I did,
and I'm so grateful that she wanted to do it too.
Okay, we're all good!
Beginning checks!
Alright, time to do my checks.
Grandmother!
Good work.
Um, there's something I'd like to talk to you about.
What is it?
Well, I wanted to wait until later,
but you might miss your shinkansen.
That's true. I'll have to leave soon.
I see.
I'll tell you now, then.
You see...
Um, I...
Grandmother, I...
I...
Subaru-chan, come quick!
We left something behind!
We need to go, now!
We need to go! Come on, there's no time!
Huh? Wait, wh-
Ow, stop!
Stop pushing!
What's going on?
You're such a freaking hypocrite!
Sorry!
Shut up!
You're the one who told me that
I should stop pretending and tell her the truth!
- I was!
- What are you so proud of?
I'd finally worked up the nerve!
Yeah, well...
Everyone's got stuff to deal with.
It's a struggle. You need to have a little sympathy. {簡単じゃないんだよ。そういうところに気を遣えるようにならなきゃ｝
- Right?
- I don't want to hear that from you!
Ow, ow, that hurts!
I already knew that, unlike you!
But you...
But you have to tell her someday!
When?
When you figure out what you really want to do.
What is wrong with this girl?!
I don't know.
Ugh, I'm done.
I'm so completely, utterly, absolutely done.
I worked up the courage because
you didn't want me to quit the band.
Then right as I'm about to pull the trigger,
you change your mind, you illogical monster!
That goes for you too, sitting there like you know it all!
I'll be the one to decide things for myself!
So piss off!
Subaru-chan...
What do you think of my act?
Man, I feel better now.
Whatever. I always knew I'd have to
do something about it eventually.
So until then, I'll be here to kick your asses!
Now let's do this!
Next episode: "Vocals, Get Mad".
TL note: reference to a song by Sambomaster https://youtu.be/d4nQm6y_gbE