Unacceptable! Unacceptable, I say!
Look at this!
This chunk of fat around your waist!
When did this get so squishy?
What do you think you're doing!?
You've definitely gained some weight lately!
Yes, you have!
- The Earth is turning red!
- I don't care about Dumb-chi getting fat.
Y-Yeah...
Leave me alone!
I'm leaving!
Stupid idiot!
I won't forget this, dammit!
Idiot!
Unacceptable!
This is unacceptable!
I can't let this kind of incident slide as a Diet Warrior!
Y-Yeah. You're pretty strict.
Oh, you're here. Since when?
She didn't notice you, since you're like air.
I'm smitten by how you've managed to ignore me right from the beginning, Kushieda!
C'mon, bastards!
Kushieda Investigative Office, we're off to stalk Amin!
Yes, sir!
Yeah!
Pink and Fatty Corned Beef
Toradora SOS!
Hurray for Foodies
Don't Be Judgmental!
Everyone Loves and Cherishes
W-Welcome!
Boss!
Our target's entered the convenience store.
Looks like she's here to satisfy every one of her stupid cravings.
Over.
Great. We'll capture her when she reaches her home.
Yes, sir!
Gotcha!
What...What is this!?
What are you doing!?
Boss, look what I found!
Inconceivable!
How could anyone consume this much corned beef?
Who goes out of their way to find a store that sells corned beef?
As expected of the Convenience
Store Enthusiast.
Shut up!
Look who's talking. You only eat sweet curry!
Corned beef usually comes in a can.
These cans are sanitized via heat before packaging.
As opposed to surstromming, which is not sanitized and then ferments in the can.
Springtime herrings are commonly used,
and they're stacked with salt between them.
Then they're pickled inside a barrel for one or two months.
They're opened to be eaten on the third Thursday of August.
Some are liquefied into slop, so you need to be careful when eating them.
- Nothing smells worse than them, you see.
- And again... What does he think he is?
Shut it, stupid dog.
Knowledge is useless in terms of tasty food.
You idiot!
I'll show you how to prepare the most delicious plate in the world.
Here it comes!
Corned beef tastes great inside of a rice ball or sandwich,
but the simplest way is the best way to enjoy it.
You'll stop caring about your life.
I wish I could fall asleep, enveloped in a sea of corned beef...
Come, enjoy this mighty corned beef tower.
B-B-But, um...!
Y-Y-Yeah...
Being judgmental won't do.
Ain't gonna know if'n ya fancy it till ya try it.
W-Well, shall we dig in?
Nom.
Delicious!
I'm sorry it's so delicious, Mama!
Mama!
See?
Most people don't understand this extreme acquired taste.
Yuck, I still don't get it.
Gotta admit, I agree with the stupid dog.
Shazam!
- I'll force everyone to agree with me!
- Hey, I used to think it was corn plus beef!
What kind of false advertising is this!?
Splendid! It's unbelievably splendiferous!
That said...
This battle ends with a tie!
Corned beef is brine-cured beef!
Corned beef mustn't be underestimated!
I'm going to Mongolia for work soon.
It's a swimsuit photo shoot!
Well, that sounds fun and delightful.
It goes down to -20 Celsius there.
Your nose hair's gonna freeze.
Are you serious!?
Inko Today
The End
Dedicated to Mongolia <3