kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
Rio-senpai!
Good work!
The parts?
We found them without any problem!
They can be found if you just look for them!
It's so warm!
Alive again...
Huh? But Rio-senpai, were you supposed to be on yard duty?
There was something I wanted to burn.
It's been half a year since Kanata came to the fort, huh?
Astonishingly, she's actually gotten better at playing.
It's because her teacher is good.
Ouch!
She's finally gotten to the point where we don't need earplugs.
Hey, Madam. Wouldn't it be better to go into the town this winter after all?
It's all right.
I won't kick the bucket so easily.
I've been living alone on this mountain for 50 years after all.
Setting off
Time of the First Snow
All right. All right. All right.
Stop!
It's finally coming along.
Noël, will you be fine on your own after this?
Yes. I'm happy.
Then why don't we get some tea?
Sure.
Hey, Kureha-chan?
Huh? I wonder where it went?
It should be here.
Oh? What's the matter?
The military almanac was here, right?
Kanata said she wanted to know more about Princess Iliya.
I'm sorry. If it's not there, then I don't know where it is.
If we go to Naomi-san's place, there might be one.
I'll ask her about it next time.
Thanks!
Princess Iliya was the eldest daughter of the current Archduke Arkadia.
I told you this before, but she was a super-famous tank commander.
Earlier, Klaus-san also said "if only she were still alive" though...
She died. It was about two years ago, I think.
In the war?
The thing about Her Highness was, even though she was assigned to the Imperial Guard,
she also traveled all over the country so that she could enhance the national prestige.
And then, on her way to a certain town, she tried to save a child who was drowning in a river and...
But I'm a little relieved.
This is just a rumor, but...
Iliya...
Kanata-san!
Yumina-san and...
You are...?
Um, it's Kanata.
Um...
Yumina-san, uh, brought Yuuko-chan with her...
Ah! Yuuko-chan is Martin-san's daughter...
The truth is, there's an old lady named Jacott-san.
Jacott-san lives alone in the mountains and...
I also buy her vegetables at the morning market...
Oh, and you said the pickled vegetables from earlier were delicious, right?
The one who grew those vegetables was Jacott-san.
And it seems that no one has seen Jacott-san lately...
She seemed to be in poor health, so we're worried about her.
She lives very deep inside the mountains, so...
Fine. I get it, I get it.
I'll hear you out, so just wait a bit.
Sure!
Regarding Princess Iliya...
In order to improve relations with the Holy City of Rome,
it was rumored that she was going to marry the Emperor.
But if she did that, she'd have been the third queen!
The third! The THIRD!
That's unbelievable, isn't it?
In other words, she would have just been a hostage.
Well, when the princess died, any possibility of that ended.
And up until the salvation at the beginning of this year, we've done nothing but bicker with them.
Good grief. We've finally arrived.
A partially-constructed house?
Didn't they say she lived alone?
That's what I thought too.
Madam!
I see. It was Yuuko?
Yes.
She's such a kind girl.
She's too good for that snot-nosed Martin.
This is such a wonderful house.
Thank you.
You see, I'm the one who built this house.
Amazing!
Then what about the other one?
That's for my son.
You have a son?
He's in a distant city right now.
He can come back when he wants.
I keep it clean so that whenever my son or that person returns, they may use it as they please.
When will your son and that person return, Madam?
Very soon, I guess.
What's coming soon is winter.
Wouldn't it be best to leave the
mountain before it starts to snow?
I can't do that.
The truth is, I have to keep that house perfect.
Until then, I don't plan to die or leave this place.
But...
Don't get carried away by a joke!
How are you going to prepare for winter?
Firewood?
Food?
You haven't prepared at all!
One way or another, it will be fine.
Thank you for worrying about me, young ladies.
Madam!
What an obstinate old lady.
Sounds just like you, that's for sure.
Give me a break. How am I...
Because, Rio, you don't listen to what others say, and sometimes you're unruly, right?
Shut up.
Hey, about that letter...
Why did you show it to me?
I told you about last week's intelligence report, but...
the truth is, the Eastern Roman Army is on the move.
Is that so? For old lady Jacott?
In that case, then bring these too!
Thank you very much!
By the way, do you know about what's happening at the peace meetings?
Well, I...
Sorry, I don't.
If only Princess Iliya were still alive...
That's right, Martin.
But didn't she have a younger sister?
4,000,000 in change.
That's the first I've heard of this.
Well, she was from a different mother, although no one's sure of her whereabouts.
She's third in line for the throne, or something like that.
Um, about that younger sister...
Uh, bye!
Thanks.
Sorry.
Want to take a walk for a bit?
Hey, Kanata.
What kind of place was the village you were born in?
Normal for the country.
There were fields, and lots of cows and goats.
But there weren't that many people.
It's not like here at all.
But it was a nice place, right?
And your parents raised you well.
I can tell by looking at you.
What kind of place were you raised in?
Well, you see...
It wasn't far from the capital.
There were beautiful forests and lakes.
It was a small village.
I lived there with my mother.
But it was also dull.
Days could go by where absolutely nothing happened.
But what kept me from giving up...
was my favorite older sister.
She would just come over and play occasionally,
but I really admired her.
She was forgiving, kind, and solemnly resigned herself to her fate.
The one I learned the trumpet from...
...was her.
But she...
...was also too kind.
Because she was so kind, she lost her life.
When I first came here, I thought this town was a maze.
I lost my way and ended up here.
At the time, I thought that I had finally reached my goal.
But I came to a realization later.
This place was simply a dead end.
That's not true at all.
I tend to get lost a lot, but...
I like being lost.
Isn't it all right to get lost?
Even if you reach a dead end?
I mean...
That's how I met you!
Sometimes I'm envious of you, Kanata.
If only I were as frank as you.
With this, we're all set.
Why are you so worried over someone like me?
Because you remind me...
...of my own mother.
I don't remember giving birth to a daughter as beautiful as you.
I was born from an unforgivable love.
She always waited, once a year, for the man who may or may not come.
And in the midst of that misfortune, she passed away.
Why do you think that was misfortune?
Because!
I'm perfectly happy.
You see...
I promised that whenever that person came back,
I'd be here to welcome him.
That promise is enough for me.
But that's...
Was there anything else I could have done?
That's right.
If there was something I could have done, I would have done it.
But you know...
Are you fine with that?
Are you really happy with that?
Since I have loving memories of him...
Since I have the hope that I can see him again once more...
it's enough for me.
It's more than enough.
If it's gotten this cold...
When I first met you, it was snowing just like this.
When Madam was young, Seize was a prosperous resort.
She fell in love with the son of a wealthy merchant.
And then became pregnant with his child.
But he was also already married.
By fortune or fate, his real wife was unable to bear any children.
So that man took the boy she bore, and brought him back to his home.
"One day, I will come back," was the promise he left her.
Even to this day, I still fantasize...
that if I had, at that time....
Jacott-san!
Life is just filled...
...with nothing but continuous losses.
But you must have first gained in order to lose.
As a result, the more happiness you gain,
the greater the sorrow you'll feel when the time comes to lose it.
But it's precisely the reminiscence of the happy times...
Precisely because they look back...
that people are able to continue living.
Oh right. Although it's probably not the best time right now...
I found it...
a picture of Princess Iliya.
Naomi-san!
Filicia, it's okay.
This was taken about five years ago, when the Princess visited Seize.
This is Shuko?
Rio-senpai.
The truth is, my parents wanted me to find a good husband,
so that he could take over the family business.
But when I heard the sound of that trumpet,
I just couldn't forget about it.
That lady...
...was Iliya-san, wasn't it?
I knew it. You really did meet her before.
It was beyond amazing.
Iliya's sound resounded within me.
And because of that, you and I met.
It's probably because I ran away to this small town.
That's why nothing mattered at first.
I always knew I was going to leave here someday.
But now, I really don't want to leave this place.
But that's all the more reason that I must.
I can do it.
It's something only I can do.
I don't plan on saying goodbye.
No matter how far apart...
...the sound will resound.
Because the sound resounds...
...it will therefore... be conveyed.
Kanata, have I been a worthy senpai up until now?
Yes, ma'am.
Thus, Rio-senpai left our side.
From now on... it will continue to resound in my heart.
An intensely, and extremely wonderful sound of the sky that she gave me.
Let’s remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let’s move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You’re just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know you know we’ll be happy!
let’s make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you count my precious hours?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
A Visitor
A Burning Snow Field
Next time: A Visitor · A Burning Snow Field