A large contingent of the Roman Army has appeared at the Seize border with Nomansland?
Aisha!
What was that gunshot?
We've secured a Roman soldier!
Is she dead?
No, she's still breathing.
Well done!
Our troops will now reconvene with the 1st and 3rd divisions at the border-
What are you-
Don't move!
Move and I'll shoot.
Commander!
Colonel, please have your men outside the fortress stand back.
What the heck's going on?
A mutiny!
The girls took our commanding officer hostage and barricaded themselves in!
What was that?
Fortunately, it missed her vital organs.
I don't think she's in any immediate danger.
Thank you, Yumina-san.
Well done.
We were planning on using her as a sacrifice to wage war.
She would be worthless if she had died.
What is going on?!
For the past month,
we have been following the Roman soldiers who were mobilizing at the rear of our country.
That was probably to gain an upper hand in the peace talks.
They sure underestimated us.
However, His Highness, the Archduke, decided to remain passive and take no action.
So, in order for them to make the first move, we need to give them a little push.
A push, like a prisoner of war being shot to death, screaming, right before their eyes.
You can't possibly be-
Peace talks are a farce!
Rome must be overthrown!
Don't you agree, Kannagi Noël--
no, my distinguished comrade, the Witch of Helvetia?
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
Enough of that!
Noël was used by you, wasn't she?!
Noël-san, you really are connected with the Invisible Reaper...
Invisible Reaper?
The one hailed as a rare, once in a century genius at the academy,
the Invisible Reaper, who revived the bio-weapons plant from the past,
is that girl sitting before you.
Your talent is wasted.
Come back to me.
Kureha-chan, throw him in the underground distillery.
My comrades have already been deployed to fight the Romans.
A little push will set the wheels in motion.
It's back to the battlefield again, huh?
Just when I thought it was finally over.
We're both jinxed.
The Colonel has been locked inside the distillery.
Thank you, Kureha-chan.
Eat some if you like.
These pastries are popular in Treize.
They're good.
Naomi-san, you're still here?
I'll leave when it gets dangerous.
This is really messed up!
The Flame Maidens were supposed to protect the city,
but instead, we're getting them involved in the battle!
Well, regarding that...
While we were hiding, I heard about the legend of the Flame Maidens from Aisha-san.
And she said that the literature handed down in Rome tells a different tale.
What does it say?
The Flame Maidens protect other lives.
Wh-What?
It's time to change shift.
It's fine.
I'd be worried with you out here.
For starters, can you really shoot someone?
If I believe strongly that it's the right choice, I might be able to.
Really?
I'm a maiden of the fortress as well.
Just like the Flame Maidens before us...
What?
You believe that fairy tale the Roman made up?
Yes.
I can sort of understand it.
The Flame Maidens protect lives.
I think that might actually be what it was.
What's the matter?
I hear it...
Hear what?
Kanata!
No matter how good her hearing is, she can't possibly hear it from this distance.
A ceasefire signal?
Yes! I heard it.
Are you certain?
Without a doubt!
It's too soon to get excited.
She might have misheard it.
Even if it's true, we don't know if the peace talks have been concluded.
Anyway, we should tell Colonel Hopkins-
There's trouble!
When I went to bring food to the Colonel, he wasn't there!
I'm glad you're safe!
Commence the strike in ten minutes.
Colonel!
Do you think that the Colonel will just listen to you?
There's no harm in trying.
Understood.
It's useless.
The Colonel was laughing...
When the Reaper that I revived killed all those people,
he laughed wholeheartedly...
He will kill...
He will fight until there's no one left.
And I had a hand in that.
It's my fault.
If you believe that, then save more lives than you've taken, Noël-san.
Aisha...
Ceasefire, you say?
Quit joking!
But I trust her ears.
That's right!
We'll vouch for her!
Even though she's easily teased, forgetful, acts like a kid and isn't sexy at all.
Onee-chan wouldn't lie!
Arrest this old woman!
Do you want a war that much?
War is what advances civilization and science.
I want to restore it... the glory man once had.
What did you say?
The Romans are attacking tomorrow morning!
So, the war is unavoidable.
Naomi-san has been arrested.
Let's go.
That's reckless!
We're opposing the Demon of Vingt!
But I want it to reach him. This sound that I've been given!
That's reckless!
You're selfish!
You can't act according to your willful notions!
We're soldiers!
Someone said... that the world is already over.
But I like this world.
I like this town.
I love the people here.
Giving up... is something I can't do.
Kanata...
Please.
Stop the war.
Aisha-san said the same thing.
But I...
I have killed many people as a soldier.
I'm just the same, Noël.
I'm... the same as you.
You have suffered enough.
So don't blame yourself any longer.
So don't...
Will you forgive me?
Thank you, Aisha.
If we do this, we can never turn back.
Are you all fine with that?
Yeah.
Then I... have nothing else to say.
Do as you please.
Thank you, Kureha-chan.
You have been objecting all this time, for our sakes.
Even I...
don't want a girl my age to be tortured!
But without Rio-senpai here...
And Noël and Kanata are so lax...
So I thought I must do my best...
Sorry for being such an unreliable Commander...
Kureha-chan.
Let's go, everyone.
Yes.
May the blessings of all of the Gods be upon the Flame Maidens.
Primary converter reactor output rising.
FAP, FAC, DMR, ECP: all green.
Superconductor circuit within stable parameters.
Fire control system: all good.
Primary and secondary armaments: operational.
Release all joint locks!
W-Weight reduction system operational. Minus influence: approximately five.
Launch preparation: complete.
We'll be fine if we do as we trained.
Let's go, my dear ones!
Right!
Prepare to fire main cannon!
Load AP round!
AP round loaded!
Target locked!
Kana-chan, the signal!
Yes!
Commence attack?!
Fire!
It's Kanata-neechan!
The Takemikazuchi...
They're inside that!
They've advanced that far in restoring the old technology?
Signal all tanks!
Go all out to prevent escape!
Commence attack!
We're not letting you through!
We don't want any more war!
Don't get in their way!
If you insist on going, you'll have to defeat us first!
That's right!
So, what will you do,
Demon of Vingt?
Turn around!
Reconvene with the forces to our rear!
The Flame Maidens protect lives.
I leave the rest to you, Kanata-san.
A very long time ago,
before the world became as it is now,
an angel sent by God to pass divine judgement was injured,
and set down its wings to rest in the far reaches of the West.
The ones who saved the angel were the maidens living in a fortress there.
Despite that the angel was sent to destroy them,
the maidens took pity on the injured angel,
borrowing the strength of an enormous spider,
and hid the angel in the valley below.
To stop the blood that was pouring out,
the maidens took turns embracing the angel's head.
And in gratitude, the angel bestowed upon the maidens a golden horn.
But before long, the townspeople discovered the angel's existence,
and set the bottom of the valley ablaze.
The maidens were devoured by the flames, and the angel's head fell.
And they slowly succumbed.
At that moment, a host of angels appeared, covering the sky above the town.
However, a miracle occurred.
A glorious sound of the heavens echoed through,
and the angels departed.
The townspeople were saved by the final maiden, who with her very last breath...
had sounded the golden horn.
Hey, you remember that girl?
The one you gave the caramel to?
She'll be caught in this too, won't she?
All units, prepare to charge!
We have no choice.
We're soldiers.
Charge!
What?
What's that?
It's an allied tank!
Which unit?
The 1121st Platoon!
It's the ceasefire signal!
No...
It's a Roman military signal!
Commander!
We can't pull back now!
Prepare main cannon!
It's useless... They're not stopping.
Commander!
Kana-chan!
That young lady...
Hey, what the heck are you doing?
I ordered you to attack!
Fire! You will fire!
Both sides, lay down your arms!
I am a daughter of the royal family, second in line to succeed the throne of Helvetia,
and fiancée to the Emperor of the Holy Rome,
Rio Kazumiya Arkadia!
I represent my father, the Archduke of Helvetia, and I am here to convey a message from the Roman Emperor!
We have attained peace.
There will be no more fighting!
Both sides are to disengage immediately!
This is an imperial decree!
Those who do not comply shall face the might of the First Helvetia Royal Guard,
in the names of both leaders!
Impossible...
So, we...
We don't have to fight anymore!
Miss!
Sergeant!
Spring is in full bloom.
Oh yeah, Noël,
what did Aisha write in her letter?
"I've recovered from my injuries and have been practising the trumpet."
Translate it!
She's fine and has been practicing trumpet.
I see. What a relief.
Aw, we even got letters from Rome, but none came from the capital.
I'm sure she's busy.
Senpai is a princess, after all.
But you know, even on the battlefield,
she was surrounded by guards,
and we didn't get to speak with her.
I hear Klaus-san's bike!
She's here! She's here!
I've been waiting for you, newbie!
I'm going to train her so har-
As of today, I will be under the command of the 1121st Platoon.
I'm Lieutenant Rio Kazumiya Arkadia.
Captain Filicia Heidemann, I request your permission to begin my duties.
Permission granted.
There are no ranks here, Rio.
Um, well...
That Roman Emperor is a pretty understanding guy...
He said he would grant a single wish as a reward for stopping the war.
And so...
Welcome home.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Welcome home, Rio.