Supervised by the OogaiFest Management Committee
33rd Annual OogaiFest
That's it for the preparations!
The cultural festival will finally start tomorrow!
Let's have a blast!
Yeah!
The President's working as hard as ever.
Let's hope she doesn't pass out from it.
Good work.
Mana, are you okay?!
Huh...
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Mana's Out of Commission!
The Hurricane of a Cultural Festival
It's overwork.
I was so worried when I heard you had fainted.
I never knew you were so exhausted...
Now that I think about it,
right after that huge crisis the other day,
Cultural Festival Meeting
she spent every waking moment preparing for the cultural festival.
Talk about overkill.
But I knew everyone was looking forward to the festival,
so I just couldn't hold myself back.
You won't be much help if you're sick in bed.
Yeah, sorry.
Either way, you still have a fever,
so get some rest tomorrow.
What?!
But the festival—
Get some rest!
Okay, good night.
Mana is such a Happy Prince.
A Happy Prince?
What do you mean?
He's a character in a fairy tale.
And Mana's just like him.
Oogai City Library
The Happy Prince
Long ago in a town far away,
there was a golden statue of a prince covered in beautiful jewels.
The prince was very kind-hearted,
and asked a swallow he met to give his jewels to the town's poor.
He gave his own jewels...
It certainly sounds like something Mana would do.
First, he gave his sword's rubies.
Next, his sapphire eyes.
Feeling those gifts wouldn't be enough,
the prince gave every part of his golden body to the people.
And then...
But... why?
The heck's that?
A Blood Ring.
It's an accessory imbued with powerful magic.
Give it a try.
You'll become stronger than you ever thought possible.
Yeah, right.
Whoah!
Incidentally, I'm now the second-in-command of the entire Selfish army.
You two will serve as my lackeys and use your power to conquer the human world.
You're the second-in-command?
Sounds like hot air to me.
I'd suggest going along quietly if you value your lives.
Don't get cocky!
You poor, poor fool.
The very power you gave us...
Is gonna knock your teeth in!
It's not comin' off!
You tricked us!
It's not my fault you two are suckers.
I made those rings from Leva and Gura's Egogy.
That means...
No, you didn't...
Now kneel before me and swear allegiance!
If you don't want to meet Leva and Gura's fate, that is.
The day is finally here...
for the cultural festival!
Gweat!
It's cool how you have a festival at school!
Is Mana's resting at home?
Yeah.
Charles should be keeping an eye on her.
Excuse me...
Where might the visitor slippers be?
Oh, those!
Right here!
The slippers.
Oh, how helpful.
Thank you.
Oh, it's nothing.
Mana?
Why are you here?
Charles should be watching you!
I couldn't stop her...
I slept overnight, so I'm fine!
That's not how fevers work!
Excuse me...
Oh, right!
I need to get to my daughter's classroom, but...
Sure!
I'll show you to it!
Wait, Mana!
A-Aguri!
Um...
Oh, sorry!
Infirmary
Do you understand what you're doing?
Huh?
The Happy Prince destroyed his body to help the townspeople!
In the end, nothing was left of him but his heart of lead!
Uh...
Everyone relied too much on the Happy Prince!
I shall handle things in your stead.
Wa...
Wait!
And you will go to sleep right this instant!
I'll call Alice over to see to it that you do.
Finally...
I, the vice president, am actually in charge of something!
I hope nothing goes wrong!
Vice President, we've got a problem!
Huh?
We've got more visitors than we expected, and now we're out of pamphlets!
A lot of kids are getting lost!
The toilet's clogged!
What do we do, VP?!
G-Good question...
I knew we needed the president...
Mana won't be coming!
You all are on the festival management committee, no?
Yeah...
I guess...
Then before you rely on others to solve such trifling issues...
try doing something about them yourselves!
Doing something right requires blood, sweat, and tears!
Is there any value in getting an answer without putting an ounce of work into finding it?
No, there darn well isn't!
They're even more spineless than I imagined.
It makes one realize just how much work Mana puts in.
I'll have to beat some responsibility into them!
Is... something wrong?
There was an elementary schooler passing by...
And she got mad at us...
We couldn't say anything to refute her...
Would you like a refill?
Um...
You're Makopi, right?
Can I get an autograph?
Huh?
I want one too!
Makopi, me first!
Makopi, autograph please!
Do something about this!
Well, it's kinda...
Stop complaining!
It may be mere performance, but at this moment, you three are this cafe's staff!
Keep that in mind,
and start acting like you are!
Okay...
Your fever seems to have come down.
Okay, by—
Not yet, I'm afraid.
You must rest more.
Aguri?
Everyone in this school is truly helpless!
Uh, what've you been doing?
Building character for this school's students!
The students here are just like the people of the fairy tale.
They only leech off the love that the Happy Prince gives them.
Oh, I don't mind too much...
It is your excessive pampering that enables them to do so!
Your actions will encourage them to continue pushing all of their work onto others,
making them targets for Selfishes!
And what will you do after you've destroyed yourself in the process?
We must make everyone stronger as individuals to prevent this outcome!
It seems you have something to say.
You might be right about needing everyone to be stronger on their own.
But hey, it's not like I can do everything.
I think everyone has things they can and can't do.
That's why when people help or are helped,
it feels like your heart races, or knots...
I think that feeling is what really counts.
Besides...
I'm sure the students here can handle problems on their own.
We're running a cafe in class 2-2.
Go there.
Nikaido, put some feeling in it!
I am...
Haha!
Can't catch me!
What the?!
Watch out!
Get away!
Did something...
That was loud...
It sure was...
Are you okay? Nothing broken?
What happened here?
Infirmary
Did something happen?
President!
I heard the wood for the bonfire collapsed!
We can't have a bonfire like this!
What do we do, President?
You all really are helpless!
Help me, Momota.
Huh?
Oh, sure!
Nikaido?
We've still got time before tonight's party!
Remember what the president said?
Let's have a blast!
We will!
Let's have a blast! Together!
Yeah...
Let's help, Vice President.
Right!
Okay.
We'll help too!
The Softball Club's helping too!
The Soccer Club's lending a foot!
Let's go, Baseball Club!
Let me help, too!
Me too!
I'll help too!
Carry it carefully!
We're putting off the evening festivities until the structure is rebuilt!
We got it, Vice President!
My heart's racing!
They're...
Um...
We thought about what you told us.
Instead of using pamphlets,
we made a chart of each class's events and put it up for display.
We gave families with children nametags at the gates,
so even if the child is lost, we can contact the parent.
We solved the clogging issue by just using the toilets in the gym.
Thank you.
Oh, no...
'N guess what?! This Ueda guy just goes and flubs it!
What a chump!
Excuse me...
You're bothering the other customers, so could you keep it down?
Okay, fine.
What the hay?
The customer's always right!
Lemme drink my tea.
Yeah, just drink your tea.
I'll go ahead and grant your desire.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Gimme a break!
Selfish!
What the heck's that?!
I won't let you ruin our festival!
Go away, monster!
Yeah, scram!
Unless you wanna go through us!
Selfish.
There has to be some place where nobody will see us...
In there!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Selfish!
Who are you all?
That was awesome!
I'm Cure Heart!
I'm here to help!
Oh poor coffee cup who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
You dang Precures!
Ira!
Will you settle down and stop this foolishness?
Shaddup! You're not the boss of me!
Selfish, show them your true power!
Selfish...
Self!
Selfselfselfselfselfselfselfselfselfselfselfselfselfselfself!
What's happening?
He's...
Stronger...
Than the rest!
I can tell!
Selfishes born from the Blood Ring are five times as fast, and ten times as strong!
And their attitude?
100 times as bad!
Selfish!
Spin!
The world is spiiiiiinniiiiiing!
Will they be okay?
It keeps spiiiiiinniiiiiing...
I'm still dizzy...
Cure Heart!
It's no surprise.
She was already sick to begin with.
We can't use the Lovely Pad without her!
I shall buy us time!
I do not get carsick!
Cure Ace!
Selfish!
It seems that Mana was in the right.
The people of fairy tales might not care if the Happy Prince is reduced to a lead heart,
but the students here are different!
You can do it!
Get him!
The love they've received from Mana took root and blossomed in their hearts!
Self!
Selfish!
I know what it is to love and be loved.
I've felt the heart race, knot, and warm.
Her love...
is within my own heart, as well!
Selfish!
That love is dear to us all...
and that's why I'll protect it!
Self?
Ace Mirror Flash!
Self!
What the heck?
Ace has a new attack?
Is it a miracle of the Lovely Pad?
Cure Heart!
Sorry about that! I'm okay now!
Magical Lovely Pad!
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Precure Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love looooove!
Huh?
This was just my way of saying hello!
I'm out!
Those girls are gone!
Who were they?
Aguri, thanks.
Huh?
You were worried about me all day,
and you worked really hard filling in for me.
I think the love the Happy Prince gave to the townspeople may have reached them.
If he were in a world where his love would be repaid like yours was today,
you might not sacrifice yourself,
and the people you help might not become Selfishes.
That would be nice.
Let's dance.
I'd like to make that dream a reality.
That's why I'll keep fighting for love with you!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
I hereby announce that we're having a sleepover!
We'll tell secrets we'd never tell outside!
Oh, my father has returned home.
Your father reminds me of that one time...
Yes, I remember...
What are you talking about?
Oh, tell me about it.
Then we shall.
It seems it shall be a long night.
Dokidoki Precure:
Alice's Daddy Arrives!
A Sleepover at the Yotsuba's!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!