You deceived us, didn't you?
I merely asked if you wanted to be a magical girl.
I just didn't explain some aspects of being one.
Why didn't you tell us?!
You didn't ask.
If you never found out, it wouldn't have bothered you a bit.
Mami, for example, never did.
Besides, you humans don't even realize you have souls in the first place.
Your body's nothing more than a collection of neurons and a centralized cardiovascular system.
So when a human body can no longer maintain life, its soul vanishes along with it.
I gave your soul a physical form to prevent that from happening—a form you can pick up with your own hands and protect.
That way you can battle witches a little more safely.
Nobody asked you to do that!
You're taking fighting far too lightly.
For example, how much do you think it would stimulate your pain receptors if your stomach were to be impaled by a spear?
This is how it would actually feel.
You can't even move, and that's how it would feel with only one strike.
The only reason you were able to remain standing during your fight with Kyouko was that anything too painful was limited.
It was only possible because your consciousness isn't directly linked with your body.
You survived your fight because of it.
If you got used to it, you could learn to completely cut off all pain.
But since your reaction times would slow, I don't suggest it.
Why...
Why did you do this to us?
You had a wish so important that you agreed to a fate of combat, am I correct?
And your wish came true, didn't it?
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll walk upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 7  Can you come to terms with how you really feel?
4sevens has the best flashlights
this is all aya's fault
a mean infinity, a base and slavish eternity
Stand.
Bow.
Homura-chan, did you know about that?
Why didn't you tell us?
No one has believed me thus far, even when I warned them in advance.
Why does Kyubey do something so cruel?
He doesn't think it's cruel.
He's a creature that doesn't understand human values.
He'll just say it was an appropriate payment for bringing about a miracle.
That's not fair at all!
He did that to her, and all Sayaka-chan wanted to do was heal someone she loved!
It was still a miracle.
He made the impossible possible.
Even if Miki Sayaka spent her entire life tending to him,
he would never have been able to play the violin again.
Normally a miracle costs far more than a human life,
but Kyubey goes around selling them for that price.
Sayaka-chan won't be able to go back to her normal life?
I've said this already, have I not? Give up on Miki Sayaka.
Sayaka-chan saved me!
If Sayaka-chan wasn't a magical girl at the time, Hitomi-chan and I would have died!
You mustn't confuse gratitude and responsibility.
There is no way for you to save her.
You want to repay her so you don't feel inferior, but it's not your place and you need to stop thinking that way.
Homura-chan, why are you always so cold?
I suppose I am. It might be because I'm no longer human.
How can I visit Kyousuke after being turned into this thing?
Just how long are you going to lie there and mope, dummy?
Come out for a bit.
We need to talk.
You're beginning to regret what was done to your body, aren't you?
I'm kind of just going with it.
I mean, I can do whatever I want with the power I got out of the deal.
It's not really something to regret at the end of the day.
You just got what you deserved.
That's a good idea. You can think of it that way.
If you live only for yourself, everything you do is your own fault.
You have no reason to resent others, and there's no way you'll have any regrets.
You can get through just about anything if you think that way.
Why did you bring me all the way out here?
It'll be kind of a long talk.
Want one?
Don't waste food.
I'll kill you.
This was my dad's church.
He was extremely honest and way too kind.
Every day when he read the newspaper in the morning, he'd start to tear up and seriously worry about things—he was that type of guy.
My dad always said that in order to save a new era, you'd need a new type of religion.
That's why sometimes he'd preach things that weren't part of the doctrine.
As a result, everyone stopped coming, of course.
He was even excommunicated.
No one would listen to what he had to say.
I mean, it makes sense.
It would seem like some sort of sketchy cult if you knew nothing about it.
But it wouldn't matter if he was talking about doing what was right, or what was obvious—he was an outcast in the eyes of society.
Our whole family was left with nothing, not even food to eat.
I couldn't accept it.
My dad wasn't saying anything wrong. He was just saying things that differed from the norm.
If anyone would lend him their ear for just five minutes, they'd realize that what he was saying was right.
But no one listened to him in the end.
I couldn't stand it.
I couldn't forgive what was happening.
I couldn't bear the fact that no one understood what he was saying.
That's why I asked Kyubey to make it so people would seriously listen to what he was saying.
The next morning, my dad's church was filled with people.
The number of believers multiplied at a frightening rate each day,
and I became yet another magical girl.
No matter how good my dad's sermons were, it wouldn't help in killing any of the witches.
I thought that was where I came in, so I got all hyped up about it like an idiot.
I thought that my dad and I would save the world—he publicly, and me from the shadows.
But one day my dad found out what was going on.
My dad completely flipped out once he found out most of his followers were there not because of his sermons, but because of magic.
He called me, his daughter, a witch that swayed people's hearts.
Pretty funny, huh? I had been fighting real witches every night and that's what he had to say.
And then my dad snapped.
He was pitiful in the end.
He drowned himself in alcohol and went crazy.
Eventually he took his whole family with him and killed himself,
leaving me behind.
My wish destroyed my family.
Everyone ended up worse off just because I made a selfish wish without knowing what anyone else would think.
That's when I swore to myself that I'd never use magic for others again.
I'd use my powers only for myself.
Miracles aren't free.
If you wish for hope, an equal amount of despair scatters across the world.
It all cancels out to zero; that's how the balance of the world is maintained.
Why are you telling me this?
You just need to stop worrying about everything and do whatever you want—
you know, since you got what you deserve becoming a magical girl and all.
Isn't there something wrong with that?
If you're trying to live only for yourself, why'd you even worry about me?
We both started from the same mistake.
You shouldn't continue regretting things.
You've already paid too much for what you got.
You should start thinking about how to get some change back.
Just like you?
That's right.
I've come to realize that, but you keep making mistakes.
That's just hard to watch.
I had the wrong idea about you.
I'm sorry for that. I apologize.
But I don't regret the fact that I used my wish for someone else's benefit.
I've decided to never regret my actions, so I don't cheapen the feelings I had when I first made the wish. Not now, not ever.
Why are you...
I don't believe that I've paid too much.
I can do plenty of wonderful things with this power, depending on how I use it.
And what about you? How did you get those apples?
How did you get the money to buy them?
Can't say anything, can you?
I can't eat one of those apples, then.
I wouldn't even want one.
You dumbass!
We're magical girls!
There's no one else like us!
I will continue to fight in my own way.
If that happens to conflict with you in some way,
you can just try to kill me again.
I won't lose, and I won't hate you for it.
Good morning, Sayaka-chan!
Good morning, Sayaka-san.
Good morning.
What happened yesterday?
I felt a little sick.
Sayaka-chan...
It's okay. I'm fine now.
Don't worry about me.
Anyway, let's get...
My, Kamijou-kun was released from the hospital?
Kamijou, are you okay now?
Yeah. If I sit at home all day, my rehabilitation won't go anywhere.
I'm aiming for being able to walk without crutches by next week.
I'm glad Kamijou-kun's doing well.
Yeah...
Sayaka-chan, go say hi.
You haven't said anything to him yet, right?
I'm... good.
So, what did you want to talk about?
I want to ask you about someone I like.
I've been keeping something from you and Madoka-san for a while now.
Huh?
O-Okay...
I've...
been attracted to Kamijou Kyousuke for a while now.
I-I see.
I never would have expected that from you, Hitomi.
Kyousuke's pretty suave.
You've known him for a long time, right?
Yeah, but we just kinda hang out cause we've known each other for a while, I guess.
Is that really all?
I've decided that I won't lie to myself anymore.
What about you?
Sayaka-san, can you come to terms with your own feelings?
Wh-What are you talking about?
You're an important friend to me.
So I don't want to try and go after him if you're already with him, or try to steal him from you.
You've spent far more time with him than I have.
That's why you should have the right to go after him first.
Hitomi...
I will tell Kamijou after school tomorrow that I like him.
I will wait one day exactly.
Please decide on a course of action that you won't regret.
It's up to you whether or not you think you should tell him how you feel.
I-I...
Madoka...
Can I go with you?
I don't want you to be alone, so...
Why are you...
Why are you so kind to me?
I'm not worth it.
That's not true...
Today, I almost started to regret what I did.
I thought, just for one second, about what would have happened if I didn't save Hitomi.
I'm a failure of a hero.
I couldn't look Mami-san in the face.
Hitomi is going to take Kyousuke!
But I can't do anything about it!
I'm already dead!
I'm a zombie!
I couldn't ask him to hold me when I've become this thing.
I couldn't ask him to kiss me.
Thank you. I'm sorry...
Sayaka-chan...
I'm fine now.
I feel better.
Anyway, let's go. We have to get us a witch tonight.
Right.
I'm surprised you're just sitting here watching.
She's fighting a witch today, not a familiar.
It'll drop a Grief Seed. It's not a pointless hunt.
And you'd let her take your prey for that, huh?
Damn, that idiot.
She's having trouble.
Sayaka-chan!
God damn, I couldn't just sit there any longer.
Anyway, just get back.
I'll show you the basics.
Hey!
Don't get in my way.
I can do it myself.
Sayaka-chan!
Are you...
It's true!
If you want, you really don't
have to feel pain anymore!
Stop... Please stop...
Someday the light of love you hold within your eyes will transcend time
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光がときを超えて
and destroy the dream of a world racing towards destruction.
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ壊すだろう
Now that you've drank every ounce of your hesitation, what do you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Will there be a fleeting tomorrow for this greedy admiration?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
I want to see you, smiling with the power to shatter even darkness,
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was young.
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Everything depends on these feelings of courage from the flower that was plucked
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
that now lays in my frightened hands.
思いだけが頼るすべて
This wish will awaken that light.
光を呼び覚ます願い
Illustrator Tensugi Takashi
I'm going to become a different type of magical girl than all of you.
I've decided that.
I don't need any reward for my work.
I'll never use magic for my own good.
Episode 8     I'm really stupid
I'm really stupid.
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Chika
Editor: limitbreakingcat
Timer: kozu
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Quality Check: kozu
rune
thedarkhaze
King_Arthur