This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old!
A
u
dition.
Unfortunately... she's only going to live 'til next spring...
We came to make sure her fate wouldn't be changed, but...
...Mitsuki can now turn into the sixteen-year-old Full Moon.
When she told her manager
and her doctor about it...
...it seems like they somewhat believed her...
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
What's that?
Meroko, Left Alone
You sure you didn't forget anything?
Yep!
Isn't it wonderful how you're getting out so early?
Yes, come in.
D-Dr. Wakaouji!
Thank you for taking care of her!
S-Sure...
Madam told me to pass on her appreciation.
Is that so?
How are you feeling?
Yep!
I feel great!
Sensei, thank you for everything!
You're still keeping the fact that you can
change a secret from your grandma, right?
Ah... yeah...
Then...
Him, too?
Ah... yeah...
Well then... take care of yourself.
Ah, Dr. Wakaouji.
Once I've gotten her settled in...
T-That's okay...
I have a patient to examine.
Thanks, though.
That doctor...
...seems like he doesn't like me...
T-That's just your imagination!
Oh well...
I can't help it if he hates me.
After all... I'm a Shinigami, and he's a doctor.
Madam was so worried about you...
I was quite surprised.
Really?
Grandma...
You still care so much about me...
Please consider just how much you've
imposed upon those who care about you!
First, Dr. Wakaouji had to take care of you.
Everyone was running around looking for you.
I'm really sorry.
Really...
Be more careful about your health.
Um...
How are you feeling, Grandma?
It's just the heat that's getting me.
There is no need to worry.
I see...
I'll excuse myself.
Congratulations on getting released, Mitsuki.
Thank you, Ooshige-san!
We'll start work again after
things have calmed down, okay?
Sorry about that.
Instead of that...
...be sure to apologize to everyone when you come back, okay?
Okay!
I'll get in touch with you again, then.
Hey! Stupid kid!
Why the heck doesn't this room have any air conditioning?!
It's bad for my throat.
Besides... we're at a high elevation, so there's a cool breeze.
It isn't cool at all!
Anyways...
What happened to Meroko?
Who knows...
Takuto.
Are you still mad?
What... you're not mad at her?
It's her fault that you lost the audition.
Meroko must have had her reasons...
T-That's true, but...
Thanks to Meroko, you...
But...
...because of that, I was able to tell
Wakaouji-sensei and Ooshige-san everthing.
I-I guess so.
All that's left is for Meroko to come back...
Meroko...
Where did you go?
I didn't do anything wrong!
I was just doing my duty as a Shinigami.
What's wrong with that?!
Takuto, you're such a jerk!
Good afternoon!
Yes, yes?
Wh-What is it?
Is Mitsuki-san here?
Yes?
We all came to see her!
We were so surprised when we heard you were in the hospital.
But... isn't it great that you're all better now?
Yep.
Thanks.
Wow!
That's such a big garden!
There's even a pond!
It's amazing!
Hey!
Can we take a look around?
Sure.
Tanaka-san.
Ah, madam.
We have guests?
Yes, they're all friends of Mitsuki-san.
This is the first time we've had so
many people over... I was so surprised!
What?
There's a ghost story at our school?
Someone saw one in the gym at our school.
No way!
In the dead of night...
In the empty gym...
A basketball goes... boom... boom...
P-Please stop.
I can't take this...
We've found Mitsuki's weakness!
This is all it takes, huh?
That's 'cause...!
That ghost must be lonely.
That's why it's waiting for someone to play with.
Eh?
'Cause... you can't play basketball by yourself, right?
That's true...
Then... could it be...
...Meroko?
You don't have to escort us out.
You shouldn't stain yourself yet.
Okay.
Thanks for coming today!
See you later then!
Bye, bye!
Ah... what an ordeal!
Hey, Takuto.
Huh?
What is it?
It's about Meroko...
Y-You're still talking about that...?!
You know... Meroko's... probably at school...
I don't want to hear it!
Ah, Takuto!
Geez!
I'm tired of it...
Are you here, Meroko?
T-This is bad!!
I can't move!
Are you all right, Meroko?
I'm fine.
What?
Takuto hasn't said anything?
Yeah.
He won't tell me when I ask him either.
M-My reason... my reason was...
It doesn't matter.
After all, I didn't get hurt.
It's just...
When you're gone...
...it feels like something's missing... something's wrong...
If the three of us aren't together...
If it's not the three of us, together, like before...
...it feels lonely.
Okay.
Let's go back together!
I want to go back too...
I want to, but Takuto...
I'm sure that Takuto wants you to come back too.
You think so?
Hmm?
You shouldn't have come back!
Why's that?!
I'm finally alone with her now!
In other words... you're a third wheel!
I-I can't!
It's better for Takuto if I'm not around...
Huh?
I-In any case... I can't go back.
Bye.
Meroko!
Geez...
It's hot... it's uncomfortable...
So hot...
D-Don't even think about it!
But... I haven't said anything yet!
It's probably about Meroko anyways.
Ah, you already knew.
Well, you see...
...I want you to go bring Meroko back.
She's at school...
Look here.
Why do I have to bring her back?
If she wants to come back, she can come back on her own.
Eh?
It's okay then?
T-That's Meroko's problem.
It wasn't anything I did!
I see.
You're right.
W-Wait a second!
Did Takuto really say that it was okay?
He sure did.
B-But...
Come on already...
But...
I don't know what I should say to him...
Wouldn't "I'm back!", be enough?
But I doubt that Takuto would say "Welcome back!"...
You're still saying that!
If you keep thinking like that... things will be like this forever!
Is that okay with you?!
Not really, but...
Wow!
What a blue sky!
And white clouds, too!
It's so beautiful...
Hey Takuto, come look!
No point.
Besides... Shinigami...
...don't have "blue skies" or "white clouds", you know.
Ah...
I-Is that so...
Yes, it is.
Meroko, come over here!
Come on!
The two of you...
Hello, Tomoe-chan?
Well...
I have a hypothetical question for you...
If two good friends aren't talking to each other...
...what should I do?
Clear Weather
Hmm...
Maybe you could set them up?
What do you mean by set them up?
Anything works.
If you set them up...
...the rest is up to them.
Set them up, huh...
Mitsuki-san.
Are you going to stay on the phone forever?
Isn't a lengthy phone call a hassle for your friend?
Ah, yes.
Ah!
Hey, Tomoe-chan?
I don't mind.
Really?!
Thank you so much!
Make sure you're ready in case of a fire.
Have some water nearby.
Okay!
Excuse me!
Fireworks with her firends, huh?
That sounds like fun!
Ah... please excuse me.
I was too forward.
There is nothing to apologize for.
I-I suppose so.
Ah...
By the way...
May I go and prepare something for the children?
Do as you wish.
Yes!
Eh?!
Real fireworks?!
Yep.
I have a fireworks set...
...but I want ones that go Kaboom !
I guess it's all right...
I'll be counting on you then!
Real fireworks?!
Yep!
Just one of the ones that goes Kaboom !
Hmm...
I suppose it's okay...
May we come in?!
Ah! Welcome!
Excuse us for imposing!
Good evening.
Mitsuki-chan's waiting for you.
Come... it's this way.
Ah!
W-What is this?!
(Soumen Nagashi [Floating Noodles]: A summer festival activity where people sit at a trough and pick out noodles for dipping.)
A long Soumen!
Yes.
Please... eat up, everyone!
This feels so nostalgic!
Hey, hey. You can eat soumen with ginger, right?
Eh? Our family uses mayonnaise, though.
Welcome!
Mitsuki!
So cute!
It's wonderful!
You look beautiful, Mitsuki!
R-Really?
Thanks for inviting us today!
Everyone!
It's about time to begin!
Okay!
Catch!
Ah!
I missed that one!
It's pretty!
Hey, hey, hey!
I wanna do one too!
Wow!
It's beautiful!
I wonder if it'll go well...
Ah?
Everyone, over here!
Okay!
It's raining at a time like this...
It isn't stopping...
Why did it have to rain...
What?
It's just an evening shower...
It'll stop soon.
I hope so...
Anyways... isn't this great?
You have all these friends now.
Yep!
It's all thanks to you and Meroko.
You know... back when my CD came out...
Something like that happened as well...
And then...
When Meroko turned into me...
...and started selling CDs...
...I was wondering what would happen.
She had us in a bind there.
But... it was for the best.
Yeah.
You...
After hearing that...
Aren't you going to tell Meroko?
You found out?
Well, it doesn't matter.
But...
To tell you the truth...
The first friends I've ever made...
...were you and Meroko.
That's why...
...you two are very precious friends.
I want you two to make up.
The rain stopped!
Let's keep going!
Hazuki...
Okay. Let's launch the skyrockets!
All right!
Do it! Do it!
Now, right?
Go!
It's so cute!
It's a bunny and a cat!
W-What's that?
I only made a bunny...
That girl...
I understand.
Hey, Meroko.
Takuto... I...
You... won't forgive me... will you?
Bye!
Hold on!
Don't just assume what someone else is feeling.
Then... you'll forgive me?
Let's do that... you know?
It's absurd to hide our name
when our cover is blown...
We... who will even lie to crying children...
The Shinigami Duo!
Takuto!
Meroko!
With out powers combined... we are...
Spring Onion Ramen!
I'm so glad.
What is it, Mitsuki?
I'm glad that...
...that there were spring onion ramen fireworks... something like that.
What are you saying... silly Mitsuki.
What am I saying...
Good night!
Be careful on the way home!
Mitsuki-san.
Did everyone go home after having a good time?
Yeah...
That's good.
But, Mitsuki-san...
You are still recovering from your illness.
Dress warmly and go to sleep.
Ah, okay.
That is all.
Grandma.
What is it?
Thanks for always worrying about me!
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Takuto! Meroko!
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
It looks like Grandma and me...
...are going to get along just fine!
Is that so?
Sure is.
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Ah!
Geez! She's so irritating !
That Wakamatsu Madoka is back again!
Hey.
Why are you going so far as to call that Madoka an enemy?
She might be a surprisingly good person.
There's no way!
The one who tore apart her costume...
It was definitely that Madoka's doing!
Anyways...
This isn't the time to be saying that!
She goes back to work today!
We have to be there for her!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
New Feelings
Look forward to it!