The students’ transformation that happened in the past few days…
…looks like it had something to do with the darkness.
Did you notice anything related to it?
There is a disturbance in the magnetic field.
I have a bad feeling about this world.
Is it an omen?
I don’t know.
But we need to be careful.
Eva…
I’m going back to sleep.
Is she feeling ill or something?
She has had a headache since this morning.
Is this an omen of the terrible situation that was just mentioned?
Perhaps Takamichi and Chachamaru don’t realize it. Well, in a good way.
Hey Chachamaru-kun, are you sure it’s actually a headache?
I’m sure of it.
by Satsuki
Darkness is on the move again?
Really!?
I don’t know what’s going to happen from here on.
We should be careful.
Anyway, what is this?
Does it have something to do with the investigation of The Darkness?
Nope, that’s not it.
I found it in the kitchen.
Oh it’s food…
Squid Cutlets, pickles, oiled sardines, dried mullet roe, pistachio...
It’s just a delicacy right?
I think I might be able to make the Worldwide Original Ramen.
Ramen!?
Yep.
I’ll call it the World Ramen Delicacy. If I can make it taste nice, I’ll treat you guys to it.
Er… Yeah! I’ll look forward to it!
The Darkness is still spreading, but you’re being so carefree…
A calm mind, is an important asset for all situations.
Oh… Now that you say it, yeah… that seems to be the case.
Yeah. The fairy in the fragment manipulated people in our class.
I think Chisame was also manipulated before, right?
That’s true, but when I was being manipulated, I didn’t realize what was going on.
I just thought of this. What kind of standards are we choosing anyway?
Standards?
Ah. I see. The people manipulated by the fairy may have some common traits.
Hmm, that might be a hint to the puzzle of the fragments, eh?
Common traits… like?
Everyone really wants to see Chisame-chan as a Net Idol!
That’s wrong! I am not a Net Idol!
Not a Net Idol, eh?
Really?
But the person in question has the same weight!
Chizuru-san…
Oh yeah! Natsumi was also manipulated! Let’s hear it from her!
Err, it’s not that important.
Yeah. Not that important.
I don’t think that’s the case.
Ara, is that right? Hmm…
Aha, that’s right, if that’s the case, then I’m stupid!
Ah, you got mail.
It’s Chizu-nee!
Ehhhh!?
That’s quite cold of her…
Hey, Misora-chan, this pose is…
Do not speak.
Misora-chan, um…
Misora…
Don’t!
Huh!? No!?
I’m not good!?
I’m a failure!?
YES! You ARE a failure.
You, Sasaki Makie, fails at life!
You don’t have to force it into here you know…
Doing things halfway makes you feel bad doesn’t it?
Sasaki Makie fails!
Ah! Negi-sensei! Where are you going?
Ah! Class Rep! I’m just…
Evangeline is sleeping with a headache.
Eva-san?
Don’t do that Chamo-kun!
We already promised Takamichi that we won’t tell anyone!
Ah! I forgot!
Hey Ane-san, please forget what I said just now.
You think I can just do that?
Negi, are you going to see her?
Let’s go together!
Uh… okay!
See? You just made it a big deal.
I’m sorry…
Alright, let’s tell the others to come as well!
I wonder if it’s alright to let everyone else know…
Ah. That’s right…
I don’t think that would be a good idea…
Oh, I agree.
As expected of Negi-sensei.
We shouldn’t say things that may hurt people!
Sasaki Makie fails!
Eva is just fine at the moment. It’s just the situation that we are in now.
“Just fine”?
What do you mean, Chachamaru-san?
Don’t tell me Eva-san’s condition has worsened?
No, my master is feeling very well.
Then what’s up with the…
Well, how should I put this…
Well, the sleeping beauty grew up.
Oh… She grew up…
That’s too much!
Oh no she’s gonna blow!
Ta~mayaa!
We’re saved…
Thanks, Oneechan.
You’re welcome.
Even so…
What the hell just happened!?
It’s the darkness, it must be the effects of the darkness…
Ah! She’s up and moving!
I wonder where to?
Wait up a minute!
Are we really doing it?
It sounds embarrassing…
It’s all good! Preparations OK!
Should we run, Ojou-sama?
We’ll get chased even if we run… I’m sure of it.
Oh come on. Hurry up! Hurry up!
She’s in high spirits isn’t she, de gozaru?
We can’t do anything about it.
Let’s go, everyone.
Ahhh… Help us…
The lush tea and whatever yada yada and the other stuff.
How incoherent…
I am The Black Rose Baron!
Yes! Applause!
Ah! Thank you, thank you…
BLACK ROSE!
Everyone! There’s trouble!
What is it?
Is there a problem?
Err… um… well…
Ah, Nekane-san!
Yep!
This is…
Black Rose!
The Baron, when did another one come out!?
I don’t know…
No, no, that’s not it, Negi-kun.
This is a fake.
Fake?
There!
Ane-san!
Owwh, don’t spoil it, Konoka!
Don’t CALL ME A FAKE!
But you’re still a fake…
Why are you dressed like this Asuna-san?
Looks like she exchanged something for it.
Exchanged?
In exchange for a Chupa-Tee…
…she received the costume.
Chupa-Tee?
Now that you say it, Nekane, you’ve been wearing that since the morning haven’t you?
Huh? What’s wrong?
Uh… erm! Nothing!
In any case, Negi-bouzu. What was the trouble you were about to tell us?
Oh! Right!
Yeah! We are in a state of emergency!
A state of emergency?
This is…!?
She…
…has come.
It’s Eva-chan!
Big!!
Everyone! Please run!
You monster!
Alright! From here on the Black Rose Baron will…
Asuna-san, please stop fooling around and get out of here!
It’s dangerous!
I’m not fooling around. I’m serious!
BLACK ROSE!
Black Rose!
Do you want to die!?
Come on, quickly!
Huh? It’s okay if we don’t run.
Nekane-san, what are you saying?
Because it’s Eva-chan.
All personnel! Take cover!!
That was the right thing to do.
Asuna-san, get away, quick!
I can’t let her pursue you!
Eva-san! It’s me! Negi!
Negi?
It’s dangerous, Aniki!
Eva-san!
Negi!
Aniki!
Asuna-san!
R…run.
She’s heavy so hurry up!
A…alright!
Aniki!
Are you alright?
Asuna-san! Thank you very much!
What you gonna do if you get squished? Stupid Negi.
Waaaah! I’m so s…s…sorry!
Can’t we do anything?
What can we do?
Chachamaru-san!
How about we discuss this with Takahata-sensei?
That’s right.
Takamichi, we’ve got trouble!
Takahata-sensei!
Did something happen?
Ah? Yeah… nothing much…
Ah! Don’t tell me…
It’s the Ramen Delicacy just now?
Aah… It failed, Negi-kun.
I’m still a long way from success, hahaha…
Takamichi…
I wonder…
Onee-chan!!
What the hell are you doing!?
Instinct?
Yeah. I think that Eva probably didn’t intentionally come to school, but rather by instinct.
Evangeline likes the school?
Nah. She hates it no matter what.
It doesn’t matter if she likes it or not, but it’s probably better if her body is the thing in control right now.
Master has been in the school for the past 15 years, that’s why.
15 years…
That’s long…
The Evangeline A.K. McDowell who has just become a giant…
Due to the many years of going to school instinctively returned to school again…
And, began to sleep on the roof as if she did it all the time.
She looks like she’s sleeping comfortably.
Looks like it.
Is that right…?
Won’t she return to her normal form?
It’s not like she did anything bad.
She is sleeping after all…
What's the matter?
Negi-bouzu! We have a problem-aru!
The building is…
Eva-chan’s body is too heavy!
This is a problem…
I don’t think it would be a problem the school disappears.
Hey, hey…
I think it’s okay to let it collapse.
Are you sure it’s alright, Ojou-sama!?
If you think about it, won’t that make this place dangerous, too?
Oh that’s true.
If it collapses, we’ll be affected too-aru!
Everything will be broken together with it!
Eeh!? If this place collapses that would be troublesome!
Negi-kun…
Everyone, please get together!
This has become a problem.
Everyone, please give your opinions.
Yep, Negi-kun!
Yes, Asakura-san.
Can’t we do anything using magic?
Well, my magic is a little…
What about Takahata-sensei?
He’s in bed because of a stomach ache.
Eh!? No way!
Because of that silly World Delicacy Noodles…
World Delicacy Noodles?
Satsuki, what are those noodles?
I don’t know about that kind of noodle.
Anyway, what about Nekane-san?
I’m sorry, Oneechan is also…
Also down from the World Delicacy Noodles.
World Delicacy Noodles you say!?
I see, that means we can’t do anything about Eva-san…
But, what about the World Delicacy Noodles!?
Yes, Mana-san?
Removal by force.
A more peaceful idea, please.
We might make her act violently! The school might collapse because of that!
But, what about the World Delicacy Noodles!?
We can ask her to come down with a “GET DOWN HERE RIGHT NOW”.
I don’t think she’ll be able to hear you.
Besides, that wasn’t a request. That sounded more like an order!
What about we find something she’s interested in?
Ah! That might work!
Let’s call the sky devil!
You mean the sky rock.
That was what I said.
30 Points.
15 Points.
No way, that was right.
Yes, Asuna-san?
Since she’s already up there, why don’t we just hang her up?
How do you do that up there?
From an empty spot I suppose.
You suppose?
Anything will do I suppose.
Geez, Asuna-san…
Natsumi, it’s your turn.
What?
Your bravery, I will never forget it in my lifetime. Thank you, Natsumi! Farewell…
I won’t do, I definitely won’t do!
Negi-sensei
Yes, Yue-san.
I think Nodoka has something to say.
Ah, yes!
Nodoka-san, what is it?
Ah yes!
My encyclopaedias might have the answer to this problem… I think.
Partner, Miyazaki Nodoka…
Show me the power within you!
Contract,
activate!
Splendid! It’s an armor-card-mya.
I see! If we use Nodoka-san’s encyclopaedias…
We might just be able to find a solution!
Let’s do it, Nodoka-san.
Alright!
…what should we do with a giant Evangeline-san…
Isn’t that a bit vague?
Ah! I got it!
Huh, really!?
What should we do?
In the meantime, we let her sleep quietly.
That’s too bad.
Life ain’t that easy.
It’s no use, eh?
Negi-sensei
Hakase, Chisame-san!
There is a way!
The Mechacabra version 2!
Chiu-chiu-san has added some power ups to it!
Don’t call me Chiu-chiu!
Why me again…
Anyway, what is the power up?
The spikes are a different colour!
I painted them.
So that’s what they call cooperation…
Anything goes. Anyway, hurry up, we’re counting on you Hakase onee-san!
Leave it to us!
Anyway, Hakase-san, how… I mean what does this Mechacabra do?
Stand by!
AAAAAAH! It’s moving again!
Launch!
It failed, huh.
Actually, that’s all it can do…
Eeeh… Negi-sensei!
Are you okay, Negi?
Yeah… somehow…
It’s already at its limit!
The walls are cracking up!
It’s useless...
Is that a band?
Chachamaru-san?
That song is waking her up-mya.
Eva is…
Climbing down from the building!
Why?
Alright!
The school is saved!
She’s following the sound.
That sounds like the Pipe of Hamelin.
Onee-chan! Takamichi!
I guess we found a solution after all.
Takahata-sensei, what do you mean by that?
The Heart of Japan.
In the 15 years Eva stayed in Mahora Academy, there was only one thing she liked.
That is the culture of the Japanese people.
Culture?
Inside Eva, she thinks the school is the Heart of Japan, that’s why she returned.
The Heart of Japan?
Eva-san…
Amazing…
That was such a beautiful story!
I’m moved!
And so, the school was saved from collapse by a hair’s breadth…
BUT, the magic world is beginning to change again. A storm is coming.
Watch it in the next episode!
Did anything happen today?
No, nothing much.
I feel tired somehow…
Sasaki Makie fails…
Now, we have picked out a Chamo!
I’m an ermine.
Be quiet.
Next time, “Takamichi, the Silent Ramen Man” by Takahata
“What the hell is that!?” By Chamo.
Now we put it into the hat…
Ahhh! Wonderful!
Chamo has just…
…gone into a bowl of Ramen!
Oh? Miss Ghost, eh?
Yeah! It’s amazing isn’t it?
Do you explode?
Well, exploding is a bit…
What about a big explosion?
Suicide bombing?