so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice
Someone was there singing for you, the happiness they sang about
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this gentle light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
It sounds like something that might wake the dead.
A Day in the Life - Rio Runs
Let's eat.
How is it?
It tastes great.
Yes. It's delicious.
At least it's edible.
That's good.
This is a traditional food in my village.
So this is that miso thing? And it's made the same way as soy?
Yes.
I brought some miso that my mother made.
There's still a lot more, so eat as much as you want!
To Treize?
Yes.
We finally received word from the Supply Corps.
Kureha and I will go to pick them up.
We were just about to run out of ammunition, medical supplies, and daily necessities.
Now we can rest easy.
What about you, Noël?
Carl's workshop, right?
Got you.
Kanata.
You're getting a full workout on that bugle this afternoon.
Eh? Really?
Heref youf hoof.
Gosh...
Where are your manners?
Wouldn't your dad cry if he saw you?
Heh... Wike a' cabe
Here, for your tea.
Fortune cookies?
You really can't stand them, can you?
But you can't blame those kids at the church.
Everyone who takes advantage of worthless superstitions to get some sort of profit is the same.
Not at all.
The ones here taste good.
Oh, my.
But Kanata has really gotten used to this place.
She's always trying so hard. It's cute.
You think?
I have to admit she's diligent and full of enthusiasm.
But I'm not the type to think you can get by with just that.
Why are you giving me that look?
That's a secret.
Come on. Quit playing me.
We'll be going then.
It might take a while to get back.
Got you. Take care.
Don't make any problems for Rio, got it?
Sure.
Commencing operation.
Drive carefully!
I don't expect you to be able to do this, but controlling the note with just the mouthpiece is one of the basics.
Try it.
Yes, sir.
How's life in the fort so far?
It's fun!
You're lax enough to say it like that.
I'm almost kind of jealous.
While we're still on it, why'd you enlist in the army?
Well, um...
I heard I could learn how to play an instrument for free.
Oh, but I also thought that it was important to protect my country!
I don't mind. Even if it's for money or whatever,
the ones with some ambition stay around longer.
Um... I'm honored...
So, why did you join?
Me? Well, probably the opposite of you.
They are pretty hard to find these days.
You don't hear brass instruments much outside the army.
I heard one a long time ago.
Just... like... yours...
Kanata?
The sound... of the sky.
What's wrong? Pull yourself together!
Pull yourself together, Kanata!
Answer me!
No!
Please, just stay still.
It's hot!
It's hot, Mom!
Is it hot?
Don't worry, you'll be alright.
You'll be alright.
Mo-
Mom!
What's wrong, Kanata?
Kanata!
I want to eat... snow.
Got it. Wait right there!
Snow. Snow. Snow. Where's the snow?
Why the hell would we have snow?
Calm down. Calm down.
Medicine!
No. That's the last resort.
Medicine. Medicine.
Medicine!
Here it is!
We were just about to run out...
Those idiots!
Damn the Supply Corps!
Dammit! I can't do anything...
What should I do?
Dammit!
Sound of the Sky
Um... excuse me...
Can I help you?
I hope the children didn't cause you any-
I apologize for my past disrespect!
So, please...
Help me...
Drink this.
Just like that.
Her fever is a bit high, but it should fall now.
Is it a serious disease at all?
I think it's roseola.
Roseola? Only kids catch that...
Adults can catch it under extreme fatigue.
When we take in new children,
a lot of them catch it right away.
The healthier they look, the higher the fever goes.
She's probably been hiding it the whole time.
Then... will Kanata get better?
She won't stay like this...
I think she'll be fine.
What a relief.
Thank you...
Um...
My name is Yumina.
Oh.
This is made with medicinal herbs.
Please have her drink some later.
Um... Thank you for everything.
Don't mention it at all.
To serve the people of this town is our joy and our duty.
Now then,
May the blessings of all be upon you.
I thank you for your cooperation.
I-I'm sorry!
How are you feeling?
I'm sorry.
I'm just like miso.
The soup?
No.
miso dregs are...
When you make the soup, you strain the miso.
The beans and things that are left - dregs.
A leftover, or extra baggage. Like that.
I've been like that since I was a kid. That's why... I decided to try harder.
So that I wouldn't make problems for everyone.
But...
You're a lot more complex than you look.
And selfish and spoiled.
Did I... say things?
A lot.
Oh right, Rio.
What?
That piece you were just humming.
What are you talking about?
It went like this.
I'm speechless.
After hearing it just once.
Not just once.
A long time ago, I heard it.
I wanted to play that piece myself.
That's why I want to...
A sound that seems to echo from the heavens. That piece...
But miso dregs
are miso dregs no matter what you do.
Kanata.
We can't just leave ourselves indebted to some church.
This Takemicaduchi is a treasure from another era.
There are thousands of secrets just sleeping inside it.
Secrets?
Right. If you want to know more, ask Noël later.
This should be it.
I'm starting it now!
This piece!
This is probably what the whole piece really sounds like.
All sorts of instruments, different parts ringing together.
They become a single music.
Just like riding a tank.
A commander, a gunner, a driver,
and communications personnel.
Everyone works together to work a single tank.
No one is unneeded.
Not a single note is unneeded.
Don't look at me like that. Someone said it to me.
The person I look up to,
and honor most.
As she told me,
Kanata.
Why do you think seniority and superiors exist?
So that those in lower ranks can make problems for them.
You don't need to be able right now.
But just remember your frustration and powerlessness,
and the happiness of having someone to care for you.
Someday, when you have to take care of someone, that will be
your experience.
So make as many problems for me as you'd like.
I made the same ones.
Of course, when you do something wrong, you'll be scolded and punished.
But when you're suffering, if your heart might break, tell me.
Understand?
Understood, sir!
From now on, I will make as many problems for you as I can!
I didn't...
Try to go easy on me.
Oh, come on. I should have stayed here!
That Kanata, getting Rio to nurse her back to health...
Come on, it wasn't a big deal.
And it looks like it's just fatigue. She'll be fine if she sleeps.
The Takemicaduchi's lights.
Sorry. I used it for a bit.
Did I do it at a bad time?
You listened to that piece, didn't you?
Yeah.
And you said you wouldn't listen to it ever again.
I had to hear it just once.
Why?
That's a secret.
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just walk it slowly
Everybody singing!
Just tell me a bit of what you think
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, little happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you hear my precious note?
All these words that there are can't even describe it
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: The Rainy Sky - A Glass Rainbow