Fionn mac Cumhaill, hero of Aillen and leader of the Knights of Fianna,
and my daughter Gráinne,
formally announced their engagement.
Everyone, tonight I want you to celebrate!
That man with the mole beneath his eye...
What is his name?
He is a knight of Fianna, Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Diarmuid...
Traitor.
You will suffer for this, Diarmuid.
Take me with you.
And run!
Rejoice, Gráinne...
Fionn has recognized our marriage!
Did you believe I'd forgotten what happened with Gráinne?
A dream?
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
That dream I had...
That was the legend of Diarmuid.
Are these my Servant's memories?
Where am I?
It appears you're awake.
Sola...
What is this?
Wh-Why am I here?
You have no memory of what happened?
I...
I was shot.
I defended myself with Volumen Hydragyrum, but...
What's happened to my body?
Evidence suggests that every Magic Circuit in your body misfired.
It's a miracle you didn't die instantly.
For now, all I've been able to do is to regenerate your internal organs.
But your Magic Circuits were utterly destroyed.
You'll never use magic again.
I...
Don't cry, Kayneth.
It's too soon to give up.
We haven't lost yet.
Sola...
If the Holy Grail is truly an omnipotent wish-granting device,
healing you should be more than possible for it.
You need only win.
If you succeed and claim the Grail, everything will return to how it was.
Therefore...
Okay, Kayneth?
Give me your Command Seals...
I'll take over as Lancer's Master,
and bring you the Grail.
N-No!
You don't believe in me?
Me, the woman who will marry into the Archibald family?
No... But...
Sola, do you think Lancer
would abandon me and swear fealty to you?
I do. He is a Heroic Spirit, here by the Grail's invitation.
He must long for the Grail, just as we do.
Even if he must change Masters,
he will accept it, for the sake of his goal.
Sola!
Lancer isn't the wonderful man you think he is!
Why do you say that?
When I asked him what he'd wish for, he said,
"I have no interest in the Holy Grail."
No Servant wouldn't desire the Grail.
He's hiding something important...
But no matter what he hides,
while I bear these Command Seals, he must obey me.
Kayneth...
I won't give you the Command Seals...
Kayneth, you still don't understand, do you?
You don't understand that we must win at all costs.
Listen to me, Kayneth...
An unskilled spiritual healer such as I
cannot hope to extract Command Seals, once bestowed.
The only way to transfer them without resistance
is with the bearer's consent.
If you truly cannot accept this,
my last resort would be to amputate your right arm.
Well?
Irisviel?
It's all right.
Magical healing puts serious stress on the patient.
I do not think she will awaken for a while yet.
Watch her for a bit, okay?
You're going to report to Kiritsugu?
I'm sure he's worried, too.
Irisviel, I have a request.
I'd like you to speak with Kiritsugu for me.
Tell him we must pursue Caster immediately.
Saber...
Our inaction will mean the suffering of more children.
Kiritsugu?
How long before we can use Maiya again?
She won't be able to move for another day or two.
I see.
You and Saber stay here.
I'm going to follow Kayneth.
Wait, Kiritsugu!
Did Saber tell you we should go after Caster first?
Apparently so.
Are you mad at Saber for not stopping Lancer?
Iri...
Saving a few, or even a few dozen children is not our goal.
Saber probably never doubted that Lancer wouldn't kill me.
But had Lancer betrayed her, what would have happened?
Our Holy Grail War would have ended right there.
There's no need to tell her where I'm going...
Lancer? Please show yourself.
Lady Sola, how fares Lord Kayneth?
Not well...
I've done everything I can, but...
This isn't your fault... It's Kayneth's!
All it means was that the Holy Grail War was too much for him.
No, but...
Diarmuid, he isn't worthy of being your Master.
Kayneth has abandoned the battle,
entrusting me with his rights as your Master!
As a knight, my loyalty is pledged to Lord Kayneth.
My lady Sola, I cannot agree to that.
Wait...
As a Servant, do you not manifest physically using my prana?
And now I have the Command Seals, as well.
Before I am a Servant, I am a knight.
I can serve but one lord.
Am I so unworthy of being your Master?!
I've told you that is not the issue...
Look at me when you speak!
Lancer, fight beside me. Protect me!
Lend me your support. Win the Holy Grail with me!
I cannot.
If Lord Kayneth has given up on this battle,
then I no longer have any interest in the Grail.
We require a miracle to heal him!
Only the Grail can bring that to pass.
If you truly feel responsible for what's happened to him...
If you desire to restore his honor as the powerful Lord El-Melloi...
Then you must win the Holy Grail for your Master!
Lady Sola,
you speak as Lord Kayneth's wife,
and seek the Grail only on his behalf?
Is that correct?
Y-Yes... Of course!
Will you swear to it? And that you have no other desire?
I swear...
As wife to Kayneth El-Melloi, I shall bring him the Grail.
That same look in her eyes...
The same look as Gráinne had.
I harbor no hatred for anyone.
However,
fate was simply too cruel.
What I seek from this life is but the loyalty denied me in my last.
I wish to keep that sad fate from happening once again.
But...
It does a man good to watch you drink...
Oh, thank you.
You should have told us you had a guest!
No, no. Don't trouble yourself, ma'am.
The simple pleasures of home are best.
My, you're such a charmer!
I told you... to take spiritual form...
...when you come and go!
Had I done so, I could not have retrieved this.
I even successfully acquired pants to do this.
Anyway, it was you who ordered me to do it.
Why must I, King of Conquerors,
go to draw water from some country river?
Because it's more productive than eating junk food and watching videos.
What's this? Are you playing at being an alchemist?
I'm not playing. I am an alchemist.
What is that?
The residue left by spell casting.
It's the remnant of magic, left in the water.
And that means someone was using magic near the river.
If we follow the trail, it may show us where to look.
Boy, did you already realize something like that was in the water?
Of course not.
But this town is unusual, in that water flows straight through its center.
So starting with the water was the obvious choice.
Rider...
Was anything between here and here?
Maybe an irrigation channel or a sewage pipe?
Oh! There was one of considerable size.
That's it.
If we follow this, it will probably lead us to Caster's laboratory.
Boy,
are you certain you aren't an unusually talented magus?
A talented magus wouldn't have to do it this way.
It's probably the simplest imaginable method.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
Not in the least!
Using elementary methods to achieve solid results
is a far greater feat than having to rely on complex techniques!
As your Servant, I am proud.
Right, then...
Now that we have his location, it's show time!
Hey, kid, shall we strike at once?
Just wait a second. We're talking about engaging Caster...
I know that.
No you don't!
Caster will be at an overwhelming advantage
while defending his home turf.
What kind of moron would go bursting in?
Listen...
In war, enemy and ally positions can change in an instant.
Fail to attack the enemy when you know their location,
and it will be too late to regret having missed your chance.
What's made you so eager today?
Why shouldn't I be?
My Master has finally contributed something of worth.
As a Servant, I must also do my duty,
and bring back the enemy's head!
Don't give up before we've even begun...
Let us go and see what we find.
It may well work out better than you imagine.
This is it!
You see? Everything worked out fine!
Unfortunately, Caster appears to be away.
Is this some kind of water tank?
Hey, boy...
I don't think there's anything here you need to see.
What are you talking about?
If Caster isn't here,
we should at least search for clues to his whereabouts.
You may be right, but don't do it.
Kid, this is too much for you.
Shut up.
I warned you, didn't I?
I warned you not to look.
Shut up!
Damn it, stop making fun of me.
Damn it...
We're past the time for saving face, fool.
Well, that's fine...
If I saw someone who could remain unmoved by this,
I'd punch them.
What do you mean, you'd punch them?
Right now, you look just fine!
That's because now is not the time for emotion.
Because my Master is in mortal peril!
Assassin? But that's impossible!
Assassin's dead.
We can't afford to be surprised, kid.
H-How?
That is irrelevant to us now.
However, one thing is certain...
Anyone who believed in Assassin's demise has been deceived.
They ran... Didn't they?
Do not drop your guard.
We killed two, and there appeared to be an additional two.
At this rate, who can say how many Assassins there truly are.
This is their preferred terrain.
We should withdraw.
Should we really leave this place the way it is?
Perhaps you'd find something if you were to look, but let it go.
For now, we'll just have to do what damage we can.
If nothing else, it will slow Caster down.
With his hideout in ruins, Caster will no longer be able to run and hide.
He'll have to emerge.
Before too long,
we shall put an end to them.
I get it.
Quit doing that...
Let us depart, kid.
Do not let it trouble you, Kirei.
Indeed, it is unfortunate that Assassin was exposed to them
before we could discern the nature of Rider's ultimate weapon.
But from this encounter,
we've found out that Rider's Master is a mere third-rate magus.
Had they not been discovered...
Other options would have become available to you?
Yes.
While your plans are certainly important,
you must remain refined and relaxed in all matters.
Elegance is required, even in battle.
But I never thought he'd be such a boring person...
We will have another chance to see Rider's ultimate attack.
Have Assassin continue to monitor Rider, but take great care as they do.
Understood, my teacher.
Episode 9
Master and Servant
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
I used too much prana at once?
I'm certain there's something I can do to help!
Surely she didn't go to Fuyuki...
Behold the Matou family magic.
We're just about to start a party.
I can't accomplish anything this way!
Next time:
Rin's Adventure