I guess it's true that Kiyoi-chan
really cares about her friends.
She was pissed.
Kiyoi-chan will do anything for a friend.
I'm glad she hasn't changed.
Do you really think you can
get away with doing this?
This is a crime!
So what?
Once I've beaten the shit out of her,
I'll take some embarrassing photos
so you can't go to the cops.
Gosh, Akira-chan's such a monster!
You'd go that far? Just because
you can't beat in her battle?
Shut up!
That bitch always slowed me down.
If it weren't for her, I could've won!
My wish would've come true!
I'll never forgive her!
I'll make her suffer so much,
she'll never think of disobeying me again!
What are you going to do to Kiyoi?
She and I are going to battle, that's all.
Well, with you as my hostage,
there's no way I can lose.
You're wasting your time.
Nobody's coming to save you.
Kiyoi...
Amika...
We got Yuzuki back, but she's still an LRIG.
What can we do to make her human again?
What if we got five coins?
Layla had five, and nothing really changed...
There are too many rules we don't know!
What's wrong?
Maybe she'd know!
Mizushima Kiyoi
You're finally here.
I was getting tired of waiting.
Akira-chan, introduce me, too!
Huh? God, you're annoying.
Hello again, Kiyoi-chan!
Remember!
I haven't seen you since that day!
I've been wanting to see you
again for a long, long time.
I wanted to play with you again.
Our positions are reversed from last time,
but we finally meet!
Where's Amika?
Who knows?
She might not be here, I can tell you that.
If you want her back,
do what I tell you, okay?
Got it?
What's your answer?
Fine.
You mean, "Yes, ma'am!"
Yes... ma'am.
I love girls who are obedient!
Now, I think it's time you battled me.
But you need to become an LRIG
and just let me attack you.
As for what will happen
to her if you hit back...
Well, you can guess, right?
Don't worry!
Kiyoi-chan cares about her friend.
She'll do what you say.
You used me to get revenge
for your friend, right?
So you should be able to do what
I tell you this time, right?
For your friend.
Okay, let's get started.
Open!
Hey, when are you going to let me have
a real battle with Kominato Ruuko?
Eventually, I promise.
You did me a big favor, and I appreciate it.
Just words?
I held back against a powerful
foe like that for you!
I know.
I ordered a pizza to thank you.
What?!
We're not friends.
And I'm definitely not working for you.
Don't forget that!
Of course.
There was something I wanted to see.
And I got the confirmation I wanted.
She's the keyhole.
Keyhole?
Hello, I'm from Pizza Hattori.
Great, thanks.
Right on time as always, I see.
Thank you.
Just be a good girl until
the stage is set, okay?
Hey, wait!
So that's the kind of
underwear you like, Suzuko?
M-Meru!
What did Chinatsu wear?
Chi-chan's was...
Wow, really?
What? What?
It's probably better that
you don't know, Suzuko.
Yeah...
Jeez, you guys are mean!
It feels strange,
talking to both of you at once.
Yeah.
When I learned your name
was Meru, I was happy.
I realized Chi-chan hadn't forgotten.
Suzu, about Chinatsu's memories...
Yeah. I know.
I want to respect her feelings.
But...
Honestly, I don't know if it's for the best.
But I will give her an answer.
Because we're friends.
Okay, let's start by having
you become an LRIG.
And no using defensive ARTS.
Kiyoi...
Unlock. Coin bet.
Turn end.
It's finally time!
I can finally beat the shit out of you!
Let's have fun until her
Life Cloth is all gone!
I'm going to pound you
until you can barely stand,
then turn you into a card
and rip you in half!
Or maybe we could stuff
her in a diary somewhere.
Now, go, Remember.
Attack.
Got it!
That's the face!
That's the face I wanted to see!
Kiyoi-chan, the girl who loves her friends...
Kiyoi-chan, the girl who's so stupid...
Kiyoi-chan, the girl I love!
Kiyoi!
I'm fine.
But...
Turn end.
Now stop wasting time and say it.
Kiyoi, don't you understand?
They're going to own you!
Still, I can't fight.
If I do, Amika will...
I won't fight.
I have to protect Amika.
I'll make a contract with you.
I'll teach you how to fight.
You memorize what I teach you and put
it into practice as fast as possible.
Do you understand?
U-Um...
You're weak, so if you want
to win, it's the only way.
I'll help you win.
Okay!
Even in my battle with Remember,
when I tried to take advantage of the rules
and deliberately lose to grant that wish,
Amika said...
Amika, will you believe
in me just one more time?
Yes... Kiyoi!
We Recommend Grape
No. 1 Orange Green Tea Mushroom
No. 2 Custard Cola
No. 3 Banana Chocolate Cilantro
I think we should try
orange green tea mushroom.
Banana chocolate cilantro.
No, it's gotta be orange green tea mushroom!
Okay...
Excuse me! I'd like a
banana chocolate cilantro.
Why do you always believe in me, Amika?
You've never doubted me,
even during the Selector battles.
Why?
I don't know how to answer that...
Because we're friends?
Is that all?
What other reason do I need?
My mom was saved because I believed you.
And that's why we're here now.
I've never gone wrong
believing in you, Kiyoi.
Amika...
Try some of this banana chocolate cilantro!
I believed in your choice,
and it turned out to be delicious!
Amika was willing to believe
in someone like me...
And I put her in danger.
Even though she's so important to me...
Remember what I told you?
I'll help you in any way I can.
But I won't help you sacrifice yourself!
I'm sorry.
But...
I'd rather disappear than lose Amika.
No...
What are you babbling about?
It's my turn.
Go, Remember!
'Kay!
Playing with you sure is fun!
Don't overdo it, or you'll ruin the fun.
I know!
Amika...
Kiyoi!
Come on, Kiyoi-chan!
Let's play even more!
This is wonderful!
Lucky, lucky me!
Lucky, lucky Akira!
Kiyoi...
If you just fight and not
worry about me, you'll...
But I know she won't!
That's not who she is!
What's wrong, Amika?
It's nothing.
Kiyoi forced herself to
carry so many burdens
and fought all by herself.
So I...
So I can also...
Are we done already, Kiyoi-chan?
This is so much fun!
It feels so good to beat someone
up when they can't fight back!
It's like it's always my turn!
Stop it!
Now, now, don't do that.
I want to play with Kiyoi-chan!
You have a wish, don't you, Kiyoi?
To end this cycle of darkness!
Piruluk...
Get lost!
Don't forget, I've got a hostage!
Oh, Piruluk-chan!
You're such a noble friend, aren't you?
Don't bother resisting.
Just give up already!
Just stop...
I can't...
Kiyoi!
Amika?!
Damn it.
She escaped!
I'm fine!
I'm not hurt!
Amika...
I'm sorry!
Kiyoi!
I'm not a Selector, so I can't help you...
It hurt to let you fight alone.
But if protecting myself can help you...
I believe in you!
So believe in me, too!
And fight!
Amika...
Shut the hell up.
It was just getting good.
Don't get in my way!
Your attack is over, right?
Then declare it.
Turn end.
It's my turn.
Grow.
Summon two Manomin.
You have one coin left.
Do you know what happens
when you lose all your coins?
Shut up.
I don't care.
You disappear.
Your entire existence.
Huh?
Jeez, Kiyoi-chan...
Don't tell her that.
I was going to tell her at the right time.
A Selector who loses all
their coins disappears...
from this world.
Literally, there's nothing left!
What?
Until now, I was still uncertain.
Even if I had to do it to
end the Selector battles,
I didn't know if it was okay to go that far.
But I won't hesitate anymore.
For my own sake, and for the
sake of everyone I know,
I'm going to end these Selector battles!
So...
I won't lose to you!
Are you saying you're going to
make Akira-chan disappear?
This is great!
I'll disappear?
Fine by me!
I don't give a shit if I lose this
rotten life and all these scars!
Piruluk.
Right.
Worst Condition!
Turn end.
All right!
Let's do this! Coin bet!
Astrology!
I'll find out exactly
what your next attack is.
I can tell you...
that I can't tell you!
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
No, the result of the fortune-telling
was that we don't know what
her next attack will be.
Huh? What the hell?!
I'll tell you.
Unlock. Coin bet.
Piru-run's taking a break,
and Milulun is here!
Milulun, coin bet.
Happening!
You stole that from me!
I'm going to disappear?
I'm really going to disappear?
That can't be real... No way.
That's impossible!
Don't screw with me!
There's still so much I want to do!
I've got work!
That's right! I've got a shoot tomorrow!
It's a swimsuit photo this time.
It's a little slutty,
but my manager said I have a
nice body, so it's sure to sell!
And my fans are all looking forward to it!
So... So...
I don't want to disappear!
My name is Aoi Akira...
A beautiful high school
girl and a popular model.
My hobbies are shopping and WIXOSS.
My favorite foods are
strawberries and melons...
I don't want to disappear!
Your face is so scary...
I really hate you, Kiyoi-chan.
What a coincidence.
I hate you, too.
I'm going to disappear...
So this is what it means to disappear?
Kiyoi!
Amika!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I was so scared.
I thought I'd lose you.
So now you understand how I feel, huh?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Okay, I forgive you!
Kiyoi, you have five coins now, right?
Come to think of it...
But...
Nothing's changed.
What's going on?
Even if you get five coins,
these battles don't end?
I wasn't told anything, either.
I wasn't even told how you can win.
That's...
Kiyoi...
Five coins isn't the win condition?
Shock.
What does this mean?
No...
If it doesn't end after you get five coins,
then how can I get Chi-chan's memories back?
I finally found you, keyhole.
I'm back, Tama, Yuzuki...
Tama?!
Bond / Crime and Punishment
It's not worth defeating
you unless you're serious.
The condition for victory
is different this time?
There's no way to get your memories back?
So now she's been chosen?
We might be able to get Tama back.
I'll take you down first!
Contact / Key and Keyhole
Contact / Key and Keyhole.