Mazui presents
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemuri asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I open my eyes again, to a sleepy morning
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to
教室のドア潜ると
When I pass through the door of the classroom
honno sukoshi mune wo hatte arukidaseru
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I puff my chest out with a little bit of pride
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind that blows past everyday life
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す　今この胸で
It started to shake within my chest
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would come now
iku oku no hoshi ga kie satteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched countless stars as they vanished
miokutta te wo futta yokatta ne to
見送った　手を振った　良かったねと
I waved goodbye, "I'm glad"
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
I've gathered you all here for one reason.
At this point we shall now commence Operation High Tension Syndrome.
Why is there no reaction?
This is the first time I've heard of this operation.
Of course. I only recently came up with it.
Yurippe, what kind of operation is it?
It's a simple one.
For one day, you will conduct everything at high tension.
That's all.
Everything you do will be at high tension.
When moving between classes, a full-speed sprint.
When drinking juice, chugging.
When talking to each other, yelling.
And don't forget to smile!
You will conduct everything at high tension.
We act as though we're spending a fulfilled school life.
And what will that accomplish?
If we live a fulfilled life, we'll disappear.
No, we won't disappear.
If we do as the operation says, we'll be faking high tension all day, like we've gone mad.
That's almost like a punishment game!
What's that?
How shallow-minded.
Correct.
To us, it's a painful task.
But Angel is very gullible.
She'll be stuck wondering why we aren't reincarnating, despite living such fulfilled school lives.
How do you think Angel will respond then?
You think she will?
Of course she will.
We'll be living happy school lives.
That is a condition for reincarnation.
Yet we won't disappear.
"What on earth is going on?!"
She'll be confused by this unprecedented irregularity.
And then she will attempt to make contact.
You mean—
Yes! With God!
She will report that an anomaly is occurring in this world!
If we follow just her, she'll lead us right to him!
To God!
That's quite a plan, but how long do we have to keep it up?
We will commence the operation at 9 am today.
The operation will end at 9 pm.
For 12 hours?!
We just have to be at high tension in front of Angel, right?
That's easy! Yeah!
We don't know when she's watching.
Come dance around! Hey, everybody!
The whole time.
Wait!
We have to stay at high tension for 12 hours straight?!
Let's go! Alright! Alright!
That's it! Follow me!
Yep.
Yeah! That's right!
Coincidentally, if the operation fails...
That's so easy, yeah!
You all fast for a week.
To run against my character this far... what an operation!
Oh, and I'm in charge of observing Angel, so I won't be joining you.
Good luck, everyone!
She's almost evil!
Do I have to do this too?
Alright. Operation start!
Yum! Yum!
What the hell's this?!
Yum! Yum! Super yum!
Oh, I can't stop! How can it be so good?!
Hey! Hinata-senpai! Let's play!
A cute girl is inviting you!
You lucky bastard!
Come on!!
I might be lucky, but unfortunately...
I'm going to be playing catch with Otonashi!!
Yeah! It's gotta be men playing catch together!!
Fine! Then I'll be practicing with GirlDeMo!!
I love GirlDeMo!!
Yeah! Go sing a love song or something!
Yeah! I'll write and sing the best love song ever!!
See you!!
Come on Otonashi! Let's play catch!!
Let's throw this ball!
It's fun just thinking about it!
I'm getting the shivers!!
S-Sure...
Wait right there!!
Let me join you!
Hey put that down!
Quit being a wimp!
I'm saying that if you've got two people throwing, it's even more fun with a guy hitting!!
I didn't think of that! That sounds like fun!
That's why I want to join! Let me join!
Yeah! We'll let you join!!
Wait!! Then won't it be better with an outfield?!
Yeah, Matsushita 5th Dan, that's right!!
Alright!! I'm in too!
Let me in there too!!
Hey! You're already ready for this!!
I've built this muscle solely to play baseball!!
Did you?!
Crap! This is going to be damn fun!!
Alright! Let's head to the grounds!!
W-Wait!!
What about you guys?
Sexy!
Hey, Oyama! If you're up for eating, then let's eat out the whole dining hall!!
Yeah! I'm with you!
TK! It'll be damn awesome if you come with us! How about it?!
Dive into your body!
I have no clue what you're saying, but okay let's go!!
How about you Shiina—
What, you're not here anymore?!
Alright! Let's head to the dining hall!
My stomach's ready for some action!!
Yum! How delicious! This omelette rice is the best!!
Academy Main Dining Hall Interior
That's nothing! This dining hall is all about the udon!
Man, this is the best!!
Mmm! Mapo tofu is crazy night!
Oh no! I finished this already?!
I gotta lick the plate clean!!
Alright! I'm getting seconds!
That's nothing! I'm getting me seconds too!
Mapo tofu gimme back!
It's going to be so fun, I can't stop shaking!
I'm totally with you!
Yeah! Me too!!
As am I! This muscle was made for it!
You too, right Otonashi?!
Uh, yeah...
What are you going to do now?
She suddenly appeared...
Going crazy, going crazy!!
That's what youth is all about!!
Youth?
Right, guys?!
It's youth!!
Right, youth!!
Youth!!
See?
Second period is starting soon.
I forgot!
But this is no time to be taken aback!
Studying is also a part of youth!!
You're attending class?
Of course we are!!
Right, guys?!
Yeah!! Studying is youth itself!!
Baseball can go suck one!!
Today, I become a scholar!!
Yes! I've built this muscle solely to study!!
Studying! Studying! Studying! Studying!!
Classroom Block B    Classroom
Now then, 1858, the Ansei Purge...
Ii Naosuke, Tairou of the Edo Bakufu—
Here comes Ii Naosuke!!
Wh-What's wrong?
I'm sorry!
Ii Naosuke is like a superhero to me!
I accidentally came.
I see...
Honnouji...
When do we get to the Incident at Honnouji?!
We already passed that part.
Akechi Mitsuhide!!
The Shorui Awaremi no Rei!!
It's time for the Shorui Awaremi no Rei, Sensei!!
What now?!
It's time for the Shorui Awaremi no Rei now!
We passed that part.
Edo... Bakufu...
Shut up, you lot!!
What are you, Soga no Iruka?!
Because we're doing Japanese history, right?
He thinks that was good?!
That's right, Sensei!
Leave him be and keep going!
Teach us more!
I want to learn more!
Hey! Teach me! Hey! Come on!
Alright, now let's go to the next page.
Classroom Block B    Classroom
During the French Revolution, as symbols of the privileged class, Louis XVI and Marie Antoinette—
It's Marie!!
Wh-What's wrong?
I'm sorry!
Marie is a moe heroine in my book, so I accidentally came!
Moe?
...were executed by guillotine...
—engine...
When will Watt's steam engine be invented?!
It's already been invented...
No, the steam-powered locomotive wasn't—
The Second Punic War!!
It's time for the Second Punic War, Sensei!!
We already passed that part.
The Punic... Bakufu...
There wasn't a Bakufu called that...
Shut up, you lot!!
What are you, Genghis Khan?!
Because we're doing world history, right?
This is just messed up...
Come on, boys! It's time for some real baseball!!
Are you ready?!
Of course!!
Baseball rocks!!
Bring it on!!
I'm already on standby!!
We still need to clean.
That's right boys!!
Let's free ourselves from worldly thoughts with cleaning!!
Good idea!!
But real men don't use wimpy cleaning tools!
They use only a dust cloth!!
It's a dust cloth battle!!
I built this body solely to use a dust cloth!!
It is time to unleash my full power!!
They're making it harder on themselves...
Alright...
Rea—GO!
Cheater, you started early!
Out of my way! Out of my way!
What are you people doing?
Um... they've always been like this.
Don't mind them.
I win!!
No! There's still the second floor!!
My body has just warmed up!!
Come on!! The second floor awaits!!
They actually look like they're having fun.
Classroom Block A    Empty Classroom
Alright!!
Don't you feel like spittin' out a hella awesome rap song?! Damn!!
Hella awesome rock, yeah!!
Just can't get enough of those lines!!
I am a woman of this turf.
I will defend this Naniwa.
You can walk your own way.
Yeah!!
Oh yeah!!
So she'll take care of all of Osaka by herself?
Quite a woman.
We're in the middle of Operation High Tension!
If it fails, everyone fasts for a week.
Sounds good to me!!
Right?!
Doesn't that Naniwa couple just rack your brain?!
Sure does!
Hell yeah!!
I'm crying from that love song, damn!!
Yui, you're a genius!!
Hisako-senpai's killer bass and line were genius too!!
She almost sounds good now!!
You're picking a fight, aren't you...
Then how about we head out there and hold an outdoor live?!
Yeah!!
Damn, this stuff's too good. I ate way too much.
Academy Main Dining Hall Interior
Yeah.
You think we'll hold out a full week like this?
Yurippe's fasting means no water either.
Damn, I'm full!! I just want to move!!
Let's do some exercise for digestion!
Yeah!!
Oh yeah!!
Why don't we learn how to dance from TK?!
Yeah! Awesome idea!!
Hey! TK!!
My stomach is destruction...
Don't worry about destruction!
Teach us how to dance now!
We need a wide open area!
Let's head to the grounds!
Grounds    Gym Storage Room
Hey you.
What are you doing here?
An outdoor live, dammit!
Grounds
Everyone's out here for it, yeah!!
Let's burn out the night!!
We're going to play baseball here right now!
Hitting, fielding, running, safe, all that!!
You stupid I-love-playing-in-a-band-with-all-my-friends freak!!
A band is more youthful than baseball, dammit!!
You stupid baseball-baseball-I-love-baseball freak!!
No! Youth is all about dancing!!
Dancing together will make us all happier!
Right! Right! All happier!
What the hell?! You're so full, must be happy!
Turning this place into a dancing ground will make us all happier!
Agreed! Let me dance with you!!
Matsushita 5th Dan, we need to talk now, happy boy!!
We're playing baseball!!
Listen to Takamatsu!!
It's an outdoor live, dammit!!
What kind of idiot are you?! It's a dance!!
Whoever enjoys dancing the most must be so happy!
You're saying balls and caps don't give you a better thrill?!
Then why not just have a sports festival?!
We can just have a sports festival.
All the normal students are already here.
The only thing we can do with this many people is a sports festival.
Yeah! Let's go sports festival! Smells like youth!!
Yes!! I built this body solely for sports festivals!!
Sounds good for digestion!
We'll be blissfully happy!
Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go, everyone!!
Relay
Race
Pole
Toppling
Ball
Tossing
Group
Gymnastics
Bread Eating Race
Cheerleading
Competition
Cheerleading Competition!
Things are getting very exciting out here.
I wonder how things are with Angel?
Let's take a look.
Yurippe-san?
Yurippe at the station here!
The hell are you making me do?!
You're putting on some high tension yourself, huh...
Classroom Block A    Student Council Room Front
Tenshi is currently talking in the student council room.
I think it'll end soon.
Damn, those guys are good!
Yeah, this is getting exciting!
Listen up, everyone!!
1000 points to whoever wins this cavalry battle!!
We're going to turn the tables with this!!
Hey, that team there is kind of scary.
Oh, where?
Hey! Bare hands! Bare hands!
You trying to kill us?!
Damn. Not allowed?
Honestly, those guys...
What's that?
The general's mark.
I'll stand out more than anyone and get more headbands than anyone!
You ready, losers?!
Charge!!
Angel must be watching this from the student council room and getting more and more confused.
Why aren't they disappearing, despite how fulfilled they look?
It's perfect! It's too perfect!
Operation High Tension Syndrome!
Are you the villain?
Thank you for the high tension interruption.
It's all ruined...
President, you can't!
We're in the middle of a meeting!
I'll be back soon.
Right into the worst possible situation?!
What have you done?
Look at this.
What about it?
CUTE!!!!
She's an idiot...
No intent to fight?
How can I explain this?
Explain?
What?
Don't tell me...
Hey, you guys! Wake up!
We're going after her!
And how are you guys so weak?!
Medical Building (Closed)
What's going on?
I don't know.
But she said she was going to explain something.
Explain? Don't tell me...
To God, huh?
So we were right?
Having so many normal students down like this is an unprecedented irregularity.
The Battlefront always made sure the NPCs were unaffected by their activities.
But this time it's different.
Regardless of whether the operation was a success, we're dealing with the Battlefront's very objective here.
There's an entrance to a basement here?
Medical Building Basement    Restricted Area
Is this... the path to God?
A password?
The security here is as tight as Guild.
There's no doubt about it.
God awaits beyond that door.
Charge!
If you don't make it, we leave you behind!
What is this place?
Beautiful.
Cute.
This is...
Hydroponic cultivation.
Yurippe, I found this.
Gardening Club
Wha—
Now then...
Now that I've suddenly left the student council behind in the middle of a meeting to check on these cute turnips...
that I had been raising for the Gardening Club after they collapsed when I remembered about them after I heard the word "cute"...
How should I explain that to them?
What the hell?!
Oh, you're all here.
What was with the security out there?!
Security?
Man, we finally got in!
Who'd have thought the door would just open at the push of a button?
What?! What about the password?!
Password?
You were just dialing it on the keypad!
I was just calculating the remaining funds for the Gardening Club.
I-It was a calculator?
Starting right now, the Afterlife Battlefront...
will fast for a week!!
No way!!
One week later
I'm sorry, everyone...
I've worked hard to get this far in memory of you, but...
This is...
my limit...
The GirlDeMo members are all down.
Well, it's not like they'll die.
You do make the best villain after all, Yurippe-san.
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつも一人で歩いてた
I've always walked alone
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返ると　皆は遠く
When I turn around, everyone's far behind
sore demo atashi wa aruita
それでも あたしは歩いた
Even so, I kept walking
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That was what strength was
mou nani mo kowakunai
もう何も怖くない
"I'm not afraid of anything anymore",
sou tsubuyaitemiseru
そう呟いてみせる
I try to whisper to myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Everyone becomes alone someday
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They live on only in memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ　愛し笑ってられるように
So I can laugh with my heart, even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will show no tears