I ended up hurting Iroha.
Don't reject her if you're gonna feel guilty about it.
No, I had to.
Why would you say that
when you know as much?
You're rather mean-spirited.
That I am.
Iroha's feelings honestly made me happy,
but there's more to it than meets the eye.
They were probably actually meant for...
You're incredible.
Just like that, you change the people around you.
What? Where's this praise coming from?
You've got it wrong.
I told you,
I'm not as nice as a guy as you think I am.
When I praise you,
I do it for myself.
Next stop: Kaihin-Makuhari.
Kaihin-Makuhari.
We'll be getting off at the next stop.
Yup.
Isshiki, that's my stop too.
Where do you get off?
Hey, this bag's too heavy for me.
Yeah, that's probably a good idea.
Guess I messed up, huh?
Oh, come on.
Even you had to know the time wasn't right.
It's not my fault.
I got swept up in the excitement.
I'm surprised.
I didn't think you were the type
to go with the flow.
I was surprised, too.
Expected "unflappable,"
but got this instead.
Yeah, you act like you have nothing but romance on the brain, but I know you're a cunni—
I don't mean myself.
I'm talking about you.
What?
How could I not be moved after what I saw?
What do you mean?
I started wanting something genuine, too.
You heard all that?
Well, you were pretty loud.
Please forget it.
I won't forget it.
I can't forget it.
That's why I threw caution to the wind today.
Well, uh...
Don't let it get you down.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Wait, are you hitting on me while I'm heartbroken?
Sorry, but I need more time.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Also, I'm not down and out just yet!
In fact, this is the best way
to make a move on Hayama!
People will sympathize with me,
and my rivals will have to back off, right?
R-Right...
Besides, wouldn't you worry about
someone you rejected?
Like, you'd feel sorry for them...
So I may have lost the battle, but I'll win the war...
I laid the groundwork,
so I gotta stick with it...
You're pretty amazing.
This is all your fault! You're the one who made me change.
Made you president, maybe, but I didn't—
Take responsibility.
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something genuine
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Uh, why exactly did you call us here?
To sort out our objectives
and figure out a gameplan.
Uh huh?
Frankly, the current plan will end in failure.
We'll likely only get one part finished, if that.
It's going to be a joke compared to
what we advertised.
What do you think we should do to prevent that?
Uh, I dunno.
The problem lies in those meetings.
Everyone gets their say, but nobody's actually making any decisions.
Let's stop trying to make friends and hold a proper meeting.
A meeting full of rejection, opposition, and confrontation, but one with a clear outcome.
That's what we need.
Well, what do you think?
I'd rather we didn't make any waves.
Besides, implementing an alternate plan this late in the game will be difficult.
I guess.
But we're still gonna do it.
I don't want my name attached to a joke.
Mihama
Library
Takasu
Community
Center
Maybe so,
but I kinda wanna put on a play.
Don't you think getting to experience both your concert and our play
would be a great deal for our visitors?
But diversifying would reduce the
synergy effect and double the risk.
Yeah, but we also need to keep in mind the budget.
Well, we can discuss what to do about that.
That's what this meeting's for.
Amen to that.
A-Amen.
Amen.
Preach it!
Um, if I may...
Why are you opposed to
a two-pronged strategy?
I'm not exactly opposed to it per se,
but I think sharing one vision will give rise to better camaraderie.
And I believe that a combined holistic approach is key to a robust image.
Is there any need to work together at all?
Of course.
Having all hands on deck will leverage more synergy and enable a bigger event—
What synergy? And the way things are going, we won't be able to hold much of an event.
So why are you still fixated on this system?
We reached a consensus, and even calibrated our expectations on the grand design.
Amen to that.
Preach it, preach it!
I think not.
There's an inflated ego,
a refusal to admit any and all fuck ups,
and a desire to sweep all mistakes under the rug.
Hence all the scheming.
Hence all the empty words.
It was all to gain peace of mind through mutual commitment.
I mean, it's a hell of a lot easier when others can take the fall.
This just feels like a breakdown
in communication to me.
We should take a moment
to cool down and start over.
Amen to that.
Preach it, preach it!
If all you want to do is play pretend,
could you take it elsewhere?
You've done nothing but
spout meaningless prattle.
Is pretending to be upper management with words you just picked up that much fun?
Mistaking vague statements for actual communication and understanding,
while never lifting a finger...
How could that lead to any progress?
It will never create anything,
never improve anything,
and never help anything.
It's nothing but a sham.
Yukinon...
Please stop wasting our time.
I-Instead of forcing ourselves
to work together,
why don't we consider this a chance to let our visitors have double the fun?
Like, it'd help both schools leave their mark on the event.
Right?
R-Right.
I think that's a good idea.
Wh-What do you think?
Y-Yeah...
Preach that, too.
Right, guys?
Yeah...
Well...
That could work.
Why'd you guys have to go on those rants?
Way to rain on everyone's parade.
I don't think I was mistaken in what I said, though.
Your words may have been justified,
but couldn't you, like, read the mood or something?
You think too highly of him if you think he's capable of that.
Even in the clubroom,
all he does is read his book.
I hate to break it to you,
but a voracious reader like myself
can also read between the lines.
Also, wasn't she yelling at you and not me?
But she just admitted my words were justified.
Why would she yell at me after that?
Yeah, that's it.
That's exactly what she's yelling at you for.
Pay attention, woman.
Hello?
Are you listening to me?
I'm talking to both of you here.
Here. It's on me.
Th-Thanks.
Cheers!
You've changed, Hikigaya.
I used to find you so boring.
Th-That so...
Maybe that's all in the eye of the beholder.
Oh, but you're still nowhere
near boyfriend material.
Uh, I'm not exactly applying
for the position anymore.
I guess I could see you as a friend, though.
You're hilarious.
Next time there's a reunion, you should come.
No way. Not on your life.
I know, right? Hilarious.
It's really not.
Could you get that?
Don't bother, Hachiman.
I don't need your help.
I can do it myself.
So you say, but you're...
I'm good.
But you know what?
I can do it all alone.
What the heck?
That sounds so stupid.
Listen up, you—
I have a name.
Rumi.
Listen up, Rumi.
Yeah?
Would you like to act in our play?
In this bright room
I wait for the thaw you bring
Yuigahama,
have you finished packing the cookies?
Yup, I just got done.
Want me to help bake the cakes?
No, we'll be fine,
so don't touch the cakes, okay?
Don't even look at them.
You meanie!
When I wake up, I see a box
Oh, jeez!
We're totally screwed!
No need to worry.
The script seemed fine.
None see it as I do
Well, the secretary did
put a lot of effort into it,
The snow turned my heart a milky white
and you...
Right.
I should go join the others.
which scatters the cold sunlight
Oh, make sure you go over the
final cue with the vice president.
Freezing rain covers my body,
And take care of the cakes, too.
Aye, aye,
and only the distant spring wind may dispel the veil
prez.
Take me to a summer garden
where I may grow azalea
I doubt you will
There are no fairy tales full of happiness
I know that all too well
But, you know,
that's where I want to go
I solved the complicated equations
all by myself
I thought it was only natural
and never doubted my actions
But this season will soon come to an end,
and only my shadow on the ground gives me company
Cover this frozen path
in a storm of flowers
and show me the way
There are no perfect crystals made of miracles
That is why we come to take
one another's hands
Oh, welcome back.
Good work out there.
Yuigahama.
Thanks.
Wait, what?
What's with the cup?
Why must you be the only one drinking out of a paper cup?
It's a Christmas present!
I picked the base and
Yukinon chose the design.
Figures.
Uh, but I didn't get anything for you guys.
Don't worry about it.
It's just a paper cup replacement.
Thanks.
You're welcome!
Also, th-thanks for fulfilling my request.
Thanks to you two,
the event went off without a hitch.
Your request hasn't been fulfilled yet.
I said I'd accept it, didn't I?
Yeah, but it's done now.
What is this, a riddle?
I suppose so. It might be one big riddle.
I figured it out,
but you might be better off not knowing, Hikki.
Huh?
All that aside,
it's still Christmas, so let's have a party!
Don't wanna.
Do you have plans, Yukinon?
If we're going to have a party,
I'll keep myself free.
Really? Hooray!
You're not asking me about my plans?
What, are you trying to say I'm not invited?
Why ask? I know that you won't have any.
I wanna eat one of your cakes, Yukinon!
That's exactly what you were eating earlier, though.
If wishes could be granted,
Also, I'd rather not. I don't want to bake anything for a while.
if desires could be fulfilled,
Aww, why not?
then I wouldn't wish or desire for anything after all.
If you're not gonna bake any, I will!
The things you're handed on a silver platter are never genuine,
Maybe I should bake some after all.
and never everlasting.
You meanie!
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
And that is why
I'll always keep searching.
So, uh, when do you wanna go shopping for Yukinon's birthday presents?
Are you free tomorrow?
Y-Yeah, I am.
I see.
Tomorrow it is, then.
Yeah.
Oh, it's Yumiko.
Yo, 'sup, Yumiko!
Gimmie a sec.
What's the plan after this, guys?
I was about to leave.
I'm not great with crowds.
B-But...
We'll see each other
in school soon enough.
Yup.
Oh, shoot!
I totally forgot to buy a good luck charm!
I even forgot to write out a wish,
so I need to rush back!
Oh, maybe I should buy a charm too.
What are you saying, Bro?!
You dumbass! Nitwit! Hachiman!
Hachiman's not even an insult!
Yukino, I'll be taking my leave here!
What's so funny?
"Dumbass! Nitwit! Hachiman!"
It seems as though Yukinoshita's dictionary of insults
just got updated with a few new entries.
By the way, are you okay with going this way?
Yes.
Well, it's New Year's, so I was wondering
if you were visiting your family.
Oh, I haven't gone back this year.
I don't have any business there,
and it doesn't make a difference
whether I'm there or not.
Then why not go?
If it doesn't matter,
then that's a load off your mind,
and you won't bother anyone,
unlike some people, who ruin things with their mere presence.
Are you introducing yourself?
Indeed.
That's why I've been trying to
minimize my social interactions.
I need to get off here.
Hikigaya.
Here's to another year together.
Super
Lightweight
9g models that don't
let you feel any strain
Don't I look all, like, intellectual?
An intellectual person wouldn't think wearing glasses makes one smart.
Shaddup, jerk!
Blue-Light Blocking
Computer Glasses
If it isn't Hikigaya!
Haruno?
And Hayato?
Hey.
Oh, right.
Yukino's birthday's coming up. So that's why.
Still, you guys sure are close, shopping all by yourselves.
My sister was with us at first,
but she ran off somewhere.
If anything, it's rare to
see you two together.
Oh, we're here for New Year's lunch.
Our parents have been close friends for years.
We just get forced to tag along.
Our parents are off making courtesy calls.
We're waiting for them to finish.
I see now.
I've got a good idea.
Hello?
Oh, Yukino?
It's your big sis!
Can you come see me now?
I'm hanging up.
Oh? Are you sure about that?
What is it?
The thing is...
Take it away.
Wha—
Uh, hello?
I don't believe it.
What are you doing there?
Uh, how should I say this...
End Call
I'll be right there.
Yukinon, over here.
Yuigahama.
You're here, too?
Well, uh, I was shopping with Hikki when we got captured.
O-Oh.
You're late, Yukino.
How dare you, after calling me
out on such short notice.
There, there.
It looks like Yuki rushed here
as soon as she could.
What will you have, Yukinoshita?
Black tea, then.
It's been ages since we last
had tea together, right?
Yeah.
Haruno.
Are you done?
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Hayato.
It's fine.
Everyone here kept me from getting bored.
Oh, Yukino. So you came.
I'm glad.
Mother.
Friends?
Yes, of Yukino's.
My, pardon me.
I couldn't tell because Hayato's the
only schoolmate of Yukino's I know.
I hope you'll continue to
be friends with my daughter.
Sure.
Shall we get going, then?
Okay.
Yukino?
I...
This is also your birthday party, you know.
Yukino, don't.
What the Lights
in Each of Their Hands Illuminate.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
Hayama Hayato Always Lives Up to Expectations.
These must be my true colors.
That's why I couldn't let go.
I locked it deep within myself.
And averted my eyes from the truth.
All I wanted was to be criticized and shown the light.
I wanted someone to see through the pretentious clown that I was.
They were eyes looking in from the outside...
...and so I held high hopes.
...thought they might be able to find me.
...thought they might be able to see through me.
Reality.
How can you be so sure that it's not a figment of your imagination?
Is anything truly genuine?