“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Dollars?
I don't know the finer details,
but anyway, there are a lot of them, and it sounds like they're pretty crazy.
But, you skipped the first day of–
I said, don't ask!
Anyway, don't go near that guy; his name is Hewajima Shizuo.
Orihara Izaya?
That guy is bad news, so don't go anywhere near him.
Yeah. His name's Simon...
...and he has a job touting for that Russian sushi restaurant over there.
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Okay! Okay!
Russian sushi!
It's tasty! It's cheap!
Onii-san, you no run away!
Russian sushi!
Excuse me.
Do you... understand Russian?
Yes, I do.
Oh, good.
We're trying to go here.
How do we get there?
From here, just take this road straight.
Are you on vacation?
Yes.
This town is very fascinating.
I'm sure it'll make for a good trip.
Thank you very much.
Come by our shop too, if you get a chance.
Ikebukuro... a shopping district stretching from east to west.
A huge town with a large-scale red-light district to the north,
where it is said that a million people gather every day.
Ikebukuro.
This town is overflowing with foreigners.
He...
and, she...
came to this town to look for something...
to ask for something.
They came to this town to change something.
Pandemonium
We haven't decided on our class representatives yet.
Do we have any candidates?
It's a new town, where nobody knows who they used to be,
with a chance to become a new person.
However...
Sonohara... Sonohara Anri, is it?
Is there anyone else?
Well then, that settles it for our female representative.
I'll leave the rest to you, Sonohara.
Well then, are there any boys here who would like to be a class representative?
I want to try it, but it'd be too troublesome.
However, I'd be ticked off if anyone else got to do it...
You do it.
Really, me?
But it'd be a pain in the butt!
C'mon, you'd get to work with her!
Yes!
Uh...
I'm Ryugamine... Mikado.
Sonohara-san.
About that representative meeting with the other class tomorrow...
I-I've never done that kinda thing before, so–
Sorry! I'm kinda busy right now. Excuse me.
You're pretty sly yourself!
You, who cried when everyone called the two of you childhood sweethearts in elementary school,
have come back assertively in a lovey-lovey rendezvous and snatched up the hunter's chance!
Yeah, yeah.
But, you were too naive with your final push.
Even if you came to Tokyo just for love, you can't live a "cheerful love-comedy" life like that here!
That's not really it...
And now... let's go flirt with some girls!
Right now, I... From now on, I...
At this moment, I am at the very peak of my popularity!
Even if a high schooler told me to do that...
Many come here looking for change.
However, change doesn't come around that easily.
Even given a change of place,
it's still the same "you" that is there.
No way.
I have a boyfriend.
Who cares? When a guy's flirting with you and takes you out for tea,
it doesn't count as cheating.
Hey, did you guys know?
Yumi's new boyfriend is one of the Dollars.
Really?
Wouldn't that be scary?
How interesting!
Let's talk all about it over some tea!
Are the Dollars like some kind of biker gang or something?
She hasn't been riding around though...
In this town,
But the springtime of youth is all about running wildly, and running...
there are those who form groups, which are sometimes violent.
They all wear different colors as symbols of their affiliation,
and they're called "color gangs."
However, the gang that has demonstrated the most influence lately,
has no color of its own.
If anything, they're colorless and clear;
that is the team color of the Dollars.
They're said to be a unique gang that recruits members for their organization through a special website.
No name
Apparently some of the Awakusu Club are in the back
The headless rider is a member of Dollars
No name
Strongest people in Ikebukuro!
> Headless rider
> Dollars
Hewajima Shizuo
What about Simon-san?
There's a rumor that the recent "slasher incidents" are the Dollars' doing.
Is that so?
Come on, let's discuss the details over some tea!
I know a great place to get some!
Dollars? Yes, I know of them.
What kind of people are they?
The Dollars are amazing!
Recently, they've been negotiating with the Chinese Mafia...
And that one time, when a member of the Yakuza got stabbed, I heard it was one of the Dollars' underlings who did it!
Seriously.
They all ran off because you were looking so gloomy.
Kida-kun!
Hello!
Hey, look it's the guy named like a manga character...
Mikado-kun, isn't it?
Want to go to Toranoana with us?
Today... there's an autograph session for Suzie Yasuda!
Don't talk about it so loudly!
Why? What's wrong with talking about Suzie...
Dollars? Yeah, I've heard the name...
Today, I heard a rumor from a friend...
Well,
I've never seen them in real life, but do you really think they exist?
You think they're an Internet myth?
No, I can't tell, but...
whether or not they're a real gang, it's probably best to stay away from them.
Dollars? They're the guys who've been fighting the Flame Haze that's sealed underground, right?
No they're not, Yumacchi!
They're like those shiny angels who fly so you can see their panties!
Why do you ask about the Dollars?
Well, I'm not exactly sure...
Did our discussion back then scare you?
I've heard rumors about them too.
They're a pretty dangerous bunch of guys.
Is that... so?
I wouldn't get too close to them out of curiosity.
Don't go investigating them for no reason.
Kadota-san, you're so cool!
Kinda like the main character's grown-up older brother, right?
Or the kind that's popular among girls who love the "older man" type characters?
No, no, no.
Shut up!
There are also some places in town where it's best not to set foot.
Oh, you're the outwardly harsh, lover boy type!
Hey! Wait a minute!
It won't break your stomach!
You try eating once!
You won't die if you eat this one time!
I'm hungry.
Me too.
Before we make our next collection, let's...
It's the headless rider!
No way!
What, a cult meeting in broad daylight?
They're serious, all right.
At times, there are those who are swallowed up by the town and disappear.
And, those who desperately search for those people...
I can... I will definitely find her.
My love will call to her.
Harima-san?
Harima-san!
I-I thought you were someone else! Sorry!
And, this town is overflowing with danger.
Excuse me.
Both here...
Hey, wanna go get some tea? Or how about a snack bar? No, wait, look! How about over there...
...and there.
He thought he had come seeking change.
Are you serious?
He had felt like something would change,
like something would've happened in this new town.
However...
what had been awaiting him was a deep darkness, hidden under what was, at first glance, a gorgeous town.
He freezes in fear.
Will he really be able to go on living in this town? He is afraid.
I know how you feel.
You get on a train, and you have to deal with perverts.
You walk down the street and there are shady-looking solicitors.
When you finally get home, you have neighbor trouble!
And what's more, there's the headless rider!
That's Tokyo's concrete jungle for ya!
So overcome it!
You've pledged to become a fine Ikebukuroan,
therefore, you can overcome this obstacle and show them all, Mikado!
Ryugamine... Mikado!
Well, don't worry, 'cause you've got me.
Kida-kun.
Also, when we're flirting with girls, smile brightly.
Smile.
Still... I don't think you'll have any luck flirting with normal women.
What are you saying? The point is just to start talking to them.
My, aren't we acting all high and mighty now that Harima Mika's gone?
I hear you're the new class representative?
What's someone who was a nobody in middle school, doing in charge on day three of high school?
They're picking on her! Though, they're being so corny about it.
It's really not that scary when you're so over-the-top about it.
Well, today we're here to correct your attitude.
Yoko's boyfriend is one of the Dollars.
Hiroshi!
Yo, you!
Mah Dollars' brutha be callin'
so I be like "wakka wakka," know wha' I mean?
This type of hand sign is used worldwide.
It's really refreshing to see something this old school, isn't it?
We really ought to save her.
But how?
Hey you, stop that!
That won't work. I'll be done for.
So...
Hey, Sonohara-san! What a coincidence!
Let's go!
Mikado! You're so cool!
That's it!
There's no other way.
Are you...
Going to stop them from teasing her?
And in this town, events that go beyond imagination frequently take place.
W-What?
W-Wait a sec! W-Wait..
What?
Your bullying is really lame.
It's really no good.
It's none of your business, old man!
Yeah. It's none of my business whether you all get clobbered or die by the roadside here.
Whether I hit you, or whether you call me "old man" even though I'm only twenty-three,
our lack of understanding will be eternal.
Humans are priceless.
Well anyway, I don't really make a habit of hurting girls.
Although, I do make a habit...
...of stomping their cell phones...
to bits!
Wai–
What's with this guy?
Enough of that.
I'm giving up my hobby of smashing phones.
H-Hiroshi!
Yo! Yo! Yo!
Hey, man!
Violence? Oh, scary! I'm scared!
Son of a...
Whoops!
I give up!
Hey, wait! Wait up!
I'll remember this!
Kamaitachi the demon has arrived.
That was truly admirable of you... trying to save a girl from being bullied.
It's been a while, hasn't it, Kida Masaomi-kun?
Yeah... thanks.
That's Raira Academy's uniform, isn't it?
Congrats on making it in.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
It's weird... I didn't expect to see you in Ikebukuro, Izaya.
This is the guy you said not to make enemies with? Orihara Izaya?
This guy's just a friend of mine.
I'm Orihara Izaya. Nice to meet you.
I-I'm Ryugamine Mikado.
Sounds like an air conditioner brand name.
Yeah.
Well then, what brings you to Ikebukuro?
I came here to meet someone.
I've already met him.
No way! Was that one of the trash cans from a store?
It just came flying here? Why?
Oh, crap!
Izaya-kun!
A bartender?
Didn't I tell you never to come back to Ikebukuro,
Izaya-kun?!
Shizu-chan.
I thought you were working at Nishiguchi.
I got fired a while back.
And didn't I tell you not to call me that?!
My name is Hewajima Shizuo.
Hewajima Shizuo?
Another one of the people I shouldn't make enemies with.
Come on, Shizu-chan.
Are you still mad at me for blaming you for something I did?
I'm not mad.
I just wanna punch you in the face!
You know, Shizu-chan, your violent nature will listen to neither words nor reason.
I don't like that. What to do?
Let it go.
There he is! It's him!
You bastard. How dare you humiliate me like that!
You know what happens when you mess with the Dollars?
Wait, he's dressed like a bartender?
No way! He wasn't here a second ago.
H-Hewajima Shizuo?!
What do you guys want?!
When faced with fear, people lose their ability to make rational decisions.
You... you aimed for my head just now?
You know, if you hit me in the right place... I could have died!
And, since you knew that, but did it anyway, I'd say you were trying to kill me!
Then, you won't care about how I retaliate, will you?
A man who has overwhelming strength
inspires genuine fear in the hearts of people.
It was as if violence itself was wearing clothes, or as if he was living purely on violence.
No, as if he was violence itself...
That sort of man.
Idiots! Don't run away! Our opponent is–
Nice work! See ya later!
I won't let you get away.
What? How did he...?
From above...
I know I not should say this now, but just so you know,
I was making delivery to regular customer of ours who lives on top floor of that building.
Simon. You...
Shizuo. Fighting is no good, yes?
Shut up! Get outta my way!
Hey, Mikado. Now's our chance.
No way. Mikado!
Wait! H-Hold–
Can't... breathe...
S-Sorry!
Sometimes this town will give you gifts.
Miracles that are very small and yet very large.
The adventure you always wanted.
The possibility that a new legend will begin. And...
Thanks a lot for what you did!
Excuse me.
Sometimes nothing happens at all.
I found you!
My love!
I hear the Dollars are at it again.
I know! They had a big brawl with some "Hewajima Shizuo" guy in broad daylight!
Apparently the Dollars started it.
The war between Hewajima Shizuo and the Dollars has begun!
...apparently.
No, you're wrong.
I happened to be watching, and those people were just pretending to be Dollars.
No, it's not that.
Lately, people calling themselves Dollars have been
mugging people on the street and taking their money...
Huh?
It's scary, huh? They're terrible, those "Dollars" people.
I'd watch my back if I were you.
Thanks.
They're really scary, aren't they?
The Dollars.
What with Izaya back in Ikebukuro,
I thought I'd get to squeeze his throat for real this time,
but then Simon stepped in.
Although, what did he come here for, anyway?
This town is overflowing with foreigners.
They come here to look for something, to ask for something,
to change something.
Welcome, welcome!
Including me.
You like sushi?
Eat sushi!
Lonesome Misery
Next time on
Durarara!!
Listen to my story.
I want you to hear our story... a story the likes of which you won't hear anywhere else,
from beginning to end.
Next time: Lonesome Misery.
You're sure to lose your mind, trembling in fear.