11th Street
Kon's Summer of Tears
Yay, summer!
Yay, it's the beach!
You seem so excited.
Well yeah! I bought a brand new
swimsuit and floatie just for this!
Hooraayy!
Don't run! You're gonna trip!
Oh no, my floatie popped...
Hey now... Cheer up, okay?
Now it's all limp and saggy...
Where'd this freak downpour come from!?
Hotori!
No, I just bought that!
Hey, cover yourself!
As a high schooler...
No, as a woman...
As a human being, have some dignity!
My swimsuit!
C'mon, stop crying. I'll buy you some curry.
One plate of curry please, Ma'am.
Sorry dear. Kitchen's closed for the day.
Sheesh, what a crybaby.
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Mister Poorman
by Masakazu Ishiguro
Mister Poorman!
You'll never amount to anything, Mister Poorman, so how about I treat you to a nice meal?
Mr. Richman is always such a jerk.
But I'm hungry, so I guess I'll go.
Wow!
If you put this picture under your pillow, you'll have a delicious dream.
scene. 1     A Morning with Yuki Arashiyama
Josephine's Summer (from vol. 2 ch. 19)
I start my mornings by taking Josephine for a walk.
Josephine
Maruko Shopping District
The early morning shopping district is nearly silent.
It's as if time has stopped for everyone but me-
Hey there! Good morning to ya!
Seems like a freak typhoon's coming this way.
Gonna rain cats and dogs tonight, they said.
What'll I do? I'm in trouble!
I relish the quiet of the morning arcade.
The early morning shopping district is very quiet-
Very quiet... Almost as if time has stopped for-
G'MORNIN!
Heard there's a typhoon headed this way.
Better make sure my veggies don't get blown away by the wind!
Well, considering how heavy they are, I think they'll be alright.
Oh, right... You've got a point.
As I walk the quiet streets each morning, I can forget about all the hustle and bustle.
It's almost like my soul is cleansed anew.
And right around this time each morning,
I exchange a simple greeting with the woman who jogs past me.
Oh, good morning to you sir!
Seems there's a freak typhoon coming our way.
They say summer typhoons bring some heavy rain.
I hope my house doesn't get damaged.
Oh yeah, I need to look through my survival kit.
Hmm, non-perishable crackers are rock solid...
Then I buy a can of coffee from the usual vending machine and head back home.
Huh?
Out of Order
The wind's wreaked havoc where I least expected it...
Are you trying to cheer me up, Josephine?
Okay, then let's head home.
Back to our warm, happy home.
What the!? It's been one thing after the other today!
Hotori!
So you went to pick up the paper while you were brushing and it got blown away, huh?
I hear there's a freak typhoon coming.
Gotta watch out for the wind and rain.
Daddy, take us somewhere fun!
Yeah, like the beach or somewhere.
Daddy doesn't have summer vacation like you do.
How about you get your sister to take you to the public pool?
Don't be so selfish, you two!
Hotori, walk the dog for me this evening, okay?
I'm, like, kinda busy today, y'know...
My children all seem to take after their mother.
My only true friend in this house is Josephine.
Mister Poorman
by Masakazu Ishiguro
Mister Poorman!
Today, Mister Richman invited me out to catch insects.
Mister Poorman, you can put the beetles inside this golden cage.
Hey, it escaped! There's only 2 bars!
I had to lower the cost somehow.
After all, it is made of gold!
scene. 2     Hotori Arashiyama's Summer
You're leaving too, Hotori!?
What about the pool?
Why are you going to school during summer vacation?
Yeah, why? Tell me! Tell me!
Hey, why? Why're you going?
Shut up!
I'm not going because I want to!
You  don't have a care in the world, do you?
C'mon, what's the matter?
Oya High School
I was late even though I woke up early!
Reme
dial
Math
Class
Oh, I thought I was late, but I guess I'm the first one here!
You ARE late.
Wait... Am I the only one in the class?
Whoa... Deja vu.
Yes, this is the second time.
Why are you late today?
You see, my dog seemed so very happy...
...So I thought I'd phrase my excuse in the form of a poem.
And of course, you won't accept it.
Okay, let's get on with it.
This is the final exam.
And this is the make-up exam.
The make-up had exactly the same
problems, just with different numbers.
So how did you manage to get a worse score?
I don't know what to tell you...
I guess it was just bad luck or something.
I just kinda went with my gut.
Your gut!?
Did you just say "I went with my gut"?
How dare you undermine the very foundation of math!
Not once have I ever heard that before.
I've devised a method to get you to finally understand math.
Devised?
Listen up, Arashiyama.
Detective work is just like math!
Yeah, I guess. They are vaguely related I suppose.
HEY! I'M BEING SERIOUS!
You see?  Basically, we try to find the culprit using the hints given.
We make inferences by consolidating what we already know.
And once you've removed all obstacles, the culprit's identity becomes clear.
There is only one answer!
See? Just like a detective novel.
I was getting carried away, I suppose.
I got it!
Sleuthing is just like math!
All of a sudden, I feel motivated!
You do?
Inspector Moriaki!
Well, if it isn't Ms. Arashiyama!
Have you solved the case?
Inspector, this horrifying case...
...can't be solved.
Agh! Oh God, the pain...
Ouch... the pain...
scene. 3     Josephine
I'm tired. I had to use my brain today at school.
I was late 'cause I played with you.
I think I'll take a nap after I walk you.
That's what summer's all about.
Hey, we're not going that way.
I'm walking YOU, remember?
Don't just pick up everything you see!
You'll get a tummy ache.
Dodo bird!
Fu-tard-ba!
Who're you callin' a tard!?
Why am I a dodo bird!?
Hey, is THAT your dog?
Yep.
Hey, Kon!
It's rude to laugh at people's pets.
Oh come on, look at it!
A racoon's walking another raccoon!
A raccoon... is walking... another...
Sic 'em, Josephine!
Tear them to shreds!
Josephine!?
Stop it! They're making fun of you!
...Hotori!
Wake up, Hotori!
It seems I'm a raccoon, not a dog.
I've decided to return to the mountains.
Thanks for everything.
Josephine?
I wish you the best.
Josephine!? JOSEPHINE!
Jo-
Josephine!
Josephine's gone...
She went back to the mountains!
Josephine!
Josephiiine!
You belong here with us! Come back home!
What the heck is she doing out there? A typhoon's coming.
Maybe she's pretending to be an actress.
That's just how girls are.
Shake.
That means you do this.
If you can't even learn "shake",
you'll get called a raccoon again.
Okay, let's try again. Shake!
This is hopeless.
She has no clue what's going on.
I've come to learn some things since I've lived here.
I think this family's hierarchy is like so.
Last
Maybe this is how Mr. Moriaki feels when he tries to teach me math.
That's some food for thought.
It seems the only one below me is the very tall male.
Mister Poorman
by Masakazu Ishiguro
Mister Poorman.
Oh hi, Mr. Poorman. I just bought a popular new DVD.
Would you like to come and see it in my home theater?
After all-
I've got nothing to do, and I've never seen it. I'll go.
Theater Room
Oh, yes! Marvelous!
That's a popular DVD for you!
You don't have a DVD player?
Mister Poorman
by Masakazu Ishiguro
I'm so cold...
Hi there, Mister Poorman. You look depressed as usual.
How about it? Would you care to visit my winter villa?
Damn.
He really bugs me, but I'd just end up going back to my freezing cold house... Okay, I'll go.
Okay, it's almost done.
Give me a hand here, would you?
Kon's Silent Rage (from vol. 6 ch. 49)
Densuke Kon
That's the ticket!
Man, it's hot...
I wonder if they'll cancel the club meetings.
Ooh, nice and cool.
Turned the AC down 3
degrees without permission
Took bottled water from the
fridge and drank out of it...
Eww, it's warm.
...And didn't put it back
Random inflated inner tube
And that stupid look on her face
She just snuck in and made herself at home.
Left the cat outside
RAGE
Jeez, it's hot!
Meanwhile, as for Hotori...
Here's your drink, my Queen.
A sweet bun for you, my Queen.
This is the life!
A torch for you, my Queen.
H-Hey guys, that's hot!
I don't need a torch, okay?
Oops, I dropped it.
FIRE!
H-Hey, wait!
Oh no, I'm tangled up!
It burns!
I can't move! Someone help me!
Fire on Mt. PomPom...
How about Sashimi and Miso soup for dinner?
Huh? Weren't you going to make curry?
That's what I went shopping for originally,
but the bald Fu Man Chu guy said to take some Sashimi.
Huh!? What in the world!?
Take with thee this Sashimi.
Maybe if you eat that Sashimi, you'll become immortal!
Oh wait, by Fu Man Chu, you mean Sanada's dad?
Hey, you know what I learned the other day?
Omelette's taste really good if you add sugar!
How have you been making them all this time?
You'd never think so, but it really is the secret to better taste!
I know. Kinda like cooking sake, right?
What's so counterintuitive about that?
Hey, let's try putting some sugar in this too.
No way, forget it.
Come on, it'll be yummy. I promise.
I said it's fine.
Really, I'm not messing with you!
It doesn't need it.
Sweets can't be beat!
I said knock it off already.
Yikes...
If you're just gonna sit there, make up a song.
A song?
It's nice to listen to people sing in person every now and then.
Okay then.
Since we're going to the beach tomorrow,
I'll make up a beach-themed song.
Seagulls sure are pretty.
But crows sure aren't.
By: Johnny of the Docks.
No good?
Not even close.
Mister Poorman
by Masakazu Ishiguro
Hi there.
Ah, Mister Poorman.
You look like you haven't had a decent meal for some time.
I've perfected the ultimate Mixed
Rice recipe. Care to come try it out?
Damn.
He really bugs me, but I bet there's lots of great stuff inside it... I guess I'll go.
I used a 60/40 mix of Koshihikari and Sasanishiki rice.
So there's nothing actually mixed in?
What's up, Tatsuno?
You expecting someone?
N-No, not really...
Like the fishmonger's kid?
Hotori's not working today.
And nobody else to interfere. It has to be today!
I'm going to invite Sanada to the beach!
Huh? Is Arashiyama off today?
She said she went to the beach. Just the two of them.
The beach!? The two of them!?
This can't be happening!
While I was dragging my ass, Hotori went off to the beach with another guy!?
In that case, I've gotta hurry and confess. I've got nothing to lose!
If I get rejected, at least I can finally give up!
If I lose just because I was taking it too slow...
Now's my chance. I've gotta invite him right now!
Would you like to go to the beach?
That's just 8 syllables, even with the question mark!
H-Hey, Sanada...
Um... If you feel like it...
W-would you...
Would you like to...
...go squid-watching?
Choked during the moment of truth...
Who cares about the beach!?
It's just a stupid beach!
I will darken the sea with my tears!
I wish I could stir the sea with my rage!
Hey, looks like it's raining.
No, I just bought that!
Hey, cover yourself!
As a high schooler...
No, as a woman...
As a human being, have some dignity!
My swimsuit!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
Living for rock!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living alone, blasting my music.
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
but my beloved has yet to confess to me.
Kyou mo kare ni wa naze ka kokurezu
We devote our beings to table tennis,
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
so we build our endurance by playing the drums.
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
We're the Maids, yeah!
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
Seaside's the best maid cafe around!
Shisaido wa zessan eigyouchuu
Thank you very maid for coming!
And the Town Still Turns
Next Episode
Checkmate, Hotori!
Hey, wait a sec!
If you're not gonna eat, I'll clear the table.
Wait, I was saving that!
If you're not gonna wear this, I'll throw it out.
Keep it! I just gotta lose some more weight first.
Oh, look at the time. I'm going on ahead, Arashiyama.
Hang on, I'm almost done!
Hotori!
Arashiyama!
C'mon guys, just wait a sec!
No!
Next time: 12th Street
Cafe Seaside
"Soremachi"
And still it keeps on turning.