Sheesh!
Yuu-chan, get changed already!
You're being annoying!
I can change after finishing this green tea bread, can't I?
You can eat that while walking, can't you?
It's uncouth to eat while walking!
I'll show you something interesting!
That's true, but...
Huh?
Yuu, you haven't changed yet?
Are you attending PE again?
You aren't allowed to leave school in your jerseys,
so it'd be bad if someone saw you walking home like that.
Hear that?
Listen to what she says.
Everyone wants to leave,
but they can't because of you.
Shizuku
Wai-
What are you writing?
Actually, it's okay.
Huh?
I wanted to stop by a vending machine.
Kaede, come with me.
Okay!
I'm going to eat until they return!
Glance
Munch
I'll change you right now!
Let me eat!
Don't resist!
What are you doing, Harupoppo?
And Yuu-chan.
I forgot that they were here!
Um...
I was going to strip her...
Strip?
Sheesh, Haruka!
What happened?
We're back!
Hey, more changing,
less playing around.
Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
What are you doing?!
Yuu-chan, you saved me!
I almost drowned!
She saved me
So forced!
Didn't you say you'd save me if I started drowning?
I didn't mean this!
Save?
Did something happen?
President Mitsuki?!
Don't get hurt or anything.
Okay!
Haruka-san's swimsuit...
Grab
I didn't think you'd come!
President Mitsuki!
I thought it might be nice.
There aren't any ulterior motives.
Really?
Isn't this a good chance to watch over Haruka and Yuu?
Well then, let's have fun!
Hey...
There!
Onee-chan can't swim!
What?!
Swimsuit Fanservice ☆ Some Crying
Onee-chan, are you okay?
Thank you, Yuu.
We're sorry.
Huh...
M-My glasses!
We need to look for them!
W-Where are they?!
I'm going to look for them, so don't worry.
Just get out, Onee-chan.
Found them!
This time you lost something even more important!
Having fun, everybody?!
We are!
Is an indoor pool okay?
Totally awesome!
It's amazing that you have a pool in your home!
Not surprising for Kotone!
Kotone-san organised this?
Yes!
Have as much fun as you can!
Even though she looks like this,
she's actually pretty wealthy!
W-Well...
I had no idea!
There!
Still, why are you having the cultural festival after-party at a heated pool?
Come to think of it...
You don't know either?
Shizuku-chan came up with it.
Shizuku-san did?
Dot
Y-You know, swimming helps your figure.
This is just to get us more active.
It's strange to see you drinking.
It was quite a chore to arrange this...
What?!
Let's swim, shall we?
Okay.
Um...
President Mitsuki, so you can't swim either?
Actually, the same goes for me!
Haruka-san started talking to me!
It's okay if we can't swim, right?
No it isn't!
I'm going to put you through some special training,
Harupoppo and President Mitsuki!
If that's all, I'm not scared.
Or is this better?
The first one, please!
Haruka's busy.
Shizuku-chan, let's play!
Hey, Shizuku-chan!
Hey, listen, Shizuku-chan!
Okay, fine..
Shizuku-chan, let's go into the pool too!
My skin can't take it!
My skin's delicate, so I have to be careful.
I see...
That won't do, Harupoppo!
Kicking is the basis of everything!
President Mitsuki, you too!
You need way more practice too.
Hey, if you can't swim, get over here!
Coach Kotone is looking this way.
That was just by chance.
Let me go!
It doesn't bother me that I can't swim!
It seems they're not very motivated.
It's me.
Bring it in.
Something's coming!
This is Yamada-san.
Yamada-san?
And that's Suzuki-san and Tanaka-san.
Wow...
Those who learn how to swim...
...get this!
I'm not interested in it at all!
They sped up?!
Hooray!
Even though I followed Yamada...
Shinobu?!
So you're home, Kotone-oneesama?
Huh, that girl is...
Kotone's little sister who's in primary school.
I'm in 7th grade!
Sorry.
Shizuku!
You've been having her freeload at your place, haven't you?
She said that she wanted to do that, though.
That can't be true!
Don't just make stuff up!
For the longest time, Kotone-oneesama has...
Hello.
When she comes play,
each and every time, she...
Shizuku-chan!
Geez, stop that!
She starts teasing her instead of me!
That really annoyed me, though.
More importantly, Kotone-oneesama.
Since you left home without asking,
mother and father are really upset!
They even neglected to talk about the engagement.
Kotone-oneesama, I'm going to have you stay home from now on.
What's the hold-up?
Let's get going!
Please wait!
Don't touch Chappy-kun with wet hands!
S-Sorry...
Hey, Kotone-chan, are you really okay with this?
I don't know the details,
but you don't seem happy, Kotone-chan.
But...
Shizuku-chan, what about you?
Shizuku-chan, are you okay with this?
Yes.
I don't think being with me all the time will make Kotone happy.
If she has a partner, she has to face them,
and not just use me as an escape!
Think before you kiss!
Shizuku-chan!
There, there, Shizuku-chan.
Is that how you really feel?
I won't give Kotone-oneesama to you!
You homewrecker!
Shinobu!
Hey, everyone!
How about a duel?
She's still doing that?
That's right.
Shinobu-chan vs. Shizuku-chan.
She'll live with whoever wins!
A swimming showdown?
Yamada, prepare my swimsuit.
At once.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Huh?
I haven't said anything about this yet,
but I can't swim.
Well, we knew that.
Shizuku-chan!
Huh?
This!
I'm ready!
Why do you have the stuffed toy on your back?
It's Chappy-kun!
Chappy-kun is really good at the doggy paddle!
I'm one with Chappy-san in both mind and body.
We've practically won!
What...
That's unfair!
President Mitsuki really believed that.
Ready!
This pisses me off.
S-Shizuku-chan, good luck!
Didn't that make her happy?!
Stupid...
Stupid Kotone!
But still...
Geez!
Shizuku-chan is the winner!
Hey!
Isn't it strange for Chappy-kun to get so heavy when wet?!
You did something to it, didn't you, Yamada?!
I'm sorry.
Well done, Shizuku-chan!
Hooray!
You did your best!
Congratulations!
Did Yamada-san do that for Kotone's sake?
Yuzu, you don't seem that nervous.
The battle was quite fierce.
I-I am pretty nervous, though.
Shizuku-chan said something about kissing back then.
Huh?
She was probably referring to that kiss on her cheek that we talked about earlier.
I wonder if she was.
Of course she was!
You always come up with weird ideas, Kaede.
That's all it is.
Yeah,
you're right.
Swimsuit Fanservice ☆ Some Crying
Swimsuit Fanservice ☆ Some Crying                      The End
I'm leaving!
It's pretty cold!
I'm glad I'm wearing a scarf.
Haruka!
Eek!
Yuu-chan's hugging me from behind!
Morning...
Her nose is running.
Is she...
Shopping with Yuu-chan
You should wear a scarf or something.
I had one but I gave it away.
Y-You gave it away?
Hey, Yuu!
I can't see anything!
Yuu, where are you?!
Hey, it seems like that person is looking for you!
This is bad!
I told you I already have a scarf!
Ah, it's just you, President Mitsuki!
Huh!
Haruka-san?!
Huh?
I-I mean...
Sheesh, Yuu, you'll catch a cold.
Wear it.
No way.
Why do you hate it so much?
Oh my.
You're preparing for entrance exams, so it would be terrible if you caught a cold.
It seems like you're doing this on purpose.
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
Little
Sister
Big
I'm going on ahead.
Do you really hate that scarf that much?
Maybe I could have it, then?
Yeah, that's fine!
Yay, Yuu-chan's used clothes!
It's my sister's, though.
I haven't even worn it once.
It wasn't yours?!
You hate it because it's second-hand?!
The scarf I used to use frayed.
And then Onee-chan...
This is mine.
You can use it.
But you know,
I saw a nice one a shop prior to that that I wanted to buy.
But why don't you use it now that you have it?
You can't let things go to waste.
I'll give it to you, then!
Huh?
Don't let it go to waste!
Yeah, I know!
Morning!
G'Morn!
Morn!
Yuu brought someone suspicious with her!
It's Haruka!
Ta-da!
Did you do the biology assignment yet?
Huh? Didn't even start.
Ignoring me?!
I thought I'd go buy a new scarf today.
Oh?
Have you decided what kind you want to get?
A fluffy-
Morning.
Ah, Shizuku-chan, mor-
Oh, that's the one I wanted!
Huh, and if Shizuku-chan's wearing it...
Oh, this?
I thought it was cute, so I bought it yesterday.
It was the last one so I ended up spending quite a bit.
Shizuku-chan stood in front of the mirror all day yesterday!
Isn't it okay?
Otherwise I can't see it.
Haruka...
They're sold out!
I know!
Let's go find an even better one after school!
I want that one!
But it seems Shizuku-chan bought it...
I don't want anything else!
Well...
Can't you use this for now?
Haruka, will you go shopping with me?
Huh?
She really hates it...
Scarf, scarf, so fluffy!
They might still have another one.
50%
This is cute!
And it's 50% off!
It's a nice colour!
Should I try it on?
Scarf!
Sorry!
They really are out.
But isn't that flower pattern one cute too?
I wanted that one.
Want to go check some other stores?
They may have similar ones.
Let's go, Yuu-chan.
Haruka...
Geez, just try it on!
Fitting room
It's not very well-balanced...
50%
If my chest were smaller, S could be good...
Yuu-chan, for me, S is a bit...
How was it?
Haruka's gained weight,
so bring this in M.
Yuu-chan!
Understood.
You'll have to lose weight, Haruka.
Y-Yeah...
I don't!
I know!
Let's ask the employee if they have any in stock!
Huh?
This is M-size.
Excuse me!
Yes?
Do you have the scarf Shizuku-chan bought yesterday in stock?
Yuu-chan!
She won't understand if you say just that!
A scarf we sold yesterday?
It was white, fluffy, and soft...
She won't get it like that!
50%
Please wait here a moment.
I wonder if they have any!
I feel like she wouldn't know even if they did.
This one?
Yay!
She really is a pro!
That is it!
We were looking for it!
It's really popular.
Take your time.
We should have asked right away.
Right!
Huh?
Haruka, that one's cute, isn't it?
That one?!
I'll buy this one.
I'll try this on again.
Haruka, Haruka!
I'll go pay for this!
Overwhelmed with happiness.
Next day
I'm a little sleepy.
I wonder if Yuu is wearing a scarf.
It seems she is today.
Wait!
H-Haruka-san?!
Haruka-san is wearing my...
Why?!
Shopping with Yuu-chan
Shopping with Yuu-chan                                 The End
Some More Crying
Thank you for waiting!
Welcome to this popular segment we have every episode!
Not every episode!
First off, President Sonoda Mitsuki.
Is she really Yuu's sister?
Noda Kotone and her self-indulgent body!
I'm completely jealous to her, for obvious reasons!
Indeed.
The D-cup Takayama Haruka-san!
Haruka is a C-cup!
Yuu?!
The super cute Iizuka Yuzu-chan!
Don't say that! It's embarrassing!
The cute Minami Shizuku-chan!
Her figure is unexpectedly nice.
The tiny and cute Sonoda Yuu-chan!
She's hiding her chest for some reason.
Ikeno Kaede.
That was fast!
It's okay.
I know!
Some More Crying
Some More Crying                       The End
Yay
Won't you kiss
Kiss and love
futari dake no jikan ga
二人だけの時間が
Time for just the two of us
futari dake no himitsu ga
二人だけの秘密が
A secret for just the two of us
futari dake no yakusoku
二人だけの約束
A promise between just the two of us
aru kara ne
あるからね
We have all of them
yorokobi wakachiaete kanashimi wakeaetara
喜び分かち合えて 悲しみ分け合えたら
If we share our joys and split our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
一人より幸せに なれるように
We may be able to become happier than if we were alone
ashita mo omoide wo saa fuyasou
明日も思い出をさあ増やそう
Let's make more memories tomorrow as well
ippai ni shichaou ne
一杯にしちゃおうね
Let's make a lot of them!
Love you
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
この広い世界で 逢えた奇跡
I came across a miracle in this wide world
tokubetsu na no anata janai to dame dakara
特別なの あなたじゃないとだめだから
But it's no good if you're not special to me
futari janai to dekinai koto da yo
二人じゃないとできないことだよ
It's something we can't do if we're not together
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
いますぐに 大好き kiss and love
I love you now, kiss and love
Love
Preview
Kaedekko, Kaedekko!
What?
I feel like we don't talk that much.
It's your imagination.
By chance, do you hate me?
Not hate, it's just...
Just?
I can't accept a certain part of you that I don't have!
Next time, trick eight!
Sakura-coloured Wedding
Sakura-coloured Christmas
"Sakura-coloured Wedding" and "Sakura-coloured Christmas"!
Look forward to it!
So, what part do you mean?
It's a secret.