I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but then a small incident happened.
What I believed in was my courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
What I wished for was that even my
smallest feelings would reach her.
The start of every new journey is always full of sadness,
but because our feelings are surely connected...
"Goodbye" isn't a word of finality, but
rather the word of a new beginning.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
Everyone, please! Escape! Hurry!
Fate!
Fate! Fate!
Fate-chan!
Fly... towards me!
Call My Name.
Looks like the earthquake's stopped...
Huh? You're right...
The Garden has completely collapsed.
Everything within it has been absorbed
into the imaginary dark spaces.
Furthermore, the dimensional disturbance
has been prevented.
There's no indication of a
dimensional dislocation outbreak.
Understood.
Returning to level three nautical velocity,
and resuming our normal patrol cruise.
Huh? Where's Fate-chan?
Together with Arf in the brig.
After all, she's a vital witness for this incident.
I'm sorry about this, but she'll be held
in isolation for the time being.
No way- ow ow ow...
Nanoha! Stay still.
If we had made a mistake with this incident, a
dimensional dislocation would probably have occurred.
This is a very grave matter.
As a member of the
Time-Space Administration Bureau...
...we can't afford to treat anyone
related to this case leniently.
I trust you understand, right?
Yeah...
Amy, fix it.
And after that, a lot of things finally ended.
From the day I met Yuuno-kun to today when
everything ended, it seems like the time just flew by.
While the aftereffects of the dimensional
disturbance were being repaired...
...we remained aboard the Asura for a few days.
And then, after that...
There have been a great number of meritorious deeds
involved with the conclusion of this incident...
...and I'll have to summarize them for now,
but I give them all my highest praise.
Takamachi Nanoha-san, Yuuno Scrya-kun.
Thank you.
Chrono-kun... what's going to
happen to Fate-chan now?
Even under the circumstances, she can't deny that she
was an accomplice in the dimensional interference.
It's because this is a felony.
Normally, the punishment for this would be
imprisonment for a couple hundred years...
No way!
However!
The situation is unique this time, and it's clear that
she didn't willingly participate in the crime.
All that's really left is getting the
higher-ups to understand.
But I'm confident in my ability
to do that, so don't worry.
Chrono-kun...
The Time-Space Administration Bureau isn't so cold as
to question a girl who unknowingly committed a sin...
...when she was simply trying her
best to fulfill her mother's wish.
Chrono-kun, are you really a nice
person underneath everything?
Wh-?!
A-As a government official, it's only
natural to make such a remark...!
It's not like I'm voicing my own opinions!
You don't have to be so embarrassed about it.
I-I'm not being embarrassed about anything!
What?! Don't laugh!
He's so cute!
The residual effects of the dimensional
disturbance should settle down soon.
From where we stand now, I can safely say that we
should be able to return you to your world tomorrow.
Thank goodness!
But as for you... the space around Midchilda is still
extremely unstable and hasn't equalized...
...and it looks like it'll take some time until it does...
I see...
It looks like it's going to take a couple months or even
a half a year until that area becomes safe again.
Is that so...
Umm... well, my tribe does nothing but
search for new relics and artifacts...
...so I don't think there's any need to hurry home, but...
...I can't just stay here in your
care the whole time, either.
Then why don't you stay at my house?
Just like we've been doing.
Nanoha, is that really all right?
Yeah! If it's okay with you...
Then, umm... uh...
I'll be in your care once again.
Yeah!
Geez, it's because you slept so long.
It's because I was up all night
working... I'm still so tired...
You know that place she was aiming for,
don't you, Yuuno-kun? Alhazred...
Yes... I heard of it once before.
I heard it existed in space long ago before
the old lunar calendar was established...
...and that it was a land filled with
secret arts and technology.
But it's also said it was destroyed during
a dimensional dislocation long ago.
Here you are.
It's said that all magic arrives
there in its ultimate form...
...and if one were to hold that power,
one's every wish could be granted...
...through Alhazred's secret technology...
Magic that would allow you to transcend
the barriers of time and space...
Magic that would even let you rewrite your past...
Magic that could bring someone back to life...
Those are some of the things she was seeking, right?
Yes...
But anyone who studies magic knows two things...
Traveling back in time and reviving
the deceased is impossible.
But since she wished for both things...
...she couldn't overlook the fact that it was
nothing more than a fairy tale world...
A simple legend.
She couldn't bear the fact that it was simply a story.
But... since that great mage risked her life in
search of it, she might've actually found...
...the path to Alhazred.
Though we'll never know if she did.
I'm sorry. I ended up going into a long discussion
when we just sat down to eat.
Let's hurry and eat up before the food gets cold.
And this will probably be the last meal
on the Asura for you, Nanoha.
Yeah...
You should just say that you're sad about seeing her go!
Chrono-kun, you're such a shy guy!
W-W-What are you saying?!
Nanoha-chan, you can come over
and play whenever you want!
Yes! Thank you.
Amy! The Asura isn't some playground!
Now, now, it's all right.
After all, our patrols are always full of free time.
E-Even you, Captain?!
And then came the morning
Yuuno-kun and I were to leave...
Well then... once again, thank you very much
for all you've done in this incident.
We're grateful for your cooperation.
I'll contact you once Fate's verdict is in.
I'm sure it'll be fine, though.
I promise nothing bad will happen to her.
Yeah, thanks.
Yuuno-kun, if you ever want to return
to your world, just let us know.
We'll make a gate for you whenever you want.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Well then, I guess it's time?
Yes!
Well...
Yeah. See you again, Chrono-kun, Amy-san, Lindy-san!
Well, shall we head home, Yuuno-kun?
Yeah.
I'm home!
Nanoha! Welcome back!
And my everyday life had returned.
It all should have gone back to how it used to be...
Mom! I'm hungry!
...but a lot of things happened, so it's a little different.
Welcome home.
I'll make my famous yellowtail and white radish meal!
Yeah!
Nanoha-chan!
Nanoha!
I'm back. I came back just like I said I would!
When I think back on the time when I
was busy working with Yuuno-kun...
...it feels like it all happened in the blink of an eye.
But those events certainly left an
impression within my heart.
All the people I met... each time I was at
my wit's end... there's so many things...
Ahh! It's been so long since I've slept in my bed!
You be sure to sleep well tonight too, okay, Yuuno-kun?
Yeah!
And really, thanks a lot for everything
you did, Raising Heart.
Thanks for all your hard work too, Nanoha.
Though... the only thing I'm worried
about now... is that girl.
That girl who's so gentle...
who has such beautiful eyes...
And a few days later...
Hello! This is Nanoha!
Huh? Really?!
Yeah. It was just officially decided.
Fate will be taken into the custody of our main office.
After hearing her description of the
circumstances, a trial will be held.
Fate will probably... no, I can almost definitely say
she will be found innocent. Everything's fine.
After all, Chrono-kun personally
saw to the case after you left.
Amy! You don't need to say unnecessary
things like that...
Thanks so much, Chrono-kun!
Anyway, the evidentiary hearing and trial will take
some time to process, so before all that...
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah!
I'll be right there!
Yeah!
What was that all about, Nanoha?
It seems that Fate will be transferred
to their main office for a while...
But they said I could see her before they move her!
I see.
She even said she wanted to see me!
Fate-chan!
We don't have much time, but I think you
guys should talk while you still can.
We'll be waiting on the other side, so...
Thanks!
Thank you.
I had so much I wanted to talk
to you about, but it's funny...
...as soon as I saw your face, I completely forgot it all.
I...
Yes, you're right... I can't put what
I want to say into words...
But I was happy...
That you faced me with such honesty...
Yeah... because I thought it'd be
nice if we could become friends.
But... after today, you'll be leaving
for a while, won't you...?
Yes... apparently, it will be a long trip.
We'll definitely meet again, won't we?
It makes me a little sad, but... I'm finally
able to start anew as my true self, so...
I came here today... to give you an answer.
To those words you said to me...
"I want us to be friends..."
Yeah, yeah!
I thought.. if I could do it... if it
would be all right with you...
But, I... don't know what to do.
That's why I want you to tell me...
how can we become friends?
It's simple.
Becoming friends with someone is really simple.
You just have to call out her name.
That's all you need to do at the beginning.
Don't say "hey, you" or call her "that person," but...
Look straight into her eyes and clearly say her name.
I'm Takamachi Nanoha.
Just call me Nanoha!
Nano... ha?
Yeah! Just like that!
Nanoha...
Yes!
Nanoha.
Thank you, Nanoha...
Yes...!
Nanoha...
Yes!
Your hand sure is warm... Nanoha.
Something I just learned...
When you see a friend crying, you also become sad...
Fate-chan!
Thank you, Nanoha...
I'll have to leave you for now, but...
I'm sure we'll meet again.
When we do... is it all right if I call your name again?
Yeah! Yeah!
When I want to see you...
I'll be sure to call out your name.
So... please call out my name, too.
Next time when you're the one in trouble,
I'm sure I'll be the one to save you...
That girl... Nanoha... is really such a good girl, isn't she?
For her to make Fate smile that much...
It's time. Are you two about done?
Yes.
Fate-chan!
This is all I can give you...
so I'll remain in your memories.
Then I'll give you mine, too...
Thank you... Nanoha.
Yeah... Fate-chan!
I'm sure we'll see each other again.
Yeah. I'm sure we will!
Thank you! You stay well too, okay, Arf-san?
Yeah. Thanks for everything you did, Nanoha, Yuuno.
Well then, I'll also be going...
See you again, Chrono-kun.
Yeah.
Bye bye... see you again...
Chrono-kun...
Arf-san...
Fate-chan!
Nanoha...
Yeah!
Make a Little Wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey, but
since you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
Ah, it's okay to keep going without hanging your head.
Because the courage you gave to me
that day is still in this hand.
Nanoha!
Coming!
As the stars begin to twinkle,
kindness is born again.
Hey, I want to always, always
cherish this love of ours.
Make a Little Wish and wrap
yourself in the lemon-colored drops of the moon.
I want to shine brightly
and I want you to stay happy.
Make a Little Wish, on days when it's raining.
or at dawn when you can't fall asleep.
Because you were there,
I was able to have this great smile, just like this.
Even in times when we're far apart,
there's always one thing I hold to be true.
That our hearts
are always, always one.
Make a Little Wish and gather
the lemon-colored drops of the moon.
Your warm tears will only
become the spice of my smile.
Make a Little Wish, I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey, but
since you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.