Well, well, well.
You pushed us to the sidelines after all that boasting about defeating the Precures, and yet, here we are.
I wonder, how will you report this to King Selfish?
We can defeat the Precures whenever we choose.
That's right.
We've just been warmin' up so they don't give us cramps.
We'll show you what happens when we get serious!
Are you all right?
He's sleeping?
The gears are already in motion...
for our ultimate plan to destroy the world!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Anyone there?
It's not a door.
Hello?
And it's not a phone.
The mirror that reflects any truth, Magical Lovely Pad.
This Sacred Treasure holds the same power as the princess's spear, and if we can master it,
we should be able to purify King Selfish.
But how do we even use it?
It's a mirror, but it doesn't reflect anything.
Then let us analyze it!
Unfortunately, modern science is unable to fully analyze this object.
Shall we test its heat resistance at 1000 degrees Celsius?
Or perhaps its stress resistance at the ocean floor?
I-I have a better idea!
Ai!
Not even Kyupirappa worked?
We've finally obtained the power to oppose King Selfish,
and yet we're unable to use it...
Hey, anyone hungry?
Crisis in Oogai City!
The Birth of the Lovely Pad!
I'm back!
Hello.
Oh, Rikka.
Mommy! What happened to work?
I'm on break.
I just had a craving for some omelette rice!
C'mon, Aguri, come in!
But with our situation, I've no will to eat...
There is still so much we lack in strength...
You can't fight on an empty stomach, you know.
But...
Oh, Aguri!
Grandmother! Why are you here?
Just a notice for the next tea ceremony.
Sorry for making you come out here.
Here.
Thank you.
Perhaps I should have some omelette rice as well.
May I join you all?
Of course!
Grandpa, Daddy!
Make us some yummy omelette rice!
Okay!
Now you come in too, Aguri!
Ah...
You simply must join us as well, Sebastian.
If you so insist.
Mommy, can I sit next to you?
Oh, of course.
I'm starving!
On to our next story.
A strange phenomenon is occurring in Oogai City.
Previously healthy people are suddenly collapsing and falling asleep.
We don't know the cause, but the number of people afflicted is slowly increasing.
What could that be about?
Ai, what's wrong?
Oh no!
People are falling asleep before our very eyes!
Something's happened to our field reporters.
What could this be?
What happened?
Mommy! Are you okay?
She's asleep!
Mana's grandpa!
They're not waking up.
Mommy!
Grandmother!
Wake up!
Those dark objects are...
Sebastian!
Watch out!
Mana!
Was that...
The Lovies protected you!
Come and get me, Precures!
This is our final measure to destroy the world.
The Selfish Plant we raised produces immeasurable amounts of Selfish Seeds!
Those seeds rain and scatter from the skies,
embedding themselves into the psyches of everyone in town!
For now, those humans can do nothing but sleep!
But when those seeds bud, everyone's psyche shall be enveloped in darkness!
Selfish!
Imagine, tens of thousands of Selfishes going berserk!
And those human-turned-Selfishes will bring about the end of their own world with their own hands!
But that's not all!
The sudden burst of new Egogy will immediately resurrect King Selfish!
And it won't be long before those seeds bud.
The world is as good as destroyed!
There is but one way to stop it...
and that is to defeat us!
But of course...
you girls...
Have no chance of defeating us!
Well...
we'll never know unless we try!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Wait.
You have a five minute time limit.
Let us get this fight started!
I understand!
Ladies and gentlemen!
This is our true power!
They combined!
Now, let's begin!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Precure Diamond Shower!
Let's combine our strength!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Now it's our turn!
Here we go!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Cure Ace!
Let us end this at once!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Where's the Lovely Pad?
Oh, do you mean this Sacred Treasure?
Sacred Treasure?
It's what those legendary warriors used.
What'll happen when I do this?
The... Lovely Pad...
And with that, this fight is over!
Oh?
What good do you think that junk'll do ya?
It's not junk.
It may be broken,
but it still holds Melan's feelings.
It's a treasure!
The Precure's Five Vows!
A Precure must always hold her head high and persevere!
Even without the Lovely Pad, we shall never lose to the likes of you!
The Selfish Seeds will bud at any moment.
We'll wait until then to strike the final blow!
We wouldn't want you to miss the end of the world, after all!
Not one of our attacks worked...
There's nothing left we can do...
I'm sorry, Sword...
I'm sorry, Charles...
I...
I thought I understood how you all felt about losing Trump Kingdom...
But I didn't understand a thing.
After having it happen to the people around me and the city I live in, I finally understand.
It makes your heart sting so much...
It's just too sad!
I can't stand it!
Cry harder, wail louder!
After all, when the world ends, you're going with it!
Welp, that was a good cry.
I'm better now.
I'm done being sad.
Now, time to fight back!
Fight back?
The Lovely Pad's broken, so we don't stand a chance as we are now.
So let's just get waaaaaaay stronger than we are now!
Aguri, you used your desire to protect the world to mature and become Cure Ace.
If strong feelings can make us mature, then we can get stronger!
Can you truly strengthen yourselves right this instant?
We can!
I know it!
After all, we want to save everyone!
Those feelings won't lose to the Selfishes!
Besides...
I'm not alone!
Really now.
You're always asking the impossible,
but you're really pushing it now!
But Heart is exactly right.
However strong our foes may be, our feelings shall never lose!
If we're all together, we can do it!
Melan's with us, too...
The feelings she held while waiting ten thousand years for us...
deserve a good answer!
Leva said this was their final plan.
That means they're at the end of their rope as well.
Let's beat them down with everything we've got!
There's nothing to fear if we're together!
We won't let this world meet Trump Kingdom's fate!
Cure Heart...
I never thought you would be the one to teach me.
You have...
No, you all have risen to a new stage of Precure!
The Precure's Five Vows!
First!
A Precure must always hold her head high and persevere!
Second!
Love is meant to be given!
Third!
To love is to defend one another!
Fourth!
A Precure must trust herself and never regret her actions!
Fifth!
A Precure must be a first class lady!
Sixth!
There's a sixth?!
If we work together,
anything is possible!
Girls, let's go!
Yeah!
Stop right there!
This is our world...
and we're gonna protect it!
You simply don't know when to quit.
Then we'll get rid of you all at once!
Even if you're strong enough to destroy the world,
there are some things you can never erase!
Our determination to protect others will never die!
I'll blow away...
every last bit...
of your foolish feelings!
We won't let you!
We'll protect our city and Melan's feelings!
However strong you may be, we won't give in!
As long as our hearts still beat within our chests...
As long as I can feel my heart race,
we will never...
Give up!
The Lovely Pad?
I can feel a tremendous power...
Did it...
The Lovely Pad responded to our heartbeats!
Lovely Pad, you have my thanks.
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
We shall make this town's heart race once more!
Kyupirappa!
We already said...
that you don't stand a chance!
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Precure Lovely Straight Flush!
Sorry for the wait.
It looks yummy!
Aguri, is something wrong?
I'm eating a meal with everyone.
I'm just happy that I can.
Me too.
I always took it for granted...
but there's nothing happier than this!
All right, save the talking for later!
Eat it while it's hot!
Don't mind if we do!
That Magical Lovely Pad...
What fearsome power...
Blasted Precures...
Next time—
Unfortunately, there won't be a next time.
Bel...
What are you...
I'm helping myself to the source of our power, Egogy.
Sadly, your battle with the Precures has left you gravely exhausted.
You don't even have enough strength left to resist.
Curse you!
I never thought you intended this from the start—
Bel!
Your services are no longer required.
Now pack up your belongings.
I'll finish the job for you.
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Wait, Mana, are you okay?
No, I'm not...
She has a fever, likely due to exhaustion.
The cultural festival is near, so she's been busier than usual...
But what do we do?!
We can't prepare for the festival without Mana!
Allow me to help!
I'll work everyone in your school to the bone in Mana's stead!
Dokidoki Precure:
Mana's Out of Commission!
The Hurricane of a Cultural Festival
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!