I haven't been the same...
ever since the day I met that guy who calls himself a god.
I guess that even without
my body, I can still touch things.
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Iki-san.
Iki-san!
Iki Hiyori-san!
Yes?!
Huh? Was I asleep?
Iki-san.
If you're still not feeling well,
you should go to the nurse's office.
No, I'm fine. Sorry I dozed off.
Snow-like
Chapter
We're doing 800 meters today!
No way!
I'm so sleepy.
I've been like this ever since that accident.
But there's more to it
than just feeling drowsy.
They say it's gonna snow today.
Snow.
What? Snow?
S-Snow.
Let's go, Hiyori.
You're gonna be late.
Oh, right.
No one else can see it.
A being that exists beyond human perception...
A Phantom.
Snow...
Why'd I have to gain the ability to see them?
Hiyori.
Hey, Hiyori!
Oh, again?
Man, when did she learn how to fall asleep at a moment's notice?
A closet martial arts nerd and a
performance artist still in school?
Talk about having a bunch on your plate.
You know, maybe we should pick out some underwear for her next time.
Yeah, something that
she'd be fine showing to anyone.
Something bland, huh?
No, it could be cute!
Boy, this is tough.
Still...
This is fun in its own way!
I'm a bird!
A flipping, flapping bird!
There are Phantoms everywhere.
Lurking in the shadows.
Soaring through the sky.
Resting on people's shoulders.
They come in all shapes and sizes,
but they're all denizens of
the Far Shore, devoid of life.
The only ones who can see them are young children, animals...
and...
those like us that exist between the Near and Far Shores.
A black haze...
So that's a "Storm"?
A dark aura that Phantoms are attracted to...
It makes me feel uneasy.
Yato-san said that when someone's possessed,
they become gloomy and lose control of themselves.
Wait...
Speaking of Yato-san, why hasn't
he contacted me in, like, forever?!
Oh, if it isn't Iki Hiyori-san.
What can I do for ya?
Don't give me that!
You promised you'd make me human again!
Yato. I'll solve any trouble at all!
I know, I know.
I'll get to it eventually.
Yato. I'll solve any trouble at all!
And when exactly is "eventually"?!
It's been two weeks now!
Well, some stuff came up!
Stuff I gotta deal with first!
I can't help you at the moment.
Are you sure you're a god?
How rude!
I'm the real deal!
Could any human do this?!
You should treat me with awe and wonder!
If anything, you seem pretty suspect...
with those sweats and that weird bib you've got on.
"Don't judge a book by its cover!"
Didn't your parents ever teach you that?
And this is my fluffy-wuffy scarf!
Fluffy... wuffy?
Look. That girl's mumbling to herself.
She must have been through something traumatizing.
So, how are you any different from Phantoms?
Huh?
I mean, you're invisible to most people, right?
Phantoms are the exact same way.
Technically, I'm from the Far Shore.
I don't really have parents.
I'm a god of war, born from a wish.
Huh?
If anything, I'd say you're more like a Phantom now.
Not again!
When did that happen?!
Looks like you dropped something!
You think this is funny?!
But seriously, you're really exposed as you are now.
Be careful.
As a living Phantom, you'll really stand out.
They'll come for you.
They'll come to corrupt and consume your soul.
And once you're possessed by a Phantom, you'll lose who you are.
You won't hesitate to cross lines
that should never be crossed.
For what you'll find beyond is the pleasure...
of a living hell.
In that case, just fix me already.
Yeah, I know!
We made a contract!
You paid your five yen in advance!
You're not getting it back!
I'm gonna save up tons of money and build a big shrine!
By the station!
I'll get a wife!
My very own bath and toilet!
All in my own personal shrine!
Yato-sama!
Am I massaging your right leg to your liking?
What about your left leg?
Mm! It's most enjoyable!
I am an almighty god!
Now, go pick the peanuts out of some mixed nuts and bring them to me!
Here you are, Yato-sama!
I like it... I like it!
So, when will you do my job?
Huh? Geez, get off my back.
I already said that you don't have to worry.
You've been saying that since last week, Yato-san!
Huh? Really?
Then say, "Yato-sama!" ten times in a row instead of "Yato-san!"
Say it without messing up
and I'll consider doing your job.
Besides, who seriously uses "-san" when addressing a god anyway?
"Yato" it is, then.
A-Anyways, I'm not exactly in top form right now.
I can't go all out!
Not until I find a Regalia.
Wait, what's a Regalia?
Regalia serve as weapons for gods.
With a Regalia, I can cut down anything.
Oh, so that's why you're completely useless right now!
You used to have one, though, right?
Did you lose it?
Huh?
No, she quit—
I fired her!
Regalia are people?
Yeah, they're spirits.
Spirits...
Hello! Fast, affordable, and reliable!
Delivery God Yato, at your service!
You need help?
I'll be right there!
Huh? Wai—
Come on!
Sheesh, that guy...
I'm just waitin' on my big break!
Youths Who Refuse To Work!
I'll get a job if my parents keel over.
Look, Hiyori. Those are what you call "deadbeats."
Youths Who Refuse To Work!
They're scary-wary, aren't they?
Yeah!
Mother, he's one of those deadbeats that you told me to never associate with, right?
But it's not like I have anyone else to turn to.
What should I do?
Pave your own fate with your fists!
My lord! The great Tono!
Yeah! I can't rely on others for everything!
I gotta take matters into my own hands!
That's it!
I'll find him a Regalia myself!
Excuse me!
Would you like to be the Regalia for a guy named Yato?
Umm, excuse me!
A Storm...
There are lots of spirits there!
I bet at least one will hear me out!
NORAGAMI
Wow. Toilet paper, huh?
Yep. If you stick it on the wall,
you can get rid of all the mold
without having it drip everywhere.
I'd leave it for half a day before rinsing it off,
just to make sure it's really sanitized.
Wow, you're a pro, all right!
Pro?
Seein' as you rushed right over at this hour,
maybe I'll ask for your help again sometime!
Yes! Please do!
Well, I'll leave it to you!
Oh, do you happen to have
an old toothbrush I could use?
Huh?
The mold's particularly thick around here.
Thanks a bunch, kid!
Not only did you fix the leaky faucet,
you cleaned everything else, too!
My pleasure!
I feel bad payin' just five yen!
Here! Consider it a tip!
I'm supposed to be a god of war.
Why am I replacing rubber seals and
cleaning out mold for chump change?
Well, it's not so bad!
At least I got a drink out of it!
Guess I'll just crash here at ol' Tenjin's place.
Looks like business is boomin'!
"Going in's easy as can be.
Leaving is what will scare thee."
Yeah!
It's pretty stormy tonight.
Oh, come to think of it, what am I gonna do about her job request?
Ugh...
Iki Hiyori
It's her.
So annoying.
Yeah?
How can I help you?
Oh, sorry to bother you this late!
Um...
I've found a R-Regalia for you, actually.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Wh-What do you think of him?
'Lia...
Reg...a...lia...
Run for it!
Regalia, my ass!
B-But you said Regalia are spirits!
That's an ordinary ol' Phantom!
A twisted ball of emotions and curses!
Isn't it obvious?!
Yes! I thought so too at first, actually!
Smells nice!
But you told me not to judge a book by its cover!
Nice smell!
So you're actually listening to what I say now?!
Well, thanks! You shouldn't have bothered!
O-Oh, by the way...
I just lost my body!
That, you should have bothered with!
Hiyori!
O-Oh, yeah!
I forgot that I can actually fight pretty well in this form!
We'll be fine!
I can handle this thing myself!
Come and get me!
Now!
Jungle... Sava...
Run!
Your hand... It's not looking so good.
Are you o—
I'm fine.
Don't touch me.
It'll blight you, too.
Blight?
It's a kind of defilement.
One that spreads.
And unless you exorcise or cleanse it, it'll stay there and eat away at you.
Smells nice!
Also, about your rear-end...
Huh?
That ain't a tail.
It's a lifeline that connects
your physical and ethereal forms.
If that gets cut off...
you'll die!
No way!
You mean I'm not wireless?!
That's your issue?!
Listen!
You're not cut out for fighting to begin with!
Don't try anything like that again!
But you can't do anything all by yourself, right?!
Get off my case!
I've been trying to find one!
My own Regali—
A boy...
Just a kid... A teenager, specifically.
A difficult age...
Smells nice.
Yato!
He'll do!
Huh?!
Smells nice!
You, with nowhere to go
and nowhere to return...
I grant you a place to belong.
My name is Yato.
You shall remain here, bearing a posthumous name.
With this name, I make thee my servant.
With this name and its alternate,
I use my life to make thee a Regalia!
Thou art Yuki!
As Regalia, Setsu!
Come,
Sekki!
A sword?!
Yato!
Ya...
Thou who dares desecrate...
this land of the rising sun!
With my advent, I, the Yato god...
lay waste with Sekki...
and expel thy vast defilement!
Rend!
That's so...
Was he crying just now?
I brought my body back!
What are you doing?
Cleansing the blight.
Water healed it?!
I got something out of this, at least.
We got lucky, running into an uncorrupted spirit.
The blade's length is perfect, too.
Wow, so this is a Regalia!
It looks nice!
It's not so much a sword as it is a naked blade.
The name's Yuki.
Less formally, Yukine.
Huh?
What?
What's...
I-It turned into a person!
Yukine.
I'm Yato, your master.
I've summoned you from the
Far Shore to serve as my Regalia.
I permit you to serve and remain by my side longer than kin.
Put this on.
You've nothing to fear anymore.
No way. That thing reeks of sweat.
Oh, in that case, take this.
It's cold.
Is there anywhere we can get indoors?
Hey.
You hear what I just said?
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
You should put on my fluffy-wuffy scarf if you're cold, Hiyori.
Oh, thank you!
But I'm okay.
On the next Noragami: "Bidden Calamity."
Uh... Well, I insist...
Next Episode
Bidden Calamity
No.