Kiritsugu...
This isn't a dream, is it?
You really...
came to...
see me again.
Yes, I did.
Thank you.
It's time for me
to return this to you.
It's Avalon.
From now on, you'll need its
power more than I will.
I'm sure it will help you
during your final battle.
I really am happy, you know.
I loved...
I was loved.
I had a husband and daughter
for nine whole years.
It was all thanks to you.
All the happiness of this world.
Joy that was never meant for me.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to show you more of the world.
No, it's all right.
If there is any happiness I am leaving behind,
save it for Ilya.
For your daughter...
For our beloved Ilya.
One day, bring her to this country.
Show her all the things
I was never able to see.
The cherry blossoms.
The summer clouds...
I will.
Then, I need to go.
I know.
Be careful.
My love.
Saber's already gone to find Rider, hasn't she?
Yes, she has.
Then I'll eliminate Tohsaka Tokiomi.
If Saber and Rider fight,
Archer will almost certainly show up.
That's when I'll strike.
You stay here with Iri.
Understood.
Um, Kiritsugu...
It has been a long time...
But you finally look like your old self.
I don't sense a Servant.
There's no barrier.
What is this?
Is that any good?
No, it's terrible.
Probably the worst of Japanese cuisine.
You know where we are, don't you?
This is where I summoned you.
You should be
more suited to this location
than any other in Fuyuki.
Hence, you should recover that much faster.
I'm going to stay here all day,
doing nothing but sleeping.
Take as much mana from me as you need,
as long as I don't die.
That should help you recover.
You should have said something earlier,
when you noticed.
Realizing you've been found out
after the fact is, well...
It's embarrassing.
Idiot!
You should have spoken up first...
If I need you, and you can't
fight at full strength,
I'm the one who'll be in trouble!
Why didn't you tell me?
I thought I'd be able to
tough it out a bit longer.
That battle on the river was more
taxing than I'd expected.
In other words,
your final attack requires
massive amounts of mana.
I didn't really notice at first.
When I suffered no ill effects,
I assumed your Noble Phantasm
was merely efficient.
Rider...
You've been expending your own mana,
rather than drawing on mine, right?
And you've done it twice now.
Yeah, well...
If I draw mana from you when I go all out,
I could end up endangering your life.
That's fine.
I started this fight.
If I'm to shed blood and make sacrifices,
then not winning would be meaningless.
I just want to prove it.
Prove that I...
That even I
can accomplish something so grand.
However, boy,
that's only if the Holy Grail really exists.
I, too, once waged a war
for something that may or
may not have existed.
Oceanus.
Correct.
I promised them I'd show them Oceanus.
And they believed me, and happily followed me.
Many died,
spending their last moments
still dreaming of seeing Oceanus.
When I got my hands on this era's knowledge,
it really hit me.
To think the world was round and closed.
What a cruel joke.
But after seeing that map, I had to accept it.
I...
I don't want anyone else to die chasing fantasies.
If the Grail's existence were certain,
I'd admire your determination to risk your life.
Unfortunately, it isn't.
Even still...
Even still, I...
I am your Master!
Boy!
You've gained confidence, haven't you?
I must say, your Magic Circuits do
seem stronger than normal.
I think a good day's rest will supply
enough energy to act tonight!
And?
To act?
What do you plan to do?
Let me think...
Tonight, I'll begin with Saber.
At this rate, how much do you think
you can recover before then?
Well, if I only use the Gordius Wheel
for flight, it shouldn't be a problem.
However, I believe I have but one
further use of Ionioi Hetairoi in me.
Oh...
I think we should save it for Archer.
Then, Rider...
Why do you want to go after Saber?
Saber...
I must defeat her.
It's my responsibility as a Heroic Spirit.
What are you talking about?
If I can't beat some sense into that foolish girl,
she'll follow the wrong path forever.
That would be too sad.
Well, do what you want.
I am the shunned.
The mocked.
The despised.
Who are you?!
None sing praises to my name.
None envy my form.
I am the shadow, cast by the light of heroes.
I am the darkness, born in the shadow of legend.
And so, I hate.
And so, I resent.
I feed on the cries of those
who drown in darkness.
And curse those who are bathed in light.
You are...
the offering!
No amount of healing will help.
I'm going to die soon.
Damn it...
What a pathetic sight you make, Kariya.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I don't blame you.
Honestly, I never would have thought
that you would last this long.
Therefore,
I have decided to give you a
most valuable trump card,
one I've kept, for just this stage.
Here...
Appears to be working already.
That worm you just swallowed
was the first to drink of Sakura's chastity.
How is it, Kariya?
An entire year's worth of a girl's vitality.
It's a top-shelf mana source.
Keep fighting, Kariya.
Burn through every bit of the life
you've taken from Sakura.
Relinquish your flesh, blood, and bone,
and claim the Holy Grail.
If you even can, that is.
Maiya-san...
Why do you fight for Kiritsugu?
It's all I have.
I cannot remember my family,
or even my name.
The name Hisau Maiya
was simply the alias on the first
passport Kiritsugu forged for me.
All I remember
is that it was a poor country.
Even without the funds
to maintain their military,
the fighting never ceased.
People killed one another, every day.
And finally, someone realized
that instead of recruiting and training soldiers,
it would be cheaper and faster to kidnap
children and teach them to use guns.
Maiya-san, you...
Point at the enemy, and pull the trigger.
That's all that remained.
I left everything else behind.
Anything human within me is dead.
The outer body keeps working,
still remembering what it learned.
That is my life.
Kiritsugu picked me up, off the ground, anyway.
He's free to use my life as he sees fit.
That is why
I am here.
Actually, Madam...
Your passion took me by surprise.
You spent your life in the castle
where you were born,
never experiencing the outside world.
Regardless,
you fight so earnestly for Kiritsugu's wish,
to change a world you know little of.
I...
It's true.
There's no way I can fully comprehend
Kiritsugu's ideals.
It's just as you say.
I do not know this world that
Kiritsugu wants to change.
My ideals...
are only words
that I learned from Kiritsugu.
Don't let him know, though.
I've always told him he was
doing the right thing,
that his ideals were worth my life.
And so, I pretend to understand.
Then, Madam...
Do you have no wish of your own?
A wish?
No, I do.
I wish for Kiritsugu and Saber
to obtain the Holy Grail.
Is that the desire of the Einzberns,
to achieve the Third Magic?
No, what I want is an end to strife.
If Kiritsugu's wish comes true,
then all wars will end.
Including the fight for the
Grail, here in Fuyuki City.
I want this Fourth Grail War to be the last.
For your daughter?
If Kiritsugu and I fail...
Ilya will be next.
But that is the only fate for
an Einzbern homunculus.
I wish it to end with me.
If that can happen,
then Ilya can live her whole
life as a human being.
Maiya-san...
What will you do after
Kiritsugu's wish comes true?
I don't expect I'll live to see it.
Even if I do, I'll have no reason to exist.
The world Kiritsugu desires to
create will have no place for me.
No, that's not true at all.
You think so?
You have to find your
real name and your family.
Those are too important to forget.
You must make absolutely sure,
and then inscribe them in your mind.
I want you to live, Maiya-san.
For me, as well.
I'll do my best.
But that's all for after the war ends.
Right now, we must stay cautious.
He and I cannot afford to let our guards down.
Tohsaka Tokiomi is dead.
I must say, you're quite...
Maiya-san!
Iri!
By my Command Spell,
I order you, my puppet...
Saber, return to the storehouse immediately!
Kiritsugu?
This is...
Maiya!
Saber?
Don't speak.
Hurry.
Follow him, outside...
Rider took Madam...
But you'll...
I'm all right.
Kiritsugu will...
Please hurry.
Maiya, stay alive until Kiritsugu returns.
I swear to rescue Irisviel.
Could Rider really...
Rider...
Yes, I understand.
No, don't cry.
Save your tears for your wife...
You can't cry here.
You're soft.
You can't break down...
I...
This morning, you finally looked
like the old Kiritsugu.
You can't falter now.
Don't worry, Maiya.
Leave the rest to Saber.
Maiya, your job
is complete.
Maiya.
Maiya...
Episode 20
The Assassin Returns
Where is Irisviel?
Don't forget.
Tonight, at midnight.
Nothing can stop my progress!
Don't mock me, King of Conquerors!
It's all his fault!
If it weren't for him...
Oh, I'm so frightened.
Next Time:
Knight on a Two-Wheeled Steed
I'm satisfied, Kariya-kun.