Father…
Come.
Evangeline!
I’m not through yet. I’m just getting started…
THOUSAND MASTER!
Negi Springfield!
Yes!
Father… I… have graduated from the Magic Academy.
My studies are far from over…
I’ll… do my best.
I’ll try hard and be a mage like you.
So please, watch over me… father.
The son of that man…
…is quickly approaching.
I need... blood.
So it’s here…
Uweh?! A school teacher?!
Eh? It says here you’re being sent to Japan, Negi.
I’ve been there once before; it’s a wonderful place!
It’s impossible, I tell you, impossible!
Anya…
What makes these people think that Negi can be a middle school teacher?!
And an ALL-GIRL’S one at that!
Negi, talk to the headmaster right now and get your assignment changed to a different location!
That can’t be done, Anya.
But still! Nekane-san!
Negi? Are you nervous?
Um, yeah… a little…
Not “a little”! You’re probably scared out of your wits!
Japan’s waaaaay too far away! You know he’d be crying once he got there and wanna go back home!
Anya.
But it’s true…
Indeed, Japan is far. But Negi wants to be an advanced mage, doesn’t he?
If so, he has to try hard no matter what.
Onee-chan…
I will!
IMPOSSIBLE, I TELL YOU! IMPOSSIBLE!
Impossible, impossible, impossible, and once again, impossible, I tell you! Impossible! Simply impossible!
Oh Anya…
Japan… Mahora Academy…
Hey, Aniki! Are you okay?
Ch-Chamo-kun…
You’re chattering your teeth, aren’t ya?
It’s just as Anya said; you’ll get mocked by the gals! You gotta straighten up, yo! Straighten up!
…this ain’t good.
Hurry, hurry!
We gotta hurry!
Here we go!
Eh? Eh?
EEEEEEEEH?!
Mahora Academy! This is a school located in the city.
The school provides education from the elementary level all the way to the college level.
The population is well over 30,000 people.
The students' living environment is sufficient and hidden among nature and contains transportation facilities...
public temples, hospitals, an enormous shopping plaza and restaurants.
This place is without a doubt the campus of your dreams.
On a side note, everyone lives in a dorm from middle school and on.
Asuna! Hey, Asuna!
Geez, we’re gonna be late!
Five more minutes…
You said that five minutes ago.
Fine, give me ten…
Keep postponing it and we’ll be in trouble!
Yes?
Ojou-sama, I have come to pick you up.
Ah, Secchan! Come in!
Good morning.
Morning, Secchan.
At it again?
Yeah, she is…
At this rate, she shouldn’t have decided to be a newspaper deliverer…
True, but she’s a scholarship student.
15 more minutes…
Again?
Shall I wake her?
What do you plan on doing?
Let’s go. You’ll be late otherwise, Ojou-sama.
But shouldn’t we…?
Those who are dead cannot hold on to their possessions.
That’s not quite the right thing to say…
Gimme 20 minutes…
I’ll cut her.
Uh… we should get going now.
A-are you okay, Chamo-kun?
I thought I was gonna DIE out there, Aniki!
Goodness, Japan’s one hell of a scary place!
What’s this?
EEEEH?! Chamo-kun, is that your front tooth?!
It’s hanging on~
IT’S USELESS AFTER ALL!
Noo! It’s over for me! I’m a kid without my front tooth!
It’s like I’ll be smiling by the window and people will stop and stare and I’ll be just like a tangerine!
Chamo-kun, you’re not making any sense…
I’m a dead drunk and I’m being so lax about it! What should I do, Aniki?
Oh! I see!
Man, I shouldn’t have gone to Japan!
Alright!
Nnh? What are ya gonna do, Aniki?
Let’s see if I can try to restore your tooth!
You mean to say you’re gonna use magic?! Don’t do it!
If someone finds out that you’re a mage you’ll be in deep-
It’ll be fine. Everyone already went to school, and none’s around here. Oh! Yes, I found it!
Anikiiii…
Here it goes!
Yay! You did it! You’re the best, Aniki!
A-Aniki, we’re in trouble! We’ve been caught!
Um… did you see that just now?
Just now… did you see all of that?
Aniki! Her memory! Use your magic to erase your memory!
Oh, that’s right! Here it goes!
Asuna!
Thank goodness!
You’re here! Come on, let’s hurry and go to school!
…Asuna?
Seems like the only thing that’s awake is her body.
Oh man… come on, let’s go! You gotta get a grip on yourself, Asuna!
Looks like they left… What am I gonna do, Chamo-kun?
It’ll be okay! She looked like she was super knocked out!
Are you sure it’ll be okay?
You’ll be fine, you’ll be fine!
NOOOO PROBLEM!
No, Aniki! You’ll be fine, you’ll be fine!
What now? You’re crying already?
Wh-who the heck are you?!
Takamichi!
Been a while, hasn’t it, Negi-kun?
My, oh my. What a terrible little kid.
WTU!? CHALKBOARDS!!!
Asuna~~~
You were attacked?! By Dracula?!
Yeah, last night.
Isn’t it
fish sticks
tonight?
No way…
I can’t believe it!
It’s true, no lies!
Hmm… that’s a bit of an unbelievable story de gozaru.
That’s scary!
I don’t wanna wander around late at night anymore!
Chizu-nee, is there really such a thing as Dracula?
That’s up for you to decide, Natsumi.
I don’t understand…
Satsuki! I wonder where Dracula comes from!
Not sure…there’s legends from various countries…
If he’s from a country that eats meat buns, then he’s awesome!
So he’s a meat bun monster…
Oooh! So you’re a mage, too?
Takamichi has taught me some magic when I was a child.
Negi-kun, you haven’t changed one bit!
Yes I have! I graduated from the Magic Academy!
But you’re still a crybaby.
I’m just kidding. Just kidding.
Takamichi, you’re mean!
Well then, we should get you introduced to the other teachers.
Hey, Maki-chan, where were you attacked?
Along the road in the girls’ dorm area. I was jogging late last night.
Were you bitten?!
Yeah, take a look!
Does your body feel weird or anything?
Not really. I mean, she just sucked my blood.
“JUST”?!
How trivial.
There’s no way Dracula exists.
Yes he does! They exist, it’s true!
It was probably just in your dreams.
No it wasn’t! Look, see?! Bite marks!
Could’ve just been a bug or something.
Class Pres!
I’M SAFE!!!
One more important thing: work hard.
Yes, Takahata-sensei!
That wasn’t Dracula! It was a chupacabra!
Chupacabra…?
What’s that…?
A chupacabra is a blood-sucking creature. They supposedly originate in South America. Right, Nodoka?
Huh? I’m sorry… I don’t know much about it…
There we go.
Does it look something like this?
What the hell? That’s it?
You need to sweep up on the arrangements, but you’re on the right track. Can’t expect any less from Haruna.
I know, huh?!
Let me take a look!
Ew… that’s kind of…
How disgusting…
You think so? I think it’s cute.
Eh?! What makes you say that?!
Do those exist?!
Targeting young, defenseless girls won't slide past me! I, Kuu Laozi, will give them the blow of justice, aru!
Ooh, barely missed ya.
Kuu Fei-san! Karate is prohibited in the classrooms! It would be bad if someone was hit!
It's not karate, aru; it's Chinese Kenpo, aru. And I'm Kuu Laozi.
It doesn’t matter either way!
A blood-sucking creature, eh?
If I manage to get a picture of this, it’ll be a big scoop for our newspaper!
Good luck on it!
Thanks!... What? I thought I heard something…
Something’s not right about it!
Eh?! It’s wrong??
That’s it, I swear! That’s a chupacabra!
Asuna-san, get a grip. There’s no way such a dubious creature would exist in this academy!
Eh?! Yes they do! They exist, alright!
No they don’t! Moreover, do something about that outfit!
Your socks are on the wrong feet; your blouse buttons are incorrect; and that skirt! It’s reversed!
I see.
Ah, you’re right! I guess we took off so quickly that it wasn’t noticeable at first!
You’re right! That’s so mean!
That isn’t something to be laughing at! You’re in the 8th grade now; learn how to get a grip!
Lighten up, class pres!
That’s just how Asuna is; she’s cute that way, aru!
But still…Isn’t it great that you know now? Takahata-sensei won’t be able to see you with your clothes messed up now.
Oh, you!
You’re so in love with Takahata-sensei!
If he saw you in that, it’d have such an impact!
I guess…
Now Asuna-kun, you seem to be having fun.
Asuna!
Are…are you okay?
That little kid’s our teacher?!
No way!
The edge of
the eraser is~~
Reedy
Field is~
Yes way. As a substitute for Ootsuki-sensei, who is on maternity leave...
we have a new homeroom teacher for class 2-A: Negi Springfield-sensei. So…
WHOA!
DAZZLING!
Yes, sir!
Episode 24:
Gaasuu Festival
It’s was hot,
wasn't it?
The girl from this morning's staring at me! I guess she did see it. My magic, I mean...
HELLO----
---TO----
---KYO---
Thomas
McGregor
SHE DID SEE!! What am I gonna do…?!
I could’ve sworn I’ve seen him somewhere…but I can’t remember.
MY UNDIES!
I HAVE NO UNDIES!!
Are you okay, Negi-kun?
Y-Yes I am! Forgive me!
It’s a pleasure to meet all of you! I’m Negi Springfield!
Like the onion?
Re-cover
and be
Re-covered
Chukara
Along with being your homeroom teacher, I’m also teaching English. I’m just a novice, but it’s still a pleasure!
He’s cute…
Fukawa-kun
play some jokes
on the temple~~
Negi-sensei…
Is Hell!!
bow
rustle...
I-I’m terribly sorry everyone…please…quiet down, please!
Safety comes-
Caution: Items Above
In the Tokyo Government Office
they have JAM BREAD!
Girls, calm down!
Target Practice
1 Shot: 100 Yen
How can there
be a person
named Taitoru?
EVERYBODY SETTLE DOWN!
Eh!? A friendly
word?
Seepuroo
Thank you… Ayaka-kun
No, don’t thank me; it’s just expected since I’m the class president.
Negi-sensei, if there is anything you need to know, come to me, Yukihiro Ayaka and I will be at your service.
Wait up~~
Aaaah!
Yes. Thank you very much, Yukihiro-san.
Calling me by Yukihiro… please, just call me Ayaka, Negi-sensei.
Uh… um… okay.
Geez, what a shota.
Outline on Class President: Ascending blood pressure, trust, and is laughing more.
And judging by her body temperature… I’d say it’s love.
Ah, the fish koi, huh?
Things have gotten a little more interesting, haven’t they?
Interesting… white anko is also interesting.
35.0.
Well, then, let me take attendance first.
I’m scared!
Dammit, I can’t remember…
I’ll try to get all 31 of my students’ names memorized by tomorrow.
Asuna-san… she doesn’t seem to have leaked anything about my magic yet… I’ll have to go to her dorm and get it all cleared up.
This one… didn’t show up today?… Evangeline-san…
If you will.
Finally… the two of us will be able to escape this endless hell of ours.
That’s freakin’ hot! Owowow! You fool! It’s hot!
Thank you for the offering.
…That’s… not it.
Excuse me, principal!
If it’s just the two of us, you can call me “Grandpa.”
I guess you’re right! So anyway, did you call me? What did you need?
I have a favor to ask of you.
What favor?
NOW I REMEMBER!
Here, come in!
T-Thank you.
This is the girl’s dorm and all, but you can stay here until you can find a room of your own.
Yes.
Oh, I almost forgot! I need to serve some tea. I’ll go get some!
Konoka-san!
This chick is friendly, Aniki! You get to bunk with a girl!
That’s not good at all…
Konoka-san!
Ah! Aniki!
P-put her down!
I’ve waited for this day, Negi Springfield, son of the Thousand Master!
Exactly who is this woman vampire that speaks of his ancestors? What is her motive? We will find out when we meet again!
Next Episode
「No Way
you have to do this
for a provisional contract!?」
Asuna
Mahora Sentai
Baka Rangers
Mahora Sentai Baka Rangers!
I’m all pumped up! Baka Red!
Can’t let your guard down! Baka Black!
Jumping and flying across river docks! Baka Blue!
Before and after meals, take...! Baka Yellow!
Everyone gets along! Baka Pi-
To be
Continued!?