It was the first time...
The first time I was able to
tell someone how I truly felt.
You were the first, Hanayo-san.
Yuzuki...
Thank you...
Hanayo-san.
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
Ruu-chan, you'll be late if you don't leave for school now, won't you?
Oh no!
I'll do the rest of the dishes.
Thanks!
Morning, Ruu!
Morning, Tama.
Is it school time already?
You're such a sleepy-head, Tama.
S-Sorry, Yuzuki!
I'm leaving!
Good morning!
My, you're alone today? Where's Yuzuki-chan?
Huh? Oh, um, nothing...
Is Akira still missing?
Yeah. A girl from her school said so.
She hasn't gone home at all.
It's already been a week or so, right?
Ruu, the train's going to go! Ruu?!
Yuzuki...
Right, we're...
Let's not be friends anymore.
We're not friends anymore.
I won't battle anymore.
And Yuzuki won't stop battling until her wish comes true.
That's what we decided.
Yes... that's what we decided.
You serious?
Yeah, the Kurebayashis in second year...
You mean the twins?
I heard they're dating even though they're brother and sister!
Wait, isn't that ince—
No way!
Whoa, so the rumor is true?
Think they did it already?
Well, they do live together.
Damn...
It's not your fault, Honoka.
You really shouldn't worry about it.
And I thought he was cool...
Gross...
Did you spread it to everyone?
What's that supposed to mean?
It's your fault for doing something people would talk about.
A-All I said was that you were acting strange.
I just asked what everyone thought...
Honoka was worried about you, you know!
I felt sorry that you and Yuzuki-san were being misunderstood.
Say what you want about me, but I won't
forgive anyone who insults Yuzuki!
Y-You won't forgive me? That's awful!
You're the worst...
That's why everyone is saying
you two are getting it on and stuff.
Apologize to her!
You're a total loser.
It's your own fault anyway.
Aren't they brother and sister?
I told you it's crazy!
Now I feel bad thinking she was cute...
There you are.
Yuzuki.
I heard you told the others not to insult me.
Yeah...
That makes me happy. But you don't have to worry.
After all, it is true.
What do you mean by that?
I...
love you, Kazuki.
I've loved you ever since we were kids.
But I believed telling you that would make you hate me.
That's what I thought for the longest time.
Goto-kun in class two, I guess...?
He's not bad!
You really think so?
As I got older, all the girls
around me had boys they liked.
Hey, Yuzuki, how about you?
We all said who we liked,
so now it's your turn!
Who do you like?
I-I'm not really interested in boys...
Aww, you're lying!
It's true! There's totally no one I like.
You're lying!
No, it's really true!
Come on now!
But it's really true...
I couldn't tell anyone the truth.
Um, do you... do you know if...
if Kazuki-kun has a girl he likes?
H-He was saying he thinks that's kinda creepy.
And you know, when he watches romance shows on TV,
he says they're totally made-up and boring.
I lied to my friends.
I lied to you, the person I love.
But I thought it was better that way.
What? You're fine with how things are?
Yeah.
I'll still love Kazuki forever.
Even when he gets a girlfriend, marries, and has kids...
I'll keep this lie up as long as I live.
Even when I'm old and alone,
I'll love him until the day I die.
But on that day...
A card game?
It's pretty fun.
What's wrong?
Are you my Selector?
I'm Hanayo. Nice to meet you!
The card... talked?!
The card did what?
You can't hear her, Kazuki? This card just...
Don't bother.
Only Selectors can hear our voices.
S-Selector...?
My wish can come true?
Right. Whether you believe that or not is up to you.
You have a wish, right?
You've got nothing to lose. Go ahead and tell me.
I... love Kazu...
What?
I... love Kazuki.
Kazuki? You mean your brother?
I love Kazuki... I love Kazuki...
I love...
I love Kazuki! I love him... I love him...
I love him!
I know this isn't right...
I know it'll never be allowed!
But I want to be with him!
I want to be with Kazuki forever!
No... I want to be Kazuki's...
I want to be his girlfriend!
All right, let's make it happen.
We'll make that wish come true.
So your wish was...
I was really doing my best...
being straightforward.
Straightforward in my efforts.
Straightforward in being hurt.
Straightforward in hurting others.
It was the first time...
The first time I was able to
tell someone how I truly felt.
You were the first, Hanayo-san.
Yuzuki...
Thank you... Hanayo-san.
As long as I get to be with you,
I didn't care if I'd get hurt,
if the entire world were against me,
or if I'd lose everything else in the process.
I love you, Kazuki.
Kazuki?
He hasn't been back since lunch.
Thanks.
She's here...
Pretty creepy...
A wish...
A wish you want to make come true,
even if it means hurting yourself or hurting someone else.
Next time we meet, I'll be a new Yuzuki!
I'll be Kazuki's girlfriend!
A feeling as straightforward as hers can't be numbed.
I don't have a wish.
It can't be helped.
That's what we are about.
Me...
and you.
No...
I'm...
Ruu?
Are you lonely, Ruu?
Because Hitoe and Yuzuki
aren't your friends anymore?
But Tama is still your friend!
Battle...
Even if we don't battle... we'll always be friends!
Tama...
I really like having battles...
But I can stop!
Thanks, Tama.
Ruu!
Excuse me...
Hitoe?!
Hitoe, why are you...
Does that mean you remember me now?
Ruu!
Hitoe has a LRIG!
LRIG?
You're... a Selector, right?
Please battle me.
It can't be... You've become a Selector again?!
No...
No—why?
I'm sorry... I'm not battling anymore.
So you say, but you're still taking Tama with you.
Yuzuki?
Guess that can't be helped, though.
You guys are really close after all.
Yuzuki?!
That said, why not do a favor for a former friend of yours?
Where are you, Yuzuki?!
Yuzuki...
Long time no see! Well, not really, I guess.
You're... a LRIG?
This can't be real...
It can't... that can't be...
It's very much real.
That scrunchie!
Looks like the three of us have met again.
It feels pretty weird, though.
Yuzuki...
What happened?
Well, there's a lot to talk about,
but before that...
Battle Hitoe.
I can't! I can't do that!
It's for Hitoe's sake.
It's for Hitoe's wish, and for me.
My wish...
Please, Ruuko.
For Hitoe and you?
Okay.
Thank you.
Open!
Hitoe... Yuzuki...
Tama! Grow!
Okay!
Tell me, Yuzuki! What happened?!
I won my battle.
And my wish was approved.
Your final attack, and your final oath.
We'll say it together.
Now, let's say it together.
I accept...
I... accept!
the Laws of the Selector.
The Laws of the Selector.
And now!
A new Eternal Girl will be born!
Adamasphere!
No Entry
Then the Yuzuki now is...
Yuzuki...
Hanayo-san... became Yuzuki?
When a girl's wish is approved, she becomes an Eternal Girl
and gains the power to make wishes come true.
But...
the one granting the wish...
It's the drawing I made in pre-school.
I'm the princess.
The black scribble next to her...
You know who that is?
You were the prince in this drawing.
Because I wanted to be your bride.
But they told me that was a bad thing.
I tried to blot it out, again and again.
I painted it over as thoroughly as I could.
But it didn't work.
"Blot it out"...
I... I couldn't blot out my feelings, either.
I love you too.
I... I love you too, Yuzuki. I love you!
I've loved you for so long...
I know we're family. I knew it wouldn't be allowed.
I lied to myself all this time.
I tried not to notice my feelings!
But I don't care what happens anymore. I don't care what the others think!
I don't mind losing everything and leaving
everyone else behind as long as we're together!
I love you, Yuzuki! I love you! I love you!
I... love you too, Kazuki.
Finally.
The wish...
came true.
That... that can't be!
The LRIG... grants the wish?
You...
will become a LRIG.
The replaced Selector becomes another girl's LRIG.
Nice to meet you, Selector.
Only when you lead that girl to victory and once again change places
will you be able to return to the outside world.
So the wish does come true.
But the one who granted it wasn't me, the Selector,
but Hanayo-san, the LRIG.
That's the Eternal Girl.
That's...
the truth behind these battles.
That
Truth
is
Cruel
Once you give yourself to the shadow of the clockwork
tokeijikake no kage ni unadzuitara
darkness begins to encroach from the door of the end
owari no doa ga hiraki hajimaru yami
Menacing answers lie hiding in wait
ayaui kotae soko ni miekakureru
Today's wish will become tomorrow's taboo
kyou no inori wa ashita tabuu ni naru
Lost in a labyrinth where the world is turned upside-down
ten to chi wo utsusu sakasama no meiro
the gears slowly start to turn
mawaridashita haguruma
Quietly from within the waves of people
hitogomi no naka de mimi wo sumashitara
a bell rings out, beckoning my very being
tamashii wo maneku ano suzu no ne hibiku sora e
I have no choice but to walk the endless path
mugen no hate made wo susumu shika nai
for this is the future I willingly chose
jibun de eranda mirai dakara
In the wake of the unreachable summer clouds
todokanai natsugumo yureru kagerou
lies the place of smiles I'll one day reclaim
itsuka torimodosu egao no basho
Hanayo-san...
I don't know anything!
I don't know...
Hanayo-san... you're terrible!
I don't know!
Hanayo-san... thank you.
That emotion is stranded.
That
Emotion
is
Stranded