Have you stopped feeling guilty?
Fight!
Isn't Kushieda-senpai acting weird?
Yeah...
Well, she was already pretty weird...
But she's been spacing out a lot lately.
What am I doing?
That reminds me, the end of the year means end-of-the-year sales.
And then cleaning the house up and down.
Get all those places I normally can't get to...
From the corner of the closet, to underneath the tatami mats...
Making everything shiny, shiny!
No, no.
That's not what it's about, it's Christmas time. Christmas!
I'm so excited.
I need to be a good girl.
Since he's probably approaching Japan now.
Who is?
Santa, of course! Santa Claus!
Give me that! I'll hold it for you.
Are you okay?
I hope he comes this year too!
What's wrong?
I love Christmas!
I get that you like it.
But why do you like it so much?
Do you need a reason to like Christmas?
The decorations all over town...
Everyone is smiling and being happy...
Hey, don't eat that before dinner!
I know, that's why I'm only having one.
No, you don't.
We're celebrating the end of your suspension tonight.
The yellowtail for the hot pot is a free-range fish.
And frankly, it was pretty expensive.
Even if you're just pretending, be as excited as the cost!
Yay, yay, we're having yellowtail hot pot!
One more time!
Lots of yellowtail! Alright!
And?
While I was suspended...
Did you and Minorin get any closer?
Nothing happened?
Just when the pesky bug that was in your way was gone too.
What were you thinking?
What do you want me to do? If you're not there, Kushieda doesn't meet up with me in the morning.
And she eats lunch with the other girls.
And after school, she always has softball...
Waiting around like that, what are you? The faithful dog just waiting for its master to come home?
Do you think if you said nothing and waited, Minorin is just going to walk up to you and ask you out?
You dull, stupid, mongrel, idiot Ryuji.
Is what I'd like to say.
You've already said it.
Well, if nothing happened, then nothing happened.
I've got it!
I'll do something about it.
The angelic Taiga-sama, who transformed into an angel of love for Christmas...
Says she's going to do something about it.
You're sick.
Say whatever you want.
Right now, I'm like a living Buddha.
Now you're a Buddha?
Weren't you an angel?
I'm an angel, an angel.
For everyone's happiness and a happy Christmas...
Angel Taiga-sama is ready to do anything, even getting naked.
Leave it to me!
What do you think?
I really look like an angel, no?
You don't.
And the crumbs are falling on your head.
Really?
Get them off, get them off!
She's here!
It's Taiga-san!
Taiga-san's come back to school!
Taiga-san, welcome back!
What's with you guys?
After watching that fight, we have become fans of Taiga-san!
The Aniki versus Tenori Taiga battle.
That was a victory for Taiga-san, right?
You threw the first and last punch...
To settle everything once and for all concerning Aniki's study abroad, right?
Silence!
The fight that day was very difficult.
A lot of things were going on and it was dangerous.
But!
The last one standing in the ring is the winner!
Meaning I, myself, am the winner!
Hey, don't play with these guys.
Let's go, Taiga.
The trembling tendons...
Of a stretched thigh...
What's going on?
Minorin!
I came back to school!
So quit that weird song and hug me!
Release me!
I'm human!
Minorin, I really, really wanted to see you!
Why weren't you where we usually meet up?
I overslept this morning, so I ran straight to school.
My thighs kept hitting each other.
Why am I here before you even though I was late?
Oh, that's because...
We got surrounded by a bunch of weirdos.
But anyway, Kushieda...
Shut up brat!
What did I just say?
Did I screw up the joke?
Am I guilty?
Oh, no! Sorry! Forget it!
What's up, Takasu?
Taiga! Long time no see.
How've you been?
Kushieda's broken again.
I really should have shaved my head.
Messing up like that...
Let me wear this for a while.
I don't see why a girl has to spend the best time of her high school life wearing a bald wig.
Aisaka!
W-What is it this time?
Morning, Aisaka!
K-Kitamura-kun, g-good m-mor—
Morning to you too, Takasu.
Why...?
Why?
Because it's morning!
No! That pose!
This?
This is...
My prostrate apology pose.
Apology?
Prostrate apology pose!
Just sitting and apologizing isn't enough to express my feelings for Aisaka!
That's why instead, a prostrate apology!
Aisaka.
Yes!
Please, don't ever fight again.
Not for anyone.
If there's something you just can't forgive...
Whatever it is, please talk to me first.
And then I saw him!
I saw that assistant professor leaving a pachinko parlor!
That's really something.
He said he was late for a business meeting, but he was in a pachinko parlor?
Yes...
And then...
I texted one of my girlfriends.
I told her about what that assistant professor had done.
And I asked her what I should do.
I see.
And then she told me some shocking information.
I'm on the edge of my seat!
There's no such thing as an assistant professor these days!
They're called associate professors now.
That means he...
Lied about his job!
He hasn't contacted me at all since then!
What does he get by making our teacher cry?
That Kitamura...
Let's pretend that we didn't know it was Yuri-chan.
Yeah, you're right.
This has been brought to you by the God of Unrequited Love...
Kitamura Yusaku, "Your Love Support Group."
Our guest co-host today goes under the pseudonym, Y-chan.
God of Unrequited Love?
What's that?
After that great confession, Kitamura became obsessed with school love.
Or rather, he's become the best friend to anyone who has someone they want to confess to.
If you tell Kitamura, he'll take away everything bad...
Kind of like a "Legend of the God of Unrequited Love"?
That's so dumb.
Just how much does our school love legends?
Isn't this broadcast kinda annoying?
Why do we have to listen to him talk about studying for exams?
Isn't it called, "Your Love Support Group"?
Quit it. Taiga's listening.
She won't be able to hear the great Master Kitamura's generous broadcast.
Hey, Taiga, you okay? Can you hear it?
Huh? It's okay.
Taiga, you're kind of quiet today.
This is usually where you'd start tossing chairs and desks around, and Haruta would be dead meat.
You noticed?
That's right, I'm trying to be a good girl.
A good girl?
Since it's Christmas time, I've decided to be a good girl.
After all, Santa is watching.
What's that?
That's stupid.
I never thought I'd hear "Santa, Santa" coming from you...
It doesn't suit you at all!
Stupid Chihuahua! It's almost Christmas!
If you keep acting like that, Santa won't go to your house.
There's definitely something wrong with you.
Did something happen when you were suspended?
Or did you just find out you're going to die and you're trying to be nice?
Why do I have to die?
You two, stop fighting.
Thank you very much!
Well then...
After finals, it's what you've all been waiting for... Christmas!
I have an announcement from the Student Council.
On the 24th, Christmas Eve, after the closing ceremony...
We're going to have a party run by volunteers in the gym.
Couples of course, and you, yes you there, lost in love...
Who can't invite a certain someone!
On the very romantic night of Christmas Eve...
This is a chance to convey your feelings to that special someone and invite them.
Christmas?
Party?
Listen up, Ryuji.
This is a chance!
You have to invite Minorin to the Christmas Eve party.
Not "ehh"! You have to confess!
Confess?
There's no way I can do that.
You should.
It's Christmas Eve.
The day before the holy day of Christmas.
Angel Taiga-sama is a servant of love.
She's the grandchild of Christmas. The ideal good girl.
Santa's also watching.
I'll support you as Cupid, so that everything goes smoothly.
No thanks.
There, there...
Hey!
How do I look?
Don't I look like Cupid?
Well, like I said...
You don't.
You're late.
The good-looking-guys only party is over here.
Merry Christmas!
Look, look, Nanako!
A really cute boy is here.
I can't say I mind great looking guys like that.
You wonderful gentleman.
The party will be long.
If you like, please, partake some of this.
Huh?
Where are you going?
What?
You trying to say it's not any fun with me?
Even though I was waiting, hoping to do some fun things with you since it's Christmas!
Yes!
Let's do fun things!
Naked!
We're naked!
What?
Cuter?
Really sexy?
And a pretty Santa is better?
Are you... Talking about me?!
And that's what my dream was about.
Perverted jerk. That's the worst.
That's pretty bad, Haruta-kun.
Aren't I the worst off?
That aside, let's talk about the real party.
We need to decide on the helpers.
Taiga, why don't you do it?
You said you like Christmas.
Sounds good!
W-Well, if everyone says so, I guess I have no choice!
You do it too, you really sugar-slug-dog!
O-Okay.
Wait a minute.
What kind of dog is that?
Minorin, too!
Let's do it together!
Sorry.
This time, Minorin's going to pass.
Why?
I don't really feel like going to a Christmas party.
This is no time to be having fun.
What's wrong?
I really messed up in a softball game.
Because of that, we lost a game we should have won.
It was terrible to watch.
In a situation like this...
I don't think it's really right for me to go off and have fun at a party.
We have more games after New Year's, so I need to practice.
Minorin...
T-Then...
Putting aside the helper thing, at least go to the party...
I'm not going to the party either.
In that case, maybe I'll be a helper instead.
Ami-chan's going to do it?
Then me too!
Doesn't a party sound really fun?
Let's show them what 2-C can do.
What's that look for?
Not happy being stuck with me?
Let me tell you, Takasu-kun...
You should be nice to me.
Why?
I'm really good at things like this.
Livening it up, winding it down, dragging a certain depressed someone to it...
These are all things Ami-chan is good at.
Oh? What's wrong?
You decided to help out after all?
I'd welcome you at any time!
I said I can't.
Minorin!
Wait, Minorin!
Ryu-chan's going out?
With Taiga-chan?
Yeah.
Studying for finals.
At the usual family restaurant with Kitamura and the others.
There's a salmon hamburger in the frying pan.
Heat it up a little before eating it.
Yacchan is giza lonely degansu!
W-What's "giza gansu"?
Ryu-chan doesn't know?
It's really popular now.
A new girl at work told me about it.
"Young people talk like this degesu."
It's giza cute, right?
Yacchan is giza, giza smart!
Enough, enough...
That's so wrong.
It's not wrong.
This is giza fine degesu!
This is absolutely correct!
Inko-chan, I'm leaving Yasuko to you.
You're the only one left I can leave her to.
No way!
What a rebellious response!
What's wrong, Inko-chan?
Where did my honest and cute Inko-chan go?
I got it.
It's this book you borrowed, Ryu-chan.
I'm sorry, Inko-chan!
I was insensitive.
We would never have a whole chicken roast.
Never!
Really?
Yes, really!
Never?
Never!
What are you doing?
So...
Did you bring them?
Of course!
I put the prize from the cultural festival's Lucky Guy contest...
Nicknamed "Aniki's notes," in here.
As long as we have these, those tests are nothing to be scared about.
But...
These actually...
Belong to Kushieda too.
We won together.
What can you do? She said she's got to work tonight and can't study with us.
Don't get all stuck in the past like an old man.
It's not like I'm stuck-
Then move it!
Since we're going to study where Minorin's working...
Before everyone gets there, talk to her even if it's just for a little bit!
Yeah!
Kushieda is off today.
When you want to order, please press the button.
Hey, Ryuji.
Isn't Minorin avoiding you?
W-Why?
You haven't really talked to her at school.
I'm the one who invited her to study.
That's because you said, "Leave it to me!"
Then have you two talked at all?
N-No.
It looks like having to work was a lie.
And she says she won't come to the party on Christmas Eve.
That's because she's depressed over messing up in the game...
Isn't that where you come in?
But...
There's something weird.
I don't know how to support you anymore.
You and Minorin...
Something's changed.
Before, you two were more...
Hey!
Takasu and Taiga!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm starving!
Hey there!
Today is really cold.
You got to wear a down jacket! Down's the warmest!
Maruo, you need to get one.
Kihara?
It's rare to see you at a thing like this.
I wanted a copy of Aniki's notes too.
And I don't feel like studying when I'm by myself.
Let's all sit down already.
Okay, okay.
We're going to take this seat.
Hey, Taiga, stand up for a bit.
Haruta, sit over there.
Okay.
Kihara, sit next to Takasu.
Hey!
Go on.
And, I'm next to Haruta, so Kitamura, you're over there.
Hey, wait a sec!
I want to sit over there too.
Umm, wait...
Let the girls sit together.
Right, Taiga, let's do that?
Don't complain.
Is it really that bad to sit next to Taka-chan?
No, no, that's not it!
Okay, let's order!
Everyone wants the drink bar, right?
Okay!
There's no point in everyone going, so I'll get everyone's drinks.
I-I want something warm.
Okay, okay.
Then, Taiga, you go with him.
To the drink bar, the drink bar.
Since today was really cold...
What are you trying to do?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
Why are you trying to stick Taiga and Kitamura together?
You figured it out?
Oh, well.
I want you to help out too.
I think Taiga and Kitamura look good together.
Me too, me too.
Kitamura's been dumped by Aniki, and is heartbroken, right?
Don't you think a new love is the best medicine?
That may be so, but...
Taiga looks like she likes Kitamura.
It's a little subtle.
I bet you didn't even notice.
Anyone would be astonished. I was pretty surprised too.
Especially since you've been by Taiga's side looking after her this whole time.
Yeah, yeah, it's only natural to be surprised.
You're wrong...
About what?
N-Nothing.
He's not wrong.
Wow, wow!
Taiga, you're really into it!
But it's so pretty.
Taiga likes Kitamura.
I knew that for a long time, didn't I?
So...
Why am I...
Takasu-kun!
Hey, Takasu-kun!
I don't get it.
Hey! Hey!
What do you think?
Do you think Maruo and Taiga look good together?
Shouldn't they go out?
No, that's...
Asking me all of a sudden...
Right? You don't think so, right?
Everyone's been saying that. But it's not true, right?
Wait a sec.
"Everyone"?
You don't think it'd be interesting if Taiga and Maruo got together, right?
Everyone says it's because you're really nice and easygoing.
But, you actually like Taiga, right?
I'm going to support you!
Seriously.
You...
About Kitamura...
Hey, Kihara!
Hurry up.
I'm coming!
Takasu-kun!
Don't give up.
Hey!
I heard you!
I said I'm coming!
It's getting gigant confusing. Guns and roses...
It'll definitely be fun, because you'll cheer up.
So you'll definitely come to the party. Right, Kushieda?
It won't be like it was.
Yes, surely.
Probably.