Sir.
Mom.
Levi!
Eren?
Yeah.
What?
Or...
Eren.
Eren!
Hiyah!
Captain!
Oh, Mom.
Move out!
I'm here.
Damn you.
Dear god.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me!
I'm human!
I'm sorry.
And then...
I mean you.
Everything.
So you say.
Forgive me.
Look at him.
We can hope.
You alright?
That's nuts.
Wait, no...!
Captain Levi.
What is this?
That's right.
They're good.
Is he insane?
Armin's life.
Captain, wait!
Armin, what...
Nor should it.
One more time!
Mikasa's life.
Get up. Get up!
What true form?
Did we get him?
Two on the left.
Ugh. Disgusting.
I know she will.
What's going on?
Hey. Talk to us.
Human? Or Titan?
Spare me, please.
One on the right.
What do you mean?
Help me. Pleas...
and Armin Arlelt!
Answer carefully.
Killed by people.
I'm sorry. He's...
We're pulling out.
Stay on your toes.
Do you understand?
Is this it for me?
Everyone's life...
No, no. She's good.
Answer me, damn you!
Help me. It's so hot.
You're all gonna die.
She get hurt or what?
Hey, something wrong?
The hell is all this?
Our lives. Our dreams.
I'm really sorry, sir.
No. My sleeve. My arm.
What? Seriously? Where?
Uh oh. Easy, big stuff.
Was I... Was I helpful?
That's a face at peace.
all of us are monsters.
Look! It's Captain Levi!
This... This isn't real!
How has it come to this?
You're mine. All of you.
Wait. What about Mikasa?
I'd tell you if I could.
Loads of inner strength.
Under the circumstances,
They won't be persuaded.
This isn't the only way!
Am I really one of them?
I'm left with no choice.
Whenever you look at it,
But it is yours to make!
Are they terrified of me?
and that creature is you.
I refuse to die like this!
And what's with that look?
They're cadets now, right?
That was all just a dream!
Whoa. You're joking, right?
Some tough little bastards.
When push comes to shove...
Lo! The threshold of Titania!
I'll burst with tears of joy!
And tomorrow, because of you,
This I swear on my very life.
We were ready. We were ready.
We hit the books. We trained.
Well, that is, if we survive.
We can't get too comfortable.
Evasion will get you nowhere!
That's right, Commander Erwin!
Just wait 'til Captain Levi...
The Titans will be eradicated!
It's just like five years ago.
Okay. Somebody talk to me now.
I... I don't know what to say.
I... I can't stop the bleeding.
Damn you. Damn you all to hell!
Can you hear me? Say something!
Still just a barricade, though.
Why is no one making any sense?
"I must return to that cellar."
That scowl will crush your fans.
Mankind will destroy all of you!
Nobody's got time for a crybaby.
I'll kill every last one of you.
Oh god. Is that what they think?
let this thought flood over you:
Gorge while you can, you bastard.
See? Bet you barely felt a thing.
your strength won't die with you;
They're bearing down on the city.
They slapped us with a gag order.
Wh-What is that supposed to mean?
Are you a human being or a Titan?
Did... Did this make a difference?
Tell me this'll advance the cause.
Eren Jaeger. What exactly are you?
The journey will be a painful one.
military causalities were profound.
The pair on the left belongs to me.
Let's take it like a man, shall we?
the torch will be carried on by me.
Do you hear me? With my bare hands!
This isn't your world. Not anymore.
Basically, we got lucky. That's it.
That sounds terrible. I'm so sorry.
Won't they be at the Vanguard, too?
I'm sorry, sir! I don't understand!
Son of a bitch is playing innocent.
Please! Scores of us saw it happen!
I will not let the situation stand!
Mikasa! You can't take them all on!
Look at me. Eren, hey, can you move?
Word'll get out, and when it does...
Cadets Eren Jaeger, Mikasa Akermann,
Equal to a hundred soldiers, easily.
My life's not the only one at stake.
What the hell are they talking about?
Humanity's fate hangs in the balance!
Whoever comes at Eren, deals with me.
My men didn't die to pave our retreat!
I need to get home. Mom'll be worried.
Why has everything been taken from us?
Sir. My apologies. I completely agree.
Theirs is a solemn and dangerous honor.
Good. Tend to our comrade below, Petra.
There's a swarm of Titans moving north.
Why are all their blades pointed at us?
Those are meant for taking down Titans.
Hey, Jean! Where in the world's Mikasa?
Sir. There's something you should know.
That's not possible. It's just now I...
We've made great strides today, soldier.
And their friend's a certifiable genius.
They'll be fine. Not a doubt in my mind.
I wouldn't. Not while I'm standing here.
But, I mean I've always been one of you.
Armin! Head for the wall! I've got Eren!
Armin pleads for the life of his friend,
We knew how to beat them. How to survive.
Why are they all glaring at me like that?
Sir, please! This may be our best chance!
But however eloquent, however passionate,
Acting as a spearhead for human knowledge.
Captain! The reinforcements are here, sir!
You two, take out the Titan to your right.
They're terrified, but they'll understand!
Son of a bitch wants to eat us. You watch!
This is the proverbial line in the sand...
Don't try to stall with pretend ignorance!
And as you say, it's just a waste of time.
If we lost her, it'd be quite the tragedy.
We need to calm down and just talk it out!
The Titan assault on Trost left us reeling.
Something tells me this is going to be bad.
Listen, you've got to tell them everything!
There's not much else you can make of that.
I'm on pins and needles! We bag an Abnormal,
the regiment's survival rates have improved.
You damn well know that we can push further!
Let me kill you again! And again, and again!
You catch that? He said we're all gonna die.
They first appeared over a hundred years ago.
I know you probably can't help being hideous.
These things weren't a mystery to us anymore.
I want all you cadets on standby. Look sharp!
Any attempt to move from where you stand now,
Damn it! Why can't I remember how I got here?
Did you give those ugly bastards a thrashing?!
Did the man hear what I had to say? Any of it?
Don't know why I felt the need to bring it up.
I'll take on the entire regiment if I have to.
reason finds no hold in minds wracked by fear.
But I can't help being tired of looking at you.
The other's so stubborn it can drive you crazy.
It's like... Like they're looking at a monster.
My conscience will not falter to watch you die!
I wish there was more time to explain all this.
Please, sir. Don't tell me this was for nothing.
She made it in after us with the group Jean led.
I cannot waste any more time or manpower on you!
hinges on your being able to control this power!
Thanks to the ingenuity of its exemplary members,
Mark my words: the last ones standing will be us!
Whatever happens next, it's bound to happen here.
well, I 'm happy to demonstrate my own technique.
I don't give a damn what they try to throw at us.
One day, the truth will come out. I swear to you!
The survivors erected Walls Maria, Rose, and Sina;
They say he's like an entire brigade unto himself!
Believe me, they know what it takes to stay alive.
I think we've bagged the craziest abnormal already.
One day... One day you'll all just be a bad memory.
Yes, sir. Matter of fact I think he heard all of it.
They're nuts if they think people aren't gonna talk.
Giant, humanoid creatures with a taste for our blood.
On you. And every last inch of your traitorous flesh.
She was assigned to the elites fresh out of training.
Am I the only one here who doesn't think I'm a Titan?
Heads up! The main unit of the Scout Regiment is back!
I'll drive them all out! Kill them with my bare hands!
We'll expend far less artillery if he's in human form!
Unless anyone's feeling up to the task, in which case,
You are a risk I am well within my rights to eliminate!
As soldiers, they all know the price of their position.
Points for tryin', but you're a li'l slow on the uptake!
One of 'em's just about the best fighter I've ever seen.
I'm too weak to stand up, and if I say the wrong thing...
We were shoved to the brink
of extinction almost overnight.
For all we know, the wall's
already been reduced to rubble.
Every moment I squander mulling
over your supposed innocence
They're just scared. They don't
understand what's happening!
Can't you just envision the
horrors in store for us, comrades?
Whether or not a swift execution
is the result depends on you!
I'm just a little preoccupied
about my friends in the Vanguard.
The three of you have jointly
committed an act of high treason!
your being sanctioned by His
Majesty is neither here nor there.
If we hadn't found the gas, we'd
have never gotten out of Trost.
puts us all in further jeopardy
from attack by the Armored Titan!
Even if you took down a few,
there's nowhere left for you to run!
There was a messenger on the way
to HQ with this look on his face.
Owing at least in part to the
Scout Regiment's absence at the time,
So, you're saying everyone who
isn't here now didn't uh... you know.
Listen to me. It's vital that you
keep this key on you at all times.
When the ability confuses you,
let their memories act as your guide.
desperate to convince their comrades
Eren isn't the monster he seems.
If they're this committed to defiance
under threat of death, so be it.
The Scout Regiment's primary function
is to establish bases of expansion.
Is it true what they say about you
saving those kids five years ago, sir?
Don't be scared, big guy! I won't
hurt you. Cross my heart n' hope to die!
We volunteered to run supplies out to
everyone, but the situation was so bad.
You emerged from the carcass of a
fallen Titan in full view of your comrades!
It won't be pleasant, but in my heart,
I know what I'm doing is for the best.
I'm going to give you a little something
to make you forget for the time being.
Hell! For all I'm aware, you're a tactical
diversion precisely for that purpose!
Behave while I'm gone and I'll let you
in on what I've been doing in the cellar.
What was that he said about me coming
out of a Titan carcass in front of everyone?
The brute strength of these aberrations
trumped an average person's many times over.
A stark illustration of the disparity
between our own strength and that of the Titans.
anything I deem the least bit suspicious,
will be met with cannon fire. Do not test me.
You won't stand a chance! You'll be blown
to hell before you can assume your true form!
Ironically, they'd embarked on a reconnaissance
mission beyond the wall that very morning.
When the time comes though, know that you
must reclaim Wall Maria and head for the cellar.
withdrawing behind them in frightened huddles
for what was to be a century of uneasy peace.
We'd even found some gas we were gonna dole
out to you guys, but then everything went to hell.
A creature of unknown origin, ability, or allegiance
has slipped through and infiltrated Wall Rose,
Not that it's any of my business, but from a
public relations standpoint, you might wanna lighten up.
That said, excursions into long-relinquished territory
still commonly result in a death-toll exceeding 30%.
Kid. Difficult as it may be, you've got to wrangle
your mind to stay focused on what's here in front of us.
You gotta hand it to the Engineering Corps for puttin'
the heap of rancid Titan corpses to good use, I suppose.