Everyone hides their secrets within their hearts.
Somone said, to uncover those hidden secrets-
is just like opening a door that should never be opened.
However, the door that can't be opened has an aura of temptation-
which attracts people to try and open it no matter what the situation is.
This probably lead to that incident.
Second Lieutenant Felicia Heideman erased the records of this incident-
and she said she wanted to erase it from the Fortress's history.
But still, I want to record it.
No one can be sure that there isn't somebody else who will make the same mistake as ours.
I will make note of this shameful incident so as to teach those sheep a lesson.
It started yesterday, when Sister Yumina from the church of Seize paid us a visit.
A banquet.
Warfare inside the fortress
Oh. This is great.
I was planning to make some salads though.
The lunch is so splendid.
We also got those from the others.
The weather is hot. So we want to finish them before they go bad.
We have a lot of food. Yumina, how about having a meal with us?
Oh, really? May I...
You got surprised?
This is called "Brandy".
...what?
This is...wine, right?
This is Calvados, a brandy made from apples.
Please forgive me, my lord!
No... Don't... drinking wine is a sin.
We are still underage!
The church has a rule that people under 20 cannot drink!
Well... if she discovers that this is homemade brandy, it will be big trouble, right?
Indeed, so please keep it a secret from Yumina and Kana-chan.
y... ya... Kanata!
Lunch is ready, Rio-senpai!
Go... got it.
I have something to cleanup, so please have your lunch first, Kanata!
What is your answer!?
Yes ma'am!
Thanks for the lunch!
Eh? She saw it!?
I'm sorry.
Okay... I will deal with this.
Senpai...
Wh...whassup, Kanata?
You said over there that there's a door that can't be opened, right?
Ye... Yes! That door can't be opened.
...right? Kureha!
Eh? Ye... Yes!
But it was opened, right?
It... it's amazing... right!
What are you talking about?
Just now, Rio-senpai...
Hey Yumina-chan, how about having a taste of this tea?
I'd like to hear your opinion.
Itadakimasu.
It... it is great!
Indeed right? I learned a new method to make tea.
How about everybody try it?
It indeed tastes good and the scent is great.
But... this somehow...
It's great!
There's still a lot, how about having some more?
Another cup!
Okay.
Oh yeah, about the other side of the door...
Senpai, something is strange!
Is... is it?
Well... Kanata-san... Does it look like Rio-san is hiding something?
Yeah...
Keeping secrets is no good! Especially hiding them from your comrades!
Well... I know nothing...
Is this true?
Someone said there are an infinite number of spirits living in this land.
Can you swear to all these spirits that all you said is true?
Please!
If there are secrets and worries, I want to share them with you!
Please let me be your comrade!
Okay. I have a suggestion.
Let's have a war simulation in this afternoon's training.
If Kana-chan wins, I'll tell you everything.
Really!?
Are you serious!?
Of course!
It's fine for Kanata as she would find out eventually,
but if Yumina knows...
What if the church knows it!?
Well, please leave everything to me.
By the way everyone, how about one more cup?
Hey, why are you here!?
It's because I still owe Kanata a favour.
This is not for fun!
I know.
I pledge on 8 million spirits that-
I am not following you because I want to have a try at wearing the uniform!
TL Note: The kanji for "infinite number of / countless" and "8 million" are the same.
So... it's not "infinite" now?
It looks nice on you, Yumina-san!
Thank you!
Noël-chan, would you mind helping Kana-chan's team?
If you assign me, I will put my full strength in to the mission. Are you okay with that?
That's what I want.
So now, I'll explain the rules.
We'll use water guns during the training.
Since they were used in the Water Festival, there are dyes inside.
You'll get dyed if you are hit.
If that is the case, please leave the field. It that alright?
Yes ma'am.
Ye... Yes ma'am!
I have opened the door. If you want to know what is inside, please beat us.
So, start the battle!
Go! Don't get left behind!
Yes ma'am.
Rio, it's your command.
Gotcha.
"Gotcha"?
We'll infiltrate from the dorm's side.
Yes ma'am.
You two, wait.
I knew this would happen someday, so I prepared this!
This is...
Report: Enemy is located in the depository and is arming.
Got it.
Moving to a place where there's no way to retreat...
Are they trying to make a last-ditch attempt?
What shall we do now, Rio?
Check your weapons and ammo.
We will start attacking.
Kureha, you will be responsible for transporting ammo.
This is a tough task, I'm depending on you.
I am glad to.
Attack!
It might be sacrilegious enjoying war games so much,
But that was really exciting!
I always used to play this when I was little.
Oh really?!
When I was still young, I used to travel with my merchant father.
My mother passed away before I was aware.
I traveled all around the country with my father.
I've been to Vingt and even the countryside of Rome.
Wow. That's great!
But, since I was traveling around non-stop, I didn't make any friends.
Therefore, I am really happy now.
The spirits will definitely forgive you.
Right. The infinite spirits here are different from those in Rome, they are generous.
Eh?
Yumina-san!
Please... Please wait a minute... We are friends....
Lay down!
Geez, I missed...
But they are scattered. This is a good chance.
Great! Let's rush in!
They are coming, Noël-chan!
Got it.
Take them down in one blow.
Wh... Wh...
What's that?!
That's unfair!
That's right. I am not going to show you any mercy.
Have a good taste of the power of science!
Let's go!
Fallback for now!
Hold our formation!
Stop!
Don't let them go!
Ooooh!!!!
Senpai, we have to find a way out!
I would have never imagined that Noël would make something like that.
I'll attract their attention. You guys find a chance to escape.
That's nonsense!
How can I sacrifice my friend to continue living?!
Let me...
That's enough for me...
Felicia...
W-W-Well...
Excuse me...
Farewell... My dear...
Stop! Felicia!
Stop there. I won't let you pass!
I will not let you kill Rio and Kureha.
FELICIA!!!
Rio... Don't die...
How dare... How dare you do this to Felicia!
HOW DARE YOU!
How impudent!
Take this!
Take this! Take this!
Go to hell!
What's going on...?
Ah..
Eh?
We've run out of ammo.
Ah... There are still lots of thing I want to make...
Noël-chan!
Ah!
Yu... YUMINA-SAN!
It's regrettable... We've tried so hard to make them...
Hold on! I am calling the medic...
That's useless... I know it well...
How can it be...
Kanata-san... You have to win...
Please... win...
*dead*
Noël-chan.
Yumina-san.
I will inherit... all of your wishes.
Ah!
This is...
So you finally arrived.
Kanata!
I knew it'd come down to this one day.
The same goes for me, senpai.
At least, please tell me what this place is.
Hmph.
This is the distillation plant.
We are secretly producing wine here to get the capital we need.
For this...
You sacrificed Noël-chan and Yumina-san to conceal the secret?
That's right.
But you've been enjoying this as well.
Don't tell me that you've forgotten about that.
Your wages in cash.
The nice meals you've enjoyed.
All these come from this distillation plant!
Knowing that, can you still point your gun at me?
Yes!
Well...
You didn't ask me to join...
I am sorry about that, Kanata...
I thought you would make a good partner to us...
Same for me, Rio senpai!
You have grown much stronger, Kana...ta.
Senpai! Rio-senpai!
But... I am so glad... You were the one... who defeated me...
Rio senpai!
What's going on...
So, Calvados was added to the tea?
That's right. It was nice, wasn't it?
So... that's why we were so enthusiastic about that silly game.
I became more and more serious as I played.
Alcohol is really scary.
But, things are going along well.
Though, I didn't expect that Yumina-chan would be so weak against alcohol.
That's really lucky.
But please remember, Kana-chan, this is a secret.
Things will get out of control if it is revealed.
Yes ma'am!
That's really obedient.
That's because, I know you kept it secret from me so as not to get me involved.
And therefore, thank you very much!
But in this sense, I've become a true member of the Fortress.
Why don't call me?!
Yumina-san?!
You went to bath without calling me? I see it.
I know I am pure and stubborn...
She started drinking on her own?
Well, that's right... But this is a good chance, wanna try some, Kana-chan?
Eh?
This is also ritual to become a full member of the Fortress.
I see.
That's great!
But, Well, Platoon leader, I have a bad feeling...
It's fine.
Come on. Let's start!
But leader!
Thinking about it now, I should have figured it out from the start...
The normally supercilious Second Lieutenant Felicia Heideman...
Was too serious in that war game.
Right. Strange as it may seem, Felicia Heideman, the Second Lieutenant, is extremely weak against alcohol!
At that point, she was already drunk.
That's really delightful. Am I right, Rio?
And their behavior, later on...
Made me speechless...
I don't want to force myself!
But I am a senpai! I am a superior!
I have been trying my very best...
Nee-sama!!!!!
Ya ya. Senpai is really great!
Felicia...
Listen. There are 8 million gods...
That's really a lot!
But, they are totally useless!
As for me...
Unfortunately, I will not get drunk no matter how much I drink.
Well... Fine! Let me sing you a song!
Great!!!!!
So~ ra~ no~ woto hi~ bi~ ke~
Senpai!
That's cool, Rio!
In that frenzy...
I felt like I was being interrogated, being the only one awake.
Hey, Kureha-chan.
Let's take a bath together, once more~
I'm sorry but I have to refuse your invitation.
Eh? Let's have some close contact~
Hey everyone~
Great!
Then...
Hurray!
And then, till the end, the maidens who turned into ruffian put me into...
No... I can't write it out anymore...
The only good outcome of this incident is that Yumina forgot everything-
and the secret of the fortress can be kept undisclosed.
People who can never get drunk are unlucky.
They have the strongest feelings on the misfortunes that occur when everyone around them get drunk!
It's just hell!
So... I want to share a wise saying from the ancients with the reader:
If you drink don't get drunk.
If you're drunk, don't drink.
You can drink, but don't if you're drunk!
Suminoya Kureha