Within the ever-expanding universe...
Fumizuki Academy is a prep school with the goal of rallying its students to victory in exam battles.
One could consider it a breeding ground for
warriors who use test scores as their weapons.
With the dignity of their class at stake,
Imagination
these warriors do battle with the subjects they excel at
in order to capture the enemy classes' strategic forts.
Those who are capable shall be crowned as victors
and live an elegant and praise-worthy school life.
Those who are not shall fall into the pits of hell and live out a tragic tale.
This is a story about the exam warriors who dare to oppose their cruel fate.
And here one can discover the consequences of losing an Exam Summoning Battle.
They have student discounts,
but a ticket still costs 1000 yen...
A medium coke costs 300 yen...
A small popcorn costs 400 yen...
I'm going to spend that much in only two hours?
Movie theaters are horrible places!
Yoshii...
What is it, Himeji?
You must've waited for a long time...
Yes...
My First Love is at the Center of the World 2
You must've waited for a long time...
Yes...
My First Love is at the Center of the World 2
You must've waited for a long time...
Yes...
My First Love is at the Center of the World 2
Want to watch that?
That looks good.
Let's watch this, Aki.
Oh, really...
I'll pass. You two can watch it by yourselves.
Why?
Why!?
How about a cartoon, then?
That's not what I meant!
Resistance is futile, Akihisa.
Men are inferior creatures.
Yuuji?
Yuuji, what do you want to watch?
I just want to get this over with.
How about Apocalypse Hell: Director's Cut?
Hold on! That's over three hours long!
Twice.
That's longer than an entire day of classes!
It will make up for the time I can't see you at school.
I'm leaving.
I don't think so.
What the hell, Shouko!? What is tha- That's danger- Shou-!
Two student tickets for two runs.
Okay. One student ticket and one unconscious student ticket for two runs, correct?
What a nice couple!
I wish I had a guy like that...
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Fly! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Third Period
Food Expenses and Dates and Stun Guns
Akihisa Yoshii. His parents are currently working overseas.
His sister is also studying overseas.
Thus, he's been enjoying a life filled with freedom.
I guess I'll have...
a light breakfast! Gotta save the better stuff for dinner.
I'll have the smaller one for breakfast and the bigger one for dinner.
Every minute of it!
G'morning, Mr. Fukuhara.
Good morning.
Ow...
Aren't you Yoshii from class F?
Oh yeah, weren't you Kubo from class A?
That's me. I'm Toshimitsu Kubo, class rank 2.
Oh dear. I won't have a chance to review before class if I don't hurry up.
Review
Wee-wee
Daydream
Lecture
Soft
trash
Later.
Hey...
What's up?
You're not going to eat that, are you?
Uh, I guess not... I mean, it's been on the ground.
Sour
trash
Can I have it?
You don't mind eating that?
Not at all.
He wants to eat something that's been in my mouth...
Uh, thirty second rule...
Embarassing
trash
I don't know...
Why!?
You have problems, man!
People are watching...
Thick and stiff
trash
Yeah, you're right...
I'll talk to you later.
All right...
Damaged goods
trash
It's mine!
Crumpled
trash
Oh, I stepped on something.
Yeah, you just stepped on my lifeline...
G'morning, Himeji.
Good morning, Yoshii!
That's really a love letter for Yuuji, huh?
But Kirishima already claimed him...
You're here early, Akihisa.
How'd it go yesterday?
My food budget for the month disappeared into the abyss of the movie theater in the blink of an eye...
What about you?
When I regained consciousness, I saw a bound cow being slaughtered.
I wanted to take the chance to escape...
But I got shocked and lost consciousness again.
And when I woke up, the cow was there again...
Wow, you actually did watch it twice.
If I tried to run away, I'd get another shock...
The thought of waking up and seeing the cow getting killed again and again was so terrifying I shit my pants!
So I stopped trying to escape.
You'll never get to see the beginning of the movie.
Well, whatever. How am I supposed to subsist until I get my allowance?
Just sell your game collection.
Dude, what?
They're works of art! There's no substitute for them!
There's no way in hell I'd trade them for food!
Have you ever heard the phrase "you reap what you sow"?
Yeah, sure, you can say that. You've got plenty of cash.
It's a matter of life and death for me!
Akihisa, do you really think my life isn't in danger?
Sorry...
Don't worry.
I never thought our facilities could get even worse.
And it's all because of...
You! You bastard!
Damn, how bitchy can you get? We gave it all we had, right?
Except you're the one who lost!
What's your problem, Aki?
You're not one to be talking here.
Neither of us were any help at all.
I guess.
Yeah, mistress, Hideyoshi's sister beat the
crap out of you because you're too simple-
"Mistress"? Are you making fun of me?
Owowowowowow! You told me to call you that!
Just call me Minami!
Okay, Minami, you were too simple-minded, so-
Owowow! My head's gonna come off!
That attack is pretty bland.
But he was supposed to be the key part of our plan!
He couldn't even ace an elementary school level test!
You can't blame Sakamoto.
I like this classroom so much... there's no problem!
Yeah, she definitely has a crush on Yuuji...
Because you can sit anywhere you want in this class...
Ding! Dong! Ding! Dong!
Let's do this, people!
Sit down, everyon-
Oh, you're all seated.
Why are you here, Mr. Nishimura?
I'm here to help you guys improve your grades, since you're all retarded.
From now on, I, the detention master, will be taking Mr. Fukuhara's place as your homeroom teacher!
WHAT THE!?
And I'll be doing the narration from now on.
Ironman's gonna become our homeroom teacher!?
Get ready for some hardcore teaching, kiddos!
We're going to have to take supplemental
lessons from that demon literally every day.
Yeah.
I wonder if there's a way out of this.
Oh yeah! Why don't we just start another ESB and win it this time?
We can't.
Why?
The rules state that a class that has lost an ESB cannot declare another one for three months.
Three-
Don't worry, they'll fly by in no time.
I'll use this time to think up new strategies.
Why am I so unlucky!?
Every cloud has a silver lining.
One for 500 yen.
Yes! Holy shit! Hell yeah!
Be sure to stop by again.
What about your food budget?
What's got your goat?
Secret Photobook
Akihisa Yoshii
I'm a man of my word!
You're a hero.
I've decided that I'll only eat one cup of ramen a day until I receive next month's allowance!
Aren't you forgetting something?
There you are!
Hey, Aki! Where should we meet up this weekend?
Meet up?
Don't tell me you forgot about your promise to treat me to crepes!
Wait just a second... I thought we finished that up yesterday?
Yesterday is yesterday. A promise is a promise.
May I come along?
You too!?
Actually, there's a movie I want to watch with you...
My budget!
Hello, this is your new narrator. It's the weekend.
The ramen craftsman wakes up early.
Okay, that one's for dinner, and- damn!
Split it in half and eat one half...
Cut the other half in half and eat half of that...
If I just keep doing this...
One cup of ramen will last me for all eternity!
I think I'm a 21st century Einstein.
He's enjoying his life in more ways than one.
Still, though, I can't waste money...
Hang on! If you think about it...
Eating crepes and going to movies with girls...
Wouldn't you call that a date?
Yeah, that's what it is! It's not punishment at all!
Well, that completely justifies spending all this money!
Himeji!
That's...
I take that back. This is definitely a form of punishment.
Why are you just standing there, Aki?
I've fallen prey to life's absurdities.
Yoshii!
Morning, Mizuki.
You're looking cute today.
Thank you.
But I spent so much time picking this out that I was almost late...
Yeah, I couldn't figure out what to wear either.
I'm so lucky that this blouse from last year still fits!
In other words, your development has ceased...
And my knee joints are being forcefully twisted.
Ow! I didn't even say anything yet!
Scorpion
Hold!!
I know exactly what you had in mind!
Tap out!
A-a-almost...!
Why the hell are you here, Voyeur?
Voluntary training.
Yoshii, what do you want to watch?
You get to choose today.
Me?
Well, they all cost the same...
so I guess a longer one would mean more bang for my buck.
Yuuji, what do you want to watch?
Will my wish ever be granted?
We'll be watching War and Peace, theatrical edition.
Give me a break... That runs for seven hours, four minutes!
Twice.
There's no way in hell I can sit still for fourteen hours and eight minutes!
If you get bored, you can sleep on my shoulder.
Sleep!? More like a coma!
It doesn't matter as long as we're together.
No! No more!
Two student tickets for two runs.
Okay. One student ticket and another unconscious student ticket for two runs, correct?
I envy people who can be so upfront about their feelings!
I want to be like that...
I changed my mind. Let's go for a shorter movie.
You're not going to eat?
It's really good.
Well... I'm really picky, to be honest.
I don't really like crepes.
Dude,
Dude, yo
Dude, you're
Dude, you're w
Dude, you're willing
Dude, you're willing to
Dude, you're willing to eat
Dude, you're willing to eat bre
Dude, you're willing to eat bread
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that'
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that's be
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that's been ly
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that's been lying
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that's been lying on
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that's been lying on t
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that's been lying on the gro
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that's been lying on the groun
Dude, you're willing to eat bread that's been lying on the ground.
If I don't watch how much I spend, my budget's gonna...
Jus
Just te
Just tell th
Just tell them
Just tell them you'
Just tell them you've
Just tell them you've g
Just tell them you've go
Just tell them you've got
Just tell them you've got n
Just tell them you've got no ca
Just tell them you've got no cash.
Just tell them you've got no cash..
Just tell them you've got no cash...
Really?
I was planning on giving you a bit of my banana crepe since there's too much for me to eat.
W
Wha
What!?
I wanted to give you a bite of my strawberry crepe...
But you don't like crepes.
Yeah, that's too bad.
I'm such a moron! What the hell have I done!?
I
I to
I told
I told you
I told you...
Himeji was going to feed me with her mouth...
No
No s
No she
No she w
No she wasn
No she wasn't.
Starch
Calories contained in a crepe
(Not really)
Starch
Sugar
One bite would have more calories than my breakfast!
Oil
Amino Acid
Citric Acid
A girl's dream
The cause of obesity
Unknown
Want to try a bite?
It's really good.
Guess I don't have a choice.
Try mine too, Yoshii!
Me first!
I don't think it matters who's first.
Open wide!
You can't do that, Sissy!
This is terrible!
Sissy was going to give that fag part of the crepe that she had bitten off of!
How could I let her do that!?
You're not going any further, you disgusting pig!
Pig?
I'll wipe you from the face of the Earth!
Wait, me?
Move, move, move!
The crepes!
Thirty second rule...
Halt, you pig!
Hold it, Miharu!
Wait for me!
Yoshii, you've dirtied my face...
Why is everyone out to get me?
She's insane in the membrane!
Insane?
Sup, Akihisa.
What are you doing here?
This way, Hideyoshi!
What!?
You pig!
Where on earth did he go?
If he dares to taint my Sissy with his filth...
They're here.
I'll skin him and burn him alive!
Where the hell is he!?
Miharu
Why are you hiding from me?
She said she was going to burn me alive...
I'm not too sure what's going on here, but
I guess you guys are running from someone?
Yeah. There's gotta be some way to deal with her...
If only I could summon my Being...
The summoning system only works on school grounds.
Oh, right.
I've got some costumes.
Why not use them as a disguise?
Disguise?
Wait... They're not men's clothes?
They said it was for me.
So I thought it was for guys at first...
No one would ever give you men's clothes!
I think it's really kind of cute...
What's with this feeling of resignation?
This is such a pain in the ass!
Found you!
Be a good boy and-
Why are you dressed like that?
Don't ask! It's embarrassing!
Filthy! Impure!
Sissy isn't going to fall for you just
because you're dressed up like a girl!
No, you're the one who doesn't get it.
I'm straight.
How dare you try to defile the sacred
relationship between Sissy and me, you pig!?
You're going to get what's coming to you.
What the hell is this!?
I guess it had the opposite effect...
No, you did fine.
So what do we do now? She's still chasing!
We're going to have to split up!
But that means I'll be her only target!
I've got a good idea.
Let's go back to school!
School!?
Oh, I see!
There!
Mrs. Takeuchi teaches modern Japanese.
And I'm horrible at that!
We don't have time to be picky!
Mrs. Takeuchi, we want to have a trial summoning battle!
Oh, sure. Permitted!
All right! Summoning Being...
Summon!
Summoning Being...
Awful! Stop trying to interfere with my love!
Summon!
We've got this in the bag as long as we've got Himeji's Being!
We'll murder her!
I'm sorry, Shimizu!
No you won't!
Me!?
No way!
Those who were KIA, meet in the detention room.
But it's the weekend!
Even supplementary lessons from hell are like heaven if I'm with you.
I'm with you!
I don't wanna!
Have you finally come to grips with yourself, Yoshii?
You're getting the wrong idea!
Wow, I'm tired.
Me too... I hope Minami and Shimizu are all right.
Shimizu must be overjoyed.
I'm sorry about today.
I dragged you around without a second thought...
But it was a lot of fun...
Hey, don't be sorry.
I had a lot of fun too, Himeji.
You've always been nice, Yoshii, ever since we were in elementary school.
When I had to leave during the placement exam...
you stood up for me, telling the proctor that it wasn't fair for me to get a zero because of that.
But he just told me that it was important to take care of your health before an exam.
My argument got ignored.
You declared the ESB for my sake, right?
I heard about it from Sakamoto.
From Yuuji?
It made me really happy to hear that.
Really?
Himeji.
Yes?
Um... about that letter you were writing...
Is it really a...
You mean this?
This is a depressing letter.
Have you heard? If you don't send a letter like this out within three days,
you'll have bad luck.
I didn't have the courage to send it out... and three days passed.
I was all torn up over it...
Like you said, it's really a depressing letter.
Himeji...
If you don't mind, I can help you-
It's okay.
I know I'll be able to deliver it by myself one day!
I see.
One day.
Will you support me until then?
Of course. I wish you good luck.
Thank you very much!
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
Breakfast.
In any case, he's enjoying his life.
Huh? What's this?
Let's see...
Dear Yoshii,
Receiving a letter like this out of the blue must be quite a shock.
But I just had to tell you my feelings.
This is a...
love letter!
Whenever I see your smiling face,
my heart skips a beat. I've finally realized that I'm in love with you.
One day, I'll be able to tell you in person.
So please accept my feelings as a fellow man, my beloved Yoshii.
Wait... "as a fellow man"!?
It's from a guy!
Sup, Akihisa.
Who's that letter from?
Oh god! I lost my letter!
And I put my new glamor shot in it!
Oh well... I didn't sign it.
Uh oh...
I wish you the best, man.
NO!
It came with a glamor shot.
One day!
Question four:
What does "sugar and spice and everything nice" in the nursery rhyme refer to?
Curry rice!
Girls aren't food.
Next episode: Love and Spice and Boxed Lunches.
This will be on your test.