[BRIGGS SOLDIER 2]
Let's get him!
[screams]
[crash]
[FATHER]
Hmm?
[gasping]
[HOHENHEIM] I won't let
you devour any more people.
[AL]
Dad!
[HOHENHEIM] He was
hoping to use them
to create another
Philosopher's Stone.
[FATHER] What else
are all these pitiful,
powerless humans good for?
[HOHENHEIM] You insist
on treating humans
as a lower life form,
but don't you see?
Only through them can a
Philosopher's Stone be created,
and only through a Stone
can a Homunculus arise.
But what does a
Homunculus produce...?
What do you create?
[HOHENHEIM]
Creation is all,
and you've done
nothing but destroy.
[HOHENHEIM] You may
think you've reached
a perfect state of being...
but in truth,
all you've reached
is a dead end!
[FATHER]
I can create...
Shall I produce
some humans for you?
[anguished moans]
[gasp]
[KING XERXES] At last
I've found immortality...
Don't you see...?
I am... still alive.
[HOHENHEIM]
King Xerxes, is that you?!
[gasp]
[baby cries]
[GIRL 1]
A body...!
[BOY 1]
I have a body again!
[BOY 2]
Finally...
[AL] No...
No, stop this!
It isn't...
it isn't right!
[MAN 1]
Look...! Bodies!
[OLD MAN 1]
Hohenheim...
[HOHENHEIM]
This is wrong.
Damn you...!
[HOHENHEIM]
No!
[rumbling blast]
[CARLY] What is this?
What's happening?
[crashes]
[GREED]
Damn it!
[DARIUS]
Greed!
[GREED]
Gorius!
[DARIUS]
You all right?
[GREED] Perfect...
Now how 'bout a lift...
You could use
someone who knows
what's going on, right?
[DARIUS]
That's true...
What the hell is happening?
[GREED]
Oh, not much--
the Father of the Homunculi
is going berserk out there!
So let's go...
we'll need anyone
who can still fight.
You...!
The fat frog-man
and the two women...
Get down... You're injured.
[OLIVIER]
Absolutely not...!
I still have forces who
need me to lead them!
[GREED]
Forget that...!
Get down here now...!
This is no time for a pissing
contest over who's in charge.
[OLIVIER] I'm not
taking orders from--
[BLISS]
General!
[BLISS] A message
from headquarters, sir.
[OLIVIER]
Operations... it's me...
What's happening?
[CARLY] General.... it's
the Central Command Center...
Half of it's been blown up!
[ARMSTRONG]
Blown up?
[CARLY] We can't
contact the north gate.
[GREED] You see
the power he has?
[ARMSTRONG]
What sort of monster is he?!
[GREED] He appears
to be an ordinary man.
However... within him
is a Philosopher's Stone
powered by many
thousands of people...
You could say
he's used its energy
to claim the powers
of God for himself.
[GREED]
As alchemists,
you understand the
trouble this presents?
[ARMSTRONG]
All too well.
[GREED] Any ordinary
human should leave now.
[OLIVIER] My men
are still fighting...
I will not just
abandon my forces...
I have a duty as their
commanding officer.
[BLISS] General...
It's Headquarters again, sir.
[OLIVIER]
What is it?
[CARLY]
Don't worry about us, sir.
Have you forgotten
who we are...?
We Briggs soldiers are
trained to respond instantly
as one force to any
threat... even without you.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 4]
Yellow Squad, come in...
Are you still there?
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 5] East gate,
Blue Squad, report in!
What's your status?
[CARLY] From what I hear,
you've been injured, General...
Please... stay and
wait where you are.
[OLIVIER]
Listen up, Alex!
[ARMSTRONG]
Yes?
[OLIVIER]
Take the radio with you.
Win at any cost.
[ARMSTRONG]
Well, of course!
[ROY] Right...
let's move, Hawkeye.
[GREED] Hold on...
you two aren't in any
shape to fight, either.
[ROY] I am
going to burn up
that Philosopher's
Stone of his...
I'll need the lieutenant's
help in order to do so.
[DARIUS] Let it go...
Now... Let's move...
[LAN FAN] Right...
I'm coming too.
It is my job to
protect the young lord.
[SIG] Take care... and
keep them safe, friend.
[ARMSTRONG]
Brace yourselves...!
Now we continue
our rise to glory!
[OLIVIER] So this is
where you met your end...
And was it you
that killed him?
[SCAR]
When he arrived here...
he was already badly injured...
If it hadn't been for those
wounds, I might have lost.
[BLISS]
Captain Buccaneer...
He was working with
soldiers from Xing...
He inflicted a mortal
wound on Bradley.
[OLIVIER] Like I always
told you, Bradley...
Briggs men are as
tough as they come.
[MAY CHANG]
Oh, Shao May...
You're really all right...?
I'm so glad.
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse!
[AL] May... You're alive...
Are you hurt?
[MAY CHANG]
Never mind me, Alphonse...!
Your body!
[cracking, crumbling sounds]
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse, no!
You can't die...!
You shielded me!
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse...! Alphonse!
[ED]
Teacher!
Teacher...! Say something!
[IZUMI]
I'm alive...
Because of Mr. Hohenheim...
He got to me at
the last second.
[ED]
Hohenheim!
[ED] Hey...!
Snap out of it...!
Lets--
[ED]
Hohenheim!
[FATHER]
You're first...
[strangled cries]
[HOHENHEIM]
Stop it...!
Leave them alone!
[gasps]
[CARLY] Your target is the man
with the long blonde hair...
Make sure you don't
shoot Fullmetal by mistake!
[BRIGGS SOLDIERS]
Right!
[CARLY]
Blue squad, hurry!
White squad...
you cover the west wing.
[BRIGGS SOLDIERS]
Roger!
[ED]
Teacher!
[BRIGGS CAPTAIN]
Fire!
[blasts]
[crashes]
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 6]
Hey, Fullmetal... Are you okay?
[ED] It's bad...!
He didn't even flinch!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 6]
Seriously?!
[screams]
[CARLY] Don't give the
bastard a chance to hit back!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 7]
Yes, sir!
[gunshots]
[explosion]
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 5]
Damn...!
That bastard's not
even breaking a sweat!
[CARLY] Copy that...
Put me through.
[BRIGGS CAPTAIN] Right...
If you're sure, sir.
Take cover, men...! Now!
[explosion]
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[ROY]
So did I hit him?
[HAWKEYE] You were off
just a little bit...
Adjust it to
twelve o'clock.
[clap]
[ROY] I can't tell how
much to throttle the flames.
[HAWKEYE] You don't
have to throttle them...!
Range fifty....no, fifty-three.
This clapping transmutation
doesn't feel natural.
[explosion]
[HAWKEYE] Incoming attack,
Colonel, dead ahead!
[loud crash]
[HAWKEYE] Nicely done.
[ROY] I'll say... this
could turn out to be handy.
[BRIGGS CAPTAIN]
Fire now!
Keep firing!
[ARMSTRONG]
Don't give him any opportunity
to fight back...
Make him use his
Philosopher's Stone!
[crashes]
[explosion]
Rrrraaaagggh!!
[GREED] Hahaha! Amazing!
If I had power like that...
then this entire world
would be mine in no time!
[LING]
Hey, Greed.
You've always talked about
wanting the entire world,
but is this really
what you meant?
[GREED]
Oh, yes...
Once I have this
supreme power,
everything in the
world will be mine.
Who knows,
maybe it will fill the
emptiness inside me...
An achievement like that
could finally quench the
thirst that I've lived with
since the day I was born!
[LING]
How ignorant you are...
What you're seeking is
not what you truly want.
[GREED] Keep quiet
you little pest.
I am Greed
the Avaricious...!
I want everything!
[ROY]
Now he's toast.
[loud explosion]
[ARMSTRONG]
No effect at all.
[ARMSTRONG] We have to find
a way through his defenses.
[BRIGGS CAPTAIN]
Come in...!
We need more ammo.
[FATHER]
What a futile battle...
You poor, helpless
humans can't hope
to lay so much
as a finger on me.
[GREED]
Maybe humans aren't able...
But what about a Homunculus?
[GREED] Wonderful--you're
just in time, Greed...
What a dutiful
son you are...
As it happens, I could use
another Philosopher's Stone.
[FATHER]
I'll be taking yours.
[anguished screams]
Augggh!!
[GREED]
Good acting, right?
[GREED] You can't
take my Stone from me
without dropping
your own barrier...
Stupid fool...
I bet you never
thought your godly powers
could be taken away, did you?
[GREED]
But you were wrong...
They will be mine now!
[ED]
Greed!
[shattering sound]
[ED]
Don't give up now!
[HOHENHEIM]
His arm... not alchemy...
[FATHER]
Hurrrghh!
[HOHENHEIM]
He's losing control.
[HOHENHEIM] He can't
keep the power of God
he claims to have
in check anymore.
[FATHER]
Arrrrrgh!!! Auuugggh!!
[rumbling explosion]
[breathing heavily]
[FATHER]
A Stone...
A Stone!
A Philosopher's Stone!
[HOHENHEIM]
Edward! Get out! Now!
[AL] Brother!
Get out of here!
Brother!
[AL] Stop!
Damn it...! Stop!
[MAY CHANG]
Careful!
[AL] Stop this...!
Stop it!
[AL] My brother...
my brother... let him---
[gasp]
[AL] May,
I need a favor.
Back then, Ed was
willing to sacrifice
his right arm in order
to bring my soul back.
So... shouldn't the
reverse be possible?
[MAY CHANG] Alphonse,
what are you saying?
[AL] All you have
to do is clear a path.
Can you do that?
[MAY CHANG]
But if you do this,
do you know
what will happen?
[AL] There's no time...!
Please, May.
You're the only one...
It has to be you.
[FATHER]
A Stone...
You vile human...
Give it to me!
[HOHENHEIM]
No, Edward!
[FATHER]
Your energy!
[clinks]
[ED]
What are you doing?
No, don't...! Please!
Al!
[AL] Keep moving... brother.
[ED]
Al, noooooo!
[AL (human)]
Well... Are you ready?
[AL] Now we put
our faith in Brother.
[TRUTH] So... your soul
has entered you, huh?
But will he be
coming back for you?
[AL (human)]
He will... I'm sure of it.
[TRUTH] I can't wait to see
what he'll be sacrificing.
[ED]
Al, you dumbass!
[thud]
[ED]
Hrrrrgh!! Ahhh!
[crashes]
[ED]
Auuughh!
[FATHER]
Ahhhh!!!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 8]
It's working...
[ARMSTRONG] Nice, Ed...
Just keep going.
[ZAMPANO]
Go, kid!!
[DARIUS]
Elric!
[BRIGGS SOLDIERS]
Yeah!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 9]
Let him have it!
[HAWKEYE]
Kick his ass, Ed!
[IZUMI]
Go, Ed!
[ARMSTRONG]
Fight, Edward Elric!
[BRIGGS SOLDIERS]
Go!!
[LING]
Greed...
This is what
you desperately wanted...
...isn't it?
[MAY CHANG]
Please don't die!
[HOHENHEIM]
Go Edward!
[LAN FAN]
Fight on!
[ROY]
Fullmetal!
[GREED]
Yeah... you're right...
This is what I wanted.
[GREED] I wanted the chance
to have friends like these.
[thud]
[ED]
Get up, you novice!
[ED] I'm about to
show you how outclassed
you really are...
This fight you lose!
[NARRATOR] The immensity
of his power has effects
unknown even to him...
but he will
not hesitate...
not when he must protect the
people who he dearly loves.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood
Episode 63: "The Other
Side of the Gateway."
When he has seen
everything through...
he will move on.