AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga, Chandy10
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10, Kanra
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
Stay in bed, Scam.
You must still have a fever,
after that beating you took.
Mario...
Soldier left you this.
Says it's money to get your glasses fixed.
Apparently it's his farewell gift to you.
Listen...
Could you apologize to Turtle for me?
I said terrible things to him...
Don't you dare come back...
That's what Turtle said.
I wanna stay your friend forever,
so don't you dare come back.
We'll always be friends no
matter where we are, Scam.
Yeah...
I'm sorry, guys...
I have to run away with Eri...
I'll even run to the ends
of the earth if I have to!
Well, I'm off to work now, Mom...
Oh, are you helping
Maeda with work today?
Be careful on your way.
Yeah...
I'm sorry, Mom...
Red Crane
All right, looks like everyone's here.
Now let's go and get you checked up.
Listen, Ryu.
Do you know where Senso Temple is?
There's a tree there that
was burned in the war
and only it's base escaped the fire.
We'll meet there at 2:00.
I'll come, so wait for me, Ryu...
I'm way too early...
Oh, well.
Eri! You're next!
Hey, Eri!
Where's Eri?
--Eri?
--She isn't here?
That's strange. She was just here...
Don't tell me she..!
Waiting is part of the fun...
Besides, I read somewhere
that girls are always late.
Come on! Come quick!
I'm sorry I'm late..!
You're sure no one noticed you?
Yes...
Shoo!
Rain...
This isn't good...
I'm sorry, Turtle...
I said such terrible things to you...
Even so, Turtle...
I think of you as a friend, too...
It might be self-centered and
shameless of me, but I really do...
Soldier...
I know you didn't really sleep with Eri...
You tried to beat sense into
me out of honest concern for me...
But I'll be okay...
Eri's the one for me...
She and I are going to be happy together...
Listen, Ryu...
You need to become
a responsible grownup.
Let's meet at 2:00 next Tuesday,
inside Senso Temple.
Turtle...
Do you think... something
might've happened to her?
Tell me, Turtle...
You knew this would happen, didn't you?
You knew this would...
Scam... Let's go home.
H-Hey! Scam!
"Laugh at me, Turtle.
It can't be helped that
my plan backfired on me.
It's pathetic, but this is just who I am."
The pouring rain drenched
Scam's heart as well.
Hey, Mario! It's me! Open up!
Oh... So she never came?
The guy waited for hours in the rain.
Of course you'd get a fever doing that...
Hot!
That was a real shock, though.
Throwing his life away like that...
Yeah. He really put
everything on the line...
I thought Scam was better
now that his fever's passed,
but he still hasn't said a word...
I have to get to work.
Could you watch him for me?
Sure! You can count on me!
Hey, Scam! Rikidosan is gonna
be wrestling on TV tonight!
Let's watch on the TVs in town!
I'll go shopping for dinner, then.
I'm gonna make stew tonight.
I learned a really good recipe at the dojo!
University Student
and Prostitute Commit Suicide
Scam! I'm back!
The vegetables were cheap,
so I bought a lot--
Huh?
He's gone...
Where did he go? To the bathroom?
Red Crane
Come again!
We look forward to seeing you again!
It's you...
Didn't you read the papers?
Eri's not here anymore.
Why did she...?
Hell if I know! Damn selfish
of her too; she still owed a lot!
What'll happen to her younger sister, then?!
Huh?!
She was working so hard
to put her sister through school...
Ah! It sounds like that woman
had you completely fooled!
What nonsense!
That broad didn't have a family!
No, wait, there was one family member...
Her drug addict of a mother who
sold Eri to me and ran off with a man!
You should just forget
about her and get over it.
You should have some fun
while you're here anyway!
I'll find a nice girl for you!
I'll make it cheap, too!
The hell with you...
The hell with you, you asshole!
What would you know?!
All you can think about is money..!
Hold on, now! You're the one
who paid money to buy Eri!
That's right. I didn't get to know Eri either...
I didn't know a thing about her...
I don't want to admit it,
but I'm no different from you...
I'm a piece of shit, just like you!
"I don't resent the fact that
she didn't open up to me.
I don't feel sad because I
assumed we had loved each other."
What Scam felt was great pity for
Eri from the bottom of his heart.
"It's horrible for someone to live a
life where happiness can never be..."
That was the only thought
that filled Scam's mind.
"Eri... Eri...
I didn't want us to die together.
I wanted us to live together."
Scam's gone?!
I'm sorry. I was only gone for a short time...
Turtle and I are both looking for him now.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Right.
Nanen Apartments
Mario!
--You find him?
--No, no luck...
He hasn't gone back home, either...
Oh...
What do we do? I hope Scam
isn't thinking of doing anything bad...
Don't be stupid!
He's not the type to roll over and die that easily!
Turtle...
That's true.
We know about how tough
he is more than anyone else.
Let's have faith in Scam and wait.
Yeah...
Yeah, Nomoto's doing well.
"One month later"
I think he'll be finished with his work soon,
so don't worry, he'll be back.
Really?
Thank you for always being so kind.
Oh, no, I'm the one
who talked him into it...
S-Scam!
Ryuji...
Mom...
I'm sorry.
Ryuji...
Scam...
I took money that our family needed.
I worried Kazuo and Tatsuo as well.
I even lied to Turtle and my friends
to borrow money from them...
And I used that money to...
To...
It's almost time for us to have lunch.
I better get started on it!
Won't you join us too, Maeda?
Oh, s-sure!
Mom?
Welcome home, Ryuji.
Turtle!
Here...
I'm sorry. It's only a little part of it.
I sent Soldier's by mail.
Where were you all this time?
Working at a construction site in Yokohama.
I wanted to pay you guys
back as quickly as I could...
Wow, you did manual labor?
Don't be like that.
I actually worked really hard.
That's good!
All right! Time to call all the others!
We're drinking all night tonight at Mario's bar!
--You're paying, of course!
--Huh?!
We're gonna drink 'til we puke!
Hold on! I don't have any money left!
Don't be in such a rush!
There's a crapload of girls out there!
Even girls in junior high now will be
grown women in five or six years!
That's smart thinking, Soldier!
Look at this tree...
Even after it was burned in the war,
it still grows new buds...
It has amazing vitality...
That day, I waited
here like Eri told me to...
But she committed suicide
with another man.
Everything she told me was a fabrication.
My mind went completely blank after that,
and before I realized it,
I was standing here again.
Then I saw a small bud
coming out of this tree...
...and then I heard it.
Yes, I really heard it...
Eri's voice, saying, "Live!"
A new bud coming out
of the burned gingko tree
gave Scam the encouragement to live.
"That's right;
I can't let this discourage me.
Life is full of encounters and farewells."
Scam vowed, "Eri. I will live."
"Watch me too, Anchan and Dad.
I will live on, steadfastly and wisely."
same ta manazashi
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it; its now
a far off distance
Lilly sets out.
Just as Turtle has even
grander dreams for the future,
he's revisited by the nightmare from 13 years ago...