Elen.
What is it?
Nothing...
I wanted to see how you would react when I called you by that name.
You found him, didn't you?
Where is Scythe?
Yes. Thanks for picking me up, Colonel Roshenenko.
Not at all.
I'm actually honored that you've remembered me, Dr. Giuseppe.
When you call me by my name,
it makes me remember my days in Moscow.
Either way, I'm amazed that a sharp and able person like you has been cornered and is now on the run...
Was the fieldwork a tad different from the work in the laboratory?
"There's a tide in the affairs of men."
What?
It's from Shakespeare.
Their tide is also mine.
What I had to make here...
...has already been made.
There's been some suspicious movements by a small weapons dealer named Roshenenko.
It seems like he's Scythe's old friend,
and he's been around here in the Bay Area.
Scythe was seen heading there, too.
In other words, that snaky bastard is somewhere in San Francisco trying to escape.
Clau?
You...
Are you insane, Clau?!
Phantom pointed her gun at us and he helped her escape!
And you still expect me to take him with us?
Yes, exactly.
Sheesh! You're such a cunning woman.
The same goes for you.
I'll be the commander at the scene.
Scythe is headed to the Woodland pier in East Bay.
It seems that several of Roshenenko's men have been spotted there.
Understood.
Come with me.
Kill him without fail.
If you do...
I also regret that we couldn't secure Zwei.
But it couldn't be helped considering the situation we're in right now.
I'll leave Zwei to that vixen.
Master...
Why did you...
When did you start asking questions?
I'm deeply sorry.
What's the matter, comrade Roshenenko?
Oh...
They found it.
Yes, don't worry.
I'll make my staff show them some hospitality.
You're going to help me?
I really appreciate it.
Bye.
So, he wants me to owe him a favor by sending a few of his men, huh?
Ein.
Can you still live up to my expectations?
Use this.
This is an appropriate ornament for tonight's stage.
There are two more magazines.
As you know, you'll need good command of the gun.
Try to avoid rapid fire as much as possible.
Yes.
Finish it wisely.
This will be your last job.
Yes.
Ms Garland will be at the pier in a moment.
I'm sure she'll succeed.
I heard you sent Zwei as well.
Yes.
He betrayed Inferno once.
If the result deters Inferno's path in any way,
I will take any kind of punishment.
You trust him that much?
What I trust is that someone who has been killing because of his missions...
...will have the urge to murder someone with his own will.
To be honest, I have my doubts...
Is it really wise to let you, who's holding a gun, live or not?
I agree.
I have 15 bullets in the magazine and one ready to fire.
If you do the math, I'd still have bullets left after killing everyone here.
What?
What are you doing?
I can't take you all down with only one bullet.
But it will be enough to kill Scythe.
These are some big words, boy.
It's much better than being shot in the back by you.
Above!
That snaky bastard!
Hey! Wait!
Scythe... where are you?!
I won't let you go, you traitor!
I don't know if you're number 1 or 2, but...
...I won't let you run off after using us like pawns.
Because of you my brother died!
Even if the higher-ups forgive you, I'll never...
...forgive you.
Elen.
Let's go back.
It's not too late.
Please...
Come back with me...
Scythe!
Ein.
I see.
Well done, Zwei.
I felt that you would surpass Ein one day...
I see why that vixen wants you so badly.
Not only did you attain great success in a short time,
but you also used Ein as a stepping stone.
Stepping stone?
I'm sure you're well aware of this.
Stop.
Please, don't.
Don't worry.
If I kill him, Inferno won't come after you.
So, please...
Elen.
Ein, kill Zwei.
When you have done that, you'll be the Ein I desire.
We're going, Ein.
You moron!
Is this how it ends after all those big words?
How did you guys do?
We killed most of them.
We have quite a few casualties, too.
But as you can see I'm safe and sound.
Get up.
You're going to kill Scythe, right?
I was told that there would be a boat waiting for us at the fifth pier.
It's on the southeastern end.
Understood.
Scythe!
You damn snake! Come out and shoot!
Hold her back.
I'll go ahead.
Understood.
He's Roshenenko's...
Master!
Scythe!
Reiji...
That's an interesting outcome.
How appropriate for the finale.
Elen.
What is it?
Nothing...
I wanted to see how you would react when I called you by that name.
Am I supposed to laugh at a time like this?
I'm sorry.
I'll make you laugh one day.
I'm sure you can go back...
Laughing when you're happy, crying when you're sad...
Back to being a normal girl.
Normal...
So please, stay alive until then, Elen.
I'll definitely protect you.
Elen...
Our promise...
Your smile...
I've lost everything.
There's only...
...the title of a killer left to me.
Phantom.