If a giant monster really is attacking japan,
will they give us permission to engage?
If this was a monster movie, we'd be goners.
We'd just be there for it to kill before the Megazord showed up.
That isn't funny.
Well, we'll soon know for sure.
Take this!
It's no use...
It's restoring itself.
Its regenerative power is incredible.
It's all we can do just to keep it from coming ashore.
I cannot reach Caster like this...
This is amazing... Just amazing!
Seriously amazing, dude!
God is with us...
God is with us!
You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
So that nobody would have to cry ever again
we all scream and pray on fields stained red with blood
yet our pleas reach no one
I will be able to leave my solace behind
The moon's beautiful light
shines on all that makes up
the beginning
With eyes kept barely open I still see you far away
and trust your grief
What a complete disaster.
In the Holy Grail War's long history,
there has never been a failure comparable to this one.
According to observer reports,
the Mion River area is engulfed by a thick fog.
However, large numbers of bystanders are beginning to gather.
This is now beyond our ability to control.
We shall have to request aid from the Magus Association.
And where is Tokiomi?
My master is heading there now, with Archer in tow.
Kirei...
I will handle the cover-up.
You go and assist Tokiomi.
Understood, Father.
What an utterly hideous sight to behold...
Mongrels or not, they are still supposedly famous warriors.
Yet not even together can they finish that disgusting thing?
How pathetic...
Do you not agree,
Tokiomi?
We must eliminate that monster before further witnesses see it.
In the name of the Tohsaka family...
King, that monster is a destructive pest, tearing apart your gardens.
I implore you to execute it.
That would be a gardener's work.
Or, Tokiomi, do you dare imply
that my Noble Phantasm is nothing more than a gardener's shovel?
Not at all!
But as you can see, the others are unable to handle it themselves.
This is an excellent chance to display the power wielded by a true hero.
I beg you...
Unbelievable.
We're leaving, Tokiomi.
I cannot bear to look upon that nauseating thing any further.
No...
King of Heroes, please wait!
Tokiomi, I have sacrificed four of my swords and spears for you.
Now that they have touched that thing,
I no longer desire them returned to me.
Do not impinge further on my generosity.
You are the sole hero capable of defeating that monstrosity.
Given how rapidly it regenerates, it must be destroyed with a single attack!
And King of Heroes,
the only thing capable of that is your Sword of Rupture—
You dare?!
You would have me draw my greatest treasure, Ea, here?
Know your place, Tokiomi!
To speak thus to a king is punishable by death!
I could use a Command Seal,
but it would severely damage my relationship with the King of Heroes.
Father Risei and I devised this entire plan to restore my lost Command Seal.
Why did it turn out this way?!
Damn it...
What is that?
There's a strange light at six o'clock, too.
That's no helicopter. Is it a UFO or something?
Control to Diabolo-1. What is your situation?
My situation...
Um... Well...
I'll drop altitude and get a bit closer!
Wait, Kobayashi!
Get back here, Diabolo-2!
If I can get closer, I should be able to see what that thing is!
Kobayashi?
Kobayashi!
What is that thing?
I-It ate it.
Control to Diabolo-1!
What the hell is happening up there?
Report!
Eyes... There are eyes...
Eyes everywhere!
Eyes? What do you mean by eyes?
Is it going to eat me, too?
Captain Ougi!
Diabolo-1, engaging!
W-Wait, Ougi!
What's happ—
I'll kill it before it eats me.
I'll avenge Kobayashi...
I'll hit it with everything I have!
Berserker?
What is he doing here?
Fool!
Stay down!
Him again?
That's...
Oh? The mad dog again?
Interesting...
King, I shall engage his Master.
Very well.
Go and play with him.
Good luck, then.
A dog ought to be facing the ground.
You dare gaze upon the heavens, where the king dwells?
Do not be arrogant,
mongrel!
Impertinent...
Fascinating.
I haven't done anything like this for a long time...
For a mere beast,
you do keep me entertained.
You've certainly changed for the worse...
Matou Kariya.
You abandoned the path of magic, but were still drawn to the Grail.
And now, you've returned looking like that.
Your disgraceful behavior
reflects very poorly on the Matou.
Tohsaka Tokiomi, I have one question for you.
Why did you give Sakura to Zouken?
What?
Should you really be concerned with that right now?
Answer me, Tokiomi!
There is nothing to say.
I simply wished my daughter to have a bright future.
What?
Any magus with two children must face a painful dilemma.
Only one may inherit the family secrets.
The other must join the ranks of the rabble.
My wife's womb was too bountiful.
Both Rin and Sakura were born with a rare level of potential.
Both daughters required the protection provided by a magus clan.
To deny the possibilities held by one
for the other to blossom...
Would any father desire that?
The rabble...
The girls and their mother I saw on that day...
He would simply dismiss them as rabble?
To fulfill my wish that both their talents might be developed,
I had no choice but to send one for adoption.
And so, the Matou family's request was like a blessing from heaven.
As a clan that knows of the Grail,
their odds of reaching the Root of all knowledge become that much greater.
A magus is one who is born with power,
and who will someday attain greater power still.
Even before they are aware of this fate,
the responsibility lies in their blood.
That is what it means to be born a magus' child.
If I cannot attain it,
Rin will.
And even if Rin cannot,
Sakura will.
She will carry on the Tohsaka family's wishes.
You...
You'd have sisters fight each other?
Even should that happen,
my descendants will be happy.
What?
Glory is yours if you are the victor.
Even a loss brings much prestige to your ancestor's clan...
Could a more joyous battle exist?
You're insane.
It wasn't even worth the explanation.
Not for one blind to magic's nobility,
let alone a traitor who turned his back on it.
Shut up!
I'll never forgive you.
You disgusting magus...
I'll kill you.
Zouken and you, too!
I will kill
all of you!
You refused to carry on the Matou line,
so its magics went to Sakura.
Perhaps I should thank you.
But even so...
I cannot forgive you, either...
Weakness, in running from the responsibility of your blood.
Baseness, in failing to see anything wrong in doing so.
Matou Kariya, you shame the paths of magic.
Having once more encountered one other,
what else could I do but kill you?
Shut the hell up... You inhuman monster!
No.
Taking responsibility for one's actions is the most essential criterion for humanity.
One who cannot even do that...
... is nothing but a dog,
Kariya.
Insects, devour him...
Devour and kill him!
Get 'em, Bluebeard!
Crush 'em... Kill 'em!
This whole place is God's toy box!
Saber!
I am in your debt, Saber!
It's time to say goodbye to boredom...
There's no need to go out of my way to kill anymore.
I can just sit back and watch them die.
Crushed... Torn apart... Smashed...
Eaten!
They'll die, and die, and die!
I'll see all kinds of guts and gore I've never seen before...
Every day... Every day.
Around the world! Everywhere!
Never ending! Never even—
It stopped?
What?
Hey, what was that?
Wow, so pretty...
I get it...
Yeah, that's why I never noticed.
Sometimes you can't see what's right in front of you.
What I was looking for...
... was my own guts...
... this whole time...
Ryuunosuke?
I finally found it.
I've been searching for it forever...
What's wrong with you?
If it was inside me, why didn't you ever tell me?
You should've just told me...
Ryuunosuke...
My Master.
You have died and left me all alone.
But don't worry, Ryuunosuke.
I, Gilles de Rais,
shall fulfill my promise to you.
Behold, Ryuunosuke!
A gift to see you off to the next world...
The greatest "cool"!
I've shot the boy we believed to be Caster's Master.
It appears we were right.
Shall we eliminate our next target
while the Servants deal with the monster?
Wait, Maiya. That is no mere monster.
It's an immortal creature, regenerating itself endlessly.
It will reach the shore before it vanishes.
If it starts feeding, it's all over.
With a new source of prana, Caster can sustain materialization.
Then the damage would only spread.
The Holy Grail War itself may need to be abandoned.
That's correct.
But how do we eliminate an immortal monster?
Our only option is to annihilate it in its entirety.
To destroy every single scrap of it
in one, single strike.
We need a Noble Phantasm not for destroying people or armies,
but fortified structures.
And Saber
possesses one as such.
Of course, Lancer's curse leaves her unable to use it.
I say
let us have them show us this chivalry
which they're so proud of.
Episode 14
The Mion River Battle
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
This light...
You waste your time.
The undefeated king sings aloud the name of the miracle held in her hands.
It is painful to look upon.
Does he plan to eliminate him?
We must stop him here!
Next Time
Golden Glow
I shall place my faith in you, Saber.