Why would you say that?
I couldn't bear to see Haruka in such pain...
I still can't understand it...
Are dreams truly worth going to such lengths to protect?
Will Prince Kanata ever go back to normal?
Dreams are la soul of Hope Kingdom's people.
Without their power...
it's hard to say if he will.
Oh! Haruharu, we're back!
I ran into Minamin on the bus back, too!
Huh?
Haruharu?
Haruka?
Yui?
Don't. Not now.
What...
could have happened?
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
He was Close the whole time?!
Driving Haruka into despair once she was alone was Close's plan.
But how could Prince Kanata say what he did?
He lost his memories, so you can't blame him.
Regardless of the reason, it was our fault...
that Haruka was alone.
Kanata...
Is it a mistake to be a princess?
Don't become a princess!
Why does it hurt so much?
Why?
Yes, dreams never cease...
to be your shackles.
The Flower of Dreams is in Bloom!
Dance, O Reborn Princess!
With Cure Flora's despair added to what I've gathered thus far,
the seeds I've sowed will overrun their world!
A brilliant plan, Close.
The greatest of dreams crumble into even greater despair.
Now, it begins...
Wh-What?!
Close...
so this is what you collected that despair for.
Dyspair...
Dyspairvil!
Oh!
What's up?
I just...
...wanted to find Haruka...
It seems we're all of the same mind.
Bad news!
It's Dreamy Shore!
It's the Forest of Despair!
How?
Let's go.
What about Haruharu?
We can't make her fight right now.
Be careful!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
Dyspairvil!
Brother!
Girls!
What the heck's going on?
Well, not that you'd know either.
Stop!
Freeze!
Your dream!
Dyspairvil!
Brother, stand back.
R-Right.
What's... that?
I need to go...
Dyspairvil!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Dyspairvil!
The girls!
Huh? Wait, what?
Why? Why can't I transform?
Why?!
I can't transform...
Why? Come on!
Don't become a princess!
Because I shouldn't be a princess?
And now... I'll never be a princess again?
I can't...
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
Vil!
We're not done.
There's no end to them!
You never known when to quit.
Close!
It's him again!
Cure Flora's despair was the best nourishment I could ask for.
The forest will feed on despair until it engulfs the world.
Flora...
Haruka's... despair?
How dare you use our dreams for something so awful!
Dreams lead people to their doom.
Just like how you girls...
left her all alone!
Girls!
You're from yesterday...
Well, stranger, you have my thanks.
The one to finish Cure Flora off...
was all you!
You drove her into despair!
Say no more!
Towa, how's Haruka?
No...
Now that she's fallen into despair,
she'll never be a Precure again, much less a princess!
Shut up!
I bet she's in a corner, wallowing in tears...
all alone!
Mermaid! Twinkle!
I did...
something that can never be undone!
Brother!
Haruka!
Where are you going?
You won't make it.
Go on!
Hurry!
Why...
Why... did it have...
to end this way?
I will be one!
I will be... a princess...
You can.
Not ever.
Why...
can't I be a princess anymore?
Is that so wrong?
Huh?
Why did I...
even want to be a princess?
I want to be a princess...
A princess?
Yeah...
The Princess... of Flowers...
Oh? Why's that?
'Cause she's sparkly and pretty!
That's it?
In that case, I shall give you this.
What's this?
A charm to guide you to your dream.
A princess, huh?
Guess she's got another quirky dream.
Fine by me.
If it keeps Haruka a cheerful little girl,
any dream is fine.
All done.
There.
Wow! Thanks, Mom!
N-Noble Academy?!
Please! If I go here, I think I can become as splendid as a princess!
But it's so high class...
The entrance exams will be rough.
I'll study!
Then give it a shot.
A-All right!
You can do it, Haruka!
Thanks!
That's right...
My dream...
Remember now?
Yes!
I've always...
always...
Every single moment...
Kanata?
I'm sorry...
Huh?
I wanted to save you from your pain...
Yet I failed to do even that...
and instead hurt you the most!
I mean it...
I'm sorry!
You know, Kanata...
having a dream is what brought me this far.
It's how I met you all!
I could never bear to be without my dream.
Even if you tell me to give up,
I'll still aim to be a princess.
I finally understand...
Your dream...
is who you are.
In that case,
in the hopes that you never lose your smile,
I will...
That's enough of that.
Oh?
Don't tell me...
Haruka!
Haruharu!
There you are!
Kanata...
Here.
I've been meaning to give this to you.
It's thanks for the play!
Why are you still here?
What can you still hope to accomplish?
I can stand up for everyone here...
and protect our dreams!
Thank you...
for daring to dream...
and leading me to such bliss.
Let's go, princess.
The Princess of Blooming Flowers...
Cure Flora!
Within the torrent of despair
Dyspairvil!
The moment the downpour begins
I'm asked once more why I still rise
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Haruka?
My spirit could be broken
I might fail in the end
Halt.
But I chose to believe in this path
Dyspair... vil!
Flora!
Embrace your passion with courage and never let go
You okay?
Thanks!
Sorry...
Huh?
We left you alone this whole time...
If you focus it toward hope (toward the light) you'll find your future
It's our...
But that just means that you two...
believed in me this whole time, right?
A princess must have a soul that shines
Come on, I know you girls!
Haruka...
With passion, persistence, and elegance, open the door to your dream
Haruharu...
Dyspairvil...
Dyspairvil!
Meeting you and protecting you
Dyspairviiiil!
Has given me strength
With ever more strength, grace, and beauty,
Yui! Perf! Aroma!
Sorry for making you worry!
and your enduring heart, seize the key to tomorrow
Haruka...
Don't you forget about me!
You're all right now, correct?
Yeah!
You never change!
One moment, you're in sorrow...
and the next, you stand on your own!
It's no surprise for a girl
To have an aspiration in her heart
We all want to be a splendid heroine
I didn't do it on my own, Towa.
It's thanks to everyone's support...
Playing dress-up isn't good enough
that I can stand here now!
I want to see my inner self in a mirror
Cure... Floooooraaaaaaa!
And let it bloom when I stand up for myself
I stumble and realize my own weakness
So what if you've got your dream back?!
It'll shackle you once more!
I want to see it, change it, and overcome it
Then let it!
Growth is the mark of a true princess
Burn bright and true to paint the beautiful path to your dream
Even the tears we shed are bound by friendship
We're not alone
No matter my wounds, I will spread my wings
Our hearts will forge the key to tomorrow
Flora!
I chose this dream!
I'll overcome all the pain and suffering in my path!
And I'll become a princess!
It's a fantasy...
You'll never be one!
You can.
I know...
you can do it.
Kanata...
Brother!
Have your memories...
Yes, it all came back to me!
B-But how?
It must be because I found a new dream.
A new dream?
Yes.
Haruka...
In the hopes that you never lose your smile, I will...
protect your dream!
Kanata!
What? He's suddenly brimming with the power of dreams...
That's right, he's Hope Kingdom's prince!
A Dress Up Key?
It came from your present!
It must have been born from your dream, Prince Kanata!
From mine?
Girls!
Let's go!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
B-Beautiful...
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Dreaming...
Blooming...
Adieu.
Back then, I exhausted every ounce of my power...
at the cost of my own memories.
But now...
Vous have gained le new dream, recovered votre memories,
and even gained la new key!
Brother!
It's a miracle!
I must thank you girls for this.
This calls for a celebration anyway,
so I guess I'll have to buy you a new present!
No, there's no need.
Because Haruka, I've finally...
seen you smile.
Wha?!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Flora!
Let the flower of yearning bloom
and fix your heart upon the land beyond the bounds
Never give in and never run away
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Dear Brother!
You seem happy, Towa.
Oh?
We wound up in Hope Kingdom?!
It can't be!
How can it be so overrun?
T-Towie...
This will not stand.
Dyspear! Prepare yourself this instant!
Go! Princess Precure:
Towa's Determination!
The Shining Rainbow of Hope!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!