Hitoe!
That's horrible...
I wish you could've seen Hitoe
getting all desperate and stuff.
Like, how she was going on
about protecting Ruu-Ruu...
Getting up in my face, weren't you, huh?!
Hitoe!
Once a nobody, always a nobody.
If you want a battle with me
that much, then you've got it...
She's here!
She came!
Are you trying to leave me out of the fun?
Look! Aki-lucky did as you told her, Ulith!
Ruu.
Tama's here, too.
It was a piece of cake!
And see, Ruuko brought her buddy-buddy Iona, too!
That's really Aki-lovely of me, right?
Hey, hey, hey, Ulith,what do you want me to do next?
Aki-lu—
This is supposed to be the entertaining show you've prepared for me?
Ulith...
You disappoint me.
ubaware kanatte risou wa kurikaesu geemu surinuketeku
The acts of theft and granting are entwined within the endless games
nichijou wa utarete ana darake tatteiru no ga yatto kana
You finally take a stand after your quiet life was beaten to a pulp
ketsuron no nai kuuron mienai ruuru no ue de odotteru suteppu de
Dance upon the unseen rules with endless speculation
kuzurete iku kyou tsunagitomeru saishuu beru ga naridasu
The final bell rings out to bind together this crumbling world
ukabu omoi no joukei ni wa kimi ga irun da yo
Within my memories you're always there
waretterun dayo
Simply laughing
yurushitakunai no? motometenai no?
You say you can't forgive? That you have no desires?
soredemo mada
So why can't you stop?
We cry OPEN torimodoshitai mirai kowashitai sekai
We cry "Open!" to take back tomorrow and destroy the world
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
akehanashitai negai GOT IT? ima
Do you finally know your deepest wish?
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
kurosu suru I wish you don't cry
We cross and I wish you don't cry
hikari to yami no saki kasanatte mata iro ga tsuku you
Another color lies at the point where light and darkness cross
"sono saki" wo shinjitemiyou ka
And I choose to believe in it
This is new.
I've never seen that before.
Iona is the Girl of Darkness.
Tama is the Girl of Light.
It shouldn't be possible for the Darkness to long for the Light.
Is it because she went to the outside world?
Is it because she met Ruu?
Ruu...
She keeps making their stories more and more exciting!
You had to bring them to a place like this?
What would you've done if somebody saw you?
I-I'm sorry!
Ulith! I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Akira...
Won't you forgive me, please...
Whoops, Aki-lucky got an earful!
Shut up!
Shut the fuck up, you bitch!
Aww, scary!
Hey, believe me...
It's all... Right, it's all Hitoe's fault!
Ugly four-eyes over there didn't even have her LRIG card with her.
B-But see, I managed to bring Ruuko—
How hideous.
What were you thinking?
A wound in such a noticeable place...
How unsightly.
Un... sightly?
Wound...
Unsightly...
Wounds are loveliest when they're hidden from view.
For that, you leave them...
in the tender places that are easily hurt.
Stop it!
Get away from Hitoe!
There's no need for you be afraid.
I don't really care about you.
No, I don't bother with fragile girls like you.
Kominato Ruuko and Iona.
I want to battle against you.
That's why I asked her to set a stage where you'd have to face me,
Unsightly...
but I didn't foresee methods this crude.
Unsightly... wound...
What a fool she is.
Why did you have to do all that?
Unsightly... unsightly...
I want to break you girls.
Break us...?
Unsightly...
Things of beauty,
things of power, things of splendor, things of justice...
I love seeing them shattered.
All things shine at their most brilliant when they're being broken.
Don't you think so, too?
It started with mere trifles.
I kept breaking all kinds of things.
I held them in my hands as the warmth left their bodies.
When I was a small child, I knew how to deceive the adults around me.
But that didn't last for long.
Then it struck me that I'd be safe as long as no one found out.
All I had to do was injure a place hidden from sight. That way, no one would say a thing.
Hidden from the outside,
the most tender place of all...
The heart.
Hitoe!
Stop, you...!
I won't do anything.
Directly inflicting pain is too crude for my taste.
You know, I prefer making people loathe themselves.
I bring them to the point where they hate their lives so much they'd rather end them...
But I made a mistake.
I was discovered when I messed up,
and then I had to behave myself again.
I acted the good girl and even made friends.
But I couldn't suppress my urge to break someone.
The boredom was so mind-numbing it made me wish I would die.
But then
I met
a LRIG.
Tama!
It doesn't get any better than being a Selector!
No one can judge you for anything you do on the battlefield.
You're free to hurt anyone you want as much as you want.
Neither adults nor laws matter one bit.
I broke them all to my heart's content.
Stepping on their wishes, making them abandon all hope...
and finally crushing their hearts.
Even now
their cries are still ringing in my ears.
Revolting...
That was your wish?
To ruin other peoples' lives?
No.
I wanted to stay right where I was.
Inside this vortex of sorrow, hate, and regret.
That's why I wished to become a LRIG.
Really? Can I really become a LRIG?
Yes. A Selector deserving of you is already waiting for you.
And...
this is the ideal appearance for you to have by her side.
After that, you came to me.
Truth be told, you were a bit too refined for my taste.
Say, has this ever crossed your mind?
That the world out there can just go to hell.
It's nothing but pretense, deceit, and shallow lies.
But the battlefield is different.
There is only truth there.
Everyone must reveal their true selves to fight for their desires and wishes,
and eventually, their hearts shatter and leave a pulpy mess along the floor...
I want to watch that despair forever.
That's why I'll keep winning my battles and turn into a LRIG again and again!
Now let's battle!
Don't you want to do it as well, Iona?
That's the reason you became Ruu's LRIG, after all.
Kominato Ruuko. You're the
greatest Selector I have ever met.
I wonder what sound your heart will make when it shatters...
And how will your cries sound when that happens?
No!
You can't, Ruuko!
It might not be to my taste,
but I didn't say I couldn't break you.
Stop!
Let's do this, Ruuko.
Iona!
She's serious. There's no telling what she'll do if you refuse.
You want to save Hitoe, right?
Ruuko, don't worry about me.
Ruu!
Let Hitoe go if I win.
Ruuko, you can't!
If you win...
Let's go, Iona.
Yes.
Ruu... your eyes are so
straightforward and beautiful.
I'll carve despair into those eyes of yours!
Open!
Iona,
Tama,
and finally
Ruu.
Hello, Kominato speaking.
Ah, Uemura-san. I appreciate you always taking care of Ruuko—
Hitoe-chan isn't home yet?
She's not answering your calls?
Let's begin, then.
Tama. Grow!
Grow!
Unsightly...
Urie!
Tama-chan...
Wow! Good one!
Ulith...
Here I come, Tama.
Iona-san! Death Beam!
You're so good, Ruu.
Breaking you is going to be well worth it!
Skyju! Attack!
Burst effect! No Gain!
Ruuko...
Tama...
They're both battling seriously?
Ulith looks like she's having so much fun!
Isn't that right, Aki-lucky?
No...
Ulith...
My Ulith is...
I feel it again.
Ruu is entering my body.
Light is spreading within me...
You're serious now, Ruu.
You're fighting seriously.
Ruu... Tama knows, too.
We share the same feelings!
Stop, Tama-chan! Ruuko!
I want to save Hitoe.
To do that, I have to win!
Ruuko, you would even hurt Tama to that end...
I'm sorry, Tama!
Ruu...
Tama understands.
I understand.
Ruuko...
Tama...
Please stop!
I can't stand watching Ruuko and Tama-chan hurt each other!
Thank you, Hitoe.
I love you a lot, too.
That's why...
I'll battle seriously!
Vimana. Attack!
Tama...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's all because I was caught.
I'm the reason why Ruuko and Tama-chan are...
Hitoe!
Don't avert your eyes!
Yuzuki...
There's nothing else...
All we can do for them is watch.
But... that's why...
we can't avert our eyes!
Such a pretty fighting style...
She truly is the greatest.
I can see why you set your sights on her, Iona.
I won't let you have something this amazing for yourself.
You and me—No,
we will savor this in full together with Ruu.
I'll shower you with my love until you can't help but shriek in pleasure, Ruu!
I've never seen
Ulith so happy before...
I've... never seen...
How unsightly.
Un... unsightly?
Unsightly...
Things of beauty.
N-No...
Ulith...
loves me...
She loves me...
Akira is Ulith's Aki-lovely.
Aki-lovely... Aki-lovely... Aki-lovely...
Tama! Arch Aura!
Iona, are you okay?
Hurry...
The battle isn't over yet!
Enercharge!
Hurry!
Ruu! Iona!
Please hurry!
Hurry and beat me!
Please...
Tama...
Tama-chan...
Sorry...
I'm sorry...
Tama.
Iona. Grow.
Everything is aflame with pure white light.
It's so bright...
She's getting strange again.
Darkness cannot cross with Light.
I knew it.
Ruu is making everything more exciting.
Level 5?!
I'm in awe!
...lovely...
Aki-lovely...
Aki... lovely...
Dark Matter!
Yikes!
Tama...
Baroque Defense!
I know this!
It can negate any attack, right?
Tama!
Strong...
You're strong... Ruu... Iona...
I... might lose...
But...
Hitoe's going to be saved.
Tama...
As I thought.
Tama is the Light.
There once lived a girl alone.
From the moment she was born into our world, she lived in solitude.
She didn't know the world outside,
and she never felt love,
nor the touch of another person.
Her life of solitude seemed to stretch out into all eternity.
Do you remember Futase Fumio's story?
The Girl of Darkness and the Girl of Light were once one and the same girl.
She was that first girl.
And that girl is...
Mayu is...
our mother.
How naughty.
Iona!
Just when everyone was having fun,
you had to go and make them all feel awful.
You're a bad girl, Iona.
You bring misery to everyone
That
Lie
is a
Scar
because you're the Girl of Darkness.
Life
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
I walk through
this endless street maze
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
to the sound of bells
I will
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
shed the life
that I was given
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
for a brighter tomorrow
I now feel catharsis in a world
hikari to yami kowasaseru sekai de
that will allow neither dark nor light
mezamehajimeru catharsis
With fear in my heart I swore
furueteiru mune de chikatta
that I would never again
mou dare hitori
lose anybody
nakushitakunai
The morrow may be drenched in tears,
ashita namida afuretemo
but I will face the wind
kaze no naka wo
with pride
kakenukeyukou
I will do what must be done for my future
hanate eranda mirai he
I will remember my wish,
torimodosu yo
and I will never give up
kono negai wa akiramenai
Ruu entered my body.
It made me feel nice and warm.
Frie...nd...
Something is entering me!
Everyone was just being played with...
This
World
is
Mine
This world is mine.