"Today"
"Study Hall"
The second day of Fumizuki Academy's
academic training camp... Class A...
Hey!!
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
Classes A and F are doing
the training camp together.
Yuuji, I'm happy that I can study with you.
Shouko, that's not your seat.
But why are we having a study
hall after coming all the way here?
Aren't they gonna give us regular classes?
Why would they? Can you
understand Class A's material?
That might be the case for you, Yuuji,
but to me there isn't much
difference between Classes A and F...
Oh? That's amazing.
...because I can't understand either of them.
That's amazing in a different sense.
The goal of this training
camp is to raise our motivation.
By studying in the same classroom,
Class F would think they
wanna become like Class A,
while Class A would think they
don't wanna become like Class F.
I don't know about Class A, but it's
not clear if it's effective for Class F, is it?
Oh, Rep! There you are!
Then, maybe I'll come here, too.
Aiko Kudou...
Hello, hello. I heard. So you guys tried
to peek on the girls bathing last night?
If you wanted to see it so badly,
you should've told me.
If you like, I can show you my underwear.
Wh-What?!
Not happening.
Hm? What is wrong, Muttsulini?
You normally love naughty
stuff, but you're quite calm.
Even I am worked up,
my heart is racing with excitement.
Don't be fooled, Akihisa.
She's wearing leggings.
What?! How cruel, Kudou!
Give me my pure heart back!
Sorry, Yoshii. Instead,
I'll show you something interesting.
What is it?
A pocket-sized recorder...
Hm? What is wrong, Muttsulini?
This stuff is quite interesting, you know.
I love Kudou. My heart
is racing with excitement.
Huh?
Yeah, it couldn't be more interesting!
Yeah, that's quite an interesting line.
Mizuki, give me a hand.
Sure, no problem.
Akihisa, those two went
to get torture equipment.
Hurry up and run before they come back.
On no, Hideyoshi. I'm not at fault, right?
Hey, Akihisa.
What, Yuuji?
It's possible that Kudou is the wiretapper.
True. The skills she
showed just now were amazing.
Akihisa, check if she's the culprit.
Okay.
Say, Kudou...
What is it, Yoshii?
If you...
Wait, there's no way she'd be honest if
I ask her, "If you're the culprit, just tell us."
What's the matter?
Ah, uhm, well, especially if you...
If I what...?
How should I ask her?
If I remember right, the culprit has
a burn mark on her butt, so... so...
I'd really like it if you
could show me your butt.
Not bad, Akihisa.
That's our Akihisa.
How daring, Akihisa.
I'd really like it if you
could show me your butt.
But it's embarrassing.
No change. Just the line as-is.
Please, Kudou! Please delete that one!
Please, Kudou! Show me your butt.
I wonder what it was.
Yeah, what was that?
Don't tell me some idiot said a foolish
thing that can worsen his problems.
Well, we can't have that. Such a
person needs severe punishment, right?
You've got it wrong! I just...
...love butt.
That's all!
Hey, stop it, Kudou!
Aiko Kudou, don't mess around.
Muttsulini!
I'll take her on! Just leave it to me.
So you'll help me? Good!
Both of you, you heard it wrong earlier.
--I want to clear up the misunderstanding,
--I love butt.
is what I wanted to say!
--Especially Yuuji's butt.
--It's really a misunderstanding!
Hey, Muttsulini!
Aiko Kudou, you've got more to learn.
Not bad. Just what
I'd expect from you, Muttsulini.
Yoshii, I'm not gonna let you have Yuuji.
I don't want him, either!
Aki... So you like Sakamoto's butt
that much? Mine's not good enough?
I sort of knew it, but when you
say it so clearly, it gives me a shock.
Everyone, you've got it all wrong!
I'm not into that kind of creepy...
Don't make fun of homosexual love!
Miharu? Why are you here?!
Honey! I wanted to see you
so I sneaked out from Class D!
Sugawa Barrier!
How filthy! It's worse than cuddling a rotten pig!
How cruel, Honey!
When I love you so much!
Hey, stop it! I'm not interested in girls!
You guys! It's study time.
Could you be a little more quiet?
I-I'm sorry, Kubo.
Also, I don't think it's nice to
make fun of homosexual love.
I think a society in which people who
are just like everyone else become despised
just because their individual
taste is a little different from that of
average people is wrong
and needs to be corrected.
He's right! Gender doesn't matter!
I'm not into that kind of thing!
Gender doesn't matter... huh?
I feel a chill for some reason.
Gender doesn't matter?
Why are you looking at Yuuji and me
one after the other? You got it wrong!
As you know, I...
...love Hideyoshi.
Got that?! Hey, wait!
Akihisa, how am I supposed to respond?
Don't get it wrong. Hideyoshi's...
...butt is what I especially love.
--Hey, this is making the misunderstanding worse!
--Kubo! Yuuji!
--Show me your butt, one after the other.
--Hey, this is making the misunderstanding worse!
Kubo, show me your butt!
I love Kubo!
--Kubo, show me your butt!
--You're putting me in a bind, Yoshii.
--There's a proper order for doing things.
--I love Kubo! Kubo, show me your butt!
--I love Kubo! Show me your butt!
--The order isn't the problem here.
I think Kudou might be
the one who's blackmailing us.
From how she can manage that
pocket-sized recorder, it's very possible.
Shall we capture her at once?
We shouldn't. We only get one chance.
If we're wrong, the real culprit
will never give herself away.
She'll destroy the proof
and blackmail you even more.
Which means that the situation will get worse.
So we can't just go barging in
unless we're totally confident, huh?
If only we could confirm that burn mark...
She'll probably get mad, but maybe
we should just try flipping up her skirt?
She's wearing leggings.
Oh, that's right.
In order to confirm it, we have no choice
but to peek while the girls are bathing!
So it comes to that after all, huh?
But what should we do?
Unless we come up with a plan,
it'd be hard to break through that guard.
But that hallway is just a straight path,
so breaking through from the front
is probably the only thing we can do.
It's not that there isn't a way.
If breaking through from
the front is the only way,
we just have to have a
strong enough force to succeed.
You mean we get more people involved?
That's right.
Then let's get on with...
What do you want from us?
Sugawa, guys...
Thanks for coming,
my fellow Class F students.
Actually, we have a proposition to make.
Proposition?
What? I'm tired, you know.
I wanna just loaf around in my room.
Guys, aren't you interested
in peeking on the girls bathing?
We're listening.
Last night, we went to peek on the girls bathing,
but the dastardly teachers
ambushed us and got in our way.
I see... And?
We'll make another attack tonight.
So I'd like to ask you guys to
eliminate the guards outside the girls' bath.
Your reward will be the
chance to see Agartha afterwards!
We're in!
Muttsulini, what time is it?
It's 20:10. 10 minutes have passed
since Class A girls' bathing time started.
This is good timing.
We're gonna split ourselves into four groups.
Those in group A, follow my directions.
--B!
--Group B, follow Akihisa's directions.
--C!
--Group C, follow Hideyoshi's directions.
--D!
--Group D, follow Muttsulini's directions.
Roger!
Listen up, guys! We have
only one goal! Reaching Agartha!
No matter what happens on your way,
use all your strength to
push forward towards your goal!
Gods and demons are mortal, too!
Kill all enemies before you!
Consider this to be the
turning point for our future!
"20:14 Hallway in front of girls' bathing room"
I gave them quite a bit of counseling yesterday.
I'm sure they learned their lesson,
so today, they'll be quiet and...
A pervasive pack of pervs are pushing forth.
"Chemistry"
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
I won't let you through here.
Summon!
Group C led by Kinoshita has
come in contact with Mr. Fuse!
We'll break through in one breath
while Hideyoshi is attracting his attention!
Keep up, guys!
Yeah!
Guys, attack him all at once!
Now! Let's go!
Hold it, Yoshii!
Keep it up! Let's dash through here!
Yeah!
Stop right there, you filthy pigs!
No guys are allowed beyond this point!
Just go on back to your pigsty!
Yoshii, we're at a major disadvantage
both in numbers and quality!
Please, Shimizu, step aside!
You're gonna enjoy my honey's
flat chest to the fullest, aren't you?!
How disgusting!
You're wrong! Minami's flat
chest isn't what I'm here for!
That's a lie!
I'll punish those pigs who are blinded
by the charm of my honey's flat chest!
Believe me. A flat chest
is just a flat chest, after all.
To me, right now, more than
Minami's horizon-like flat chest,
it's important that... My elbow is about
to be twisted clean off! Ow, ow, ow...!
I let you run your mouth!
How dare you repeat it again and again!
Looks like he needs another punishment.
Yoohoo, Yoshii! What did you come to see?
It'd make me happy if you came to peek on me.
Not happening.
I will not permit an affair.
To see even Kirishima is
here, too... This is unexpected!
Could it be that this
is what you're here for?
There's still one unfound hidden
camera left in the changing room.
What?
It's not mine, but I found it by accident.
Kudou...
Well, shall we start now, Muttsulini?
Let's fight!
Summon!
We'll leave this to you, Muttsulini!
I'll take care of this!
Educational counseling!
I knew you guys would
come, you bonafide idiots!
I-Iron Man!
Do we have to break through
him without using our Avatars?!
There's no way we can!
I'll give you thorough
counseling today. Be prepared, Yoshii!
Is this it?!
Don't give up, Yoshii!
Hm?
Sugawa!
Let go of me, Sugawa!
You can't let yourself get taken out here!
You're a probationary student.
So your Avatar is the only
one who can defeat Iron Man!
So, please... Run for now and survive!
Don't interfere with my counseling.
Sugawa! Sugawa!
--Summon!
What?
Back up Yoshii's withdrawal!
We're gonna clear a path
through the enemy for you!
Run on through, without looking back!
Guys...
Yoshii is our hope! Protect him no matter what!
Yeah!
Yoshii...
Okay. I'll leave it to you guys.
And I'll survive and
achieve our goal without fail!
Everyone... I'm sorry... I'm sorry!
I... I... vow to reach Agartha without fail!
Akihisa Yoshii of Class F.
Come to the counseling room immediately.
Well, this is how it normally turns out, right?
It's already morning...?
When I didn't get much sleep at all...
Hm?
So that was a dream!
Geez...
No way I would!
What? Is Yuuji sleeping in
someone else's bed again?
What do you mean "again"?
He tosses around in his sleep a lot.
He came into my bed around dawn and...
I won't forgive you! For trampling
on my pure heart, I won't forgive you!
By the way, Kudou told me
something strange yesterday.
Something strange?
She said that there's still an unfound
hidden camera in the changing room.
What?
I wonder if she's the culprit after all.
Well, that's not necessarily the case.
It's hard to think that the culprit would
say things to cast suspicion on herself.
We have no choice but to check.
But if that information is true, we're in luck.
Why?
Because if we obtain that hidden camera,
we can see the girls changing.
We may be able to find the culprit.
I see...
I'm confident that I can find
that hidden camera in 5 seconds.
But is there really a camera in there?
The girls found the hidden
camera the night before last, right?
It's hard to think that the culprit,
who excels in taking sneak pictures
and wiretapping, would set it up in a
way that it can be found by amateurs.
A fall-back plan.
That's right. The camera they
discovered first was a decoy,
and its purpose was to turn
people's cautious eyes to us.
The one still in the changing room
that Kudou found is the main one.
Then all we have to do is
go get that camera now, huh?
That's not possible.
It's locked outside of bathing time.
But the way we've been doing is...
Akihisa, what do you think the
reason we lost yesterday was?
The reason we lost? Because half of
the girls were sent for defense, maybe?
If that's the case, we'll just
strengthen our forces, too.
We'll have the other classes on our side.
The other classes, too?
There's another reason
for this plan other than
strengthening our forces.
Hm?
That is, to protect ourselves.
Protect ourselves?
Even if we succeed in peeking,
unless we find the true
blackmailing culprit, we'll be punished.
I see. If we are many,
they won't know who actually peeked.
But they've already identified us.
Fumizuki Academy is a pilot
school that's getting lots of attention.
When a scandal happens, they'll
have to either punish those involved,
or hide it at all costs.
So we just have to attack in a big group
so that they can't easily punish us, huh?
That's our Yuuji!
You have no equal when it
comes to coming up with dirty plans!
Call it being resourceful.
Let's gather up comrades before evening.
"Today" "Study Hall"
For Class A, it makes sense to persuade Kubo. Akihisa, you go.
You're suited for it, Akihisa.
We're counting on you.
Okay, but why me?
When push comes to shove,
use this to protect yourself.
Huh?
Hey, Kubo. You got a minute?
Yeah, of course. Now, sit down.
Well, I'm okay here.
If you say so...
By the way, I have a favor
to ask. To tell you the truth...
I'll do it!
That was quick!
Er, sorry. I just lost my calmness.
Let me hear what this is about.
Ah, okay. To tell you the truth,
we're gonna peek on the girls bathing and...
I refuse!
That was quick! Why?!
I lost respect for you, Yoshii.
Among a group of people, there are rules.
By following those rules, society is formed.
So you planning wrongdoing
means that you're unfit for society.
Is that what you want?
To start with, peeking on girls
while they're bathing is filthy!
Sorry, I failed.
I see... Glad that you're okay.
I didn't do anything dangerous, though.
If we can't get Class A to help us,
then we'll just ask the other classes, huh?
You're plotting something again, aren't you?!
I-I'm not thinking of anything.
I'm not going to waste my breath asking
you not to cause trouble anymore, but...
To think that, of all things, you're
planning to peek on the girls bathing...
If it's while bathing, you'd compare
me with the others, I can't use falsies,
and I can't push them up, either, you know.
Since I never thought you'd peek,
I didn't even go on a diet!
That's mean, Akihisa.
No, what I want to see is...
...Yuuji's butt.
No!
"Training Camp" "Showdown" "Night: Third Day"
And thus, once again, the night of the showdown has...
So Classes D and E are the only ones
who're gonna help us after all, huh?
Class B's rep is Kyouji
Nemoto, so they lack unity.
Class C's rep is that Yuuka Koyama.
I don't blame the guys for flinching.
But this is better than yesterday.
Girls can only send half the group
for defense during the bathing time.
As long as we can hold back
the teachers, it can work out.
I've already notified each class
on when to start the operation
and where to gather.
Good. Let's get ready.
We've got a problem!
Hm?
They did it! Our enemy was waiting
to ambush us in the dining hall!
What?!
Right now, our forces are split
and scattered on each floor!
To think that they made a move before us!
They read our thoughts.
Damn! Was it Shouko?
She probably had no
tolerance for Yuuji peeking.
We have no time to hesitate.
We're gonna reorganize our forces.
We'll make our move!
We're not gonna let you peek!
Dammit! Why are the girls here?!
Who knows?! Fight back anyway!
Concentrate on one point and
break through here! Follow me!
Yeah!
Yuuji! There are lots of enemies at the front!
I bet there are traps set
where there are fewer enemies.
So we'll outwit them!
Yuuji... We've been waiting for you.
Shouko...! They outwitted us when
we thought we were outwitting them!
I told you I would not permit an affair.
I'll make sure your body understands it.
Dammit!
I need to give you some serious counseling.
Ms. Takahashi, the Year 2 Head Teacher...!
Yuuji, we should withdraw!
Sorry, that won't happen.
Kudou... Mr. Ooshima...!
You never learn, do you?
Akihisa, if you wanted to see it
that bad, why didn't you talk to me?
Now that it's come to this, I just
have to fight all the way till the end!
Summon!
Go!
He's fast!
What?
Ooooooouch!
Wh-What?
Her score is in the 7000s?!
This is too overwhelming!
What do I do?
What else?
Now that it's come to this, we'll just
do whatever we can with all our might!
Yuuji...
Everyone, listen up!
From here on, forget about the plan!
Take actions based on your own will!
Believe in yourself! You can do it!
Think using your heart,
judge using your brain,
and do what you think is most correct!
From here on, I'll leave the
matter to your own discretion!
Got that?! Let's go!
We're sorry!
Th-The four of you aren't
doing the same as the others?
Is it your pride as commanders?
No, that's not it. We know...
Yes, Yuuji's right. We know...
that we don't have to do that.
Don't tell me that help is on its way...?
You don't understand anything.
What we're talking about is nothing like that.
They knew very well... that they
were dealing with people who wouldn't
forgive them even if they got down
on their hands and knees and apologized.
Although this is the third night of the
training camp, Akihisa and the others
still haven't been able
to find their blackmailers.
What will become of
Akihisa and Yuuji's futu-- Argh!
Flash! Shine! Light bulb, shiny flash!
I'm not making progress.
Someone's interfering... No, no!
The issue is, I don't have
enough common multiples
Okay, I basically get it.
What is the truth... Baby?
If you see this, draw a
diagram and explain it, Baby!
No word or number can describe you
My heart is being shocked by
the magnetic force between S and N
(S! S! Super! Sticking together,
Number! I say No.1 boy!)
Congratulations! From here on
out you're My, ma-my "treasure"
You're special to me,
no matter what happens
I'll hold you ever so
tight and never let you go
I want to be in love, in a
dream you can forget about limits
It's special, right? After all,
we came to know each other
Forgive me for being like this
Flashed! Shined! Right answer, perfect match!
Idiot Test!
Question 7.
What do you call physical
and mental torture used
to make a person obey you?
I'm sorry, Shouko!
I'm not going to ask the details.
Next episode!
"Me, Peeking, and Far Away Paradise!"
This will be on the test.