Tests are such a drag.
These quizzes...
Gotta get my act together.
Man, I just wanna go and do something fun!
Study! Study!
Get a load of her, trying to look all cool by herself.
At least an average score...
No one cares about a loser like you.
What's her deal?
She should've just stayed in the nurse's office.
She missed a few days of school, and now
she's getting all kinds of special treatment.
Supplementary lessons again?
Wearing a sweater instead of a uniform...
I wish she'd just kill herself already!
You waste of space.
Help me.
Help me, God!
Your prayer...
has been heard loud and clear!
Hey, doesn't this Phantom
seem unusually large?
Well, it is exam season.
They're all pretty stressed out.
With you here, this will be a walk in the park.
Let's go, Tomone!
Okay, Yato-san.
Come, Hanki!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Thou who dares desecrate
this land of the rising sun!
I now lay waste to thee with Hanki...
and expel thy vast defilement!
Rend!
You weren't even a plaything for my Regalia.
Yato-san? Hey, Yato-san!
Oh, right.
Revert, Tomo.
You and your disgusting, sweaty hands...
H-How... dare you?!
I'm your master!
We need to talk, Yato-san.
Huh?
I'm quitting. I will no longer be your Regalia.
Wait, Tomone. It's only been three months—
I can't take it anymore!
I can't go on like this! We are through!
Living like a vagrant with a minor god who doesn't even have a shrine...
Every fiber of my being is screaming in protest!
Huh?
Uh... I should be the one crying.
A-All right! All right already!
Hanki, I release you.
It's gone!
Let me give you one last piece of advice:
You should give a full month's notice
before you quit! It's common courtesy!
Thanks for nothing,
you jobless, sweats-wearing bum who calls himself a god!
So that's the real you, huh?!
See ya!
Damn it!
You'll come crawling back to me
once I make it big! Just you watch!
I'll have 120 million worshipers and be a god amongst gods!
You dumb bitch!
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Yato - 365 days a year!
I'll solve any trouble at all!
Stupid Tomone... I can't believe a Regalia actually quit on me.
Just my luck...
Time for a break.
There's no way I can build
a shrine with just this much.
Wait, I have to find a new Regalia first!
Yato - 365 days a year!
I'll solve any trouble at all!
Even if I am a god, I'm essentially unarmed without a Regalia!
Completely naked!
I can't take on any jobs like this!
Not like I get many jobs in the first place...
Hello! Thank you for calling!
Fast, affordable, and reliable!
Delivery God Yato, at your service!
Huh?
Milord has gone missing?
Chapter
A Housecat, a Stray God, and a Tail
Milord?
There are people who actually give their pets these kinds of names.
Name: Milord
Missing Cat
Phone
Ono
Yeah, like "Lord," "King," or "God"!
God...
Wait, didn't you name your dog after Zenny's leader, Ami?
That's so lame!
What do you mean, "lame"?!
Shiina's the love of my life!
I'm all about The Hundred Archfiends!
How can you like that flashy pop band?
Milord! Milord!
How can you like Zenny's?!
The members of Zenny's are gods!
No, The Hundred Archfiends are!
Hey, Milord!
Hey, Hiyori!
Who are your gods?!
I've finished downloading my god!
We're now in the final round of the showdown of the century!
The two circle around and—
Oh my! He grabs his leg!
What will Tono do?!
There it is!
His deadly Jungle Savete!
Sorry. We should have known you weren't into this stuff.
Right, you're a closet martial arts fan.
I wouldn't say I'm a closet fan.
You haven't told your parents, right?
I think my mother would throw
a fit if she found out I'm into it.
Milord! Milord! Milord!
"My, how uncivilized!"
"You must focus on being a lady...
who won't bring shame to the Iki family!"
"And then someday... find yourself a handsome husband!"
Where be'eth you, Milord?! Milord!
How do you know what my mom sounds like?!
Anyway, Hiyori, are there
any guys you like besides Tono?
Yeah! Like someone who's within your reach!
Huh? Hm...
Someone I like...
I don't think there's anyone.
Milord!
Hey! Wait!
Come back, Milord!
Hey!
Hiyori?!
Hey! What happened?!
A girl jumped in front of the bus!
That's dangerous, you know!
Running into the middle of the street like that...
You could've died!
Oh, uh, more importantly...
Hiyori?! Hiyori?!
Say something, Hiyori!
Hiyori!
Is she all right?
I just called for an ambulance!
Wha...
What?
What?!
Hiyori?!
Can you hear me, Hiyori?!
Hiyori!
Thank goodness! You're awake!
Are you all right?! Are you in any pain?!
Hurry, dear! Examine her!
R-Right!
She seems just fine.
What a relief!
Father...
The results of your CAT scan looked just fine, and your EEG appears to be normal, too.
You were hit by a bus and somehow only got a few scratches.
A bus...
I'm worried, dear.
If anything should happen to our precious Hiyori...
Iki General Hospital
This is our hospital,
so you should keep her here a while!
Come, now. There's a whole list
of patients waiting for their turns too.
But...
What about the other guy that got hit?
Oh, I saw him!
I think.
Huh? There was no one else there.
Hiyori was the only one lying the middle of the street.
Huh?
Maybe your memory is still a bit hazy, Hiyori.
But he was there.
Are you tired? You must be exhausted.
You should just get some rest.
I know for a fact that a guy was there.
Plus...
I remember seeing another me on the road.
I don't want to die!
Where is she?! I want to see her!
When will they finally let me leave?
Mommy...
It hurts.
It hurts!
My legs hurt so much.
We'll go when you're all better!
These voices... What's going on?
I can't breathe.
It hurts. It hurts!
I just want to go outside!
It's hopeless.
So you can hear the voices of the Far Shore?
If you can move like that, you must be fine.
You're that guy!
Thanks for this morning!
I didn't really need any help avoiding that bus,
but you're the first human that has tried to save me.
Wh-Who are you?
I'm a god.
Hello, police?
There's a weird guy in sweats here, and he's saying he's a god—
Wait, wait, wait!
I really am a genuine, bonafide god!
I'm the Yato god!
Yato god?
I've never heard of you.
Not once!
Well, right now I'm an up-and-coming stray god.
But just you watch!
I'll soon be known far and wide!
ME
I'll be a god that everyone bows and prays to!
And then...
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
I will someday stand above all the other gods of this land!
Tonight's gonna be pretty stormy.
This place is crawling with 'em.
I can't really stick around without a Regalia.
And Nora's busy tonight, so...
Wait, those are for me!
Hey, what's your name?
Hiyori. Iki Hiyori.
Hiyori...
All right, I've made sure
you're okay. Now we're even!
Huh?
See ya!
Wai—
My body feels heavy.
I can't... stay awake.
Yato...
NORAGAMI
Hiyori!
Ami-chan! Yama-chan!
Are you all better?
Yeah!
Man! I'm glad you didn't get hurt!
Sorry for worrying you!
Jump into the street again
and I'll hit you with a Jungle Savate!
I bet she'd actually love it
if it was from her dear Tono!
Oh, come on!
Whoa, Hiyori!
S-Sorry.
I get dizzy spells from time to time.
Huh?
Were you up all night playing video games?
Was that just a dream?
I feel like I met someone
that night in the hospital.
Sweats...
Are you okay, Hiyori?
You seemed a bit off today.
Yeah. I've just been really sleepy.
Maybe you slept a little too much in the hospital.
The accident was just the other day, too.
What is it, Hiyori?
Name: Milord
Missing Cat
Phone
Ono
Hm? Oh, from the other day!
That's right.
I remember there was a guy
in sweats when I was chasing this cat.
Milord!
Sorry, you guys. Go on without me.
Huh?
I...
must henceforth locate Milord.
What?!
Milord!
Milord?
Nope.
Milord!
If I find that cat...
I might be able to remember.
Milord!
I'm starting to feel lightheaded again.
This smell...
Hey!
Milord!
Come out! I got some nice catnip!
Things are starting to get really stormy.
Milord!
Wait! Stay right there!
Don't run, now!
What's the matter?
Smells nice...
Smells nice... Smells nice...
Smells nice!
Smells nice.
These things are weak,
but there's too many of them!
Too many for me to handle!
You teased them and
made them angry, didn't you?
Milord, you need to learn some self-control!
Smells nice!
In you go.
That barely did anything!
Come, Hanki!
Shoot! I forgot that
I don't have a Regalia!
Iki Hiyori?!
What the hell—?!
All right!
You want a piece of me?!
You idiot! You can't—
Jungle...
Savate!
I-I got it!
The great Tono has paid me
a visit from the heavens!
I'll be a devoted follower for as long as I live!
I think we lost it.
This girl saved me again.
We finally meet again, Yato-san.
I had a lot to ask you that night,
but you just ran off so quickly.
No dodging the questions this time.
I want straight answers!
Just so you know...
Your soul's slipped out.
Huh?
Your body's stuck up there.
What?! That's me?!
H-How is this... Am I dead?!
No, it's more like your body's just asleep.
Sheesh. Some lucky cat you are.
I'll hand out fliers and
look some more tomorrow.
Okay?
Don't worry. I'm sure we'll find him!
Yes?
Milord!
It's Milord! Milord!
My wish really did come true!
Thank you, Yato!
Smells nice...
Gross! Let go of me, you sicko!
I'm not a sicko! I'm a god!
Again with that?!
Oh, yeah! My tail!
Huh? It's gone.
What? What's going on?
It was all a dream?
It wasn't, right?
What happened to me?
It must've been the accident.
There's the Near Shore, where the living reside, and then there's the Far Shore.
Basically, you're existing in between the two right now.
The Near Shore and... Far Shore?
Yeah.
I guess the Far Shore is
what you guys would call...
the afterlife.
You're alive, but at the
same time, you're a Phantom.
Phantom?
They're embodiments
of emotional energy.
They possess people
and cause all sorts of trouble.
Wait, so that big frog just now... Was it also—
A Phantom.
What?! So I'm the same as that thing?!
No, not exactly.
Huh?
You're sort of half-and-half.
Uh... I don't really understand.
Losing your body will be common for you now.
So, how do I go back to being human?
I don't know if you can go back.
This is just the way
you are now. Accept it.
You can't be serious!
I can't live like this!
I don't want this! Turn me back!
You're a god, right?! Help me!
Money.
You charge money?!
Well, duh! There's no way I'd work for free!
It'll cost you this much.
Fifty thousand? Five hundred thousand?!
I don't have that kind of money!
Are you crazy?
I'm a god, remember?
And everyone knows you're supposed to offer five-yen coins to gods!
Fi—
Huh? Um...
Your wish...
has been heard loud and clear!
Iki Hiyori.
May our fates intertwine verily.
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
Step #1 in "Project: Make Yato a Major God"
is to come up with a brand-new chant for the portable Yato shrines!
What's wrong with a simple "heave-ho"?
Instead of "heave-ho," let's use "ya-ho"!
On the next Noragami: "Snow-like."
Snow-like
Next Episode
Remember! That's "Ya-ho, Yato!"