UNPARALLELED PERIL
ONE PUNCH
THREE, TWO, ONE, KILL SHOT
JOIN THE FIGHT, CERTAIN VICTORY, THE STRONGEST EVER
SANJOU, HISSHOU, SHIJOU SAIKYOU
WHAT WAS THAT? FRUSTRATION
NAN DATTEN DA? FRUSTRATION
THERE'S NO STOPPING ME
ORE WA TOMARANAI
ONE PUNCH, IT'S OVER, VICTORY AFTER VICTORY
ONE PUNCH, KANRYOU, RENSENRENSHOU
I WIN, I ALWAYS WIN, OVERWHELMINGLY
ORE WA KATSU, TSUNE NI KATSU, ASSHOU
POWER, GET POWER
RIGHT TO THE VERY LIMIT
GIRIGIRI GENKAI MADE
HERO
PEOPLE SHOWER ME WITH PRAISE
ORE O TATAERU KOE YA
BUT I DON'T DO THIS FOR THE FAME
KASSAI NANTE HOSHIKU WA NAI SA
HERO
SO I JUST FIGHT EVIL IN SECRET
DAKARA HITOSHIREZU AKU TO TATAKAU
(NOBODY KNOWS WHO HE IS)
COUNTLESS ENEMIES FILL THE SKY
SORA OOI OSHIYOSERU TEKI
BUT I WON'T TURN MY BACK AND FLEE
ORE WA SE WO MUKE WA SHINAI
HERO
I'VE MADE UP MY MIND AND I WON'T GIVE IN
NARABA YURUGINAKI KAKUGO SHITA TAME
A FIGHTING HERO
TATAKAU HERO
A SOLITARY HERO
KODOKU NA HERO
I WANNA BE THE STRONGEST HERO
I WANNA BE A SAIKYOU HERO
Advance Fearlessly
Towards One's Goal
CITY A
HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
CLASS S, RANK 17
PURI-PURI PRISONER
CLASS S, RANK 16
GENOS
CLASS S, RANK 15
METAL BAT
CLASS S, RANK 14
TANK-TOP MASTER
CLASS S, RANK 13
FLASHY FLASH
CLASS S, RANK 12
WATCHDOG MAN
CLASS S, RANK 11
SUPERALLOY BLACKLUSTER
CLASS S, RANK 10
PIG GOD
CLASS S, RANK 9
DRIVE KNIGHT
CLASS S, RANK 8
ZOMBIEMAN
CLASS S, RANK 7
KING
CLASS S, RANK 6
METAL KNIGHT
ABSENT
CLASS S, RANK 5
CHILD EMPEROR
CLASS S, RANK 4
ATOMIC SAMURAI
CLASS S, RANK 3
SILVERFANG
CLASS S, RANK 2
TORNADO OF TERROR
CLASS S, RANK 1
BLAST
ABSENT
CLASS B, RANK 63
SAITAMA
the earth
is in trouble
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
When my worries keep me awake under the crescent moon
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
All I can do is close my eyes and think of you
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I want to see you, I feel like crying
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I feel so romantic
romantikku na kibun
I hope my feelings reach you
todokete kono omoi
I know so very well
datte zutto shitteiru no
how hard you always work
ganbatteru koto takusan
You're the one I love
daisuki na hito ga
You're so strong, yet still I worry
tsuyokute shinpai
Only I ever see your weakness
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
I'll find you before the stars
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
Come right back home
massugu kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
NEXT
TIME
THE
DOMINATOR
OF THE
UNIVERSE
THE
DOMINATOR
OF THE
UNIVERSE