I wish I never found out
about love.
I love you.
My tears won't stop.
Everyone is supporting me.
- If this is how it's going to be,
- Everyone is making me shine.
- I wish I had
- So I'll continue to sing.
- never met you.
- Just like the moon that waxes
and shines even
after it wanes.
Good morning, Eichi.
Please watch over me from
up in the sky again today!
Takuto! Meroko!
Good morning!
Hi!
Hey, you!
At least wear a pair of socks
when it's this cold!
Do you want to be hospitalized
again or something?
Okay!
Mitsuki! Breakfast!
Mitsuki...
Yes?
Well...
How is school?
We've recently started
practicing for graduation.
I see.
Ma'am...
What do you think
about them?
Seems to me they aren't
quite meshing right.
Yeah.
W-Well, I guess it'll
still take some time.
What do you mean
"ah ha ha"?
Is it still bothering you?
W-What are
you talking about?
I'm not bothered by
anything in the least!
Hey, I've told you numerous times
that I don't think you're at fault.
But...
No "buts"!
I told you before, the whole thing
is Izumi's fault, right?!
Yeah.
Gimme a break. How long are
you gonna mope like that?
Don't make me
worry anymore.
Takuto! Thank you!
Idiot! Stop that!
Mitsuki...
Yes?
Umm... About your room...
W-Why don't you move
into the main house?
Huh?
Ma'am!
It's inconvenient where
you are now, isn't it?
And we have to think
about your health.
Grandma...
Please move into
the main house.
Okay!
Yay!
Good morning!
Thank you for helping out
every morning.
No problem.
Grandma, Ms. Tanaka,
I'll see you later.
Take care.
Thank you for helping
Mitsuki again today.
Sure thing!
Well, shall we go.
Okay!
See you later!
Have a good day!
Come, Ma'am.
It's cold out here, so let's go inside.
Yes.
Huh? Work?
Yeah.
Given what happened,
and considering your health,
I told the office to turn down
work whenever possible.
But just today...
It's no problem at all, Ms. Oshige!
This is my first job since my recovery!
I'll do my best!
Thank you, Mitsuki.
See you later!
I'll come pick you up later!
Okay!
So, greetings from
the honored guests finish here
and then the diplomas
will be handed out.
- Did you watch Yaba last night?
- We'll start with the boys from Class 1
- Yeah, yeah!
- lining up by the stairs
- It was really funny!
- and then three people will
- Did you see it, Mitsuki?
- come up on stage at a time.
Yeah.
Hey! You!
Stop the chitchat!
Oops.
Takuto...
Please!
Okay.
All right, shall we go?
Okay!
Good morning!
- Good morning!
Dr. Wakaoji...
Hi!
What are you doing here?
I heard you were working
again starting today.
I asked Keichi to be here
in case of emergency.
It's not only that.
I wanted to hear you
sing in person, Mitsuki.
If you don't feel well,
let me know immediately.
Yes!
How long has it been
since I fell in love with you?
My feelings keep
getting stronger.
They're silent like the snow.
What did you say?
U-Unbelievable.
No way.
Are you...
Are you really...
Yes, I'm Takuto Kira.
That's a lie.
I don't believe you!
I can't believe...
I can't believe that Takuto died!
Keichi...
But how do you explain
the way you look?
What about your voice?!
The Takuto I know is
a totally different person!
First of all, why wasn't I
aware of it before now?
I see.
So that's what happened to you
after Route L broke up.
Yeah.
I apologize for getting
all worked up like that earlier.
It's okay.
But it still doesn't
sit right with me.
But I've explained
everything to you!
No, it's not that.
It doesn't sit right because we were
such close friends back then.
Huh?
Why... Why are you a Death Spirit
who is trying to take Mitsuki's life?
It can't be helped.
I don't want to do this either. But...
If the snow falls forever,
will I be able to let go
of these thoughts of you?
Hey.
About what we were speaking
about the other day...
Yeah?
Sorry to tell you this,
Death Spirit,
but I have no intention
of letting Mitsuki die.
If the cause of Mitsuki's death
is her throat illness,
I, as her doctor,
will root it out.
That is my mission.
It is true that I am a Death Spirit.
But...
I don't have any intention
of letting that girl die.
Takuto.
Our objectives are the same.
I want to scream in
the winter sky
I look forward to
working with you!
that I want to
see you right now.
Wow, it was so much fun
to work after such a long time!
You're not overdoing it, are you?
Are you feeling all right?
I'm totally fine.
I see. That's a relief.
Ms. Oshige!
Please stop right here!
What? I don't need to
drop you off at home?
No.
Well then, Ms. Oshige,
thank you very much!
You're welcome.
Everyone!
Oh, Mitsuki!
Good evening!
Did you just get back
from your check-up?
Well then, please take
good care of Mitsuki.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So cool...
She's been driving you around
ever since you were released
from the hospital, hasn't she?
Wow.
But is it really okay for a racecar
to drive on ordinary streets?
I feel like it's really starting to
hit me that we're graduating soon.
But even after we graduate, we'll still
see each other at the same junior high.
Right, Mitsuki?!
Y-Yeah!
Graduating all together, huh?
I hope that we'll all be
in the same class again.
Yeah, that would be great!
Wouldn't it?
You say that...
But you want to be in the same class
with Machida, don't you, Kumi?
W-What are you
talking about?
Oh, you're blushing!
Stop that, Wakana!
I'm jealous!
I want a boyfriend!
Shut it!
I want one too!
- See you!
Okay, see you at school!
- Bye!
See you tomorrow!
See ya!
I lied.
What about?
That I would be going to the same
junior high school as everyone.
Mitsuki...
I won't be able to go
to junior high, will I?
But it's all right.
Until then, I will give my all in my singing,
and I'll live with all my might.
I'm sure Eichi would
want that too.
So that's why you're
saying it's all right?
Yeah!
So you're gonna lie
to me too?
Huh?
Please be honest with me.
I am being honest—
That's not true!
If you want to live,
say you want to live!
If you're scared,
say you're scared!
Don't lie to me.
It's natural to feel that way.
Don't hold it all within yourself.
In that case...
So if I were to say that,
is that gonna change something?
That I want to live, or that I'm scared...
Is that gonna change something?
To tell the truth...
To tell the truth, I really...
It'll be all right. Don't worry.
I won't let you die.
I won't lie to you either.
I will protect you.
I won't let you die
no matter what.
The only person who can
protect her now is me.
That's right.
This is the best way.
Betraying someone you love and
seeking happiness just for yourself...
I'm the worst.
So you finally understood?
Whatever will be, will be.
We should be together too.
Who would want that?!
You're very defiant, aren't you, Mero?
But this is the last chance.
Now... Come back to me.
You're mistaken.
What I felt as I watched
the two of them
was that loving someone is
something much more tranquil.
Takuto forgave me.
He forgave the person
who betrayed him and
was the very cause of
his possibly becoming a ghost.
And also, despite putting himself
in potentially dangerous situations,
he always protected that girl.
I believe that loving someone means
having that kind of tranquil big heart.
What are you saying, Mero?
In that way... In an even bigger way...
I do love Takuto after all.
Why? A guy like Takuto who can't
even do his work as a Death Spirit?
That's exactly why.
Because he has a much more
beautiful heart than we do.
He doesn't have to be able to do the work
of a Death Spirit who just reaps lives.
I love Takuto as a person.
Mero...
You probably don't
understand, do you?
That's your misfortune, Izumi.
My misfortune?
Goodbye!
I wonder where Meroko went.
Jeez...
That idiot.
Huh? Umm...
Meroko!
Takuto, who are you
calling an idiot?
Jeez, where were you?
We were worried about you!
Both of you are really kind,
aren't you?
I love both of you!
M-Meroko, what's the matter,
saying things like that out of the blue?
Huh? Nothing!
Th-That hurts!
Get away from me!
Then, just Mitsuki...
That feels so warm!
Mitsuki! Dinner!
Okay!
Grandma?
What is it?
Your suggestion to move
into the main house... Umm...
Could you wait
just a little longer?
Huh?
Umm... It's not that I don't want to move,
and there's no deep meaning behind it!
I guess I could say
I first need closure.
Or how could I put it?
Ma'am...
I see.
If it's a decision
you have made, Mitsuki.
I understand.
Grandma, thank you!
Don't worry about it.
I look forward to you moving in.
Ma'am...
Come, finish up.
Okay!
I'd like the three of us,
Takuto, Meroko and I,
to be together in that annex
just a little longer.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
Hey, Meroko.
What?
You said that a keyword
hasn't appeared
since Eichi's backwards name
disappeared, right?
Huh? Yeah. Why?
Could you lend me the Death Spirit
Handbook for a moment?
What's up all of a sudden?
Here.
Okay then.
Huh?
TAKUTO KIRA
I am the keyword.
W-What are you doing?!
Takuto! Do you understand
what this means?
Of course.
Then why?!
What the heck is fate anyway?
It's stupid.
If no one is able to change
that girl's fate, I will change it.
Takuto...
There's no way
a half-baked guy like you
could do something
like that alone!
Meroko! You...
Yeah!
TAKUTO KIRA
MEROKO YUI
Me too.
What happened?
She relapsed from
her transformation all of a sudden
back into her
12-year-old self!
My Death Spirit powers are
just a little weak right now.
Don't worry about it.
Takuto, could that mean...
It's fine.
Do you not trust me?
But...
I decided that I would help her
achieve her dream in one year.
I'm keeping my promise!
Next time on Full Moon:
"I Can't Be Full Moon."
- Look forward to it!