Today shall be simply epic.
Hey, we're running outta time!
You gotta get ready!
Then bring my dress!
Helping you change is a maid's job!
Don't be silly.
You can dress yourself, right?
My... self?
Yeah. For the win!
Okay, all done!
Let's go!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
I'd like to announce that we have
a transfer student joining our class.
Akagi Towa
Her name is Akagi Towa.
Go on, Miss Akagi, introduce yourself.
I'm worried...
Good luck, Princess Towa!
Akagi Towa
Bonjour.
I, Akagi Towa, hail from the land of Hope Kingdom.
While there is much I've yet to learn about this world,
rest assured that I shall spare no effort
to protect the flames of hope you all bear.
May we all work together to reach that goal.
Nice joke!
You don't hear an intro like that every day!
That's for sure.
The straight-faced delivery made me take her seriously!
Akagi Towa
I am ser—
Hey, Teach! There's an open seat here!
Guess we're safe for now...
Thank you for your offer.
Don't mention it, Towie.
Towie?
A Forced Smile?
My Roommate's a Princess!
Phew, your introduction went well!
Yes, but...
my classmates seemed to snicker once I finished.
I'll say...
Incidentally, where did the
last name "Akagi" come from?
The Principal gave it to me.
For convenience, she said.
Yeah, "Scarlet Castle" totally fits! Mrs. Mochizuki's a genius!
I hope this school can help me find my path.
There's no need to rush.
Yeah! For now, just take a load off and put on a big smile!
Smile...
So, you had an announcement?
Ahem!
Towa, your Keys!
Towa has three Keys!
If you add them all up...
it means we've gathered all 12 Keys!
Not quite.
My Keys were transformed from
Keys that Dyspear herself created.
They aren't part of the 12 Keys
needed to reclaim Hope Kingdom.
Tch, tch, tch! Don't let that get you down!
I know we'll get the last three!
It's rude to mimic others!
You're so unrefined, Haruka!
But I think that's one of your good points!
By the way, where's Kirara?
She seems to have left.
Guess she's at work.
Work?
With the attention she drew at Bauanne's show, she's been busier with modeling work than ever.
Modeling?
Yeah! Kirara's dream is to become a world-famous top model!
And she's on the fast track to making it come true!
Okay, that's it!
Let's see...
Next on the schedule...
Kirara, got a sec?
I'm publishing a new magazine soon.
Want to be its cover model?
I can put in a good word for you!
Totally!
I'd love to do it!
Great! I'll contact you later.
Thanks for the offer!
I can't let this chance slip away!
Eureka, you've got it!
Not bad.
It was simply what Minami taught me yesterday.
I shee...
You seem tired.
Perf, bring us tea!
C'mon, enough with the jokes!
I do not jest.
A cup of tea will relieve you of your weariness.
Amanogawa, are you falling asleep?
Uh, I mean...
I'm awake!
Is that so? Then we'll move on.
Open your textbooks to page 33.
Are you okay, Kirara?
Oh, large bowl of rice, please!
Here you go.
Is work that exhausting?
Work's part of it...
Oh, look over there!
That must be the new girl!
She's so splendid!
And she sits at the same table as Minami and Kirara?
Huh? Towa, where's your food?
A waiter has yet to take my order.
Geez, Towie...
Towie?
We get food on our own here.
On our own?
Towa, help yourself!
Have a beverage!
Thank you.
Oh, we're honored to be of service to you, Lady Towa!
Excuse us!
She already has a fanbase...
That's royalty for you!
You've gotta learn, Towie.
The rule of this dorm is that students do everything themselves.
My, how quaint.
Don't give me that!
You're on your own tomorrow, got it?
Without making Perf do everything, of course.
I understand.
I shall handle my own affairs.
I suppose there's plenty to get used to.
Incidentally, Towa, you're assigned to do chores tomorrow.
Kirara, show her the ropes, if you'd please.
Oh, that's right!
Of all the times to get laundry duty...
Goodness, we do laundry as well?
Yeah, we do everything.
This ain't a castle here!
But what would a princess know?
I'll have you know that I can do this "laundry" and whatnot!
You sure?
Even after you needed other people to hand you clothes, tea, and food on a silver platter?
I can do whatever I set my mind to!
Hey, let's settle down...
Shoot, I gotta go!
You've got work already?
Yeah, it's a magazine shoot.
See ya later!
Thanks for lunch!
Kirara!
Is this about the cover model offer from before?
Yeah! It's official, they picked you!
So good luck, 'cause you're gonna get way busier!
Thank you very much!
I'll do this!
Kirara, are you tired?
Your expression looks kinda forced.
Oh, sorry!
Let's just take a break.
Oh, okay...
Sorry...
Kirara?!
I'm fine!
Oh no!
Oh, that's fine, don't worry!
I'm so sorry...
Welcome back.
Glad to be back.
So, work kept you busy the whole day?
Yeah.
So, your dre—
Sorry, I'm goin' to bed now.
Good night.
Ribbon Pigtails!
How did your stature change so?!
Well, I am a growing boy, 'kay?
That's quite the growth spurt...
Anyway...
we've gotta gather the despair needed to revive Lady Dyspear, 'kay?
I suppose so...
To gather despair, all we gotta do is make those humans grieve in sorrow, 'kay?
Sounds exciting to me, 'kay?
Lock, you've changed...
I didn't change a bit.
I just wanna have some fun, 'kay?
I'm gonna get the next load of sheets!
You doin' okay, Towie?
But of course!
I can handle this!
Shirogane, dorm mother.
Huh?
You need to spread the sheets to get the wrinkles out.
Today is a wonderful day for laundry.
Was the sky in your homeland this beautiful, too?
My... homeland?
Towie! Towie!
Watch the sheets!
Why didn't you pin them down?
Pin them?
Yes! The studio and staff are just perfect!
That leaves...
Hey, wait up.
I can't wait!
I'm making my lifelong dream a reality!
Show me your dream, 'kay?
I run the number one fashion magazine in the world!
I'm gonna throw that dream in the cage of despair, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Get goin' Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
We finally caught up!
I'm sorry...
If you don't know something, just ask!
I can't help if I don't know you need it.
Right...
Goodness...
I never knew this was here.
How nostalgic...
It reminds me of a place I often played in as a child.
I loved to pick flowers in the sun or chat and play with the fairies.
This place looks a bit similar.
When my homeland... when Hope Kingdom was still beautiful...
May I ask you something?
How can I learn to smile?
What's that mean?
Ever since I wandered into the Forest of Despair, I feel as though I've forgotten how to smile.
So please, can you show me a splendid way to do so?
If I smile, I'm certain I'll grow closer to finding the warmth our principal spoke of!
Towie, you already did smile.
What? I did?
Listen well, Towie.
If you wanna smile... do this!
Kirara?
Cootchie-cootchie-coo!
Wait, Kirara!
This is not the smile I had in mind!
Any smile's a good smile!
Don't sweat the small stuff!
Kirara?
That's right.
Maybe I was the one...
who forgot how to smile.
Guess I was overthinking things.
Sorry, Towie.
And thanks.
See? Just like that!
I finally found you!
A Dyspairvil appeared!
Dyspairvil!
Seems I've got some more despair...
Dyspairvil.
It's her!
'Sup. Took you long enough.
Huh? Is he Lock?
He grew up!
How?!
It doesn't matter how! Let's go, girls!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Prepare yourself this instant!
Dyspairvil!
Dys! Pair!
Dyspairvil.
A red pen?
Good idea, Dyspairvil.
Show them who the fashion police is.
Dyspairvil!
Leave it to us!
Shooting Star!
Shine, O shooting stars!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Surge, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Flame!
Dyspair!
What?
Scarlet!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Scarlet Violin!
Phoenix!
Soar, O wings of flame!
Precure!
Phoenix Blaze!
Burning!
Adieu.
You did it!
No big deal, 'kay?
Open!
The door to your dream!
Let's make this magazine a hit.
Ribbon, okay!
Hairstyle, okay!
Kirara, you're looking a thousand times cuter than ever!
Ready, Towie?
I'm fully prepared, of course.
Let us go, Kirara.
Hey, wait up, Towie!
I shall not.
Aw, geez!
Gotcha!
Goodness, it seems you have.
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
It's summer vacation! Let's hit up Haruka's place!
Go! Princess Precure:
To Haruka's House!
Our First Sleepover!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Chiba Prefecture - Sara (Age 5)
Tokyo - Misato (Age 5)