Princess Anko!
This girl is Tamako,
the daughter of a mochi maker.
Somehow, I wound up meeting her during my travels
and decided to stay here for a little while.
Good morning!
Oh, fine.
Just one, okay? Here you go.
Last, but certainly not least,
this girl has fallen for me.
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
All done!
Time to make some breakfast.
Tamako.
Yes, Dad?
Put the one at the bottom-right somewhere else.
Grandpa!
Aha!
Episode 2
Valentine's Day, Where the Flowers of Love Bloom
Perfect!
Oh, right!
Red bean mochi soup: heart-shaped edition!
It looks delicious.
I'll let Dad try it.
It's freezing!
Good morning, Anko.
Hurry up and get changed.
It's so cold!
Sis,
you shouldn't use the heater to keep your clothes warm.
I'm keeping yours warm too!
Ripe fruits!
Oh, dear.
I've had it with this bird.
How long are you going to stay here?
I shall grace you with my presence 'til the spring.
Spring...
Why spring?
Winter's too cold for traveling.
I put in that mochi from earlier, free of charge!
Besides, with spring comes blooming flowers and girls' fluttering hearts.
Yeah. That's spring, all right.
That'll make the search for my prince's bride that much easier,
I think.
Prince?
The prince of the royal family I serve.
I left in search of a bride for him.
But where could my prince's bride be?
Should I take you to a pet shop?
What's that?
A place where such females may be found?
I guess it is to you.
Look at this, Dad.
What's that supposed to be?
Valentine's Day mochi!
Oh—
There you go again.
Ain't happenin'!
We're not gonna put such frivolous mochi up for sale.
But I want more people to eat mochi!
Our mochi is fine as it is.
The world's gonna leave mochi behind at this rate!
Valentine's?
Lunchtime is packed with girls wanting to buy chocolate.
I see.
Girls who hope these chocolates will make their love bloom!
I get it now.
Midori!
Oh, good morning!
What's wrong?
I got rejected.
What?! Already?!
No, wait, really?
Yeah. Right before Valentine's Day too.
All right!
Let's go stuff ourselves with cake!
Yeah!
Who're you gonna give yours to?
Not telling.
Handmade?! Way to go!
Good morning!
Oh, Midori!
Mornin'!
What are you drawing?
Mochi.
Ah, I see.
You're designing new kinds of mochi, right?
Yep.
Chocolate's so nice.
Chocolate
Just having it there on the cover makes the whole book look cute.
And on the other hand, we have mochi...
It's a cruel world we live in.
That it is.
Morning...
Kanna!
Good morning!
Morning.
How late did you go to bed?
A bit too late. I was drawing up some blueprints.
May I?
Of course!
Wow, you're renovating your house?
Not quite. I thought I might make a chocolate house for Valentine's Day.
Good idea. You're awesome.
I know, right?
Hold on a second, you two.
You're completely forgetting the point of Valentine's Day.
And what's wrong with that?
You're one to talk, Midori.
You've been getting chocolate from girls for years now.
And from a few guys as well!
That's pretty messed up too.
That reminds me. I overheard some guys talking about their chances of getting chocolate from you.
What?!
You're amazing, Midori!
You're popular with guys and girls!
And yet you're still single.
Sh-Shut up!
Aw, look! She's blushing!
You're so cute, Midori!
I don't care!
Oh wow, do I see tears?
What about you, Tamako?
Huh?
Are you giving chocolate to anyone?
Hmm.
Hmm?
All right, let's begin class!
See you later, then!
Later!
See ya!
Oh?
So you've returned, my girl.
Here, Tamako.
Come again!
Bye!
Five freshly fried croquettes, please!
Coming right up!
The yellowtails are nice today.
I'll take some, then.
Two blocks of firm tofu, please!
Okay!
Thank you, come again!
Huh?
Our market has no Valentine's Day spirit at all!
Whoa!
Got any plans for Valentine's Day?
Vale—
No! I'm hoping I get some chocolate from Sayuri at Usa Bath, even if it's just out of courtesy—
What?
I-It's nothing!
Are you in love, my boy?
Not at all!
We'd better spice things up too.
Yeah, yeah.
Mine
Mochizou's
I want to spice things up!
It totally sucks right now! Over.
What does? Over.
Our...
Our what?
Hey, you! Get off that.
What's wrong?
I can't hear her otherwise.
What were you saying? Our what?
Over.
I want to make our market more exciting!
Oh, right. Our market.
They're holding the weekly meeting over at Usa Bath today, so I was thinking of going.
You should come too, Mochizou.
Over.
Fine. I'll be there.
Thank you!
Over.
You could stand to be a little more excited too.
Shut up.
Meeting Today
Bath opens afterward
Usa Bath
So how'd it go? Did the new one work?
The old one was pretty good too, though.
Oh my, please take a seat.
I like both.
'Sup!
Tamako!
What are you doing here?
'Sup!
Oh, what's this? My son and Tamako are here today too?
Valentine's Day
What's with that T-shirt?
Entrepreneurs need to keep up with the times, Mamedai. That's just common sense.
Common sense? All I hear from you is common nonsense!
There they go again.
What?! Nonsense? You wanna fight about it?
Stop it, old man!
I apologize, Dad.
Don't you dare call me Dad!
Ah, I'm sorry!
Here you go!
Thank you!
Er...
Well then,
let's start today's Usagiyama Market meeting.
Let's hare it for Usagi!
Usagiyama!
As usual, we're a market...
...full of spirit!
First on today's agenda:
Looks like Tamako from Tamaya has a proposal for us all.
What?!
Go for it, Tamako!
Um!
Valentine's Day's comin' up real soon, so we, as Usagiyama Market, should do somethin' to make things more excit—
What is it, Mochizou?
Um!
Valentine's Day's comin' up real soon—
You too?!
Relax, you two.
Damako and Mojizou are lookin' mighty nervous, so we should—
No, no, no!
Stop right there, old man!
What I'm saying is, we should do something to make Usagiyama Market more interesting for Valentine's Day.
That sounds wonderful.
Like what?
Er, something pink-ish, I guess?
I could make some heart-shaped bouquets and put them on sale.
As for us...
We could give away free chocolates with every purchase!
We could run a special sale for couples.
Let's turn our bathwater pink, Dad.
Then I'll arrange some beef in the shape of a heart!
That sounds nice.
Wow!
Things are really heating up, Mochizou!
All right! I'll do everything I can too!
I'll make a commercial for the market!
I'm in the Film Studies Club, you see.
Oh, wow!
Go for it, my son!
I'm against this.
Mochi shops and Valentine's Day have got nothin' to do with each other.
Come on, Dad! We're all getting into it!
Just like the rest of the world!
They're who they are. We're who we are.
We're not the same.
Damn baldy!
I'm not bald yet.
Tamako Market
Not only A,
but also B.
Umm...
Done yet?
Sorry. You can go to the club meeting without me.
Oh no, a split end!
No way!
It wasn't just A. B was the same.
So, "They valued not only their words, but also their feelings."
Your hair's really pretty, Midori.
Huh?
You're right.
Excuse me.
What are you—
I'm going to find split ends in Midori's hair!
Stop it, Kanna!
Finish your homework already, Tamako!
I'm so jealous, Midori.
Oh!
Hey there!
Sorry for dragging you into this.
Tamako!
What's with that costume?
Cute, isn't it?
Here you go, Kanna!
Power Udon Noodles.
Gotcha.
Valentine's Day, my ass.
Tamako's doing her usual thing again, but this time everyone's going along with it.
Thanks for waiting.
Huh?! What the hell?!
Valentine Power Udon Noodles.
Come again!
What the hell is this?!
When did they—
Oh, my!
Love is in the air!
I want her
to tell me
she loves me.
Yes, this is a market in love!
Let's all celebrate Valentine's Day hare, in Usagiyama!
Bunny bunny, bounce bounce.
Tokiwa, cut.
And that's scene.
You two, loosen up a bit.
You're useless like that.
What'd you just say, Mochizou?!
Don't be a jerk!
Maybe I should nail you with a hammer.
I'll pound you into mochi dough.
It's fun just watching them.
Do it right next time, okay?
What are those youngsters up to, my dear An?
They're making a commercial for the market.
Commercial?
An advertisement.
Oh, really?
Midori!
Grandpa!
Come here a second.
How's our Valentine's Day special?
You'll make an appearance in Tokiwa Hall's commercial, right?
Of course.
No way!
I wish you'd do that "Don'tcha want some toys?!" thing you used to do when you were a kid, though.
S-Stop that, Grandpa!
You're so cute, Midori!
How about that Valentine?!
Everybody loves...
somebody!
Amazing!
That's so cool!
Wow.
"Everybody loves somebody."
All right, let's go.
Come forth, my prince's bride!
Eek!
What the heck are you doing, bird?
Filming a commercial!
So this is the rumored talking bi—
Oh, my girl!
Awfully bold, aren't we?
I'm allergic to birds!
All right! Let's pull it together and go for another take!
The girls in this town are rather lively, aren't they?
A little to the left, Tamako.
Like this?
That's good.
Now smile.
Like this?
Great!
Anko!
Take over for a bit.
Sure.
Thanks.
Sorry!
Shall we go for coffee, my girl?
Hello!
Pardon me.
Welcome.
I understand, my girl.
Understand what?
Your chest aches, does it not?
I'm not—
But you mustn't fall for me.
Who'd fall for a bird?!
No need to hide it.
Also, it's not like that.
Everyone has feelings they can't put into words.
At least, I think so.
That's why they ache inside.
Since the very first day
When I fell for you
I still kept it, snugly hidden in a closet
In the blink of an eye, I take off into the azure
For having pilfered a bit of candy cane
Sorry, Dad.
Did you finish cleaning up already?
I'll take care of the rest.
Are you still mad?
Hey, Da—
Huh?
I tried putting chocolate inside.
"Eat these together and you'll know how your partner feels."
They're Lovey-Dovey Heart Mochi.
Pfft!
"Lovey-dovey!"
We're not doing this if you don't put a sock in it right now!
Sorry.
Yeah, I think I'd rather not do this.
I'm sorry! I think they're great!
Let's make these and sell 'em!
Thanks a lot, Dad!
Sis.
Give this back to Mocchi.
Thanks for helping out today, Anko.
The bird took Midori away somewhere, so I had to yell "cut!" all the time!
Inbox
Tamako
Our bird...
Sorry. I hear our
bird caused you
some trouble.
My girl,
you should try putting some sunflower seeds in your mochi.
Some fruits might be good too.
Kiwis, bananas, mangoes...
Oh, it's from Midori!
The girl with the yellow hair, eh? Let's see.
You're in the way.
Inbox             932
Midori
Don't mention it
It's my bad for leaving
halfway through.
I'm looking forward to
the commercial, though!
Tell that gentlemanly
bird I said hi.
Inbox             932
Midori
Don't mention it
It's my bad for leaving
halfway through.
I'm looking forward to
the commercial, though!
Tell that gentlemanly
bird I said hi.
Don't mention it
It's my bad for leaving
halfway through.
I'm looking forward to
the commercial, though!
Tell that gentlemanly
bird I said hi.
Don't mention it
It's my bad for leaving
halfway through.
I'm looking forward to
the commercial, though!
Tell that gentlemanly
bird I said hi.
Inbox             932
Don't mention it
It's my bad for leaving
halfway through.
I'm looking forward to
the commercial, though!
Tell that gentlemanly
bird I said hi.
Inbox             932
Don't mention it
It's my bad for leaving
halfway through.
I'm looking forward to
the commercial, though!
Tell that gentlemanly
bird I said hi.
Inbox             932
It's my bad for leaving
halfway through.
I'm looking forward to
the commercial, though!
Tell that gentlemanly
bird I said hi.
Inbox             932
It's my bad for leaving
halfway through.
I'm looking forward to
the commercial, though!
Tell that gentlemanly
bird I said hi.
Inbox             932
She says hi.
This is weird.
You can't plug it in?
It has been ages since we've used this.
Is it broken?
Maybe a karate chop will fix it.
Usagiyama Market
Hey! This is a market in love!
You! How the hell are you doing that?!
What's this?
What's going on?
Oh no, what's happening?!
It's a market in love.
Let's celebrate Valentine's Day hare in Usagiyama Market!
Bunny bunny, bounce bounce!
Tamako really loves the market, doesn't she?
Right.
Everybody's free to love somebody.
Usagiyama Market!
Hey, when you look at it this way, our market's pretty cool, right?!
Right!
Good work, Mr. Bird.
That was great, Mochizou.
Dela!
Where are you right now?
Ehh?!
Every day's hot over here, but the ocean's wonderful as always.
We picked loads of the kiwis and mangoes you love so mu—
Good morning, Midori!
Good morning!
You see, Midori...
This Valentine's Day...
I ended up just giving chocolate to Dad like usual.
To Mamedai,
my father.
From Tamako
I see.
Do you think the day will come when we give chocolate to someone we like?
In your case...
you might not live to see it!
Midori!
That was mean!
Geez!
Some flowers bloom brilliantly, resplendent with colors like a bird of paradise, and some do so subtly.
Feelings, whatever they may be, are like flowers.
And those that bloom in our hearts are the most dear of all.
Hey! You got some nerve, rippin' off one of our creations!
You're the one who's ripping us off!
No way! We were first!
You wanna fight?!
Oh, I do!
How could this be?
Today's Valentine's Day, and yet...
I haven't received a single chocolate!
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
Cold, isn't it?
Tamako here.
Try heating up mochi in the microwave, then adding a dash of chocolate on top. It's delicious!
Try it out sometime!
Episode 3   Gettin' Hot For That Cool Girl
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?