Dela
This is Dela's Bar.
A bar where select guests may immerse themselves in moody music and fancy conversations.
Welcome to Dela's Bar.
Um, there are four of us. Is that all right?
Of course! Welcome, ladies.
An ice tea, please. Lemon.
Do you have roasted green tea?
I'll have hot coffee.
Don't you have sandwiches and stuff here?
I told you this was a bar! A bar!
Why are you making orders like you're in a cafeteria?!
I'm okay with water.
Actually, I'm good. I don't want anything.
That won't do, Shiori.
Here's a Dela's Bar Special Passion Fruits Platter, just for you.
Hey, that's favoritism!
No fair!
Oh, are you all hungry?
I have sweet bean mochi!
One,
two,
three,
four,
five!
Hey, you even have one for me?!
Huh? You don't want it?
N-No, I do! Goodness gracious.
I better clean this stuff up quick.
It totally ruins the atmosphere of Dela's Bar as a high-class and authentic place.
But a bar and sweet bean mochi go surprisingly well together.
It's kinda like belles-lettres.
Stop your random rambling.
Oh, turns out I had one more!
Hey! Just how many are you carrying around?!
Sorry, I can't eat any more.
You shouldn't've eaten so much, Shiori.
You're the one who gave her that much to eat!
I know, right?
It's all right. Sweet bean mochi goes in a different stoma—
They're banned, so put them away!
What? Banned?
We're taking this from the top again. Got it?
My girls,
you are customers of Dela's Bar.
In other words, you are the chosen ones!
The select celebrities!
I don't get it.
We can't be celebrities when they aren't even chosen.
Did you say something?
Nothing at all!
Um...
What's wrong, Ms. Shiori?
This is my first time at a bar.
What should I do?
Oh! That's a good question!
I wish the rest of you girls were as wise as Ms. Shiori.
Hey!
We're underage, so we can't drink alcohol.
You fool.
Huh?
You're greatly mistaken if you think a bar's just a place for drinking!
It's not?
Dela's Bar is
a place that exists for people to enjoy its atmosphere and the conversations here!
You say conversation, but 80% of it is just your one-sided blabbering.
Oh, you pitiful girls.
All of you have such unsatisfying expressions!
Oh, with Ms. Shiori being the exception, of course.
You grouped her with us for a second, didn't you?
Let me teach you myself.
Let me teach you how to become a dignified person such as myself so that you, too, may sell like hot cakes!
Rice cakes?
I said hot cakes! Are you doing this on purpose?!
I have a question!
It seems comrade Tamako'd like to be rice cakes more than hot cakes.
I wanna be smooth, then.
I wonder what I should be.
What about you, Shiori?
I guess... I'll go with rice cakes.
Don't worry, Shiori. You're hot cakes enough in my eyes.
Let me ask you,
is being that pushy one of the techniques to being hot cakes?
I'm better off staying as I am, then.
It's gotta be rice cakes!
Tamako'll be in real trouble if she doesn't cake this seriously, won't she?
But it won't really be an issue if she's not popular.
That's right. Not an issue at all.
Hey, we really should start serving mochi here too.
Oh, right! I still have sweet bean mochi!
I told you it was banned!
This is Dela's Bar.
A bar where I get toyed with by customers who just barge in.