I've been wondering if it's really okay for the Dollars to exist.
I have to...
I have to do something.
No matter what you learn about your partner or see her do, don't turn a blind eye to it.
A regular "gathering of the triumvirate."
She wore a Raira uniform...
a-and had big breasts...
I can't believe it.
I can't believe he'd...
The Yellow Scarves have surrounded some girl.
Where?
Behind the ward office... Oh, they're heading out. It looks like they're taking her somewhere.
What does she looks like?
That uniform...Maybe it's a Raira one? She's wearing a Raira uniform and has glasses...
And she has big breasts.
Why is Sonohara...?
Everyone in the Dollars! This is an emergency!
That's right, we should all help each other!
We can't just let them keep doing whatever they want!
The Yellow Scarves have gone too far!
Well now...
I'll enjoy the rest from the comfort of my living room.
Anyone who's close by, please help out! Everyone come together!
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Are you in the Dollars?
You're the one who made a scene with the black biker, aren't you?
Huh?!
You bitch.
These people...are the Yellow Scarves?
Oh, officer, over here!
Hurry, hurry!
Tsk.
Wait!
Hey!
What did I do...?
This way.
Go straight. There's a door in the back.
I desperately thought I needed to do something.
Where the hell did she go?!
I found the girl. I got her to escape out the back of the Orb Ikebukuro building. They're still after her.
Is anyone near the Orb Ikebukuro building?!
But I've been confused and have done nothing but run away.
Panic! The exit's right there!
The danger is cheaper than the fear!
Why...?
Alright, it goes "click."
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
No fair, Horada!
The gourds, gaurds, guards for the Orb Ikubukuro building are also in the Dollars. Under and out!
Um, the area behind the Orb Ikebukuro building is where I work!
Who are you?
Why...?
Why are you helping me?
Damn...
Are you all right, sir?!
I helped out a bit; just one of the Dollars passing by. Well, I really was thinking about quitting, but...
Don't quit!
You can't quit!
I figured you'd come back.
A dream?
Where'd the girl go?
Is this...a dream?
Move it!
The girl has transformed into a bunny!
Dammit, where'd she go?
You bastard...
Won't you lose her if you don't hurry up?
Dammit!
What are you doing, you idiots?!
Wh-What happened?
The Dollars are screwing with us.
Call for backup!
We're going with numbers on this one!
I'm being helped by people I've never met.
It's like I'm having a dream.
The bunny's safely crossed the overpass!
Togusa, pick her up.
Roger that!
Fighting isn't good.
I'll turn you into sushi.
They're ringing! There're so many of them!
Ours aren't the only phones that're going off, though...
Theirs are, too.
What? A girl in a bunny suit?
A bunny suit?
With big tits?
Yeah. A bunny? Okay.
Where did the bunny go? Whoever sees it, report it immediately!
Is that her?
You can't tell if she's got big tits with that on, though.
She'll just have to show them to us.
But...
...my dream...
...has always been a lie.
Wait!
I'd only been having dreams about a happy family smiling cheerfully.
That's why this isn't a dream.
It's reality.
That's what this hand taught me.
And then, I suddenly realized...
...that he knew about my hand.
Even though he'd never touched it before...
This is...
Um...
How come you never notice what's important until it's too late?
Kida...
Why...?
"Why," you ask?
Do you think it's weird I saved you from that group of Yellow Scarves?
Eh?
That's my erotically cute Anri for you.
That looks really good on you.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What are you doing?
What were you spying on us for?
Tell me, Anri.
What are you after?
I...You...
What about me? Is this my fault?
Am I an idiot for protecting you?
I guess I am.
Don't...say that.
Does Mikado know?
What were you planning to do about him?
I...
Do you...
Do you think you understand him...
Why won't you tell—
Was it fun?! Tricking me and sucking up to him—
What am I...saying...?!
I...
I just didn't want to hurt anyone or have you get hurt.
I've run away from you, too.
I...
There she is!
We found you.
You're in the Dollars, aren't you, bitch?
No, I'm not.
Pft. Don't screw with us.
Don't hide it now.
If you're not part of the Dollars, then what are you?!
You want to know...what I am?
Hm? What?
What are you?
I said, "What are you?"
Oh, that's it! You're a crusader for justice!
You try to tempt us by saying, "Let's protect the peace!"
Well, we want to show you what happens when someone betrays us.
We beat the shit out of them!
What...did I do...?
And so, you can't be the only one without any bruises...
Shut up!
This thing's been going "beep beep beep" all friggin' day!
You think I can read all that?!
What am I going to do about some girl and a bunny?!
Shut up!
Huh?
Huh?!
I found the girl. She's okay. It's all settled.
Because...
Because the fortissimo of Ikebukuro has appeared!
Um...
Hm?
Thank you so much for saving me again.
Who are you?
Hey.
I've turned my phone off for the rest of the day.
See you.
Celty...
The mission was a success!
All hail the Dollars!
We did it! We did it!
This is what we're made of!
There's nothing to be afraid of if we all help each other out!
Thanks, everyone...
I've found it...
...the thing that's most important to me...
Mikado...?
Aww, it's already game-set?
Shizu-chan sure knows when to get involved.
However, this isn't over yet.
With this, I'll soon be able to put them
in check and checkmate at the same time.
Ah, Celty, it came out! Get that mushroom!
Celty, that's totally impossible.
See, that's why I told you to be more careful...
Eh?! Not that!
Celty...
E-Excuse me.
I didn't want to wake you because you were sleeping so soundly.
I-I'm sorry for causing so much trouble.
It's no trouble at all. Just stick around here for a while.
Living by yourself would be dangerous.
Is that alright?
If you need anything, I can go get it.
Th-Thank you very much.
You're taking some time off from school starting today, right?
I already told Mikado about it, so...
You know Ryugamine?
Uhh, yeah, somewhat.
Um, I...
You don't have to worry about anything, Anri.
It's okay! I'm on your side, and this shady-looking guy in white is tr—
is, well, a friend.
Hey, what gives?
Why did you start to write "trustworthy," then stop?
Why, huh?
Celty?!
What a surprise.
What is?
It's just that I didn't know she lived with a guy.
The shogun hasn't shown up since.
Whatever, it doesn't matter. We know what we have to do.
Everyone here knows what we have to do, right?!
We're going to completely crush the Dollars!
I'm calling the police!
Where are you right now?
Those yellow guys are at it again.
They're all fired up.
My friend said someone got totally messed up.
We can't afford to lose. Let's pool our resources like we did before.
What are you thinking about right now?
The Dollars shall disappear.
What? What does that mean?
What? Isn't that our founder?
Our leader's running away?
Does that mean...we're going to disband?
Huh...
Nine thirty-four PM: the Dollars of Ikebukuro announce that they'll disband.
That's not it! To "disappear" equals being
"clearly colorless"—the reason why we're the Dollars!
Our leader's so irresponsible.
No he's not! Believe in him!
Say something!
Explain yourself!
The Dollars shall disappear.
You're the worst.
Huh? We can't access it anymore.
Really?
We can view the front page, but the message boards have been completely closed off.
Hey, what's this mean?
It means he's being serious.
That's enough.
Just drop it.
I had a lot of time to myself, and lots and lots of time to think.
Their faces kept appearing in my thoughts.
Their smiling faces would appear, and just stay there.
Um...
Is it alright...if I have a talk with you?
Of course. I wanted to talk with you, too, Anri.
I feel like I can tell you everything, since you know about me...
I see.
I understand.
So, those two guys you're always with don't know about your true identity.
Kida and Ryugamine are always helping me out.
And yet, I...
First, we have to stop this conflict.
Alright.
I guess the only thing you can do is discuss it with Mikado.
Um...how well do you know him...?
Anri, how much do you know about Mikado?
Eh?
So you don't know...
He's in the same boat as you.
He's hiding something significant from you because you're a close friend and you're important to him.
Anyway, you should ask him yourself.
I'll bring him here.
Don't get any weird ideas while I'm out.
Don't bombard her with questions or
perform any crazy experiments on her.
I know. Trust me.
Okay, I will.
I won't be long, Anri.
Celty...
I...don't want to keep running away.
Let's get out of here!
If you're going to hate someone, hate the guy who ordered us to do this—Kida Masaomi!
Why couldn't I move that one time?
What was I hesitating for?
What was I afraid of?
Saki, I won't be afraid anymore.
I won't run away anymore.
Next Time: All Mixed Up.