I can tell you,
but can I take your soul?
Okay, as long as
we can save Takuto!
Well then...
Well, I will have you kiss me.
A-A kiss?
Yes, it's a ceremony for the promise
to entrust your soul.
If you are serious about
entrusting your soul,
then you should be able to do it.
Mikki...
I-If I kiss...
If I kiss you,
you'll really teach me how to
prevent Takuto from
becoming a ghost?
Do you want to go
that far to save Takuto?
I want to save him!
It's only natural that I do!
Natural? I've never heard of a human
helping a Death Spirit, even in fairytales.
But... But Takuto
is my precious...
Precious what?
Precious...
friend.
Hmm... A friend. Then I'll ask you,
what is a friend?
Can you do anything
for a friend?
I-I don't know very well,
but I feel that if there is something
that I can do for my friend,
I'd do anything I can.
Takuto is a Death Spirit who
came to cut off your life.
Do you understand that?
I understand that, but...
But that doesn't matter at all!
It doesn't matter whether
you're a Death Spirit or not.
A friend is a friend!
Why?
How can this child work
so hard for somebody else?
I believe that loving someone means
having that kind of tranquil big heart.
You probably don't
understand, do you?
That's your misfortune, Izumi.
My misfortune?
I-I understand.
If you'll teach me how to
save Takuto, then I...
If Takuto is really going to be saved...
I-Izumi, by all means!
What's so funny?!
I think I'll decline.
Huh? What do you mean?
Actually, I don't know of a way to
stop him from becoming a ghost.
W-What?
See you later, Mikki.
Please wait!
I beg of you,
I need to save Takuto!
So... So...
Izumi!
If you find out something,
please tell me!
I haven't disappeared yet.
Takuto, what's wrong?
Mitsuki.
Were you in pain again?
S-Stupid, that's not
the case at all!
More importantly, are you making
progress preparing for your concert?
Y-Yeah, of course.
Good. Jeez, you better not become
careless just because I'm not around.
Got it?
Yes.
Takuto...
Gosh...
Why are old books so heavy?!
Hey Takuto.
Huh?
Are you all right?
What do you mean?
I mean...
Takuto, please don't go away.
Please don't.
I'm so tired.
I'm home.
So that's it?
I was wondering what you were going
to say with such a somber face.
Stupid, I won't disappear that easily!
But...
My goodness... Don't worry
about unnecessary things.
Just think about
your concert right now.
Takuto...
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
If loving someone was going
to feel like this, I wish I never—
Mitsuki?
I'm practicing for the concert!
Listen, Takuto.
Okay.
My tears won't stop.
Both Mitsuki and Takuto
are working so hard.
Each one thinking
about the other...
Well, then.
I'm going to do
some investigation.
I might find a hint for preventing
him from becoming a ghost.
All right, what have we here?
Then, please also give
my regards to Full Moon.
Yes, thank you
for all your work.
Oh? Is that you, Ms. Oshige?
Oh, Mr. Todoroki!
Good morning.
Huh? Where's Full Moon?
Oh, yes. Full Moon is preparing
for her concert right now.
Oh yeah, I heard. So Full Moon is in
seclusion doing special lessons?
She's really putting
her heart into it!
In seclusion? Who said such a thing?
Gosh, this industry...
Mr. Todoroki!
Yeah, I'll be right over.
Okay then, we'll catch up later.
I'll look forward to the concert!
Thank you very much.
Whatever the rumors may be,
Mitsuki can't be
forcing herself right now.
If Mitsuki cannot transform to Full Moon
on the day of the concert...
Don't think about such a thing!
Takuto and Meroko were saying that
they are definitely going to transform her,
so I have to work to
make this concert a success.
Ow, ow! So hot!
All right, what does it say here?
Drip one drop of the morning dew
collected from the roses on his eyelids
and recite a spell.
Okay then!
Mero-Mero!
Morning Dew of Roses!
Well then...
Now, for the spell. S-Susha,
doriapisuku, ekkutirijira, furikapasu!
Hey.
What have you started now?
H-Huh?
What do you mean "Huh?"
I-I mean... Sorry.
This isn't working at all!
Meroko?
What are you doing?
Oh, I see.
It's a legend of
the human world after all.
Of course it wouldn't
work on a Death Spirit.
I keep on making
a bunch of mistakes.
That's not true.
You did it for Takuto's sake.
What you're doing is not wrong at all.
Mitsuki...
What are you doing?
I-Izumi!
Izumi, why are you here?
What in the world do you want?
Huh?
I did little bit of research on how to
stop him from becoming a ghost.
You researched for us?
Yes.
Then Takuto can be saved?
Possibly...
Wait a minute, is that true Izumi?
It's Mikki and your choice to
believe me or not. Which will it be?
I beg of you! Please teach us!
This is the Mystic Lily that
blossoms in the Spirit World.
It's also known as
the Flower of Forgetfulness.
When you eat it,
you lose your entire memory.
Hence it's name.
This will save Takuto?
Yes. I believe a Death Spirit
who recovers his memory
becomes a ghost because of
the attachment to his life on earth.
That's why, if his memory is erased
with this Flower of Forgetfulness...
Erase his memory?
Does that mean his memories as
a Death Spirit will also be erased?
Yes, he'll forget everything...
even about you two.
Oh no.
Takuto is going to
forget about us?
I couldn't find anything else
that would work.
I think this is probably the only way
to stop him from becoming a ghost.
Izumi, here, let's eat some
roasted sweets potatoes.
Wait! If I remember correctly,
the Flower of Forgetfulness is...
Yes.
The flower only blooms on
the day of the lunar eclipse
in the Spirit World calendar.
When is that?
It's today!
What? Then, is there a chance?
This Flower of Forgetfulness
blooms in a cave
at the Forbidden Forest
in the Spirit World.
Normally, the entrance to this cave
is closed and you can't enter.
But the entrance opens only
during the lunar eclipse
when the flower blooms.
The flower possesses
a strong power
and does not allow
anyone to approach it.
It's such a powerful flower
that even Death Spirit power
becomes ineffective near it.
Is that so?
- But for Takuto, I—
- Mero.
You'd be breaking the laws
of the Spirit World.
Who knows what kind of punishment
will be handed down.
Are you prepared for that?
Nobody will wake up with this.
It's now connected
with the Spirit World.
Now Mitsuki, after I enter the cave,
measure the time with this.
I'm going to lose my sense
of time inside the cave.
You have to get out of the cave
before all of the sand falls, right?
Yeah, if I don't do it in time,
I won't be able to come out
until the next lunar eclipse.
If that happens...
Meroko!
Are you really okay? Isn't this
a serious violation of the regulations?
If it's about violating regulations,
I've already done that many times.
Being such good friends
with you is actually a violation.
Meroko...
I also want to help Takuto
as much as you. Now, I'll be off.
Meroko! Be careful!
It's been so long.
Hey, Meroko?
What are you doing here today?
I bet you made a blunder again and
were called in by the Division Chief.
Y-Yeah.
I suppose it's
something like that.
Well, I'm in a hurry so...
Hey, wait Meroko!
Sorry, I don't have time
to hang out right now!
Oh boy, she really went ahead.
She has some courage.
The lunar eclipse
hasn't started yet.
Looks like I'll be on time.
Huh?
Meroko!
Oh no!
What a forest...
I found it!
There it is!
Thank goodness.
What?
The lunar eclipse has started.
Please make it in time.
Meroko, are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
Oh right, I can't use my powers
inside the cave.
That's...
the Flower of Forgetfulness!
You can do it, Meroko!
A small wound
like this is nothing.
Meroko, run away! Meroko!
Meroko, the time...
There is only about
half remaining.
Just a little longer,
I'll make it on time!
Huh?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Meroko!
Meroko...
Meroko! Please return now!
I can't...return.
But if you keep on going—
Mitsuki!
I finally found something
that I can do for Takuto.
Meroko...
That's why I'm not going to
give up until the end!
What...I can do...
What I can do for
Meroko right now...
Why do I like you so much?
Your voice echoes and
it sounds almost sad.
This is probably
the only thing I can do.
Meroko, don't give up.
Mitsuki...
- Why do I like you so much?
- Your voice echoes and
- it sounds almost sad.
- Up to now who was supporting me?
- I realize, now that I'm far away
- what was supporting me.
Why do I like you?
That's too easy to answer.
Meroko!
Meroko! Meroko!
No way...
Mitsuki.
Meroko!
Your feelings reached me.
Meroko! Meroko,
get a hold of yourself!
Meroko!
This is the Flower
of Forgetfulness?
Takuto doesn't need to
become a ghost now.
Thank you, Meroko.
No, I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
I was able to get it with
the help of your singing.
Oh, there you two are!
Good morning, Takuto.
Good morning!
Huh? What happened to you?
Oh, this? I had a little fight with
the cat on the second block.
Oh yeah?
More importantly, I was thinking about
the production for the upcoming concert,
and I was recalling all of
your past performances.
Like, didn't we grow wings
the first time?
And after that, we shined
the pendant at the solo concert.
Isn't it going to be your last concert?
Let's make it incredible.
So it will become memorable
for everyone who watches it!
What's up?
Oh, Takuto, it's because what you said
was unexpectedly sentimental!
What does that mean?
It's fine, it's fine!
No, it's not!
- After Takuto's memory is erased,
- But still, you're really roughed up!
- we can't hang out like this anymore.
- How rude!
Whose fault
do you think it is
- Staying a Death Spirit
- that I look like this?!
- by losing his memories
- You said it was the cat on
the second block, right?
- or becoming a ghost
- Y-Yeah, it's because of the cat.
- by holding on to the memories.
- The cat, the cat, the cat!
- Which one would make Takuto happy?
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Takuto... If... I'm only saying if,
but if there were a way to
prevent you from becoming a ghost,
what would you do?
Huh? If there were a way,
I would've already done it.
But you become a ghost because you
regain your memory, right? Then...
You're saying I should
lose my memory?
No thanks. I wouldn't go
as far as to lose my memory.
Takuto...
Next time on Full Moon:
"I Can't Confess!"
- Look forward to it!