[slashing]
[crackling]
[roaring]
[growling]
[Heimdall] Ragnarok round one
has ended with Thor as its victor.
The human race is one step closer
to its inevitable end!
[heavy metal music playing]
[sorrowful music playing]
[chuckles] He went out with a smile.
That's Lü Bu for you.
[sniffling]
Indeed.
He couldn't have died
a more fitting death.
[grunting]
Let's pour one out for him.
Hm.
A toast to our comrade.
Here's to the honorable, Lü Bu.
The great Flying General.
[sighing] Hm.
[male god 1] Did you genuinely think
your champion stood a chance?
Think again, you foolish mortals.
[male god 2] The power of the gods!
[male god 3] Bow down!
Offer sacrifice!
Ho! Yes! Are you starting
to get it, humans?
You can try all you like,
but you can't defeat Thor!
[voice breaking] Why do the gods
sound so pleased amongst themselves?
They're like children.
Aren't they supposed to be
the ones in charge here?
Hey, where are you going?
Right then. Come along.
The exit is this way, Master Thor.
Huh?
He won, didn't he?
What reason could he possibly have
to look so annoyed?
[whinnying]
[snuffling]
[snorting and whinnying]
Yes, me too, Red Hare.
Now that my liege
has fought his last battle and perished,
what meaning is there in living anymore?
None.
Everyone, may we all perish with him.
[all yelling]
Huh? Wait...
Let us follow after our beloved general!
[yelling]
[whinnying]
[all yelling]
Stop at once!
The round is over already. You lost.
I said that's enough, so knock it off.
- Very well.
- Huh?
I guess this one's for him.
[crackling]
[exclaiming fearfully]
You asked for it.
So here's a farewell present
for your dear liege.
A glorious honor! May the name
of our lord echo in the thunder!
[all yelling]
Whoa, what was that sound just now?
[rumbling]
Wait, Brünnhilde.
Slow down a bit, will you?
Uh... Hey...
Do... Do we know
what'll happen with Lü Bu and Randgriz?
They took a real beating. What's next?
What do you mean, "next"?
That's a foolish question.
[wind whistling]
[shattering]
[Brünnhilde] This was
a battle of souls, Göll.
Once a soul is shattered,
there is no way to repair it.
It won't come back to life or be reborn.
One is simply reduced to dust,
floating in the universe.
Huh? Floating where?
Niflheimr.
In other words,
the soul completely disappears.
There's no afterlife.
So there is no next.
If you would be so kind, then go ahead
and offer yourself, Randgriz.
As you wish, sister.
My pleasure.
[whimpering]
Why? That's awful.
How can you say that
as if it's no big deal?
We'll never be able
to see our sister again!
Why? Are you gonna pretend
you won't miss Randgriz's beautiful smile?
Are you even remotely sad that
we basically watched her funeral?
Am I sad?
You think we can beat the gods
by crying our eyes out?
Look, do we really have to go this far?
[sobbing] Just to win
this stupid challenge?
There is much at stake.
The fate of all humanity
rests on our shoulders.
[sobbing loudly]
The first round is now over.
Instead of dwelling on the past,
we must prepare for the future.
Our next order of business,
is to select our representative
for round two.
I don't know.
Lü Bu was the toughest hero.
And despite the odds,
he still couldn't defeat Thor in the end.
[dejectedly] So who else even could?
[beeping]
Excellent question.
For our next battle,
why don't we send out this fellow?
Huh?
He's a human who despises the gods
more than anybody else.
Let's bet on the man
with the strongest will.
[gasping]
Isn't that file number...
one?
[crowd cheering]
We're back.
You may recall the gruesome state
of the ring at the end of round one.
But thanks to divine intervention
it has been restored!
Is everyone ready?
Because it's about time for round two!
[gods cheering]
Those weak meatsacks
don't stand a chance against us.
We'll make this pathetic fool
go down as easy as the last.
[humans shouting angrily]
We're all counting on you!
Next up for the humans,
representing the hope of mankind,
may he carry it through the entire match!
And here he comes!
[rumbling]
[rock music playing]
[gods exclaiming]
[humans exclaiming]
[overlapping animal sounds]
Huh? Who in the world
could have predicted such an entrance?
"Rule over the fish in the sea,
the birds in the sky,
and over every living creature
that moves on the ground!"
That's right.
Thus did god bless our challenger,
making him in his own image.
To think the day would come
that this man would rebel,
and stand up against his creator!
- [humans gasping]
- But there's no possible way!
Oh my goodness, it's actually him!
[Heimdall] In other words,
you could say he's a man among men.
Talk about a man's man!
The only thing he holds
is in the weight of his fists!
A keen disciple of raw, unarmed combat!
The originator of original sin!
In the whole of history, no one
despises the gods more than this guy!
If there's anyone who deserves
to sock it to 'em,
there's no debate, it has to be him.
He's the father of humanity.
Introducing...
[shouting] Adam!
MICHELANGELO
Ah, a beautiful work of artistry.
Sour.
[angelic choir music playing]
MANKIND FILE
- Could it be? The first mortal?
- What nonsense!
How's a puny thing like him
supposed to take on a deity?
The boy's a total shrimp
compared to the last guy.
I must say, I disagree.
I think he's rather dashing.
Oh my! What an unexpected
turn of events we have.
Even the gods are making a commotion
over his appearance.
See that, folks?
That's what you call star-power!
On that note,
who might be facing off against him?
Man's progenitor is no slouch.
Well, we had the strongest of the Norse
gods representing us in round one.
This time it's the deadliest
of Hindu Devas!
Let's check him out!
What the...
- [tinkling]
- Huh?
What's with the sudden hold up?
[Brünnhilde] Hm?
What's that? A last minute change?
So who's next?
Wait, say that again.
[stammering] You're kidding!
[sorrowful string music playing]
That music piece sounds familiar.
I know this song. Master Bach composed it.
W. A. MOZART
CHILD PRODIGY
A partial arrangement named "Air on
the G String" from my orchestral suite!
However,
in all my years of writing
chorales and cantatas,
I've never heard
a more heart-rending performance.
My stars, what a heavenly rendition!
Huh? That's Master Hermes, though.
Hold on. Is he actually
going to be the next opponent?
But he... He wasn't on the list,
so there has to be some mistake, right?
There's no way!
[clearing throat]
Apologies for
the technical difficulties, folks.
Moving along.
I shall finish introducing
our fighters for round two!
In this corner, there's Adam,
you know, the man-among-men man.
And up against him is...
this gentlegod!
[stammering] Actually...
it's the one standing behind him!
Why hello there, everybody!
Ah!
So please be gentle!
[screaming]
[groaning] Not that creepy old fart!
- [gods clamoring]
- Is this really happening?
Master Zeus is
the contender for round two?
Seriously? What's that
grandfather doing up there?
Is he also a god?
Can he throw a punch without keeling over?
Oh!
Ha!
Ho!
[snapping]
Come on, maestro!
Hit it!
Hmm.
My goodness.
Let's hope I haven't gotten too rusty.
[music stops]
It's been several millennia
since I've played that tune.
I shall herald you to battle.
SLAYER ON THE G-STRING!
- [hard rock string music playing]
- [chuckling]
Wait, this melody. Could it be?
Why, it's "Slayer on the G-string"!
- Amazing!
- A celestial performance fit for a god!
What can I say,
this song always gets me pumped.
Oh yeah!
[Heimdall] Adam was
the first man to walk the Earth,
which makes him the father of mankind.
Therefore, Zeus being Zeus makes him,
the father of the gods!
Of rather, he's the GFOC!
Godfather of the Cosmos!
The holy patriarch of the entire universe!
[gods chanting] GFOC! GFOC!
- [GFOC chant continues]
- [Zeus laughing]
- [crowd cheering wildly]
- [GFOC chant continues]
[Zeus groaning]
[chuckling]
[chanting continues]
Do you have any idea
what it is we're looking at, Brünnhilde?
Why are they acting so excited?
Haven't got a clue.
What are those creepy gyrations?
- So weird.
- Who does that old geezer think he is?
[Heimdall] The gift
of creation is at his whim.
Whatever displeases him
is sent back to the void!
A timeless tyrant, and absolute Olympian!
[chanting continues]
Eons ago, he waged a war
with the mightiest beings in the universe.
The clash of the titans!
In the end, he overthrew his own father,
killing Cronus himself.
- Yeah.
- He is the biggest battle buff ever!
Truly the infinite among infinites,
a real god of gods!
Give it up for...
Z... Z... Zeus!
Oh yeah!
ZEUS
[gods cheering]
No, it's the ruler of the gods!
Wha... What's happening here?
Aren't we in enough trouble already?
I... I... I know he's strong,
but why's the final boss starting now
instead of during the last round?
I don't know. But I didn't think
that he'd show up this early.
[fireworks launching]
[laughing] Oh yeah!
[gods cheering]
[laughing]
I thought I was prepared, but...
I never expected this.
[Japanese pop ballad playing]