Be sure to watch TV in a well-lit room
and a safe distance away.
Full Moon wo Sagashite
Original Subtitles by a.f.k.
Searching for a Full Moon
Toosugiru koi no michishirube
To
The road to love is far too long for me.
Mou suki wo fuyasenai Non Non
Mo
There's no way for me to love you any more. Nope! Nope!
Yume no naka wa maru de betsu sekai
Yu
It's as if the world inside my dream is a completely different one
Sutoreeto ni omoi mo ieru no ni
Su
where I can even tell you how I really feel.
Okiniiri no fuku wo mainichi kichau no
I wear my favorite clothes every day
Ano hito no mesen ga kocchi ni chiratsuitekimasu you ni
so that person will turn his gaze towards me.
I LIKE YOU no kotoba nara ieru
"I like you!" If I could bring myself to say it out loud
Renai soudan suru koto mo dekiru
I would even be able to talk about love with you.
Anata no haato ni tsutsumaretai no ni
I want to be tucked into your heart
Doushitara tsutsunde kureru no
and I will do anything to be there.
I bU wo anata kara kikitai
"I love you!" Those are the words I want to hear from you
Kisu suru shunkan no chikai kokyuu wo
and my breath will quicken when we kiss.
Anata wo mane suru atashi wa ichiban kawaiku naru hazu
A
The me who is performing for you is the cutest of them all!
Transcription, TLC, Editing: Zalis (ReDone-Subs)
Retiming, Encoding: E_B (Soldado)
Typesetting, KFX: shani-san and E_B (Soldado)
QC: May-chan, Yogicat
Itsu kara uso desho itsu kara
Since when? You’re lying, right?
Donna fuu ni dou yatte doko made shitteru no?
How did you do it and how far did you go?
Watashi ni wa nai mono motteru no?
Does she have something I don’t?
Souzou bakari ga fukurami dashiteru
These constant imaginations just keep piling on...
Everyone, thank you for coming today!
Here's the last song.
I-It can't be.
E-Eichi-kun?
So, your dream of becoming a singer came true?
Y-Yeah. What about your dreams?
They did.
That's great!
Mitsuki...
I... love you.
Eichi-kun...
Eichi-kun!
A dream?
Eichi-kun?
NO MATTER WHAT, I WANT TO SING!
Nee miagete
Say, won't you look up?
konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
The night sky stretches so far...
sou sugu ni...
Yes... very soon...
I'll be fine, right?
Sure.
konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
The night sky stretches so far...
sou sugu ni...
Right... very soon...
It hurts...
Mitsuki-san.
How many times have I told you
to stop doing that?
Music is such a vile thing.
It reminds me of your father;
it makes me sick.
I'm very sorry. But I...
Don't talk back!
Okay...
Has your fever gone down?
Yes.
Is that so? That's good.
Dr. Wakaouji is here to see you.
So behave yourself.
Dr. Wakaouji!
Sorry for calling you in during your vacation.
Please don't worry about it.
So, how's her health?
She seems to be doing much better this morning.
Really?
Good morning, Mitsuki-chan.
Good morning!
The lump is looking a bit swollen and red. Is it okay if I apply some medicine on it?
Yes, please.
All right, all done!
Thank you very much.
Um... Dr. Wakaouji.
What is it, Mitsuki-chan?
Can we pretend that you're taking me
to the hospital for a detailed checkup today?
You need an alibi to get out of the house?
So, where do you plan on going?
Ta-da!
Seed Records' Debut Artist Audition!
Notification of Passing the First Review!
Huh?
I'm keeping this a secret from Grandma, so...
No way.
Aw...
Just yesterday, didn't you have to leave school early with a fever?
Then there's that swelling in your throat.
As your doctor, I can't allow you to do that.
But, I finally managed to
get past the first review...
You can't sing in a loud voice in your current condition, now can you?
You can think about auditioning
after your throat gets better.
Mitsuki-chan, let's try an operation while the tumor's still small.
I don't want any surgery.
Because... I might lose my voice, right?
We'll cross that bridge when we get there.
I can't guarantee that it won't happen.
If that's the case, I don't want the surgery.
Doctor...
What's even more terrifying than dying...
...is not being able to sing
for the rest of my life.
That's why...
I'm sorry.
Mitsuki-chan...
Um... it's about Mitsuki-chan...
Could you possibly convince her... to go through with the operation?
I've already suggested it time and time again,
but she still refuses to listen.
For heaven's sake... She's just
as stubborn as my late daughter was.
She is unable to give in!
I see.
Another failure...
I wonder if I'll have to wait
until my throat gets better.
Mitsuki, let's make a promise.
Until we meet again,
we'll work hard to reach our dreams.
I'll become an astronomer.
And you'll become a singer.
It's a promise, okay?
Yes...
But, just when will that happen...
...Eichi-kun?
All right.
W-Who are you? And how'd you
come out of the wall?
So she's the one? Kouyama Mitsuki, age 12.
Huh? Why does he know my name?
Wait a minute, Takuto.
A-Another one came out! Who ARE you guys?
Were you trying to lose me?
You're just too slow.
Hey now, is that the attitude
you should have towards your elder?
You don't have to bring up your seniority
every time, you know.
What!?
E-Excuse me.
Who might... you be?
You... can see us?
Yes.
W-W-W-Why can she see us!?
Living humans shouldn't be able to see us, right!?
You're kidding...
But... I can see you.
What do we do in this kind of situation?
If it's come to this, we have no choice.
Let's do it!
Yeah!
It's absurd to remain unknown
when our cover is blown...
We are the Shinigami, the ones
who silence the tears of children.
[Shinigami: Gods of Death]
Takuto!
Meroko!
Together, we are...
...Negi Ramen!
Y-You call yourselves Negi Ramen!
It sounds so tasty!
Takuto, I really can't stand our duo's name.
It sounds so good.
Just deal with it. The chief picked it for us.
Bunny ears and kitty ears... So soft!
It's because we're in the Pediatrics Division.
Pediatrics? Shinigami have kids, too?
Eh... kids?
Now that I think about it, if you're Shinigami...
Did you come to pick me up?
That's what we're here for.
You're not supposed to say that!
It's too late for that.
So I'm going to die today.
Just pretend you didn't hear that.
You're not supposed to die for another year.
One more year?
Is it because... my cancer gets worse?
Well, that could be why.
Ah... sorry. Please, don't cry.
She's not crying.
Well, while we have the chance...
Let's see, In times like these...
Um, here...
Actually...
...there are people who are
trying to prevent your death.
Eh?
Then... I'm not going to die?
No. It doesn't work that way.
Fate cannot be altered.
I see.
If I only have one year left to live,
I can't hesitate any longer.
Hey, Takuto...
You're going on and on and on and on...
Just what are you trying to do!?
I'm going to report this to the chief.
So what? Now that she's seen us,
she can't un-see us.
We just have to wait
for the year to run out, and...
Huh?
Where'd she go?
Takuto, over there!
Wait, you little kid!
Stop right there!
Hey, you!
Wait up!
Taxi!
Oh, man! I was just a single step behind...
Get out of the way!
I-Idiot!
Shinigami-san, thank you.
I've made up my mind to audition.
If I only have a year left, I've just got to
become a singer before then.
Is this the place?
This is it, Eichi-kun.
I'll be sure to keep...
...the promise we made!
Where'd she go off to?
She seemed like a good girl,
but she played us for fools.
Oh, she's over there!
Really?
What's she doing?
Does it matter?
Hey, wait! If we approach her like this,
she'll run away again.
Heh, I know that.
Sheesh, why won't it open?
Is there a key around here somewhere?
It's open!
All right! Nowhere to go but up!
Yep!
They're so cute! I wonder what these are.
Decorations, perhaps?
Let's see how it feels...
We caught you.
Ah, S-Shinigami-san.
We can't have you go running off like this.
Now, be a good girl and
come back to the house with us.
Yep, yep.
P-Please wait a minute!
I want to go through the audition.
I don't want to just go home like this!
Then why were you trying to get in from there?
Yeah. Why not just use the front door?
I don't look like I'm 16, so I can't.
Do I look like I'm 16 to you?
Well... no, you don't.
That's it, I'm going in through here.
Quit it, you dummy! It's dangerous!
What if you get hurt?
But if I don't hurry, the registration for the audition will be over.
I... have to become a singer-
Did something happen?
If I... talk too... loud...
My throat...
Then isn't it impossible for you to audition?
But...
Please, if I only have one year left to live...
Please, at least let me audition.
If I fail, I'll be a good girl and do what you say.
So... I beg you!
You're serious about this?
I get it.
I'll make you 16 years old.
I'll also make it so your body is healthy...
...as long as you're in the form of a 16-year-old.
Take that.
When I give the signal,
it'll start circulating throughout your body.
You'll feel weird,
but you'll just have to endure it.
That's a good girl.
You can't feel the difference?
No...
Why not check yourself out over there?
Wow! I'm really 16 years old!
Thank you, Shinigami-san!
It was nothing...
Thank you so much!
No problem at all...
Hey! Get away from Takuto!
Are you satisfied?
Well... I want to try dyeing my hair, too.
What are you doing, Takuto?
What?
You're disobeying our orders from above...
...by using the Dead Arts on a human.
If they find out, you'll be in for it.
Yeah...
Surely you don't have feelings for that girl.
Huh?
No! You're mine, Takuto!
I'm never gonna give you up!
Since when was I your possession?
Don't worry. It's not like that...
Huh?
If she still has regrets chaining her to this world when she dies,
she might refuse to come with us.
And we can't have that.
I guess that's true, but what are you going to do if she makes it?
She'll have even more to regret.
It'll be fine. There's no way she'll make it so easily.
Once she turns 16 and goes through an audition...
...only to fail and to have to face reality,
she won't have a shred of regret left.
Wow... All the girls here are really cute.
I wonder if I look too plain.
Everyone's staring at me.
Do I look strange or something?
Or maybe just lame?
Can I... sit next to you?
Uh... sure.
What agency are you from?
Agency?
You're not part of a theatrical group
or a recording agency?
No.
Will I not be able to make it
if I'm not part of an agency?
Unfortunately, it's probably impossible for you.
Just between us...
They've already decided on who they're selecting.
What!? Then why are we auditioning!?
I-I'm very sorry. Sorry.
Wasn't that scary?
Why is that?
This audition will get lots of coverage on the morning news and the talk shows.
With all the attention...
...from getting "chosen" on TV
from among tens of thousands of girls,
it's the perfect chance to turn a newcomer into a big seller.
Is that so?
You... already knew that.
Yeah. Sorry.
The judging you've all
been waiting for will now begin.
Bye, then.
Please come in when your number is called.
To start, will Number 1 please come in?
Ah, so that's how it is.
I feel kinda... let down.
I thought this was a world based
more on talent than anything else.
Don't say that you want to be a singer ever again.
Grandma always discouraged me.
You should wait until your throat
is better before you audition.
Dr. Wakaouji tried to stop me, too.
You have one more year before you die.
One more year.
What am I... doing here?
Eichi-kun...
Number 21.
Number 21, please come in.
I'm Number 21, Kouyama Mitsuki.
Pleased to meet you.
What genre of music do you like?
I like... Japanese... pop.
If you become a singer,
what type of music would you like to sing?
Well. I'd just want to sing...
...since I like singing.
Why don't you sing for us, then?
Cue the music.
There's no way she'll make it...
...if she's going to be this  nervous.
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's only one thing that's never gonna change:
zutto egai-
...the dream I've-
Wait, stop for a second.
Your voice is too soft.
Sing with a louder voice.
Eh... louder?
Is something wrong with your throat?
Does it hurt?
Then I guess it's impossible for you to sing.
Impossible...
It really was... impossible...
Please excuse me!
Are you going to run away?
Shinigami-san!
Your throat is fine, so sing.
You like to sing, right?
You really enjoy singing, Mitsuki. And I...
...love to hear you sing.
That's right...
I'm very sorry. Can you please let me try one more time?
Uh... sure.
Cue the music again.
It's fine if it's painful.
No matter how much it hurts inside...
...whether it's pain, or love...
...it's all part of my dream!
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's just one thing that's never gonna change:
Zutto egaiteta yume
The dream that I have always been drawing.
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
How would I, as I am right now
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
look to those small eyes I used to have?
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, won't you look up? The night sky stretches so far.
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Wow! I have such a loud voice!
u
ni
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
It doesn't hurt at all!
ya
ku
ka
ra
I can sing in a voice like this!
ha
ya
ku
Full Moon wo sagashite
and find the full moon.
Full
Moon
This is fun!
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now.
ssho
Day by Day
Day
by
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
I hold the past fate dealt and the hope tomorrow brings here in my heart.
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain.
ssho
More and more
More
and
more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
Mo
tto
mo
She's...
Many Thanks for You!
Many
Thanks
for
You!
Um... I'm done...
Call Miya-san! Get Ishikawa-san, too!
Okay!
Nishida! Send everyone else home!
We've decided on number 21!
Okay!
Hey, what should we do here!?
I've been chosen!?
Today's audition is over. The third round of judging that we had planned...
...will not be held.
Takuto!
W-What should I do, Eichi-kun?
I made it!
There's just one thing that's never gonna change:
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
Zutto egaiteta yume
Zu
The dream that I have always been drawing.
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
I
How would I, as I am right now
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
A
look to those small eyes I used to have?
no
ko
ro
no
chii
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, won't you look up? The night sky stretches so far.
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
So
Yes... very soon... you will understand...
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
Se
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up...
Full Moon wo sagashite
Full
...and find the full moon.
Moon
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
I
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now.
tsu
de
mo
i
ssho
Day by Day
Day
by
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
Kyo
I hold the fate dealt by the past and the hopes of tomorrow in my heart.
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
I
Together, forever! As long as I'm with you, I can overcome any pain.
tsu
de
mo
i
ssho
More and more
More
and
more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
Mo
More and more and more... to be closer to you, I stand here now and give...
Many Thanks for You!
Many
Thanks
for
You!
PREVIEW FOR NEXT TIME
What have you done, Takuto?
That girl made it, didn't she!?
Oh, shut up. Why should we care?
It couldn't be that... you've fallen in love with that girl!?
I-It's nothing like that at all!
But you're out of luck. That girl has someone named Eichi-kun, whom she likes a lot.
She's becoming a singer because of a promise with Eichi-kun!
S-Say what!? It's impure
to do that because of a boy!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
THE PROMISE WITH EICHI-KUN
The Promise with Eichi-kun.
Look forward to it!