This is Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
The thing we were
fearing most happened!
A word appeared backwards in
the Death Spirit Handbook!!
That meant that her life was in
danger of being shortened!
This time, Takuto was there
to help,
so everything ended up okay,
but what's going to
happen from now on?
We're gonna have to keep
our eyes on her at all times!!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Hey, how long do
I have to do this?!
Uh! Don't move!
It's my homework I have
to submit the day after tomorrow.
All right, all right.
I'm gonna take a short break.
Me too!
Hey, let me see.
Okay.
What?!
What in the world is that?
It's you, Takuto.
Exactly what part of this
is supposed to resemble me!
See...
Huh?
The cat's ears.
Hey, come on...
Hey, Takuto...
Look at mine too.
You know...
I tried putting some twinkling stars
in your eyes.
Maybe I'll do that too.
S-Stop!
Maybe I'll draw flowers
around the edges.
Don't bring that thing to school!
Why?
You're really awful at drawing!
What do you mean awful?!
I put my heart into drawing this!
Even if you put your heart
into drawing it,
a bad drawing is a bad drawing!
I can't believe that's
the best picture you can draw
when I endured posing for so long.
I'll never model for you again!
Huh? But...it's for my homework!
Why should I care?!
Uh, wait, Takuto!
You really don't need to go
that far.
But...maybe it is a bad drawing?
Oh, my goodness!
What's the matter?
I'm so hungry, I can't move.
Goodness! Hungry...
If he drops dead in
a place like this,
rumors will spread throughout
the neighborhood.
A-All right.
In that case, please come in.
Sorry to trouble you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Huh? Where did that old man go?
Huh? Uh? Uh?
This is terrible!
It would be bad enough
outside the house,
but if he dropped dead
inside the house,
rumors wouldn't end just
with the neighbors!
Are you all right?!
Ohhh...so sorry.
I suddenly got sleepy
as I was inspecting
the Feng Shui of the house.
Ohhh...
That looks marvelous.
What do you mean by
Feng Shui?
Is this how his shoes were?
Wait! Takuto!
Uh...Takuto, your shoelace!
It's untied!
Now that I think of it,
she hadn't drawn my shoes yet.
Thank you for everything.
You're very welcome.
Uh, I'd like to give you this
to thank you.
Huh? You're giving me something?
Huh?
Come, hold out your hands.
All right.
W-What is this anyway?
It's a Saint's Stone.
If you're gonna give
me something
you ought to give me
something nicer.
Not some stupid "Saint's Stone."
Huh...did you say something?
N-Nothing at all.
That's good.
Well then, thank you again
for everything.
You're very welcome.
That burden is off my shoulders.
Madame...
Welcome home, Madame.
I have returned.
Oh?
What is that?
Th-This is a Saint's Stone.
The old man said...
it's a miracle-working stone with
a long and distinguished history.
Throw it away now.
Yes, ma'am.
KEEP OUT DEATH SPIRITS
I wonder if she managed
to draw my shoes.
Hey, Takuto.
What is it?
What did you think about
my drawing?
Nothing in particular.
Don't you think I made
a good drawing?
How can I put this...
I was thinking of you, Takuto,
as I put my heart into
drawing this with love.
Put your heart into it?
I put my heart into drawing it.
Uh, well...
I do understand that you put
your heart into it but...
You do understand?!
It was love, love, love,
love that moved my brush!
Huh?
I'm going back.
Uh, wait!
He didn't have to get mad...
And he didn't have to go
that far
in saying that it
was badly drawn!
I wonder what that is?
Since the two of us
are finally alone,
let's go on a date.
Sorry but I'm going home.
KEEP OUT DEATH SPIRITS
W-What?
Takuto, did you do
something just now?
It wasn't me!
In any case, one more time...
Here goes!
Takuto!
Owww!
What's the matter?
I don't know.
But there's something here!
Yeah!
W-What's that?!
It's not in here...
If it isn't listed in the book...
In the case of unlisted problems...
Contact your manager directly.
Uh, is this the manager?
This is Green Onion Ramen...
who can quiet even crying children.
Please excuse my asking,
but is it possible that even though
we Death Spirits were previously
able to enter a place,
we're suddenly not able to
enter that place anymore?
Huh? It's possible.
Why is that?
Yes... Yes...
Huh?
A barrier has been established?
Huh? A barrier?
Did you find out the cause
of this barrier?
Yeah.
According to the Manager,
something called a Saint's Stone
is creating this barrier.
Saint's Stone...
The identifier is...
The inscription,
"Keep Out Death Spirits"
which is carved on
the back of the stone!
And?
What did he say we
should do with that stone?
We should either smash it
or submerge it in water.
All right!
But, having said that,
we're not able to
enter the barrier.
Let's have her do it.
Good idea.
But I wonder who brought
the Saint's Stone here.
Was it that old woman?
Maybe it was her.
Uh, there's no way she'd
do something like this!
How do you know that?
I mean, she's the one
who would be in
a fix without us.
That's for sure.
Gimme a break!
In any case,
we've got to contact her.
Hello, this is Mitsuki.
Miss Oshige?
CALLER ID:
PUBLIC PHONE
Who could it be?
Hello! Hello?!
It's me. Takuto.
And Meroko...
Stop fooling around!
I'm not fooling around!
Stop making prank phone calls!
I-Idiot! Don't hang up!
She hung up.
But, what'd she mean
by "prank"?
I wonder if the barrier is
not only blocking us physically,
but our voices as well.
If our voices don't work,
I know our next move!
"Come outside the house.
Takuto"
This should do it.
What do you mean this
should do it!
Huh?! Stop that, Meroko!
Come on, Takuto.
Do you know what
you're writing on?!
This?
That's right!
Aargh...my drawing...
This is an emergency situation.
Forgive me.
All right. Done.
Go!
I did it!
Goodness. Right when
a person's sweeping up.
Go!
Uh, it came back!
Huh, why?
What happened?
Huh?!
What is it?
The writing's vanished!
- Really.
- Could it be that?
My drawing has vanished, too!
Hmm... Writing won't work either.
My Takuto is...
Takuto and Meroko...
haven't returned.
I wonder if they're still mad.
She's putting tea in
her miso soup,
and sauce on her pickles.
I wonder what's the matter.
Gimme a break...
They're so stubborn!
Huh?
Takuto and Meruko didn't
come back, after all.
Did I hurt them that much?
Let's call it quits.
She has school tomorrow,
so she'll come outside.
Tomorrow's too late!
Why?
She has to...
Hello...
Who is...this?
Have you forgotten
my voice, honey?
I'm getting tired of this!
Uh... Wait...wait!
Don't hang up!
Huh?
It's me, me! Masami Oshige!
Miss Oshige!
What was the meaning
of that just now?
I'm supposed to be the only person
who knows this number
but when you asked
"Who is this,"
I thought maybe you now
had a boyfriend or something.
Eichi is the only boy I love!
Oh, that's right.
Then why?
I received a prank phone call
yesterday.
Huh, I see. That's worrisome.
Should I change the number?
No. Since there was
only one call like that.
Are you really all right?
Yes.
Okay. By the way, please arrive
at the autograph session
in Ikebukuro thirty minutes
prior to start time.
All right.
That's all I wanted to tell you.
Well, see you at the venue.
Okay!
I need to leave at 12:00
or I won't get there in time.
What am I gonna do?
If Takuto and Meroko aren't here,
I can't transform myself
and leave.
Owwee!
Come on, let's call it quits!
How can we possibly call it quits
when we've come this far?!
Damn!
I could do something if
only she came outside.
Mitsuki!
I'm gonna have that housekeeper
ask her to come outside.
In that case, leave it to me!
Excuse me...
What is it?
Wh-Who are you?!
Are you possibly from
the Koyama Family?
Y-Yes, I am.
I'm so glad.
To tell the truth,
I was the recipient of
extreme kindness
from the young lady of
the Koyama Family
and have paid a visit
to express my appreciation.
May I bother you to please
ask the young lady to come outside?
Uh, I will ask Madame.
Yikes.
Thanks.
See, it went well, didn't it?
In what way?
You were so creepy
that she fled!
I mean, what was that fireball
about anyway?
It's a special effect.
From the ghost story
"Peony Lantern"?
Bingo!
W-What are you doing?!
One can't leave things to you,
after all, Meroko.
I'll do something
no matter what.
What am I gonna do?
If I cancel,
I'd feel awful about Oshige and
the people who are waiting.
Dr. Wakaoji sent a pizza?
I wonder why?
What's this?
"To Mitsuki:
I cannot return to the house
because of the Saint's Stone."
"It's a stone which has
the inscription,
"Keep Out Death Spirits."
You don't need to
understand why!
Just do as I say and deliver
the note together with the pizza!
"If you don't understand,
just go outside
and I'll do something about it.
In any case, hurry."
They weren't able to come back
because of the barrier.
Takuto! I'm sorry to
have doubted you.
All right...there's nobody there.
Mitsuki! Where are you going?
Uh, umm, I'm just taking
a little walk.
That won't do!
But, I'm feeling well today...
I ate pizza and
I'm brimming with energy.
I told you, no!
There was a very creepy and
obviously suspicious couple outside
who were asking
about you, Mitsuki.
It's my responsibility
if anything happens.
Therefore, stay inside
the house quietly today.
N-No way...
I wonder who she means by
creepy and obviously suspicious?
She's talking about us!
What am I gonna do?
I wonder if I have to call
Miss Oshige
and tell her I can't make it.
One of those stones must
be the Saint's Stone!
A stone with
"Keep Out Death Spirits"
inscribed on the back.
Hurry! Hurry!
There's no time!
What are you doing, Mitsuki?!
Uh, nothing...
Madame will scold you.
More importantly, Ms. Tanaka...
That stone from yesterday.
Huh?
You moved a big stone
into the garden yesterday, didn't you?
We have been out of touch
for long time...
Is something up with that stone?
I want to submerge that
stone in the pond.
Why?
Why? Can't I?
I don't care what
you do with it,
but keep it a secret
from Madame, all right?
Secret?
I had one too many
pickling stones,
so I threw it away in the garden.
Huh? That stone was
a pickling stone?
I got a new stone yesterday.
Is that what it was?
Huh, a new stone?!
I found it...
1...2...3!
The ancient pond
A frog leaps in
The sound of the water
The barrier is broken!
There's no time! Hurry!
Takuto! Meroko!
Hurry! Let's go!
Okay!
Do your best today!
We did it.
I'm sorry to have doubted you.
Huh, what are you
talking about?
And also, when you went to
all that trouble to model for me...
No, it's me who should apologize...
Why do I have to do this?!
It's great that we get to come
to a mini-concert.
But why's it all the way
in the mountains?
Quit complaining!
The Hiiragi-en concert has been a dream
for Mitsuki for a long time!
Oh really? She did say that
she grew up
in the same circumstances
as those kids.
Yeah, I hope it all goes well.
Hold on, Takuto!
That kid's about to
take her outfit!
What's the meaning of this?!
The kids at this school
must have been looking forward
to this concert for a while!
Next time on Full Moon:
"A Little Concert."
- Don't miss it!