Summer vacation's going to be over soon.
Yeah.
Then school's going to start.
I can't wait!
Can't wait?
'Cause I'll get to see everyone in class again!
Everyone in class...
Tooruuun!
Watch it, Yutaka!
Ah, I didn't win again.
By the way, Run-chan.
You always seem to be surrounded by guys.
Why is that?
Really? It doesn't seem that way to me.
Have you ever been c-confessed to?
Confessed?
Come to think of it, the other day...
You have?
Satou-sensei gave me this.
Huh?
He gave it to me, saying, "I like this kind of thing."
Liking candles is pretty unusual, isn't it?
Are you sure... he means the candles?
Huh?
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
Won't you come with me?
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう？
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　あつまるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日射し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ちあわせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
And we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはまる
Summer Festival
Hey, hey, look at this!
Summer
Fireworks
Festival
Want to go together?
What's this?
Oooh!
It's the fireworks festival they hold every year.
That's right.
There're lots of night stalls. It's pretty lively.
Really? Look, it's this weekend.
Since summer vacation's about to end,
it would be nice to go to a festival together.
It sure would.
We can all wear yukata, too!
Sounds great!
Yeah.
Well, it's fun to do this now and then.
Then it's a date!
Hey,
what are you doing for the rest of today?
No plans.
Too hot. Don't wanna move.
Hey, how about we go for karaoke?
Karaoke, huh?
Karaoke? Sounds good! I love karaoke!
Oh?
Yuuko, you're a karaoke fan?
Yep. I like to choose ringtones that I can sing along to.
Really?
Run, what do you like about karaoke?
Let's see... for one, the jambalaya at that place is amazing.
But the ramen's surprisingly good, too.
Also, they give you big servings for the parfaits and ice cream!
Huh?
I thought we were going to karaoke?
Yep, we are.
Karaoke
This room's a bit cramped...
Ah, I'm going to order our food and drinks.
What would you all like?
I'll have a melon soda.
Grapefruit juice.
Tooru, anything to drink?
Uh... iced tea.
With pleasure!
Ah, hello? I'd like to place an order.
Hey, they've got the new songs that came out this month.
Two iced teas,
melon soda and grapefruit juice, one each.
I'll enter the first one.
Also, a jambalaya and fries, please.
Yes.
Yes. Yes, thank you very much!
Okay, here I go!
Take me, summer breeze! Sweep me off my feet.
Take me, summer breeze!
This love of mine
floats upon the wind.
Catch me, summer breeze! Hold me gently.
Touch me, summer breeze!
A sweet single summer's dream.
I'll take off with you!
Yuuko, not bad!
You're really good!
I'll take off with you!
Take me, summer breeze!
Thank you.
Ah, better enter the next one.
Huh?
Tooru's giving this some serious thought.
Maybe she's really picky about something?
Take your time deciding.
Why is she glaring at me?
Ocha Melodical Beauty Bang Bang
All right, my turn!
I bravely try to wake up,
but I'm pulled back into a slumber.
Teary, teary, mumble, mumble,
trying to escape from life.
Caught up in emotions,
I argue with my best friends.
But I still get in the last word!
Let's spread this vague magic
all across the world,
carried by those catchy words!
(3, 2, 1, say!)
Ocha Melodical Beauty, Bang Bang!
Keep smiling along! ...
Tooru.
Done with the song book and staring contest?
Letter to the Clouds
Flowing with the
Clouds
Beyond the clouds
Ah, this song?
I'll enter it for you.
Eh?
... Glow like a star!
Okay! And, send!
With an appli-tic fortune, wake up the future!
Good job!
Go on.
It's starting!
Do your best, Tooru!
Eh?
Uh, um...
Here, the microphone!
What's wrong, Tooru?
Beyond the Clouds
Take a look, I will always
Here's your order!
The jambalaya's here!
This one's hot, so please be careful.
Ah,
I've got the grapefruit juice!
Thank you for coming today.
Here you go, Nagi-chan.
Thank you!
The melon soda's mine.
Here you go.
Well then, excuse me.
The current song has been canceled
Thank you.
Huh?
Guess she didn't want to sing.
Sorry I almost made you.
Wounded by the twilight,
the country girl's maiden heart
the country girl's maiden heart.
This love need never come true.
Just let me see you, once more.
Lots of spirit there!
Just two more songs...
The calories you have burned total
so far
If I sing two more songs...
I can eat eight fries.
Dieting?
Quit worrying and just eat.
Hey, Tooru!
Don't you like that song?
Huh?
Friends
This one, right here.
Right?
B-But I've never sung it before...
I probably can't.
You'll be fine!
Ah!
Tooru, it's not on!
Huh? Oh...
I'll start.
Run-chan...
Let's go, hand in hand,
across this great big hill.
One, two, three,
let's find more fun things to do!
A pure white blanket,
and a giant puppet,
and a polka-dot skirt.
Though we can't split them in two to share.
Even if we fall and want to cry
we'll be there for each other.
When our fast-beating hearts fill up,
we'll be as happy as can be.
Let's go, hand in hand,
walking straight ahead.
One, two, three,
let's find more fun things to do!
Just three more.
Don't know when to give up, huh?
Nobody's input another song?
Ah, then I'll do one.
Finish eating first.
Then the next song will be...
I still want to believe...
Someone next door?
I thought that was empty.
Maybe he just got here.
Right now, I want to...
Wow, that guy's good.
The song's so sultry it hurts, though.
It's starting!
Run-chan!
Don't sing!
Huh? Why?
Just because.
Huh?
Tooru!
Shh!
Soon enough, you'll understand,
Don't tell me...
This voice...
the answer in my heart.
What?
What, what?
I wish I could sing karaoke with Run-chan.
Okay, come on! One more time, here we go!
Karaoke was so much fun!
Let's go again sometime!
I wish I was better at singing.
Come to think of it, they had a TV show about improving your singing.
Really?
For next time:
Method 1
It's been a while since I've worn a yukata to a festival.
I can't wait!
I've got a bunch of yukata. Which do you want?
This one with the chic color is nice.
It looks sophisticated.
Let me see...
I don't remember one with that color.
Oh yeah.
Huh?
This one's changed color from the mold.
I guess my current ones won't work.
Maybe my old ones will fit you?
I'll go get them.
Those look very adult.
They're probably Run-chan's mom's.
Maybe I can break 1*0 cm in those.
I'll never be an adult at this rate...
Mom!
Yes?
Oh, my!
Look! We put them on!
What do you think?
Today's the festival, isn't it?
Those bright colors are wonderful!
You both look spectacular.
Thanks!
Thank you very much.
But the festival isn't until tonight, right?
It's still ten in the morning.
We got over-excited!
There they are!
Ah.
Fried Soba
Cotton Candy
Thanks for waiting.
Okay! We're all here.
Yuuko-chan, you really do look cute in anything.
Well...
Nagi-chan- oh, you curled your hair!
You're right.
So she did.
It looks cute!
Well... you know... every now and then...
The fireworks won't start for a while,
so let's check out the stands to kill some time.
Can we go to a mask stand first?
Sure.
Tooru, do you like kids' anime?
No...
The stalls from the shopping district always try to give me stuff.
I feel guilty.
Ah, so that's why.
Ooh, a candy apple!
Fried Squid
Frankfurters
Candy apple?
Yuuko-chan, can I have a bite?
Go ahead.
Here.
Yummy!
Oh? Tooru, do you want some too?
I'm fine.
Really?
Run, let me have some of your cotton candy, too!
Sure.
Delicious!
Huh?
What? Huh?
Whaaaat?
Ring Toss
Yuuko-chan and Nagi-chan are doing the ring toss!
Ah! I got third place!
3rd Place
5th Place
7th Place
Congratulations!
Here! A fireworks set.
Giving fireworks as prizes at a fireworks festival?
All right! I'm up next!
I'm going for first place!
Uh-oh.
I've already spent so much.
Night stalls are pretty expensive.
You have to spend carefully.
Worst case, you end up broke for the second half of the festival.
But just looking at things makes you want them.
That's why you have to deliberately buy things that you can enjoy for longer.
Candy carving?
Nagi, shouldn't we do something we can all enjoy?
I'll bet you've never done candy carving before.
It's pretty fun.
Really?
Wanna give it a shot?
Candy Carving
This is my first time.
You can pick an easy one, then!
Oh no!
It broke!
Let me have another one!
Sure, miss.
This is pretty tough.
Come on, hurry up!
But I haven't seen all the shops yet!
Thank you for your patience.
We will soon begin launching the fireworks.
The fireworks started!
Everyone, hurry!
The crowds...
I know someplace good!
To the top of the hill! There's a secret spot there!
Nagi, forget about the candy carving!
My drinking gourd!
It's right at the top of these stairs!
What?
Somehow, I don't really care about the fireworks anymore.
Nagi, let's go!
Whaaat?
I can't go on!
Don't give in, Nagi-chan!
Don't be too late...
We're here!
Oh no...
All in a row!
Wow!
A... Amazing...
And that concludes tonight's firework show.
On your way home, please take your trash with you
What?
It's over... already?
or deposit it in the designated areas.
Oh no...
The finale alone just doesn't feel like enough.
It's kind of sad, isn't it?
Oh!
That's right! I won some fireworks at the stall earlier!
Oh yeah! Nice going, Yuuko!
But we don't have a light.
Not to worry!
Matches?
A candle?
You brought those?
How come there were only sparklers in this thing?
How plain.
But I kind of like sparklers.
Well, I suppose.
They are pretty.
This tastes so good!
You've had way too much.
Ah...
Wha- Satou-sensei!
Why are you-
Now how do I respond to that?
Please don't come near me like that!
That's my line.
By the way, sensei,
are you here alone?
I am not!
Get me another Nama Sake!
But look, you're alone!
Like I said! I am not alone!
There you go again...
Summer vacation was a lot of fun!
Guess it was.
We went to the beach, too.
Let's watch the fireworks again next year!
Sure!
I'll finish carving that candy next time, for sure!
So that's your priority?
What? It was fun, wasn't it?
Yep! It was surprisingly addicting.
Right, Tooru?
Yeah.
It was fun.
The tall shadows
akane ni narabu
茜に並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kageboushi
背高かげぼうし
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　お喋り
Our chatter goes on and on,
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigato
いつもありがと
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれて　ヨカッタな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
ル・ル・ルン・
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風とココロ　ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
つぎの角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Next time
When it comes to the end of August...
Summer vacation homework!
Or copying from someone who actually did it.
I panicked finishing my picture diary, but I forgot what the weather was like!
Next time on A-Channel!
"New Semester"!
Besides, it's not like we're elementary schoolers...
See you next week!