So Ra No Wo To
I'm gonna wet my pants.
Phone Duty -
We Have an Emergency
"The mission to confirm maintenance,
to the HQ-command line,
for high-level emergency situations."
Th-That's quite a name...
It's an extremely important mission.
If we fail, we could
all be punished.
Under certain conditions,
a level-one warning is issued,
and all forces in the area are placed
on emergency standby.
That's right. It's really important.
Wh-What kind of mission is it?
You see...
You watch the phone.
You know this phone is our hotline
to the capital's HQ, right?
Has it ever rung?
No.
That's right.
Thankfully.
But maybe...
Yes, it would be bad if it rang,
but it would be even worse
if it didn't ring when it should.
So once every six months,
they test to ensure it works.
And we call that...
Well...
Remember it, already.
The command communications line
for high-level... What was it?
No... It's the command communications
line for the high-level...
The mission to confirm maintenance,
to the HQ command line
for high-level emergency situations.
Exactly.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Please let me do it!
I've always wanted to try
talking on the telephone!
Is it that exciting?
It works in more or less the same way
as the Takemikazuchi's intercom.
It's just that the distance
is a bit further.
But it's amazing.
You can talk to people
really far away!
It's wonderful.
Well, it's kind of strange to talk
to someone you can't see.
But once you get used
to it, it's nothing.
But the issue is that we don't know
when it'll happen today.
You still want to do it?
Of course!
OK.
Then, you watch the phone
the entire day.
Ring, ring, ring!
This is Private Sorami Kanata of the
1121 Platoon, Helvetian Republic Army.
And when the call ends,
you replace the receiver on top.
OK!
Fi-Fi...
You're so cute!
Filicia-san!
What are you doing?
It hurts to watch.
The train's leaving.
Train?
I need to rush some
documents to HQ.
Claus-san comes next
week, right?
So I'm off to the station.
Take care of the phone, OK?
Right!
If we don't do it right, they might think
we've actually been attacked.
Don't screw it up!
Leave it to me!
Hey!
Yes?
I'm not asleep!
Not... Not asleep at all!
Have you seen Noël?
She wasn't in her room.
Um...
The hanger again?
OK...
Kanata, what do you
want for lunch?
I-I-I'll get it.
Don't worry about it.
It's my turn.
But...
Why do both you and Kureha
try to keep me from the kitchen,
even when it's my turn?
I used to cook all the time
before you two came.
Well, you see...
It should taste fine.
I-It doesn't taste as
bad as it looks...
What?
Wait, it's got a very strong
taste! It's wonderful!
Doesn't it?
Then I'll go at it even
harder than usual.
Hey! Is anyone here?
Yes!
Sempai, it's Naomi-san!
I'm busy.
But I need to stay by the phone!
Hey, you've got a visitor!
Darn it! Fine.
OK, I'll be right there.
I don't want any more sandwiches
mixed with cutting board...
What's this?
Drink up.
It's apple cider.
It's made at the farm where we
usually get our apple juice.
So these are related to
our calvados, right?
Huh?
Oh, I see... She found out.
We can give these two
as gifts, right?
Eh? Yeah, that's true.
Gifts?
Phone Duty - Reserved
for Emergencies
Tonight, there's a merchant
guild's meeting.
They help us out with a lot of things,
so from time to time, we give them presents.
Keep that in mind.
Okay!
What? They tried their
hardest to hide it.
How'd you find out?
W-Well, uh...
I'll tell you sometime, maybe.
Would you like to eat
lunch with us?
What?
You want me to go, too?
Everyone wants a real explanation
from the military
about the news in this
week's papers.
News?
About how the peace treaty conferences
aren't going well.
They aren't?
They're working out the reparations
and territorial lines.
It's natural that it would drag on.
Really, the old guild guys
want to see you.
You've gained a lot more fans.
Ever since you played a Flame Maiden
at the water-throwing festival,
their numbers have
been growing.
What a pain...
So, yeah. I've gotta go to this.
Now I'm a Fortress Maiden,
heart and soul, too!
I will complete my mission!
All right. It's in your hands.
Right!
Kanata, I'll give these to you.
Sorry that they're so old.
These are trumpet...
These are wonderful, wonderful,
wonderful!
Thank you!
You're really sounding better
with the trumpet.
They're a present for
practicing so hard.
And they'll keep you awake.
Ah... This is...
C... D... E... F... G...
A.
I guess summer's over...
Iliya?
Maybe I drank too much.
Noël-chan, are you there?
It's raining!
The laundry's gonna get wet!
The courtyard's within the
theater of operations!
Kanata!
Let's play!
Hello!
Kanata!
Let's play!
Save me!
Thank you so much.
No, I'm glad your laundry is safe.
Yeah... I-I'm sorry to
ask you for help!
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry for visiting so suddenly.
I have to return to Treize tomorrow,
so I came to say goodbye.
O-Oh, thank you.
There's no need to say
goodbye to soldiers.
Don't be like that, Seiya-san.
I've heard he's been less than polite
to people from your base.
I'd like to apologize
for that, as well.
Where is everyone?
They're all gone.
Rio-san, too? The black-haired one?
Yes.
I see...
I'd like to see her...
Is this your book?
What is it?
A trumpet book.
Rio-sempai gave it to me.
I see. I thought so.
No, no. I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Are you here alone?
That's right.
I'm here for the uh...
command communications line...
for high-level HQ emergency situations...
So basically...
You're waiting for this to ring?
Yep!
But I've never used one
before, so I'm nervous.
I'm not sure that I'll do it right.
How about practicing?
Then Yumina-san is also attending
the guild meeting?
Yes. She's going to get donations
from the guild.
Here you go! Enjoy.
Yummy!
Isn't it? You have some too, Seiya-kun.
Fine, I'll drink your stupid cider.
But don't think you can
buy me off with it!
What are you making?
Can you two guess?
A phone!
Is this really a phone?
Yes, it's a phone!
I make it for the kids,
'cause kids love phones.
Go, Seiya-san.
A phone, huh?
Hello?
Wow!
Wow, Seiya-kun!
I can hear you!
That's not right.
Say, "Hello," first.
You always say that
on the phone.
H-Hello?
Hello?
Wow!
I can really hear his voice!
Practice with that.
OK!
Um... This is...
Hello?
H-Hello!
This is Private Sorami Kanata of the
1121 Platoon, Helvetia Republic Army.
Very well.
I-I'm honored to receive
this phone call!
Very well.
So, uh...
Wait, birdie!
Mishio-san!
No, Mishio-chan!
What happened?
The phone!
Um... Is the priest and our...
Yes?
Oh gods! How horrible!
You came here to thank them for everything
they'd done and to say goodbye,
but instead, you messed around
and caused trouble for them!
No dinner tonight!
Yes.
Me, too?
It's OK now.
Thanks.
But your clothes are soaked.
I'm fine. I have a change...
I've got a good idea!
This is embarrassing...
Not at all!
How brilliant you look!
But thank you, Yumina-san!
I'll wash and return them.
No. You can keep them!
They're too big for the kids,
and I can't imagine anyone looking
as good as you in them!
I'm sorry, Kanata.
Will you play with us again?
Sure.
Come back soon, Seiya-kun.
I...
M-Maybe if I'm free.
Then excuse us.
May all blessings be upon you.
Th-Thank you!
Now, then. I need to clean up.
I forgot.
I have to go to the bathroom.
I'm gonna wet my pants...
Someone, hurry!
Hurry...
Geez, those old guys...
What's wrong, Kana-
Sempai, please...
Save me!
What's wrong, Kanata?
I can't hold it anymore...
I'm gonna wet my pants!
Go, you'll get sick!
Thank you!
She was holding it in
this whole time?
She'll really do whatever she's told.
What's wrong?
I'm OK!
Kanata!
No, I can't get it...
I can't move at all!
Man, her timing sucks.
Hello?
This is Master Sergeant Rio Kazumiya of
the 1121 Platoon of the Helvetia Army.
It's been a while.
I heard we were confirming your line.
So I insisted...
Are you going to run?
No!
I'm not running!
I know.
You simply haven't forgiven me.
After all this time,
what do you want?
Please! I want you to save this
country... Save Helvetia.
Morning, Kanata.
Noël-chan, surely you haven't
been in there the whole day?
Yes, I sleep well there.
No!
We're back-
How cute, Kana-chan!
What are you two doing
in the hallway?
Kanata fell and can't get up.
Is she hurt?
Then stand up!
Fine...
What a spoiled girl.
No... No...
One... Two...
No!
A Typhoon Passes! - Illusion and Reality
Next time:
A Typhoon Passes!
Illusion and Reality.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.