This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old!
The other day we went to Hiiragi Preschool to give a mini-concert...
...but a boy was causing all kinds of mischief!
Actually... it was because he would've been separated from a girl he loved right after the concert.
Full Moon  had the same sad experience, so, as a present, she sang to them with all her heart.
I was moved by that song, too...
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Ooshige-san sure is late...
And also... Takuto and Meroko aren't here today either...
Sorry!
Huh?
The Shinigami Chief has called us in today...
There's no way we can go with you!
If there's anything, call me with the whistle.
Okay? Okay?
What are you doing, Takuto?
We're leaving!
I-I know!
Well... that's how it is...
Well... it looks like Takuto and Meroko have their own work to do...
Guess it can't be helped, huh?
But where's Ooshige-san...?
Hello! Ooshige-san?!
Eh? Why's that?
What?!
You're in the hospital?!
Go for Broke! Substitute Manager!
Yes. Well...
That's why...
Today, Akiba-kun will be
your manager in my place.
Ah.
Okay. I understand.
Yes. Okay.
Then... get well soon!
Ah...
Somehow... this is turning out to be a rough day...
Oh yeah.
Akiba-san, who's coming in her place...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Full Moon-san!
U-Um...
Y-You've got the wrong person!
Huh?
Um...
Akiba-san?
Yes?
That's me...
Nice to meet you!
I'm Full Moon.
P-Pardon me!
I'm Akiba Kotarou, your substitute
manager for today!
I couldn't recognize you because
you were in disguise...
I'm so happy to see how lovely you are!
Ah.
Ooshige-san told me to wear a disguise whenever I'm somewhere with a lot of people.
Just as one would expect from Ooshige-senpai!
It'd be bad if fans saw you here, right?
However...
Today... I, Akiba Kotarou...
...will give you such management that won't lose to Senpai's...
...and fully support you in every step of the way!
So please, rest assured!
Full Moon-san!
Wow! It's Full Moon !
It really is!
Signature, please...
She's so cute!
Oh no! I've already made a mistake!
But it will be all right!
We can get away now!
Let's go!
Ah!
Looks like we managed to get away.
Well, then, for our first job today...
Let's go to the autograph session!
Yes!
But... where are we?
Uh...
No idea!
Um... you don't know...?
No worries whatsoever!
Whoa...
We'll just have to look at this.
T-This is the wrong map!
Ah... um...
Couldn't we just ask somebody?
That's right!
We can do that!
Let's go find somebody immediately!
A-Akiba-san!
Here!
Please continue to show your support for me!
Really, thank you so much!
Yes!
Ah.
City FM?
Yes.
We'll be done in another
fifteen minutes, so it's okay.
Yes! We'll be there soon.
Yes! Bye!
Ah! Akiba-san!
Fifteen minutes is impossible!
It's all right!
There are only one, two, three, four, five, six...
...38, 39, 40, 41, 42...
...387, 388, 389...
...1421, 1422, 1423...
T-This is a disaster!
There are tons more fans lined up than I thought!
Even two hours wouldn't be enough!
All right!
Please continue to show your support for me!
How's that?
It won't do.
We won't make it in time.
What?
But I can't write any faster than this...
Everyone!
The remaining autographs will be
Full Moon-san's handprints!
That's not good!
All the fans who've been waiting for so long...
So it won't work out after all...
Isn't that nice..!
I'm so envious...
I'd rather have one of those as well...
It's much better than a typical signature...
Here!
Here! Here! Here! Here! Here! Here! Here! Here! Here! Here!
Everyone.
Please continue to show your support for me!
Of course!
Looks like we somehow made it on time.
I'm glad that the fans were all happy!
Okay!
Today's guest was Full Moon-san.
Our show's about to come to an end.
To finish, could you tell us about your plans for the future?
Yes!
I want to keep on singing with all my heart and release lots of CDs!
I've heard that there are
also plans for live concerts.
Yes!
Live?
Oh no!
I forgot to give her this!
Yes. I'd like to meet my fans...
Wha..?!
Full Moon-san!
Akiba-san...
Hey you! What are you thinking?!
They are on air you know!
Ah... sorry about that.
Well then...
H-Hey! Wait!
Full Moon-san!
Here's the schedule for a live concert!
I'm terribly sorry!
It's all right. I screw up like that all the time.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you very much!
I'll try my best to do the next job without fail!
What's up next?
Yes!
A mini-concert in a department store!
I'm sorry, Full Moon-san!
Akiba-san, is this...?
The special live performance... is next week...
Look!
This young lady is Full Moon !
I'm extremely sorry for the mix-up!
Don't be...
The babies were very cute... so, it's all good!
Thank you for saying that.
You must be hungry.
The weather looks fine...
Let's have lunch here.
Here?
I... used to be an adventurer.
I've even climbed Mt. Everest.
Wow!
That's amazing!
Well, it should be ready.
Thanks for the food!
It's so good!
I'm glad!
There's plenty of it, so eat as much as you want!
Yes!
But... why did you become a manager?
It's my dream.
When you're on an expedition...
There are often times when
the going gets tough.
At those times...
...music brings you incredible strength...
To support those whose songs give courage to other people...
That's my dream.
Full Moon-san.
Full Moon-san, your dream is
to be a top singer, right?
Dream, huh?
It's not my only one, though...
Ah...
The weather is great, isn't it?
It really is...
Feels so good...
Ahhhhhhhh!!!!
W-What's wrong, Akiba-san?!
We're going to be late for the next job!
Eh?!
What's the next one?
An appointment with Takasu-san!
Oh no!
This is bad... this is very bad...
Anyways... we have to hurry!
All right... since it's come to this...
Full Moon-san.
Dash!
Full Moon-san!
Take a right at the next intersection!
Okay!
To gain some time...
...at the crossing, long jump!
Okay!
Here too, long jump!
Let's do it with all we've got!
Oh! You're doing great, Full Moon-san!
Keep that pace!
Okay!
Here we take a shortcut!
Here, triple jump!
Okay!
We're almost there, Full Moon-san!
Yes!
And here?
Last spurt!
Y-You really were making an effort.
For me...
To run like this...
It's the first time in my life...
Takasu-san!
You're late! And by a full hour too!
I am so sorry!
It's my fault that we are late!
No! I'm also at fault!
I'm sorry!
No, I'm responsible!
No! It's my fault too!
I don't care who's fault it is! Just go inside already!
No, I'm...
Okay!
So... well...
It's about time we should
release your first album...
An album?!
We have around thirty demo songs here, wanna listen to them?
Yes!
What the..?
Come on!
Work!
Damn...
That's strange...
Why isn't there any sound?
It's been acting up recently...
Sorry.
Looks like we might not be able to do this today.
Eh? No way...
No good...
Wait a sec.
I wonder if it can be fixed...
I wanted to hear the songs...
All right! I'll fix it!
Eh?
A-Akiba-san?
You should leave it alone...
Takasu-san will be mad at you!
It's fine!
I'm good at video games.
Akiba-san!
I don't think this is quite like a video game!
Huh?
That's funny...
Hey! What are you doing?!
Ah... not much... just...
Whoa!
The data for the songs has been totally erased!
What?!
How can you possibly make up for this?!
That was the data for the first album!
I-I'm terribly sorry!
So sorry, Takasu-san!
Akiba-san didn't do it on purpose!
Would it be better if he had done it on purpose?!
Besides...
Why on earth is an incompetent guy like you a manager anyway?!
If you're just going to screw up and cause other people problems...
...why don't you just quit now?
Get out of here! You're useless!
It's just as Takasu-san says...
I'm just not fit to be a manager...
That's not true.
No.
That's how it really is...
Eh?
I'm always like this.
Doesn't matter who's management it is I am assigned with...
I mess up everything.
They always end up in failure...
The job with you today, Full Moon-san...
I told myself I would do my best from the start...
Look how it ended up...
I'm hopeless, aren't I?
What are you saying?!
Akiba-san, weren't you trying your best for me?!
Just before...
You were only doing that because I said that I wanted to hear the songs...
Besides...
I had many new experiences
with you today, Akiba-san!
Eh?
For me...
Getting to play outside was always...
...something that I didn't get to do much...
But...
I ate lunch like I was on a camping trip...
I got to run live I've never done before...
It was really fun!
Full Moon-san...
So... don't say that.
Let's do our best!
Okay, Akiba-san?
Forgive me...
Eh?!
What's with that...?!
No matter what... that substitute manager messes up way too much!
Just like a certain someone...
What's that?!
I'm doing my best at my job as a Shinigami!
He definitely works as hard
as he can, but still fails...
Yey. Yep. I understand, like totally.
Hello?
Ah! Akiba-san?!
Thank you very much!
Sorry about everything yesterday.
Um... I've been doing some thinking...
I think I'll just quit working and go back to the countryside.
What are you saying?!
Please don't say that you're quitting.
Let's go and apologize to Takasu-san together.
No.
It's just as Takasu-san said.
I should stop being a manager.
When I'm around...
...I just cause trouble for everybody.
I have to leave for the station soon...
I'll be late for my train...
Full Moon-san.
Thank you for everything.
A-Akiba-san?
Akiba-san?!
Hello? Akiba-san?
What happened?
Akiba-san said that he quit!
We have to go to the station fast!
Otherwise, we'll miss his train and
Takasu-san will still be mad...
Ah... what should we do?!
Takuto!
I got it. I got it already! Calm down!
Akiba-san...
I have to hurry.
That's right. In a situation like this...
To gain some time...
At the crossing, long jump!
Okay!
Long jump here too!
Here we take a shortcut!
Here, triple jump!
All right!
I... did it!
Akiba-san!
F-Full Moon-san!
A-Akiba-san, don't quit.
You came all the way here to tell me that...
Yes.
You mustn't quit, Akiba-san.
No.
If I'm around, I'm just a burden on everyone...
I've already made up my mind.
That can't be...
Then... your dream to help singers...
You're just going to give up on it?
Akiba-san...
From platform 23...
Train 21, bound for Komachi through Akita...
Well... I'll get going.
will be departing shortly...
Akiba-san!
In a short while... boarding will begin on platform 23.
You mustn't give up!
There might be many more hardships before your dream comes true...
But if you give up, then all hope is lost!
Ah...
Akiba-san!
You mustn't give up!
He's gone...
It looks like a lot happened
while I was gone, Mitsuki.
Takasu-san seemed to be in a jam, too...
Oh well... Luckily, the songs were saved in another computer.
Eh?
So the songs weren't completely lost?
Well... just a copy...
That's great...
Eh?
Wait... Akiba-san didn't need to
give up on his dream then...
Hey, Mitsuki.
Can you come with me for a bit today?
Eh?
Okay. We're here.
Ooshige-san, what is this place..?
This will be a store that will sell Full Moon  merchandise.
Eh?
Mine?
Manager, what about the cable here?
Hmm...
This area should be used for the display window...
So the cables should be on the other side, and install the switches there.
Okay.
Sure, boss.
Akiba-san...
Full Moon-san! Ooshige-senpai!
Welcome!
You're the first customers.
Akiba-san...
You didn't go back to the countryside?
And... you're a manager?
It's just as you said, Full Moon-san.
I mustn't give up, right?
That's why... I'm going to work hard here now, as the manager.
It's my pleasure to work for you, Full Moon-san!
Congratulations!
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Thank you very much!
I'll continue to support you with everything I've got!
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Thank you!
I'll do my best too!
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
That place you had to leave for a while...
Sukoshi hanareta basho
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Takuto!
Isn't this good? Isn't this good?!
Huh? What is?
It's about that girl, of course!
A dazzling summer love is in the making!
Meroko will definitely cheer her on!
Y-You idiot!
Like that could ever happen!
For her to fall in love with some weird guy from who knows where...
Ahhh! Takuto... you're jealous!
You're terrible! Even though you belong to me!
Shut up! That's not it!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
First Kiss!?
Look forward to it!