Kaoru-san,
it looks like we're in the same class this year too.
I'm glad.
Yeah.
If you're happy about it, then I am too.
Anyway, where is he?
Hey, hey!
What's with that long face?
Are you that happy about being in Class 10 with all the rowdy kids?
What is it?
Nothin'.
He isn't used to being split into a different class from his friends.
This is Sentaro's first time.
Um... You have a petal in your hair.
That's okay. I'll get it myself.
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
Nishimi-kun!
I'm so happy we're in the same class again!
Are we?
Th-That's cruel.
We just introduced ourselves.
Oh, that's right.
You set up his ticket for the sleeper car too, didn't you?
S-Sorry about that!
He said to keep it a secret from you.
Because of that, I had a nice trip.
Thanks.
It's finally over!
We should've decided the class rep by drawing lots in the first place.
No kiddin'!
Hey, I heard there's already a fight in Class 10!
I'm just glad I wasn't put in there!
Hey, are you done already, Boxing Club?!
I thought you had a little
more spirit than that.
Sen!
Hi, Bon!
Don't just say "Hi"!
Why are you fighting on the first day of the new school year?!
Just gettin' a little exercise.
That was fun. Been too
long since I had a fight.
Hey, Sen! Are you listening to me?!
Hey!
Wh-What?!
W-Wait a minute!
Don't go!
What do you want?
You're going over there with that banged-up face?
Is it that bad?
Ricchan.
Sorry, but would you take this guy to the infirmary and patch him up?
Alright, go! Go!
Ricchan, I'm counting on you.
Okay.
It still hurts a little,
but I should get used to it eventually.
The pain will go away, and I should be able to relax and smile again.
I'm going to submit this painting to this year's public exhibition.
This is the one Sentaro-kun modeled for.
Um... Uh...
Oh, no, that's okay.
You don't have to force yourself to give me feedback.
S-Sorry.
I don't know much about art.
Oh?
That's a strange thing for you to say.
After all, painting and jazz are
pretty closely related, aren't they?
A painting is created on
a space called a canvas,
while jazz is created during a time called a performance.
It's like etching your living self into that place and time.
Or something like that.
I was only repeating someone.
Junichi-san was talking about that when I went down to the basement.
Fukahori Yurika
It's very interesting to listen to him.
I'd like to talk to him more about all kinds of things.
Um... I went to Tokyo during spring break.
And I dropped by Jun-nii's boarding house, but he wasn't there.
Oh, that's too bad.
Apparently, he hadn't been back for a while,
so there were a lot of letters stuffed in his mail slot.
Someone said he might be staying over at another person's place.
Oh...
One of those letters may have been important.
I wonder where he went.
Aren't you done yet?
Just put a little spit on cuts
like these, and they'll be fine.
What'll you do if they get infected?
Come on, close your eyes.
Wh-What?
Rikko, I'm glad you're in the same class as Bon.
From now on, would you look after him more instead of me?
Um, well, I'd better get going.
Bon!
Glad I caught up to you before you went home.
Are those tears?
This glob looks like a tear.
That's the tear of a broken heart.
In Greek mythology, the god Apollo
fell in love with Daphne, the daughter of a river god.
He became obsessed and chased her all around, but she wouldn't stop running.
At last, she gave Apollo the ultimate rejection
by turning into a bay laurel tree.
What an awful case of heartbreak!
Of course he would cry!
He's so grief-stricken that he fashions a wreath out of the laurel tree!
Wh—
Who's he?
This is second-year Matsuoka Seiji-kun.
He's the Great Hope of East High's Art Club.
Oh, stop it! You're embarrassing me!
Kawabuchi Sentaro-kun,
we're both in Class 10, huh?
Nice to meet you!
Bon,
do you remember that guy from last year?
Nope.
I'm gettin' the chills.
Oh, that's right, Sentaro-kun...
Are you free on our next day off?
I want to get you a present as thanks for being my model.
Hey! Wait up! Hey!
Idiot! Apollo, my ass!
I could never see this guy
wearing a laurel wreath!
Ricchan, do you have detention?
Yeah. I forgot my math homework.
That's unusual for someone as level-headed as you, Ricchan.
Who said I was level-headed?
I'm as careless as can be.
I get more absent-minded in the spring, but I better snap out of it.
This song...
It's from "The Sound of Music."
I love this song.
Yeah, I figured you would like that movie, Ricchan.
Oh, no, I didn't see it.
I wanted to, but before I knew it, it'd already stopped playing.
I bet it was a good movie, huh?
How could I miss it?
I guess I thought I'd be able to see it anytime.
I'm pretty dumb, huh?
What is that again?
"My Favorite Things."
Yeah, that's it!
No, I better not. I had my shot.
Oh yeah, there was somethin' I wanted your advice about, Bon.
About... my date.
With Yurika-san?
Y-Yeah.
Well then, I'll give the perfect advice to a romantic beginner like you.
Don't go.
That's all.
Huh?! What the hell is that?!
On a real date, you're sure to freeze up and blow the whole deal.
D-Don't you make fun of me!
I can handle a date, piece of cake!
Oh, sure!
You really think you can keep TPO in mind
TPO = Time / Place / Occasion
in front of that princess
and behave accordingly?!
T... TP—
You know what that is?
You don't, do you?
But for your own sake, you better not go.
TP...
Geez, what a pain.
I wish everyone would just stop falling in love.
That dope!
Well, don't blame me for what happens!
Sentaro-kun, tell me if you see something you want.
Oh, nah. I never get expensive stuff like this.
Even this jacket is a hand-me-down from Jun-nii.
Oh, really?
And from then on, all we
talked about was Jun-nii.
When Jun-nii was in high school, nobody was cooler!
He was good at fightin' and smart too.
Oh, really?!
We had a good time talkin' about him,
but now all I got left is a feelin' of emptiness in the pit of my stomach.
What are you doing, Sen?
Did your date go well?
C-Course it did!
That's right.
A date is a piece of cake for you, right?
Y-Yeah, that's right.
Liar.
It didn't go well at all, did it?
Just like I predicted.
Sen,
stay away from her from now on.
What makes you say that all of a sudden?
You really are dense, aren't you?
Any way you look at it,
you and a refined girl like that just don't match up.
It's what you call being "out of your depth."
Crap. Maybe I went too far.
Hi, Kawabuchi-kun.
What?
I heard you went on a date with Yurika-senpai.
She said she had a great time.
H-Hey, is that true?!
Did she say anythin' else?!
You wanna know?
Yeah!
She said you were handsome,
and that maybe she'll hold your hand next time!
Really?!
MUKAE
RECORDS
JAZZ
POP
CLASSI
Oh, Bon, you're here, huh?
Hey, you wanna try playin'
"My Favorite Things" again together?
What's this?
I thought he'd be mad at me for what I said at lunch,
but he seems to be in a great mood.
Hey, what's that?
I thought only jazz was allowed in here.
Oh, that kid with the mushroom cut, Matsuoka, forced it on me.
I couldn't refuse, so I just carried it here.
Oh?
Wh-What's that mean?
Good for you, making a nice friend that lends you records.
Hey Sen,
would you come upstairs a second?
Sure.
What, did a new record come in?
Just come up here.
'Kay.
Is he... going to listen to that record?
What am I so anxious about?
Kawabuchi-kun,
did you listen to the record I gave you yesterday?
Nah, I can't get into music that has girls squealin' over it.
Isn't that the purpose of making music?
Don't you wanna become popular?
Don't really care about that.
Anyway, I'm not interested.
Well, I wanna be popular.
My dream is to become a star!
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Huh? A star?
SEIJI
Wait a second!
Are those the underpants
of somebody who aims to be a star?!
Oh, these?
I've got a lot of brothers,
so if I don't tag them like this, they'll disappear in a hurry.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
And we're poor, so we can't afford to buy new ones often.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Amongst all my brothers,
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
I'm called the "good-for-nothing."
Really, singing is the only thing I'm good at.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
I wanna prove that I can become somebody who's able to support his family.
To me, this band is the first step.
So,
Please remove
your shoes
before the
physical.
Kawabuchi-kun, I need your talent.
A-Awesome!
That was wonderful, Maruo-kun!
Much better than I expected!
I lost.
Alright, now all we need is a drummer.
Seiji, are you gonna tell me who it is you have in mind?
Oh, you'll find out soon enough.
Be ready for a surprise.
Hey, Rikko!
Yeah?
No school tomorrow, so if you're
free, wanna go to the beach?
Ma told me to take the midgets.
But lookin' after them alone is a tough job,
so I thought I'd ask you to tag along and help out.
Well, if you're busy...
Bon!
Hold on there.
You free tomorrow?
What do you say we have us a clammin' contest at the sea?!
Huh? "Clammin"?
Say, Sentaro...
I like clamming, but...
Ricchan,
what's "clammin"?
Is it some kind of competition?
Oh, Kaoru-san!
Clamming means digging up clams at the beach.
Oh!
It's confusing when this guy calls it a contest.
Are you going too, Ricchan?
I guess.
Great!
Then the threesome's set!
This is gonna be fun!
I'll need to mentally prepare myself this time.
If those two have a romantic moment.
I'll casually get out of their way and just pray for Ricchan's happiness.
Or that was the idea,
but maybe that's a not an issue.
I got a hamaguri clam!
That's a short-necked clam.
Hi.
Fancy meeting you here, Kawabuchi-kun!
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you.
What cute little girls and boys.
You know, there's a place over there where you can find a lot of razor clams.
Razors?!
You must be Ritsuko-chan.
I've heard about you from Yurika-senpai.
She said you were exceptionally cute!
Hey! Where are the razor clams?!
Oh, they're right over here.
Follow me.
What's with that guy?
Sweet-talking everyone...
Don't criticize the guy when you don't know 'im.
Nii-chan, you come too!
Sure.
Interesting, right?!
Who wants to try it?!
Me!
Me, me!
Salt!
Looks like they're having a good time.
Shall we join them?
I'll pass.
For some reason, that Matsuoka guy rubs me the wrong way.
What's wrong, Taiichi?!
Oh, no! I'll be back in a bit!
Crab!
You were surprised when the crab pinched you, right?
Thank goodness that's all it was!
Hey, Seiji!
Don't tell me your drummer is Kawabuchi!
Please, anybody but him!
I-I'm against it too!
He isn't as scary as you think.
All I have to do is set him free from what's tying him down,
and then everything should work out fine.
Hey, Bon!
Catchin' any short-necks?
Better not underestimate me!
I'm good at this kind of simple task.
Well, I ain't gonna lose either!
Alright!
Clammin' contest!
What do I get if I win?!
How about the record that Ricchan's dad gave you?!
Forget about it!
'Cause I'm gonna win anyway!
What about the Beatles record?
Kawabuchi-kun, did you listen to it?
Yeah, I heard it. Wasn't bad.
Did it stir up your interest?!
I wouldn't go that far. But still...
I'm thinkin' I'll help you out with
that band you're gonna have for the school festival.
Really?!
You'll join my rock band?!
Yeah.
Yay!
Bon, don't worry.
I'm so happy!
I'm just gonna be away 'til
the festival's over with.
We're just gonna be apart for a while, Nishimi-kun.
Let's send each other letters, okay?
I don't buy it!
I was wrong about you, traitor!
Wait, Bon!
Listen to me!
Don't touch me!
I don't want to hear it!
I don't need you anymore.
Kaoru-san! Wait!
Kaoru-san!
I know. I acted like an angry little kid.
But being separated from him scares the hell out of me.
I abandoned him without thinking.
Since coming here, I'd forgotten
that I'm not good at getting along with other people.
It's better this way.
After all, I've made it this far all on my own.
No problem... at all.
Good evening.
Tsutomu-chan, hey!
Look at the end of the counter!
It can't be.
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.