We're not asking for freedom if it comes in shackles
Especially in a world so imperfect
Anime-Koi
Presents
Chaika The Coffin Princess
kyou
It's days like today
kyou
that make me want to live
mou)
(I think. I think.)
mou)
It's the important people in my life
who help me make it through
mou)
(I think. I think.)
mou)
ryou
My vision narrows being surrounded by love
ryou
What do you expect me to do on a night like this?
We cross vows at the end of the road
Seeing into ourselves in our own reflections
utsushidaseyo
We're not asking for freedom if it comes in shackles
Especially in a world so imperfect
We're not interested in the answers that only lead to farewells
We'll look for you
until we find you
That's far enough, Brother.
What are you doing, Akari?
I know that you have the most active libido of anyone on this continent.
However, I cannot allow you
to disregard your sister and violate Chaika.
I don't even know where to begin correcting you...
but I'm not doing anything indecent.
You're too modest, Brother.
A defenseless girl sleeping before you
is like raw meat before a wild beast.
What do you take me for?
Oh, it's you, Guy.
You remember me? I commend you.
Unknown person!
Well? Did you come with some information for us again?
I have information on the next hero.
Simon Scania, a wizard of the Koenigsegg Empire.
His existence was last verified four years ago
in the town of Rademio, about three days from here by vehicle.
Four years ago?
That may be a clue to help you locate him.
You actually know all there is to know, don't you?
About what?
The locations of the remains.
I'm afraid I do not.
I am no more than a messenger.
I'm getting the unpleasant feeling that we're being deceived.
Do you? That's good.
You should feel untrusting and concerned.
That is desirable.
The Valley of No Return
Come on up and have a look!
We've got magic fuel of the
highest purity, freshly excavated from the southern mines!
Magic fuel, so many!
Buy this, and this!
The Valley of No Return?
It was always a place where fog tended to gather,
but since roughly four years ago, it no longer clears.
Four years ago?
And people who enter that valley never return?
Are there Fayla there?
I've never heard anything about that.
People who go there to find out never come back.
No one knows if they're alive or dead.
Missing? Simon Scania?
Yes. He was a wizard employed by the army,
but he vanished immediately after the war ended.
But a man who was called a hero, disappearing?
After the recent matter with Count Abarth,
and the revelation that Dominica Scoda died of illness...
Something seems off about what became of the eight
brilliant heroes after the war.
That's true.
There are even rumors that they were cursed by Emperor Gaz.
Cursed?
There were many dubious legends about him, like how he lived for 500 years
or that he had the magical talents of a monster.
Rumors aside, from
a financial perspective as well...
Emperor Gaz's remains are unparalleled as magic fuel of the highest purity.
Might obtaining them cause one to lose their best judgment?
It may be possible.
Regardless, if Chaika's group hopes to make contact with Simon Scania,
they are bound to show up here in Rademio.
We will continue the investigation.
I'm counting on you.
Don't!
He's using Fuchan to search the area.
Don't interrupt.
That's why I'm testing to make sure he's concentrating!
Well, don't test him by stabbing his head with a needle!
Vivi.
Yes?
What is a needle to you would be a sword to me, correct?
Yes.
Then you shouldn't point it at someone so easily.
Weapons can help people, but they can also harm them.
You must be careful in choosing when to use them.
Yes, sir.
Found them! Gillette-dono!
Oh, Gillette-dono...
I've located Chaika Gaz and the saboteurs.
Where?
On the opposite side of the town.
Simon Scania's location, Valley of No Return?
Yeah. It fits the timing of his disappearance.
I'd say it's possible.
Chaika, make ready your Gundo to fire at any time.
Right.
Come out!
I'm impressed you could detect us from that distance.
Four...
One of them should be a wizard.
Surrender.
We're not interested in a meaningless fight.
In your dreams!
Chaika Gaz, I ask of you:
What do you intend to do with the remains of Emperor Gaz?
Father, funeral.
A funeral?
That's...
That's all you wanted to do?
Uh-huh.
We mustn't believe her.
It's just a ruse to get away from us.
Akari, will you look after Chaika?
I'm taking out Gillette.
Not much chance I'll win, though.
Understood.
You intend to fight, no matter what?
Then I will devote all my strength to settling this.
I, Cavalier Albéric Gillette, declare war on you!
Let's go!
Toru!
What? What's going on here?
What are you guys doing?
Hold on, are you killing each other?!
No fair, Toru! Let me in on it!
A dragoon?!
It's on their side?!
We're not doing this for fun!
We want to escape! Help us!
Huh? What about killing?
You don't want me to be killed by someone else, do you?!
Oh, fine.
Okay, here we go.
I never expected a dragoon...
You saved our skins!
Any longer, and we would've been in trouble!
Chaika, is something wrong?
All magic fuel, left behind...
Just buy some more.
Well? Want to go back by vehicle?
No, with them around, I don't want to go near the town.
Head north.
Beyond the forest, there should be a valley of deep fog.
Efun... Heluste... Ru... Belguil... Fai... Sev...
Come, resounding perception.
The Locator!
Unclear.
What?
Search magic ineffective.
Probably also magic.
Magic? You mean the fog?
Yes.
Is that even possible?
Possible in theory.
But great power. Magic source needed.
Eh?
Remains?
Yes. Possible.
But why?
I guess we can't just wander down there carelessly.
Fredrica.
I want to take a look from above.
Can you carry us and fly over the valley?
I don't want to.
Because you won't keep your promise to me.
Last time, you said you'd fight me if I helped you, too.
But that was...
I never said I wouldn't fight you! Someday—
When is "someday"? Today? Tomorrow?
Just... someday, okay?
Brother, are you okay with this?
Huh? Hey! What are you doing?!
Remains down here! Search!
Oh, come on...
Guess I have no choice.
Chaika!
Hang on!
Brother!
You should be fine now.
Grateful!
Uh-oh.
Brother, what do we do?
There's nothing we can do!
Damn it!
Oh dear...
Is something wrong?
I had that dream from before again.
I still think about it sometimes.
When we fell from that cliff,
Akari should've been the one to survive, not me...
Toru, don't blame yourself.
I know.
I was able to come this far because you were always with me.
You're more important to me than anyone.
I feel the same way.
If I hadn't met you, my days wouldn't have felt so complete.
Because you were with me, I...
I'm grateful to you.
Toru...
What is this?
Incomprehensible.
Chaika, maybe I should've gotten rid of you sooner, after all.
Akari, please, calm!
Me, here! That, not me!
Then what is that?
Details unclear. Only possibility, magic.
Magic?
Illusion. Mind control. Multiple effects.
An illusion...
So you're saying Toru is seeing his own fantasies as reality?
Hey, wait up!
Exactly. Mind influences, fog transforms.
Wait!
Here. Say, "Aah."
Aah.
Stupid Toru! Stupid, stupid!
Hmm...
That Chaika and the building are all fog?
But the fact that he's seeing illusions like those
must mean that such desires exist in Brother's heart.
Unforgivable.
We must wake him immediately.
Chaika, remove this barrier.
I'm going to save Brother.
Danger... I think.
Me, Akari, Fredrica only safe inside protective barrier.
Remove, contact with fog immediately.
Minds controlled, like Toru.
We can't breathe the fog in?
So we just have to stand here and watch?
Only one way.
Toru, come here. Chance come.
Remove magic, grab Toru, activate magic again.
Our journey is ending soon, isn't it?
Yeah. Only one of your father's remains is left.
Once we defeat Albéric Gillette and take it, it's over.
Can you win?
It won't be easy.
But there's no other choice.
It doesn't matter anymore, Toru.
Eh?
Gathering the remains doesn't matter anymore.
Doesn't matter?
What do you mean?
I mean...
Whoa!
I've come for you, Chaika.
Albéric!
"Albéric"?
I'm going to marry Albéric!
What? Marry?
But what about the remains?!
Well, if I join Albéric, I'll get the last one, right?
Here. For you.
Oh, I'm so happy!
We're holding the ceremony after Father's funeral is over.
Huh?
But, you and I were...
When you're the princess of a kingdom,
you have to choose a marriage partner of proper lineage.
You can't hang around with the likes of a saboteur forever.
That's true, isn't it?
Well, thanks for everything, Toru.
Goodbye!
So long!
Wait...
Wait, Chaika!
Chaika! Wait!
You're...
You're just going to leave me?!
Toru's coming this way.
Chaika, remove the barrier.
R-Right!
Chaika! Don't leave me alone!
Chaika!
Chaika?
Brother, snap out of it!
Akari?
Hey! Snap out of it!
H-Huh?
It was all an illusion?
Sorry for the trouble.
When you all fell, you were the only one I couldn't catch.
So, what do we do now?
If we leave the barrier, we'll get trapped in an illusion again.
We can't move...
Move, possible.
Shoot interference magic into fog.
Partially obstruct opponent's magic.
So we'd be able to walk through areas where you fire that magic?
Right.
Use magic, move, repeat.
I see. From there, we'd only need to destroy the opponent's Gundo.
Okay, let's try it.
But what do you suppose the wizard is using this magic for?
We just have to catch him and ask...
If he's alive.
Ruler that controls...
Come forth, The Commander!
Let's go!
Uh-huh.
Eim... Halmus... Rom...
Ruler that controls...
Come forth, The Commander!
That's it!
Chaika! Can you see it?
Yes!
Naint, milta, ru...
Fly, blade!
The Ripper!
Looks like the magic has been undone.
Where is Simon Scania?
Brother.
Is that...
Who's there?
Sheesh. Barging into people's houses like that...
Are you Simon Scania?
You live here?
It broke...
Useless piece of junk.
Magic ain't worth jack when it really counts.
Want some?
No, thanks.
You're Simon Scania, right?
Simon? No.
I'm not Simon.
It's definitely him.
One of the eight heroes looked like this guy.
He's changed a lot, though.
I won't go back to the army. No way in hell.
The enemy discovered my unit's location.
I almost died.
Almost died?
They all died, other than me.
I know who it was...
It was Marco!
He sold us out to the enemy!
That bastard pretended to be my friend!
So it was Marco's fault.
Yeah. It was that bastard, Marco.
He's probably referring to the war.
He even took Elena, my beloved wife, from me!
Every damn one of them! All traitors!
Die!
I get it.
He was betrayed by his friend and his wife,
so he abandoned the army and came to this valley to live alone.
Then what was that magic before?
Anyone who gets deceived is a fool.
They all cry, lose hope, and waste away to bones.
He tries to show people illusions of friends betraying them
to put them through what he went through.
Like what happened to me.
Return remains.
Me, daughter of Gaz.
Gaz's daughter?
Father, funeral. Need remains.
His remains?
Those are the most useless pieces of junk in this world!
Just take the damn thing!
Hey.
We'll be taking this.
What? You want it?
N-No! I don't need that thing!
Take it!
Hey, is climbing the cliff the only way back to Rademio?
It just doesn't feel like it's over.
He was called a hero and obtained a fortune, plus the remains.
Not a very happy ending.
Guess it does no good for me to worry about it, though.
Toru, kind.
Nah, I wouldn't say "kind"...
Toru...
Um?
Illusion... Toru and me, together...
Oh, that?
Yeah, well...
Don't worry about it.
I no betray. Never.
That'd never happen anyway, right?
Me and you being, well... Right?
It couldn't possibly happen.
I mean, I guess I saw you because Akari and Fredrica were
out of the question...
Brother, why am I out of the question?
Huh? Well, you are, aren't you?
Right, Chaika?
Chaika?
Driving.
Wait...
Are you upset?
Driving!
Huh? Hey...
What?!
shitai mitai ni aruku michi
We're walking on the road like corpses
gira gira to taiyou ga teritsukeru
While the blazing sun beats down on us
omae wa itsuka namae sae
You'll fall into the depths of hell one day
wakaranaku naru kurai ochite yuku
And not even remember your name
hito wa naze ikiru no ka
Why do people live?
inochi kirikizan demo
Even when our life is in pieces
owarinaki bonnou wo daite odore ba
We embrace our endless desires and dance
mujou ka
Is that cruel?
kawaki no tani kara yojinobore
Climb up from the valley of thirst
kaze no oto ga kodama shite
You'll hear the echoing wind
goran warera wo michibiku kairaku wa
See, while the desires guide us
kanashimi wo tsukkitte iku genri
We have to push our way through sadness to get there
osoreru na
Do not be scared
furueru na
Do not tremble
ikiru no da
Live on
Empire of mountain pass?
Simple people, princess.
And all from same homeland.
But me, almost no memories of empire.
Next week, episode 8:
"Empire of Consolation."
Empire of Consolation