Princess Theiamillis is
currently undergoing a trial for the right
to the Fortorthe Empire's throne.
Corona Convention
A computer picks coordinates at random,
and she must claim the territory at
those coordinates for the Empire.
In the event that there is
intelligent life at the coordinates,
she must force them to swear loyalty.
This is the mission she must undergo.
Now that you
understand the situation, neanderthal, swear
eternal loyalty to me, and transfer
the rule of this apartment this instant.
I refuse.
I'm not giving up on the
5,000 yen monthly rent here.
I've been living here this whole time!
I plan on rebuilding my ancestors'
shrine on this very land.
Hmph. Selfish, every last one of you.
That's our line!
A-Also, there's bad guys
that will eventually show up
to try to get their hands on
the abundant magic here, so...
We get it, okay?
You want to have a cosplay party
and that's the backstory, right?
Can't you do that somewhere else?
Why does it have to be here?
It has to be here...
Please, believe me...
Anyway, Shizuka-dono has
forbidden us to use force.
We need to change how we go about this.
Yeah...
A way to fight without using force...
How about this?
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
More Invasions?!
Game Rules
Okay, I'll explain how this will work.
The five of us will each
get one sixth of the room.
No-man's land
So, the remaining sixth will be no-man's land
relegated to the furniture and such, correct?
Each sixth will be worth 180 points.
That means each centimeter
will be worth one point.
Lost Space
So, we fight over the points
through card games, huh?
That's correct.
The winners take points from the losers,
and in doing so, expand their territory.
Whoever comes in first takes three
points from the person in last.
Whoever comes in second gets one
point from whoever came in fourth.
Third place doesn't lose or gain any points.
When you run out of points, you're
kicked out of the room, then?
We will hold five games a day.
Each person will have a chance to
choose which game they'd like.
I'm sure everyone will be
skilled at different games.
Sounds fair to me.
Two of these girls have
never played cards before.
Sounds like a piece of cake.
I sure hope so.
I came in last again...
I was fourth. That was close.
Neanderthal, give me your
point, since I came in second.
Shut up.
You're getting pretty cocky for second place, Tulip.
Stop calling me that!
I'll call you what I want, Tulip.
H-How dare you!
Okay, today's results are in.
Here's the results for the five games.
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
Yurika got her butt kicked.
Why did this have to happen to me—
Tomorrow's dinner!
You shouldn't have put it there...
It seems that our strongest
enemy at the moment is Kiriha.
Yes, she takes risks and
always gets the right cards.
She'll be tough.
Anyway, that's all for today.
I'll see you again tomorrow.
Good night!
Sweet dreams!
Right.
Blue Knight.
Let's go home, Ruth.
Yes, Your Highness.
Good night, everyone.
Good night, Ruth-san.
Huh?
Wait!
There we go.
What are you doing?!
I'm going to sleep here tonight.
Go home!
Good night.
Hey!
Jeez...
Let's go to sleep.
Yeah.
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
Kiriha came in...
...first!
It's late!
You just don't wake up
no matter what I do, do you?
You tried to wake me up?
Huh? Well, yeah, I guess...
Oh, thank you.
I was up anyway, so, you know...
Oh yeah, Sanae.
Make sure the invaders don't try to do
anything to this room while I'm out.
What? You know I'm trying to take
this room from you, too, right?
You only want to stay in your home.
I can trust you more than the others.
You can?
Yeah.
Watch the place for me.
Sure. Got it.
See you later.
Talk to you later.
What took you so long, Kou?
Sorry about that.
We need to hurry or we'll be late, Makkenji!
Acting like it's not your fault...
I just saw him off...
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
I was first today.
Oh, that's not—
Hm?
You pull the yarn through to the
right before you finish the stitch,
Satomi-kun.
Oh, I get it.
I knew something was up.
Sorry, I'm pretty bad at this.
Everyone's that way when they start out.
you didn't have to get that for me.
Don't worry about it.
It's a hobby of mine.
Is it?
Well, thanks. I'll try it.
This is pretty good!
I like this blend, myself.
It's got a nice, mellow
aroma to it, don't you think?
I bet Satomi-san would believe her...
I wish he'd believe me...
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
Don't count me out yet!
Kisshouharukaze High School
You're going to join the cooking club?
I haven't decided yet.
I'm already busy as a landlady, so...
You must be pretty impressive
for them to scout you, though.
Yeah, but...
Neanderthal... I wonder if there's something
I can do to make him swear
his loyalty to me faster.
Loyalty isn't born overnight.
It's born from the time you spend together.
I understand that, but—
The time we spend together, hm?
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
I'm back in first.
Huh? Kou, you're not headed to your club?
The club president is busy today,
so we're not meeting.
Why not go home, then?
What are you doing here?
I keep thinking about how
obnoxious everyone at the house is...
Huh?
Nothing.
I just thought I could
relax better at school.
That's what he was saying!
I see.
Relax better, huh?
I'm back—
K-Kiriha-san, why are you dressed...
I was waiting for you, Koutarou.
I've been using your kitchen.
I have some here for you, too.
What are you up to, Kiriha-san?
I just thought it'd be nice, Koutarou.
Huh?
I wouldn't mind if you felt
like you owed me, though.
I'll pay you for your troubles.
Would that work?
I thought you'd say that.
Very well. That's a deal, then.
Hurry up. It'll get cold.
This looks pretty good.
Here you are, Satomi-sama.
Oh, thank you, Ruth-san.
I've made a deal with Ruth, as well.
I had Theia-dono and Ruth help me in exchange
for making some for both of them.
Well, let's eat.
Wait!
Huh?
Koutarou, please, can you let me possess you?
I'm a ghost, so I can't eat anything,
but if I possess someone, I can taste it!
I see...
But, why me?
I don't want to owe anyone
else here anything!
I have a truce with you, so how about it?
I'm not going to get sick or anything?
Of course you won't!
Please. I haven't tasted food in so long!
Fine.
Come on, do it!
Thank you!
This is all you have to do?
Yeah, now I'll get to taste it!
Eat up!
That was surprisingly simple.
Useful!
Surprising!
I don't really understand ghosts.
All right. Let's eat—
Well...
Hm?
What about Yurika-sama?
Hm? Didn't you have your own dinner?
Um, she can have some of mine...
There's no need to show her pity.
It's your own fault.
You didn't help out, either.
B-But...
I'm so hungry...
Come on.
I'll give you some of mine.
R-Really?!
Okay, let's finally eat!
Let's eat!
It's been so long since I tasted this!
It's great!
Yeah, this is pretty good.
I'm glad.
How is it, Princess Theia?
Well...
It's not bad.
Not as good as Fortorthen cuisine.
Why'd you have to say that, Tulip?
Just say it's good.
Shut up!
Stop calling me that!
I think I got a lot of potatoes here...
Give me more meat.
Shut up! No more talking!
Ignore Yurika! Eat more, Koutarou!
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
Your Highness, and everyone else, you can do it!
There we go!
I'm out!
I'm first!
And now, I'm gonna hit the restroom.
So, is everything going as planned, Kiriha?
Hm? What are you talking about, Theia-dono?
You can't hide it from me.
You're making dinner every night lately,
pretending to ease tensions,
but I know you're planning something.
I'm not sure about that.
You've been up to something
lately yourself, Theia-dono.
What are you guys up to?
You're going to do something?
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
Yurika couldn't stop losing.
The timing's a bit weird, but we have
some transfer students for you all.
Yurika Nijino
Kurano Kiriha
Theiamillis Gre Fortorthe
Yurika Nijino-san.
Ruthkhania Nye Pardomshiha
Kiriha Kurano-san.
And a transfer student from
Europe, Theiamillis-san,
and Ruthkhania-san.
I want everyone to get along with them.
Nice to meet you all.
I tried to stop them.
Told them they were going too far.
Damn you all...
You're trying to invade my high school, now?!
Kurano-san, you're really beautiful.
You really think so? Thank you.
All of the guys have been staring at you.
Especially your boobs.
Be careful. There's a lot of perverts out there.
Thank you.
I'll be careful.
What an act...
She looks like your perfect honor student.
You two speak great Japanese.
We studied really hard to learn.
It's a primitive language,
so it was pretty difficult.
What first made you interested in Japan?
I guess I got into
traditional Japanese music.
You know that one song that
was a big hit last year...
What was it?
"Festival Flame Drums", yes?
That's right!
I thought that song was really great.
She's acting like herself,
but she's doing her best to
gather information, I see.
She comes off like one of those
transfer students that are a little weird.
Nijino-san, are you okay?
The teacher's pretty mean,
making you copy down the book
right after you transferred
just because you got an F.
I know, right?
I mean sure, it was a middle
school-level problem, but...
Well, you can do it, Nijino-san!
Uh, yes!
You can do it, Yurika!
And she's...
Well, pretty much same as ever.
Why did they have to come to
the one place I could relax?!
That's exactly why they're here.
They're trying to put some pressure on you.
I see...
In that case, I need to make my own plans.
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
I'm not going easy on you all anymore!
What shall we do for lunch, Your Highness?
I hear the croquette
pockets are really good.
Really?
Hey, you freshman!
Huh?
You're interrupting our sacred practice.
Who do you think you are?!
Are you daft?!
Ah, we're very sorry!
Oh? Sacred, you say?
And who do you think I—
Theia-chan!
Sorry, they just transferred here.
Let's go.
Hey, what are you doing?
That was close, Theia-chan.
The men's cheer team is known to do things
to people who don't listen to them.
They're the strongest bullies in the school.
Oh, really?
So, they're the ones who
control this school, huh?
Hmph.
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
I really need to start winning soon...
Dear Magical Girl Rainbow Yurika,
Please come to the student union after school.
Satomi Koutarou
Right Here
La, la, la! I never thought
I'd succeed so quickly!
I'm sure he wants to...
Yurika, I finally understand now
that we're going to school together.
You're a real magical girl.
I'm sorry for doubting you this whole time.
You finally believe me, now that
I'm going to school with you!
That was easy!
Geh.
Um, are you okay?
You're being nice? To me?
Today's such a good day.
Way to go, Yurika!
I'm glad you're okay.
Yep!
Oh, yeah. Do you know where this is?
The student union...
Go down the hallway here,
take the connecting hallway to the
right, and it should be right there.
Thank you!
See you later!
La, la, la!
She's fun.
I think this is it.
Satomi-san!
It's me, Yurika!
It's Magical Girl Rainbow Yurika!
Who are you guys?
We heard about you.
Huh?
You're one of us.
You friend, Satomi-san, told us.
Huh?
He said you love cosplay more than anyone.
What?!
Yes, we are...
The Cosplay Society!
Cosplay?
N-No! I don't really like cosplay...
Satomi-san also said you wouldn't admit it.
We're taking her with us.
Right!
You've got it all wrong!
That went well.
Yurika's out of the race now.
You're pretty devious,
aren't you, Koutarou...
Hm? I did this for Yurika.
I mean, if she has a place to express
herself in the Cosplay Society,
then she won't need my apartment, right?
I'm not sure about that...
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
Yurika won today!
What are you looking at?
Did you find something interesting?
You've forgotten to camouflage yourselves.
You're right!
Oh no!
Anyway, to answer your question,
I did indeed find something interesting.
Kisshouharukaze High School
Club Obstacle Course
Marathon
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
Lost
Space
Yurika's made a comeback!
Yurika always picks old maid for her game.
Yeah.
Well, everyone gets to pick
what they want for their game.
I guess no matter the game, we're still playing cards.
No... I'm not cosplaying...
Yurika, it's your turn!
Hurry up and take a card.
O-Oh yeah.
Yurika got her card!
She's out!
Huh?
What? I did! I'm out!
So, Yurika came in first three times in a row.
Yurika's doing better, lately.
Heh, heh, heh!
Yurika's better at cards when she's tired.
Your cosplay plan's backfiring.
Yeah, but...
I'm done!
I'm out!
Princess, you can't be selfish—
I'm tired of this!
I'm tired of playing these
card games all the time!
I'm in agreement with Tulip.
I'm pretty tired of this, myself.
So, you finally realize you're
meant to be my servant?
Hell no!
Tired of this, huh?
I thought this would happen sooner or later.
Huh?
Well, it's my turn to pick
the game next, right?
How about participating in this?
Kisshouharukaze High School
Club Obstacle Course
Marathon
"Club Obstacle Course Marathon"?
Huh?!
What?
I see.
We fight, fair and square, in
a school-sanctioned competition.
That might not be so bad.
You're willing to challenge me in
a test of strength and stamina?!
Sounds good to me!
We're playing old maid again?
I said I was tired of this...
Well, it's another week before the marathon.
Guess we'll just have
to wait until next week.
I picked the old maid again!
Next Episode: Friends and Promises