This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
So you're telling me...
that the chocolate I just poured into a mold and let cool doesn't count as handmade,
so you won't accept it?
That's what you're saying?!
Well... yeah, pretty much.
I see...
I get it!
If that's what you want...
Remember this!
Next year, I'm gonna make one that even you'll like
and smash it into your stupid cheeks!
Kaburaya Junior High School
The Chocolate Files
Making chocolate from cocoa beans is just impossible!
It would seem so...
But I'm not giving up.
I'm gonna make the best chocolate ever with my own two hands!
And if Fuku's still not happy,
I'll clap him in irons and read him this book from cover to cover!
And if even that's not enough, I'll hammer the chocolate into his mouth!
Mayaka, I'm rooting for you!
Uh-oh...
If there's any way I can help, just let me know!
Oh right, Chi!
Do you know any candy stores or places where they sell the ingredients?
Now that you mention it...
I remember there was an ingredient shop for professionals near the marketplace.
Would you like me to show you?
You would?
Sure.
Hooray!
Can you keep this...
...a secret from Fukube?
Then I'll show you where it is on Sunday.
Aren't you forgetting someone here?
Okay. Thanks.
Oh, Oreki.
Yeah?
Don't you tell him either, okay?
Sure...
On pain of death.
I won't.
I really wish you wouldn't glare at me like that.
That's Satoshi's.
Hey, Houtarou!
You showed up at just the right time.
How about a battle for old times' sake?
Well, I don't need to be home in a hurry.
This reminds me of junior high.
Yeah, me too.
I'll take the Viper 2.
You're using Raiden, right?
It's the only one I know.
I thought he'd keep running away.
Is this how he always fought?
No, it's definitely different.
During junior high, he only focused on winning the game.
He wasn't picky about the way he played as long as it meant he'd win.
If he lost, he didn't even try to hide his frustration.
That wasn't fair!
He was a really sore loser.
Switch sides and let's go again!
Is he gonna dash above me?
Good game, man.
I like how vigorously you pull on the joystick, Houtarou.
Hey,
about that game...
Why did you rush at me like that at the end?
In a battle between giant robots, close combat's the really exciting part.
Don't you agree?
This is how he is now.
He's changed a lot from junior high.
Jeez!
Why am I so nervous already?!
He'll be only too happy to accept it, I'm sure.
That'd be nice...
By the way, Chi...
Do you have a guy you like?
Uh, I...
Itchy...
Here, a block of chocolate to remember me by.
From Oreki Tomoe, with heartfelt...
Condolences
condolences.
Oreki, good morning!
Morning.
How did Ibara's chocolate turn out?
It's done!
But it wasn't easy.
We had to sample lots of other chocolate to get it right.
I bet you sampled as much as you could, huh?
You're mean, Oreki.
Sorry.
Anyway, after all that we were able to complete it.
So that's what it means to put your heart into something.
Isn't it wonderful?
So what's the plan, then?
Mayaka can't get out of going to the Manga Lab,
so she'll probably just leave it in the clubroom for him.
It's a shame.
Satoshi will be happy with that.
Oh...
Oreki...
Um... Today is Valentine's Day, right?
My family has this rule against giving presents to people close to us during the year.
So...
Even on Valentine's Day...
What's that...
Um...
supposed to...
mean?
They say it's gonna snow today.
What, seriously?
And I forgot my umbrella, too...
We'll be late!
Y-Yeah.
Let's go!
O-Okay...
Earth Sci. Prep. Room
To Fuku
Please accept this
Valentine's Day chocolate.
Mayaka
Houtarou, are you going to the clubroom?
No, I'll wait in the library and see if this sleet stops or turns to snow.
The clubroom's so cold.
You're going there?
Yeah.
Ibara can't go because she has to be at the Manga Lab.
News travels fast, I see.
You heard from Chitanda?
See you later.
Satoshi.
Good luck.
With what? Jeez.
Earth Sci. Prep. room
Library
Oreki!
Ah, Chitanda.
Do you know where Fukube is?
He didn't turn up?
Nope. What if something happened to him?
I saw him about half an hour ago.
He said he was going to the clubroom.
Okay. Then I'll wait a little longer.
Fukube... you're late.
Oreki!
Wait!
This is terrible!
The sleet finally stopped, so I'm going home.
It can wait until tomorrow.
Hey...
I'm sorry.
But please, at least hear me out.
It's my fault for carelessly leaving the room unlocked.
What am I going to say to Mayaka?
Satoshi,
what happened?
Well...
The chocolate...
The chocolate that Mayaka made...
was stolen!
I get it. I'll help.
Thanks.
I don't want to see what happens if Ibara finds out her chocolate was stolen.
I'm not a fan of horror stories.
History of the Hanya mask
As the winds of spring rise...
Beginning of Spring
Hyouka
Oh, Oreki,
Freshly waxed.
No entry.
we can't use the west stairway to reach the fourth floor.
Let's take the east.
Sorry, do you have a moment?
Does this look straight to you?
Not at all.
It looks trapezoidal.
You lowered it too much.
Huh? Well...
Oh, crap.
It was here.
It was in a transparent plastic bag.
About this big, shaped like a heart.
Quite big.
It was here when I went to look for Fukube.
When did you return to the clubroom?
Past five.
I didn't want to lock the door for just fifteen minutes...
You shouldn't blame yourself, Chitanda.
It's my fault for being so late.
Does Ibara know?
No.
It might not be the nicest thing, but I'd prefer to look for it first.
It's not in this room?
No. Fukube and I checked this room and looked around the building.
Satoshi too?
We met by the stairs, so we came to the clubroom together.
I see.
How long was that Artisan guy there?
Artisan guy?
That guy with the glasses.
Oh, the Artisan Workshop member.
When I went to look for Fukube,
I'm sure he was already working on that poster.
Great.
If he was there, he might remember who came and went.
I see!
Wait.
What if he was the culprit?
Not a chance.
Who would just hang around putting up a poster after committing theft?
True that.
You're asking if I saw anyone pass by?
Yes.
Sure.
I remember all three of them.
Three...
Who were they?
Do you remember any character—
One.
Two.
Three.
So the culprit is still on the fourth floor.
Satoshi, what clubs meet on the fourth floor?
The Classics Club, the Light Music Club, the Astrology Club and the Philosophy Circle.
But I think only we and the Astrology people are still here.
By the way, I'm surprised to see
that you're actually trying.
What if the sleet comes back?
Cut it out.
Now we can get it back.
But why would anyone do this?
That's the problem.
First of all, let's consider the possibilities.
General Use Room #5
Coming!
Huh? The Classics Club?
Give back our chocolate!
Sorry, we just wanted to ask you something.
What?
Um...
A box of Valentine's Day chocolate was taken from our clubroom.
We're looking for anyone who might know what happened.
Chocolate?
Why would we even...
Did you see anyone pass by here between a quarter to five and five?
Well, the discussion was getting kinda lively.
I don't remember exactly when,
but only Nakayama and Yoshiwara left the room.
Oh, and Oda too, maybe.
Three out of five?
Has anyone gone home?
No.
Is Oda that girl?
She's Nakayama.
Lemme make this clear, detective boy.
None of 'em brought any chocolate back here.
Hey guys, any of you seen any chocolate around?
Man, you just gotta rub salt into the wound, don't you?
I wish...
No chance.
You heard 'em.
Is that all?
Thank you very much.
Sorry to have bothered you.
Well, whatever.
Where were we again?
Sawakiguchi got angry...
Of course.
But we have to get Mayaka's chocolate back!
Houtarou.
Let's just return to the classroom for now.
I should put an end to this.
Is there any way to reach the fourth floor other than the east stairs?
Realistically speaking, only the freshly waxed west stairs.
But there was no sign anyone had used them.
I see.
By the way, have you checked the girls' restroom?
I'll go look!
Do you really think it'd be in the restroom?
It might as well be.
Might as well?
Satoshi!
I've pretty much figured it out.
Shut up.
I see.
It wasn't there.
Then there's only one place it could be.
Huh?
Why are you all here?
Um... Mayaka—
So?
How was it?
The chocolate I made.
Straight to the point.
Ibara—
I'm sorry, Mayaka!
I left the classroom unlocked, and the chocolate was stolen.
I'm sorry!
I see...
It was stolen...
Mayaka, I...
Don't make that face. It's nothing you should apologize for.
But it's hard.
I'm going home.
Don't worry about it, Chi!
Step aside.
What do you want to do?
I'll find the chocolate, even if I have to use force.
Otherwise, how could I face Mayaka tomorrow?
It's not your fault.
I can't forgive myself!
Mayaka should've been happy today!
I can't say I understand how you feel.
I'm nowhere near as emotional as you are.
But please leave this to me. I've got an idea.
I can't do it with you around, though.
You have an idea?
Yeah.
It was Nakayama from the Astrology Club.
Ibara's chocolate was quite big.
You wouldn't be able to hide it under a guy's uniform.
Even if you did, you couldn't move naturally.
But a girl's uniform is different.
If you tie it to your leg, the skirt will hide it.
I'll deliver Ibara's chocolate to Satoshi today.
Leave this to me. Calm down and go home.
Okay.
I'll believe in you.
Shall we get going?
Yeah.
Satoshi, give me your bag.
I'm giving you Ibara's chocolate.
Now I've fulfilled the promise I made to Chitanda.
You were the one who stole Ibara's chocolate.
Nice job, Houtarou.
When I heard the chocolate was stolen,
I thought you were the only one who'd do something like that.
After I talked to the Artisan guy, that confirmed it.
You said he'd lowered the poster too much.
You wouldn't have said that unless you'd told him to lower the right side of it before.
You probably waited in the guys' restroom on the third floor until Chitanda passed,
Earth Sci. Prep. Room
then took the chocolate from the empty clubroom.
But it was too big,
so you couldn't put it in your bag, nor was there another bag big enough in the clubroom.
You couldn't risk running into Chitanda while escaping with it in your hand.
So in the end, you...
You didn't hesitate for one moment before breaking it into pieces?
Now we're even.
Even?
Last April, you helped me escape Chitanda using that Golden Web story.
Oh, that's right.
But no one got hurt there.
Except for you.
Could you at least explain yourself?
If you say it was just a joke...
What if I do?
I'll have no choice but to punch you.
For Chitanda and Ibara as well.
I'd rather not get punched.
I don't wanna say it, but I guess I've got no choice.
Do you think I'm the dedicated type?
You're more of a hobbyist.
That's where you're wrong.
People like that immerse themselves in a particular field,
and in that field they don't want to lose to anyone.
Are you different, then?
I am. I can never be the best.
But to be honest, I've already stopped trying.
You felt something was off at the arcade too, right?
I wasn't going on about losing.
Yeah.
I used to dedicate myself to a bunch of things for the sake of winning.
I was a real bore, wasn't I?
I wanted to win so much, but even if I did,
it was a boring, nasty way to win.
It's not fun unless you have fun winning.
One day I realized that.
I dedicated myself to not dedicating myself to anything.
I've had lots of fun since then.
I'm happy every day!
But there was one problem left:
Mayaka.
She's really nice. In a class of her own.
It's like a dream that she wants to be with me.
Then...
But...
Should I dedicate myself to her?
I want to be with her, that much is for sure.
But I don't want to dedicate myself.
It's all just for my own convenience.
I haven't even considered her feelings.
Don't you think I'm a bit too selfish?
Even though I don't want to neglect her.
But if I let go of my easy-going style and accepted Mayaka,
I'd end up turning back into my old self.
To be honest, that's what I'm scared of.
That's why you won't accept her?
Yeah.
Last year, and this year too.
But I still don't have an answer.
This was the only way not to accept a chocolate I couldn't accept.
But you hurt Chitanda!
These things don't go as well for me as they do for you.
Chitanda was the mistake in this equation between Mayaka and I.
Mayaka! Wait!
Chi?
Um—
I'm sorry, Chi!
I know who stole the chocolate.
Last Valentine's Day I told Fuku that I'd wait for his answer.
Today was the anniversary of that day.
Then the chocolate...
He probably has it, yeah.
I... see.
It feels like I've deceived you. I'm sorry.
It's okay... I'm the one who let things escalate.
Then, when Oreki said that he thought one of the Astrology Club members had stolen it...
I think he was covering for Fuku.
I see.
But how could Fukube just act as if it got stolen?
I know, right?
Yeah!
It pisses me off so bad!
But the fact that I still love him pisses me off even more!
Chi, let's go and eat a cake somewhere!
Okay.
And that's the whole story, Houtarou.
What you gonna do?
We can't tell Chitanda this.
I know. I'd rather get punched.
Do you know how you're gonna answer?
I just need a little more time.
I see.
You're pretty stupid for someone so smart.
Guess I should tell him, "I'm sorry. I didn't know anything about you."
No way I could.
Yeah, I delivered the chocolate to Satoshi.
I see. I'm glad to hear it.
Don't worry too much about all this.
Oreki,
thank you for everything you did today.
Sure.
Mayaka
Call
Write message
FaceTime
Send contact details
Add to most used
Hello. Um...
We've gotta talk.
Not bad.
The situation is unscientific
A montage of emotions
Who's calling who?
You look away when our eyes are about to meet
I can feel it
Am I just imagining things? It's so cold of you
It takes talent to read minds
You know
I wanna know
Don't you?
I'll fix the fire of youth in your heart while I can
If we can do it today why leave it for tomorrow
I want to solve your mystery
Look for the back of the boy, burdened with secrets
Even today
You are a fantasy and I'm drawn to you
This growing curiosity
There's no twist in the story
I can't stop thinking about it
It's so interesting
But why?
Next time: Doll in the Distance.
Doll in the Distance