Don't drink too much even if your customer asks you to...
I'm always the one picking you up.
Anyway, thank you.
I'm glad I have such a capable sister.
Jeez...
Judy!
Why...
Why?!
Is this where Judy Devens passed away?
Who are you?
Everyone called you Phantom, right?
I heard about it from Judy's friends.
You're the one that kills people in American gangs.
So you're a true assassin, right?
You're an assassin, right?
The assassin, Phantom.
Yeah, that's right.
Cal?
Please! Kill them all!
The guys who were at the alley last night, the guys who shot,
and the guys who were supposed to retrieve the money.
Kill all the people who caused Judy's death...
Can you do it?
Judy...
I met Phantom.
Reiji will definitely avenge you...
With that five million...
Cal.
Let me make it clear.
Five million isn't enough.
Really?
But you only need a little more.
You could make it even by yourself.
What should I do?
Become my assistant in the meantime.
Wow!
Hey, so if I become your assistant,
I'll be able to see the moment when Judy gets avenged with my own eyes, right?
Before that, there's something you need to get.
Have you decided yet?
Hold on.
Just pick the one you want the most.
But I want all the clothes here equally.
If I just picked one, I'd have to give up the others, right?
Don't worry.
This isn't the only chance that you'll get to shop.
I'll bring you here again if there's something else you want.
Really?
Yeah, so pick a set of clothes you want to wear today.
Then...
Hey, hey, is it cute?
Does it look good on me?
Yeah, it looks really good on you.
This is my first time wearing such light clothes!
Give me a second, okay?
I'll cook after I'm done here.
Why are you cleaning?
Because it's really dirty.
There's no helping it.
An assassin who cleans his own house doesn't sound too tough.
Just leave something like this to your assistant.
All right, thanks.
I'll do my best to earn that money on top of the five million.
Hey Reiji, do you have any family?
Family?
They're in heaven.
Really?
Yeah.
Just like me.
Are your parents already...
I have no idea.
I ran away from my bastard old man,
and then Judy took me in.
If she hadn't, I'd be dead already.
So that's why you're siblings?
Yup, she's my only family.
But Judy died...
Sorry.
It's all right.
What am I to do now that Judy's dead?
Where should I go?
What should I do?
I don't have any idea.
I was like you once,
not knowing what to do.
There are many ways to die.
Cal.
Cal, give me your hand.
Yes?
Your reward for today.
This is...
Thanks, Reiji!
I'll treat it with care.
I'll treat it with a lot of care...
...forever.
All the actors have gathered.
Claudia, the woman who used me through crafty tricks,
and now wants to create another scheme.
Godoh Daisuke, her partner who wants to make inroads into Inferno along with her.
Wisemel, the one who discovered the conspiracy and is trying to stop it.
And there's another new actor.
Let me create the best stage.
Now, it's time to get busy.
Ein.
Could that sniper be Judy's killer?
Probably.
At the very least, they're part of the same group.
Let me witness it...
There! Someone's there behind the water tower!
Show me that face of yours!
Reiji?!
You bastards...
You can't, Mr. Godoh!
You scared me...
I...
Want to...
Reiji!
Did you get shot? Did you hit him?
No, it just scratched me.
Reiji, you idiot...
Why did you do that?
I had to see that person's face no matter what.
Idiot...
Good job, observer.
He's the one who killed Judy.
You've avenged her.
Mission completed.
Very well. Withdraw via route C immediately,
and wait for instructions.
Yes,
Master.
Hey, I heard some rumors.
Is it true that Issac of the Bloodies died?
Yes, it is.
Then avenging Judy is done...
I see.
Hey, so how was it?
How was my assassin training?
If it's fine with you, I can help you with your assassinations from now on.
No more assassinations.
No more...
Then does that mean...
I'm fired?
However...
I wouldn't want to miss your cooking.
For the time being, I'll let you be my kitchen maid.
Really?! Yay! Maid!
I've always wanted to try that!
Maid clothes are really cute, aren't they?!
Reiji.
What's up?
You know,
I really want to become your assistant.
Cal, that's...
I know that you don't want me to become an assassin.
Because you know the pain of an assassin.
Cal, you can walk whatever path you want. Do whatever you want...
But why do you want to become an assassin?
Do you hate assassins?
Yeah.
Does that mean you hate yourself too?
Yeah, I do.
Killing is like my second nature and I can't go back.
That's why I hate myself.
But Reiji...
I'm already broken.
Do you want to become like me?!
Sorry Reiji... I...
Cal, I said too much.
Sorry.
But it's true.
I don't know how many have died because of me.
If I weren't there, they would still be living.
They could have all gone back to their families and lovers.
It's not your fault.
You just accepted a job that was going to be done either way.
It's not as pretty as you described...
Then, do you really want to kill?
Do you shoot just because you want to kill?
Do you like to kill?
You don't, right?
But Cal...
When you kill your first person, the whole world changes.
Everything you see... Everything you hear... Everything changes.
You won't be your kind self anymore.
I don't want you to become like that.
This isn't where you belong.
You shouldn't come into the world that I'm in.
But...
But you'll always stay in there, right?
If I go there, then I'll always be able to stay with you.
Cal...
I don't want to leave you...
I want to stay by your side forever.
I want to help you.
I just...
...want to be with you.
I get it now. I...
...really do want to go back.
By doing that,
I can stay with you.
There's no need. I'll go to your world.
I'll go to where you are.
Let me go... Let me go back...
Back to the world where you are.
Reiji said he'll stay by my side...
There's no...
There's no mistake to that!
I can't believe you've got work this late.
This might take a while.
You can go to bed.
No, I'll stay up.
I picked up a broken video cassette recorder during the day.
I want to try to fix it.
Just buy a new one.
That's such a waste.
Maybe it can still be used.
It can still be used, huh?
That's right.
Come back soon.
Yeah.
Promise.
Yeah, I promise.
It's a promise!
Yay! I did it! I did it!
Hmm... I think the video store is still open.
Reiji! Reiji!
You can't go in!
It's dangerous!
But Reiji is... Reiji is...
Reiji!
Reiji...
You'll come back, right?
We promised...
Liar...
You said you wouldn't leave me...
You said you'd be with me...
Correct. He's a liar.
You've been deceived this whole time.
Who are...
...you?
At a time like this...
Just cry.
Right now,
you can be like your old self...