Yer back, eh?
Ushio's presence has vanished.
Finally, that little girl has been eliminated.
What a joyous day this is.
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Made in Black
Haine!
Shoot!
Akari!
I can't take ya along, Brother.
Ya wouldn't taste good anymore, either.
The immunity!
By the way, Shinpei, I know ya just got back, but
yer on the edge of the cliff, ain't ya?
The event horizon!
The post-loop limit is super close.
If I die from here, it's over!
Crap! They were gunning for this!
Has she been watching me as a crow this whole time?
I'm powerless.
I can't even defeat a single stray Shadow on my own.
Brother...
It's okay, Akari.
I'll protect ya.
No!
Don't give up.
It's all over if I die.
Think objectively!
Wait! Please wait!
If ya make me loop, the fact that ya copied Akari will revert too!
Are ya okay with that?!
Ya can inherit copied data too, can't ya?
Then, back then, ya didn't eat all those people at the shrine?
It's all yer fault.
I had to use my regained power just to chase after ya.
I'm going to shave yer life down to nothing.
Damn it!
Bye-bye.
Wait!
They stopped?
You...
They're gone.
Can we assume we're saved?
She's gone, and the strays are too.
How were we saved?
This is...
Damn it...
Wh-What's wrong?
It's nothing.
History
Alan
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Gotta contact the others.
Alan
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
No way...
Ushio's dead?
Yes, the situation has changed.
We should meet up and reform our plans.
Okay, where?
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
How about the north eastern island of Torajima?
That remote island you can only get to during low tide?
Yes, low tide is in 30 minutes.
I've told Mio and Sou as well.
I'll meet them at Kofune's and head to the island from there.
All right, then we'll see you on Torajima in 30 minutes.
Yep.
See you in half an hour, Miss Nagumo.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
Damn! I can't get through!
We've gotta get out of this mountain fast.
It's dangerous here.
R-Right!
I've gotta let everyone know that Ushio's gone!
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Call ended
Haine, when did ya copy that body?
Take a step back and think about it.
This isn't in Ushio's memories.
It's a hole in their pseudo-loops.
Wonderful.
I won't let Shinpei survive to see the ritual.
I have work for you, Shide.
Bistro Kofune
Leave it to me.
I'm back!
Where are Mio and the others?
She left with Sou.
About half an hour ago, they said they were gonna meet with ya.
Did they say where they were going?
No, they didn't.
Shinpei, did something happen?
Watch those kids for me!
Ya kids hungry?
U-Um...
I'll have a smoothie, please!
They're going to meet me?
Don't tell me there's a Shadow of me.
How? I was never copied!
The times at the funeral and Koba Mart were basically erased from history.
No...
No!
Ya gonna copy this too?
No, he's already
been copied by Mother.
It was Haine who copied me, right?
And Haine came after the festival ended on the third loop.
And now they're using my Shadow from then in this one!
But how did it make the call?
They can't use a copy of my phone without erasing the original.
Shin?
From my room?
What're ya doin' here?
Mio? Who did this to ya?
So that phone call from earlier was...
Ya could've pulled it out a little gentler.
S-Sorry.
I'll give ya my memories.
Mio?
Sis is dead, so now it's possible her hack was undone.
That's what Shin said!
She could be our enemy again!
No way. Mio did this?
Mio got a call from yer phone saying Sis died.
That true?
Yeah, but I didn't make that call.
My Shadow tricked them.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
But I'm sorry that I couldn't protect Mio.
I knew yer Shadow existed.
I saw it in Sis's pseudo-loop.
And ya told me that Shiori, or Haine,
copied ya and gave birth to it.
Yeah.
But I can't believe two versions of my phone are able to exist and be used in this world.
What an oversight.
I just remembered.
He copied my phone in the third loop.
Then Haine absorbed everyone into her body in the end.
So Haine carried it into this loop.
This is bad.
Haine read Miss Nagumo's memories too.
Now her number's exposed.
Where did Mio and the others go?
It's Miss Nagumo.
Hello?
Yo, me.
It's my voice.
How's it feel gettin' a call from yerself?
Is this Haine?
How are ya calling from Nagumo's phone?
What happened to her?
Come see it with yer own eyes, observer.
Hizuru's group is on Torajima,
and Mio's is at Alan's garden.
It's yer choice on which you'll save.
Wait! Hey!
Hello? Hello?!
He hung up.
Calm down, Shin.
Think of all the possibilities.
I know that!
Haine is thinking with yer mind right now too.
She's using yer objectivity against us.
Step back.
Why is Haine doing something this elaborate?
Searchlight Ruins
Navy Listening Station Ruins
First Battery Ruins
Third Battery Ruins
Hitogashima Elementary School
Hitogashima Junior High
Hitogashima Lighthouse
Transmission Tower
Mt. Takanosu
Hishigata Clinic
Bistro Kofune
Second Battery Ruins
Omoto Beach
Hamaji Market
Club Miyako
Koba Mart
Alan's Field
Hitogashima Port
Ja River
Shinja Pond
Funeral Home
Crematorium
Graveyard
Shrine Grove
Fourth Battery Ruins
Hito Shrine
Torajima
Quarry Ruins
Do I go for Mio or Nagumo?
She could be lying about both and they could be dead already.
That doesn't mean we just don't do anything about it.
I'd rather regret doing something than regret doing nothing.
Let's gather up anything and everything we can use as weapons!
Summer Time Rendering
10 minutes earlier
Alan's field
What are ya doing here,
Karikiri?
These cucumbers look fantastic.
Alan has quite the green thumb.
Don't ya think, Mio?
Get back, Mio!
I prefer pickles the Japanese way.
But I've come to love western pickles as well ever since I tried some at Kofune's.
It must be that French influence.
Where's Shinpei?!
But Mother hates both.
Such a pickle, isn't it?
I wonder what humans taste like.
Simultaneously
Torajima
Is something wrong?
This area is dangerous.
Wh-Whaddya mean?
Hizuru, was it really Shinpei that called ya?
Ryuunosuke cannot distinguish between humans and Shadows over the phone.
However, the call did originate from Ajiro Shinpei's device.
Ushio was killed, right?
It's possible Shinpei's already dead too.
Yes, it is.
His looping ability could have run out, leaving us in a world observed by Haine.
But even if that's true, our goal remains the same.
Kill Haine.
That's all.
Any luck contacting Mio?
No, we've got no signal here.
Alan said Mio and my brother left to go see Shinpei.
We can only hope they're heading here.
Mio...
First, I'll go to Torajima alone.
Can you shoot at the island from here, Nezu?
Only the southern side.
That's good enough.
I'll give you a signal if Shinpei's a Shadow.
Tokiko, I'll need you to send Guil and Ros charging in at that point.
Roger.
And you, Totsumura...
Why are you here again?
Oh well. Do your best to survive.
R-Right!
So are ya going in unarmed?
I have this.
Everyone, keep your guards up.
I'll return here if I can confirm that it's the real Shinpei.
Gotcha.
Let's meet again, Hizuru.
You insensitive old fart.
Don't raise any death flags.
Huh? Flags?
If this battle ever ends, I'll turn my experiences on this island into a novel.
I've yet to write a non-fiction work.
It's faint, but I can hear it echoing in my head.
A sound that irritates the nerves, like nails on a blackboard.
Unbelievable.
A Shadow's presence.
No, this is Haine's presence.
I have to lure her over this way so that Nezu can have a clear shot.
Has she seen through us?
Miss Nagumo! I'm so glad you're safe!
What about the others—
Enough with the charade, Haine.
I can't believe you transformed yourself into him.
Where is Shinpei?!
Fourteen years ago, I said I'd kill Hizuru if we met again.
And that was right here.
Farewell, Ryuunosuke.
Impressive.
So you're Shide, huh?
Karikiri Masahito.
But you're human.
I don't sense a Shadow from you.
Did you sneak up from behind when you killed Ushio too?
My, my, so this won't work on ya, eh?
Ya have powers of prediction, I hear.
Minakata Ryuunosuke.
So you did know my secret.
I copied Minakata Ryuunosuke 14 years ago.
But my personality from when I was human couldn't bear the fact that I'd eaten my friend's brother.
So I expelled that part of myself, along with Ryuunosuke's data.
But there was a slight accident.
The coordinates shifted, then they were printed.
Coordinates?
Ow, that smarts.
Coordinates in time, not space.
More precisely, two seconds ahead in time.
My, oh my!
Ryuunosuke is currently controlling Hizuru's body from two seconds in the future.
Is that right, Hizuru?
I know ya can hear me.
Well, Hizuru?
Ya got close to Haine and caused her to have doubts.
Because of ya, Haine was deeply hurt.
Her illness has progressed,
and she only has a few months left to live.
It's yer fault, Hizuru.
Haine's forced return,
yer precious brother's death...
It's all yer fault, Hizuru!
How dare you!
I won't let you hurt my sister anymore!
Ya cannot beat me, Ryuunosuke.
Haine's eye sees yer shift and relays that information to me.
In other words, yer two-second advantage is meaningless here.
This is mud.
Things that were once Shadows.
And those who are currently nothing at all.
Allow me to tell you about my power too.
A game isn't fun unless it's fair.
The mud reacts to my will and changes its form.
Talk about creepy.
Just how many people...
What would Sis call it?
A mass of bodies? No.
And because it is made of nothing, it has no weakness.
An armor of corpses.
Allow me to get a little serious now.
It's as I expected.
He's letting me dodge and is aiming to kill me once I land, just like Sis said he would.
But it's not Shide that can see where I am two seconds in the future.
It's Haine relaying that information to him via telepathy.
There's a slight time lag.
So I need to be faster.
Faster!
Just leave all the movement to me!
Making those moves with a human body is simply amazing.
But it seems ya can't keep it up forever.
Yer wound's opened up.
Is that where I shot ya last night?
All because ya had to go and cover for Shinpei.
That's not the only thing.
The bones in my right arm are cracking.
The muscle fibers all over my body are all torn up.
Sis is not going to last much longer.
I hate to admit it, but running is not an option.
I already sent the signal.
If I can just get him into Nezu's sights somehow,
that could create a tiny moment for me to escape.
Wait.
Sis?!
I'm not running.
I'm not running, Ryuunosuke.
Hizuru, huh.
Huh? How come I'm awake in yer time?
I've never talked to ya in real-time before!
Wow! Pinch me, I must be dreaming!
How? How?!
Pipe down already!
It's an emergency.
My hand was forced.
I'm so happy, Sis.
Listen closely and listen well, Ryuunosuke.
We can win.
Oh?
With Ajiro Shinpei's safety being uncertain,
we have no choice but to fight here.
Even if we run, we'll all die tomorrow anyway.
But—
Don't think.
Thinking is my job.
You saw it too, didn't you?
The material that exceeds common logic.
However, he's still human on the inside,
so we need to destroy that armor.
Listen, you're the only one who can execute the strategy I'm about to relay.
I'm leaving my body in your control.
Put your back into it, Ryuunosuke.
Yer still holdin' back, worryin' about my safety, ain't ya?
Go ahead and break my body.
Make full use of me!
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time