“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
They found her.
Now the most important thing is...
Was it fun?
Fooling me and sucking up to hi–
I don't want to run away anymore.
You can't run away from your past, Masaomi.
Even the things you're worried about now are still related to the past, aren't they?
If you have to blame someone,
blame Kida Masaomi, the one who ordered us!
The Dollars are disappearing.
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Russian Sushi! Russian Sushi here!
It's tasty! It's cheap!
Onii-san, want some?
Boss man!
Hello. This is Russian Sushi.
I didn't know who to call,
so I thought I'd call you.
What do you mean?
I wanted to tell you what that person is thinking.
Namie-san. How many points do you think this gets?
Ote? Checkmate?
Or is it an atari?
What, she's not here?
What are we gonna do?
Those yellow guys are still on a rampage.
It looks like that Horada guy is really throwing his weight around.
What's Kida up to?
Who knows?
Horada?
You mean Horada... as in that Horada?
Which Horada is "that Horada?"
Despicable.
Suspicions are stirring up my insides.
Did Mikado plan everything when he started the Dollars?
Was Anri allied with him? Or was she using him?
Either way, it's despicable.
However, worst of all is the fact that I'm picturing it all happening in my mind.
What do I do?
Where do I go?
There's no place for me to go anymore.
Come in.
I know why you've come here.
I thought things would get out of hand if I didn't do it.
I thought it would be the most Dollars-like thing to do.
Even if it's just the way we do things...
Even though the Dollars have no way of doing things.
Now we'll go back to being colorless and clear.
I think the Slasher and the Kokinzoku will calm down.
I've finally found out what's important. I think this is what's right.
I know. However, that's not why I came here today.
Hello?
Hey, it's Horada.
What is it? Is something wrong?
Not at all. You don't even have to show up anymore.
What I'm saying is, you're fired.
Shogun, fired. Kicked out! Laid off!
What the hell are you saying?
Ryugamine Mikado, is it? Your little friend's name?
What a surprise!
Who knew that the Dollars' boss was also friends with our boss?
Wait a minute. Who did you hear that–
That's of no concern to you.
How dare you hide that fact from us this whole time?
Everybody's standing here with a look of pure shock on their faces.
What are you going to do?
We're gonna take down the Dollars' boss, of course!
Everyone's been itching for a little brawl.
Well, I also put a bounty on your head.
You can't walk the streets of Ikebukuro anymore, pal.
See ya.
Mikado...
Do you like Sonohara Anri?
Is Kida Masaomi a close friend of yours?
What do you mean?
The number you have dialed is not in range of–
You have reached the voice mail for–
Coming!
Yo.
Simply amazing! What happened to you?
What's it to you?
I got shot.
Your legs and oblique muscles are significantly injured.
Wait, how are you still standing and walking like a normal person?
How? Because I can, stupid.
Hewajima-san?
Why are you here?
Crap... Who are you again?
It's Anri-chan.
Anri-chan, you'll have to forgive him.
What on earth happened?
Well, at first I thought I'd slipped and fallen in the rain.
And then blood started gushing from my stomach and legs.
Then I thought, "Did I just get shot?"
And then I was like, "I should kill whoever did it," but they'd all run away by then.
How stupid of you.
Want to die too?
I apologize from the bottom of my heart.
Just get me fixed up already.
I have to go and kill those bloody guys.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'll kill them!
I'll kill the guys who shot me, and that bastard who ordered them to, Kida Masaomi!
The number you have dialed is not in range of–
My suspicions about Mikado and Anri had vanished.
If the Kokinzoku were going to attack Mikado...
And if they were going to kidnap Anri to lure him out...
Why did I freeze up back then?
What was I so unsure of?
What was I so afraid of?
You can't escape. The past follows you around indiscriminately.
No way. That can't be.
It's all true.
Masaomi... Does Masaomi know about me?
I don't know.
However, apparently he wasn't quite himself when he confronted Anri-chan.
Perhaps that's because he'd found out that it was you who started the Dollars.
No way... Who could've told him?
I do know of a certain informant who loves to see people distraught and suffering.
The Dollars is something that you started.
Do with it as you wish.
However, just because the Dollars are gone,
it doesn't change the situation you three are in.
Why haven't either of them told me?
Why didn't you tell either of them?
Because I thought that I should deal with the Dollars' problems by myself.
That's what they thought too.
Not everything you see around you is real.
Everyone has their secrets. They have things they can't tell anybody.
There's no such thing as a normal person. So don't be afraid!
Face the reality of who Anri-chan and Kida-kun are, who you are.
If you love her, tell her everything!
You need to resolve the conflict amongst the three of you, not between the Dollars, the Slasher and the Kokinzoku.
Hello, Celty?
I'm trying to run right now, but Shizuo got shot,
and Anri suddenly ran out of the house...
No, she didn't run out yet.
They were talking about how Kida Masaomi had ordered him shot...
It's no use. I can't breathe. Sorry! I can't quite get the story straight.
But she's fast! Anri-chan runs really fast!
Hey, Kida!
What's wrong? You look pale, no good.
You get hungry again?
Simon.
You no look good, Kida. Something wrong.
Well, Simon... Your sushi is the best.
By the power vested in me, I officially declare it a five-star restaurant!
Russian Sushi has always been delicious!
You go to fight now?
Or you go to kill and be killed?
What? What do you mean by that?
Are you trying to act all psychic?
Did Izaya go and start something again?
That's not it at all!
Killing and being killed no is good.
Everyone where I'm from who fights is dead.
Kida, your eyes are the same as a man ready to run to his death.
Simon...
No good. This is Ikebukuro. Not the same as my town.
It nice, and people give you food even if they have no home.
They not all die if they go to bed without vodka.
A kid like you no need to kill people, Kida.
Sorry... I have to go.
Kida...
Somebody...
Somebody from the Kokinzoku. Somebody!
There's nobody. Nobody here. Which means that...
Interesting. Very interesting!
After the three friends, each with their own secrets, faced the slightest bit of ill will,
they found out one another's secrets in an almost ideal fashion!
Well, most of the ill will here is mine.
Anyway, the person who's supposed to settle all this isn't very patient and isn't making it very interesting.
It'd be nice if we could pick who had what role. Right, Namie-san?
Are you happy with the way the Kokinzoku is right now?!
Listen up! We're not some flash mob like the Dollars.
We have leadership that they don't!
The Dollars' leader even announced
their breakup, but don't be fooled!
It's just a trap! Kill every last one of his people!
If we can take down the Dollars with this many men, we'll
rise to the top of Ikebukuro, and all of Tokyo too!
Do you understand! Just imagine! A town where all of the
people, all of them, do exactly as we tell them to!
That thorn in our side, Hewajima Shizuo, is gone.
The ones who act all high and mighty for being Dollars are Kadota and his posse.
We'll take them down, and then we'll get their leader.
If we do, we'll have nothing to fear!
Now, go forth into Ikebukuro!
Are you sure that was a good speech? You're talking about killing people.
That was all they needed to hear.
As long as Hewajima Shizuo is gone, there's nothing to be afraid of.
We'll get taken out by the police!
If it comes down to it, we'll make it look like the Dollars are fighting each other.
There's no way we can pull that off.
Shut up, man! We'll do it! We'll pull it off.
Horada-san...
We'll pull it off for sure. I know we will.
The cops?! The cops are here already?!
You little punk! What're you here for?
Oh, Celty! You eat sushi again?
I'm looking for Kida Masaomi and Sonohara Anri. Have you seen them?
I saw Kida. He looked very serious, yes?
Probably fighting. I could not stop him.
Do you know where he went?
I see no yellow people out today.
Kida must be where they are.
Got it. Thank you.
You're ready to accept what we're about to see, right? No matter how bad it is?
Yes.
What's the meaning of this?
I don't see very many people I know here.
I can't get a hold of them on their phones, either. Don't tell me you guys...
Well, those who were opposed to me becoming the leader were attacked and shot
by an unknown group of folks last night, and they're still recovering as we speak.
How scary! It must have been the Dollars.
Ain't that right, guys?
You bastard!
You're pretty stupid, coming here all alone.
Like a moth to the flame, as they say.
Shall I do the same thing Izumii-san did?
Break your legs and be like "Here's my question!"
What... did you just say?
Did you just say Izumii?!
And afterwards, since we've done so many regrettable things as the Kokinzoku,
I think that we should change our gang name and color.
Yeah, maybe we should be pale, like your face right now.
You... No, you guys...
Don't tell me...
You've finally realized it?
That's right, the people you see here are all members of the Blue Squares that you hate so much!
Don't call them remnants or anything creepy like that though.
We just took out the Kokinzoku.
Seriously, the moment we took off our blue rags and offered our loyalty,
you took us right in.
What's wrong?
Are you finally going to bow before us?
No. On the contrary, I feel relieved.
Now that I've been fired from the Kokinzoku, I'm nothing more than a flirty high schooler.
I'm just a good-for-nothing who couldn't save the girl he loved.
I'm just an idiot who thought he could turn away from the past and live a normal high school life.
Which is why I came here.
I'm... I'm just Kida Masaomi.
That's why... That's why I've come here!
The past that's been haunting me had, at some point, overtaken me.
You can't run away.
Intently, intently, intently, intently...
The past and its memories are very lonely.
And so, now it's my turn to chase after my past.
The past is very lonely, so I have to hurry and catch up with it.
What the hell are you ranting about, you moron?
It's not like I'm only prepared to die.
I came prepared to kill, too.
Or rather, let me clarify, prepared to kill... you.
I'll say it again. That's why I came.
Nobody can deny me that!
Idiots! What are you doing?!
Crush this moron!
What was I so unsure of?
It's such a simple matter.
Hey! There's just one of him!
I am me. It's that simple.
Saki, I'm not afraid anymore.
I'm going to catch up with my past a little here.
Come on, hurry up and do something! You worthless crap!
Don't try and scare me like that, you little bastard!
You... I'll kill you! I'm serious!
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry. If you kill this person,
Mother will be sad, so I intervened on my own.
No, I know. I'm sorry.
It looks like Mother is very close by.
Kida-kun!
Anri... Why...?
Masaomi...
Mikado?
Ryugamine-kun... Why?
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time:
Durarara!!
Selfless Devotion to Justice
Even now, when I think about it, it's weird,
but I experienced something that would change my life...
Something that was very strange,
and yet could happen anywhere.
Next time: Selfless Devotion to Justice