[YUZUKI]
I've been thinking.
If we want answers, we're
going to have to hunt down
the mastermind behind this game.
[RUKO]
Mastermind?
You mean the girl
in the room, right?
You saw her after
you became an LRIG.
But then we'd
have to play WIXOSS.
Not only that, we'd need
to have a wish granted.
[YUZUKI growls] I told you,
we're not resorting to that!
We'll find another way!
[RUKO]
Okay.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[RUKO]
I admit it.
I don't have a wish yet.
But things have changed.
That's not true anymore.
We have to free Yuzuki
from the card.
There's a chance
to save my friends.
Nothing's more
important than that.
[IONA] You want to
see Tama, don't you?
[HITOE] It's too dangerous!
We don't know what...
[YUZUKI] Who's to say it
won't get even worse?!
[RUKO] We've been told nothing
but lies this entire time.
I can't play by their rules
if I expect to win.
But I can't make my wish
come true on my own, either.
And if I do nothing...
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO] ...I might be
trapped--forever!
--[TAMA] Ru?
--[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO gasps]
[TAMA meows]
Bet you were the one
giving me weird dreams!
[TAMA]
A-ha, a-ha!
[HATSU]
When you're finished, Ru,
are you up for a game of WIXOSS?
[RUKO]
Huh?
I made a new deck
and I'd love to see
how it stands up against yours.
We haven't played in a while!
Umm... Uh-huh!
Sounds fun!
[RUKO] I've never seen someone
use that LRIG before.
Whoa, that's a really
cool effect, too!
You always say that, but
then you stick with Tama,
no matter what.
[RUKO]
Huh?
Uh. Well, actually,
I just recently
put together a brand
new deck as well.
[RUKO gasps]
I... think I'll give this
one a shot today.
[IONA]
Why aren't you using me?
This isn't a Battle
between Selectors--
there's nothing at stake.
Are you really that childish?
Let's see.
There's no tangerines to peel,
but we gotta bet something,
or it won't be any fun!
[HATSU]
The loser gets the groceries?
Okay, sure, you're on.
[IONA]
And now you're ignoring me.
You can't do this forever.
I'm still here.
[IONA]
I haven't given up on my wish.
She's here in this world
and I will find her.
[YOUNG MAN A]
Hey, you're Akira, right?
The model?
[YOUNG MAN A]
I knew it!
Whoa, she's even
cuter in person!
Oh yeah, I used to see you on
ads in the subway all the time!
That's awesome!
[AKIRA]
Would you shut the hell up?
[YOUNG MEN gasp]
[URITH (I)]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[YOUNG MAN A]
W-Wait. Is that Iona?
--[AKIRA growls]
--[YOUNG MAN A grunts]
[AKIRA] The next one of you
punks who says that name
in front of me is gonna get
their teeth kicked in.
Got it?!
That's Urith, not Iona!
[YOUNG MAN B]
Uh, whatever you say!
[URITH (I)]
Akira.
You promised not to call me
that in public, remember?
Ah. You're right, I'm sorry.
[URITH (I) sighs] You didn't
put makeup on today.
[gasps] Uh-huh.
It's cause I...
I wanted to make you happy.
[URITH (I)] Hm.
I think you look beautiful.
[AKIRA]
It's all thanks to you.
I feel like I've been reborn.
I'm not afraid of
anything anymore.
[AKIRA'S MOM]
Akira, you have a guest.
[AKIRA]
Leave me the hell alone!
Tell 'em to screw off, you old
hag, and that goes for you, too!
If you want me
to see people so bad,
then pay to have my damn
face fixed, why don't you?!
[AKIRA'S MOM]
Akira! Watch your mouth!
[EDITOR] Please, ma'am.
Let me speak to her.
[AKIRA'S MOM]
Are you sure?
The editor's here...?
[gasps]
[MALE STAFF]
Hey, Akira!
[EDITOR] We have something
we wanna talk about.
[AKIRA gasps]
Don't worry,
we're all friends here.
[AKIRA]
Don't give me that!
What in the hell could you
possibly want from me?!
I bet you came to laugh
at me, didn't you?!
Because of this!
[EDITOR] No, we have a request
from a "certain someone."
What're you trying to say?
[AKIRA] Back then, I closed
my heart to everyone.
I don't know why
I decided to go along.
It must've been fate, I guess.
Hop in! Glad you came down.
Go on.
[AKIRA]
And then...
[AKIRA gasps]
[MAKEUP ARTIST]
See?
Hardly took a minute and you're
looking as cute as ever!
If you can manage as smile, I
think we'll be back in business!
[AKIRA gasps]
[MAKEUP ARTIST] Ooh,
someone else wanted to see
when we were done.
[AKIRA gasps]
What is this? Why are you here?
Oh, of course, I get it now!
You set this up!
Just couldn't resist kicking me
while I was down, could you?!
[URITH (I)]
No!
Yeah? Then what's your excuse?!
It better be damn good!
Or I'll screw your
face up as bad as mine!
[URITH (I)]
Go ahead.
If that's what it takes
to make you happy.
[gasps]
[URITH (I)] I can't heal
the scar on your face, but...
I want to heal the ones
in your heart.
Wait a sec...
You're not her, are you?
I'm Urith.
[gasps] Urith?
[AKIRA]
That stuck-up little LRIG?
[URITH (I)]
Iona isn't here anymore.
[sighs]
[AKIRA] I finally understood
the true rules of the game.
That Iona had her wish granted.
And that she threw
away her humanity.
[AKIRA laughs]
[AKIRA] Is she messed up
in the head or what?!
I was fighting so hard
to screw her over
and she did it to herself!
That's crazy. [laughs]
Akira...
My face wouldn't even
matter
if she hadn't put me
through that crap!
I'd just be... I'd just be
normal if it wasn't for her!
[sobs]
[URITH (I)] You're beautiful
just how you are.
[gasps]
[URITH (I)]
I've wanted to be with you,
for a long time now,
even when I was Iona's LRIG.
Oh, screw you!
After all that crap you said
about me?! You can go to hell!
Can't you see I did
it for your own good?!
[gasps] Huh...?
Those feelings, even
though they were painful,
they helped you to grow.
Helped you shine
brighter and brighter!
I could feel your heat.
Feel your obsession.
Your beauty can't be tainted
by her or anyone else.
It can't be tainted by WIXOSS.
[AKIRA gasps]
[URITH (I)] That scar is
the mark of your passion.
You're beautiful, and more
precious than any treasure
in the world.
[AKIRA whimpers]
--[AKIRA] No! Get off!
--[URITH (I)] Akira!
[door slams]
[AKIRA] Even after I pushed you
away, you still watched over me.
[AKIRA]
What is your problem?!
Are you too stupid to knock
before you come in my room?!
[AKIRA'S MOM]
I'm just bringing in your mail.
Calm down.
Huh?
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
What is this?
A makeup kit?
But why?
[GIRL STUDENT B]
Hey, Akira!
Oh, wow, it's
been a while, huh?
[AKIRA]
Uh...
You haven't come
to school in forever!
Jeez! Coulda sent us
a text message or something!
[AKIRA] Going out in public
again's easier than I thought.
I can almost pretend
like nothing happened.
Everything can be like it was.
Huh? A commercial?
[MAN A]
It was Iona's request, actually.
She wanted you
to do it together.
[AKIRA gasps]
Iona...
Okay, what are you
trying to pull?
[gasps]
You made it!
Here, step inside!
I was afraid you were
going to turn me down.
I'm so happy!
I hated Iona.
I hated her so much.
It's okay.
[AKIRA]
I know I'm not smart.
I know I'm poor, but at least
I had confidence in my looks.
Even when I was
around other models,
I was always the
center of attention.
At least until
Iona showed up.
Then it didn't matter
how I dressed
or how I posed or smiled.
All anyone could see was her.
It was like I was just there
to make her look better.
I had one thing and
she took it from me.
She made me invisible.
It was 2012.
"Valentine's Day Special".
Natural Makeup Lessons:
How to Rock the Hottest Looks
Without Being Busted
By Your Teacher.
That was your first
job, wasn't it?
And the next one.
The "Summer Of Excitement"
edition from the same year.
It was "Items You Never
Leave Home Without."
Why do you know all that?!
It's like I said.
I want to be together!
[gasps]
I know it seems strange.
Like I'm a stalker, almost.
But I mean that from
the bottom of my heart.
I have taken more than
just Iona's face, you know.
I have her wealth and
connections to use
however I please, to make
all your wishes come true.
Huh...?
I'll make everyone recognize
your beauty, just like I do.
I'll take you to places that
Iona couldn't imagine
in her wildest dreams!
You see now? I just
wanna watch you shine.
Brighter than ever.
Until the end of time.
[AKIRA]
Urith...
[AKIRA] I never knew there
was someone out there
who loved me so much.
And I never knew that love
could make me so strong.
That I needed it so badly.
You took that "Aki-Lucky"
ugliness from my heart.
And put her to rest for good.
Now, thanks to you,
it's like I'm reborn.
I've become "Aki-Lovely."
[URITH (I)]
"Aki-lovely"?
Yep. Cute, huh?
Is something wrong?
That's enough for you?
Huh?
All that hatred for Iona
faded away, just like that?
Your passion dried up
and now the game is over?
No... That wasn't
what I meant at all.
It's just, as long as
I have you with me,
I don't have to be afraid
of anything and, uh...
I told you before, all that pain
and hatred burning inside you?
That's what really
made you shine.
In other words,
it's what made me love you.
[AKIRA gasps]
Akira. I need a favor.
Will you help me?
[RUKO] Let's see...
Carrots, potatoes, onions...
Oh, remember, that's two
of the bags of potatoes
with five in each.
[RUKO] Ugh! That's
gonna be so heavy!
Do we have to make
so much curry right now?
If you're gonna
insist on gambling
and then complain
when you lose,
you had better
work on your game.
[RUKO groans]
[phone rings]
Kominato residence.
[YUZUKI]
Ruko! Did you see?!
Ah? Yuzuki?
[YUZUKI]
The latest issue of LonLon!
Akira! She's back!
[RUKO]
What do you mean?
[YUZUKI] She was in an article,
and her scar's gone!
I wonder if she became
a Selector again, too.
You don't think her wish
was granted already do you?
[RUKO]
I don't know.
But I'm glad.
[YUZUKI]
Well, you shouldn't be!
Why not?
The thing is...
Akira...
...looked like she was
using the magazine
to find other Selectors.
Wait, she's doing what?
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO] I, uh, I'm about
to go grocery shopping.
Can we meet up tomorrow?
Cool, 'bye.
How's Yuzuki?
[RUKO]
Oh. Great!
Well, better get going
if we wanna eat!
[sighs]
[AKIRA, URITH (I)]
If you want to smile again,
then start with your skin!
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO]
Iona?
[IONA]
Urith, actually.
You're sure?
She's an Eternal Girl now.
But even though
she's taken my body,
she's still bound by
the contract of my wish.
Am I missing something?
I thought your wish was to be
the LRIG of a powerful Selector.
[IONA]
That's only the first half.
Or rather, a means to an end.
Once I have a partner,
my true wish--
[AKIRA]
Is to find another Selector
as powerful as your own.
And battle her.
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO]
Akira.
Long time no see, Ru-Ru.
Didja miss me?
You liking your new partner?
[whimpers]
[AKIRA chuckles]
[RUKO]
You want to battle.
[AKIRA]
What?
Don't act so surprised, Ru-Ru!
Anyway, I got a brand new deck
I'm just dying to try out.
With this little
cutie right here.
Hi! My name's Milulun!
So nice to meet you!
Wait. Why would you-- I
mean, after what happened,
you still wanna do this?
[AKIRA]
Yeah, no, I get it.
You mean because
I'm Aki-Un-lucky now.
Sure, I can cover it up,
but this scar is never
gonna go away...
What am I supposed to do?
Spend the rest of my life
being ashamed of my own face?
[MILULUN]
Ooh, my poor buddy!
Um... Yeah, but-
Ru-Ru, please, you have
to battle me again,
so I can get my
confidence back
and claw my way
out of this hole!
--[RUKO whimpers]
--Just once... Ru-Ru...
I'm begging you, please!
[RUKO]
I'll do it...
--[gasps] Thank you!
--[MILULUN] Aki-lucky!
[RUKO] I don't even care
if Akira or Iona
are planning
something with this.
I won't back down.
[AKIRA, RUKO]
Open!
Wow, don't you
look fancy, Iona!
That's one way to lose weight.
You had it all and you'd
rather be trapped in a card.
Gotta say, that is
royally messed up!
Well, if you're such a
glutton for punishment,
then let Aki-lucky
whip your ass!
Milulun, Grow!
[YUZUKI]
What if she goes after Ruko?
[HITOE]
Hm?
I mean, you've seen how Akira
tears into other Selectors.
If she doesn't have Tama,
Ruko might not hold up.
[HITOE] What kind of girl
do you think Tama was?
[YUZUKI]
Huh?
Before she got turned
into an LRIG,
she was a normal girl
just like us, right?
Uh... Oh, yeah.
Guess you're right.
Kinda hard to imagine though.
She used to make those
little "meow" noises.
Maybe she was a cat!
Either way, she's Ruko's
friend, just like we are.
[YUZUKI]
I know.
That's why she won't give up.
[IONA grunts]
You're so weak!
Summon, Babel!
[IONA]
Ruko, get serious.
[RUKO]
What?
Use my card's ability.
It forces them to attack.
You know how this works.
Just summon a high-powered SIGNI
and let them impale
themselves on it.
[AKIRA]
Wha--?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Ru! You let your card
call the shots?!
[RUKO gasps]
[giggles]
[RUKO] Am I not taking
this seriously enough?
I wasn't trying
to go easy on her.
I'm not afraid of winning,
but this still feels all wrong.
What is it?
[TAMA]
Ru!
Slash Miracle, go!
Counter this!
My pleasure!
Ready? Use Anti-Spell!
Milulun!
[IONA screams]
[RUKO]
Iona!
--[car horn honks]
--[RUKO gasps]
--[AKIRA gasps]
[WORKER]
Hey!
Sorry, girls, but this
is a construction zone.
I don't know what you're doing,
but could you move it, please?
[RUKO]
I-I'm sorry, sir!
[AKIRA]
Aw...
And just when things were
starting to get good, too!
What a shame!
Uhm... Akira.
[AKIRA]
Wow, Iona.
Sucks to be you, huh?
All that trouble
to become an LRIG
and you get stuck with
a braindead loser
of a Selector like her!
Anyway, don't think
you're getting off
with just one battle.
I'll be back, again and again.
You're gonna learn real fast
what true misery looks like.
And, bitches, that
goes for both of you.
[MILULUN]
Bye-bye-lun!
[IONA]
Ruko.
I tried!
Huh?
I'm serious! I wasn't
going easy on her!
I just--
Everything felt
wrong that time!
I'm sorry, but if I don't have
Tama there with me,
then there's no point!
[IONA]
I see.
[CHIYORI]
So cool!
Everything's true,
just like in the books!
Why didn't you tell me
I could be a card?!
Well, normal people would
probably flip out in a bad way.
That and I was bound to secrecy.
It comes with the territory.
Whoa!
That is so cool!
Ooh, and after I win
and I'm an LRIG like you,
can I pick my own outfit?!
I'm gonna go all
pink for sure!
Or maybe mint green!
How 'bout both?
I seriously don't care.
Face my Moonlight Chorizo!
[ELDORA]
Huh?
Heh! That's gonna be my
number one special move.
Ah. I mean, I know chorizo
is a kind of sausage,
but when you put it with
"Chiyori" it sounds super cool.
I'm so lucky.
Ya know, if I wasn't with you,
I'd have to feel guilty
about this whole ugly
Selector business.
Hah! Chiori-tto!
[URITH (I)]
Could we speak for a moment?
Huh...?
Uhh...
Iona?
[RUKO]
I liked being with Tama!
[YUZUKI]
Is it because Tama's gone?
[RUKO] I liked battling
together with her.
[IONA]
Take advantage of me.
[RUKO] It's not
the battle part I liked.
[IONA]
You don't know anything.
--Even about Tama.
--[RUKO] I just want Tama back!
[RUKO] Next time:
"That Accidental Reunion."