“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
They're picking on her!
Though, they're being so corny about it.
Turning right!
Well then, let's hear it.
Tell me about these human experiments you guys are supporting.
It was me. It had to be.
Where was I riding to?
I found you!
My love!
Don't make excuses.
Or do you want to become the "raw material" yourself?
Give it up. Maybe it is better that you have no head.
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
It's like you only lose the important things, isn't it?
Like an umbrella you just bought.
Although, there will always be more vinyl umbrellas...
An umbrella isn't very important, but something like a winning lottery ticket...
If you put it somewhere safe and forget about it,
and then look for it later on, you'll only find items that are unimportant.
When all you care about is that one thing you lost...
'Evening!
Looking for something, are you?
Sometimes I think, that when I'm asleep here,
it must be awake over there.
Ever since my memories got foggy,
I've felt like the passing of time has gotten foggy, too.
For as long as I can remember, I've never seen my whole self,
not even in my dreams.
There is that part, and there is this part.
What kind of scenery is over there that I don't see?
What does that part see?
I always have the same dream over and over,
and as I dream, I look for answers.
However,
the dream always ends the same way.
Nanka's Dream
Certy, this is amazing!
Last night you said that you didn't have any work for today, right?
Well, I did some calculations,
and today is your 265th day off!
Why the sad face?
He always tries to interpret the faces I don't make.
I've heard that when people have dreams,
it's actually them sorting out their own memories.
Is that true?
Why are you asking that out of the blue?
"Why do people have dreams"?
If I could answer that in one sentence, I'd have to say: "I don't know."
There are many questions that have yet to be answered by medical science.
Especially that one.
It's a well known fact that you dream during the REM, or rapid eye movement, phase of sleep.
He's a doctor. A witch doctor, to be precise.
At that moment, what is it that triggers the sights and sounds you perceive in the dream?
Still, I'm not too sure exactly what it is that he does.
And, what else is going on in the brain as you sleep during REM?
He lets me stay here, though,
and it's thanks to him that I have my job as a smuggler.
Our scientific knowledge doesn't have any way of finding out.
Well, there's also the question of what a memory really is to begin with.
Are you listening?
I'm grateful for all of it.
And I know that lately,
there have been some feelings of attachment between us when we're together.
However...
You seem to think that all of your memories are inside your head,
but we don't know that for sure.
Of course they are.
Before we go too far, you should get dressed.
Let's go somewhere together!
I'll take the day off, also.
Look! I'm even turning off my cell phone.
How about I turn off the land line, too? I'm not going to read any mail today, either!
Time for some rest and relaxation.
Well now, where shall we go?
Shall we ride your favorite "horse" to the beach?
Or maybe go to a hot spring?
I don't want to go anywhere.
Why not?
If it's a day off you want,
then I'll cook you some food as a token of my appreciation for your hospitality.
Homemade cooking!
What do you want to eat? Let's find a recipe.
I'm impressed, Certy!
What looks good?
I'll borrow it then. Thanks.
You're a life saver. I really overslept this morning.
Don't mention it, son.
It's about time the fatigue from coming to Tokyo set in.
Or should I say, this is your "hunter's chance"!
It's the perfect opportunity for you to scoot closer to the cute girl next to you,
and have her show you her textbook!
Hey, what's the matter?
Is it too much trouble to wear a necktie, too?
Are you all right?
You didn't forget your wallet too, did you?
No way.
It's tasty. Russian Sushi!
Simon.
Have you seen Yumacchi?
Karisawa. You eat sushi? I no see him.
This morning, shop owner leave and say:
He's not here?
Today's the release of "Accel World" from Dengeki Bunko, right?
"I go to take medicine."
We bought it together, went for some tea, and then he went home.
He not come back. We have no toppings now.
Then the maids from the shop came after me with this phone.
I now look for him.
I thought it must be Yumacchi's.
Then why are you out here grabbing customers?
Hello! Excuse me!
What are you looking for?
I said, Yumacchi!
Who are you?
Lost and found?
Please write here what you are searching for. Tell me.
Have you always been around here doing that?
I'm asking everybody!
My cell phone!
Welcome back!
What am I looking for?
It's enough that Castano came back in one piece.
Karisawa, Yumasaki and I promised we'd stop nosing around, but still...
"Yagiri Drug Manufacturing."
They are rumored to be connected to the Awakusu Club,
or the "Nebula" company from North America.
Well, I'm not going to find out anything like this.
Have you seen Karisawa-san?
She no here.
Really?
Hey, how about Russian sushi?
Certy! Just cut it with a kitchen knife, like normal!
It's tasty! Delicious!
Delicious!
Wait. Why are you crying?
Crying? No, I'm just really impressed.
It's great, really it is!
These sweet, little veggies with this spicy, and salty miso soup!
Something's fishy.
No. Your cooking is like nothing I've ever tasted.
It's just like you!
That's not a compliment.
I get it. I messed up the flavoring again.
Enough.
Don't eat it if you don't want to!
Why wouldn't I want to? It's so tasty.
I said don't eat it!
What are you doing?!
What's the meaning of this?
Hey, you really do have a talent with cooking.
What? You really do, for not having taste buds.
What are those? Taste buds?
Your sense of taste.
Your brain can't experience tastes that aren't written in your DNA.
Although, in your case, you don't have to eat,
so your brain has nothing to do with it.
Don't look so dejected.
Come on, let's go play a game.
Don't treat me like a child.
That's the one thing I hate the most.
I am not.
I may have learned some things from you,
but I still have some faint memories from hundreds of years ago.
My head has even more of them.
Do you really need memories from hundreds of years ago?
What do you mean?
Come on, I'm always saying this.
You're better off the way you are.
What do you know?
Before long, I'm going to forget what my own face looks like!
Wait! I didn't mean it like that!
Certy!
You've finally come back!
Excuse me, Sensei.
I have an urgent patient waiting, but I couldn't get a hold of you.
Sonohara-san, is there something wrong?
They're gone.
Gone?
What?
What's gone missing this time, Mikado?
Sonohara-san's shoes...
Again? How sneaky...
I bet I know who did this.
Kida-kun?
All right!
H-Hey! Kida-kun!
Kida-kun was a little scary just now, unlike how he normally is.
Really? The only thing that worries me is him running off all of a sudden.
When I was little, I would always lose things,
and I'd run to my mother in tears, shouting:
"It's gone! It's gone!" after which we'd look for them together.
Your mother must be really nice.
Yeah. Both my father and my mother are.
It's okay. I'll go home like this.
Thank you, Ryugamine-kun, for helping me look.
Give it up, Kida-kun. It's not a criminal case.
No, Sonohara-san went home already.
I don't know.
Me? I'm still looking for them, of course.
Anyway, I'll see you tomorrow.
There they are!
What am I doing?
Weird, isn't it?
I can't remember. Vacant land is weird that way.
Once something is gone, you can't remember what was there in the first place.
It was there until just a while ago, wasn't it?
A pretty large building at that.
What am I doing?
I get mad whenever Shinra tells me to give up looking for my head,
but then again, I have a job, and I suppose I've made some friends.
Have I become human?
Hey, didn't you have something you wanted from me?
I remember.
There was a tall, narrow, blue building here, wasn't there?
Oh yeah, that run-down joint.
There was the old lady with the tobacco shop on the first floor.
That's a smuggler for you.
I can still feel the presence of my head in this town, though.
Hello! Good day!
Me?
I, beautiful Japanese, looking for.
Tell me what you are looking for in your heart.
Can I see that, please?
Okay!
I wonder if they met up already.
Today, I looked for several different things.
I found some of them, and others I didn't.
His bags weren't there, so I thought he'd gone to work.
However, I felt like something was out of the ordinary.
Fireworks?
Yes, big ones too.
They were strapped to his chest as he was surrounded by several adults.
That's a lot of fireworks.
You certainly have some violent employees, don't you?
Let's not talk about that.
He had a strange reason for coming.
"My girlfriend was kidnapped."
"The only place she could remember was this place."
"Tell me what happened."
That sounds like the truth to me.
Can you make it so he won't remember us after he wakes up, Sensei?
I'm afraid there's no way to erase someone's memories as conveniently as that.
Also, I remember this man.
We'll let him go. I'm not sure if he'll go home after that or not, though.
Sensei, my supervisor and I both trust you.
We've also been keeping your little secret safe.
That's right. It seems you've been living with that strange person again.
At that moment, I forgot all about it.
About my head, and the memories I had kept for several hundred years.
I wasn't thinking about them at all. I just...
I just...
Hey. Would you go out with me?
I have no problem paying for two at a restaurant.
I know of a good place. Please, Certy.
It's so lonely eating by myself.
What is this intricate, bizarre food?!
Fried sushi, cheese sushi,
bean curd sushi, borscht sushi.
This one is sour cream sushi, yes?
We shouldn't have gone with sushi.
What are you saying? Special set! All free!
So, a fortune cookie for dessert, is it?
For heaven's sake...
You see, these things have written fortunes inside them; basically, they are fortune-tellers.
Well then, let's open them. This one's yours.
Let me see.
This says, "You will find what you're looking for."
You sure are happy about that one.
I'm so happy, Shinra!
What does yours say?
Looks like there wasn't one inside.
I cannot shed tears.
When this part is sad, does the other part shed tears?
Thank you.
I hope not.
I hope it smiles for me instead.
What's wrong?
Scared again?
There's nobody there. We're alone.
Are you remembering something?
You don't have to remember anything.
I've said it before, haven't I? I don't care about your past or future.
I just want who you are now.
Who we are right now is eternal.
I love you,
Certy.
That night, for the first time in a long time,
I had a dream of myself when I was whole.
I am here.
I'm here.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time on
Durarara!!
Dependant Love
My love is different.
It's not like the usual love that only demands and consumes.
It is a perfect love.
Next time: Dependent Love.
I am what Seji needs.