Lulu!
Don't you worry. It won't be
long before I exclude you too.
From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
Beware
That's why we wanted to become true friends.
We crossed that barrier...
Ginko, Kurechin... thank you.
I love you both very much.
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Storm!
We must remain an invisible existence at all times.
Let us begin the Ritual of Exclusion.
Ritual of Exclusion
EXCLUSION
Friends are important above all else, don't you think?
We, those gathered here today, are all friends.
Don't you think that those who deny
our feelings are the scum of the earth?
Those who stray from us are irredeemable.
Those who don't stain themselves our color are nothing but trouble, right?
Those who can't read the atmosphere are evil.
Can't read the atmosphere = Evil
EXCLUSION
Humans and bears are severed.
And yet, there are those who try to overcome that barrier.
We must proceed to select the next evil to exclude.
Let's search evil!
Invisible Storm
EXCLUSION
Excluded
Evil is Excluded
Evil
She's been selected! We have our evil.
Girls, I trust you are prepared.
We will now move to exclude the evil!
Megabear Energy is charging!
Spark spark! Scum scum!
Scum... scum... scum...
One shot from that, and she's super done for.
The bear will be vaporized in an instant.
Wait!
Aren't I the evil? Exclude me instead!
But of course. You're next.
Lily Dark!
Evil
Tsubaki Kureha
This is your punishment.
Evil
Tsubaki Kureha
You're going to kill your friend.
Evil
Tsubaki Kureha
You don't obey this world's rules, and that makes you evil.
We must remain invisible.
If you're invisible, then who will find you?
Friend?
What nonsense, growl.
That girl is not my friend.
I came here to eat Tsubaki Kureha. That's all.
Kureha is my prey.
I've never once thought of her as a friend!
Ginko...
Tsubaki Kureha... is not my friend!
That's a lie.
That's a total lie.
Then just try and explain
why you crossed the barrier!
It was to eat you, growl.
Then why did you stay by my side?
You two tried to protect me from the Invisible Storm.
That's because if you became invisible,
you wouldn't taste delicious anymore, growl.
It's all right now, Ginko.
From the very beginning, you were my friend.
You crossed the barrier, and found me from within the Invisible Storm!
You gave me love!
No!
I am your enemy! I came to eat you!
I am... a bear!
The bear revealed its true form!
Now, exclude it!
Exclude!
I remember everything now.
Flashback
Stop!
Traitors have to be excluded!
Why...
She won't be approved because she's a bear?
Is it wrong to be a bear?
If only... If only she were a human girl...
Would we be able to stay together?
Would I be able to protect Ginko?
Please tell me, Kumaria-sama!
That's right. The one who desired a promised kiss...
was me!
restricted number
Tsubaki Kureha. This is a challenge from the Severance Barrier.
Is your love true?
Yes, it's true.
In that court and with their Lily Approval,
a bear can become a human girl.
In exchange, you must part with that which you hold most precious.
Like what?
This is just what I think,
but when Ginko did it, she must have parted with the love she received from you.
Lulu-chan, you were wrong.
The one who parted from her love to grant her wish wasn't Ginko.
It was...
It was me.
The Lily Judgement shall now begin.
Defendant Tsubaki Kureha.
Please state your case.
I want to be with Ginko forever!
So please, turn Ginko into a human girl!
Your Honor, the defendant is committing the sin of pride.
Deliver a guilty verdict!
Pride? What's that?
So basically, you're saying you want to change Yurishiro Ginko's appearance?
There's no other way.
It's because bears are excluded.
And I'm sure Ginko would be much happier as a human too.
Don't you sound confident? Shiny shine!
That is what we are referring to as pride.
Then let it be pride!
Please! Turn Ginko into a human girl!
Very well. However, there will be one condition.
What?
You are to part with your love.
Basically, you'll forget all about Ginko.
When you awaken, you will certainly reject her.
Reject?
That day, I wished for
something that I should not have.
I foolishly believed that my selfish love was true.
You must wait.
The time will come.
When the Invisible Storm descends, you must find Yurishiro Ginko.
If you can become her friend once more and exchange a promised kiss...
You two can be together forever.
Shiny shine!
Really?
I inquire of you, defendant Tsubaki Kureha:
Will you turn Yurishiro Ginko into a human?
Or will you back down on love?
I won't back down on love!
Turn Ginko into a human girl!
Lulu-chan, in exchange for that
which was most precious to me,
I went and wished for Ginko to be human.
The Lily Judgement shall now begin.
Defendant Tsubaki Kureha.
Will you admit your own sin?
I admit it. In the past, I committed the sin of pride
and wished for Ginko to become a human girl.
Following that, were you able to find what you desired from within the Invisible Storm?
I was. A certain girl...
Flashback
She taught me.
I...
I found it—the true love that I desired!
Sumika...
Thank you.
I'm no longer scared.
So long as you don't forget love, you will never be alone.
So long as you don't back down on love, even if you were to lose something, you won't become invisible.
And so...
I will dive into the Storm!
What's with her?
Lulu-chan, thank you.
I'll take this star, this true love, and deliver it to Ginko.
Don't come!
Scum...
You are my friend.
No! You're not my friend, growl!
I'm a man-eating-bear!
The Loner Queen Ginko!
I came to eat you!
Stop! Stay away!
Hurry up and shoot me!
If you don't, I'll eat them all!
I'm a crimibear! Growl!
Ginko.
You can't... Kureha...
I finally found you.
Heed my wish, Kumaria-sama!
Kumaria-sama!
She's regained her form!
Then perhaps it is time for us to go as well.
Now this is sexy!
Shabadadu!
How very cool!
Shiny shine!
Kumaria
STAR OF LOVE
Tsubaki Kureha. Is your love true?
It's true.
I will...
...break myself!
Kumaria-sama!
Please turn me...
...into a bear!
Lily approved!
What is this?!
Kureha...
What have you done?
Ginko, thank you for not forgetting love,
and for never backing down on love.
Here is my promised kiss.
We'll be together forever from now on!
Together forever, growl!
Lily approved!
I...
I super can't believe this...
A human became a bear?
How abominable!
Scum...
We... can no longer shoot...
What are you doing?
That's no longer a human!
It's a bear!
It's evil!
Evil must be excluded!
Don't hesitate!
Don't think!
Shoot!
We have finally accomplished it after joining all of our efforts as one.
That's right.
We have well and truly excluded the fearsome evil that had run rampant in our school.
Indeed, we must remain
an invisible existence at all times.
So let us begin the Ritual of Exclusion!
Friends are important above all else, don't you think?
We, those gathered here today, are all friends.
Shoot!
Flashback
People who don't stain themselves
our color are nothing but trouble, right?
Those who can't read the atmosphere are evil.
Well then, girls, let's select the next evil to exclude.
Defective
I found you.
viens avec moi
Come with me
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu ni
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
And so, with their promised kisses fulfilled,
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shitara
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
they were guided by the star of love to set forth beyond severance.
The Place Where Love Becomes a Kiss
LOCATION
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so approve me
Hey, Onee-tama.
kaze ni matta ehon no page ga
The sight of the wind flipping the pages of a picture book
What happened to them next?
kage ni natta kioku wo yurasu no
uncovers memories of days long past
I wonder...
What do you think, Milne?
zutto
Until you come...
I dunno!
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
But I figured something else out.
karappo na sekai no naka
in this empty world
What's that?
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
I could've just given you a promised kiss myself!
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
Milne...
Right?
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
We'll be together forever.
Yep!
Onee-tama, I love you!
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
Thank you!
nee
Hey
ano mori de matteru kara
I'll be waiting in the forest for you
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
There's no telling where the two girls are headed.
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
But that is of no matter.
karappo na sekai no naka
in this empty world
For the world wakes and changes along with your love.
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you