Tora Dora! Episode 6 English Translation by KloneDesu
() Are notes/information for the timer/editor.
What? How to lose weight?
I've never been on a diet or anything.
No way! But you're so thin!
Let's go.
Yeah!
I just seem to have the right metabolism to stay thin.
Oh, so it's just your metabolism!
That's good, I envy you...
Looks like Kawashima has become the women's center of attention.
Yeah.
If I push it, I just get stressed out.
I think eating what you want is the best way to stay healthy.
I can't just stand and listen to that statement!
What is this about?
W-What are you doing?
What the—
Let go!
Take that and that and that and that!
Sensei, Kawashima's hiding some fat on her tummy!
and that and that and that and that!
and that and that and that and that and that!
And that! And that! And that!
You only take up to 300 yen worth of meat to a picnic!
You call this 300 yen worth?!
Bananas aren't in the meat family!
This is a meat bun! This is expensive ice-cream!
This one's a hot dog!
Take this! The Combinish Attack!
High!
Calo—rie!
I salute the diet-mentality that has turned into star dust.
Well then~!
We did the Combinish Attack nicely!
That was quite a tough opponent!
Those bast—
A-Are you okay, Ami-chan?
They are so terrible!
You poor thing.
Umm...
That was an early summer storm.
Oh? So Ami gets like that when you do something like that.
Huh?
I feel refreshed.
Leave it to Minorin! That was quite a nice job.
Women can be overwhelming when they collaborate.
I couldn't keep quiet as a dieting warrior.
When you face the fat head-on, the god of stupor will smile upon you.
She will surely understand one day.
Hmm... Is that how it works?
What's with him?
Oh yeah.
You want me to make salad for tonight's dinner?
You're going to make it?
I learned it during elementary school; I can make the dressing myself too.
First you buy the lettuce, you pull on it—
then you tear it off and then you put it on a plate.
See, all done!
You didn't wash the lettuce.
You didn't put it through running water and what happened to the dressing?
You are so picky about small things, you sister-in-law.
Sister-in—
Takasu-kun!
Wh-What is it, Kawashima?
P-Please! Can you stay with me for a minute?
That's the kid from before.
Hey, Kawashi—
You...
Hey... How long are planning on sticking together?
You completely ignore my existence... and just stick, stick and stick...
Stick... stick... stick... stick... stick... stick
Hey, Taiga! Now is not the time—
I'm scared, Takasu-kun!
Stick... stick... stick... stick... stick... stick
You publicly obscene woman!
Hey, Kawashima. What was that about?
It's not—someone you know is it?
N-No. This sort of thing just happens when you model.
It's just that the fans kind of bothers me...
And to think I even transferred over...
You're going home now, right?
Uh-yeah.
Will you shelter me at your home for a bit?
It'd be scary if I meet him again.
I see. If that's the case, leave it to me.
A wooden apartment that has holes for wind to blow through
or a safe luxury apartment with an auto-lock.
Which do you prefer?
The luxury apartment!
Then it's decided.
If that's the case; come to my house.
Huh? Hold on a second.
Why do I have to go to your place?
That's fine, I'm not forcing you.
Although Ryuuji's house is so unsafe that even I can break in.
It's alright; it's none of my business anyway.
W-Wait, Aisaka-san!
I told you to wait damn it!
Well, I guess that's fine.
Here you go.
It's sweet...!
Ryuuji's mass produced kumquats that were pickled in honey.
I tried adding soda to it.
It's too freaking thick.
Jeez, making me drink this stuff.
Don't give me that diet-warrior crap.
Your brain's probably shrunk too.
You really make an amazing transformation don't you?
I'd love to show the class your true identity.
Like I have any intent on showing my true self.
So that's how it is.
Well. Is your throat in optimum condition after drinking the kumquat and honey juice?
You don't intend to show your true self?
In that case, I'll have a look at the made up self.
To my hearts content.
Wha—?
Good... morning...
Ka-Kawashima, You seem tired.
Yeah, my stress from yesterday didn't go away.
Oh yeah. You had a frightening experience.
That's not it.
Five hours in Aisaka's apartment after this and that... No... six hours.
D-Did Taiga do something?
Jackson... Uganda...
U-ga-n-da?
Falco... Akezu Michihide…
Matsumoto Seijou...
Shanshou Niisuu... Oda Nobunaga singing a French song.
Dazai Osamu carrying out an ambush personally.
Amaterasu being sealed up...
H-Hey.
Are you okay Kawashima?
Yeah, I made her do it!
150 impersonation medleys.
Got quite a rise out of it.
I have no idea how you even do an impersonation of Akezu Michihide.
I told her that I'd throw her out if she didn't listen to me.
She was near death!
T-That's so cruel...
No. I'm really thankful Aisaka.
Ki-Kitamura-kun!
Kitamura?
Aisaka! I have a favor to ask you!
Ami-chan, your face seems pale.
Are you sure you don't want to go to the infirmary?
I'm fine, just fine.
H-Hey.
Come here you stupid chihuahua.
It's time to feed you.
Who do you mean by "stupid chihuahua"?
Who else could I be talking about?
You act like a cute girl, bark all the time, and you're in heat all year long.
Wha—?!
Whatever, just come with me.
Are you kidding me?
Why do I have to—
I've promised my friends that—
Michael Jackson being a bus guide.
Mona Lisa that faces her future troubles at 200 mph.
A jolly thinking person.
I already made copies of the videos.
It might happen to pop up on some magazine covers.
Stop that!
Fine, I get it! I just have to go right?
Damn it!
Umm... Ami-chan?
I'm sorry. I forgot that I was supposed to eat with Aisaka-san today.
I'm really sorry.
Hey! Wait damn it!
Thank you for the food~!
Thanks for the food...
What the hell is this?
As long as she only shows her outer-face, Ami will never make any true friends.
Since you guys know her true self, I want to leave her to you.
Easier said than done.
It's one thing for me, but no matter how you think about it, Taiga and Kawashima won't mix.
Aisaka!
Please. You're one of the few female friends I have that I can count on.
I told you—
Wha—?!
Oh, thank you Aisaka!
That Kitamura, he pushed his burdens on us and went to the student council.
You're lunch is amazing Kushieda!
It may look huge but this lunch actually has ultra-low calories.
These guys are chopped veggies.
These guys are konjak.
And this is the rice!
Why do I have to do this?
Here Ami, I'll let you have the kelp.
Like I'd want that.
Aww, Is that so?
I envy you...
N-Nothing.
Well, it's time for lunch.
Huh?
Why do you have the same courses as Aisaka's lunch?
So, why huh?
Well, this is— uh.
The problem's gone now.
Mine is fried eggs and frizzled stuff, Ryuuji's is just seaweed and rice.
Ahh! My food!
Here you go!
Now you have a meatball lunch.
Huh? Oh. Thanks.
Why is it that you let Aisaka-san do whatever she wants?
Do you think so?
Ryuuji was my dog in his previous life.
It's a dog's joy to be able to serve his master.
Right! The two are destined to be together!
There's no such thing.
Sheesh Minorin, not again.
S-Sorry. I was just kidding, kidding.
Sheesh.
Oh?
Hey! Everyone, listen to me for a bit!
We have an event sponsored by the student council, but we're low on members.
Could someone volunteer?
Sorry Kitamura. There's a special deal today at Kanooya's Supermarket.
Oh, Takasu! You'll do it?!
Wha—
Then get changed and come out front.
Sheesh. Why do I have to do this?
I told you that I'm also volunteering to take responsibility for it.
You know you just want to be with Kitamura as much as possible.
That's one way of putting it.
You're pretty honest aren't you?
Takasu-kun! I'm going too.
I just transferred so I want to get used to this school.
Minorin.
As a diet-warrior I couldn't help but assist the women that frantically move their bodies.
It's not like I'm trying to get thinner or anything.
Let's do our best together, Takasu-kun.
Yeah.
Alright you goons!
Time to beat some spirit into you!
If you dare to loaf off, I'll make you see hell!
Hey, hey, calm down!
Did you put your working gloves on?!
Are you holding your trash bags?!
Did you make sure you're all dressed appropriately?!
Yeah!
Don't take the city lightly.
If you that's all the spirit you have, you'll be thrown off the ship damn it!
Put some spirit into your replies!
Yeah!
The chairman is amazing as usual.
Alright, I'll explain how it will go.
First—
Kitamura-kun just ended up going with the rest of the student council.
Sorry, we have to go through a different route!
What did I come here for then?
Hey, doesn't this piece of trash look just like you Aisaka-san?
Especially how it's hopelessly tiny!
Then this piece of trash is just like you Kawashima-san.
Especially how it's soft, lax, and bloaty.
Let's go that way Minori!
Oh, you tryin' to elope?
I don't mind that at all!
Let's go, let's go.
Yeah! The trash is waiting for us!
It seems they left.
Let's try to get along as the left over people.
Err—um...
I guess picking up trash can be fun too.
I wonder if it's because I'm with you, Takasu-kun!
Kawashima, you know—
Hey, hey. Let's go over there next.
Watch out!
Hey, are you oka—?
Oh god! This is freaking nasty!
What the hell is this?!
What the hell! Damn it!
Ka-Kawamshima?
Oh, I'm so surprised!
My shoes are all wet—
Noooo!
Kawashima!
No, no, no! Take it off!
Don't move.
No! It's climbing up!
Don't kick my face!
No!
Damn it!
Alright, salvaged!
It's okay now. The frog went back to his home.
'kay?
God! I don't want to do this crap anymore!
Wha—?
Ka-Kawashima?
Just kidding.
Was that funny?
It's raining.
Oh no. I'm going to get wet.
We have to get under somewhere. Right Takasu—
Hey, I think it's enough of that.
What?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
I'm the one who doesn't understand it.
Why did you force yourself to come to such a troublesome event?
You don't understand?
Oh. So you don't get this sort of thing Takasu-kun?
I've already known about your fake "outer face" for a long time.
Can't you be more like—
Yeah, the face earlier.
I have to use this face.
Huh?
You don't understand my feelings right?
Yeah, to be honest.
I'm fine with that.
You know, I'm an airhead anyway.
Kawashima?
What's wrong?
Hey! Kawashima!
Hey, what's wrong? If you're going to hide from the rain—
Hey, what are you—?
That guy's from the other day.
Why's he...?
Um... To be honest, he's—
A stalker.
S—Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Because it's so vexing!
Vexing?
I don't want to acknowledge it.
The fact that my life's been messed up thanks to someone like that.
I had to move here because of him.
Huh?
I didn't want to be a burden on my parents so—
I decided to stay with some relatives over here.
I'm also taking a break from my modeling job for a while.
But, he still chased me all the way here.
Hey! Hey!
Takasu-kun! Kawashima-san!
Hey!
That's weird. I heard they went this way.
Its okay, lets just go home Minorin.
Wow! I found some cute mini-ghosts!
Wow, they're so cute!
Ghosts?
Taiga?
Watch out!
Why should someone as suspicious as you be calling me a ghost?
Oh my god. What is she doing?
You're up against a stalker!
First of all, whose permission did you get to take those pictures?
You're pretty damn creepy.
Why not? It's not something that you'd lose.
Like hell. I'll break that camera—right along with its owner!
What the hell are you running for?!
Hold it!
W-Wait Taiga!
That idiot.
Why?
How did—? Isn't she scared?
But that guy's a nut-case.
Kawashima?
Because of him I had to take a break from work, move, and even transfer to a new school.
I got irritated, stressed out, and even ate a bunch of candy.
This means that I've lost to that worthless guy and Aisaka Taiga, doesn't it?
Huh?
Takasu-kun. Didn't you say earlier, to stop making up my fake self?
Y-Yeah. I suppose.
Fine then. Fine.
I'll quit this now.
I'll quit it. I'll quit it. I'll quit it. I'll quit it. I'll quit it. I'll quit it. And then—
Ka-Kawashima?
And I'll live with this face with this bad personality.
I'm not going to just stand by and take it.
Hey—!
Kawashima.
After that, Kawashima was amazing.
The track team paled in comparison.
She ran through the city with a magnificent form.
She utterly destroyed the shivering stalker's camera.
The stalker was terrified by the sudden change.
And then—
You liar. You're on frenzy like a demon.
You can't be the Ami-chan I know!
You're not an angel! You're personality is horrible!
So what? I'm this cute.
Who cares about personality?
Kawashima.
Hey, you alright?
Hey, Kawashima!
I did it, Takasu-kun!
Is that so?
But—I was scared.
Here. This'll warm you up.
This is a honey and kumquats.
Wow, how did you know?
Taiga just really likes it.
Taiga?
You just call Aisaka-san by her first name, don't you?
Do you still think that we're—
She's alright isn't she?
She's selfish, messed up, but she doesn't have anything fake.
And she still has friends, she still has you.
What would you do if I showed my true self, Takasu-kun?
Huh?
Would you fall for me?
K-K-K-Kawashima?
Well?
W-Wait a second...
I—
Taiga. Were they there?
Taiga?
Waterproofing. Waterproof coating.
A one-touch attachment is possible with a slight wiggle.
How's this, Taiga?!
Ginimu's special honor group.