Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home, just as any other
Goodbye, Sun
Night falls to draw me in
We'll be fine, because this world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Don't worry.
We'll get to see each other again.
The Second Child and Her Wonderful Demons
So much floating stuff!
What's going on?
I wonder.
This time of the year again, huh?
It's the station opening.
Station opening?
What's that?
What opens?
Why's all that stuff floating away?
Why? Why?
Better avoid Yase for a while.
The station opening is one of the things Yase really hates.
Don't need these.
Don't need them!
Yay, they float!
I take my leave.
Hey! This ain't over he—
I said I'm leaving!
Veritably fearsome.
Damn it.
She's like this every time the station opening takes place.
Chapter Ten
Present (5)/ Station Opening
I don't need this.
No need for this.
Don't run! Don't yell! Don't wreck everything!
We were just having fun!
Yeah!
Exactly!
Whatever you break with your hammer won't fix itself!
You know that.
But why?
Broken stuff repairs itself here.
Yeah, why?
Why?
You see...
How should I put it?
Uh...
I'd like to know that too!
They left!
Hey! Help me clean up!
This too. And this as well.
Things you don't need can't be destroyed.
This world is incomprehensible.
Though I suppose letting it float away when the station opens lends it some sense again.
My...
My favorite cup!
Where is it?!
Yase! Yase!
Look! There they are.
Yase's here too, right?
Upstairs?
Won't let me in?
What?
Come on! Let us in!
Yase?
Chapter Eleven
Present (6) /  Yase
Whoa!
So that's the station opening?
All the floaty stuff is going here.
Basically we just have to find Yase's cup in here, right?
What the hell?
Why am I even here?
Thanks!
Reminds me that Yase's place had a lot of stuff...
Why is she throwing nothing away?
Why is she hoarding everything with so much care?
Hey, why?
The station opening is there to let you get rid of your junk, right?
Then why isn't Yase throwing anything away?
Hey, why?
Which is your favorite, Yase?
None of these!
This one!
Wow!
Don't take up all the room!
Looks great!
You're so tall, Yase.
I can't bring myself to throw any of this away.
Everything here is connected to memories together with Mom.
How could I throw that away?
That doll...
Give it to me!
No!
We might reach Mom if you let
something connected to her float away!
She will come back!
My doll is back!
Why?!
Nothing came back, huh?
Neither her doll nor her mother.
I see.
Guess we gotta get crackin'!
The cup is linked to her mother!
A, Un! No time to waste!
Right!
And I felt we were so close...
"Felt"?
Sure was optimistic.
We'd never have found it.
So you want me to give you my
cup instead of the one Yase lost?
Yes.
Please.
No way.
Pretty please?
This cup is a very valuable object to me.
I can't just hand it over to console someone.
Especially not Yase.
Discipline yourself and drop the hammer!
I'm not clueless.
Yase's pissed at the station opening.
She hates people and holes up in the mountains.
I can just about guess that it's all your fault.
Being her elder gives you no right to float away what she loves.
You see...
I need to have that cup!
Will you struggle?
Get it if you can!
We're gonna get it!
What a chaotic troupe.
I'm gonna get it!
Chapter Twelve
Present (7)/
Yase and Kurama
What's that? Is it yummy?
Give it a try.
You might not like it yet.
Mom! It's so bitter!
Haha! Yase's grown fangs again!
She has no composure at all.
Fine! Fine!
It's not over yet!
I'm an ogre born from a drawing.
You don't have to try so hard to change.
You can just stay the way you are.
Mom!
I was a drawing! I could have been anything!
I wish I was like you.
You're a wonderful girl too, Yase.
Really?
When I grow up, I'm gonna be like you, Mom!
She was always like that.
She accepted me for who I was.
She was always watching over me.
Little by little, she calmed my ogre heart.
But now she's gone.
Those days are gone forever.
Nothing important
ever comes back once lost.
Never.
Yase!
Koto?
What's wrong, guys?
Why are you so dirty?
For you!
What is it?
No way!
Sorry. We looked for your cup, but we couldn't find it.
So...
Nothing important ever comes back once lost.
I'm really sorry.
Anyway, we borrowed that from Kurama's
temple so we wouldn't come empty-handed!
Kurama...
No, no, listen!
He let us have it!
He was a bit grumpy at first,
quite stubborn, actually, that old fart,
but he let us have it when we told him we'd give it to you!
Kurama...
Kurama could never understand
my feelings
and my sadness!
Guess it didn't work out.
Yase?
Calm down!
We might reach Mom if you let
something connected to her float away!
She will come back!
Yase...
Mom...
Are you okay, Yase?
What's gotten into you?
Thank you, Koto.
Everyone, thank you.
You went so far for me.
In the end we never found it.
It's okay.
I'll use that cup instead.
Really?
Sure. I'll treasure it.
Yase, this ain't over here.
I guess I should thank you, Kurama.
Thanks.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
What do you mean?
Hey, Yase? What's going on?
Yase!
Shut up!
She's a mystery.
Oh, I see!
You see what?
The station opening's almost over.
Will you sit still?!
Damn it! You should throw away those prayer beads.
Yeah!
Totally!
Some things you just can't throw away.
You little—
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
I've been feeling restless inside since Koto's trio arrived.
She's stupid, random and cheeky,
and I've gotta shell out for it.
She doesn't care about others at all.
Nothing will change, no matter the circumstances.
The Youthful Youngest Child's Problems and the Beginning and the End
Next time: "The Youthful Youngest Child's Problems and the Beginning and the End".
Not until they come back.