The summer sun sure feels nice, doesn't it?
Yep!
The flowerbeds seem to be doing well in all this sunlight too.
Some of them don't seem to be.
Oh! These are the Gardening Club president, Mizushima Aya's...
Marigolds
Mizushima Aya
Gardening Club
The Gardening Club? Oh, I see!
So this section of the grounds is for the Gardening Club's flower beds.
Th-This isn't good!
What's the matter?
I completely forgot to go to the Gardening Club !
What?! How much have you missed?!
All of yesterday.
Just a day?
Wait...
When did you join the Gardening Club?
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
And so, I'll be attending the Gardening Club today.
Then I'm coming with you.
Huh? Why?
You're the Fashion Club's precious vice president!
As president, I need to introduce myself too, don't I?
I need to warn them what'll happen if they try to steal you away.
Nothing, nothing! I didn't say a thing!
Oh! They're sure working hard!
The girl carrying the soil must be... a first-year?
No, that's the club president, Mizushima Aya!
Huh?! The president?!
We've Finally Found You!
The Third Precure!
Hey, Aya.
Huh?
Please stop, President!
It's not that simple!
The flowers...
Are you all right?!
Because I'm such a klutz, our precious flowers are ruined...
Don't cry, President!
I'm sorry. It's my fault for calling out to you so suddenly.
No. It's not your fault, Hanasaki.
Um, I just wanted to say that I'm sorry for not coming to club yesterday!
You're apologizing to me just because you missed one day?
You're so brilliant, Hanasaki...
Um... she's crying again.
You mustn't cry, President!
Please excuse me. I can get rather emotional at times.
By the way, who's this?
The president of the Fashion Club that Tsubomi's vice president of...
Kurumi Erika!
It's very nice to meet you!
She's kinda scary.
A-Aya, were you carrying that soil over to use in the flowerbeds?
Th-That's right.
Marigolds
Mizushima Aya
Gardening Club
The flowers aren't doing too well, so I thought
I'd change the amount of fertilizer we're using.
Mister flower, are you not feeling too well?
Try to get better soon, okay?
When you talk to the flowers, Hanasaki, it makes me feel like they'll get better.
Don't be silly.
But your flowers always seem to do so well.
Hanasaki, do you have a green thumb?
A green thumb?
That's what you call people with a natural affinity for raising flowers!
No way! I couldn't have one!
No, I think you might.
After all, you're the granddaughter of a botanical gardener!
Huh?! You mean the famous botanical scientist, Professor Hanasaki Kaoruko?!
Y-Yeah...
That's amazing! Please, can you
introduce me to Professor Kaoruko?!
Huh?
I'm the president of the Gardening Club, and yet I'm so terrible at raising flowers.
It's more like they wilt just from me touching them.
That's why she decided to just
focus on mixing the soil today.
That's why I want to ask Professor Kaoruko's opinion on what I'm doing wrong!
In that case, it shouldn't be a problem.
I'm... I'm so happy...
Let's go!
Huh?
But first, I need to clean up all that soil I spilled!
Ah! Why do I have to be such a scatterbrain?!
Get a grip, President!
Jusht where could the third Precure be?
There's no need to get so flustered!
I'm sure the new Precure will appear sooner or later.
I'm sure they will too.
Huh?
Grandma!
And I'm sure, when you find them, you'll sense something special about them.
Shense shomething?
Indeed.
Hey, Tsubomi's grandma!
Why, if it isn't Erika.
Today we've brought one of our upperclassmen from school!
Ta-da!
She's the Gardening Club's president, Mizushima Aya.
I-It's a pleasure to meet you.
Um... no.
Huh?
That's Lord Coupe!
Huh? Lord Coupe?
Look!
My grandmother's over here.
I'm really sorry about that!
It's quite all right. No need to be so tense.
She's nervous because she
admires you so much, that's all.
Aya has some things she wants to ask you about, apparently.
I'll help as best I can.
Thank you very much!
What do you think about her?
Do you sense anything about her?
I'm not shure...
I'm always careful with my soil ratios and drainage, but somehow I just can't seem to raise flowers well.
And?
If there really are people in this world with a green thumb and without,
I'm sure I'm fall into the latter.
So I was hoping you'd be able to give me some advice on where I'm going wrong!
Don't you get fed up with this?
Huh?
Grandma?
"Why do I keep messing up?" Don't you get
fed up with always looking at your failures?
Look around you.
This world is packed full of so many beautiful things.
And yet, you choose not to enjoy all the wonders the world has to offer.
Don't you think that's a waste?
Yes.
All life is wonderful.
But raising that life is always the hard part.
It's not something you can jump right into and just magically be good at.
So whether you have a green thumb or not is irrelevant.
What's important is to give them a lot of love and a lot of time.
A lot of love and a lot of time...
I'm sure you'll do just fine.
So have a little confidence.
Thank you so much!
I won't be so negative anymore!
That's great, Aya!
Yeah...
Thanks to you, I got to hear some great words of advice from Grandma.
Don't cry!
Good morning!
Aya, how are the flowers doing?
They're still not doing great, but I'll take my time and be patient with them.
Good morning, everyone!
Hm?
Itsuki!
I'm sorry to intrude like this, but I have a favor to ask of the Gardening Club.
Sure! What can we do for you?
Well, the student council is proposing that we install some green curtains.
I'd like to ask you to help us test if it's really viable.
What's a "green curtain"?
It's a "curtain" made of plants that'll shade the
windows from the bright sunlight during the summer.
You really know your stuff, Hanasaki!
Oh, not at all...
If the experiment with the Gardening Club works out, we'll set them up all around the school next year.
If that's what you're after, we'd be glad to help!
Thank you!
Our plants should arrive by the time school finishes today.
I'll leave it to you!
Okay!
If we grow these out, we should be able to cover both the windows in this classroom entirely.
Let's give this all we've got, everyone!
Right!
The green curtain is complete!
How wonderful!
Looks like covering the school in these next year should be very possible!
We did it, President!
And the seedlings you planted
have all grown beautifully, Aya!
All that stuff about you being bad at raising plants must've been your imagination!
Yeah, but it's all because you guys helped me out.
Thank you!
What's going on?!
They did say on the weather forecast that a typhoon would be passing nearby...
Huh?! A typhoon?!
Will the plants be all right?
We only just arranged the buds.
I'm burning... I'm burning up!
O' typhoon, rage more, and scatter these plants to the winds!
A new dawn beckons for the Desert Apostles!
I've had an epiphany!
My new finisher shall be...
this!
A typhoon for a typhoon.
With this Typhoon Punch, the Precure and that accursed third fairy...
shall fall!
Tsubomi!
Erika!
School's canceled for the day cause of the typhoon.
I know, but the green curtain...
You're worried about it, right?
I'm worried too!
That's why I can't let you go on your own, Tsubomi!
Erika...
Come on, let's go!
Right!
Aya!
Hanasaki, Kurumi!
At this rate, the vines are all going to untwine!
Let's set up a tarp to protect it!
Right!
Are you okay?!
Yeah!
Just a little bit more! Give it your all!
Okay!
Aya seems different today.
Yeah, she really seems more reliable than before!
I wonder why...
When I look at them, courage seems to flow through me!
Aya...
She has both kindness and strength!
She's a shweet girl!
We did it!
It's all set up!
And the wind seems to be dying down too.
We should be all right now, shouldn't we?
Yeah.
It's wilted...
The bud that I planted...
That's perfect!
We did it, Aya!
Huh?
Aya?
Hey!
Itsuki!
You were all worried about the green curtain too, huh?
Aya's gone.
Why is that every plant I touch ends up dying?
Hrm?
The Flower of your Heart is wilting nicely.
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
Very well. We shall make use of this today.
You're up, Desertrian!
Bitter melon!
Everyone, get out of here!
Thish ish bad!
Huh?
Aya's Flower of the Heart is the one...
...that was stolen!
Bitter melon!
Pleashe, hurry and shave her!
Right!
Go forth, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
I love plants so much, so why am I no good at raising at them?!
Wh-What are you talking about?
You did raise them well!
Look!
Wha—?!
Why?!
I put so much love into them, yet this happened!
Aya...
Bitter melon!
Excellent work, Desertrian!
We shall ruin all plant life in this world...
and then reduce the hearts of
people to the driest of deserts!
We won't allow it!
Aya's heart is filled with her genuine love for plants!
You're just abusing her heart in
order to make a Desertrian from it.
I've had it up to here with this!
And on top of that, you're using the very plants she loves in order to destroy other plants.
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Desertrian! I shall leave you to defeat Cure Marine!
Bitter melon!
Marine!
Fear not. Because your opponent...
shall be me!
Take this!
Typhoon Punch!
Blossom!
Bitter melon!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
This is the end for you!
I'll put all the strength from the Flower of my Heart into my fist!
Typhoon Punch!
Blossom Screw Punch!
Hmph.
It seems we shall have to settle this another time.
Things are finally getting interesting.
Blossom!
Marine's got the Flower of her Heart!
She recovered it for us!
Thank goodness!
You guys!
Did something happen to Mizushima?
Oh, she's all right!
I think she's just exhausted
because she was working so hard.
I see...
Huh?
It's... it's so cute!
What'sh with thish warmth I feel?
Could thish girl be the third Precure?
U-Um...
We'll leave the rest to you.
Very well.
Aya!
Everyone...
When I saw that the seedling had withered like that...
You can still save it!
Huh?
Here, take a look.
Some of the tendrils are still alive and growing well.
I'm sure the seedling is going to do just fine.
You're right.
And yet I just gave in to my despair and gave up on them so quickly.
I'm sorry.
From now on, I'm going to raise you with a lot of love and give you a lot of time.
I feel like the flowers are saying "Thank you" to her.
Huh?!
No... I mustn't cry!
From now on, I've got to be
strong and care for my plants!
Right!
Aya, I think you're strong enough already.
Don't they always say "Adversity builds character"?
In the language of flowers, a
sasanqua means "genuine love."
Aya has genuine love for plants and the strength to protect them!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
I've finally found my partner!
With eyes and hair of sparkling gold...
...and shining golden ribbons and frills!
And beauty shurpasshing Venus hershelf!
The strength to protect those she holds dear...
...and bearing a heart full of burning justice!
Shining bright, like the Sun in the sky!
Introducing our third member...
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure:
Cure Sunshine
is Born!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!