My favorite food...
Strawberries, I guess.
That's pretty cute, Iona-san.
Look at this ranking...
Akira's popularity dropped again.
She's over the hill, I swear...
and now she even started ditching work.
Well, she never really fit our style, anyway.
She feels a bit unrefined.
So what do we do about next issue's cover model?
How about we drop Akira and go with Yuuko?
Well, that was awkward...
They really could have discussed this somewhere el—
Winter Fashion Models
I like having them with sugar and milk, as long as it's not condensed milk.
Huh? Oh, right, the strawberries.
I use the back of my fork
Winter Fashion Models
to smush them all up.
I'll make you apologize to Hitoe if I win!
Open!
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
I'm home.
What happened, Hitoe? You're soaked!
What about your friends? Weren't you with them?
You should go dry yourself off before you catch a...
Hitoe?
Hey, I'm first! Aki-lucky!
Piruluk-tan, show your stuff!
Don't you go easy on her just because she's a scrub. You hear?
Hey, Ruu?
What?
Can Tama fight?
All you want.
Draw. I'm placing a card in the Enerzone. Piruluk-tan, Grow!
Oh, and I'm summoning Sky Cat-chan, too!
Tama, Grow! I summon Kukri and Vonia!
Don't get too excited, squirt!
What... is this feeling?
Battling Akira is really painful.
It is painful...
But still!
The hell? Isn't she supposed to be a WIXOSS newbie?
She is one.
This seems to be her first serious battle.
What?!
She's quite...
gifted.
You trying to tell me something?
So I'm not as gifted as she is, huh?!
You're pissing me off, Piruluk!
Just shut your mouth and follow my commands!
I'm gonna get this over with quickly.
Arts!
Peeping Analyze.
Average Sword Flamvell
Arch Aura
Ruu-Ruu?
Looks like you're playing by pure power there.
So that means you must have a lot of...
level 4 cards!
Missed.
Damn it! Who cares if I missed?!
I want to know what her wish is, Piruluk.
My wish...
Aww, I wonder if you'll go all ouchy-ouchy when I see your wish, Ruu-Ruu.
Come on, Piruluk-tan. Go ahead and show me what's troubling her.
I see nothing.
Hey, stop acting like some broken piece of trash.
She has
no wish.
That's right. I... have no wish.
Wh-What?! A-Are you serious?
You don't have any wishes,
and you're still battling as a Selector?
No way! You've got to be
kidding me! That makes no sense!
All the Selectors are like, super serious and stuff, you know?
And you're just doing this for the fun of it? You're awful!
For someone without a wish to
participate as a WIXOSS Selector is...
blasphemy.
I don't care what you say.
Huh?
I don't have any wishes,
so I'm not scared of anything either!
Arch Aura!
Tama!
What the hell is wrong with you?
You don't have any wishes, right?
Then...
why the fuck are you trying to take mine from me?!
I-I just wanted you... to apologize to Hitoe, and...
Stop fucking lying!
Making me grovel before you... You were enjoying this!
Wait!
"Played WIXOSS in the library with Ruuko and Yuzuki."
"We bought pork buns on our way back..."
"Ruu...ko..."
"Yuzu—"
Hitoe?
What's the matter, Hitoe?
The words... they're disappearing!
They're disappearing! Everything I wrote...
It's disappearing!
It's all disappearing!
Hitoe...
Akira's late again?
Iona, you don't know where she is?
I don't.
Man, this sucks. That brat...
That's it. Akira's scratched from next month's issue.
Better yet, why don't we just drop her altogether?
Sure, why not.
Iona...
I smell battle... and a loser, too.
Do you remember that unhealthy girl who battled Iona here?
That was only her second battle, but already her second loss.
One more defeat would have spelled certain doom for her wish.
Then you approached that poor, cornered girl...
You sweet-talked her into battle, baiting her with a free win.
You ended that poor girl who had just lost her second battle...
Her wish, and her life.
You took them from her.
You got a problem with that?! It's my choice how I battle!
You're right. It is your choice.
Still, too bad about the next battle...
That girl Iona beat before
had no trouble beating you.
That's when you stopped scavenging the scraps Iona left behind
and started looking for weak, fledgling Selectors.
And yet...
You lost.
Pathetic.
I don't want your dirty hands to
disgrace any more Selector battles.
What?!
Your wish is to see Iona's life ruined.
You want to beat Iona, right?
Isn't it weird, then, that you're
avoiding a Selector battle with her?
Like I said, it's my choice how I battle!
And it doesn't even matter since you're
going to bite the dust when I win!
Thank you very much!
Looks like Yuuko's here.
The hell? Wasn't today's shoot supposed to be me and Ion—
You don't have a shoot today.
Looks like you lost your place here while you were out looking for Selectors.
Oh, you poor thing! How ironic to see you fall to ruin before Iona does... right?
I need to go.
Sore loser.
I don't care if my life is ruined...
As long as I get to tear your life to shreds with my own hands!
I guess it's game over for her.
It doesn't look like you're running a fever.
Do you still feel sick?
My head still kinda hurts...
Well, let me call your teacher and tell them you'll stay home for the day.
I made Grandma worry...
Ruu...
You were enjoying this!
Why do I enjoy battling so much?
I know what horrible things will happen if I go on... and yet...
Don't cry, Ruu.
You know, Tama likes seeing Ruu having fun in battles.
So don't cry. We can have plenty of batt—
Stop it!
Ruu...
Hey, Kazuki? Let's go hang out sometime!
Yeah, I'll go too!
Sure, why not? Let's head out.
Whoa, that's unusual for you.
So, wanna grab some food?
Yeah, sure.
Let's go!
Do you have a minute?
You know, you and Kazuki-kun don't really give off a good impression.
People are kinda creeped out seeing you two together all the time.
That was too blunt.
Don't make that face. We're actually just worried about you two.
Worried?
I feel bad for you two when I hear all the bad rumors,
so I wanted to give you some advice...
What's that to you?
Why do you care?
Well, to be honest, I'm only
concerned about Kazuki-kun.
I couldn't care less about you.
I mean, I feel so sorry for Kazuki-kun when I see him being stalked by you.
Yeah. You may not know, but Kazuki-kun is pretty popular.
Just because you're around, all the bad rumo—
What an attitude.
Guess that means there's some truth to the rumors!
Now, now...
Damn it...
Yuzuki.
Don't talk to me!
What's wrong with everyone?
They're the creeps...
Hiya there!
You're a Selector, right?
Yay! I finally met one! Wahoo!
It's so hard finding Selectors, you know?
Can you pretty pretty please
battle cute little Chiyori-chin?
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Huh?
You're in for a lot of pain
if you lose in Selector battles.
Yuzuki!
Yes! I know!
It's written right here!
A WIXOSS... novelization?
Yup!
If you lose three times,
the WIXOSS factors expand inside your body
like a hot air balloon, and you go kaboom!
And then you die, right?
That's so scary!
It's not lik—
It's really cool that you still want to battle,
all for the sake of seeing your wish come true!
I'm sorry. My girl here is a bit soft in the head, you know?
That's so rude, Eldora!
At least I'm strong in battle!
Anyway! My dear Selector-san, I'd like to offer my commemorative first battle to you!
I...
Oh come on, Kazuki-kun!
Honestly, it's not like that...
Hey, let's go to one more place!
Well, uh, sure.
There's so many things I want to ask you!
Let's do this, okay? Please?!
All right.
Yuzuki!
Let's do this...
Yay! It's time to battle!
I'm going to step out for a bit, so take a good rest, okay?
Why do I feel like... I've been looking for something all this time?
If I can't have that something...
It feels like there's no reason to be alive.
I lost! I lost, darnit...!
Goodness, she's strong!
Way stronger than you, Chiyori.
So sorry to have bothered you there.
Come on, Eldora!
All great heroines lose their first battle!
Yeah, right. That only happens in novels.
Let me give you this!
And let's meet again, okay?
Bye-bee!
Yuzuki...
I guess I won.
Yeah.
Losing three times means my wish won't come true.
But there's no telling how many times I have to win for it to come true, right?
The conditions need to be met.
"Conditions"? Yeah, there's the rub.
You'll probably tell me something later again...
I wonder what would happen if my wish were to be reversed?
Would I never be able to win Kazuki over?
No, it has to be worse than that.
Maybe Kazuki would hate me and I'd never be able to see him again.
I wonder where Kazuki went.
Yuzuki.
Maybe he went to Momoka-san's place to pick up some cards.
The guys with him seemed new to the game.
You think he's showing them all sorts of things?
Yuzuki, listen to me.
Or maybe they went to the movies and
stopped by the food court for some matches.
Or maybe they went for okonomiyaki and then they exchanged mail addresses—
Yuzuki!
I don't want this.
I'd rather just disappear than see Kazuki taken from me!
Even if you're upset,
you should never say such a thing.
I'm serious...
Hanayo-san, you're a liar!
But... I need you to have a chance for my wish to come true!
I lost to Akira. But I was able to beat that girl, Chiyori!
If I still have the chance to win...
if the chance to get Kazuki isn't gone yet...
If my wish isn't gone yet...
Then rather than having him taken from me...
Yuzuki.
I'm your LRIG. I'll follow you.
No matter where.
I don't think I asked for much back when I was living with my mother.
She seemed so overwhelmed
even when she was all by herself.
But...
I don't know what Ruuko is thinking.
She's scary.
I didn't know why I was scaring my mom... which scared me in turn, too.
Kominato
I'm fine as long as I have Grandma and my brother with me.
I didn't want to make anyone scared again, so I learned not to ask for much. I think...
And still...
You know, Tama likes seeing Ruu having fun in battles.
No... No, no!
The hell you're acting like you're the victim here?
You enjoyed making me grovel before you.
Ruu-chan... Ruu-chan...
Ruu-chan, wake up.
I'm sorry. I told her you were asleep.
I'm sorry to bother you all of a sudden.
Do you like parfaits? I ordered one on the off chance that you might like it.
Thank you...
Hitoe loves chestnut parfaits.
This one looks good!
Maybe I should bring her here next time.
Uhm...
I found your number and Yuzuki-san's number in Hitoe's cell phone.
You must think I'm a horrible mother, going through her daughter's phone.
But, you see...
That's the notebook Hitoe was keeping on battles—
You recognize this?
Y-Yes.
The words written here...
Hitoe told me that she can't see them.
She also said she doesn't know you girls.
Sharing all the fun and happy words with everyone...
It made me happier than I've ever been before.
Having friends really is nice.
"Today, I bought matching pairs of scrunchies with Ruuko and Yuzuki."
"They looked really cute with them."
"They said I looked cute, too."
"Sharing all the fun and
happy words with everyone..."
"It made me happier than I've ever been before."
Sharing all the fun and happy words with everyone...
It made me happier than I've ever been before.
Having friends really is nice.
"Having friends really is nice."
She was so happy about having made friends.
But now, she's...
Ruuko-san, if there's anything you know or may have noticed, can you please tell me?
Even if it was just an argument you had with her...
Wait, I'm not trying to place the blame on you or anything, but it looks like something went off in her,
and she's in shock, and...
Ruuko-san...?
Hitoe lost three times...
We didn't know that such a thing would happen if we lost...
We had fun... battling together was fun... and then...
R-Ruuko-san? Calm down...
Ruuko-san?
I don't know...
What...
I should do.
This
Heart
is
Pure White
I just don't know!
Once you give yourself to the shadow of the clockwork
tokeijikake no kage ni unadzuitara
darkness begins to encroach from the door of the end
owari no doa ga hiraki hajimaru yami
Menacing answers lie hiding in wait
ayaui kotae soko ni miekakureru
Today's wish will become tomorrow's taboo
kyou no inori wa ashita tabuu ni naru
Lost in a labyrinth where the world is turned upside-down
ten to chi wo utsusu sakasama no meiro
the gears slowly start to turn
mawaridashita haguruma
Quietly from within the waves of people
hitogomi no naka de mimi wo sumashitara
a bell rings out, beckoning my very being
tamashii wo maneku ano suzu no ne hibiku sora e
I have no choice but to walk the endless path
mugen no hate made wo susumu shika nai
for this is the future I willingly chose
jibun de eranda mirai dakara
In the wake of the unreachable summer clouds
todokanai natsugumo yureru kagerou
lies the place of smiles I'll one day reclaim
itsuka torimodosu egao no basho
So you wanted to do this, too.
Smile of Sacrifice: Cure Eru
Why are you saying that?
I want to do it with you.
I want to do it.
Just let go and have some fun.
That
Girl
is
Desire
That girl is desire.