6th Street
“Pandora Maid Service”
Ignorance does not equal shamelessness.
Sanada Fresh Seafood
It merely reflects purity.
Until the time comes, it's best that we remain pure.
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
“Pandora's Box”from Vol. 3, Chapter 20
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
Is that you, Hotori?
How'd you know?
You put your hand over your mouth and stumbled backwards.
You can see that too?
My guardian spirit taught me how.
Miss Shizuka, when did you become a psychic!?
Gotcha!
Oh, a mirror.
You were watching me through that.
Can't even see through such an elementary trick.
You require more training before you can become an apprentice, lass.
I came to shop for Tattsun's birthday present today.
At an antiques store, of all places.
Oh, maybe this scale...
I've measured the perfect amount of sugar for your coffee!
Yeah, I bet she'd love that!
Kinda pricey though.
Hey Shizuka, would this be good?
That's kind of hard to say.
Let's see, I think it's...
Maruko's skies have the best view of the moon.
Well? You buying it or what?
You still want full price for that!?
Oh yeah, kinda off-topic, but I went to Africa recently.
I see. So that explains your weird clothes.
They're coming outta the god damn walls!
Here. I brought you a souvenir.
Yay! Oh, happy day!
What the heck is this!?
Creepy! Weird! Unnerving!
A trinity of freakiness!
Those all mean pretty much the same thing.
Basically, it was a gift forced upon me at a wealthy local's wedding ceremony.
But he told me that this mask grants the power to locate anyone and anything...
Whoa... I so don't want this...
Now, now.
Just think of it as a love charm.
Stop it!
Oh, I just thought of a present for Tattchan.
Her name's Tattsun.
A real cute one, 'kay?
Happy trails!
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
I can't help but think she's just conning me into buying her junk.
Good heavens!
Actually, mice don't really like cheese that much.
It's two days early, but...
Happy birthday!
Reserved
Thanks, everyone.
I haven't had a partly like this since grade school.
This is from my family.
We call it our seafood salad.
Thank you! I'll treasure it forever!
I'd rather you eat if while it's still fresh, though.
So you're saying that this is a Sanada Scat Salad.
Too much rhyme, that's a crime.
That's the last thing I'd expect you to complain about.
Gift List
Okay, what else...
A crate of veggies from the grocery store.
Two free cleaning coupons from the cleaners.
Gift List
A free bottle of every drink from the 100 yen shop.
I bought you a cake. Accept it with gratitude.
T-Thank you...
Now that the party's in full swing,
it's time for the main event!
We just started.
The main event is Tatsuno's party, remember?
Nice segway, MC.
Hang in there!
Here! A gift from me to you.
Thank you.
A beat-up old box?
There's something inside.
Oh, I get it.
I'm supposed to wait until my actual birthday to open it, right?
Sorry, but that birthday wish won't be coming true.
Huh?
The key's missing.
When I bought it from Kameido Antiques, the lady said it didn't have a key when she first got it.
What?
But that's what makes it so romantic!
Those long, autumn nights, thinking about what could be inside...
...isn't that just enchanting?
She said I could pass it off if I fed her that.
No way! It's kinda creeping me out.
Josephine Joestar, Jojo! I've always wanted to say that.
Man, that was fun!
We should have parties more often!
This place is pretty much eternally reserved, anyway.
When's your birthday, Sanada?
February.
That was forever ago! Thanks for nothing!
What about you, Granny?
April.
Kon?
It's, uh, not really important.
Huh? How come?
C'mon, don't be shy! Seaside will throw you a huge party!
Well when's your birthday?
Mine's in May.
Girls born in May are blessed with wisdom and intellect!
I could do without your "wisdom" for the rest of my life.
So, when is it, Kon?
Speaking of May...
She's changing the subject.
Ta-da! I found Kon's student ID.
Don't do it! The consequences of asking are dire!
Let's see...
September 8th!
That's today!
Well, I guess that's why she didn't want me to say it.
Look what you did, you little jerk!
You killed the mood, now what?
You better fix this.
Happy birthday!
Uh, ¡Feliz cumpleaños a tí!
Oh yeah, you need a present!
I'll run to the candy store real quick!
Enough with the pity party!
If you keep picking at it, it'll tear off.
The only thing left that I could give was that love charm.
Oh? I would've rather got that.
Instead of this Pandora's Box.
Okay, if I give Kon the romantic box, and Tattsun the love charm...
Yeah, that'll work out perfectly!
Why don’t we fix the mood here first?
We'll throw you a real party next year, Kon.
‘Cause now I've memorized your birthday!
September 8th. Futaba Kon's birthday!
A mortifying memory, Futaba Kon.
Now, none of us will forget.
Don't make it into a stupid poem!
Cup noodles are best if you cook them 45 seconds less than suggested.
-A few days later-
Kawai Apartments
Oh, I got it!
Wow, awesome! You could be a thief!
...and be apprehended by me!
Maybe if I went senile, you could!
Now then, what's in the box?
Charms?
Aw man, that's boring!
Hey, this is a love charm!
Guess Tatsuno should have stuck with this instead.
Now that we opened it, it's kinda sad.
Pandora's Box became an ordinary dirty old box.
How is that a love charm!?
Why would I care about marrying a rich guy from Africa?
Excuse me!
Ah, yes. You're Hotori's friend, Tattchan, right?
No, I'm Tattsun.
I mean, Tatsuno.
I've been told that you buy old knicknacks here.
I sure do.
I'll just have take a peek and...
MEDIA ROOM
“Business Trip Maid Service”From Vol. 2, Chapter 17
Your assignment is to create and upload a functional website.
Hey, is "upload" the same thing as "uphill"?
God, just shut up! At least try to help a little.
I'll work on the tags, so you focus on the material.
Thanks, Suzuki.
Man, I wish I could have been with Suzuki! Why'd I get stuck with the dumbass jock?
'Bout the only thing I'm good for is lifting weights!
You don't have to be so serious about it.
Just wing it and throw together something simple.
Finally, I got the title up.
Maid Cafe Seaside
I wanna get this page up and running so we can attract customers.
Oh, nice! Making an advertisement for our project.
That's like two birds with one stone!
Arashiyama.
Here's the drawing you asked for.
Wow, thanks! This is perfect!
Okay, here's the Tattsun Maid pictures I promised you.
Marvelous!
I'm gonna put this drawing up on the site.
You'll get busted for false advertising.
You're the one who said to just do whatever.
Well, I guess we'll have to rethink our plan.
Dismissed. You're to turn in your assignments in two weeks.
Ahh! I didn't even get anything done yet!
Thanks for waiting.
Okay, who had the curry again?
Ah well, you can just share.
You're horrible! You're even worse than a normal waitress!
Store
And she just has to remind me about it while I'm sneaking off from work.
She's starting to act like a cranky old lady.
That group offense warrants extra salads and coffee.
Kobuhei, you dumbass!
Don't hurt the poor maid's feelings!
Hey, Tattsuntsun!
My nickname just got even more unpleasant.
Do you have a compyooter at your house?
Yeah, but mostly for my brother to play his games.
How about we work on our project after work?
Well, the thing is...
Kon's got a fever, so she's sick in bed.
She lives alone, so I thought I'd go and take care of her.
Impossible! I thought they said idiots can't catch colds.
Of all the times to get sick...
I don't think I've ever caught a cold.
'Cept that time I stayed home in middle school, anyway.
You always bragged about never missing school!
Yeah, you had perfect attendance.
I doubt these guys would ever catch a cold.
Hey, is Sanada home right now?
Oh, Hiroyuki?
Yeah, he got back a while ago.
Perfect.
So there you have it.
Can I go work on my project at
second-choice-Sanada's house?
There I have what? You're still on the clock!
But it's for the advertising too.
Well, we don't have any customers now, anyway. Guess you can go.
Yippie!
There's four of 'em right here!
Oh, you guys are here everyday so I just thought we had weird-shaped furniture.
She's horrible!
The hag's 100 times worse!
She's in a whole ‘nother league.
Those words cut like a knife!
W-Wait! You're going to Sanada's house?
Since he's got a computer too.
You can go too.
Hey, wait up!
Huh? Weren't you going to check on Kon?
We can go together later.
My PC? Yeah, no problem.
When?
Now!?
We'll pick you up a little something.
How about potato croquettes?
Since we're right here by the butcher's.
The butcher's!?
If they buy something that simple, they'll be here in just a few minutes!
And those are the cheapest things they have too!
Hey, could you get me some cream puffs from Romand?
What? All right, fine.
Since when have you been Mr. Gourmet?
You selfish little turd!
All right! That gained me 20 minutes!
Ah! Oh, crap!
I've got all those nude mags under my desk!
Excuse us!
Whew! Made it!
I forgot the most important thing!
All that downloaded porn is still on there!
Hey, what's this folder for?
Sanada, you creeper!
It could happen!
My only choice is to delete all the files!
I don't even have to think about it!
Hey, we're here!
Hey.
Hey Sanada, you look kinda worn out.
Feels like I just suppressed my dark side to become a Jedi.
What're you talking about?
Here's your cream puffs.
Sorry to barge in like this.
Hey, no problem.
So anyway, I wanna put this picture on our front page.
I don't have a scanner, so no can do.
Scanners? I thought you were training to be a Jedi.
Anyway, that's not what I was asking about.
A scanner's a machine that scans and digitizes documents onto your computer.
Huh? Can't you do anything if you have a computer?
Ugh, that sounds like something a
computer-illiterate geezer would say.
Well, this was pointless then!
C'mon four eyes, we're leaving!
Four-eyes?
So I deleted all that for nothing!?
Hey, isn't that the novel I lent you?
1/4th Bloodlust
Just shoving it up there...
I'm taking it back with me.
NOOO! DON'T LOOK THERE!
Oh, oh god...
See? You can dress it up all you want, but a turd is a turd.
Disgusting! From now on, I'll call him Hustleryuki.
It'd be much weirder for a boy his age not to have those lying around.
Come on, let's go feed Kon and go home.
"A man, a plan, a canal: Panama" is a palindrome.
Densuke Kon
DENSUKE KON!?
I knew he was a man!
Men are scary. Men are the devil!
She's a girl living alone, so she used her dad's nameplate.
Maybe she's asleep.
It's unlocked.
Wow, pretty careless.
Kon? We're coming in!
Careless! Careless!
C-c-c-c-c-careless...
...less go! That was awesome, Tattsun!
Keep it down.
You're in a sick person's home!
But you started it...
That's a wicked fever.
Kon? Are you okay?
It's a lot worse than I thought.
Go air out the futon. I'll make her an ice pack.
Got it!
That guy looks just like the guy who runs the cleaners.
When she's calm and sleeping like that, she's actually kinda cute.
It hurts... I'm gonna die, mommy.
Mommy?
Kon!
You need to rest!
No choice but to kill you two.
Calm down!, Kon!
Hey, watch it!
You were just mumbling in your sleep!
It was just gibberish!
Really?
Dead serious!
Oh, okay.
Okay, Kon. Just get some rest.
Oh, thanks guys.
I'll be fine on my own if I just get some sleep.
Whatever you say.
Hotori fell from a desk too.
Looks like your temperature's gone down from all that sweating.
I'm gonna go cook something, so behave yourself.
What'cha making?
Leek and egg rice gruel.
That sounds kinda yummy.
I'm not making it for you.
Fine. I'll just eat those cream puffs then.
Huh? They're not here!
Of course they aren't. You gave them to Sanada.
Shoot. I gave them to Hustleryuki for nothing!
In memory of Sanada. For his playboys were found by two girls today.
Today's cream puffs are kind of bitter.
She's got enough CDs to open a store.
She really loves music.
Whoa! A GITAH!
Looks like the strings are kinda fat and a few are missing.
Is this a beginner's guitar?
It's a bass.
You're an inch away from getting decked by every bassist in the world.
Oh, so this is a bass, huh?
Hmm? There's no music coming out!
God, you're a pest!
Look, the amp's not even switched on.
So the music comes from that huge speaker?
W-What's going on?
Nothing at all!
Okay, let's just go back to bed, 'kay?
You're the one who flipped the switch!
We're back!
Sorry we're late!
Hey, welcome back.
Hey there!
Hey! You ditching work again?
Granny aside, I'm worried about this store!
I went and came back, okay?
Hiroyuki seems kinda depressed. Something happen?
Y-Your son, Hustleryuki has lecherous tendencies.
Why that little...!
Did he do something to you, Hotori?
Over my dead body!
You sure? You sure you're okay?
Uh-oh.
Today's been a total bust.
The Next Morning
Tattsun's staying home today.
I wonder if she caught Kon's cold?
Speaking of which, my dad's been feeling crummy since last night.
Must be a virus going around.
I don't feel too hot either. I think I'll go home and sleep.
Temporarily Closed
Huh?
Granny, what's wrong?
Oh, Hotori?
First time in ages that I've caught a cold.
It's nothing serious, but I don't want you catching it, so go on home, dear.
It's spreading at an alarming rate...
I better be careful too.
Idiots can't catch colds.
Oh dear, I must have a cold!
I'm so healthy it makes me sick!
What should I do?
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living for rock!
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
Living lonely, blasting my music.
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Kyou mo Kare ni wa Nasake Kokurezu
and I still have yet to tell him how I feel.
Toppuu ni Inochi wo Sasage Ashikoshi wo
Putting our lives in the hands of a tornado,
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
we train our legs by playing drums.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We're the Maids, yeah!
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Chiisai no wa Zessan Eigyou Chuu
The little one's working inside, making a profit!
Thank you very maid for coming!
And so they took flight, vanishing without a trace.
Eloping... how romantic!
Sounds like that geezer was quite the delinquent as a kid.
No, he wasn't a troublemaker.
I meant flight, as in flying off in an airplane.
Really? Then what if they escaped by sea?
Eswimming, I guess?
How is that even possible?
Next time: 7th Street: Lovers' Midnight Dash
Café Seaside
7th Street“Lovers' Midnight Dash”
‘Keeps on turning lazily.