Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
胸を張って歩き出せる
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す今この胸で
Now, with these hands that tremble
Mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
見送った手を振った
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne, to
よかったね、と
So happy for them
Detention Room
Ahh, they finally let us out.
I've been lying on that hard floor for so long my neck is killing me.
So Tenshi's downfall didn't turn this school into paradise, huh?
Why are you still undressed?
What was with those guys?
Below Contact Bridge 1 - Pathway
Next time they come, we'll turn things around like we did with Tenshi.
They're normal students, so that's not allowed.
But still, it's strange.
What is?
There were never any normal students who would force us to reflect on our actions before.
Maybe Tenshi was stopping them before.
Maybe...
The NPCs are supposed to be a model of good students for us to follow.
Their emotions are like those of real people, too.
So no matter how obstinate they are it's not anything out of the ordinary.
In other words, there's bound to be some extremists among them too.
And that would be the acting Student Council President.
He's even worse than Tenshi at turning things around.
What should we do, Yurippe?
Should we seduce him?
What about you is seductive?
What was that?  As if you've seen them before!
Just looking at you with clothes on is more than enough.
Damn you!  Have you ever felt anything like these?!
This perfect softness?!
Like I'd ever!
How foolish.
So, what shall we do about our activities from now on?
Anti-Angel Operations HQ
You finally asked, huh?
Let's test the waters a bit.
For the time being, just do whatever you want in classes.
Ah, don't mess with the regular students too much, though.
That's all.  Dismissed.
Otonashi-kun.
Here.  Take this with you.
Huh?  Isn't that pretty important?
Why are you giving it to someone like me?
Just take it.
Tenshi won't be moving against us anymore.
We proved that last night.
The remaining problem is the substitute Student Council President.
If we start making disturbances, how will he react?
Study Building A - Classroom
Oh man, my heart is pounding!
I'm eating snacks in the middle of class!
I ate it!  I totally ate it!
Boldly eating snacks in the middle of class!
I'm being so reckless!
Round's mine once I get past this!
Too bad.
Ouch!  Are you serious?
Riichi, Chi-Toi, Doradora Oyaman.
Aw, damn!  You'll win it all, Hisako!
Ah, just wild heaven.
I can't believe I lost to a girl.
Could you be a bit more quiet in that corner, there?
Ah, our bad.
Sensei!  I need to pee!
You again?  Go ahead.
What's she doing?
She's going to the bathroom at one-minute intervals.
What an idiot.
What shall we do?
Just chatting like this is fine.
I mean, look at that...
Sensei! I need to pee!
Yeah, just go.
Ah, what an idiot.
That's as far as you go!
He's here.  Naoi Ayato-sama.
I... I need to pee!
Let's get outta here!
I'll be back.
You.  What do you think you're doing?
I guess you can't hear me.
Fine.  Take him like this to reflect on his actions.
What are you telling me to reflect on?!
For sleeping in the middle of class...
and threatening innocent students.
I'm amazed you're able to ask such a stupid question.
In a way, it's impressive.
What'd you say?!
Damn you!  You trying to run?!
I'm right here!  Bring it!
What's the point in keeping this up?
Academy Cafeteria 3F - Rear
Say... are you hungry?
Not really.
It's not quite mealtime yet.
I see...
In the cafeteria, see...
There's this Szechuan Tofu that's so spicy that nobody will touch it...
But when I tried it, it was so good I was shocked!
Ah, so anyway...
If you want, why don't I treat...
... you...
... to some?
What are you doing?
Huh?  Oh... I'm coming.
Academy Cafeteria - Inside
Man, it still looks scary.
Whoa!  God, this is spicy!
I heard that one would usually eat it with rice...
Really?
Really, what?  Isn't this way too spicy?
Not really.  It's just...
Just...
Delicious.
I see.  It's not just that you like spicy stuff.
Szechuan Tofu is your favorite, huh?
What's wrong?
I... like Szechuan Tofu?
Uh... why would you ask me that?
I never knew.
Tachibana-san.
What are you doing at this hour?
Can't you guess for yourself?  We're eating!
Eating during rest hours is against the rules.
I forgot.
That's right, isn't it?  It's against the rules...
I think she really did forget.
Behold the power of her beloved Szechuan Tofu!
Come with me.
Damn it!
Eating some Szechuan Tofu during rest hours shouldn't warrant this!
And where the hell are we?
This is like an isolation cell!
I'm sleepy.  I'm going to sleep.
Wh... hey wait.  Is this really the time for that?
Is there anything else to do?
You don't think it's strange?!
Holing us up in this isolation cell-looking place?
This place is for us to reflect on what we did.  It's to be expected.
Even so, would people ordinarily be able to sleep in a place like this?
Good night.
She actually fell asleep...
UTW Presents:
What was that noise?  An earthquake?
A battle?  Is help coming?
That's right!  I had this!
Yuri!  We've been imprisoned.
It's broken...
This junk actually made me think we had a chance!
... nashi-kun... Otonashi-kun.
Can you hear me?
Otonashi-kun.
I hear you!
I'm going to trust that you can hear this, Otonashi-kun.
Listen well.  It turns out Naoi Ayato is not an NPC.
He has a soul just like us.  He's a human.
No way...
It's not that hard to believe.
He used to be the Vice-President, so he must have had excellent behavior.
If so, he wouldn't be able to maintain his existence, and should've disappeared.
But it turns out that he was beating up on the regular students in secret.
He acted like a model student, but worked evil deeds on the side.
I guess that's how he maintained balance in this world.
What would he accomplish by doing that?
And now that Tenshi has lost her position, he's free to do whatever he wants in this world.
We still don't know his objective though.
Regardless, the battle has begun.
A battle worse than anything you've seen yet.
He knows that we won't attack the regular students...
So he's holding them hostage and using them as shields.
We have no choice but to do as he says.
At this point, it's been completely one-sided.
One by one, our comrades are being cut down.
I think... that maybe Tenshi is being confined.
I've searched the detention room we were confined in...
but I wasn't able to find her.
I think she's confined in a place that's harder to rescue her from.
Hey, Otonashi-kun.  I was thinking...
Maybe right now you're with Tenshi.
Please, Otonashi-kun.  Take Tenshi with you.
We need her to put an end to this terrible conflict.
There's no time.
Come to the grounds.
I have to go now.
Alright.  Good luck!
Damn it!
Why do I have to be stuck in here?
Wake up, Tachibana!
Please help me.
My friends are in trouble!
What a strange thing to say.
Aren't we the ones who need help?
Yeah, I'm well aware of that.
But I think you're the one that can do it.
Please!
They're waiting for you!
Guard Skill: Hand Sonic
You think you can do something with that door using that?
No good, huh?
Well, it wasn't made for offense.
It's intended for self-defense.
Self-defense?  Not for offense?
I've got it!  Do you remember when we first met?
You stabbed me right in the heart, remember?
That was because you made such a strange request.
Right.  But because of that, I thought you were my enemy.
I don't have any memories.
So the truth is, I don't have any real reason to fight you.
Maybe if I had memories...
Maybe if I hadn't asked that dumb question in the beginning...
I might have been your ally in this world.
There was never a person like that.
But wouldn't it be alright if there was?
There's nobody.
Even if there were, they'd just disappear.
That's right.
Being her friend would mean...
Having a fun academy life...
And disappearing from this world.
I see... I could almost laugh.
It's just so pitiful... so heartless...
What the hell kind of system does this world have anyway?
Hand Sonic: Version 2
It's a thinner form for high-speed maneuvers.
Version 3.
It's a little inelegant.
It looks cool.
But, even with this, the door's not going to open.
Are there any others?
There are.
Version 4.
I tried making it in the shape of a flower...
Does this make me look cute?
Well, it's certainly quite ominous...
Wait... that might work!
Just... try something out for me.
Hand Sonic...
Version 2.
Version 3.
Version 4.
You can do it!
Let's hurry.
What is... this?
Hinata!
Are you alright?!
You actually ran straight up to me first...
Are you coming on to me?
This isn't the time for jokes!
How did you get out of there?
I broke the door.
How many years do you think that took to make?
As the acting Student Council President, I order you...
Return to your cell quietly.
Tachibana.  Look around you.
You understand this is wrong, don't you?
Hand Sonic.
You're going to defy me?  God?
I'm God.
Is he insane?
After doing all this?
That's ridiculous.
So none of you realized that this world chooses its God?
We all have memories of being alive.
We all had terrible lives, right?
Why?
It's because of that that we have the right to become God.
It is because we know the pain of living that we have right to become God.
And I've finally reached that stage.
So you'll become God and do what?
Grant peace.
What, to us?!
You're just slaughtering people!
Only because they resisted me.
You all obtained souls with the right to become God.
But you still suffer from the memories of your past life.
A God has been decided...
Therefore, allow me to grant peace to you all.
Yuri!
What more are you planning to do?!
What... do you want?
You're going to rest in peace now.
You remember Iwasawa Masami, don't you?
In her previous life, she lost her voice, and her dream of singing.
Brought up in a horrible family environment, she met a pitiful end.
But she was able to realize her dream in this world.
That's why she disappeared.
She was able to rest in peace.
I'm gonna help you rest in peace now, too.
I'll be a wonderful dream.
You know nothing about my past!
It doesn't matter if I don't know.
All the time I've spent planning...
it wasn't just to build a cage for Tenshi.
It's hypnotism.
Now... close your eyes.
You're going to have a wonderful dream now.
Even in a world like this, you can have a wonderful dream.
No way... no way...
No...
He can't...
Ah, it's them...
No.  This isn't real.
Don't make such happy faces.
I couldn't protect you!
You were killed one by one.
One by one.
Until nobody was left.
You know what?  I'm glad you're my sister, Onee-chan!
No.  NOOO!
STOP IIIIT!
Don't replace her memories with fakes!
Our lives in the real world were the real deal!
They weren't a lie, they were our lives!
We all lived our lives in earnest!
That's how these memories were carved into us!
Memories of living as best we could!
No matter what kind of lives they were...
They were our lives!
You can't just slap a new coat of paint over them...
Even your life!  It was the real thing!
My brother died...
I was born into a family of famous ceramics artisans.
Sign: Naoi
My twin brother and I...
My brother showed his talents at a very young age.
He was presumed to be the successor to the family.
I, on the other hand, spent my days holed up playing in my room.
Neither my parents nor anyone else had any expectations for me.
A life without meaning.
"You're the one who died."
That's what I was told.
Yes.
The me still alive here is my brother.
We switched places.
And so the person who had died was me.
And thus began a meaningful life.
I was shut off from the world, ostensibly because of my injuries.
They said I was rehabilitating, and I underwent severe training.
You should be ashamed!
Hearing my father's angry voice every day.
Making trash like this...
My training was amazingly harsh.
My brother had been so far ahead of me.
But I...
I was going to keep trying to change my life into a meaningful one.
I refused to go back to those lonely days.
I won a prize at a small exhibition.
For my brother, it would have been nothing but a disappointment...
But for me, it was the very best I could do.
What's this?  Are you crying?
Of course not.
I thought so.  That would be stupid.
You'd never embarrass me like that.
Honestly, I expect better of you.
I'm so glad.
My strict father will let me continue training.
Sign: Hayato
Someday, I'll be the best ceramics master in Japan!
But, my father became bedridden.
With no chance at recovery.
He could no longer spin the pottery wheel.
He couldn't teach me about ceramics anymore...
he didn't even scold me anymore.
When I fed him...
he would just gently smile at me.
The meaning of my life...
I don't have a future with skills like this.
I can't make it on my own.
Is my life just going to be taking care of him now?
Is it?  God?!
You're the one who died.
The one who died then really was me.
The one who'd struggled so hard since then was always my brother.
The one here now is my brother.
There was never anyone but my father and brother.
My whole life was just a lie.
I was never anywhere to begin with.
Even your life... it had to have been real!
You're the one that worked so hard!
The one that struggled so furiously was you!
Am I wrong?
You don't know anything about it.
I understand.
Because you're here right now.
Well then, will you accept me?
A person like me?
Who besides you could I accept?
The one I'm holding is you.
Nobody but you.
You're the only you!
They're just astringent persimmons, boys.
Yay!  I beat Nii-san!
What are you so excited over some unripe persimmons for?
Still... well done, Ayato.
Those were the words I wanted to hear the most.
He... recognized me.
Sign: Ayato
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつもひとりで歩いてた
I've always walked alone
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返るとみんなは遠く
When I turned around, everyone was far away
soredemo atashi wa aruita
それでもあたしは歩いた
Even so, I walked on
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That's what it was to be strong
mou nanimo kowaku nai
もう何も恐くない
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
sou tsubuyaite miseru
そう呟いてみせる
That's what I try to tell myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Eventually, everyone will be alone
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They'll continue to live only through their memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru youni
孤独さえ愛し笑ってられるように
So I can love and laugh even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakau n da
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenai n da
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will never show you my tears
UTW Staff
Translator:
Ershin
Timer/Editor:
Nikon
TS/Karaoke:
ar
TLC/QC:
Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c 146] Monster Stream.
[c 147] It's finally here!
[c 293] How big is this thing?!
[c 148] A carnival of despair.
[c 145] Should we go with Tornado?
[c 253] God never falls. Uwaah~
[c 245] Heave-ho!
[c 190] Another idiot, huh?
[c 215] Overdrive is passive.
[c 232] Don't underestimate my craftsmanship!
[c 30] He should be able to get back your lost memories.
[c 37] Please don't lose sight of yourself.
[c 54] Thank you, Onii-chan.
[c 133] That can't be it.  I can't even die!