Welcome, Selector.
Give me a name.
Selector? Name?
Yes, a name for me.
Mel.
For memories everything is given life
for memory subete ga umare
Everything is erased, everything is overcome
subete wo keshite subete wo koete
The memories that make me whole scream throughout my head
watashi wo kumitateru kioku sakendeiru wa atama no naka
find my real
Where did it all begin to change?
doko kara kawatta no
The things I believed in have all become lost
shinjiteta mono maigo ni natta
Even if the seasons turn
kisetsu wa sugitemo
The place from my memories remains forever unchanging
omoide no basho wa ano koro no mama na no ni
Tell me of enigmas and fear
nazo fuan oshiete
Should I continue on?
susunde mo ii no
I'm searching for my past and future
kako mo mirai mo sagashiteru
Die memory, if only I could see you
die memory aetara ii ne
Smiling like you did back then for our promise
ano hi no egao ano yakusoku
In these endlessly repeating days
kurisaesu nichijou no naka
Distorted by the ever-present static
noizu ni makare yugandeku
I still don't know, I still want to, I still can't lose it
mada wakaranai mada motometai mada nakusenai
Flip open the card of your broken heart
oreta mune no kaado wo hiraki
Lost in the storage of my memories
samayou no kioku no naka
find my real
Girl
Ideal and Reality
How many Selectors are there?
I wonder.
Where can I find them?
I'm not sure.
Hey, I hope you weren't lying about being able to sense other Selectors.
Of course I can, as long as they're close by.
Tell me immediately when it happens.
You sure are taking this head on.
It's just a game. I want to get it done and over with.
I'm home.
Welcome back. You've been pretty late these days.
Yeah, the restaurant's been busy.
What about dinner?
I already ate.
Oh, but Mom. Could you set aside a midnight snack?
Tomorrow is the aptitude exam.
Sure thing.
Hey.
Aren't you going to do more Wixoss research tonight, Chii-chan?
Don't call me that.
Didn't you use to love that name?
Monthly Aptitude Exam
Math
English
Chinatsu, how'd you do?
All right, I guess.
I'm not totally sure about the second question on the math part.
You can't fool me. I know you're
aiming to get into the top ten.
Where else would I aim?
Lucky you, you're definitely going to get the special recommendation.
Man, I'm in the mood for something sweet.
Oh, me too!
Sorry, I've got work today.
See you tomorrow.
Welcome!
Thank you very much!
You want me to add another day?
One of the new girls quit on us.
Didn't you say you wanted as many shifts as possible?
I guess five days a week is too much.
You have to worry about schoolwork, too.
I'll take it.
Wow, wow!
You're so lucky, Chii-chan.
You're good at studying and the horizontal bar and everything else.
You can learn it fast too, Suzu.
Let's practice together.
O-Okay!
Suzu, all in!
I know you can do it. Let's give it one more shot!
Okay.
Gather up all your energy, and jump!
See! You did it!
Yeah, I did it!
You know what? I'm gonna be just like you one day, Chii-chan.
What? You're fine just the way you are, Suzu.
No way, I'm gonna do it.
All in.
Wait up, Chinatsu.
Let's walk together for a bit.
Dad, aren't you earlier than usual?
Yeah, there's some work that needs to be done.
If this goes well, it seems like I'll get a promotion.
Really?
If I get a raise, then I'll be able to help with your tuition, okay?
Yeah.
Dad's company?!
Having to move... isn't there anything you can do?
Sorry... I'm sorry...
Just think about how hard Chinatsu's worked
to get into a private preparatory school.
I want to be just like Chii-chan.
I'm not going to give up.
Well then, take care.
Yeah, you too.
Chii-chan.
Don't call me that.
There's a Selector straight ahead.
You're a Selector, right?
Will you battle me?
If that's what you want.
Mel...
Don't worry.
She's just lost consciousness.
You are chaining yourself down.
That's why you lost.
Why didn't you use a coin?
I taught you how yesterday.
I don't want to. I refuse to manipulate other people's minds.
You think it's unfair?
Or that Suzu would hate you?
She does look up to you.
I just want to win proudly by my own strength.
But you lost. If you lose two more times, you'll disappear.
Then I just need to get them back.
Enercharge, Lancer...
Code Order Steak Combination        Code Eat Texas
Deck List
Oh, so you can make decks like this too.
Code Order Steak Combination        Code Eat Texas
Deck List
Aren't you scared of the game?
Not really. It's just a game.
I want to get it done and over with.
Magazines
There's a Selector nearby.
Is that you, Chinatsu?
We were at cram school.
What about you?
I thought you worked somewhere totally different.
Yeah, well...
Wixoss?
Sorry, I'm in a rush.
Too bad, they're gone.
Sure-fire win decks, how to pick the best SIGNI...
I don't really get all this complex stuff.
Suzuko.
Magazines
Business
D-Don't talk to me in public.
People will think I'm weird.
Only Selectors can hear my voice.
More importantly, you have a visitor.
A visitor?
Opinion
Discovered. Homura Suzuko-san of class 2-C.
Huh? Why do you know my name?
Enemy research, of course.
Magazines
Enemy?
Apology. I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Mikage Hanna, class 1-A.
Mikage Hanna-san?
Gratitude! You read my debut article?
Doctor Hanna's Game Review!!
"Doctor Hanna's Game Review"...
Um, I'm not going to battle you even if you follow me.
Doubt. Did you not win a battle and increase your coin count from one to two?
Right, Nanashi-chan?
Precisely, Hanna-sama.
She has two coins sparkling like the sun!
Nanashi-chan?
Conclusion. You shouldn't have any further reason to refuse a battle with me.
How about if I lose, I'll go back to having only one left?!
If you're even writing articles for a magazine,
it's obvious that you're strong.
Naturally. My victory is likely.
I really don't want to battle.
Unfathomable.
Understood. I'll invite you again some other time.
Wait! Aren't you scared, Hanna-san?
Deny. I have two reasons to battle.
The first is pure curiosity as a game writer
regarding the Selector battles.
The second is the reward for winning these battles.
There is a memory I wish to alter.
What?
Goodbye. I'll take my leave for now.
Ril, is there more to winning than just getting to quit being a Selector?
As a reward, you will be able to change one of your memories in any way you'd like.
A memory?
You can erase, rewrite, or revive a memory.
You can even implant a false memory.
If that is what you wish, Suzuko.
What I...
Private Academy
Morikawa Chinatsu
Morikawa.
Have a moment?
Morikawa, weren't you trying to earn a special recommendation?
Yes, because it'll waive my tuition fees.
That rank is raising a few red flags.
You're still working part time, right?
How many days a week?
Five days.
No way, seriously?
It's the truth!
Five, huh.
And I guess you can't cut back your hours to have more study time.
If I get a raise, then I'll be able to help with your tuition, okay?
I'll... discuss it with my parents.
Oh, also, there's something I need to confirm.
There's a rumor you've been wandering around the city late at night.
Is this true?
It's a lie! Who told you—
Well, I'm sure it's just a mistake,
but do keep your recommendation in mind.
Excuse me.
You're a Selector, right?
When do you get off work?
Do you want to have a battle after you're finished?
How many battles have you had?
This is my third! I'm at one win one loss so far.
And you?
Is there a reason to tell you?
Oh, right, yeah. Guess that'd give me an advantage.
Kagari, you're keeping her waiting.
Oh, sorry. Now then.
Open!
Mel, attack.
Okay.
Yukime, you all right?
Yes. She appears to be the type to favor overpowering her opponent.
Turn End.
My ability should prove effective
against an enemy like her.
Got it.
Coin Bet!
Predict.
She used a coin?
What's her ability?
I wonder. It's your turn, Chii-chan.
I can't attack carelessly.
Draw!
I saw them!
A Servant and Hambur.
Hambur has the Accessory reinforcing ability.
Isn't that dangerous?
Don't worry. We can counter it with the cards we have in hand.
So that's her ability.
I play two Ketch on the field. Attack!
Kagari, this is your chance.
You got it. I use Triplet Flame Stomp to banish them all!
Won't you use a coin?
Mel, attack!
Yay, my second win!
Hey, don't get so depressed.
I'm sure you'll win next time.
Anyway, see ya later!
You only have one coin remaining now.
Mel, you said that I would disappear
if I lost all my coins, right?
Yeah.
What did you mean by disappear?
What will?
It couldn't be... me... that disappears...
Isn't this a game?
That's why I wanted to get it over with...
That's why—
You just have to win.
You can win, Chii-chan.
Suzu wants to be like you, Chii-chan.
Stop...
Chii-chan is always—
I told you to stop!
You aren't Suzu.
Suzu is...
A Selector is approaching from behind.
They're walking this way.
It seems they noticed us.
Morikawa?
Huh, so that's her.
Guess she became a Selector.
Chinatsu, good morning.
That's too bad about the aptitude exam.
I've never seen you score outside the top twenty.
Oh, wanna hold a pity party?
Hey, good idea. Do you have work today, Chinatsu?
What are you doing? Stop right now, Morikawa!
Why would you do such a thing?
Do you understand that any trouble you cause could affect your recommendation?
I won't apologize.
Morikawa...
I will not apologize.
What, but why?
Well, you know...
Morikawa-san, you caused a stir at school, didn't you?
That's...
We can't really condone that sort of behavior or risk it happening here.
It is true that you've been very serious and a huge boon to us here,
but I'm afraid today is your last day.
They never intended to keep me.
Once the project launched, they had no more use for me.
Then this company apartment...
Yes, we only have it until the month is over.
All in... all in...
All in! I know you can do it.
Let's give it one more shot.
You know what? I'm gonna be just like you one day, Chii-chan.
Chii-chan
What? You're fine just the way you are, Suzu.
Suzu
No way, I wanna be like Chii-chan.
Chii-chan
All in?
Go all in for what?
Because you want to be like me...
Who does?
Suzu?
Hello!
You're a Selector, right?
Please battle me! Thank you in advance!
Chii-chan.
Fine.
Yay, awesome!
Come on!
Open!
Onee-san, you only have one coin!
How sad. Maybe I should lose on purpose...
Just kidding!
Rio's gonna win!
Stop that, Rio-chan.
Lying makes you a bad girl.
I'm sorry, Onee-san.
That's my good girl.
Mel, Grow!
I play two SIGNI and end my turn.
It's Rio's turn now. Okay, Mama! Grow!
Sure thing.
I'll put down these two and finish my turn.
Rio-chan, what about attacking?
I totally forgot, oh no!
She's an interesting girl. Now then, it's our turn.
R-Right.
Mel, Grow.
Attack with all SIGNI.
Something scary's coming!
Turn End.
It's our turn again, Rio-chan.
Alrighty then, I'll use a coin.
Bet!
Okey-dokey, Cheating!
Then I'll put down these two cards and finish!
What happened?
It seems like she used an ability.
I'm not sure.
Let's attack for now.
Bingo! Did I surprise you?
Operation success!
An ability to plant a bomb.
That can happen?
Your acting was very skillful, Rio-chan.
Really? Next I'll try an attack!
Mama, Grow.
Attack with Ferma and Descart!
Attack.
Mel!
Hey, Chii-chan.
Won't you use a coin?
If you don't, we'll lose.
Lose... me?
Dad's company?!
No...
No... no...
No, no!
No! No! No!
I...
will not lose.
Coin Bet!
I can feel your memories and emotions.
Berserk.
Mama... Mama!
Mama! Mama!
Chii-chan, that was incredible!
You were so cool when you were battling, Chii-chan.
It's like you were bursting with life.
Your strength and feelings flowed through me, Chii-chan.
Bursting with life?
I want to be just like you, Chii-chan.
I want to be just like Chii-chan.
I... had forgotten about Suzu.
Chii-chan?
I was a model student,
a hard worker, and always righteous.
But... for whose sake was I even working so hard?
Is Suzu...
really necessary?
Flashback to a faint memory just outside my consciousness
flashback bouyaketa mama no kasuka na kioku
It's always kept me going until this very day
zutto tsunaidekureta kyou kono hi made
You pull back your tiny hand
chiisana te wo hiku no da
And I can no longer remember
dareka omoidasenai
Before I lose the something resounding in my heart, I will fight
mune ni hibiku nanika wo ushinau sono mae ni tatakau
I don't want to erase everything that makes me whole
keshitakunai watashi wo tsukuriageta mono
So I will reclaim it in my heart
ima kokoro ni torimodoshite
I'm undeletable and nobody else
keseyashinai hoka no dare ni mo
Can change who I truly am
hontou no jibun wa kawaranai kara
And finally I can remember
ima nara omoidaseru
Doubt. Are you scared of losing?
I'm planning to run away until the time limit is up.
What does it mean to disappear?
Do you really understand?
There's no time!
That's what it means to disappear?
We'll be fine as long as we're together.
Next time: Selector / Honey and Poison.
Selector
Honey and Poison