Don't drink so much just because you couldn't get any customers.
I'm always the one who has to come and get you.
I do appreciate... that I have a good little sister.
Geez...
Huh?
Judy?!
Judy!
Why? Why?!
Promise
Is this where Judy Devens died?
Who are you?
They all called you Phantom.
I know who that is. Judy told me he goes around the country killing gangsters.
You're a real assassin then?
You're an assassin?
Phantom, the assassin.
Yeah... you are right.
Cal...
Please kill them all. You can have this money.
The guy who came to that alley last night...
The guy who fired a gun there...
The guy who was supposed to receive this money...
Please kill every single one who was involved in Judy's death.
Would you do it?
Judy... I was able to get acquainted with Phantom.
I'm sure that Reiji will avenge your death...
for that five million dollars.
Cal...
Ah...
I'll tell you straight. Five million isn't enough.
I see...
But the shortfall is small enough... that you can earn it.
What do I have to do?
Be my assistant for a while.
What?
This is amazing!
Hey...
Becoming your assistant means...
that I can be by your side when you avenge Judy, right?
Before that, there's something we have to pick up.
Have you decided?
H-Hold on a sec.
Why don't you pick the one you want the most?
But I want all the clothes here equally.
If I pick one, that means I have to give up everything else, right?
Don't worry. This isn't the only opportunity for you to shop in your life.
If there's something you want, I'll bring you here again.
Really?
Yeah. So today, you can pick the one you wanna wear now.
Okay!
Let's see...
Hey, hey, do I look cute? Do I look good in this?
Yeah. You look really good in it.
I've never worn such light, smooth clothes before.
Hm?
Wait a bit, okay? I'll prepare food when I'm done here.
Why are you cleaning?
Because it's really dirty in here.
Well, I guess you can't help it.
An assassin who cleans his room...
wouldn't seem like much of an assassin, huh?
You can leave this kind of stuff to me, your assistant.
Yeah, thanks.
I have to be useful to you in order to earn what that five million doesn't cover.
Say, Reiji... Do you have a family?
Family?
They're in heaven.
They are...
Yeah.
Then you're like me.
Are your parents already...
I don't know. I ran away from the worst damn excuse of a father.
And Judy took me in.
If it wasn't for her, I'd have been dead by now.
That's why you two are sisters, huh?
Right. She's the only family I got.
But Judy is dead now and...
Sorry.
That's okay.
Now that Judy's dead, what should I do?
Where should I go? What should I do?
I don't know what to do.
I didn't know... what to do, either.
What?
People die in different ways.
Cal...
Cal, give me your hand.
Hm? What?
Your compensation for today.
This is...
Thank you, Reiji!
I'll take good care of it.
I'll take good care of it... always.
The main actors have all gathered now.
Claudia, who cunningly used me and is once again devising a plot.
Daisuke Godo, who plans to encroach upon Inferno with her help.
Wisemel, who noticed that plot and is now trying to stop it by force.
And in addition, a new actor...
I shall make this play the best one.
Now...
we will be busy from here on...
Ein.
Could it be that he's Judy's killer?
He probably is.
At least he's one of those who were responsible.
Please let me be by your side.
There he is! There's someone behind the water tower!
Show...
Reiji?!
your face!
You bastards!
No, Mr. Godo!
Huh?
That surprised me...
W... wanted to...
Reiji!
Were you shot?! Did it hit you?!
No, it's just a scratch.
Stupid Reiji!
Why did you do such a reckless thing?!
I wanted to see his face at any cost.
You dummy.
You did a good job, observer.
He was Judy's killer.
You avenged her.
Yeah.
Mission completed.
Good. Leave immediately via route C and await your next instructions.
Yes... Master.
Hey, I heard a rumor... that Isaac of the Bloodies died. Is that true?
Yeah.
Then it's over... the revenge...
I see.
Ah... Uhm... How was my training to become an assassin?
If you like, shall I continue to help you with your assassinations?
Forget about being a killer.
What?
Forget about it.
Then... Then I'm no longer needed...
Am I?
But...
I'd hate to give up that cooking of yours.
What?
You can be my maid and do the cooking for a while.
Really?! All right! I'm gonna be a maid!
I wanted to try being a maid once. The uniform is really cute, you know.
Hm?
Reiji...
What is it?
I...
I still want to become your assistant.
Cal, that's...
I know... that you don't want me to become an assassin.
You know the pain that comes with being an assassin, so...
Cal, you can take any path. You can become anything.
Of all things, why do you want to become an assassin?
You don't like assassins?
No, I don't.
Then you don't like yourself?
Right, I don't. I ended up becoming a killer and can't escape.
I hate myself.
But Reiji...
I'm already broken. Do you want to be like me?!
I... I'm sorry, Reiji... I...
Cal... I was too harsh.
I'm sorry!
But it's true. I don't know how many people have died because of me.
They would've been able to live on if it wasn't for me.
They would've been able to go back to their loved ones.
It wasn't your fault.
You're just doing the job that someone has to do.
That's just an excuse.
Then did you want to kill people?
Did you shoot those people because you wanted to kill them?
Do you like killing?
That's not true, right?
But Cal...
once you kill, everything in the world changes.
The scenery you see, the sounds you hear...
Everything changes.
You won't be able to accept people with a kind heart like you're able to right now.
I don't want you to become like that.
This isn't a good place for you to stay.
You shouldn't come into the same world I'm in.
But...
But that's where you're always gonna be, right?
If I go there, I'll be able to be with you forever.
Cal...
I don't want to be separated from you. I want to be with you forever.
I want to be of help to you.
I want to...
be with you.
That's right... I...
I wanted to go back.
I thought I could be with you if I did...
That's okay. I'll go there.
I'll come to your side.
No, I'll go. Let me go back... to the world you live in.
Reiji... You said you'd be by my side.
You promised... You promise, okay?
I can't believe you have to work this late...
I may not come home until late. So go ahead and go to bed.
No, I'll stay up.
I found a broken VCR this afternoon.
I wanna see if I can fix it, so...
You can buy a new one.
That'll be a waste. It might still work.
It might still work... huh?
I guess you're right.
Come home soon.
Yeah.
Promise?
Yeah, I promise.
It's a promise, okay?
In this case, the Peace Party will have to stop their support to the Middle East.
Yes! It works!
Hmm....
Then, from the viewpoint of international support, it'll provoke antipathy from...
I wonder if the video rental store is still open...
Huh?
Reiji! Reiji!
You can't go in! It's dangerous!
But Reiji is...! Reiji is...!
Reiji!
Reiji...
You'll be back, right? You promised, right?
Liar.
You said we'd never be separated.
You said you'd stay with me.
That's right. He's a liar.
He's been deceiving you all this time.
Who... are you?
Next episode
Old Home
It's okay to cry at a time like this.
You can go back to being your old self now.