Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Hey, Konata.
Can I use your computer?
There's a document I wanted to type up for the committee next week.
Sure.
Let's see...
I've been having difficulties lately,
I've been a head nurse recently,
but I should have it finished in time,
I've been having difficulties lately, but it's a maniac transfer,
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
therefore, I intend to speed things up,
so I intend to cross dress more,
so I intend to speed things up,
by giving it my all...
...while keeping the committee-mood in mind,
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood in mind,
and managing to work out all the details.
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood in mind, and dying to not work out the NSFW details.
committee mood in mind, and managing to work out all the details.
Hey.
Can we talk about this computer for a sec?
It's not easy using other people's computers, Kagami.
A Fine Line
I left my inbox alone for a couple days,
and now it's megas full!
You don't look like someone who would get a lot of mail.
Nee-san,
how could you say something harsh so casually.
Of course I do.
Maybe it's because I visit all of the appropriate sites.
90% of it is junk mail or spam.
I don't know what to tell you,
so let's not admit those things to an officer, okay?
But you know I always wonder,
mail of this sort,
I'm Mi*noru.
Are you free today?
Are you free tomorrow?
Are you free the day after tomorrow?
Are you free the day after the day after tomorrow?
When are you free?
Am I annoying?
You're not looking for me?
I made a deposit!
Just kidding.
Are you free tomorrow?
Acknowledge me!
Ah, I want to go to Panama.
Congratulations! You've won!
All the food you can eat!
You've won 5,000,000 bags of rice!
Congratulations! You've won!
You've won 100 old 10 yen coins!
My name is Yoshiko.
Please listen to my request.
how do they come up with such interesting subjects?
That's true.
Antenna Hair
Elf
Nun
Twintails
Tsundere
Ponytail
Maid
Yandere
Cat Ears
Pretty Girls
Music
Images
Games
Movies
Miscellaneous
Music
Images
Antenna Hair
Preparing to copy files
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Images"
2 hours remaining
90 minutes remaining
58 minutes remaining
It's going pretty fast.
It might finish a lot sooner than I thought.
41 Minutes remaining
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Images"
38 Minutes remaining
60 Minutes remaning
It happens every time.
The way it goes up and down makes it useless!
I think I'll have a cup ramen for a midnight snack.
I've just been played.
Hello.
Come in.
I heard that Konata and Yutaka caught colds.
Are you okay, Yutaka?
This hasn't happened in a while.
Yo Konata, you oka-
Oh, Nee-san.
Come in.
So you're too sick to attend class,
but not too sick to play games, eh?
Well, you know.
You should understand, Nee-san.
Hello!
Ah, it's you guys.
You all came to visit.
Thanks!
She's stuck in bed,
but this is the first time she's had so much energy!
I guess I should thank you, Minami-chan.
No.
I didn't do anything...
She had some close friends back in middle school,
but maybe you two just have good chemistry.
She's always talking about you, Minami-chan.
She must be having so much fun at school now.
You know how they say sickness comes from the mind.
It's like people forget they're sick when they're having fun.
Hello!
Oh, Minami-chan and friends.
You all came to visit.
Thanks!
She's stuck in bed,
but this is the first time she's had so much energy!
I guess I should thank you, Minami-chan.
No.
I didn't do anything...
She had some close friends back in middle school,
but maybe you two just have good chemistry.
She's always talking about you, Minami-chan.
She must be having so much fun at school now.
Minami-chan, Tamura-san, and Patty-chan...
Welcome.
Are you okay?
Get well soon, okay?
But...
I wonder why my body is so weak...
I really don't like how I make others worry about me.
Don't worry about it.
There will be people out there who will want to protect you because of that.
Well, maybe that's how it appears on the outside,
but it's usually hard on the person.
In other words,
it's like how people who actually have little sisters,
don't see the charm of little sisters.
That's it!
Here it comes!
The attacks from the normal folks!
So this is the "no idea what you're talking about" aura!
It can't be helped, Senpai!
We're outlaws!
Speaking of worry about weaknesses,
you're pretty concerned about your breast size, aren't you, Minami-chan?
Is that true?
N-No, it isn't...
They say that your breasts get bigger if you massage them, right?
Yeah, I've heard about that.
I-Is it really okay?
Minami-chan?
There's no one else I can ask besides you, Yutaka.
I-I'm going to touch it...
Okay.
Control yourself!
Control yourself, girl!
Ah, Tamura-san, so you're a member of that circle.
Yes.
I participated in the previous Summer Comiket, too.
I have a few of your books.
Ah. It's an honor.
Is that so.
I would really like to see the manga you draw, Tamura-san.
Let me read some, Onee-chan!
Oh, sure thi-
I-I don't think that's...
Now, now, Hiyorin.
Doujins are meant to be read.
Please have some mercy!
At least not the general audience!
That's bad manners, Hiyorin.
Anyone...
Anyone but them!
"That's incredible."
"Then let's go over the answers."
"Xylitol gum..."
"Yes, has the ability to reduce cavities."
"That's because,
when Xylitol is...
...absorbed by the bacteria,
the bacteria's...
...ATP is...
...depleted, and at the same time,
the bacteria in the cavity...
...is broken down."
If it's that good for your teeth,
I'll give it a try, too.
I was chewing gum to help my teeth,
but in the process, a filling came out.
So now I have to visit the dentist...
The assiduous yet slightly unfortunate Miyuki-san is moé.
There there.
And so, Miyuki-san was crying today.
Oh?
It was moé!
R-Really...
That's what Onee-chan said.
Is that why Miyuki-san was so gloomy today?
I feel bad for this Miyuki-san, but...
I'm taking that story!
Well,
I was having a hard time coming up with some new ideas.
How do you normally come up with ideas for manga?
There really isn't a single method to it,
but for the most part, they come from my personal experience.
P-Personal experience?
You read them, didn't you?
Um, well...
You read them, didn't you!
After I begged her not to show you...
S-Sorry.
Those aren't based on personal experience...
But there were a lot of good stories that I enjoyed.
Thanks...
Would you call it déjà vu?
I felt like I'd experienced some of those parts before.
I would also like to read them.
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
That was probably the one based on you two.
Sensei, good morning.
What's wrong, Izumi?
Were you up all night playing games again?
Or were you watching late-night anime?
Man, they sure air a lot more late-night anime, nowadays.
It's a great time to be alive.
Couldn't you just tell me you were studying even if it was a lie?
Really,
I was thinking about going a little crazy and buy a DVD recorder or something.
Don't even think about it.
Even if you record it, you'll never get around to watching it.
Just like how games seem to pile up, right?
Huh?
What are you talking about!?
Hey, you better cut that out!
That's not funny!
Just so you know,
I'm not going to have anything to do with this!
Ah.
Hello?
You didn't hang up just now, did you?
Well...
I had three bars, but I somehow still got disconnected.
Yeah, well...
I guess I was a little immature back there.
I'm sorry.
Well,
it's not like I hung up on you because I was angry, all right?
Machida Dentistry
I've returned to this place once again.
All right,
let's see which one fell out.
Oh, all we have to do here is just stick it back in.
It'll be over in no time.
But you have another tooth in the back that's showing signs of decay,
so we should treat that one early.
What's wrong?
I just realized right now,
but strawberries smell like shortcake!
Ah.
Don't you mean shortcake smells like strawberries?
Since it has strawberries inside.
H-Huh?
Well,
sometimes we easily confuse stuff like that every now and then.
Oji-san, Onee-chan.
Good morning!
Good morning, Yu-chan!
Morning!
"Today's Bow-Wow!"
There are so many animals!
They're doing a special on pets.
"First, we have...
...a Welsh Corgi, Ku-chan!"
Ah, it's a corgi!
So cute!
The owner's not too bad either.
She scores high for the thigh highs.
TL Note: zettai ryouiki (lit: absolute territory) refers to the area of bare skin exposed on the thighs between the skirt and stockings/socks for female characters.
And her zettai ryouiki is nicely balanced, too.
I bet she'd look good in a gothic maid outfit.
"Next we have a Siberian Husky, Silviana-chan."
Ah, it's a husky!
You don't see many of them these days.
I like them, too.
That girl has to be a tsundere!
So moé.
Every girl with twintails looks like a tsundere.
So you play games, too, Kusakabe.
I like them, but I suck at them.
Wanna play a bit?
Hiiragi, you're good.
Amazing!
What was that, it was unbelievable!
Look, look!
Isn't Hiiragi amazing?
She really is.
Is this for real?
When I see how much fun she's having,
I feel like I've already lost from the moment I was fixated on winning.
I'm not even close!
A complete classic!
You like the stinky, don't you?
Oh, Patricia-san!
Hello-desu.
You've been coming over here a lot lately, haven't you?
Patty is a very research-inclined exchange student.
Which is why I've been assisting her...
by providing her with the culture most representative of Japan.
The stuff you're teaching her...
...is only a small fraction of the Japanese culture.
Otaku are the pride of Japanese culture!
My ultimate mission for coming here,
is to absorb as much as I can, and bring it back to America with me!
The only thing I can admire there is her passion.
Say, Patricia-san,
what kind of music are you listening to?
Hm, let's see...
Orange Ran**,
Chemist**,
Suneoha**,
Porno Graffi**,
L'arc~en~Ci**,
*inn,
Night***,
and many others.
I'm listening to many different Japanese artists.
That's a surprise.
But you know...
All of those people did anime songs, right?
Man,
you're very observant, Konata.
And you only listen to their anime songs, right?
I want a maid.
A maid.
Oh, a maid?
You live by yourself instead of in a dorm or anything, right?
Right.
Cooking, laundry, manga and anime, I have a really busy schedule!
I guess it can be pretty hard if you're not used to it,
so I can understand why you would want to hire a housekeeper.
No, no.
Not a housekeeper,
but a maid.
Aren't they the same thing?
No, they are totally different!
What have you been learning in this country?
No,
I think you're impression of Japan is a bit off.
I-I can't let you have this.
It's deep fried...
He won't give up because he knows you're soft.
You're so hopeless...
I'll give you this, so come over here.
Eat slowly now, okay?
But now I feel a bit lonely...
My classmates think she's quiet and scary,
but she is really kind, cool, and stylish!
Izumi-san's cousin, Kobayakawa-san, is really fond of her.
My,
is that so?
Minami-chan?
Circular notice!
Minami-chan is cool and stylish, isn't she?
Ah, speaking of which,
Izumi-san also said,
"She looks all cool, like she has no weaknesses."
"But when you see her with Yu-chan, you can tell she's a really nice person."
That's what she said.
I'm sorry, this is a sale item.
So it's limited to only one per person.
My...
Minami-chan is cool, and has no weakness.
Also, Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san said,
"Minami-chan looks like someone who can do almost anything efficiently."
"It seems like there's nothing she can't do."
"I admire how she's so cool!"
Minami-chan is...
...also admired by...
...Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san.
Mom?
One of the items you wanted was limited to one per person.
Minami-chan can do almost anything perfectly and efficiently...
Yo!
Ho!
Welcome!
What are you watching?
A mecha anime I borrowed.
Sure looks cool.
You really like these things, don't you?
Well, I'm not really interested in mecha.
You're not interested in mecha?
Then why have you been watching?
In order to attract a more diverse audience,
recent mecha anime almost always...
...have a cute boy or girl as the main character.
Then can you really call that a mecha anime?
Okay?
Hiiragi?
You got it?
For sure, okay?
I'm counting on you tomorrow!
Yes, yes.
I'll take care of it.
Now Misa-chan,
Hiiragi-san said okay.
So maybe you shouldn't keep bothering her.
But from my past experience,
"I'll take care of it,"
is the line of someone who never really intends to.
Bah.
You're pretty sharp about the oddest things.
Kagami-sama!
Let's stop by Gamers on the way home!
I don't have anything to buy today,
and I have some business to take care of,
so I'll pass.
Why not?
Can't we stop by just for a bit?
I don't want to!
Please?
Stop playing with my hair.
Besides, don't they have bookstores near your house, too?
Once you've gone to a place like that,
don't normal bookstores just not satisfy you anymore?
Like they don't have everything you want and stuff.
That's because the stuff you want is too unique.
So,
what are you buying?
I'm getting this today.
You sure watch a lot of stuff.
No, I didn't watch the anime.
But from the moment I saw this cover,
it just felt like we had a connection somehow.
It's been on my mind for a while now.
I'll never understand you.
But you know,
I've recently been able to appreciate the value of buying albums for their cover.
I mean,
you choose light novels based on their covers, too, right?
Well, I can't really deny it...
And when it turns out to be really good, you feel like you struck a bargain.
But if it doesn't,
you bought it on a whim and don't regret it that much.
In other words,
a once-in-a-lifetime chance!
You might have thought that was a convincing argument,
but that's quite a stretch.
Let's take it easy.
Is this a once-in-a-lifetime chance as well?
That was nasty.
Cover your mouth.
Well, you can't really predict when you'll sneeze.
This is the first time I've heard someone actually "a-choo" when they sneeze.
Even when sneezing,
there's a world of difference between us...
It's no fair!
It's unfair how cute your sneeze is!
Stop messing with her.
After a round, it actually smells good now.
But I heard it's over now.
You two sure get along with each other.
Do you guys ever fight?
Sure we have!
She may look like this,
but Ayano's pretty scary when she gets mad.
Oh yeah, there are people like that, now that you mention it.
Geez.
Not you, too, Hiiragi-chan.
By the way,
you're always scary, Hiiragi.
So is that how everyone sees me?
Minami-chan runs the same time as you in the 100m dash, Onee-chan.
Is that so?
But,
I bet if we actually raced,
I'd win because of the difference in our breast size!
Just kidding!
Smo----oth
Fl----at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Flat chest...
I-I would think Minami-chan would win because of her height.
You just casually dodged that comment, didn't you?
Don't you agree, Hiiragi?
Yeah...
It's funny, isn't it, Hiiragi?
What do you think, Hiiragi?
Yeah...
Misa-chan's "don't respond to everything so indiscriminately",
and Hiiragi-chan's "don't talk to me while I'm reading",
voltages are clashing with each other!
Man,
the characters in Japanese anime and games are really full of moé.
That's right.
Huh?
Isn't this image buggy?
Oh, don't worry about it.
That's how it's supposed to look.
But it's still quite naughty...
What kind of game are you high-school students playing there?
What are you guys doing?
Yu-chan doesn't need to know!
Finally done!
It's been a while since I wrote something this long.
And now to submit...
This page cannot be displayed
No, go back!
Go back!
Warning : Page has expired
Hey, there!
I really don't wanna chew you out like pieces of trash.
Depressed.
Yes.
It doesn't matter what's happened.
The two of you,
you know,
made a pledge to build this show together from the ground up, right?
And look at this.
You destroyed it all at the end.
Disappointed.
Yes.
I've done many things to make people call me dark and gloomy,
but this is the first time I've had to mediate such a pathetic fight!
Understand?
If we don't resolve this immediately, boys and girls,
it's gonna make me look bad, too.
Right, Shiraishi?
I'm terribly sorry.
Gotouza-sama.
Hm?
What do you think, Akira?
I'm sorry, Gotoh-
What!?
I'm sorry, Gotouza-sama!
In that case,
why don't you guys clap hands together and make up.
Okay?
There's one more episode left.
How about you just get your act together again and finish off Lucky Channel?
Well?
How does that sound?
We understan-
Louder!
We understand!
Good.
That's that.
I'll leave the rest to you guys.
Do your best to survive in the anime industry.
Then I think I'll head home first.
I'll let the producer know.
Call me if anything else happens.
I can send over some able-bodies, if you want.
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star:
Ah, shut up already!
Hey, people!
Can't you at least do a proper job on the last one!?
Are you listening?
Hey!
Oh, just forget it.
I'll do it myself!
Next time: "TBA"
「 TBA 」
What?
They haven't decided on the title yet!?