Ami-chan, does that mean you took it?
That big...
It's still a job, after all.
By big, do you mean it's as big as this?
No, it's even...
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Oh, it's Yuusaku.
What are you talking about that's big?
Don't tell me you're talking about br-
Gosh! I'm talking about dogs.
I have to take pictures with a super-huge dog for a magazine shoot.
Oh my god, what have you mistaken it for?
Maruo, are you all right?
Somehow, you don't look too well.
All right, everyone sit down!
Now, let's begin the final homeroom session before we go home.
Class President, please give your instructions.
Kitamura-kun?
Stand. Bow. Let's eat.
What?
A gag?
Somehow, things aren't going well...
But let's cheer up, okay?
Kitamura?
Weekends are tomorrow.
After the break, it's the long-anticipated student council president election.
Oh, so it's here.
We have an event!
Kitamura-kun, cheer up and give it your best shot, okay?
You're the number one candidate for it.
Actually, you're the only one.
Yeah! Let's make it more exciting!
But it's already decided that the next president will be Kitamura.
Kitamura, good luck.
We'll also help you-
No...
I'm not going to run for it.
I'm resigning my seat as vice-president.
I'm quitting the student council.
I'm quitting... I'm quitting...
Kitamura-kun?
I'm quitting it all!
All!
All!!
All!!!
Kitamura-kun?
All!!!!
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed that and I've won
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
The Stars Are Far Away
In the end, Kitamura didn't reply.
What happened to Kitamura-kun?
He said he's quitting the student council.
Student council...
Were you bullied by that evil Student Council President?
What's that?
Let me go!
What are you thinking?!
Minorin, what's wrong?
Look at that! This is bad!
Ki-Kitamura-kun.
Sign: Interview Room
What's with his hair?
He's not even responding to us.
That's why we want to ask the people who're closest to him.
So, any ideas?
Nope.
I can't believe there are still people who express themselves like this.
No... I don't really...
Kanou-san, what about you?
I don't know, and I can't even comprehend.
Besides, he has already left the student council.
Whatever he does has nothing to do with me anymore.
Kanou-san...
Miss Koigakubo, you're wasting your time on that idiot.
Wait...
Kanou-senpai, you're getting colder and colder, aren't you?
I bet that you're reason why Yuusaku's gone bad.
Hey, Kawashima...
Perhaps you're correct.
Huh?
But if that's the case, I'll be even more disappointed in him.
Ami-chan, have you found out why Maruo is like that?
Nope, but I think the student council president knows.
You mean Kanou-senpai?
Taiga?
Get in!
I've brought the mastermind here!
T-Taka-chan, save me!
Kushieda is horrible!
What did you do?
I didn't do anything...
Last night, Kitamura called me and asked me how to dye his hair blonde...
So I told him how...
You saw what Kitamura-kun was like yesterday, didn't you?!
Didn't you question yourself why he's asking you that?
But I never thought he'd really do it...
Is Maruo really quitting the student council?
Hey, Ami-chan...
Let's try and do something for Maruo's sake...
That self-proclaimed honor student is doing this to get people's attention.
He's probably like, "Has anyone noticed that I'm deeply troubled?".
He's a junior,
and yet he dyes his hair blonde to show people that he's gone bad. How lame-
Stupid Chihuahua!
Don't tell me you're not worried about Kitamura-kun.
What use is there to worry about him?
It'll just make us look like idiots.
What?!
Both of you, cut it.
Hey, isn't that Kitamura?
Where? Where?
Calm down, Kitamura-kun!
I said I'm going home.
Kitamura-kun!
Wait!
Kitamura-kun...
People who think someone is bound to help them if they shout out loud are very lucky.
All right, everyone.
Class is about to begin.
I was thinking that we should visit Kitamura's house.
Huh?
I don't have club activities or work today, and I'm worried about him.
So what do you think, Taiga?
Never mind, I think it'll be easier to talk to him with less people.
I see.
Then Takasu-kun, wait for me at the gates.
I'll be back after going to the club activity room.
S-Sure...
Are you fine with it?
Although I'm really worried about him, I'm no help at all.
Huh?
Besides, I really want Kitamura to quit the student council...
He has to be separated from that stinking president.
Taiga?
That's how it is. Go help him, you mongrel.
Even if she says that...
Sorry for the wait.
It'd be great if Kitamura-kun is at home.
I have no idea on what's going on with him...
Yeah...
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
You're very quiet today.
Well, no, um...
I'm just wondering what's going on with Kawashima and Taiga, so...
Kawashima hasn't said anything like that to her childhood friend before, has she?
I think Amin is definitely worried about Kitamura-kun.
Look, Amin works in the world of adults.
So I think she knows a lot more than we do.
Definitely about Kitamura-kun, too.
But having things only she knows,
she must be really patient to deal with kids like us.
I wonder...
But I don't think Amin is wrong.
There aren't a lot of people in the world who can talk about their friends like that.
That's why I think Amin has her own reasons for being so direct today.
Or should I say, I wished for her to do it.
I shouldn't say this, but there are a lot of things you don't know.
For example, not being able to understand someone you want to understand.
True.
But I think Amin has considered all of it already.
Because we're still immature,
we cannot understand him.
But I think... that's why we're his final salvation.
Oh, what am I saying?
I think Kitamura-kun's house is over there.
Kushieda... How should I put it?
You're a very kind person.
Kind?
No, I'm not!
I'm actually very arrogant-
-and dishonest...
Kushieda?
In the end, Kitamura wasn't at home.
So we didn't get to see him.
I'm back!
Oh, you came over.
W-Welcome back, R-Ryuuji-kun.
What's wrong?
Did you eat something weird?
Yo.
Sorry for intruding.
K-Kitamura?
Yasuko-san let me in, so I did-
Not that!
Actually, I ran away from home...
Huh?
Aisaka, do you usually come here?
Ya-chan said I'm allowed to eat here whenever I want...
S-So I'm just going along with her good will...
I see.
It must be great to live near Takasu.
Yeah.
My, my... Tatami mats sure are great.
I don't have Tatami rooms in my house.
M-My house is fully western too!
Well, Japanese style is the best.
Yeah... We have the same interest...
Nutmeg... Nutmeg...
H-Hey, let me help you.
Help wha-
All right, I'll help you peel them. I'm good at this!
Good?
I see.
You just want to show off your good side, right?
Yeah.
Fine.
So, let's make that tasty fried egg again!
S-Sure!
Yeah, put the egg in the pan and close the lid...
Lid? What lid?
What other lids are there apart from frying pan lids?
Now add a bit of water.
Water? Add it to where?
It's on fire!
It's on fire! Add some water!
No!
Well, Kitamura, this is...
Hey, Kitamura?
Don't eat it!
Actually, I'm not that good at cooking...
It still tastes like fried egg. It's just right.
Kitamura-kun?
Aisaka.
Thank you for making it to cheer me up.
I've cheered up already.
Oh, this must be Takasu's beef patty!
Yeah, it has my specialty red wine sauce.
It's good!
As expected from you!
I'll try and make it next time...
Sure, I don't think there'll be a
problem if Takasu teaches you.
Wow, I'm full! The food was awesome!
That's great.
So, tell us what's up with your hair.
Ryuuji!
I don't want to be the student council president anymore.
No one will have any expectations if my hair is like this.
So yeah, that's it.
Even if you say that...
Y-You don't need to push yourself to be the student council president!
After all, it's what you've decided by yourself!
I think just that is enough.
Thanks.
Hey, Ryuuji, take the video games out!
Huh?
Sure! Let's play!
Tomorrow is the weekend, so let's play to our heart's extent!
Yeah, let's play!
I fell asleep...
Huh? Where's Kitamura?
Kitamura-kun?
Ryuuji, I want to eat ice cream...
What? There's none here.
I want ice cream...
You're hopeless.
I'll go to the convenient store.
Are you coming?
Huh? Where's Kitamura-kun?
Oh, he went inside to sleep in a futon by himself.
How cheap...
I'm going to look at Kitamura-kun's sleeping face...
Here, it's cold, so put this on...
Taiga?
I'm still no good...
What am I happy about?
I'm so selfish...
Kitamura-kun's pain, sadness and troubles...
I didn't realize any of it.
I'm really no good.
No good at all...
You're not-
I am!
I am no good.
I can't help Kitamura-kun...
I can't help him!
When I was in trouble, Kitamura-kun would always reach his hand out for me.
Because of that, I was able to relieve myself...
He told me "You can live...
You can live in this world..."
Kitamura-kun is...
Kitamura-kun is my...
Final salvation, right?
Taiga, look at the Big Dipper.
That's the North Star.
Orion.
Where's the Orion?
Look, those three consecutive stars.
Oh, I see it.
Those stars look like they're close to each other,
but they're actually very far away, aren't they?
We learned that in elementary school.
It's like Kitamura-kun and I.
The things you see aren't always real.
How hard must I try in order to understand the unseen truth?
How far away is...
...the distance between Kitamura-kun and I?
You want to understand him because you don't understand him, right?
You want to understand because you like him.
You reach out your hands so you'll gradually get closer to it.
Yeah.
Good morning, Takasu.
Morning...
I drank the milk in the freezer.
Sorry.
It looks like you had a lot of fun last night.
You should've woke me up.
S-Sorry...
Oh, right.
I had a feast with Taiga last night.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
Oh, it's already this late.
I'll make breakfast right now.
Taiga?
Hey, wake up! You look bad!
Never mind since she's fast asleep.
She looks so happy.
You stink of milk!
What an amazing stretch!
K-Kitamura-kun?!
Oh my god! Don't tell me you saw me sleeping!
I'm sorry, but I did.
No!
What now?! You saw my weird sleeping face...
No! No! He saw such an awful side of me...
Calm down.
We've been kicked out.
It can't be helped.
Let's go have breakfast-
All right, let's go have fun!
I was busy the whole time due to the Cultural Festival.
It has been a long time since I went out to have fun.
Oh, right! I know a good place!
100 hits of every ball speed...
Kitamura sure is a weird guy.
It the best to sweat it out as a healthy student!
No matter how you look at it, it's a sickness.
All right. Takasu, it's your turn next.
No, I'm...
Kitamura-kun, I'll go next!
Oh, Aisaka, you seem determined.
Taiga?
Just watch.
I'll hit it for sure.
All right. Aisaka, don't spread your arms.
Nice! You hit it!
I might have discovered our next star player!
Amazing! You're amazing, Aisaka!
Why is such a talented person like you not in the baseball club?
Board: Home Run
I'm back.
That was an awesome home run!
Aisaka, you have talent!
T-That's not true...
Oh, welcome back.
Ryuu-chan, can you help me hold Kitamra-kun still?
Like this?
Yes, don't let him go.
Taiga, help me!
Just then...
Your father gave me a call...
He sounded very desperate...
So I thought it'd be best for you to go home normal.
So you've teamed up on me with my parents...
In the end, guardians are just guardians!
You're going to become the student council president, aren't you?
So dying your hair blonde is a no-no.
I'm not going to become the student council president!
I'd rather die!
I wonder if Kitamura-kun made it home safely...
Beats me.
I think he's serious about it.
Is he really?
Do you remember what Minorin said during the summer at the villa?
She said she loves horror, so that's why she says she hates it.
Oh, that reverse psychology thing?
Kitamura-kun says that he doesn't want to become the student council president...
I wonder if he means the opposite...
So he actually wants to?
Don't you think so?
Even if that's the case, we can't do anything about it with him being as he is right now.
But...
So we have to get his spirit up, huh?
Is it really all right?
Yeah, I've decided on it.
Then put this on.
Yeah.
Let's go!
Student Council President Candidate
What kind joke is this?!
No way...
Seriously?
I was thinking-
Quiet down!
I'll announce it right now.
When I, Aisaka Taiga, is elected to become the student council president...
This school, your high school life and your memories of this election...
...w-w-will be all buried!
What?!
banira soruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
amai dakenara soruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni soruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla
Next Episode Preview
One Step Forward
When I am elected to become the student council president, everyone will be in a pit of terror.
It's abyss.
I'll still bu-bury...
You're still...
Come over here, you guys!
Hurry and shake hands with me.