Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Into the Darkness
Ya okay?
Yeah.
It doesn't hurt.
Found ya.
After Shiori grabbed me, her face seemed to change.
So I'm the only one who saw that?
It had to be her.
That was the girl who appeared at the end of the summer festival.
What does this mean?
Ya took damage to yer memories after fightin' with Shiori's Shadow.
It was turnin' ya into some kinda black mud.
But it couldn't completely erase me in time.
I somehow restored my body from the leftover data and made it back here.
Thanks to that, I could tell ya the truth.
It's actually raining!
I did say ya'd need an umbrella.
R-Right.
I shoulda known ya'd be able to detach yerself from even time itself.
Let's head to the old clinic now.
In this rain?
It's deep in the mountains, man!
And the sun's about to set.
So what?
Ushio went.
We ain't got time.
Y'don't hafta come if y'don't wanna.
Ushio knows the way.
Seriously, dude...
Idiot.
Of course I'm goin'.
Y'think this rain'll ever let up?
Tomorrow's the festival, so hopefully it clears up.
Are ya going, Mio?
I don't think now's really the time to be thinking about that.
Yer right. Sorry.
Oh, I mean it's 'cause I ain't got no yukata.
Hey, no sweat.
I've got one I can lend that'll look great on ya.
Thanks, Tokiko.
But I...
Can I ask for a favor, Mio?
Stay with me tomorrow!
Tokiko?
Man, this sucks!
I'm soaked to the bone!
Hoo boy.
Oh? Are you kids locals?
Oh, yes.
Hold on a sec, Mio!
And who might you be?
Oh! I'm sorry!
I'm Miura from Wakayama's northern station.
Do you know the Kobayakawas that run the Koba Mart?
Looks like ya beat me here.
Am I supposed to comment on yer outfit?
I was bein' super serious when I picked it!
What about yer clothes, huh? Ya gonna be fine?
Don't tell me ya came empty handed!
Don't worry!
I'm with him!
Whoa! Ushio's yer "equipment"?!
Do Not
Enter
What made ya wanna search the old clinic anyway?
Back in the summer of fourth grade,
I once tried sneakin' in here.
Totsumura and his friends invited me for some kinda test of courage.
What a guy. And he's a police officer?
It says "Do not enter."
Can't he read three simple words?
Yer one t'judge.
But we never made it inside.
What are you boys doing?
My Dad caught us.
It's our property, so I didn't really think much of it then.
He had a right to be there.
But it's weird, right?
What in the world was my Dad doing at this ruin?
"Where does a wise man hide a leaf? In a forest."
"But what does he do if there's no forest?"
What in the world would ya hide in a ruined building?
Ushio, any Shadows nearby?
Now that Ushio has her memory back,
she can sense the presence of other Shadows.
Well?
We should be good for now.
Oh, fer cryin' out loud.
Are y'all for real?!
What's with the swimsuit?!
We ain't goin' for no swim!
What, and yer off to play baseball?!
Now, now...
This is my battle outfit!
Best y'don't make light of it if y'know what's good fer ya!
She's scary!
She's nothin' like Mio!
Explain it to him, Shinpei.
Wearin' real clothes would get in the way of her transformations.
I could wear armor, but my real body is my flat shadow.
If that gets stabbed, I'm dead.
If I'm in a fight, this swimsuit's the best.
And I only need to copy something once to be able to transform into it as much as I like.
As long as I have enough space, I can keep adding to my repertoire.
Cool, right?
Yeah, but it's hard to keep from staring.
Hey!
Wow. Are these relics?
They seem historically valuable.
It was built back in the Meiji period, so it's been standing for over 100 years.
I heard they declared it abandoned in the 60's.
There must be somethin' here that links it to the Shadows.
The stairs are all broken.
Guess we can't check the second floor.
Could ya get up there with yer Shadow powers, Ushio?
Yer scared of ghosts, ain'tcha?
Ain't that just the cutest!
I shoulda never told ya.
How ya like that?
Holy cow!
A medicine cabinet, huh?
Whoa!
What the...
Mercuric chloride!
Mercuric what?
It used to be used to treat syphilis.
But now we know it's deadly toxic, and no one uses it!
I can't believe we had this stuff just lying around.
Old patient records and prescriptions?
Stomach flu, bronchitis, pneumonia...
Is there anything that's related to the Shadow sickness?
Sh-Shinpei...
What's up?
Look.
What the heck is that?
That's creepy.
Carved from wood, huh?
Looks pretty old.
It's carrying a fish in its left arm.
Is that a sea bream?
I think I've seen it before. What was it?
Like the thing that blesses a business.
Ebisu?
That's it.
Ebisu (Webisu)
1. One of the Seven Gods of Fortune. Typically portrayed wearing
kariginu with a fishing rod in his right hand and a sea bream in
his left.
2. God of outpatient care.
3. God of fishing. Defied sea bream.
Also a whale in ancient times.
4. Yorigami. Believed to have drifted ashore
from the ocean.
The god of fishing...
But when ya think of Ebisu, ya think of a fat old guy.
This is like feminine or somethin'.
I've never heard about a female Ebisu.
What is it?
Hiruko
The first god created from Izanagi and Izanami when Japan
was created, according to the Kojiki. However, he was a
weak child and was soon put onto a boat of reeds and
cast out to sea. This section from Kojiki describes Hiruko
as a leech-like with no arms or legs, giving birth to
the interpretation that Hiruko is heteromorphic.
Hiruko
The first god created from Izanagi and Izanami when Japan
...........from Kojiki describes Hiruko
...rms or legs, giving birth to
Hiruko is heteromorphic.
No way.
Hiruko?
Hiruko?!
What would somethin' like that be doin' here?
No idea. It's just a guess.
But if this really is Hiruko...
Besides, what does Hiruko look like?
I ain't never seen it.
It just says it's leech-like with no arms or legs.
And heteromorphic.
Why would a god like that be worshiped as a god of fortune?
Jinjou Elementary......
Japanese Language
Textbook
Ministry of Education,
Science, and Culture
A cook book?
Did a family live on the second floor?
This is an old album from the Hishigata family.
Hey, Ushio.
What's up?
Creepy!
Over here.
What was on the second floor?
It'd take more'n a day to search the whole place.
There.
Ya could probably fit through that tiny gap if ya tried.
These Shadow errands take a lot out of me.
Ya owe me takoyaki at the festival tomorrow.
I'll buy ya 10 or even 100 pieces.
Ya mean it? No take-backs, Shinpei!
Well? Find anything?
The floor, it's...
The heck is this?
It's too dark to see.
What if ya do that flash thing?
Ya don't need to actually copy anything, though.
Oh, right!
There's a key hole!
This wall might be a door.
Come back for now.
Looks like we can't smash our way through.
We gotta find the key, then.
Damn! There's definitely something suspicious there.
I'm hungry after all that work.
How can ya be so laid-back?
Here.
A rice ball? How?
It's about time fer dinner.
Not ya too, Shinpei.
Yum!
So good!
Yep, rice is still the best.
I'm stuffed!
Ya ate way too much by yerself.
Ya mentioned feminine, right?
This statue's stomach is swelled.
Like it's pregnant, maybe?
Ya got a point.
But was Hiruko ever blessed with children?
Wait.
My Shadow scan can see inside things.
Like human bones and organs, which is why I can copy them.
There's something in its stomach!
I'll see if I can copy it.
She's using her hair!
Th-That's...
A key!
A secret door!
A hole leading down, huh?
Be careful, guys.
I sense the presence of Shadows down there.
A door that can't be opened without a Shadow's help...
All this under my house?
Dad...
Ushio.
I'm not scared. Not if I'm with ya.
Let's go.
Summer Time Rendering
Don't ya dare look up!
I heard a bunch of these underground canals were dug during the war.
A locked entrance...
It's likely no one's been here in decades.
No, is it a pathway just for Shadows?
Do ya sense a Shadow?
Over there.
I feel chilly. I got a bad feeling about this.
You two, listen to me.
If we end up in a sticky situation,
Ushio, focus on protecting yourself.
And Sou, do everything in your power to protect her.
Ya saw my power, didn't ya?
I'll protect y'all!
Even if I die, I'll just end up looping again.
But what if ya die first?
Will ya still be able to come along?
If that ain't possible,
then I'll see ya on the 24th with the fireworks?
No, I can't even begin to think about an even worse situation.
What worse situation?
A situation where I never see you again!
You're worth a hundred of us in battle.
We can't risk losing you.
Ya talk too much!
Enough of yer objective stuff and just say what ya really feel!
But that was how I really feel.
That promise was one I aim to keep my entire life.
Promise?
This time, I'll protect you!
Shinpei, ya mean...
I don't get it, but I ain't gonna let ya die again.
Will you let us protect you, Ushio?
Wh-Whatever. Do what ya want!
A human-shaped dark stain.
This is really old.
Looks like someone was erased by a Shadow here long ago.
Oh, a rat.
Don't scare me like that!
It's there.
I sense a Shadow around the corner that rat just turned.
Has it noticed us?
Dunno, but I'll go scout ahead.
Remember what I said? I'll go.
Be careful.
Three shots per Shadow.
Three shots should keep it from moving.
Was it there?
Yes, just one.
Is it... eating?
Hey, Ushio, if ya can sense other Shadows,
doesn't it realize yer nearby too?
Couldn't say.
Ain't gettin' nowhere just thinkin'.
I gotta act now!
A preemptive strike!
I'll immobilize it first.
Then Ushio will deliver the finishing blow.
Sou's our backup.
No reaction.
That's proof it ain't noticed us yet.
It's in danger, yet it ain't movin' out of the light.
Good. The bigger the target the better!
Just five or six more steps!
Crap! It can still smell!
The Shadow withdrew!
I'll just... think of it as a baseball!
Hell yeah! A clean hit!
Crud!
Not yet, Ushio! We'll take care of this thing ourselves!
This is bad! It's gonna get Sou!
Calm down! Be objective! Objective!
If not now, when?!
You're shaking, aren't you?
You could shoot a million times and not land a single nail.
Relax and concentrate.
Just like you've done ever since that day.
Ever since Mom and Dad died,
if I looked at it this way,
I was able to brush anything off like it was nothing.
Look.
Ushio!
Not bad.
We... We did it.
We did it, Shinpei!
Y-Yeah...
Hell yeah!
Sorry for shooting ya too.
It ain't nothin'!
It turned out fine. I sure calmed down.
I was freakin' out when ya missed at first.
I knew all along that he'd definitely hit it.
Ya stayed up all night practicing, didn't ya?
Y-You were awake?
You should've said something then.
What's up?
It's too early to relax.
The first Shadow I sensed is still around.
I get this really bad feeling like I'm hearing nails on a chalkboard.
Do ya know the direction where it's coming from?
There.
Left at that intersection I think.
Okay.
Hey, Shinpei!
He just goes towards danger with no hesitation.
It's 'cause he's seen
what the future looks like if he does nothing.
Ya want to protect Mio too, don't ya?
Of course! With my life!
Then ya ain't got time to be cowering.
Forward, never backward!
It's the wound Shadow Mio gave me!
When my power returned, I printed a new arm from Ushio's data, but it was just a facade?
Does that mean I haven't recovered from the damage to my body?
Erase!
Hey, Shinpei. I got a question.
Can Ushio copy that nail gun?
If she could, then we'd have two, right?
We tried that, of course. A copy was made.
But it wouldn't activate.
According to Ushio, when copying machines,
it'll just produce an imitation that won't function
as long as the real thing still exists.
Original
A
Copy
(unusable)
A
Original erased
Copy
(usable)
A
Then we can't make more, huh?
Like the key from earlier, it's fine if they're only a shape.
Things that need electricity, gas, or some other kind of energy can only work once the original is erased.
So what's that nail gun?
Right. It's actually a copy.
There are a lot of benefits to a copied version.
I can run out of nails, gas, or electricity,
and Ushio will just use the original data to print me a another one good as new.
What was that?
Gunfire?
Shinpei!
Things suddenly look a lot different here.
It's a natural cave.
And this smell of salt.
Is the sea nearby?
Crap! No way!
When?!
I sense Shadows all around us!
We're surrounded!
H-How many are there?
Run, Ushio!
Run!
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Meal Time