It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Ushio! We can't get caught!
Don't worry!
I'm totally back!
And ready to kick some ass!
Return
Guil!
My armor isn't returning.
It's being erased.
The strays were annihilated too.
She can hack them the moment her hair blades touch them, huh?
It seems you've evolved again, maverick.
Thanks for stabbing me in the back last time.
But this time...
I won't lose!
Ah! Hey!
My hacking can erase the armor.
Shide is human inside.
Just gotta strip him of his armor.
And this time, I'll be able to finish him for good!
I'll bet that's what they're thinking.
Things didn't play out exactly as we expected.
They most likely transported her only memories in order to revive her.
I shoulda killed her when I had the chance!
Pouting won't do us any good.
We must be objective.
There being two Ushios now is not the worst-case scenario.
Ushio's growth is surprising.
But it might be possible to kill her now.
Her hair blades are certainly a threat, but...
I have my "echo."
In the case of a tie, I'll only lose my armor.
But my blades will find deadly purchase!
Time out.
Why? Mio?
Mio?!
What?! Why?!
What's the big idea?!
Calm down, Sis.
Just lemme hit him once!
S-Seriously? That's the plan?
Shinpei, yer a genius.
Welcome back.
Glad to see you're raring to go.
Shinpei, yer leg!
That jump ya made was hard on me.
But it's nothing. It's just one leg.
Please take care of her, Shin.
I will.
Shide!
Yes?
Where do ya think I came from?
What?
As I figured, looks like ya don't know.
That means I can conceal the hand print when I'm inside Guil.
Goodbye.
Don't let him shoot!
Impossible!
Normally, Guil takes form of this pacifier.
Throw it, and he'll get ready to attack.
Can I try it out?
Sure.
Hup!
S-Sorry!
Ya okay, Sou?!
He's dead!
No, he's not.
So what's it like inside?
It sure was strange.
I couldn't see a thing 'cause it was pitch black.
But I could hear everything outside.
It was dark because Guil doesn't have eyes.
But that improved his hearing,
so just leave the fighting to him.
If I combine that with Ryuunosuke's two-second predictions,
even I might be able to fight Shide.
During synchronization, any damage Guil takes will be felt by the pilot, so keep your guard up.
Now we gotta figure out if the hand print is hidden while inside Guil.
Yeah.
I'd like to test it, but Haine will notice if the signal is lost.
Try it too early, and we give them time to investigate.
Hm...
I'd like to see how two hours go.
Won't Guil be spotted easily?
Guil's signal is no different from any other strays.
They'll never know if we're in a place where it's normal for strays to be.
If ya wanna hide a leaf, the best place is in a forest!
But if he's spotted?
Then we move to plan B!
No, C?
Once I'm out, it's time to fight.
I'll play it by ear and be ready for any possibility.
I like this plan.
I swear I'll bring her home.
Here they come.
Shinpei, yer back?
Is it really ya, Shinpei?!
What happened? Where's Ushio?
Shinpei?
I thought Shinpei's confidence came from concealing the hand print among the strays to look for Ushio.
And with the two of 'em, he'd be ready to try and enter Hiruko Cave.
But I was wrong.
Did he loop, Haine?
What in the world did ya see?
What makes him so confident is...
Ushio!
Hey, guys. I'm back!
Glad to see ya again!
Where do ya think I came from?
Hiruko Cave...
That brat set his restart point to Hiruko Cave!
So that's why he's been lurking and hiding with the strays.
And he used the loop to point Ushio at my throat!
Look alive, people.
We're gonna destroy Hiruko's main body!
July 24th
(10th loop)
Summer Time Rendering
Karikiri!
It's almost time for the procession. Please head over.
Ah! Hold on!
Ow, ow, ow!
Kogaito, my stomach's killin' me!
Are ya okay?
I can't do it! Diarrhea's coming!
Gotta lock myself in the bathroom!
Oh dear.
Would ya like some medicine?
You handle it.
What a pickle this is.
We're in its flat shadow, yet everything's so normal.
So weird.
Y'think they've caught on to our plan?
Yeah, but that's what we want.
Now they'll definitely make us their priority.
Until they kill us, they won't start mass murdering people on the surface.
Guil sensed a Shadow.
At 2 o'clock. Twenty meters ahead.
So they have noticed us.
Something shot at us!
Needle-like objects...
Teeth?
It's trying to paralyze us in place!
Toki! I'll fight it!
It's fine.
I'll stop it here.
Now.
Go on ahead, everyone.
I'll be fine by myself.
What? I'm not leaving ya here!
Get goin', ya dumbass!
This ain't no time to be dilly-dallying!
Okay.
Thanks.
No. I ought to be thanking ya.
Thank ya very much, Shinpei.
For forgiving me.
Tokiko!
Don't ya dare die.
Same to ya, Sou.
Don't slow everyone down.
Help... Help...
It was awakened to serve Haine, and then forced to fight...
Let's go, Guil.
Let's help it rest in peace.
A dead end?
Naw, Hiruko's nest has to be up ahead.
Yeah, they've made a wall.
It ain't just some black wall, either.
I can't sense anything beyond it.
It's made of mud!
He's coming from the sea and the shrine.
They're moving super fast!
Move!
Blood?!
It regenerated.
Let me try.
Don't touch it!
Ushio, yer hand!
That was close...
My hack got reversed.
This wall is part of Hiruko's body!
Damn it! We've come so far!
Hiruko's just on the other side!
We'll blow it up with a bomb.
A what?!
Where ya gonna get one of those from?
Right here.
Mio!
Before we came here, I had Mio steal something for me.
Y—
Ya mean...
The aerial fireworks!
What is Shinpei's position?
The barrier.
They just made contact.
He's in the perfect position, then.
If the restart point was too far from the sanctuary,
we wouldn't be able to mount a surprise attack.
But if it was too close, he'd find your main body.
We should hurry.
I've lived a long time and I have my own unshakable faith.
Not once in all these years has someone been able to break through the barrier entirely.
That do it?
Let's go.
I smell gunpowder and something like steak.
Stop. Don't remind me of steak!
I also smell raspberries and rum.
Ain't nothin' that high class down here!
Get down! Nezu!
Now, please wait for just a moment.
Don't mind me. Just go before the hole completely closes!
Are ya suicidal, old man?!
When ya ain't sure what to do,
ask yerself what yer future self would do.
That's yer answer.
That way, you'll have no regrets.
I'm counting on ya.
Sure.
Take care of Ryuunosuke for me.
Y'know what ya are? Sad. That's what.
Masahito, or is it actually Iwao in there?
Does it really matter which, Ginny boy?
We used to be friends, remember?
Move. I don't wanna hear yer screams.
I dare ya.
If ya wanna get past here,
yer gonna have to kill me first!
Shinpei?
Feels like my head's gonna split!
Hiruko's presence...
Oh, right. Ya can sense a Shadow's presence now.
Mother's continuously emitting her Shadow-controlling signal.
Before Sis reprogrammed me,
Mother's voice used to sound nice to me.
But then it started sounding really creepy afterwards.
I'm a Shadow, so I can just erase my sense of creepiness,
but Shin is human, so he's helpless.
No way!
We should finish this quick.
U-Ushio, ya okay?
I'm fine.
Just focus on my presence.
The ringing in my ears is fading.
Mother's signal was just canceled out.
I feel better.
See?
Thank ya.
She canceled it out by broadcasting at the same wavelength.
How in tarnation?
Ushio.
Yeah, let's finish this.
We used up all the fireworks.
It's fine.
We got my fists.
And these guns ain't runnin' outta ammo.
I'll smash this wall to pieces!
Sounds like a plan.
But there's one thing we gotta do first.
Ryuunosuke can see two seconds into the future.
So follow my eyes.
Shide!
Today's the day we settle this for good!
She spun her hair at super high speed to form a barrier!
Too shallow!
He's seeing through all of her moves!
Haine!
Decided to join us from the surface, huh?
As I thought, he's off by two seconds.
When Shinpei closes his left eye,
I can sense Ryuunosuke inside him.
So this is how he previously avoided Shide's attack.
If he wished it, he could also enhance his body like Hizuru did.
Shinpei himself obtained the strength to fight against us!
That's what gave him such confidence!
Ya hound me even from the grave, Hizuru!
As long as Haine's watching us, I can't use Ryuunosuke's two-second predictions to deliver a final blow.
Even if I read his moves and she picks up on that,
Haine observes the change and Shide dodges!
But that's fine!
They learned last time just how scary Ushio's blades can be.
One hit would be a lethal blow for Shide.
Which is why Shide and Haine are forced to concentrate on our movements.
I just gotta pretend I don't notice, and lure Haine...
into the kill zone!
You're too eager to be an assassin, Mio.
At this range, I can sense the position of every Shadow in the area.
For instance, there's a Shadow copy of a nail gun behind that boulder.
Which means someone's hiding back there.
Sou!
What?!
This is the real kill zone!
Nice!
I can't move...
Sou... But how?!
I didn't sense him...
No, that's obvious!
He's just a normal human!
So his nail gun is Nezu's original?
The one I sensed was a copy printed by Ushio.
It was a trap!
No! Analyzing this now is pointless!
It hurts... It hurts!
Be objective. Where did I make a mistake?
No, no!
What's important is—
What's important is two seconds from now.
Their actions two seconds from now...
I have to tell Shide!
I told ya that ya can't keep taking us lightly forever.
Damn puny humans...
What fun this is!
I can sense it.
Haine's pain.
Her unfulfilled desires, her sadness, her loneliness.
Ya wanna go home, don't ya?
If ya do, the flow of time will stop.
Ya won't have to face destruction.
An unending world together with yer family.
Together with yer loved ones for all eternity.
I know ya just wanna live like that forever.
But I'm sorry.
We can't come to an understanding.
Stop!
Yer hands weren't made to hurt others.
They're for holding others' hands,
for stroking their head, and for holding them tight.
We...
It's disappearing.
The mud...
The armor Haine gave me...
Haine's been defeated.
Haine!
If Mother dies, all Shadows will vanish.
Bye-bye, Shin.
Ushio!
I don't get it, Shinpei.
I beat the bad guy.
Everything's finished now.
And yet, I can't stop crying.
Ushio, that eye.
Shinpei!
Hold it.
Me and Sis, we ain't disappearing.
Mother is still alive.
But how?!
Ya held back, didn't ya, Sis?
My right eye is burning up!
Shinpei!
There's a presence emanating from our right eyes.
But what is it?
Just marvelous.
Shide!
N-No way!
How is he still moving?
Both of Shide's inner bodies were definitely killed!
Are ya immortal?!
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time
Tokoyo