My favorite food is... I guess, strawberries.
I see! You have cute tastes, Ms. Iona...
Look... Akira's popularity dropped again.
She's seriously not good now...
She even ditches work too.
Well, her style really doesn't match us anyways.
Like, she feels cheap.
So what should we do about the
front page model for the next mag?
You want to drop Akira and go with Yuko?
Well, that's nice... It would be great
if they took that talk somewhere else.
I like having them with sugar and milk.
Not with condensed milk.
Huh...? Oh, right, strawberries.
I use the back of my fork...
...to smash them to bits.
If I win... I'll make you apologize to Hitoe!
Open!
The truth rests solely on
the front/back of a card
It has not yet been solved
Upon the dazzling, dizzying stage,
destroy those entangled emotions
as many times as it takes to satisfy you
What should the tomorrows
wandering after fate's beckoning
choose and discard so that
they can become one?
I can't afford to disclose my reproachable hand
The days spent draining
the already-dry sea of regret
desire within limited words forgiveness
for the unplanned smile
I don't mind forgetting reality
I don't want to know anything now
Okay?
I'm home...
Hitoe! What happened? You're all wet!
Where are your friends?
Weren't you with them?
You better wipe yourself off,
or else you'll catch a cold...
Hitoe?
Hey, I'm first! Aki-lucky!
Piruluk-tan, show your stuff!
Don't go easy on her just
because she's a scrub, you hear?
Say, Ru?
What?
Tama can battle?
Yes.
Draw. I'll drop a card in the
Ener Zone. Piruluk-tan, Grow!
Oh, and I'll summon Sky Cat-chan too!
Tama, Grow! I summon Kukri and Ponya!
Don't get too excited, squirt!
What... is this feeling?
Battling Akira is going to be painful...
It is painful...
...but!
The hell?! I thought she
was a WIXOSS newbie?!
She is...
It seems as if this is her first serious battle...
What...?!
Gifted...
She is quite gifted.
What? You trying to tell me
something? That I'm not?!
Damn you, Piruluk! You're pissing me off!
Just shut your mouth and follow my commands!
I'm just gonna get this over quick...
Arts!
Peeping Analyze.
Ru-ru?
Looks like you're following
textbook examples there.
So, that means... you must have a lot of...
...level 4s!
Missed.
Damn it...! Who cares if I missed?!
I want to know what her wish is, Piruluk!
Wish.
Ru-ru? I wonder if you'll be all
ouchy-ouchy if I see your wish...
Come on, Piruluk-tan!
Go ahead and show me her pains!
I see nothing...
What?
Hey, stop acting like
some broken piece of trash.
She has...
...no wish.
That's right... I... have no wish...
Wh-What?! A-Are you serious?! You're
battling as a Selector without any wishes?!
No way! You've got to be kidding?!
That makes no sense!
All the Selectors are, like,
super serious and stuff, you know?
You've been battling for
the fun of it?! You're so horrible!
A person without a wish participating
in WIXOSS as a Selector...
...is blasphemy.
I don't care what you say.
What...?
I don't have any wishes,
so I'm not scared of anything!
Arc Aura!
Tama!
What the hell is wrong with you...?
You don't have any wishes... right?
Then...
...why the hell are you trying to stop mine?!
I-I just wanted you to...
apologize to Hitoe, and...
Stop frekkin' lying!
Beating me until I groveled...
You were enjoying it!
Wait!
"With Ruko and Yuzuki..."
"...playing WIXOSS at the library."
"On our way back,
we bought stuffed dumplings..."
"Ru... ko..."
"Yuzu..."
Hitoe?!
What's the matter Hitoe?!
Words... disappearing...!
What?!
Disappearing! All the words in my notebook...
...are disappearing!
Disappearing!
Hitoe...
Is Akira late again?
Iona? Do you know where Akira is?
No...
Screw it... That brat...
It's set. Akira's off for next month.
Better yet, why won't we
just drop her for a while?
Sounds good.
Iona...
I sense battle... And a losing one at that.
Do you remember that
poor girl that battled Iona?
Looks like that was her
second battle, and her second defeat.
Lose one more, and she loses her wish...
Then you approached
that poor, cornered girl...
You sweet-talked her into battle
with a free win as bait...
You're the one who ended that poor girl
who just lost her second battle...
Her wish... Her life...
You reaped them away from her...
You got a problem with that?!
It's my choice how I battle!
You're right. It is your choice.
But, too bad about the next battle after...
You lost so easily to that girl Iona beat.
That's why you stopped feeding off
the scraps that Iona left behind...
...and started looking
for weaker, new Selectors.
And yet...
You lost.
Pathetic.
I don't want your perverted hands
to disgrace Selector battles.
What?!
Your wish is... to see Iona's life ruined...
You want to beat Iona, right?
But if so, isn't it weird for you
to avoid battling Iona?
Like I said, it's my choice how I battle!
It doesn't matter because if I win,
you're going to bite the dust!
Thank you very much!
Looks like Yuko's here.
Wait a minute... I thought the
shoot today was with me and Iona...
You don't have a shoot today.
What...?
While you were so busy
looking for Selectors...
...you've lost your place here, you know?
Oh, you poor thing! How ironic to see you
"bite the dust" before Iona does... right?
I need to go.
Loser.
Who cares if my life is ruined...
I'm gonna tear your life
to shreds with my own hands!
I guess its game over for her.
It doesn't look like you have a fever.
Do you still feel sick?
My head hurts.
Well, let me call school and
let them know you'll be off today.
I made Grandma worried...
Ru...
You were enjoying it!
Why am I enjoying battles so much...?
Even when I know what horrible things will
happen if I continue to battle... And still...
Don't cry, Ru.
Tama likes seeing Ru having fun battling.
So, don't cry. We can have plenty of battles...
Stop it!
Ru...
Hey, Kazuki? Let's go out sometime!
Yeah, me too!
Sure, why not? Let's head out.
Whoa! That's unusual of you.
Say, let's get something to eat!
Sure!
Let's go!
Can I speak with you for a minute?
You know? You and Kazuki
aren't leaving a good impression.
What?
Like, everyone's creeped out
seeing you both together all the time.
That was blunt.
Oh, don't make that face.
We're really worried about you two.
Worried?
It felt bad hearing all the bad rumors about
you two, so I wanted to give you some advice...
What's that to you?
Why would you care?
Well, to be exact, I'm only concerned
about Kazuki-kun. You? I couldn't care less.
I mean, I felt bad seeing
Kazuki-kun stalked by you.
Yeah. You may not know,
but Kazuki-kun is pretty popular.
Just because you're around,
all the bad rumors...
What an attitude.
I guess that means that rumor is real...
Now, now...
Damn it...
Yuzuki.
Don't talk to me!
Everyone... What's wrong with everyone...?
They're the creeps...
Hi ya there!
You're a Selector, right?!
Yay! I finally met one! Yay!
It's so hard finding Selectors, you know?
Can you please, oh pretty please,
battle with cute, little Chiyori?
Let me... advise you something...
Huh?
In Selector battles...
...if you lose, you're going
to be in a lot of trouble.
Yuzuki...
Yessy! I know!
It's written right here!
A WIXOSS... novel...?
Yup!
If you lose three times, the WIXOSS
factors expand inside your body...
...like a hot air balloon,
and you "Kaboom!" and die, right?
That's so scary!
Wait, that's not--
Battling regardless of that, for the sake
of fulfilling your wish, is so cool!
Ha, ha, ha, ha...
I'm sorry there. My girl here is a bit soft
on the top, if you know what I mean.
Wow that's so rude, Eldora!
At least I'm strong in battle!
Anyways! My precious Selector-san. I'd like
to offer my commemorative first battle to you!
I...
Oh come on, Kazuki-kun!
That's not true...
Hey, let's go some place!
Well, uh, sure.
There's so many things I want to ask you!
Let's do this! Please?!
Okay.
Yuzuki!
Let's do this...
Yay! Yay! It's time to battle!
I'm going to be stepping out for a bit,
so have a good rest, okay?
Why do I feel like... I've been
looking for something all this time?
If I can't have that something...
I feel like there is no reason to be alive...
I lost... I lost, I tell you...!
Yeah, she's strong.
Way stronger than you, Chiyori.
Like, so sorry to have bothered you there.
Come on, Eldora! All great
heroines lose their first battle!
Yeah right. Like, only in novels.
Oh! Let me give you this!
Let's get together again, okay?
Bye-bye!
Yuzuki...
I guess I won.
Yeah...
Losing three times means
my wish won't come true.
But there's no telling how many times I would
need to win for my wish to come true, right?
Only when the conditions are met...
Conditions? That's a weird way to word it.
I feel like you'll tell me
something again later...
I wonder what would happen
if my wish is reversed?
What?
I'll never be with Kazuki again?
No, it has to be worse than that.
Maybe Kazuki will hate me and
I'll never be able to see him again.
I wonder where Kazuki went?
Yuzuki.
Maybe he went to Momoka-san's
place to choose cards.
The others with him seemed new to the game.
I wonder if he's showing
them all sorts of things.
Yuzuki, listen to me.
Or maybe they went to the movies
and stopped by the food court
to play some games.
They may go out for some Okonomiyaki, and
then they'll exchange their addresses, and...
Yuzuki!
No.
If Kazuki is going to be taken away
from me, I'd rather disappear!
Even if you're upset,
you should never say such a thing.
I'm serious...
Hanayo-san, you're a liar!
But... I need you to have
a chance for my wish to come true!
I lost to Akira. But I was
able to beat that girl, Chiyori.
If I still have the chance to win...
If the chance to get Kazuki isn't gone yet...
If my wish isn't gone yet...
Rather than having him taken from me...!
Yuzuki...
I'm your LRIG... I'll follow you...
...no matter where.
When I was living with Mom,
I don't think I asked for much...
Mom seemed so busy being by herself...
But...
I don't know what Ruko is thinking about...
She scares me.
I didn't know why I was scaring
my mom... and that scared me too.
"Kominato"
I'm fine as long as I have
Grandma and my brother with me.
I didn't want to make anyone scared again,
so I didn't ask for much, I think...
And still...
Tama likes seeing Ru having fun battling.
No... No, no...!
The hell you acting like you've been a victim?
Beating me until I groveled...
You were enjoying it!
Ru-chan... Ru-chan...
Wake up, Ru-chan.
I'm sorry. I said you were asleep.
What?
I'm sorry to bother you all of a sudden.
Do you like parfaits? I just
ordered it, but I hope you like it.
Thank you...
Hitoe loved eating marron
parfaits. This one looks good.
Maybe I should bring her here next time.
Um...
I found your number and
Yuzuki-san's number in Hitoe's cell phone.
You must think I'm a horrible mother
looking at her daughter's phone.
But...
That's... the memo Hitoe
was keeping on battles.
You know this?
Y-Yes.
The words written here...
Hitoe told me that she can't see them.
She also said she doesn't know you girls.
"Today, I bought a matching pair
of scrunchies with Ruko and Yuzuki.
They were both really cute with them.
They said I was cute too.
Exchanging all the fun and happy words
with everyone... made me happier
than how I already was.
Friends are really beautiful."
She was very happy about making friends.
But, now she's...
Ruko-san? If there's anything you know or
may have noticed, can you please tell me?
Even if you had an argument with her...
No, I'm not trying to place blame or anything,
but it looks like something went off in her,
and she's all in shock, and...
Ruko-san?
Hitoe lost three times...
We didn't know what would happen if we lost...
It was fun... battling together
just for fun... And then...
R-Ruko-san? Calm down there...
Ruko-san?!
I don't know...
I...
...don't know...
...what to do!
Nodding to the clockwork shadow
opens the door to the end,
bringing in the darkness
There we catch glimpses of the perilous answer
Today's prayer becomes taboo tomorrow
The upside-down maze reflects
the heavens and the earth
The gear begins to turn
Listen carefully among the masses
and that bell resounding in
the skies beckons the soul...
I must move forward even beyond eternity
Because it is the future I chose
The unreachable summer clouds
and flickering heat haze
One day I'll get back my place of smiles
So you wanted to do it too.
Why are you saying this?
I want to do it with you.
...I want to do it.
Just give up, and have some fun.
"The Girl's Desire."