Kyouma,
I want...
...you to be...
...the messiah.
You want me to be the messiah?
Ridiculous.
I'm a mad scientist...
I desire chaos and destruction!
What's up with him?
We'll now resume Operation Urd.
Mr. Braun's still downstairs, man.
I don't care!
Wait!
I told you.
I'm against this.
Against what?
Just this morning, you were helping me.
This morning?
Then... I knew it.
Yes.
The experiment already happened.
The D-mail changed the past.
Seriously?
The world line changed?
I think so.
Thus, you've lost some
of your memories from before the change.
Is this about that Lotto 6 thing?
That's right.
So why are you the only one who remembers?
Titor told me that I have the power.
To prove it, we'll need to move world lines again.
The power?
The power to retain memories,
even across world lines...
The magic eye: Reading Steiner.
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
Daru?
There's no record in the outbox...
But as for the inbox,
the D-mail arrived five days ago.
It succeeded.
Did the past change?
Why do you remember that?
We sent a D-mail to Daru five days in the past
telling him the position of the cards,
so he could win the Faris Cup.
Mayushii?
Quick question: in the Faris Cup last week...
What? I lost? Immediately?
I see... Thanks. Bye.
Daru's message didn't alter the past.
With the way the game went,
it should've changed.
It wasn't enough to change world lines.
Then we need an easier way to tell
if the past has changed.
I-It's not like I suddenly agree with
these experiments, okay?
So... what do you think?
About you being the only one to remember?
I told you.
It's the power of the magic eye, Reading Steiner!
In order to see if that's true,
I'll have you send the next D-mail.
I'd rather not.
Worried about a time paradox?
It feels unfair to change the past.
I've only lived 18 years,
but I wouldn't change any of it.
It's all part of my life, even the failures.
But you love experiments, right?
I-Is that so wrong?
In other words, you'll just sit back and watch
as others sacrifice themselves.
A true mad scientist.
Enough!
But seriously...
Please
I want to send a D-mail too !
Moeka
But seriously, if we're going to perfect the D-mail...
Please ?
It's okay, right ?
Please !
Moeka
...we'll have to continue our experiments...
I'm...
A lab member too, right ?
Moeka
Kiryuu?
Enough!
I can't?
She overwhelmed us...
Okay, we're here!
Those crêpes were good...
Yeah.
Hey! You look bored.
I'm waiting for someone.
Hey, don't scare Nae!
I didn't do anything!
Come on, Nae.
Let's leave this loser alone and go inside.
Hi!
Big sis!
This is for you.
Thanks!
Here's one for Okarin too!
Yo!
Good morning, Suzu.
It's the part-timer girl!
Hey... What happened after that?
With what?
The time machine!
Did you ask John Titor?
Yeah, but I don't know if
what he says is accurate...
Which part?
Why are you so interested?
You're a Titor fanatic, aren't you?
That's not it.
Kurisu!
Good morning.
More sparks between you two?
What's her problem, anyway?
Fighting makes me sad.
Don't worry! It's okay.
Thank you.
No private messages.
We want something simple that'll make it clear
whether the past has changed.
"I changed my cell phone four days ago,
and I want to tell myself not to do it."
I see.
So if the past changes,
you'll have a different cell phone.
It'd be obvious.
Then let's begin the experiment!
All right! Activate the Phone Microwave
(name subject to change)!
It's so round...
What's this?
I used the wrong number for
the Lotto 6 you asked me about.
This is my apology.
I... I see.
Good... Good to hear!
The day nears when your heart's eye will open.
Yes!
Well, if you'll excuse me...
You're leaving?
You seem busy.
Goodbye.
Wear Mayushii's cosplay sometime soon, okay?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm not really into that...
So you won't?
I think you'd look great...
Goodbye.
Bye-bye!
Good kid, huh?
Yeah.
This feeling again.
Which means...
the past has changed?
Wh-Where's Shining Finger?
Shi...
Japanese, do you speak it?
Rukako didn't stop by?
Rukako? Nope.
Then Moeka... Where's Moeka?
Moeka? Who's that?
Kiryuu Moeka!
She wasn't here today?
Well?
Who's that?
Kiryuu Moeka... I've never heard that name before.
What?
Another D-mail?
Wh-What do you mean?
The past changed, and Moeka's very existence was erased?
Impossible!
Up to July 31st, my inbox still has messages from her.
Sending...
"Something wrong?"
"Sorry, I'm kind of busy."
"I'll message you later."
In other words,
the past altered in such a way that,
ever since four days ago,
when she received that message,
this Kiryuu... Moeka person
changed her actions and never came to the lab.
I suppose so.
And this time, only you remember it.
The Reading Steiner, was it?
By the way, just saying that is embarrassing.
I don't think you should call it that.
I'm not interested in your personal opinion.
The power to retain memories across world lines.
Is it for real?
Here I am!
We'll talk tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Okarin!
I really do have that ability.
I want you to be the messiah.
That means...
I...
I'm amazed they can sleep at the lab.
He said it's because he's a mad scientist.
I know! Let's all sleep over at the lab next time!
Only if the guys aren't there.
I know. Why not come to my hotel?
Can I really?
Of course.
Sure!
Okay, I'll come over soon!
Ruka?
Yeah...
Yeah... What?!
Really?
What?!
You didn't bring the magical blade, "Summer Rain"?
Um...
Don't say that, Okarin!
Today, Ruka is my guest.
He's going to wear my cosplay!
Um... I...
Come on. Let's transform, Ruka. Transform!
Um, I mean, I...
Let's take off your clothes...
No, don't touch me there!
Okay!
I'll put it on myself,
so allow me!
You have to know the trick to putting this on.
P-Please... don't take off my clothes!
This is quite lesbian.
Except Rukako's a guy.
Which makes it...
even better!
It's Kirari from Rai-Net.
You're as cute as I imagined, Ruka!
This is really embarrassing.
It's okay!
Cute is justice!
I want to get a low-angle shot of this.
What do you think, Okarin?
That's right...
It's me!
I've just been victimized by a
fierce psychological attack!
This is bad!
My soul... My soul is being devoured!
Wh-What's wrong, Kyouma?
What's with him?
Kurisu!
Stop staring, my perverted assistant.
I'm not staring!
Even more win!
What do you think of this cosplay?
Does it look good?
Yes, it's very cute.
C-Cute... Well, I...
Let's try on the others!
Wait!
I came here because I had a request for you.
You didn't come here to wear my cosplay?
I-I said, "No," but you wouldn't listen to me...
I'm sorry. I was just really happy.
So what did you want to ask?
Actually...
I want you to let me send a message to the past!
Yesterday...
I came by to apologize for messing up
the Lotto 6, but before I could...
Another D-mail?
Wh-What do you mean?
The past changed, and Moeka's very existence was erased?
Impossible!
I'm sorry for eavesdropping when I shouldn't have!
I didn't mean to!
Ruka, what kind of message
do you want to send to the past?
Actually, I...
I want to be a girl!
I don't like the way I look.
I think I'd feel better about myself if I was a girl...
I've always felt that way.
W-Wait a second...
What is she saying?
Assistant, you appear to have
made a fatal mistake.
Mistake?
Rukako is no girl.
He's a guy.
What kind of joke is that?
You don't believe me...
If you call yourself a scientist,
then see for yourself.
Such a cute girl couldn't be a guy.
Excuse me for a second.
Are you okay?
I'm serious!
I really want to be a girl!
Please!
But I don't know if sending a D-mail
would be enough to change your gender.
I heard about this thing...
If you eat lots of meat
when a baby is in your tummy,
you'll have a boy.
With a lot of vegetables, you'll have a girl.
You want us to send a D-mail telling your mom
to eat lots of vegetables?
Would that be possible?
Very well.
I shall grant your wish.
Thank you!
Good for you, Ruka!
Yes!
Isn't changing someone's gender a bad idea?
Do you think it's possible to affect it
just by eating vegetables?
True enough.
There's no scientific evidence for it.
He must've really been worried about it
if that made him feel better.
Rukako, from now on, you're Lab Member 006!
Y-Yes.
Let's begin the experiment...
Wait. You're 17 this year, right?
Huh? Yes.
In other words, you were born in 1993.
So what?
When did cell phones become popular in Japan?
It looks like it was around 1996,
and only later did they get messaging capabilities.
In other words, when he was born,
there's a good chance his mom
didn't own a cell phone.
Then we can't send the D-mail?
Oh, no...
We could change it so it sends sinister microwaves.
You have enough sinister microwaves for everyone.
Good... Insult me more.
That's the stuff...
I see.
I'm terrified by my own talent!
Not this again...
If she doesn't have a cell phone,
send it to her pager!
Pagers...
A system using EM waves to
transmit messages to small receivers.
During the 1990s,
they enjoyed enormous popularity.
The emergence of cellular phones
rendered them obsolete.
Pagers?
I've never seen one!
You're very knowledgeable.
I guess you're a Cell-Pager, not Cel 7?
It's written right there.
Why not read it yourself?
Lab Member 006, Urushibara Ruka!
It's time for your first mission.
Find out if your mother had a pager
and acquire that number!
Y-Yes, sir!
My mom had a pager!
Here's the number.
You did it!
You've thought about what to write, right?
Yes!
"Eat vegetables for a healthy child."
I heard you can only send 18 hiragana...
You can only send numbers to a pager.
To transform these to numbers...
One sec.
You need two digits for voiced consonants.
What?
You can send a total of 36 English letters.
That message puts you four characters over.
Then...
How about we turn this into numbers?
Eat veggies for a healthy child.
Okay, starting it up.
All right.
Is this really okay?
Don't worry about it.
My Reading Steiner activated!
That means...
I see... Some people are like that, huh?
Yes, it's cute!
Ruka, I think you'd look great
in something like this.
Y-You think?
This is...
You pervert!
Where are you staring?
No, I mean...
Wait.
It's difficult to ask if Rukako became a girl.
However...
This failed.
Just what kind of perverted things are you imagining?
Geez, Okarin!
I can't take my eyes off
you two perverts for a minute.
I'm not a pervert! I'm a perverted gentlemen!
It doesn't matter! It honestly doesn't matter!
But...
the world line changed.
Something happened...
but what?