Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Now, it's time to begin.
Let's go!
Ngaah~
Hurry up and start already!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Oh yeah, we have to wear or summer uniform starting today.
I'm sure people like Konata are probably going to forget and wear the Winter uniform.
There's always at least one person in the class who forgets.
Onee-chan, good morning!
Uwa... there was someone this close to me.
All Kinds
of People
Crap!
I forgot to apply for the limited present from Zat-TV.
I actually kind of wanted that apron from 'Apron of Love.'
You didn't have enough love.
Huh?
You lack love Kagami, that's why you forget.
Actually, I was pretty busy lately with council meetings and exams and stuff.
No, no... those are just excuses.
I've never forgotten.
Don't compare me to someone who fools around all day!
I didn't like how you said that either.
Aha!
I wonder... how do you actually win those prizes?
Simply put...
It's love!
I get it...
I'm simply a woman with no love.
Well, if you just apply with conventional methods...
There's no way you're going to win.
Huh?
How do you write yours, Kona-chan?
I write them to win.
How?
First of all, the writing must be very neat.
You have to write a postcard that will look irresistible to the selection committee.
Like what?
For example...
Outlining your postcard with a highlighter.
Yeah, that would stand out.
Furthermore, you can put in a little sketch of the present.
A sketch...
I don't think I can draw that neatly.
Well, in that case...
You'll just have to attack with quantity.
I might be able to do that.
But, no matter how many you plan to turn in, don't even think about using a printer.
You have to individually write them.
And, make sure you turn in at least 100.
A hundred!?
100 is the standard.
That'll cost quite a bit.
In order to get something you really want...
You need passion and a fighting spirit.
But...
Wouldn't it be cheaper to just buy the prize somewhere else?
There are things in this world that money simply can't buy.
Ah...
Will 100 postcards really fit in a mailbox?
You don't put them all in at once.
You have to put a little at a time.
On different days too.
Hmm?
Depending on the committee of selectors,
They'll reject you right away if you try to win with numbers.
Well, there are those cases where you just can't fight the system.
But then again, the opposite is true as well.
Then, what should you do?
You need love!
Okay, okay.
If you just want to win something...
You should check the free newspaper or ads,
Then apply for the one that looks the least popular.
Your chances of winning will go up a lot.
Yeah, I'll give it a try.
Is there any love there?
Kagami and Tsukasa...
You two don't look too alike for being twins.
Oh, because we're fraternal twins.
So we're about as similar to each other as normal sisters.
Unlike identical twins, fraternal twins can vary in looks and personality.
I see.
Tsukasa does seem pretty laid back, unlike violent Kagami.
What was that!?
If you did your hair in the same style, you might look a little more similar.
Kona-chan!
Haha, never mind...
Kagami just can't be cute.
Shut up!
Stop creating an image in your mind and then insulting me!
Can you guys communicate telepathically?
Huh?
You know how twins live similar lifestyles...
Or have similar preferences for the opposite sex, even though they could be far apart...
Like both marrying another pair of twins.
And, if one of them is in danger, the other one can sense that from the other side of the world.
Don't you guys experience any phenomena like that?
So, you can use telepathy, can't you?
Show it to me...
*Bii bii*
You just read too much manga.
Even Mana Kana...
Mana Kana?
Those two differ slightly, too.
Mana has a hesitant sort of personality.
But Kana seems to be more of an optimist.
Also, they say when they sing, their voices are a little different.
Speaking of which, Mana and Kana always thought of themselves as fraternal twins.
But recently, they found out that they were actually identical twins.
What!? Really!?
Is it that surprising?
I heard the definition of fraternal and identical twins changed a little recently.
Which means that you two could actually be identical twins!
Your common ground is...
You both like snacks, right?
Yep, I love them.
I guess...
And you're both left-handed.
Yep.
I guess...
What is your favorite color?
White, I think.
Black.
Just like the colors of your hearts.
What did you say!?
I got kind of hungry talking about eggs and snacks and stuff.
We weren't talking about food.
Ugh, it's freaking hot.
It gets so hot when the train's crowded.
I guess it's that season again.
Hot!
I guess they didn't turn on the A/C yet.
H-Hey...
Izumi Soujirou
Konata-sama
After a long courtship, we
Narumi Kiyotaka
and Kobayakawa Yui,will be
tying the knot on June **.
A Ladybug Samba, Punk Version.
My cousin's older sister is getting married this month, you know.
Ah!
She's a June bride!
I'm envious.
Of this?
Huh?
Why would such a wet and gloomy season be the 'happiest' season to marry?
Umm... uh...
Eh?
Why June is the best month to get married?
Yeah.
The word June is derived from the mythical Roman goddess Juno.
Juno is equivalent to the mythical Greek goddess Hera.
And she watches over fertility and marriages.
Therefore, those married in the month of Hera will be blessed with happiness, or so they say.
Really?
But wasn't Hera Zeus's wife?
Yes, that's true.
I have an image of 'jealousy' when I think of Hera, so I don't think it's as happy as people think.
Which would you want to wear for your wedding, a dress or a kimono?
I want to wear a dress.
I've been wanting to wear once since I was a child.
Hmm, I think I'd prefer a dress too.
But kimonos are cute too.
I think I'd want to wear both.
Lately, they've come out with minis and colorful ones too.
Wow... a mini-dress?
One with lots of frills on the hems might be cute.
So many frills, so many dreams!
Right?
Tsukasa, you're Angel Salvia.
Actually, with your hairstyle you'd look more like Angel Daisy.
Yellow from the waist up, complete with a miniskirt!
Tsukasa-san, you might look good in a mini.
Really?
Attire is important, but I think what is also equally important is whom your partner is.
A childhood friend, or a princess-type.
It's tough choosing for which image to go.
One might be wealthy, and use Beho*mi and I***zun magic spells.
But if you're going for true feelings-
You have to be Bianca!
Oh, Kagami... you're pretty pure.
I thought you'd go for the rich guy.
What's this... no punchline?
Yo, Konata.
Hm?
I'm stuck in that game I borrowed from you the other day.
Wait a sec, Kagami.
Eh?
These things are interesting because you have to solve them yourself.
Hmm, I suppose you have a point.
Yep, yep.
In other words, you understand the value of doing something yourself.
So Konata, you're going to do your own homework from now on, right?
You know, the detectives in manga and dramas always happen to be at the scene of the murder.
Like Conan and Kindaichi.
If they didn't do that, there wouldn't be a story.
Do you think so?
Can't they do 'regular' cases?
'Regular?'
Like traveling all around Japan to find a missing person.
I think that tailing someone has the potential to make an interesting game.
It's got thrill and suspense too.
I guess.
Or taking a husband's case to investigate his wife's love affairs.
Or finding a pet who's run away?
Yeah, yeah.
But would watching something like that even be interesting at all?
No, probably not at all.
See?
Also in actual murders, we rarely see the complex or intricate tricks that we do in dramas.
Hmm...
That's true.
Like forging fingerprints, or manipulating body temperature, or erasing the luminol traces.
Eh?
Stuff used to evade forensic investigations.
Well, something too intricate might lead to 'copycat' cases.
Or involve outside parties.
Ah, those...
Complicated cases like those will either go unnoticed or unsolved, or something like that.
That's pretty dangerous in various ways.
It's been raining a lot lately, I don't like it.
It seems so...
I used to like the rain a long time ago.
Well, you get wet and your laundry doesn't dry, so...
I never really liked it.
Why did you like it, Kona-chan?
Because the baseball programs would get canceled, so I could watch anime at their normal times.
I see!
That's a very Kona-chan-like answer.
But recently there've been a lot more dome games.
What's the matter?
A lot of times in manga, a really smart student goes to the same school as a really stupid character.
Cut that out!
Shut up!
Get lost, you douche!
If you think about it, it's pretty amazing.
If you're going to talk about that...
There have been some anime lately where the students and teachers are the same age.
Or even reverse.
Sensei?
What is it, Tachi*na-san?
Everyone wants to see something where there's a huge gap between someone's actual age and mental age.
It's something everyone wants to see regardless of age or place in the world.
I don't get it.
You shouldn't question things like that.
On the other hand, it's a wonder how students of such different caliber get into the same school.
Yeah, I definitely agree with you on that one.
This might sound a little blunt, but...
I'm amazed that you actually made it into this school, Konata.
Probably because you're good at cramming overnight.
Did you cram for your entrance exam too?
What?
You mean you actually did?
Well, I don't think cramming overnight is possible in this case.
You surprised me.
But I'm amazed that you actually studied.
Were there any studying games for the DS?
My dad added some conditions.
If I got a D-rank, he would give me an Apple Pippin.
For a C-rank, I'd get a 3DO.
For a B-rank, he would give me a PS2.
Izumi-papa, you really know how to handle your daughter.
I was just thinking...
I'm more surprised by the fact that Tsukasa is in the same school as we are.
How can you say something so bluntly?
Hmm...
Yes!
I win again!
Dammit... I don't stand a chance at fighting games.
You play them a lot more than I do.
Bring it on.. I'll take you on at other games.
Oh really?
Are you sure...?
Then let's play?
A quiz game!
N-no way!
I lost to Konata at a game that tests one's intelligence?
I don't believe it.
Don't tell me this girl remembered all the answer patterns?
She has a photographic memory when it comes to games.
What do you want to play next?
Don't go through my games!
Hmm, that's weird.
Didn't you have some really easy party game?
How do you know what games I have?
You might stand a chance against me with that game.
And it smelled so bad...
Kagami, you haven't been eating any snacks.
Usually you eat a lot more.
There's no big reason for it.
Oh I know...
A diet for the upcoming summer?
That's not it!
Not like you have anyone to whom you can show off your swimsuits.
Shut up!
Mind your business.
Speaking of which, you guys were born on Tanabata, right?
That means your birthday is coming up pretty soon.
Yeah, so?
Kona-chan, you remembered it for us?
Yeah.
17, eh?
17 is a pretty critical age.
What's so important about it?
It's the age where you start thinking about engagements and bad things start happening to you.
Really?
When your birthday approaches, you start to get worried...
And you tend yo buy evil-warding charms, or powerstones.
That sounds fun.
Yeah.
The more I brought them, the more it started to get fun.
Well, I've got a 'what the hell!' charm...
Err... an all-purpose charm.
A 'what the hell!' charm, eh?
I suppose it protects you from everything including traffic.
Yeah, yeah...
By the way, did you guys know that your birthday was Ponytail Day?
No, I didn't.
But why is July 7th Ponytail Day?
Because Orihime wore a ponytail on that day.
I'm not so sure about that.
They have a Japanese Association for Ponytails.
Every year they give out the 'Japan Ponytail' reward to actresses who look good with ponytails.
Is that so?
But, I get the feeling that anyone would look good in a ponytail.
Let's see about that.
I can barely make one because my hair is so short.
But small ponytails are pretty cute too.
Kona-chan, yours looks pretty good.
You'd be totally fine wearing that ponytail to school.
Really?
Yeah, really.
O-onee-chan you too...
Kagami, you know...
I know, I know, I'll take it out.
You look manly, like a samurai.
Well, excuse me!
You know how drunkards often tie their ties around their forehead.
Does that signify anything?
Oh that?
Isn't that just them trying to loosen their neckties?
But when they pull it over their head, it gets stuck?
Hmm...
If you're going to talk about that, don't you think the takeout lunch box is a little unnatural?
A takeout lunch box?
Like the one that Kato-chan from The Drifters usually carries.
I'm still not quite sure.
When I think about drunkards nowadays...
They always tie their neckties around their heads while carrying takeout lunch boxes.
Don't you?
I hope Orihime and Altair can meet each other this year.
*dream~ dream~*
Maybe your 'what the hell!' charm will give her some divine grace.
Thanks for nothing.
I'm collecting all the Comp-Matsuri Quo-cards.
Speaking of which, do you ever use the Quo-cards you're always collecting?
Hmm?
No, I don't use them.
Eh, then why do you collect them?
When merchandise of a title you like come out, don't you want to collect them?
As a fan and a collector?
I wonder about that since you're not going to use them.
You shouldn't use it!
You have to keep them safe somewhere.
I get really irritated when I see someone use them as if they were normal cards.
Items like these should never be used.
Putting them up for auction or selling them to a shop is definitely out of the question.
Not only do you fail as a collector, but you fail as a fan, too.
Even if you tell me that...
For me, I need at least three copies.
One is for eternal preservation purposes...
So, I place it in its designated case and put it away.
The second one I'll take out occasionally and look at it.
And the last one?
For kicks.
What's that?
When there's something you really want, don't you feel safer when you have two or three copies?
Eh?
Hmm...
Okay okay, you don't.
It's okay... I know I'm an otaku and strange anyway.
Well, I kind of understand what you were trying to say.
Tsukasa, you seem like you would be pretty popular with guys, but I've never heard any stories about you.
Eh?
Well, Tsukasa is a little plain and doesn't stand out that much.
Yeah.
Or maybe it's because your scary older sister over here watches you like a hawk.
Did you say something?
I don't think it's so much as me being plain, but that Kona-chan and Yuki-chan have such unique personalities.
Miyuki-san knows a lot of things, she's pretty, has good style and the glasses-look.
Not to mention, she's naturally klutzy and doesn't like the dentist...
Hey hey, that started to sound really weird halfway through.
But I haven't heard any rumors about Miyuki either.
Maybe she's just too pretty that they guys have a hard time approaching her.
I don't think that's true...
Because she's really kind and looks out for others.
That's true.
Maybe a lot of people confessed to her...
But she's turned them all down.
So she turns them down...
Or maybe she didn't realize the confessions were actually confessions.
That's possible.
Yuki-chan is pretty dense sometimes.
If they tell her in a roundabout way she might not get the message.
Geez, the males in your class are pretty pathetic.
Isn't there at least one guy with the balls to convey his feelings to Miyuki and just ask her out?
Maybe not.
Our class doesn't have that many fetishists.
Huh?
Miyuki-san's character is popular with fetishists.
Fetishists, huh?
That stinks.
Oh my, is it this late already?
I think I'll excuse myself.
Oh, really?
Please don't mind me and take your time.
Well then, excuse me.
I'll see you later.
Later.
So, there's more to this.
That person is actually-
Wah!
O-oh... I'm sorry.
Yes!!
I-I'm sorry.
No no no.
That just happens sometimes, doesn't it?
I've done it before too.
Me too.
Everyone has to do it at least once.
Konata, you've done it too, right?
Nope.
That was definitely moé.
Miyuki-san.
Good job!!
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
We're gonna start the Lucky Channel today like *kyu kyu kyu~*
I'll be the navigator, Kogami Akira.
And...
Uh... I'm Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
Pleased to meet you.
Okay, okay.
We've been bringing this program to you guys for...
Tada!
Three times now, including today!
Shiraishi-san, have you gotten used to the job yet?
W-well, not exactly...
I'm sorry.
For some reason I feel like you haven't completely opened your heart to me yet, Shiraishi-san.
You're standing a little farther than usual too.
Eh!?
I was thinking this might be the gap in our friendship.
*sniffle*
A-ahhh! That's not true!
I think we'll get started now!
Umm, today we've got some good news for our loyal fans.
Believe it or not, we're introducing one of the regulars of Lucky Star!
*Panpaka pa~n*
Today we'll be introducing Takara Miyuki-san.
Um, she's the class president, very bri-
That's 'bright.'
Bright, skilled in both the pen and sword, the perfect superhuman.
Shiraishi-san, you know Miyuki-san, right?
But of course!
Miyuki-san is so nice!
But above all, I can't get enough of those glasses.
She's really pretty too.
Usually when someone's that pretty, I find it difficult to approach them.
Surprisingly though, she's really easy to get along with.
Hmm... I wish you'd talk that much on the radio too.
Eh?
So if I have you talk about Miyuki-san, you wouldn't stop?
Ahh, that's not what I meant.
I guess.
So Miyuki-san, huh...
The beautiful character...
With the large breasts...
And various other turn-ons?
Isn't she lucky to be such a pretty character?
Akira-sama, is this jealousy?
I hear they're pretty popular among fetishists too.
I don't think the fetishists would-
But if you're talking about popular among fetishists...
The lolicons are all over-
Too bad!
It's time to say goodbye again!
So, if you have some questions, opinions, or comments you would like to make about the show...
Just send them to Akira, *puriizu*!
I'll look forward to seeing you next time.
See you!
So how is she, really?
Just as we described her.
No way...
She probably smokes a lil' bit of this... behind the school, doesn't she?
She's not you, Akira-sama, so no need to worry.
Uh huh...
That was funny!
It was a very unique song.
I would like to hear a song that's pleasant to the common person now.
Oh, you'll know the next one Kagami.
Eh?
Try to guess it by the intro!
It better not be another weird song.
Oh, what was this?
Dunno.
Kagami, the answer is?
Oh! Full Metal... it's Full Metal.
Really?
On top of that, it's Kagami's favorite one, Fumoffu!
Is that so?
I-I just read a little bit of the novel, and looked at the pictures.
Tatoeba ne namida ga koboreru hi ni wa
例えばね 涙がこぼれる日には
Even if there are days
when the tears... stream down my face...
Ah! Kona-chan,
you're really good.
You can put on
a pretty mature voice.
Isn't she just copying them?
Sono senaka wo hitorijime shitai kedo
その背中を ひとりじめしたいけど
I want you back all for myself, but...
So what are you
gonna sing, Tsukasa and Miyuki?
I wonder if I can sing anything...
I don't know too much about it either, so...
Yasashisa wa tokidoki zankoku dakara
優しさは時々 残酷だから
Because sometimes
kindness can also be cruel.
It doesn't matter what you sing.
Look at Konata.
We should just sing
whatever we want to.
T-then I'll look for something.
I'm not too
confident with my voice..
Motomeru hodo kotae wo miushinau
求める程 こたえを見失う
The more I search,
the more I lose sight of the answer.
Don't worry about it.
We're the only ones that are
going to hear it, so just take it easy.
R-really?
Then...
Ameagari no machi niji ga mieru nara
雨上がりの街 虹が見えるなら
If you can see the rainbow in the town after the rain...
Ima arukidasou nani ka ga hajimaru
今 歩き出そう 何かが始まる
Let's start walking now as something is about to begin...
Preview
And next week's Lucky Star is...
Tsukasa here.
The other day, I laughed so hard that I couldn't breathe.
At school in the morni-
What? I'm out of time already?
「A Matter of Motivation」
Next week: A Matter of Motivation.
Look forward to it!