I am leaving now.
Morning!
Oh, good morning, Futaba--
Yoko, good morning.
"I Am Graduating from Bread Crusts"
Yoko, did you hear? It's such a nice day,
but it's supposed to rain in the afternoon.
It's a shame.
Oh, what are you doing?
--Ow, that hurts!
--Wh-What is the matter with you, Futaba?
Wh-What do you mean?
What's the matter with you, Yoko?
What is the matter with me?
Morning...
Man, I'm tired and my body feels heavy.
I'm so proud of myself for going to school.
Oh, good morning, Hayama!
You are so polite!
Oh, I know what this is.
What is it?
It is a surprise, or what is it called?
Like a candid camera ruse to surprise me.
Goodness gracious. I will not be tricked
by this. You can stop your act.
Oh, Yoko is acting strange!
She said, "goodness gracious"!
I cannot believe you're saying that to me!
I finished crocheting lace yesterday!
It took two whole months!
Crocheting lace? Why don't you just buy it?
Aw, this is my hobby.
Look, isn't it just the cutest?
Oh man, what a girly hobby.
Oh? What's the matter, Yoko?
They are even like this when I am not present.
What is the matter with those two?
U-Um...
Hm?
H-H-Hayama, w-well...
What's up, Nishiyama?
Y-You're the last one to...
turn in the worksheet.
I have to turn all of them in at once, so...
Shoot, I haven't done it yet. Why don't you do
it for me, Nishiyama? You're class rep, right?
Huh? But...
Ah, I see. This is a dream.
You're making it hard for Nishiyama
by not turning it in. Oh, Hayama.
Aw, all right. I guess I'll do it now.
What a terrible dream.
Hayama. Oh, that Hayama! Hayama!
Hm?
What a troublemaker! Curse her! I'll show her how
I am when I'm not holding back. Just watch me!
What's this...
Hey, Hayama!
Look how much trouble you're
giving Nishiyama! Hurry up and turn it in!
I'm doing it now.
Nishiyama's not class representative
because she wants to be!
She was forced to be class representative, because
nobody else wanted to do all the extra work!
Nishiyama's really timid,
so she couldn't say no.
Maybe they haven't changed all that much.
I feel so lazy! Maybe I'll
ditch afternoon classes.
That won't do! You should go to class.
So lazy...
I am still not used to these two like this.
But, if this is a dream,
what is everybody else like?
Whoo! I'm so annoyed!
I hate the world! Maybe I'll
break all the school windows!
If I steal a motorcycle and don't know
how to ride it, it's the world's fault!
Hayama's sister is the top
bad girl in this school, right?
Bad girl?
She even comes to school. Talk about devoted.
Oh? Yamaji!
What, Nishikawa? Address your teachers properly.
Huh? What's this?! Violence at school?!
Yoko, what are you doing?
You just punched a teacher!
Oh my, I could not help myself.
But he's a teacher!
And I did not punch him.
It was a slap. Oh, goodness.
That's what you wanted to clarify?!
What's this?! It's an offense to hit a teacher!
Report to the faculty room, immediately!
If there's a problem, they can come to me.
Why are you so rebellious?!
Yoko! Stop!
Now, now. What's the fuss?
Class is starting soon.
Return to your classrooms.
Or maybe... you want to be
punished by Ms. Shino?
And that's what happened in the dream.
My dream!
That was your dream?!
Of course it was. I would do no such thing.
R-Right...
Wasn't it interesting? It's too bad I
woke up right when it was getting good.
Wasn't my personality pretty terrible?
Well, it was a dream.
It wasn't too different from the real me.
You weren't even there, Futaba.
Don't say that!
"Central Shopping Arcade"
It does seem pretty fun to be a different you.
Especially since you're usually
hiding your real self, right?
Oh, there she is! Futaba!
Sakura!
Well, how do I look? I tried changing my image!
Oh, how cute.
I think it's pretty good, too. You know how
I'm going to be an idol when I grow up.
Ah, you mentioned that.
So, can you listen to me sing? I need to get used to
singing in front of people, so I don't get nervous.
♪ I'm in full bloom! My charm is never-ending! ♪
♪ I won't let you even glance at other girls! ♪
--♪ Today and tomorrow, forever and ever! ♪
--U-Ugh... recital...
--Unlike my sister, she's completely off...
--♪ Today and tomorrow, forever and ever! ♪
Sa-Sakura!
Hm?
Why don't you practice before
performing in front of people?
Yeah, they say to wear a bucket
on your head to cure your tone-deafness.
Do that!
Wha--
What's this.
A bucket... So I should sing with this on?
Y-Yeah. That's what I heard.
♪ I'm in full bloom! ♪
♪ I'm in full bloo-- ♪
Sakura?
F-Futaba?
I might throw up.
Good thing we have a bucket!
Hm...
Doesn't look good.
I tried doing it like Sakura.
Oh, then how about this?
Yeah?
It does not get in the way...
Want to try on glasses, too?
Hayama. Glasses.
Glasses aren't an optional feature for braids.
Maybe I should cut it shorter.
Why would you?! How could you cut your hair?
I thought it would be a good change.
The ends are damaged, anyway.
Long hair uses a lot of shampoo and
water, which can get expensive, too.
B-But. It would be a waste to cut your long hair.
You've been growing it out since you were young.
Right? It would be a waste.
You can't go back once you've cut it, either.
Your normal hair style fits you best, Miss Yoko.
You think so?
A princess hair cut is a must for a rich girl,
even though you no longer are one.
Not because it looks good on me?
Thank you very much!
I am not just so-so anymore! Do you not
think I am a pro at working part-time?
You're amazing, Miss Yoko. You're best in the
world at anything you do. You're a professional!
A pro at working part-time?
Well, at first, I couldn't believe
she was working part-time.
She probably grew quickly
because of this environment.
Oh, found it! It's here!
This is the shop from the book.
Welcome!
Wow!
Which one should I get?
Miss Yoko?
Ni...
Nishikawa?
Huh? Who's that?
A school friend... from before.
Oh, Osakabe!
Huh? You know her?
Yes, we were in the same grade
at my previous school.
Oh, Mannenro Girls' Academy,
right? The rich girl school.
Hm? Even rich girls work part-time?
Oh, you're learning how the world works?
No, I no longer have the
standing to be a rich girl.
I am working for the income.
Oh...
"Strawberry Tart"
These two cakes are our seasonal recommendations.
Oh. I'll have those, please.
Miss Yoko! Miss Yoko is a real pro!
Um...
You can contact me here, just in case.
Let me know if there is
anything I can do for you.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
M-Miss Yoko!
You were amazing! A pro! You did your best!
O-Of course. I have leveled up.
This is nothing! I am a pro part-timer!
Oh, even though all you have
is pride, you tried so hard!
I-I will take a short break. I need a drink.
That's mayonnaise!
I heard you had it rough yesterday.
It was fine. It is true that I do not want to be seen
like this. But, I cannot go back to my old self.
Because, the me now is the actual me.
Miss Yoko...
Morning!
What a wonderful day it is!
Tee-he-he. He-he!
Tee-he-he, ow ow ow!
Same reaction as in the dream.
You don't have enough feminine charm!
What do you mean?
How can you say that when
you're eating like that?!
Even I'm trying my best to
become an idol by doing this!
Futaba, why don't you put
effort into something, too?
That's what happened.
I see...
I was shocked to hear that I didn't
have enough feminine charm,
so I wanted to show people
that I'm a girl. Tee-hee!
Miss Yoko is trying her best, so I
thought I could try my best, too!
Futaba!
Oh, my! The birdies are having a little chat.
Hayama is all polka-dotted! Are they hives?!
Oh, these are good.
They are.
Oh, do you want some, Odagiri?
It's okay. I'm satisfied from
just you offering! Tee-hee!
Huh?! What's the matter, Odagiri?
Are you feeling sick?
It's almost lunch time, so I
shouldn't eat sweets now.
Are you sure?! They're burnt milk caramels!
Yup. I'm okay.
You're drooling!
Oh, so you're not very feminine?
You should've just asked me for pointers.
I do various things to better myself.
You do?
I take rose supplements to smell better,
do stretches to maintain my figure,
and regularly do sit-ups and use dumbbells.
I also do this and that and this.
You do that much?
Amazing! You're fervently doing so much!
Yeah, I'm trying hard! What's wrong with that?!
"Lucky Number" "Lucky Color"
My lucky number's three. My lucky color is yellow.
What are you looking at?
At my horoscope. Girls like
checking their horoscopes, right?
That's true.
Oh, Futaba Odagiri. You're not
stopping by Mr. Stuffed's?
There's a new curry challenge.
If you finish three kilos, it's free!
Three! Yellow!
No, that's not related.
Mm, I-I can't.
What?!
I couldn't finish three kilos
of food. I am a girl.
What are you saying? Are you
trying to make a fool of me?
You're Futaba Odagiri! Don't say you can't
finish it. It's rude to those who've lost to you!
It's fine. Go ahead.
Yes. You are the best when
you are shining brilliantly.
Okay!
"Stuffed Hut"
Delicious!
Feminine charm is at absolute zero.
"Stuffed Hut"
Thanks for the food!
I won't lose next time!
"Stuffed Hut"
Futaba!
I heard that you wanted to raise your feminine charm.
Ah... er...
I made this for you.
Wait! It's probably a special soup that will
raise my feminine charm or something, right?
Nope! It's a drink!
Doesn't make a difference!
Here.
The color! And the smell!
I have some for everyone.
What happened to you?
You think...
...our feminine charm went up?
Anyway, what are you doing here so early, Yu?
Daddy has a job for your dad!
Oh my, for my father?
That's great, Miss Yoko!
Having connections is great, isn't it?
Thank you so much. How can I thank you?
Huh?! Then, maybe you'll sign
a marriage application?
Huh?
Well, you know. It'll be just
for fun, like playing pretend!
Geez, I would be okay with that anytime.
Let's go submit our marriage application.
Let go of me!
I've been learning how to sing.
♪ Aren't you head over heels?! ♪
Well, looks like this is his fate.
I am the daughter of the Nishikawa Family.
My father is a company employee,
and I am his only daughter.
Woah!
Wow, that's so normal.
I am now the same as you. I will not be
easily captivated by food like before--
U-Um...
N-Nishikawa... um...
This is my return gift for Valentine's!
"Dietary Supplement Cookies" "10 packs of 4 sticks"
Huh?
I thought it should be cookies, but I
wanted them to be useful, too.
A-A-Are these for me?
Miss Yoko.
She's super happy.
Wait, isn't White Day next week?
What?!
Are you still thinking about it?
I am pitiful. I have not changed
a bit since I met you two.
Huh?
You have changed.
Really?
When we first met, you said, "Why are
you eating here, too? How bothersome!"
You were more like a rich girl.
Then, I thought, here is a protected species.
What?!
What are you saying, Futaba?
You mean, endangered species.
What? But there'd be a lot
if you look in the right places.
When did we start talking about animals? Um...
If it's an endangered species,
maybe they'll go extinct.
That's why we need to protect them.
Um, why have you been talking about animals?
Oh! Found another endangered species.
Huh?!
Yeah, it'd be annoying if
there were a lot of them.
What would be annoying?
Aren't they talking about you?
Hey!
Kondo is a different kind of protected species.
Why are you wearing that again, Sonobe?!
And that's a rare beast.
We shouldn't get too close.
Sonobe!
Let's go, Miss Yoko.
Don't feed the animals.
A-And that's...
A-A dangerous, poisonous one.
Run away!
Huh? What?
Hayama! Futaba!
Wait for me!
I am graduating from bread crusts!
Oh...
I am trying an instant food today.
"Yakisoba Noodles"
Wow!
Gah! No!
She's done it! She put the sauce in first!
What she said before... It's all over!
Huh? What?
Oh, look.
She's sulking.
It is not like I enjoy instant noodles.
They are such a hassle, anyway!
Bread crusts are more abundant
and taste delicious.
You brought some?!
"Thank you very much!"