Bye-bye!
It's gone by so fast, huh?
I was thinking about how
you'd just entered our school,
but you'll already be a second-year soon.
Yeah.
Then Run will be a third-year...
See you.
Yeah.
Bye-bye!
Toru? You awake?
Yeah.
It's the new semester today, right? Don't be late.
Okay.
I'll be back!
Fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
Kirameku tooku no sora to hitotsu ni naru
Kazeyomi kimama na watashi no yukue wa kanata
Issho ni ikou
Shinkokyuu hazundeku, sekai no spring breath
Taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
Ohayou to sayounara no aida wa watashitachi dake
Nandemo dekiru ne
Sukitooru hizashi, umaretate no sora
Machiawaseta yakusoku no morning arch
Te o furu kimi e to totte oki no kyou o watasou
Oshaberi ga hajimaru
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
THE ALIEN
Good morning, Nagi.
Hey.
What's the matter, Nagi?
You're not lookin' too spirited today.
I really got into a book yesterday,
and I was up late reading it.
Oh, you didn't get enough sleep?
It's not good to stay up late.
Actually, while I was doing that,
I ate two boxes of chocolates.
I'm hating myself right now...
She lost to the allure of sweets!
Th-the other day, I stayed up till morning
reading a book! It's called "On That Night."
Oh, that one? You've read it?
Yeah, it's a tear-jerker, right?
When the boyfriend gets sick and dies,
did you cry like crazy, too?
I know, you get tears just rememberin' it, huh?
I...
On That Night
I only just started reading it!
I-I'm sorry!
Huh?
You're doing your homework NOW?
Yeah. I couldn't finish it yesterday.
That's unusual.
I was up late reading a book.
A
This should be U.
No, it's A.
This is I, right?
Wrong. It's E.
I.
E.
What?
Finished?
A little more. Just a little more!
Why you...
This is 3, right?
It's E.
So, this is MU, right?
It's 7.
They're backwards and upside-down.
3 E MU 7
Run-chan.
You just do your homework?
No! I finished it during vacation.
Run's talkin' to a boy.
Huh? But you were just copying it.
I was comparing answers with Nagi.
Toru's gonna get mad again!
This is about when Toru gets here, right?
Should I go to her and
do somethin' to pass the time?
Or should I try to break things up?
What's wrong, Yuko?
English is hard, huh?
Run is still!
S-say, Toru...
What?
Right now, um... That is...
Let me in.
No!
Wh-what are you doing?
Now's no good! It's no good!
I can't breathe...
Toru, you're here?
It's all right.
It's okay now, Toru.
Huh? Toru?!
All third-years, please ensure
you take proper care of yourselves.
First- and second-years,
remain dedicated to education-
Now listen up.
If you aren't careful, this third semester
will be over before you know it.
Let's roll up our sleeves and do our best!
Hey, you there.
Me, ma'am?
That's right. Mind if I ask a favor?
I'd like you to pass these out to everyone.
Health
News
I'd like you to pass these out to everyone.
Okay. But first, a question.
Hm? What is it?
What is my name?
Ma'am, don't tell me...
Sort
of
You're our homeroom teacher, correct?
Sorry!
When you're an adult, it's hard to recall things
off the top of your head, unfortunately.
Miss Kamate! That is unbecoming a teacher!
Miss Kito!
Huh? Why?
Forgetting a student's name is unthinkable!
I have completely memorized the faces, names,
year and homeroom of all students in school!
Oh, that's awesome.
It is only natural for a teacher!
You never know when
one of your precious students
will come to you with a problem, do you?
At a time like that, you can't very well ask,
"Who are you again?" can...
Kito. Kito. Kito!
At a time like that, you can't very well ask,
"Who are you again?" can...
It's your fault she ran off,
so make up for it by taking these.
Oh, and buy me dinner on the way home.
Thanks to you, Torun,
I finally finished my homework!
So we weren't comparing answers?
I bet you hadn't done a single thing, had you?
Ooh, correct! How did you know?
Why you...
We're close to becoming second-years,
so pull yourself together.
Great weather today, isn't it?
Don't change the subject.
There's a kitty cat up there.
Maybe it can't get down.
We can't leave it. I will help it!
Yutaka?
Don't do that. It's dangerous!
I'll be fine.
I may not look it, but I, Yutaka,
am great at climbing trees.
Wait just a little longer. I'm coming.
Please stay still...
I've got you!
U-Um...
They're both mad!
I'm very sorry. I'll clean up the fallen leaves!
That's not the point, is it?
What would you have done if you'd fallen?
That's right! You could have gotten hurt!
Torun... Miporin...
What are you happy about?!
Still, she did well, huh?
I, Yutaka, did a good job, right?!
I'm glad you're all right, kitty cat.
No! Stop that! Hey!
Don't lick me there!
GRIND GRIND
Stop being cozy with it and start cleaning!
I give up! I give up!
GRIND GRIND
Toru!
There you are!
Run-chan...
Will it be a while longer?
Are you all already done?
Yeah, we're done.
Huh?
Look! There are lots of leaves and bits
stuck in your hair!
I'll get them for you.
Y-you don't have to. I can do it myself.
There's no need to be shy!
Staaaaare...
Okay, it's all clean.
Th-thank you.
What's wrong, Toru?
Nothing, really.
S-so cute...
Durian Burger Fair
Limited Time
Durian Burger
Is something wrong, Toru?
No.
It'll get cold if you don't hurry up and eat.
Yeah.
This durian burger is delicious!
It's better than you'd think, huh?
Toru! You've got some ketchup on you.
By your mouth.
Oh, you're right. Thank you.
Run-chan, you've got some, too. Here.
I bit my tongue...
Is that blood? Or ketchup?!
Run. Toru.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sorry we're late.
Some foreign guy asked us for directions.
Somehow, we were able to answer...
Hahh huss haa heen huff!
Huhh hunn hree huh he huh?
Huh?
What language is that? Is she testing me?
She just bit her tongue.
Look, look!
I'm collectin' points. I want some
of this shop's merchandise!
Oh. This, huh?
So if you all don't need yours,
you could help me out...
Here you go.
Thank you, Toru.
Hoo han haa hine hoo!
Thank you too, Run.
I'm not collecting them, so I'll pitch in.
Really? I'm so happy!
So, what are you collecting for?
A keychain with a stuffed bear on it. It's cute!
Huho-hhan,
Hi hinn ho hoo hike he hear hoo!
Hi han hay hoo hun!
Y-yeah. Um, I'm going to the bathroom for a bit.
Okay.
So, how many more points does she need?
Ow...
Plain white is too ambitious. One point.
But the lace is cute. Two points.
Hih haa hill? Hee hoi!
That man threw away his points!
Aah, what a waste. But they're already
in the trash. I can't get them out from there.
That's it! If I stick around here, I might get some
from other people throwin' theirs away!
Yuko sure is taking her time.
The heck is she doing?
Um...
I don't need my points,
so if you like, help yourself. Here.
Hang hoo!
Thank you very much.
Huh high hah!
There might be a lot people
who aren't collecting points.
At this rate, it won't be long
till we get that merchandise.
Yuko sure will be surprised when she gets back!
Um...
Are you collecting point cards?
Heh!
Yes!
Why?
Why isn't anyone throwin' their
point cards away?!
For a limited time...
It's a durian burger! For a limited time!
We HAVE to go eat one!
Not today.
Huh? Why not?
You have to do your homework, don't you?
It's for a limited time...
Here you are.
Okay!
Please come again.
How'd it go?
I got it!
I'm glad, Yuko-chan.
Yeah. Thank you.
I sure was surprised, gettin' all those at once.
Ta-daa!
Right? It's cute, huh?
Yuko, you really like cute things, don't you?
Well, sure. Cute things are cute!
Finished!
Look!
What is it?
A paper crane!
Small, isn't it?
So small that I can't see it.
You're cruel, Nagi-chan.
Lend me your magnifying glass.
I don't have that on me!
Huh? But that on your face...
What the heck do you think GLASSES are?!
Here.
Thank you!
You lent them to her, huh?
Sure, why not?
Run. Is your head working?
She's impersonating Nagi!
If you're not gonna use them,
then give them back!
I thought you wanted something
in place of a magnifying glass.
Huh? Well, fine.
Nagi-chan, you're getting smaller!
Wow! So small...
Yeah. Your eyes are.
By the way, that impersonation
earlier was nothing like me.
Huh? I don't know...
You seem rather confident.
I wanna see it!
Yeah, do it! An impersonation!
I don't really want to show anyone, but...
Nagi-chan, those magnifying glasses suit you!
Huh?
WATCH, dammit!
You said you didn't want to show us.
That's not what I meant!
Okay then, one more time!
I'd like to see it again, too.
How could I do it NOW?!
Look, I'm watching this time.
Forget it!
Nagi-chan's mad!
Sorry. But Nagi, that was spot-on.
Yeah. Spot-on!
You weren't looking, were you?!
How about this place?
They have a limited-time durian burger. See?
Nah, no way. The students
come to places like these.
Indeed. Because it's for a limited time.
That won't do!
Getting something to eat on the way home
from school is the first step toward delinquency!
We have to go warn them right-
Aah, where's the harm?
But!
So, we're goin' somewhere else.
Yes, yes. You sure push people around, you?
Please wait a moment! I'm not done-
The thing is, I'd like to go somewhere
fancy and more grown-up.
Is that okay? Aah, that makes me happy.
You're treating, right?
Kito is.
Just a moment!
We're splitting the bill!
So that diet plan is all half-assed.
It is?
Really? I believed in it, too.
Right? That's why I was surprised.
So I switched to another one.
It's okay to eat fries?
Gah!
For today, yes. I've done the math.
Really?
Toru?
Are you tired?
I'm fine.
It's already this late?
We talked too much, huh?
Should we go ahead and go?
Yeah.
Yup. Let's go...
To space!
You're saying something weird again?
The truth is...
...I am an alien!
Nagi's going to make fun of her again.
I knew it!
I thought that was the case.
It makes sense!
Huh?
No matter how much you eat, you don't get fat.
You fly in the sky sometimes, right?
Moshika moshikashitara kiita koto nai?
Maybe, by chance, you've heard, haven't you?
Run-chan!
Moshika moshikashitara kiita koto nai?
Maybe, by chance, you've heard, haven't you?
Omou dake sore dake tsuujichau ndesu
Just by thinking, just by that, it comes across
Sore wa nani nanika to kikaretara, sou
If asked "What? What is that?" Yes
Kotae wa tada hitotsu, oshiete ageru
There is only one answer, I'll tell you
See ya, Run.
Kotae wa tada hitotsu, oshiete ageru
There is only one answer, I'll tell you
See ya, Run.
Wink hitotsu
One wink
Take care of yourself
Wink hitotsu
One wink
Okay!
Wink hitotsu
One wink
Okay!
Nandemo fuwafuwa
Everything is soft and fuzzy
See you, everyone!
Fushigi na koto bakari yo
Everything is so strange
Run-chan, wait!
Fushigi na koto bakari yo
Everything is so strange
Yeah.
Fushigi na koto bakari yo
Everything is so strange
Yeah.
Bye-bye!
Uchuu no shinpi, telepathy ne
That mystery of space, it's telepathy
The food on Earth was delicious and good!
Uchuu no shinpi, telepathy ne
That mystery of space, it's telepathy
The food on Earth was delicious and good!
Donna koto datte omitoushi
It can see through anything
What do you eat in space?
Donna koto datte omitoushi
It can see through anything
Demo demo ki o tsukete
But, but be careful
Space food!
Demo demo ki o tsukete
But, but be careful
Is that so?
Demo demo ki o tsukete
But, but be careful
Is that so?
Ima wa himitsu no mama de, ahan
For now, we'll keep it a secret, ha ha
Made on Earth!
Ima wa himitsu no mama de, ahan
For now, we'll keep it a secret, ha ha
Run-chan!
Oh, you're awake?
You really fell asleep, huh?
A dream?
Okay! We're at your place, Toru.
Sorry. And thank you.
Not at all.
Well, I'm going home.
Not to outer space, right?
That's unusual for YOU to tell a joke, Toru.
See you.
Yeah.
Bye-bye!
Will everyone be that happy
when they graduate?
You going somewhere?
The convenience store.
It's night now, so be careful.
Okay.
Too bad it's gotten so dark.
Guess I'll cheer up with something sweet.
R...
Run-chan...
Toru!
Run-chan!
What's the matter, Toru?
Run-chan, you...
You won't change, right?
Right!
Yume to harukaze no kagaku
Dreams and the chemistry of spring breeze
Tomaranai yokan
A premonition that won't stop
Lucky, happy, kono yubi ni tomare
Lucky, happy, Stop at this finger!
Itsumo kashimashiku hashiru sono saki wa
Always running boisterously, and the destination
Wakaranai kedo sore ga ii ne
Is unknown, but that's fine
Hajimaru yo
It's going to start
Honpou, my pace, jugyouchuu wa gahaku
Uninhibited, leisurely paced, drawing during class
Kirehashi ni wa keikaku
A plan on the scraps
Doko ni yukou? Kitto ima ga paradise
Where shall we go? Surely, right now is paradise
Nejimakisugi no munasawagi
Apprehension, wound up too tight
Yakusoku wa chikoku dakedo douchaku
Later than promised, but we showed up at the same time
Skirt no stage wa donna hibi ni naru no?
What sorts of days will the skirted stage bring?
Yume to harukaze no kagaku
Dreams and the chemistry of spring breeze
Tomaranai yokan
A premonition that won't stop
Lucky, happy, kono yubi ni tomare
Lucky, happy, Stop at this finger!
Itsumo kashimashiku hashiru sono saki wa
Always running boisterously, and the destination
Wakaranai kedo sore ga ii ne
Is unknown, but that's fine
Hajimaru yo
It's going to start
Toru! You're late!
We've been waitin' so long!
Come on, let's hurry and go home.
Hyaa!
Toru Nagi
Bye-Bye!
Yuko
Run