I'm Mami Tomoe.
A ninth-grader at Midakihara.
And...
A magical girl contracted with Kyubey.
Another weird dream...
Good morning, Madoka!
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 2 That sounds wonderful
You were late getting home last night, Madoka.
An upperclasswoman invited me over.
I'm not going to go on about your curfew, but you should at least poke your head in before dinner.
Sorry.
So people really can't see him...
Wow, what a wonderful room!
I live alone, so don't worry about bothering anyone.
I'm sorry I'm not really prepared for guests.
Mami, these are great!
They taste amazing!
Thank you.
Now that Kyubey's chosen you, you're involved.
So I thought an explanation was in order.
Sure, whaddaya wanna hear?
I think she means the other way around, Sayaka...
It's beautiful!
This is a Soul Gem.
It's a jewel born forth when a girl contracts with Kyubey.
The source of their mystic power, and proof that they're a magical girl.
Contracts?
I'll fulfill any one of your wishes!
Really!?
Wishes?
It doesn't matter what! I'll make miracles happen!
Fabulous riches!? Immortality!? Maybe even a feast fit for an Emperor!
That last one is kind of...
But in exchange, those who hold one of these jewels—a Soul Gem—has the duty to fight witches.
Witches?
Hey, Mama.
Wha... What if?
If you were told that magic would make any of your wishes come true, what would you do?
I'd get rid of both the chief partners at my company.
Yeah, that's it.
The president's getting way too old, but he says he won't retire until he has a replacement.
Why don't you take over?
I wonder...
If I get sales to go along with it, planning should fall in line. The only problem is old Baldy the beancounter...
So maybe...
Mama, you look scary...
So what's a witch?
Are they different from magical girls?
If magical girls are born from wishes, then witches are born from curses.
If magical girls spread hope, then witches scatter despair.
Made all the more horrible in that normal humans can't see them.
Unease and suspicion, consumption with rage and hatred.
They sow the seeds of catastrophe through the world.
Quite a few unexplained suicides and murders are caused by witches' curses.
Their formless malevolence eats away at men from within.
If they're so dangerous, why doesn't anyone know about them?
Witches conceal themselves within a magical barrier, never to show themselves.
Like the labyrinth you two wandered into.
It was pretty dangerous in there.
Most people who get sucked in never make it out alive.
And you fight against things that scary?
Yes. I risk my life.
So I don't mind if you think it over carefully before deciding.
Since you were chosen by Kyubey, you have the chance to make any of your wishes come true.
But in return, you risk your life.
I'm not sure.
How about you come along on a witch hunt?
You can see what it means to fight witches for yourself.
And it'll help you decide carefully whether there's something you want so badly you'd risk your life for it.
Good morning!
Good morning.
'Mornin.
Good morning, Sayaka!
What's wrong, Sayaka?
We're the only ones who can see him, right?
I guess.
Um...
It's nothing! Let's just get going.
You can talk just by thinking.
We already have that kind of magical power?
No, I'm just passing messages.
It's fine, though. Nice and convenient!
This feels kinda weird...
What's gotten into you two?
You keep looking like you're about to say something.
Well, um...
Well...
You mean you can understand each other just by gazing into each other's eyes already!?
I can't believe you went that far in just one day!
What did you two even do last night!?
It's not really...
Well, a lot happened, but...
Two girls can't do that!
That's forbidden love!
You forgot your bag!
Hitomi's acting like you today, Sayaka.
What's that supposed to mean!?
Hey, you look pretty unconcerned about being at school.
Why would I be?
I told you, that girl from yesterday just transferred into our class.
Isn't she trying to kill you?
I think I'm safer at school. Mami's here.
But she's a ninth-grader. Isn't she pretty far away?
Don't worry. I can hear you loud and clear.
She's within range of my telepathy!
Um...
Good morning!
Don't worry, I'm keeping an eye on you. I don't think she'd go after him in public anyway.
I hope so...
Well speak of the devil.
So that transfer student is a magical girl like you, Mami?
I'm sure of it. A strong one, too.
But then isn't she an ally of justice devoted to hunting witches too?
Why'd she attack Madoka, then?
She was after me.
I think she wanted to stop a new magical girl from being born.
But why?
We'd be fighting the same thing, so why not another ally?
It's not like that.
If anything, you'd be more competition.
Why?
Defeating a witch has its own rewards.
So under the right circumstances, we end up clashing.
So it caught her attention when Kyubey first called out to Madoka,
and that's why she was after Madoka all day?
Probably.
Don't worry, Madoka!
If she tries anything, I'll smack her a good one!
We've got Mami backing us up too.
That's right. I'm not sure how much good Sayaka will do, but I'm here for you.
Don't worry.
What do you mean, you don't know how much good I'll do!?
So so far you've studied referring to people and things in the active voice.
Now we're going to work on the passive voice, where B is affected by A!
These sentences are formed by combining B and a past participle of a transitive verb.
For example, "kare ga atashi no koto ga suki" means "He likes me."
Here!
Hey, Madoka.
Have you thought up a wish?
Have you?
I can't think of anything.
I kind of figured everyone would have one, but...
There's plenty of things I want and things I'd like to do.
But I can't get over the "risking my life" part.
I don't want anything that  bad.
Wow, I'm surprised. Most girls go right for it.
I guess we're just ignorant.
I guess.
Yeah. Ignorance is bliss.
It's not like wishes you'd give your life for are that unusual.
I guess lots of people out there have them.
So if we can't think of any because of how lucky we are...
Our ignorance is truly a blessing.
Why us?
It isn't fair!
There are people who would love a chance like this!
Sayaka...
It's okay.
Picking up where you left off yesterday?
I have no such intention.
I wanted to finish him off before he met Madoka Kaname.
It's too late for that now.
So, what are you going to do? Will you become a magical girl too?
I...
What gives you the right to ask!?
Do you remember what I said yesterday?
Very well. I won't warn you twice.
Pray.
Wait! Homura!
What did you wish for when you became a magical girl?
Sorry, Hitomi, we've got something to take care of.
Another secret?
Well...
I'm jealous! I just feel like a fifth wheel now!
I told you, it's not like that...
Akemi!
Let's go get a coffee after school!
I'm busy today.
Sorry.
All right, time for your first experience of what it's like to be a magical girl.
I hope you're looking forward to it!
Are you prepared?
I'm not sure if this is enough, but...
Look what I brought!
I figure it's better than nothing.
Well, I'm glad you're prepared for that kind of thing.
Did you bring anything, Madoka?
Well, I...
I thought I should start with a design.
You're certainly enthusiastic enough.
Oh, man, you've got me beat.
This is a trace of the magic the witch used yesterday.
Tracking forms the basis of witch-hunting.
Using the Soul Gem, we can follow the aura witches leave.
That's less fantastic than I expected.
It's not lighting up at all.
I let her go yesterday.
Her tracks have faded.
If you had gone straight after her...
Maybe I would've caught her.
But dealing with you two was more important.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I knew you were an ally of justice!
On the other hand, that transfer student is a real pain in the butt!
I wonder if she's really that bad...
So, Mami, do you have any idea where the witch might be hiding?
A witch's curse can have the most impact around crimes and accidents.
So it's best to check major roads and red-light districts where fights tend to break out.
After that, deserted areas suitable for suicide.
It's worst when they haunt hospitals.
They suck life force from those already weakened, with no one the wiser.
There's a strong magical wave.
And it's close...
There it is!
Look, Mami!
A witch's kiss...
I knew it.
This woman...
It's okay. She's just fainted.
Let's go.
I won't let you get away today.
Wow, this is great!
This is more for peace of mind than anything, but you should be able to protect yourself with it.
Stay close to me.
Okay!
St—stay away!
Are you afraid?
No way!
I'm scared, but...
But...
Keep going! You're almost to the focus of the barrier!
Look. That's a witch.
Eww...
You're going to fight that?
Don't worry. I won't lose.
Stand back.
One day, perhaps the light of love
which shines in your eyes will fulfill
one dream of this scarred world
If you would slake your desires,
there is no future but casting off your pride
When I was a girl, I dreamed of you
Wielding something like unto ancient magic
I want to be by your side as you smile, filled with the strength to smash even gods
Mami!
I'm fine.
I'm not going to look lame in front of girls who're going to be my juniors!
In my trembling hand, I grasp
the courage of a laurel
As my emotions waver,
my prayer awakens the light
That was disappointing.
Erupt Finale!
She won!
Wow...
This is a Grief Seed.
The egg of a witch.
Egg...
If you're lucky, you'll find them on witches.
Don't worry, it's perfectly safe in that form.
If anything, it's precious for how useful it is!
My Soul Gem has dimmed since yesterday.
Now that you mention it...
But using a Grief Seed...
Look.
It cleared up!
See?
It restored the magical power I used.
That's the reward for hunting witches I mentioned earlier.
It has one use left.
Here, you can have it.
Homura Akemi.
It's her!
Or do you have something against sharing?
It's your prize.
It belongs to you alone.
I see. That's your answer.
She really ticks me off!
I wish we could get along with her...
That's up to her.
Where am I?
I...
Oh no? Why did I—
Why was I going to do that!?
Don't worry. You're okay now.
It was just a bad dream.
Case closed, huh.
It's way too hard for me to decide on a wish I want granted right away.
But I really admire Mami working so hard to help people.
If I could become such a helpful person...
That sounds wonderful.
Or so I thought.
Illustration: Hekiru Hikawa
She puts on a cool air, but she's too shy and scared to talk to anyone.
Sitting alone and crying isn't what a magical girl should be doing.
Episode 3 I'm not afraid anymore
I'm not afraid anymore!