“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Dollars?
They're like those shiny angels who fly so you can see their panties!
Get the amount right this time.
If you're not watching properly, it won't come out right at all.
We don't know that much about the Dollars either.
I will tell you everything I know, though.
They're like the color gang, only we don't know what colors they wear.
The latest issue of Dengeki Bunko just came out...
and then we picked out about ten volumes of... well, other stuff.
Yeah, other stuff!
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
You won't get away!
Turning right!
Real men have abs.
Hey, this is the first time we've done something like this since we joined the Dollars, isn't it, Kadota-san?
Shut up and sit down!
The Dollars aren't shiny angels who fly so you can see their panties, are they, Dotachin?
I said, don't call me that!
All right, we lost 'em!
You're crazy!
Damn!
Well then, let's hear it.
Tell me about these human experiments you guys are supporting.
I'm Kadota Kyohei.
I really don't like being called "Dotachin."
The events you see now are from eight hours prior.
On the Move
From here on out, I'll be telling you about the famous Castano Incident.
The person who disappeared was my classmate.
A friend of a friend, to be exact...
I never met her though, so...
A friend of yours, Tanaka Taro-san?
Speaking of which
a lot of people have been disappearing lately.
Or rather, there are a lot of rumors.
You're a real rumor nut, aren't you, Kanra?
According to the rumors I've heard,
it's usually kids who run away from home,
and illegal immigrants that disappear.
In other words, it's the people who don't leave any traces behind that disappear.
And a lot of those people are disappearing in the area between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
Furthermore, after they disappear, they're never heard from again.
Really?
Some of the rumors are even scarier...
Like that the bodies are disappearing because the Dollars are killing and eating them.
What a nice old sign.
This is it, huh?
The supplier our informant was talking about.
I bet there are tons of illegal squatters in there.
All right. Hurry up, let's stock up on some rice seeds and get them delivered.
Castano! Castano!
Hey, hey!
Look at this!
Teenage girls! They're worth twice as much!
No, let's stick to our guns today.
If we go for the likes of them, another one of those things might show up again.
That headless thing?
Let's go with this guy for today.
What's up?
Doesn't he seem kind of defective?
He's human, isn't he?
Well then, since he's a middle-aged man, we'll just have to offer a discount.
Hey.
Hello, mister rice seed!
I am Japanese! Just like you!
But, I am look a lot like foreigner! Un poco sad.
Sometimes they tease.
We can't really sell him as food, can we?
What does "Un poco sad" mean?
So, I think that without a little-brother-type, fairy-helper character like Yuuta,
all you have is a masochistic, hair-fetish wolf.
It's not a "little-brother" as much as it's a "boy-in-drag."
I want a little-sister-type, fairy-helper character.
An older-sister-type would be all right too.
You had better not keep talking about this over dinner.
Dotachin! Let's go eat!
Let's go eat!
Oh my, oh my! Kadota-san, as usual, this is amazing craftsmanship!
This bathroom is bigger than my bedroom!
Apparently, the concept is an "upper-class cabaret club, offering calm relaxation."
We'd better hurry. Today only comes once a month.
Who is it?
It's from Castano.
"Dish broke."
Just buy a new dish.
Dollar store! Dollar store!
I Japanese!
Maybe he was trying to type "I've been kidnapped"?
You're reading far too much into it.
He's a fussy one. Put him to sleep already!
Got it.
Hey! It's cheap! The toppings are cheap, yes?
So you heard the rumor too, Sonohara-san?
Yes.
It's all right. That rumor is baloney.
That's right! It's not necessarily true that Harima-san got kidnapped and disappeared,
or that she was abducted and killed–
Why did you have to put it so bluntly?
I'm done for.
Here you are, nigiri for three!
It's okay, our sushi has only fish, yes?
No human meat, even on half-price special day!
At the sushi shop across the street though–
Not more of this again?!
Simon! The hanging sign out front is all folded up!
The sign?
Yeah! The sign! Let's go fix it! Okay?
Let's fix it!
That sushi shop has no fish on special days!
It's human meat! Human! Scary, yes?
Togusa-san,
don't you want an Italian car?
Italian? Italian cars are good!
I'll kill you.
Italian cars are pretty expensive, since they're foreign.
Bring me a Setouchi clam please!
Amber jack and striped jack for me!
That was close!
Yeah, it was.
Who uses a whole bottle of that stuff? Especially on themselves?
It's no use; I'm too sleepy.
Don't nod off until we've delivered him.
Oh god... my eyelids!
Watch the road!
Excuse me.
What is it?
This guy is the verge of sleepy.
Better for everyone if we ditch him, no?
Castano! We brought sushi!
Hey! We even brought a leftover dish of "Russian Sushi" for you!
What in the world?!
That text you got earlier... he didn't break any dishes.
Yeah.
It was a bowl!
Dotachin.
"Kanji Conversion Made Easy."
That Castano...
Castano was kidnapped by a bunch of man-hunters.
We'll never see him again.
What am I gonna do now that Castano's gone?!
Who is going to support me now?!
We all knew just how important Castano had been to Togusa.
Nobody could replace him.
Neither Karisawa, nor Yumasaki, nor myself. I felt sorry for him.
If he was kidnapped when he sent that text, then it hasn't been that long.
Let's find them before they can deliver him somewhere and get him back.
But how?!
I know how.
I saw their car take off.
Hajime!
He's here! The tough, little-brother-type, fairy-helper character!
In El Paso, Texas, a real alien was actually dissected! We went to the site of the experiment, and saw it for ourselves.
Got it. So if we find them, we should let the foreigner inside go free.
Yeah. We don't know when or where they
plan to hand him over to their superiors,
It was a while back. I had been trained with the right equipment, so I decided to put the technique to use in my experiment...
but we want to save him as quickly as possible.
Okay. It's a black van, right? Do you have the license number?
Yeah. I'll tell you.
Wait a second.
Go ahead.
Thank you, Hajime.
Yeah.
Do you eat sushi?
Yeah!
I'll see you later.
Is this wasabi?
There's some in it.
It's all right. Russian wasabi isn't very hot.
Don't lie to him!
Let's go.
Right!
It's a black van... and this is the license plate number.
Take care!
Their implementation team is a subcontractor for a certain corrupt company.
So they're the lowest of the low.
They kidnap people who can't be traced if they disappear, and hand them over to the people in charge.
Sounds like they're using humans as raw materials for something.
It's just like cannibalism.
The contractors had a pretty low delivery rate this month, didn't they?
Yes... it seems our "raw materials" have gotten more careful–
Don't make excuses.
I want you to cut all contractors who can't bring up their numbers.
But...
Or do you want to become the "raw material" yourself?
You can go now.
Seji.
Stupid Shinra!
Shines so bright, wish bang bang! Let's dance...
We searched desperately for the black van that had kidnapped Castano,
knowing deep down that we would find him.
We looked in every place we could think of,
Find the scent... go!
but we still had no clue as to where Castano had gone.
A feeling of uneasiness washed over me.
Would I ever hear that phrase he used to say again?
The one he always said when I was a kid.
The one I never thought I'd hear him say as an adult.
Don't have tickets? I have tickets!
That's right. When it comes to being a businessman, Castano is a dying breed.
And so, Togusa entrusted the greatest joy of his life to Castano...
Togusa's goddess for eternity: Hijiribe Ruri.
The goddess to whom Togusa had devoted his totally one-sided love.
Castano is Togusa's magician,
who gets him those hard-to-get front row seats that are the closest to his goddess.
We have to save Castano, for Togusa's sake.
Dotachin. What are you talking about?
And who are you talking to?
I just thought of something. What if we call Castano's cell phone?
Maybe we'd be able to negotiate with the people on the other end.
I love sushi! Especially tuna.
What's the matter with you?
That's Dotachin's voice!
Oh, right. I was walking down the street, and someone was sleeping by the road.
His phone rang, so I thought I'd–
Me?
I'm out in front of the "Taishoken" shop in south Ikebukuro.
Well hey, they're giving out free Russian sushi today!
Izaya! I told you not to come to Ikebukuro!
Shizu-chan, you found me! Later.
Izaya!
Wake up! Hey! Wake up!
Hey! Wake up! Wake the hell up!
Cut that out. If you don't, he'll fall into an eternal sleep.
But if we don't hurry, Castano will...
That's right! If he gets delivered, they'll kill him!
What are you doing?
I'm going to use this guy's contacts to find out where they're taking Castano.
It's almost time to hand him over, huh?
If it's the guy upstairs who shows up, be sure to get a good look at him.
Yeah.
I am Japanese, no? You find out soon you be mistaken, no?
You're still saying that?
In that case, your family register should say you're Japanese, right?
That my point! The register burned up in air raid!
How frickin' old are you?!
Yeah?
Hey, it's me, it's me.
Kanazawa? You're awake now?
My bad. I'm on my way there right now. Wait, where are we supposed to hand him over again?
Come on, do I have to tell you again?
We're amazing! We did it!
This again!
What's with you guys?
We're the Dollars!
Dollar...?
S! Remember the name!
I'm sleepy... so sleepy...
Let's go.
The story of how we joined the Dollars is really quite simple.
When I think about it, Togusa, Yumasaki and Karisawa have been around since the beginning.
What qualities does a guy like me have that would make them want to hang around me?
They're a good bunch of people.
One day, I got a text on my phone. It was a strange invitation, saying,
"Won't you join the Dollars? There are no rules or restrictions.
You just have to call yourself one of the Dollars."
The Dollars: An organization that has just recently been rumored as slightly out of the ordinary.
At first I thought someone was pulling a prank, but just to test it, I accepted,
and the next day they sent me an URL and a password.
When I logged in, my screen name was displayed on the Dollars' website.
Nobody seemed to be the leader of the group, that I know of at least.
There are some smaller organizations within the larger one,
and although there's a vertical hierarchy in place
no one group looks like it's at the top.
There is nobody below me, and I've never felt like I'm under someone else's command.
Still, I'd be lying if I told you that I've never wondered who came up with this strange organizational system.
I will say that some people have come to suspect that it is a certain guy.
That rude man who started calling me "Dotachin."
Tuna really is great!
You won't find what you're looking for in that direction, though.
I'm sorry, Certy!
How much do you think we can sell him for?
Well, he is on discount.
Or is he?
Is that the guy?
Probably.
What the hell?!
Castano!
Castano! We're here to rescue you!
Think you can do it that easily?
Cocky punks!
How retro!
What does "shara" mean?
T-The headless guy!
A-And we only have an old guy who we're prepared to sell at a discount!
We won't do it anymore! We won't do it anymore!
What?
Castano!
Dotachin!
They're running!
You won't get away!
Turning right!
Maybe I should go home.
Well, you'd better tell us who you give your "merchandise" to first.
No, no, no. It's boring if he just tells us without us torturing him first.
Here, pick one of these.
We'll go with the torture method that you pick from one of these books.
Hey, guys. I don't care what you do, just don't use gasoline inside the car like last time.
Gasoli–
Togusano!
We do our morning ceremony, no?
I-I'll tell you! I'll tell you! Please, let me tell you!
Yagiri Drug Manufacturing, huh?
It's quite an elegant looking place.
Is this really it?
The place where they're doing human experiments?
We half-believed, half-doubted it.
At least from what we saw on the surface.
However, like with most things, there's usually more to them than meets the eye.
In this town, Ikebukuro, there are more of those cases than anywhere else.
Well then, shall we go eat somewhere first?
I agree!
Let's go eat the morning special at Russian Sushi!
Good idea! Let's go, let's go!
All right! That settles it!
You can use as much money as you like.
Thanks, nee-san.
Talk to you later, Seji.
Let's go.
And those are the details of the so-called Castano Incident.
Well, at least for today, our friend came back in one piece, and we're all happy.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Peerless Citizen
Durarara!!
Next episode
Shut up. Be quiet. You're on my nerves.
My body moves of its own accord when I can't suppress my own anger.
It doesn't care what happens to it.
Next episode: Peerless Citizen.
Still, I hate violence!