Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
I trembled with anxiety
Afraid of knowing the truth,
I shut the door to it
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
and found shelter in my dreams
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
that was dyed a deep blue
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
I ended up hurting your heart
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
and the truth behind my smile,
I will deliver my gentle love to you
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
Let us always walk together,
free from the shadows of loneliness
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Episode 13
Call My Name
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Incoming Call
Time-Space
Administrative Bureau
Make a little wish! Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
as long as you're here with me, I can keep smiling happily
Ah, don't look down, we'll be fine
The courage you reached out to me that day lies in my hands
With every twinkle, kindness is born anew
I will always, always cherish this dear feeling
Make a little wish! Wearing the lemon-colored moon drops,
I want to sparkle, and I want to be your energy
Make a little wish! Even on rainy days or sleepless dawns,
if you're here with me, I can smile brightly just like this
Even as we live apart, there's something I believe in
It's that our hearts will always, always be as one
Make a little wish! Collecting the lemon-colored moon drops,
they can become warm tears, the spice to add to a smile
Make a little wish! Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
as long as you're here with me, I can keep smiling happily
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha