I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a little incident changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
I wished for a very small feeling
to reach its destination.
The start of a new journey
is always full of sadness,
but, because I'm sure our
feelings have gotten across...
"Goodbye" doesn't have to be the end,
it can mean a new beginning.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
hiza wo kakaete heya no katasumi
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
itsumo fuan de furuete ita
I trembled with anxiety
hontou wo shiru koto ga kowakute
Afraid of knowing the truth,
tobira wo tojita
I shut the door to it
yasashii uso ni ibasho wo mitsukete
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
yume no naka ni nigekonda
and found shelter in my dreams
daremo shiranai kodoku no umi wo
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
fukai ao ni someteku
that was dyed a deep blue
sabishisa kakusu
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
ichizu na omoi kimi no kokoro wo kizutsukete iru
I ended up hurting your heart
hitomi no oku no himitsu suikomaresou na
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
egao no ura no shinjitsu ni
and the truth behind my smile,
yawarakana ai boku ga todoke ni yuku yo
I will deliver my gentle love to you
furetara kowaresou na nukumori ga ima
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
kako wo hanare afuredasu
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
zutto soba ni iru kara
Let us always walk together,
kanashii kage ni madowanaide
free from the shadows of loneliness
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Everyone, please! Escape! Hurry!
Fate!
Fate! Fate!
Fate-chan!
Fly... towards me!
Episode 13
Call My Name
Call My Name.
Looks like the earthquake's stopped...
Huh? You're right...
The Garden has completely collapsed.
Everything within it has
fallen into imaginary space.
Dimensional distortion
has been prevented.
No indication of dimensional dislocation.
Understood.
Resuming normal patrol course
at level three nautical velocity.
Huh? Where's Fate-chan?
She's with Arf in the brig.
She's a key witness for
this incident, after all.
I'm sorry, but she'll be
detained for the time being.
No way– ow ow ow...
Nanoha! Stay still.
If we had made a mistake
in handling this incident,
a dimensional dislocation
would probably have occurred.
This is a very serious matter.
The TSAB can't afford to treat anyone related to this case leniently.
I trust you understand, right?
Yeah...
Amy, fix it.
Boo.
And so, a lot of things
finally came to an end.
From the day I met Yuuno-kun to today, when everything ended,
it seemed like time just flew by.
While the aftereffects of the dimensional
distortion were being dealt with,
we remained aboard the Arthra for a few days.
And then...
Without your exemplary actions,
this incident would not have been resolved.
Even if it's a bit informal, I'd like to award
you for your distinguished service.
Takamachi Nanoha-san, Yuuno Scrya-kun.
Thank you.
Chrono-kun... what's going to
happen to Fate-chan now?
Despite her circumstances, she was still an accomplice in the dimensional interference.
It's still a serious crime.
The usual sentence is centuries of imprisonment.
No way!
However!
This is a special case,
and it's clear that she didn't
willingly participate in the crime.
All that's really left is getting the
higher-ups to understand that.
But I'm confident that I
can do it, so don't worry.
Chrono-kun...
The TSAB isn't so cold as to punish a girl
who unknowingly committed a crime,
when she was simply trying her
best to fulfill her mother's wish.
Chrono-kun, are you actually a nice
person underneath everything?
Wh–?!
A-As an Enforcer,
it's only natural to say that!
It's not like I'm voicing my own opinions!
You don't have to be so embarrassed about it.
I-I'm not embarrassed about anything!
What?! Don't laugh!
So cute!
The residual effects of the dimensional
distortion should settle down soon.
As of now, it's safe to say we should be able to return you to your world tomorrow.
Thank goodness!
But as for you... the space around
Midchilda is still extremely unstable,
and it looks like it'll take
some time before it stabilizes.
I see...
It could be a few months to half a year
before that area becomes
safe to travel through again.
Is that so...
Um... well, my clan does nothing but
search for new relics and artifacts...
so I don't think there's any need to hurry home, but...
I can't just stay here in your
care the whole time, either.
Then why don't you stay at my house,
like you've been doing?
Nanoha, is that really all right?
Yeah! If it's okay with you.
Then, um... uh...
I'll be in your care once again.
Yeah!
Geez, it's because you slept for so long.
It's because I was up all night
working... I'm still so tired...
You know that place she was aiming for,
Al-Hazard, don't you, Yuuno-kun?
Yes... I've heard of it once before.
I heard it was a world that existed long
before the old calendar was established,
and that it was a land filled with
secret magic and technology.
But it's also said it was destroyed during
a dimensional dislocation long ago.
Here you are.
It's said that magic is in
its ultimate form there,
and if one were to hold that power,
their every wish could be granted
through Al-Hazard's secret technologies.
Magic that would allow you to transcend
the barriers of time and space...
Magic that would even let you rewrite the past...
Magic that could bring
someone back to life...
Those were some of the things she was seeking, right?
Yes...
But anyone who studies magic knows these two things.
Traveling back in time and reviving
the deceased are impossible.
But since she wished so strongly for both things,
she couldn't help but believe in a fairy tale.
But... since she was such a great mage
and was risking her life in search of it,
she might've actually found
the path to Al-Hazard.
Though we'll never know if she did.
I'm sorry for getting into a long
discussion when we just sat down to eat.
Let's eat up before the food gets cold.
And this will probably be the last meal
on board the Arthra for you, Nanoha.
Yeah...
You should just say that you're sad to see her go!
Chrono-kun, you're so shy!
Wh-Wh-What are you talking about!?
Nanoha-chan, you can come over
and play anytime you want!
Yes! Thank you.
Amy! The Arthra isn't some playground!
Now, now, it's all right.
After all, our patrols are always full of free time.
E-Even you, Captain!?
And then came the morning
Yuuno-kun and I were to leave...
Once again... thank you
very much for all you've done.
We're grateful for your cooperation.
I'll contact you once Fate's verdict is in.
I'm sure it'll be fine, though.
I promise nothing bad will happen to her.
Yeah, thanks.
Yuuno-kun, if you ever want to return
to your world, just let us know.
We'll make a gate for you whenever you want.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Well then, I guess it's time?
Yes!
Well, then...
Yeah. See you again, Chrono-kun, Amy-san, Lindy-san!
Shall we head home, Yuuno-kun?
Yeah.
I'm home!
Nanoha! Welcome back!
And my everyday life had returned.
Everything should have gone
back to how it used to be...
Mom! I'm hungry!
but a lot of things happened,
so it's a little different.
Welcome home, Nanoha.
Did you grow taller?
Yeah!
Nanoha-chan!
Nanoha!
I'm back. Just like I promised.
When I think back on everything
that I've been through,
it feels like it all went
by in the blink of an eye.
But those events will
certainly remain in heart.
All the people I met... the times I was
at my wit's end... so many things...
Ahh! It's been so long since I've slept in my own bed!
You be sure to sleep well tonight too, okay, Yuuno-kun?
Yeah!
And really, thanks a lot for
everything you did, Raising Heart.
Thanks for all your hard work too, Nanoha.
The only thing I'm worried
about now... is that girl.
That girl who's so gentle...
Who has such beautiful eyes...
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
And a few days later...
Incoming Call
Time-Space
Administrative Bureau
Hello? This is Nanoha!
Huh? Really?!
Yeah. It was just officially decided.
Fate will be taken into the custody of our main office.
After hearing her description of the
circumstances, a trial will be held.
Okay.
Fate will probably...
no, I'm positive she will be
found innocent. It'll be fine.
After all, Chrono-kun personally
saw to the case after you left.
Amy! You don't need to say
unnecessary things like that...
Thanks so much, Chrono-kun!
Anyway, the hearing and trial will
take some time, so before all that...
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah!
I'll be right there!
Yeah!
What was all that about, Nanoha?
It looks like Fate-chan will be
transferred to their main office for a while,
but they said I could see
her before that happens!
I see.
She even wants to see me, too!
Fate-chan!
We don't have much time, but I think
you guys should talk while you still can.
We'll be waiting over there.
Thanks!
Thank you.
There was so much that I wanted to
talk to you about, but it's funny...
as soon as I saw your face, I completely
forgot everything I was going to say.
I...
You're right.
I can't get the right words out, either.
But, I was happy...
that you faced me with such honesty...
Yeah, I thought it'd be nice
if we could become friends.
But, you'll be leaving today, right?
I suppose so. It's going to be a long trip.
I'll be able to see you again, right?
It makes me a little sad,
but this will finally let me
start being my true self.
I asked you to come so that
I could give you an answer.
To those words you said to me...
"I want us to be friends."
Yeah, yeah!
I thought if I could...
If it would be all right with you...
But, I... don't know how to do it.
That's why I want you to tell me...
how do we become friends?
It's easy.
Becoming friends with
someone is really easy.
You just have to call out their name.
That's all you have to do at first.
Don't say "Hey, you" or
call them "that person,"
but look them straight in the
eyes and call them by their name.
I'm Takamachi Nanoha.
Just call me Nanoha!
Nanoha...?
Yeah! Just like that!
Nanoha...
Yeah!
Nanoha.
Thank you, Nanoha.
Yeah...!
Nanoha...
Yeah!
You have warm hands... Nanoha.
I think I understand something now...
When you see a friend crying,
you feel the same sadness.
Fate-chan!
Thank you, Nanoha...
I have to leave you for now, but...
I'm sure we'll meet again.
When we do... is it all right
if I call your name again?
Yeah! Yeah!
When I want to see you...
I'll be sure to call out your name.
So... please call out my name, too.
Next time when you're the one in trouble,
I'm sure I'll be the one to save you...
That girl... Nanoha...
is really such a good girl, isn't she?
Fate's smiling so much...
It's time. Are you ready to go?
Yes.
Fate-chan!
It's not much to remember
me by, but it's all I have.
Then, I'll give you mine, too...
Thank you, Nanoha.
Yeah, Fate-chan!
I'm sure we'll meet again.
Yeah, I'm sure we will!
Thank you. Arf-san, stay well, okay?
Yeah. Thanks for everything
you did, Nanoha, Yuuno.
I should say goodbye, too.
See you again, Chrono-kun.
Sure.
Bye-bye. Until we meet again.
Chrono-kun...
Arf-san...
Fate-chan!
Nanoha...
Yeah!
make a little wish koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Make a little wish! Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
as long as you're here with me, I can keep smiling happily
ah utsumukanai de yukou daijoubu
Ah, don't look down, we'll be fine
ano hi sashidasareta yuuki ga kono te ni aru yo
The courage you reached out to me that day lies in my hands
Nanoha!
Coming!
mabataki wo suru tabi ni yasashisa ga mata umareru
With every twinkle, kindness is born anew
nee konna itoshisa zutto zutto sodatetai
I will always, always cherish this dear feeling
make a little wish remon iro no tsuki no shizuku matotte
Make a little wish! Wearing the lemon-colored moon drops,
kirari kagayaite itai anata no genki de itai
I want to sparkle, and I want to be your energy
make a little wish ame no hi mo nemurenai yoake ni mo
Make a little wish! Even on rainy days or sleepless dawns,
anata ga ite kureta kara tobikiri egao deita no konna fuu ni
if you're here with me, I can smile brightly just like this
hanarete ikiru toki mo shinjiru mono ga aru kara
Even as we live apart, there's something I believe in
nee kokoro wa itsumo kitto kitto hitotsu dane
It's that our hearts will always, always be as one
make a little wish remon iro no tsuki no shizuku atsumete
Make a little wish! Collecting the lemon-colored moon drops,
atatakai namida ni shite egao no supaisu ni shiyou
they can become warm tears, the spice to add to a smile
make a little wish koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Make a little wish! Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
as long as you're here with me, I can keep smiling happily
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha