Akemi Homura: she who flies against time.
You've relived the last month repeatedly and transversed several different parallel worlds by changing probabilities in the past,
in pursuit of the resolution you'd like for all of this.
Your presence here has answered a question of mine—
namely, exactly why Kaname Madoka carries such great potential as a magical girl.
Now I can form a reasonable hypothesis.
The latent ability of a magical girl is determined by the relative effect of their role on fate.
I could understand if she was the princess of a country or some sort of hero,
but I was at a loss as to why Kaname Madoka, with her average life, was the collective center of so much.
But say, Homura,
don't you think it'd make sense if Madoka became a powerful magical girl because you've continued to relive the same time over and over?
I knew it. You're the cause.
I guess it'd be better to describe it a side-effect of your magic.
What do you mean?
You've reversed time for a single reason. You want to protect Kaname Madoka.
You've probably heavily intertwined a number of parallel worlds by traveling back in time over and over for the same reason and purpose,
with Kaname Madoka at the center of everything.
If, as a result, these "lines of fate" from other parallel worlds—
which under normal circumstances should never interact with each other—all connected to the Madoka in this timeline,
then I could see why she'd have such extraordinary power.
All of this fate—this cause and effect—circulating within the time period you've continued to live repeatedly
has spun together and linked to Madoka, because she is the reason for everything.
Excellent work, Homura.
You're the one responsible for making Madoka the strongest magical girl ever.
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll walk upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 11          The final sign left
i
Miki Sayaka
Funeral
The body of a 2nd-year middle school student from the municipal institution Mitakihara Middle School, Miki Sayaka-san,
Miki
who went missing the 12th of this month, was found in a hotel in the city.
The crime scene shows no signs of struggle and the police are continuing the investigation by searching for evidence of a potential accident or crime.
The weather is up next.
There will be a slightly strong breeze from the northwest accompanied by rain.
Welcome back.
Hey Madoka, about Sayaka...
You really don't know anything about what happened, right?
Yeah.
Sayaka-chan and Kyouko-chan died.
It's not really that surprising.
The symptoms that everything would turn out this way have shown for a while.
And you don't care?
But everyone died because of you!
Just to put an example out there, do you feel like you're inferior to a group of cattle?
Do you even know how the food comes to sit on your table?
Stop it!
Responding that way doesn't make any sense.
If you think what I just showed you was cruel, then you don't understand what's really going on.
By choosing to become part of a human household, they breed free from opposing natural forces and are sheltered from survival of the fittest.
Cows, pigs, and birds, compared to wild animals, generally have a reproductive rate far better than the rest.
Wouldn't you say you humans have the perfect symbiotic relationship with them?
Are you trying to say you're the same?
Actually, we're treating you humans much more equally than the way all of you treat cattle.
While this may not be the best arrangement, we recognize that you are sentient beings when we negotiate with all of you.
You don't believe me?
How about I show you then?
I'll show you the history through which the Incubators and humanity have walked together.
We got involved with your world before your recorded history.
Countless numbers of girls have formed contracts with Incubators, had their hopes realized, and lost themselves to despair.
It starts with a wish or desire and ends with them being cursed or falling into despair.
It's a cycle which many magical girls have repeated.
This includes girls who have changed history forever and led your society to new stages.
Stop it already!
Everyone... Everyone trusted you.
They trusted you and you betrayed them!
We were not the ones to betray them.
It was their own desire.
No matter the desire, if it's something irrational, then it will always distort reality in some way if it comes true.
Then it's obvious that natural law dictates that only bad could eventually come from that.
If you want to call the result of that action "betrayal," then having the wish in the first place would be the mistake.
But I won't call it foolish.
You could also say their sacrifices have further advanced the story of human history.
Thus all the tears shed until now have led to the foundation on which your current society is based—your current style of life.
If you understand that, then how can you treat the fate of a few humans at most differently than the rest of humanity's?
Have you felt nothing watching all of those girls all this time?
Didn't you try to understand just how much they were going through?
If we were able to understand, we wouldn't have had to go out of our way to come to this planet in the first place.
In our civilization, the phenomenon you call emotions is regarded as nothing more than an extremely rare mental disorder.
That's why we were surprised when we found you humans.
The existence of a world where every single individual carries their own emotions and coexists never even crossed our minds.
If none of you ever came to this world...
You'd probably still be unclothed living in caves, I guess.
Losing a student like this is pretty hard...
I'd imagine.
It's even worse that they don't know what happened.
There's another girl missing amongst the seniors... The last staff meeting was a complete mess.
I guess they don't know anything, do they?
It sounds like Sayaka-chan had some relationship trouble.
She was pretty damaged by the whole incident.
Normally it'd all end with everyone the wiser, but for it to turn out like this...
The police seem like they're just going to end the investigation saying she died because of the stress she endured running away from home.
It's not like they have any leads.
How's Madoka-chan faring?
I have no clue.
My intuition tells me she knows something,
but it doesn't seem like she's lying.
This is the first time I haven't been able to tell what she's really up to.
Pretty pathetic on my part. She's my daughter, and I just don't know.
I never thought I'd hear you be negative.
She's seemed kind of weird lately.
I'd assumed that she's just been dealing with a lot by herself, but no matter how long I wait, she never comes to ask me for help.
I thought she relied on me a little bit more than that.
Kids that age sometimes become adults in the blink of an eye.
I'm sure it's quite jarring to the parents though.
So that's what's going on?
You'll just have to believe in her.
I'm sure what Madoka-chan needs at this point is some time to sort out her feelings.
You need to give her some space.
It's pretty difficult not being able to do anything.
I guess that's something you've always had trouble with, huh, Junko?
mi         Homura
Can I come in?
The Walpurgis Night...
Kyouko-chan said that the two of you were going to kill a witch so powerful that she wouldn't be able to do it alone.
You've been getting ready for that here this whole time, right?
Is the entire city in danger?
Unlike the witches you've seen so far, this one has no need to hide in barriers to protect itself.
Just by its coming into existence, several thousands of people will fall.
That means we have to take it out no matter what, right?
Kyouko-chan's dead too. You're the only magical girl left who can fight. That means—
I'll be fine by myself.
Even though it may not be possible for Sakura Kyouko, I am capable of taking out the Walpurgis Night myself.
I never really needed Kyouko's support in the first place.
I just wanted to give her a chance to save face.
Really?
I don't get it...
I want to believe you. I don't want to think you're a liar.
But I can't make myself believe that you'll be okay...
I can't make myself believe you're telling the truth.
There's no way I can tell you how I really feel.
Homura-chan...
I mean...
I mean... I'm living in a different time than you!
I've come from the future, you know?
I've met you over and over again, and each time, I've seen you die.
How can I save you?
How can I change your fate?
I've been looking for that answer and that answer only.
I've gone back and started from the beginning over and over again.
That means... Huh?
I'm sorry.
I'm sure you don't get any of this.
I'm sure you're put off by all of this.
To you, I haven't even known you for a month—I'm just some transfer student.
But to me, you...
Each time I repeat all of this, the time you and I live grows further apart—
our feelings grow further apart, and my words stop reaching you.
I think I lost myself a long time ago.
Homura-chan...
My desire to save you:
the first emotion I had that started this all.
And now that I've come this far, the only star left that will help guide my way...
You don't have to understand.
My words don't have to resonate within you.
But still, I beg you. Let me protect you.
mi         Homura
The thunderstorm is separating and beginning to spin at an incredible rate.
It's clear it's going to turn into a supercell!
Give the instruction to evacuate at once!
It's coming.
Are we having a sleepover?
Are we going to go camping?!
That's right. We're going camping.
Homura-chan...
This time... I'll end it all.
What's wrong Madoka?
I need to use the bathroom.
Is it true that Homura can win by herself?
Even if I said no, would you believe me?
There's nothing I can really say to convince you at this point.
Just watch for yourself. See just how far she can get against the Walpurgis Night.
Why does she go that far to fight?
It's because she still seeks hope.
I imagine if it comes down to it, she'll nullify this timeline, like she has done in the past, and continue fighting.
She'll continue to repeat this meaningless chain of events having come out none the wiser.
Giving up and no longer moving forward holds the same meaning to her now.
The moment she's convinced that there's no way for her to change your fate, that all of this was pointless,
Akemi Homura will lose to her despair and change into a Grief Seed.
She knows this for herself.
That's why, to her, there is no choice.
It doesn't matter if she even has a chance to win; she has no choice but to fight.
You're saying that she has no chance for salvation as long as she holds hope?
That's right.
She's the same as all the magical girls in the past.
Madoka, you saw it too, didn't you?
But...
But...!
Just where are you trying to go?
Mom.
I have to go save my friend.
Leave that to the firemen.
Civilians have to sit still.
It can only be me!
You're being selfish!
Do you even know how much the people around you—
I know!
I know that all too well.
I love you too, Mom. Dad too.
I know how much you all care about me.
I know just how much I have to value my own life.
That's why you're wrong.
Everyone's important to me. I have to protect every single one of them.
That's why I can't be here. That's why I have to go.
You can't explain what's going on, can you?
Then take me with you.
I can't.
Stay by Dad and Tatsuya. Make sure they feel better.
You said I grew up to be a good kid, right?
That I don't lie and don't do anything bad.
Do you still believe that?
Will you trust that what I'm doing is right?
You won't mess up, will you?
Someone's not tricking you, right?
No.
Thank you, Mom.
If it continues any further...
I have to do something to stop it here!
That can't be...
Why...
Why can't I beat her no matter how many times I do this?!
If I do this again, Madoka will just have more fate attached to her.
The only thing I did in the end was...
That's enough.
That's enough, Homura-chan.
Madoka...
You can't be...!
Homura-chan, I'm sorry.
Illustrator   Buriki
If you told me it was wrong to harbor hope, I would tell you that was wrong. I'd say it as many times as necessary.
I'd keep saying it forever.
Episode 12   My best friend
My best friend.