Uh,
i-it's not what you think.
This is just what they call arriving "fashionably late".
Since I like to think I'm a member
of the elite, I'm going to—
Didn't you want to be a stay-at-home dad?
You even said something about how "to work is to lose".
Ugh.
Oh, well, you know.
It's actually wrong to think that being late is a bad thing.
Oh?
Speak your piece before I break your face.
Cops only spring into action after something happens.
And then there's that whole cliché about superheroes arriving late.
But does anyone blame them for it?
I'd go so far as to say that tardiness is justice.
Hey, wait!
Don't hit me! No!
Good grief.
There are too many problem children in this class.
Kawasaki Saki.
Are you arriving fashionably late, too?
Black lace!
Are you retarded?
In this bright room
I wait for the thaw you bring
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
O
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
O
My Teenage
Romcom..
.........SNAFU
O
When I wake up, I see a box
None see it as I do
The snow turned my heart a milky white
which scatters the cold sunlight
Freezing rain covers my body,
and only the distant spring wind may dispel the veil
Take me to a summer garden
where I may grow azalea
I doubt you will
Fairy tales are rarely full of happiness
I know that all too well
But, you know,
that's where I want to go
Yoyogi Prep School
Yoyogi's
Summer Courses
All right, now it's your turn to ask a question.
A Japanese one, then.
Complete the following idiom:
"When the going gets tough..."
"The Tokyo-Chiba line stops functioning"?
What's this supposed to be, a quiz about Chiba?
Yuigahama, you should know that these days, the trains slow down, but they never stop.
The right answer is "the tough get going".
Next up, geography.
"Name two of Chiba's specialty products."
Miso peas and boiled peas?
What, you think this prefecture has nothing but peas?
Whoa!
Oh, it's just Hikki.
I thought a weirdo just started talking to me out of the blue.
You got invited to this study group too, Hachiman?
What's with that "Oh crap, someone we didn't invite showed up!" expression you have there?
We didn't invite you, though.
Do you need something?
Stop trying to say things for the sole purpose of hurting someone.
What's that?
Oh, I'm researching summer courses.
Oh wow.
Are you already preparing for your entrance exams?
I'm sure all college-bound students start preparing around now.
I'm also trying to get a prep school scholarship.
Scrap?
Scholarship.
Prep schools have started exempting good students from paying fees.
If I get a scholarship and have my parents pay my tuition fees,
all that money will be mine.
That's just a scam.
So evil.
I'm not hurting anyone, so what's the big deal?
Oh, Bro!
Komachi.
What're you doing here?
Well, a friend asked me for advice.
Oh, hello!
I'm Hikigaya Komachi.
Thanks for taking care of my brother.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Totsuka Saika, his classmate.
Wow, you're so cute.
Right, Bro?
Yeah. He's a guy, though.
Surely you jest.
Wait, really?
Y-Yeah.
I'm a guy.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Hikki's classmate, Yuigahama Yui.
Hello!
Pleased to meet—
Can I introduce myself now?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yukinoshita Yukino.
I'm neither Hikigaya's classmate nor his friend.
It's regrettable, but I guess I'm an acquaintance?
What exactly do you regret? And why a question?
Um...
I'm Kawasaki Taishi.
Hikigaya and I go to the same cram school.
My elder sister's a second year in Soubu High, just like all of you.
Her name's Kawasaki Saki.
Black lace!
Oh, I know Kawasaki!
She's kinda scary.
Isn't she your friend?
Well, we've talked.
Actually, don't ask a girl those kinds of questions.
They're hard to answer.
I don't think I've ever seen Kawasaki acting friendly with someone.
Anyway, Taishi's sister has become quite the delinquent recently.
She comes home late and stuff,
so he asked me for advice on how he can get her back to normal.
When did this happen?
Recently.
Ever since she started going to Soubu High.
She was super-serious and kind back in middle school.
That means she changed once she became Hikigaya's classmate.
Hey, why're you saying it like I'm the cause?
What am I, a virus?
I said nothing of the sort.
You have a persecution complex, Hikigerma.
You said it!
You just said germ!
Just a slip of the tongue.
It's the Hikigerma!
Tag, you're it!
Too bad. I had a barrier up just now.
Barriers mean nothing to the Hikigerma.
"Barriers mean nothing?"
Just how powerful is the Hikigerma?!
But y'know...
You say she comes home late at night, but how late is late?
I go home pretty late too.
Well, she comes home like after five and stuff...
Isn't that more like early morning?
Don't your parents say anything to her?
They both work, and I have a younger brother and sister too,
so they don't yell at her too much.
"Family reasons", huh?
They're everywhere.
Very well.
Are you planning on doing something?
Taishi's the younger brother of Kawasaki Saki, a student at our school.
What's more, he wants help regarding Kawasaki Saki herself.
I believe this falls under the Volunteers Club's activities.
I thought about it
and came to the conclusion that rather than having someone else fix them for her,
Kawasaki should solve her problems herself.
Well, duh.
What exactly are we gonna do, though?
Do you know about animal therapy?
So...
What are you gonna use my cat for?
We're going to bring out Kawasaki's gentle side by having her interact with an animal.
She'll definitely pick it up if she thinks it's cute.
Oh, come on. She's not some sort of prehistoric school gang leader.
I decided on each of our roles.
I want you to take your positions.
Meow.
Meow. Meow.
What on earth are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Weren't you just talking to little old Kamakura—
More importantly, I'm sure I asked you to be on standby.
Can't you even do something so simple?
I'd taken your incompetence into account,
but to be quite honest, I had no idea it'd be this bad.
Her eyes are telling me I'm dead if I say another word.
You're worse than an elementary school child.
How can I make it any clearer to you?
Hey, Komachi.
What's up—
Hey, Bro.
This is Taishi. I just borrowed Hikigaya's—
Don't you dare call me "Bro"!
Why'd you hang up?!
I'm busy.
Busy waiting for your sister.
Well, about your plan...
You see, my sister is allergic to cats.
There are things you can't talk to your parents about because they're too close.
Maybe she could to talk to another adult about it?
Kawasaki.
Do you need something?
I hear you've been going home late recently.
What have you been doing and where?
Who'd you hear that from?
I need to maintain client confidentiality.
Answer my question.
Does it really matter where I go?
I'm not causing anyone any trouble—
But you might in the future.
You're in high school.
Did it never occur to you to consider your parents' feelings?
Wait.
You've never been a parent, teach.
How would you know how they feel?
Huh?
You're single and all.
You should worry more about your future than mine.
Like getting married and stuff.
I feel so sorry for her.
I'm going home.
Someone marry her already, please.
She changed for the worse, right?
So if she changed again, it'd be for the better.
And how do we get her to change?
There's only one reason a girl would change!
And that's love.
Hey there.
You look sleepy.
Do you work late or something?
Don't take too much on at once.
Thanks for your concern.
Hey...
You don't have to pretend to be tough, you know.
Oh, thanks, but no thanks.
Uh...
I think I got rejected.
Well...
Good work.
Don't laugh!
Nah, it's all right.
I don't mind.
I am not your Bro.
Huh?
What are you on about?
Look, Bro.
Apparently, a weird store gave Taishi's sister a phone call!
Romcom
}SNAFU
My Teenage
O
Romcom
SNAFU
My Teenage
Basically, she got a call from the manager
of Angel something-something, right?
Yeah.
I checked it out,
and there are only two places in Chiba City that have
"Angel" in their name and operate until early morning.
And this is one of those places?
Maid Café Angel
I don't really know much about these things.
What's a "maid café" like?
Neither do I, so I called someone who does.
Ahem!
'Tis finally my turn to shine!
Oh god...
Why are you making that face when you asked me to come?
Just thinking about dealing with you is giving me a headache.
Shut up and follow me.
The maids will be fawning over you in no time.
Fawning...
What?
I kinda don't like this.
More like, y'know, this is a place guys go to!
What are we supposed to do here?
Looks like ladies are welcome here too.
o
Ladies
welcome!
Dress up as
a maid
Ladies
welcome!
Welcome Byack,
Woof
Maid Café Angel
Welcome byack, Master, woof!
Th-Thanks for waiting,
M-Master.
Does it look good on me?
Wow!
You look so cute, Yuigahama!
Don't you agree, Hachiman?
Oh, uh, yeah.
I see.
Thanks.
You're just a girl in a maid outfit!
You lack the soul!
I'd much rather....
Wh-What?
Master.
Yukinon, oh my gosh!
You look amazing!
You're so pretty!
Thanks.
Anyway,
it looks like Kawasaki isn't here.
Did you check it out?
Her name wasn't on the work schedule.
Considering they called her place,
I don't think she's using an alias either.
Strange.
What is?
A cold, aloof girl was supposed to work in secret and go,
"Welcome back, Maspurr."
"What are you doing here?!"
That's how it was supposed—no, destined to go!
What the hell are you on about?
Let's go to the other place.
At the top floor of Hotel Royal Okura,
lies "Angel Ladder".
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Where are the other two?
They said the dress code's too much for them.
I see.
Oh, get this!
Yukinon's place had, like, a million of these dresses!
And she lives alone!
Seriously, Yukinon. Who are you?
You're blowing things out of proportion.
I just have these because sometimes, I get the chance to wear them.
Normally, people wouldn't even get the chance to.
Man, is this for real?!
Stop gawking like a tourist.
Stand up straight, with your chest out.
And pull your chin in.
Kawasaki.
I'm sorry,
but who are you, again?
Not even his classmates remember what he looks like.
That's Hikigaya for you.
Yukinoshita...
H-Hey.
Yuigahama.
Then is he from Soubu High too?
Yep.
Well? What are you doing here?
Don't tell me you're on a date with that.
No way.
If you're talking about this thing to my right,
there's a line, and you just crossed it.
You two are the ones quarreling here.
Could you stop randomly hurting me in the process?
Your brother's been worried about you since you started coming home so late.
I've noticed people getting up in my business lately.
You guys are to blame, huh?
I don't know what Taishi said, but don't let it bother you.
Stay out of this.
Cinderella's magic runs out at midnight,
but yours will run out now.
If my magic does run out,
the only thing waiting for me is a happy ending, don't you think?
I don't know about that, you little mermaid.
I think only a bad ending awaits you.
Hey, what are these two even saying?
We can't work late at our age.
Basically, Yukinoshita's implying that Kawasaki's lying about her age.
Oh. Why doesn't she just say that, then?
You have no intention to quit?
None.
Hey, Kawasaki.
I work when I, like, don't have any money too,
but I don't lie about my age.
I just need money. That's all.
I get that, but come on...
There's no way a guy who goes around saying "to work is to lose" would "get" it.
She overheard that, huh?
You don't take life seriously enough.
I'm not working because I want money to goof off with.
Don't group me with the other idiots.
Also, you guys are acting all high and mighty here,
but can you cough up the money for me?
Can you handle what my parents couldn't?
W-Well...
That's enough.
If you bark any more...
Hey, your father's a member of the prefectural diet, isn't he?
How could someone so well off understand anything about me?
Hey!
Yukinon's family has nothing to do with what we're talking about right now!
Then my family has nothing to do with it either.
W-Well yeah, but Yukinon...
I just dropped my glass, that's all.
It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Let's just leave.
Kawasaki.
We need to talk about Taishi.
Let me have some of your time tomorrow morning.
I'll be at the Wac at 5:30 AM.
What?
I'll tell you what it's about when you come see me.
Later.
Wait.
That's not enough money.
So I have to pay for myself, huh?
Taishi.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I should be asking you that.
Sis, what have you doing until five in the morning?
It's none of your business.
Kawasaki.
Let me guess why you're working and why you need the money.
Taishi,
has anything changed since you entered your third year of middle school?
I started going to cram school, and that's about it.
Oh.
So she wanted to cover her brother's fees.
That's not it.
Huh?
He's been going to cram school since April,
which means the Kawasakis already took care of his tuition fees.
I get it now.
It's not just Taishi that needs his tuition fees covered, right?
Our school's geared toward getting its students into college,
so a lot of people start focusing on that once they get into their second year.
They start thinking seriously about summer courses and the like.
Sis...
Like I said, you don't need to know.
I wanna go to college,
but I don't wanna cause any problems for you or our parents because of that.
Um, can I say something?
Our parents both work too.
I once ran away from home when I was a kid because I hated coming back to an empty house.
It wasn't my parents, but my brother who came to pick me up then.
And he's been coming home before me ever since then.
I'm really grateful to him for that.
He just comes home early because he has no friends, right?
Hey, how'd you know that?
Are you Yukipedia or something?
Oh no, I'm well aware of that.
I just thought this'd be a nicer way to put it.
So what's your point?
Just like how you don't want to cause any problems for your family,
Taishi doesn't want to cause any problems for you either.
As a younger sibling myself, it'd make me happy if you understood that.
Yeah, something like that, I guess.
Hey, Kawasaki...
Do you know what a scholarship is?
Is that what you call "siblings"?
Depends on the people involved.
You could also call them your closest strangers.
Yeah.
That I understand.
Oh, yeah.
Looks like you met up with her after all.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Y'know, the girl with the sweets.
Good for you.
You broke your leg and got to know a cute girl like Yui in return.
What'd she just say?
Yuigahama was the girl with the sweets?
She was the owner of the dog I saved on the day of the entrance ceremony?
What's wrong, Bro?
Nothing.
Wanna buy some bread on the way home?
'Kay!
Field Trip Course
And that's the end of the field trip.
You're free to go.
Hikki!
You're late!
Everyone else left for the restaurant already.
Aren't you gonna go?
Huh?
Oh, well, I was kinda, like, waiting for you...
I'd feel bad leaving you behind and stuff.
You're so nice, Yuigahama.
You don't need to worry about me, though.
Huh?
I only saved your dog by chance.
I'd probably be a loner even if that accident hadn't happened.
There's absolutely no need for you to worry about me.
Sorry.
I know you went out of your way for me.
But you don't have to do this anymore.
If you're being nice to me because you're worried,
then don't bother.
Oh, how should I put it?
It's not really like that, y'know.
Yuigahama's an extremely nice girl.
And she'll probably stay nice until the very end.
You idiot.
I hate nice girls.
Just exchanging greetings with them will get them on your mind.
Start texting each other, and your heart will be set a flutter.
If they call you, you're done for.
Enjoy staring at your logs and grinning like a fool.
However, I won't get fooled again.
That's what your kind calls kindness.
If you're nice to me, you're also nice to others.
I always end up nearly forgetting that.
Reality is cruel,
so I'm sure lies are a form of kindness.
Thus, I say kindness itself is also a lie.
I always ended up with these expectations.
And I always ended up these misunderstandings.
And before I knew it, I stopped hoping.
A highly-trained loner is once bitten, twice shy.
As a veteran on this battlefield of life,
I've gotten used to losing.
That's why I'll always...
hate nice girls.
He Goes Back To The Path He Originally Followed
I heard laughter in the distance,
but it faded away
Rather than laugh it off,
I'd like to drown in silence,
and frozen in time,
lament my misfortune
Be honest and tell me it was all a lie,
before the sea swallows the last lights of dusk
I was able to go back
to our wonderful days
Now I am all alone with you again
Hello, hello, alone
I had high hopes for her, though.
It's not like Yuigahama quit.
That doesn't mean anything if she doesn't show up.
I had no idea what Yuigahama liked or what her hobbies were, did I?
I had no idea
what Yuigahama liked,
did I?
Oh,
I'm sorry.
......I think I got a bit
......carried away.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I think I got a bit carried away.
I wanna talk to you about this properly.
You don't have to
care about me.
You don't have to care about me anymore.
So, this is the end.
...Idiot
Idiot.
Next Episode:
His and Her Beginning Finally Comes to an End
"His and Her Beginning Finally Comes to an End".