This isn't the first time you've experienced today—July 22nd.
To Ajiro Shinpei
Nagumo Ryuunosuke
One could say you've repeated it multiple times.
Which means you must be a time traveler.
Yes.
I see.
But it most likely wasn't me that made the reveal.
Have you met my younger brother?
...show for you today!
Today, we’re coming to you live from Kinokawa,
where we’ll be showcasing seasonal delicacies from Wakayama!
There’s a lot of wonderful things to cover, so let’s hurry on over and—
You're up, Ryuunosuke.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
3rd loop
Tuesday, July 24th
Wake up
Eat breakfast (egg sandwich)
Help at restaurant
with Mio
Lunch service ends
Think in my room about
what to do
Read through a few
of Ms. Nagumo's books
Forbid Mio from going
out alone
Toki comes over to do
Mio's yukata.
Sou and Mio come to my room.
Mio, Sou, and Toki and I go
to the summer festival
I see.
That was an interesting read.
Enemy
I could make this the plot for my next novel.
My brain's gettin' all jumbled up.
I can't keep up with this.
You believe me because of this book, isn't that right?
Because Swamp Man is a true story.
The Swamp Man that appears in this story acts just like the Shadows.
The protagonist is even named after your real name.
I met a certain Shadow on this island fourteen years ago.
It killed my family.
That experience is precisely why I believe you.
Wh-What happened?
That I cannot say.
It involves my true identity, you see.
If I tell you and the Shadows copy you, they will learn my secret.
The Shadows target families.
Hizuru's destined to be chased by them with her return to the island.
Family?
I see! So that's why Ushio, Mio, and I were targeted!
No, wait a sec...
What about Alan?
You need not worry.
I've already taken care of his Shadow.
His Shadow cannot be reborn now.
It's like the measles. Ya gain immunity.
If ya catch the Shadow Sickness and kill yer shadow,
it'll never come back again.
S-So if yer Shadow gets taken out,
then y'can never be copied again?
Damn straight. And I've got this immunity,
so my Shadow can no longer exist.
Whether ya believe me or not, I don't care.
So are ya not immune, Miss Nagumo?
Why'd ya come back to the island if yer in danger?
That I can't say, either. But...
I'm here to save you.
That much is certain.
Although, perhaps you'd be better off not trusting me.
Oh! No, please!
What's your plan?
Our time limit is 54 hours.
Everyone will disappear at the summer festival.
There was this Shadow with four arms,
and it felt like it was controlling all the other Shadows.
My step-sister, Mio, is in danger.
Would ya mind helpin' me defeat her Shadow first?
According to your notes from earlier,
her Shadow will make an appearance in front of the Kofune restaurant at 9 PM tonight.
Correct.
Very well, but there is one problem that must be taken care of first.
The Kobayakawas, right?
Hm?
Y'all will fail if ya do as ya have so far.
What?
I've seen it.
Shiori's Shadow was at the shrine grounds on the 24th.
So you're saying I will fail to eliminate Shiori's Shadow?
Yes, so please let me come with ya!
That Shadow will taste my vengeance!
And if the worst outcome happens and we fail again, I want to know why!
Very well.
But I alone will enter the house.
What's going on with her?
She's just been listening to something.
That's 'cause he ain't got Hizuru's memories.
What?
Got it, Sis.
Among them is the specialty in Momoyama, Arakawa Peaches,
which are well regarded nationally.
They're currently in season.
Oh, Hizuru!
Sorry to intrude during dinner—
I mean, pardon me.
But since I'm here, I thought I'd give you the souvenir I brought.
Aw, ya didn't have to do that!
Let her in.
Come on in.
Pardon me, then.
My husband Tatsuo and my daughter Shiori.
Why, hello!
Make yourself at home.
Sorry Asako, but do you mind if I open my luggage here?
Not at all!
Say, Hizuru, why don't ya have dinner with us?
I'd love to catch up.
Um, this is just a guess, but...
What is it?
Does Miss Nagumo have a dual personality?
No thanks. I'll actually be heading home soon.
The Shadow's real body lays flat on a surface.
Attacking the 3D version won't damage it, but...
Mama.
it relies on the 3D body's eyes to see me.
If they realize I know how to kill Shadows,
they'll be on guard and keep their distance.
It would be best to take them out all at once.
Asako!
Only lured in one, eh?
Dual personalities?
Why wouldja think that?
She mentioned that I met her younger brother.
So that means—
Close, but not quite right.
Is she gonna be okay by herself?
We're to wait here.
Ryuunosuke has the power to fight Shadows.
Ryuunosuke?
Yeah, he's strong.
I'm gonna give it to ya straight.
I dunno about these loops or whatever.
If you go inside, the reason Kobayakawa Shiori's Shadow gets away might change.
Hizuru!
She's trying to find out exactly why this plan fails.
Listen, she trusted ya.
And ya said she wouldn't die today.
If that was a lie, I swear I'll make ya pay.
Right.
I remember she was strong.
Was that Ryuunosuke?
Nezu, could you tell me more about this Ryuunosuke fellow?
Well, if ya look into it, yew'll find the answers soon enough.
Hizuru had a twin brother.
That was Ryuunosuke.
She found his corpse on
Mt. Takanosu fourteen years ago.
I heard Hizuru scream, so I came runnin'.
It was a terrible sight to see.
Papa? Mama?
No... But why?
Why'd ya kill them?
He was eaten.
There were bite marks all over his body.
Everyone made a big fuss about it, sayin' it was wild dogs.
But Hizuru said it was murder.
The bites served as a distraction from the strangle marks on his neck.
Did I miss?
No, I know I felt contact!
No one believed her.
Then they cremated the remains the same day.
Nezu, that sounds just like what happened to Ushio.
Yep, sure does, don't it?
It might all be connected.
These monsters live on this island.
I've vowed to exterminate every last one from this island, even if it costs me my life.
Are ya prepared to do the same, Shinpei?
Yes!
Yer dangerous.
Ya know how to kill Shadows.
Are ya with that traitor?
And ya were able to follow Papa's and Mama's movements.
If ya can move faster than Shadows, are ya even human?
Copy me... Make a Shadow...
and ask it...
You cocky little...
Okay, I will.
After I kill ya.
Ya rotten old hag!
Ya stabbed yerself to get me?!
Was the wound too shallow?
Still, it's strange. My first strike with the hammer should've been lethal.
Something's weird about that Shadow.
Sorry for hurting your body, Sis.
So she's on the third floor.
It's just like Sis said.
Asako and Tatsuo are eliminated. Shiori got away and she's on the third floor.
I'll chase after her, but things may turn out as Shinpei said.
I-Is that from Miss Nagumo?
Asako and Tatsuo are eliminated. Shiori got away and she's on the third floor.
I'll chase after her, but things may turn out as Shinpei said.
Change to plan B.
Plan B!
It's our turn.
Here.
Why don't ya show me just how prepared ya are.
Summer Time Rendering
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Third floor. Went through the north window.
Roger.
Third floor, went through north window
Diary
Kobayakawa Shiori
It's pointless.
After you unleash that light to copy me, you'll be unable to move for a few seconds.
It seems scanning a whole human's worth of information takes a lot out of you.
Do you really think I'll miss that opening?
The moment you try to copy me,
I'll kill you.
This time for sure.
How boring.
Bye-bye.
Plan B!
I missed the third shot!
Bring it on!
What?!
Yer gonna turn tail and run?!
Damn!
Shinpei!
N-No...
Did ya do it?!
Ya sicken me. Let go, idiot!
Did ya kill Ushio?!
Ow!
That's enough. Step aside, Shinpei.
It can't move a finger now.
One or two ain't enough.
Ya gotta pierce the Shadow in three spots.
Then they'll be locked to the spot.
Meaning ya could capture one!
C-Capture?
Was that the point of plan B?
Yep.
Y-Ya never told me!
Obviously not. I never trusted ya.
Still, that's amazing. We captured Shiori!
Now we can change the future!
It seems it can't withdraw from its 3D body if you catch it like this.
This is a new discovery, Shinpei.
Thanks to you, it didn't escape.
We would've failed without you, no?
Yer young, but it seems ya got stones.
Ya got gumption.
What's so funny?
This one's different from the other Shadows.
We went with plan B to learn more about it.
How's it different?
First, answer Shinpei's question.
Did you kill Kofune Ushio and birth her Shadow?
Oh, Ushio, huh?
Yup. I killed her.
I wrung her neck until she stopped breathing.
Why'd ya kill her?
Why Ushio?!
What're y'all after?!
Killing people and replacing them, what's yer goal?
The end.
The end is coming this summer.
So I'm leaving.
I'm taking my family and leaving.
What?
What the hell are ya talking about?
Please don't act so scared.
I think you've misunderstood something, Shinpei.
The human was killed by a Shadow, yes.
The Shadow copied me perfectly. Body, mind, and memories.
That makes me Kobayakawa Shiori.
I've just been reborn.
Don't lie! Yer not Shiori!
Ya killed Shiori and her family!
Shinpei, join me in becoming a Shadow.
Come with me.
Whaddya say? Be my big brother.
That's enough of that.
Converse with a Shadow for too long,
and you'll only be misled.
Damn it!
It was a tough one for sure.
What happened to Asako and Tatsuo?
They were normal. One blow with the hammer was all it took.
"For a Shadow to die, damage that would be lethal to a human must be dealt to its flat form."
Either my sister's hypothesis was wrong,
or there's not enough data to draw a conclusion yet.
What it said was odd, though.
Going home with its family or whatever.
The copies...
The copies act like they're the original humans.
Shiori did mention being reborn.
What's the difference between a perfect copy and the original?
That was the theme of Swamp Man, wasn't it, Ryuunosuke?
What do you make of this?
I told him about the dual personalities.
I see.
Well, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Minakata Ryuunosuke,
Minakata Hizuru's younger brother.
Um, just so I know, was it you that wrote these novels?
Oh, no! My sister is the writer.
I don't have a way with words like she does.
I come to the surface when my sister is forced to deal with things she dislikes, like interviews or meetings.
I take it you've read some of my sister's books, Shinpei?
Huh? Some? Well...
He's a freak! A Nagumo freak!
Oh, is that so?
None of this was mentioned in the recording.
My sister is probably being bashfu—
Miss Nagumo! What are ya doin'?!
Try not to get the wrong idea, boy.
I'm not being bashful,
and I'm certainly not hiding anything!
I simply saw you were getting off topic and decided to cut in like so!
Yer nose! It's bleeding!
Ya okay?
Of course not! My vocabulary is weakening!
So she goes back to Hizuru when her hair's untied?
Don't let the Shadows' words move you, Ajiro Shinpei.
You musn't falter, even if they show up looking like your friends, relatives, or any of your loved ones.
Save the philosophical talk of copies and originals for after everything is finished.
We were too late for the Kobayakawas.
But it's not too late for you.
Can you really kill Mio's Shadow?
We'll wait outside until it's time.
Let's exchange numbers.
Let us know if anything different happens.
Try to act as similarly as you can to how you did previously and keep a close eye on things.
You will be the observer.
Right.
I'm home!
Mio, sorry I'm late...
Oh, welcome home, Shin.
It can't be...
It stings!
I hate onions! My eyes!
Huh?
I can't see a thing!
What? Yer cookin'?
Can't ya tell?
There were onions and chicken in the fridge,
so I was gonna heat them up!
Whoa! That's dangerous!
This makes no sense.
Mio's never tried to cook before!
Why're ya...
Ya seemed down this morning, Shin,
so I thought maybe I should make something.
I see. Thanks.
But leave the rest to me.
This is too dangerous for me to watch.
Don't worry. I'm fine, okay?
I-I'm gonna go wash my face!
Thank goodness Mio's not a Shadow.
And I can still turn this into curry.
She can be so cute sometimes.
Hold on a second, me!
Different developments are bad!
Oh, that's right. Because of me,
Mio's actions have already changed.
I'll make the curry.
That's how I did it last time.
Well, Miss Nagumo and Nezu are armed and waiting outside, so things are already "different."
I should try my best to keep things the same that don't have to do with killing Shadows.
If I change anything, others' actions will change too. There's a link.
If that happens, my knowledge of the future will no longer be useful.
Man, Mio, talk about a stomach rumble.
Are ya that hun...
gry?
Yup!
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Memento