Are you going anywhere for winter break?
Yeah. I'm visiting my mom's family on the 2nd.
Let's visit the shrine on New Year's together, okay?
'Kay!
Hey, how does a Christmochi tree sound?
A what?
A Christmas tree made of mochi.
We can mix in some mugwort to make it green like a fir tree,
and decorate its tip with a star-shaped
.piece of mochi sprinkled with soy flour.
What size would it be?
Small enough to fit in your hand.
It could end up as Tamaya's specialty!
Mochitree!
Tamako!
Whoops.
See you later, Midori, Kanna!
Usagiyama
Market
Ow!
The sky was so blue.
The ocean was blue too.
Some saury for me, please.
Thank you!
Tamako, take some bream head with you too.
Name
Kitashirakawa Tamako
The flowers were so beautiful.
Tuberose Field
Two blocks of firm tofu, please.
Sure thing.
Just Meat
Freshly fried! Freshly fried!
I hear ya.
They smelled so good
that I felt sleepy.
Then I felt cold.
Then there was light.
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
Yo!
Oh my.
Today's another cold one, isn't it?
Did school let out for the holidays today, Tamako?
Yeah.
Let me put my stuff away.
Go ahead.
These are pretty.
They just got in today.
Really?
Apparently their fragrance really comes out at night.
Wow!
Huh?
Hmm?
Oh no!
Are you all right, Tamako?
Can you breathe?
My face! My face!
That startled me!
Oh my, what's this?
Was it mixed in with the flowers?
Is that a bird?
Is it?
I'm sorry, Mr. Bird.
Did it hu—
You shouldn't...
Huh?
...fall for me just yet.
It talked...
didn't it?
Tamako!
Eek!
Huh?
Episode 1
She's the Cute Girl from the Mochi Shop
That surprised me, my girl.
Sorry.
Why are you on my head?
Are you feeling shy, my girl?
How can you talk like that?
No need to flatter me.
But I'm not!
I'm scared!
And I want you to get off me!
Hey there, Tamako. Did you get a pet bird?
No, I didn't!
Oh, that's a nice bird!
No, it's not!
Do that thing again, Tamako.
Here we—
Huh?
Welcome!
Thank you very much!
Book of Birds
Wow, they're pretty cute.
This is why your shop's such a joke!
Book of Birds
Hm?
The hell'd you just say, bastard?!
Mochizou!
Oh hey, Tamako.
What's up with that hat?
It's not a hat.
So they're at it again.
Yeah, they are.
Sheesh, our dads...
Don't act so high and mighty just because you set up shop three days before I did.
You think this is all a game, huh?
Does tradition mean nothin' to ya?
What the hell is that monstrosity?
"Rice Cake Oh! Zee."
Lame!
This sign's so freakin' lame!
Oh wow, that's cool.
You changed Oojiya's sign?
That's Tamako for you.
Now it's time for mochi to take the global stage!
They'd call them "rice cakes" in English.
Mochi's just mochi, dammit!
This is why I hate stubborn,
old-fashioned craftsmen like you!
What'd you just say?!
Excuse me.
You really like doing that, don't you?
Huh? My head feels lighter!
Tamaya
I'm really sorry.
That must've hurt.
Maybe we should put some ice on it inside.
Welcome back.
Hi, Grandpa.
Want one?
Gently. Gently.
Grandpa.
Hm?
Why do we run a mochi shop?
Who knows?
It was started a long time ago by my grandfather.
Why do you ask, Anko?
I keep telling you to call me An!
But Anko's a cute name.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I'm home.
Hi there, Anko.
Welcome back!
Oh hey, it's Mocchi!
Welcome.
Hey!
You brat! Did you think you could just sneak in during the commotion?!
Er, uh, that's—
What's that? A bird?
I think so,
but I found it at the florist's,
so maybe it's a flower?
Perish the thought!
It woke up!
Thank goodness!
I'm a noble retainer to the royal court.
I left my country in search of a bride for my prince,
but I somehow lost consciousness during my travels,
and when I came to, you were in front of me.
Then you went all-out in courting me, didn't you?
It's talking...
I have an important task to complete. I must find a bride for the prince,
Creepy!
but as a special exception, I'll allow you
to remain by my side for just a little while.
Rejoice, my girl.
What?!
You sneezed at me, remember?
With all your might.
Yeah...
Among my kind, the females sneeze as a show of courtship.
I've recognized your intent, my girl, so I'll show you my wings. They're my pride and joy.
Behold!
Wai—
"Behold," my ass!
How long's this bird gonna talk?
What can I say? I'm very refined.
Let's throw it away, Tamako.
How rude!
Since when can birds talk?
Do not treat me as some mere fowl!
My name is—
This bird's gonna introduce itself now?
Like I said, I'm no ordinary bird. I am...
Dela Mochidis Gusting.
I dare you to say that again.
I'm Dela Mochidis Gusting.
Mochi ain't disgusting!
Dad!
Don't you dare call me "Dad"!
I'm sorry!
Anyway, where on Earth am I?
The people here are most strange,
and it's awfully cold too.
I'll go take a bath!
Can't you use our bath once in a while?!
Yeah, yeah.
It's cold!
Look, you can see your breath! It's all white!
Are you going to keep that bird, Tamako?
I'm not sure yet.
I know you bought a book on birds.
So you found out, huh?
I've never seen a bird like that.
It's really unusual.
Usa Bath
And it doesn't have a very nice name.
Mochidis Gusting, right?
We should change it.
Oh, Mochizou!
Tamako!
What a coincidence. Are you heading home now?
No. Actually, I just got here.
Really? You look kind of wet.
Oh, right! Mochizou, my birthday's coming up!
I-Is that so?
Will you get me a present this year?
You've never given me one.
Wh-What would you like?
She's gone!
I-It's freezing!
Bird! What the heck are you doing?
I-It's f-freezing...
You all right?
Wh-What is this place?
What do people do here?
It's a bathhouse.
You wash your body and warm yourself up—
In you go, my boy!
Hey, Mochizou!
You're back?
Tamako—
Shh! Quiet!
So this is a bathhouse.
Don't talk!
You wanna knock the old man off his chair?!
You dare reject who I am?! You impud—
I'll throw you away.
Whoa! What was that?!
What do you mean?
Didn't that bird talk just now?
I've dreamed of being able to talk to animals ever since I was a kid!
My name is Dela Mochidis Gusting.
I'm a retainer to the royal court.
Mochizou, that's incredible!
How much do you charge for a bird?
This place is so warm!
It smells nice too!
A blue sky!
You tricked me?!
I like you, my boy.
Mochizou?
Wh-What?
I can hear that bird's voice for some reason...
Oh, yeah.
My girl?
I'm right he—
Whoa?!
Oh wow, this is...
Looks like it likes this place!
It has a cute side to—
It's gone?!
Where'd it go?!
Oops, I slipped!
Hey!
Tamako, cover yourself!
Huh? What?!
Dumbass.
Tamako Market
Tamaya
Mochi! Mochi! Tamaya's Mochi!
Pipe down!
Delicious mochi!
Thirty sweet bean mochi for Mr. Kimoto, right?
Yeah.
You have club activities, don't you, Tamako? You can go.
It's fine. I'll just make the thirty we need for Mr. Kimoto.
I'm off!
Hmm?
Tamako...
Got it. Hit the other cheek too.
Ow! What are you doing?
My boy,
are you a pervert?
No way!
By the way, why am I sharing a bedroom with you?
Because you peeked at the women's bath.
You're too dangerous to leave at Tamako's place.
So I...
Open the window.
Huh?
Fare thee well, my boy!
Hold it right there, dammit!
You're really good, Midori.
I'm falling for you!
Ah! You brought out the mochi already?
They're delicious.
They're freshly made!
It's like a picnic at Lake Tama!
Go ahead, have one.
I'll take you up on your offer.
Oh, Tamako. Got some flour on your cheek.
Thank you very much.
New Year's Eve is almost here, isn't it?
Tamako's birthday.
Is there anything you want?
Um,
a sign, maybe?
What?!
Well, Mochizou's place got a new sign yesterday.
That was one of my dad's masterpieces.
So carpenters make signs too?
I want something like that for our place!
Maybe a neon one. That way it'll really stand out.
Might be a little difficult to get you one.
We also—
Tamako!
Are you okay, Tamako?!
I'm sorry.
No, no! Don't be!
It's her fault for leaving her
forehead here in the first place.
You can say that again.
Show me.
That was head on.
I mean, the shuttlecock hit her forehead head on, right?
Oh, the captain's here.
Good morning!
We have to celebrate Tamako's birthday this year.
We'll do it when they take a break from making mochi.
Let's all sing "Happy Birthday" for her.
All right!
Bye-bye!
See you later!
So you've returned, my girl.
Yep!
Stars and Clowns
Stars and
Clowns
1F - Records
2F - Records
Coffee
Do you like riding on people's heads?
Hello!
Welcome.
Hmm...
So it's not this song either?
It's hard to find, isn't it?
What is?
There was a song my mom used to sing a lot when I was a kid.
It was a really good song.
Oh?
Went something like this.
It's not this one, though.
It's really hard to find.
I want to know how the rest of it goes, so I've been looking for it at this record store for a while now.
Wouldn't it be better to just ask your mother?
It would.
I'd love to, but when I was in fifth grade, my mom—
Cry upon my breast, my girl!
My feathers will wipe your tears away!
I'm fine.
Anyway, I want everyone to eat the mochi that my mom loved so much.
After all, I am a mochi maker's daughter.
One Einspänner Gold Blend coffee.
Thank you!
It's bitter!
Coffee's supposed to be bitter.
It symbolizes the bitterness of life.
Thank you!
This won't do!
I'm on a journey!
I have an important mission to complete!
I need to leave before New Year's Day!
New Year's Eve.
Thanks for the food!
Now, let's experiment with some new mochi recipes!
Out of the question!
Today's New Year's Eve. Sorry.
Oh no! I forgot!
Today's the busiest day of the year for us!
It's mochi hell.
But aside from that, Tamako...
What?
He's really let himself go, hasn't he?
He's pretty heavy.
You should just change your name to Mochidel Icious.
No can do. Mochidis Gusting is a noble name.
Anyway, you help out too, Anko.
Let's head to the shop.
Huh?!
Anko'll do it if you call her An.
Didn't you just call yourself Anko?
Oh, Anko. Your cheeks are like mochi! So cute!
I'm an exception!
An.
A weird bird called me An!
Hey! Don't make my daughter cry, Mochidel Icious!
It's Mochidis Gusting!
Change your name.
I refuse!
Three rectangular mochi! Thank you, come again!
Come again!
These special New Year boxes aren't selling at all.
I thought it was a great idea.
People obviously prefer the actual New Year delicacies, Gohei.
I have to give it to her this year.
Her birthday present, I mean.
I-Idiot.
Tamako and Anko's room
Great. My feathers look good now.
Oh crap. I'm too heavy.
Will I really be able to cross the seas like this?!
No, it doesn't matter. I decided to leave.
Besides, if I stay here any longer...
I'll be in danger!
Real danger!
No!
Express your gratitude with mochi
It's over!
Now we can relax and wait for the new year!
I'm hungry!
Guess I'll make some New Year's soba noodles.
Listen up, everyone!
I know this is hard for you to take, but I'm leaving.
Huh?
Today marks the date of mine departure, my girl!
"Mine departure"?
Meetings are always followed by farewells.
Don't cry. I understand how you feel, though.
Crying is not enough to make a man change his mind.
Don't stop me! Don't stop me, my girl!
I see.
Take care, okay?
Since you're here, you might as well eat before you leave.
Freshly pounded soft mochi.
You haven't had these yet, right?
They're the best ones.
Here.
How is it?
Huh? Mr. Bird!
All right!
This year...
Let's give her our presents.
Hey, Mochizou!
What's that, a present?
No, well...
Get a hold of yourself!
Oh no! Someone call a vet!
What's wrong?
What happened?
Choking on mochi! Gonna die!
Hang in there, Tamako!
Tamako!
No, I didn't mean me.
Gimme that!
It came out!
Mochidel Icious!
Th-Thank goodness!
That was so scary!
I'm so sorry!
And so, for some reason, I wound up in the shopping district of some unknown town.
And then, for some other reason, I met a girl from a mochi shop along the way.
Thank goodness.
Well then, I wish you all a happy New Year.
Happy New Year!
Oops!
Oh dear!
Ah!
Ack!
I did it again!
My birthday's over.
I'm sorry. We just get so busy every year.
Nah, I keep forgetting every year too.
Your phone's blinking, Sis.
Inbox
Kanna
Midori
Many Happy Returns
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
Inbox
Kanna
Midori
Many Happy Returns
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
Inbox
Kanna
Many Happy Returns
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Oh, it's from Kanna!
Inbox
Kanna
Many Happy Returns
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
Kanna
Many Happy Returns
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Carpenter
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Carpenter
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Carpenter
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Carpenter
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Carpenter
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Carpenter
Inbox
We can get married now!
Waiting for your proposal,
Kanna.
Carpenter
Inbox
She must've tried really hard.
Kanna
Midori
Many Happy Returns
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
Inbox
Kanna
Midori
Many Happy Returns
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
You turn sixteen today,
don't you?
Inbox
Kanna
Midori
Happy Returns, Tamako!
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Inbox
Kanna
Midori
Happy Returns, Tamako!
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Inbox
Midori
Happy Returns, Tamako!
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
Midori
Happy Returns, Tamako!
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
Happy Returns, Tamako!
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
Happy Returns, Tamako!
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Wow, this is so nice.
Inbox
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
You're probably very
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
busy, so I'll wish you
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
through a text.
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
Happy Birthday, Tamako!
(>_<)
Inbox
Now if our business prospers, I'll have nothing left to complain about!
These soba noodles aren't so bad!
That's my bowl.
Looks like it'll be a while before I find a bride for my prince and return to the island.
Dela!
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
Happy New Year! Tamako here.
Mirror mochi is usually placed on top of a stand that has calligraphy paper spread out on it,
along with bitter oranges, seaweed, and false daphnes.
Apparently a lot of people make this decoration on the 28th.
Episode 2  Valentine's Day, Where the Flowers of Love Bloom
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?