Thankful to someone?
It seems I am needed!
This is a present from me!
I-I lost...
You bind him with a scarf
embedded with wires...
She's asleep!
Valentine's Fair
It's finally the season, huh?
Yes, it is.
The season that I want winter to end soon
and hope I can save on my heating bill.
That wasn't what I meant...
Didn't we just have this conversation?
It's almost Valentine's!
Valentine's is an important day!
It's the day to gorge on chocolate!
That's not what Valentine's is for.
I've also heard this conversation before...
Miss Youko, do you plan
to give chocolate to anyone?
I was not planning to.
It's not a big deal.
If you're thankful to someone,
you can give some to them.
I see.
Thankful... to someone?
A Day to Gorge on Chocolate
I just remembered.
Hm?
Something happened the other day...
Oh, my.
It cannot get down from the tree.
Wh-What should I do?
It's really high up.
The tree looks thin, so it might
not take my weight if I climb it.
But, I must rescue it!
It seems I am needed!
I have more important things to do
than make these useless things.
Useless things?
So, Yamaji helped me rescue the cat.
What?
Isn't that an event that's
more fitting for me?
Event?
So, what happened to the cat?
Well, after we got it down, it ran away.
I can't believe it.
It was over, just like that?
I apologize I could not meet
your expectations.
You set off a flag for it
coming back to repay you.
Repay me?
You've heard stories of animals
who repay people for saving them.
My, if the kitten came to repay me,
it would be so cute and lovely indeed.
Like...
I got this fish for you.
Here!
Salted salmon?!
I got this cash for you, here!
Cash?!
I guess I'll let you touch
my paw pads... just this once!
So cheap!
And she gave it a personality, too!
Where's Yamaji?
Huh?
Y-Yama—
You called?
Yamaji!
Y-Yes?
Um, this might be a weird request.
If the kitten comes to repay you,
please save the moment!
I'm not sure I understand.
Please!
Teru.
Teru!
What?
Bel?!
Teru, thanks for always taking care of me!
I'm very thankful that you
took me in and were so kind to me.
So,
Here, this is a present from me!
That dream sounded like a farewell!
It's because of Miss Youko's story.
Well, it wasn't a bad dream.
Thank you very much...
That's what happened this morning.
Oh my!
Good for you, Hayama.
She was repaying you.
You're right.
Of course, the way a cat shows its love
is different from how humans show love.
Being able to understand and receive that love
shows how good of an owner you are.
Once an animal lover,
always an animal lover.
You're a model pet owner.
That's something I can't ignore.
Hayama's a model pet owner?
Now that's a very bold talk.
Then, Nishiyama, this happen
to you too, I wonder?
Eru giving you a repayment gift I mean.
Of course she has!
But, just having her by
my side is a gift in itself.
Isn't that how a pet owner should think?
Yes?
Nishiyama!
Then, why don't you two have a competition
to see who cats like more?
What?
Hayama Bel (1 year old)
Didn't you take pictures of your cat before?
Whoever takes a cuter cat picture, wins!
Stay still, Bel.
H-Hey, don't come here!
My almost-tendinitis wrists that have been holding
the camera since morning are quickly healing!
Master Beelzebub!
They're all so cute, I can't pick!
They're all best shots!
I brought my pictures.
Me, too.
Here are my best shots.
We will judge the results.
Oh, they're cute.
So cute!
They are very cute.
But, it is like comparing
two peas from the same pod.
What do you mean?!
That's not true!
Well, she is cute.
Yes, so cute!
I guess, maybe it's a tie.
Can I have this?
Yeah, let's trade.
You won't get a real competition
between two cat fans, I guess.
What was the competition for, then?
Well, we got something
out of it, so all is good.
Oh.
Well, if we want a competition...
Odagiri Futaba!
We have a competitor.
The older Tsuji sibling.
You're probably going
to challenge me, right?
I'll challenge you this time!
What?!
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo hamburg!
You're on!
Huh?
What?
They wouldn't let me in!
Is this one of the places
you're banned from?
Oh, I forgot!
You had forgotten?
They let me in.
Which means, I win by default!
Total victory for me!
Oh, yeah!
Woo-hoo! Oh, yeah!
I-I lost...
Wait a second.
Think about it carefully.
Woo-hoo! Oh yeah! Whoo!
That's not right!
They wouldn't let me in,
because I'm a bigger threat!
W-Wait a sec!
Listen to me!
Think about it seriously!
Anyway, congratulations on your win.
Oh, uh, what was your name?
Ni... Ni... Nishi-something?
How do you know my name?
He only said the "Nishi" part, though.
"Nishikawa"!
It's "Ni-shi-ka-wa"!
And it's Miss Nishikawa Youko to you.
Add the "Miss" you glutton!
Yamaji!
You be quiet!
That's pretty cool.
It's just like Sasame told me.
Oh, you heard from your sister.
Yup.
You're, uh, one of her friends, right?
What?!
Well, thanks for always
taking care of my sister.
Oh. Well... er...
It's my... pleasure...?
Miss Youko is being considerate!
Sasame!
Hm?
Guess what, I won against Odagiri!
You didn't win.
From what you said,
that doesn't count as winning.
What?!
B-But she said "congratulations."
You know, uh, Nishi... hara... kawa... tani...?
It's Nishikawa.
Right, right, Nishikawa!
And I was even polite and said "thanks
for always taking care of my sister"!
What?!
It's what a big bro would do.
I was super being an adult.
Brother, you idiot!
Huh?
Why did you say weird things to Nishikawa?!
You probably made Nishikawa feel awkward!
But, isn't what you supposed to say to friends?
Yeah, if we were friends already.
Nishikawa and I aren't that close yet.
Oh?
Wait— brother, you idiot!
We're still building our friendship!
I didn't even say any—
Hey, Sasame!
Do you have any good ideas?
When I give Yuu the chocolates,
I want it to be memorable.
Hm, memorable?
I wonder how many types of chocolates
I can eat with my allowance this year—
I'm not talking about you!
Don't you think a hand-knitted scarf
and handmade chocolate is best?
Eh, isn't that too normal?
Really?
You bind him with a scarf embedded with
wires and force-feed drugged chocolate.
Woah.
Big sister!
You're going to do it?
I'm going now.
I need to get ready.
Be careful on your way home.
Thank you!
So that's what Miss Usuda is planning?
Young Master Takezono
will have a fine Valentine's.
I also want to...
Huh?
I also want to make chocolate.
Apologies, but my hearing
has declined recently.
Chocolate!
I want to make chocolate!
Ah, I see.
You want to keep it as emergency food.
No, for Valentine's!
And who will you be giving it to?
My friends.
And, I will send a mountain
of chocolates to father, too.
You're going to hike up
a mountain with everyone?
No, I am talking about Valentine's!
Oh, Sonobe.
I want to make chocolate.
Good.
This time of year is as busy as
Christmas, so even a cat's paw—
—or rather Miss Youko's paw,
would be helpful.
Not for the shop!
I want to give homemade chocolate
to people I am thankful for.
Of course, I will not slack
on my duties here.
Miss Youko wants to make
handmade chocolate?
She will probably start off energetically,
but get exhausted because
she's not used to making sweets.
And then she'll be sick in bed, and Valentine's
will be even busier than Christmas!
That's my situation.
Please, you'll be helping me so much!
No way!
Why do I have to?
Why not ask someone else?
You're the person for the job.
What?!
You don't have anything to do
on Valentine's anyway, right?
How rude!
What are you doing?
I was asking Nishiyama to
give me a hand at the shop.
I can help!
You don't need to pay me, either!
What?
You can pay me with cakes instead.
I refuse.
I will properly pay you for your work.
Aw, too bad.
By all means, Hayama too.
As long as I don't have
to wear that maid dress.
All... right... mm, hmm...
I can't hear you!
All right, let's work hard today!
Yes!
Miss Youko didn't faint from exhaustion.
What?
Wait a second!
What's the deal with these clothes?!
Oh, good, they fit perfectly.
This isn't what we agreed on!
You didn't want to wear this maid outfit,
so I prepared a different one for you.
It's fine.
It looks good.
I agree.
I wanted to make some for you two,
too, but I didn't have enough time.
Is prepping for Valentine's that tough?
I pulled two all-nighters making
Hayama's new maid outfit.
Not my fault!
Thank you for waiting.
We will allow people to enter
in order, so please do not push.
Welcome!
I can ring you up here once you have
decided what items you would like.
Wait, why did she make me work, too?
Don't say that.
Look how busy it is.
What about that other guy?
The former butler?
My apologies!
I have my hands full with making a special
chocolate cake I'm giving to Miss Youko.
Why are you making that now?!
Excuse me, Miss Sonobe?
She's asleep!
She did say she hadn't slept for two nights.
How can she be sleeping when it's this busy?
Now, now.
Nishiyama, you're a capable woman after all.
O-Of course!
Welcome!
So easily manipulated...
I apologize for the long wait.
Don't worry.
It is Valentine's.
Keep it up!
Thank you very much!
I-It's so busy!
Sonobe.
Wake up, Sonobe!
Sonobe!
Oh, you're tired already, Hayama?
How careless.
You're amazing, Nishiyama.
Of course.
I'm just getting started.
I'm going to take a short break, then.
Wha—?!
Excuse me.
Y-Yes, right away.
As expected from a capable woman, right?
She makes life hard for herself.
Thank you very much.
One limited edition Gâteau Chocolat.
Okay, one Gâteau Chocolat.
What, it's the Tsuji siblings!
What are you doing here?
I-It's not a big deal if a guy
buys Valentine's cakes.
Yeah, it's not a big deal.
There are lots of limited edition items
during Valentine's and Christmas.
He saves up a lot of money for this!
Doesn't it take courage for a guy to buy
chocolate-flavored things around Valentine's?
I don't really care.
I get tons of chocolate at school,
so it doesn't faze me.
Wow, that unexpected.
That's right
Brother is popular at school after all.
Even in my school club,
I'm an important mascot character!
Ah...
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
Sorry.
I just wanted to see Nishiyama
working hard on the job.
Nothing interesting to see here.
Oh my, then would you like
to start working here, too?
She's awake?!
No thanks, that's not my thing.
If you agree now, I'll throw in a dessert.
"That's not my thing"?
Oh, no thank you.
Sold Out
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much for working so hard.
I got to catch up on my sleep thanks to you!
Sonobe!
Kneel!
February 14th
Yesterday was pretty tiring.
I want to try on a maid outfit sometime, too.
Maybe I'll ask Miss Sonobe next time.
Won't work.
Huh?
Miss Youko said that Miss Sonobe likes
making people who dislike it wear them.
Ah, I see.
That's why Nishiyama is a maid, too!
Nishiyama... a maid?
No way.
Sh-She asked me to wear it,
and that was the only thing she had.
I-I wasn't wearing it because I wanted to.
Ah, it makes sense now.
What are you talking about?!
I never want to wear those clothes again.
I don't like wearing it or anything!
Y-Yeah, right?
It fit you size-wise,
but it didn't look that good.
It looked like the clothes were wearing you.
You look better in more straight-cut clothes.
Y-Yeah, right, that's right.
I thought it looked pretty good on you...
D-Don't make fun of me!
Nishiyama!
I actually think that, though.
It's because you're complimenting
her when you usually don't.
Thank you for all your help yesterday.
Th-This is a thank you for everything,
including yesterday.
Here!
Oh, is this the charcoal stuff
to get rid of odors?
They're truffles!
I made them myself.
What?!
I put the gratitude I have for you
into them when I made them.
Miss Youko made these herself?
They don't melt, but they're edible.
Right?
I can do it if I try.
You're amazing, Miss Youko!
It's not melting?
Not really.
Oh, Tsuji!
Here you go.
What?!
Chocolates?
A-Are you sure?
Yes, please accept them.
Nishikawa... gave me chocolates!
Wh-Wh-What to do?
What to do about gift's cost?
Two times? Three times more?
More?!
Like a house or something?!
Here, for you too, Yamaji.
What?!
I get some... too?!
Thank you very much!
I will offer them on the family altar!
You can just eat them.
Chocolates should arrive
to father today, too.
That is all of them.
Huh? What?
That's it?
What about me?
Where are the chocolates of gratitude for me?
Miss Youko?!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
The next "Three Leaves,
Three Colors" is the last episode!
The next "Three Leaves, Three Colors"
is the last episode!
Let's have Miss Youko say the title.
Let's have
Miss Youko
say the title.
Okay, I will.
Okay,
I will.
Next time is, "I Am Graduating from Bread Crusts."
Next time
is, "I Am
Graduating
from Bread
Crusts."
I hope you enjoy it.
I hope
you
enjoy
it.
Well, that's not happening.
ha ha ha
Well,
that's not
happen-
ing.
Next time: I Am Graduating from Bread Crusts
Nope...
It
will!
It will!
It
will!