It's been five days since
I started as a professional hero.
There haven't been any
serious incidents so far.
However, for some reason
Genos is staying at my house.
What are you writing over there?
I'm recording the details of
your lessons and training regimen.
Crap.
He's raising the bar again…
I can't think of a single thing
I can teach the guy.
I feel bad, like I'm scamming him or something.
Come on, think.
Or just make up some
techniques or a spiritual theory.
Bah, strength training is all I've got!
I know Genos won't be satisfied
with that. Plus, the dude's a cyborg!
By the way,
at the seminar they said
if you're a C-class hero
and you have no hero activity for a week,
your name will be removed
from the Hero Registry.
Will you be all right, Master?
They said that?!
Yes.
But I was watching TV
and there wasn't anything going on.
The news only reports major incidents,
like natural disasters,
terrorism, and dangerous monsters.
You always fight the most powerful enemies,
so you probably do not know it,
but C-class heroes primarily
take care of purse snatchers,
robberies and random attacks.
With C-class so full of heroes,
to survive they must actively look for cases to resolve.
I hear many of them get
discouraged and change careers.
Like a salesman doing cold calls,
nothing will come your way without legwork.
This is no time to be reading comics!
So we're going?
You stay here!
If I'm with a S-class hero,
a C-class like me won't get any credit!
But as your disciple—
Genos, from the beginning my intense desire
to be a hero was what drove me to strength training.
That's how I made it this far.
For you, perhaps things will change
if you aim higher as a hero.
Frankly speaking, you're a cyborg,
so training your body won't do.
Instead, a change in mindset
may lead you to greater strength.
Damn, I'm just making all this crap up…
So… in other words,
it's not about having raw power or technique.
It's about training your mind.
To do that, you must first fight your way
through the professional hero industry.
Aim to break into the top ten
of the S-class heroes.
That will be your goal for now.
I understand.
I will try!
He bought it… Sweet.
After that, I sped around town.
Frantically looking for bad guys…
I ran.
And ran.
But...
The city was as quiet as ever!
I give up…
Just one more day left.
Guess I'll head home.
I'll leave tomorrow's problems to tomorrow's me.
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
THE FOLLOWING DAY
It's quiet today too!
There's nothing to do!
I'm gonna lose my registration!
Hey!
You're that guy…
What was it?
"Seed-on-the-Ground…"?
No wait, "Lost-and-found…"?
Jack-o'-lantern Panic!
It's Speed-o'-Sound Sonic.
I've finally found you, Saitama.
Today is the day we—
Hey sorry, I'm busy. See you 'round.
Huh?
Do you really…
think you can run from me?!
What the—
I didn't see what happened.
His face should have
been sliced open, but the blade…
I told you… I'm busy.
Plus I'm pissed, so anyone in my way…
gets punched.
That's him!
He's very, very dangerous.
Please stop him.
So you're the offender, eh?!
Well, the hero, Tank-Top Tiger, is here now!
Hero?
Sonic, they think you're
some sort of criminal.
Maybe getting tossed in a cell
will cool off your hot—
She means you, cue ball.
Huh?
He's been running around town with
this scary look on his face since yesterday!
But I'm a hero too!
I've never heard of a hero like you.
So what?
I just started!
In any case, you're causing
problems for everyone.
If you're really a hero,
then don't go around frightening people.
You're hurting all
the other heroes' reputations.
Hey, isn't that Tank-Top Tiger?
Oh yeah, it is Tank-Top Tiger.
No way!
Awesome, he's the real deal!
Even C-class heroes get recognized
if they're in the top ten.
So how 'bout it, new guy?
Wanna go a little wild here
and make me look good?
Exploding Shuriken.
EXPLODING
SHURIKEN
Tank-Top Tiger?!
Is this really happening?
What are you doing, Sonic?
He was interfering, so I put him to sleep.
Hey, call a hero!
A hero!
Run!
Saitama…
So you too have become
one of these worthless "heroes?"
Then all I have to do is create a situation where
you have no choice but to fight me, Saitama the Hero!
Hail of Carnage!
Huh?
Hey! Cut it out!
Saitama, come stop me!
You're a hero!
I'll kill them all!
Damn it.
Can't everyone just let me do my job?
I don't have time for this!
I gotta find a bad guy to take down.
A bad guy?
If you're not coming, I'll go to you!
I'm right here.
I wonder if this will count as work?
The man apprehended
in City Z by the C-class hero
is suspected of being involved in
several heinous crimes, including assassination.
City Z…
What's the status of the
investigation I requested?
The one for the ghost town?
Yes.
Let's see…
We've submitted an official request.
Well now, doesn't that sound interesting?
Want me to go?
T-Tornado?
Where'd you come from?
What's it to you?
Aren't I allowed in here?
Of course.
But for City Z,
the investigation is just a formality.
What?
You think I'm not good enough?
Not at all.
The Association decided that
this was not an S-class matter.
Yes, exactly right.
You'd better tell me if you find
anything that looks like it can fight.
It'd be so much faster if I just went myself.
You're such an idiot.
CITY A – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Reports have come in from
each location being investigated.
First is Watchdog Man,
S-class hero, investigating City Q.
"Nothing unusual."
Nothing unusual?
That's right.
That's hard to believe.
We all know City Q is a hot spot with more
casualties and monsters than any other area.
Knowing him, I'm sure he's implying that,
"Whatever occurs, I'll be able to take care of it."
Though he has focused his efforts on City Q,
his monster elimination track record is top-notch.
S-class heroes don't pay
much attention to details.
They're not cut out for writing reports.
Next, City W.
Class A hero Heavy Kong
reports: "Nothing unusual."
For City H, reports from Mushroom,
Class B, and Horsebone, Class C:
"Nothing unusual."
For City D, Lightning Genji, Class A:
"Slow restoration after the devastation caused by
the gigantic creature aside, nothing unusual."
Cities B and D both sustained extensive damage.
The Association took a lot of heat for that.
In order to prevent further such disasters,
we must detect any covert activity
that could threaten the community.
Well, this investigation was requested
for that express purpose.
But early detection of monsters is proving difficult.
City F, A-class hero, "Snakebite" Snek.
"Hammerhead, former leader
of the Paradiser terrorist group,
has been spotted in a suit and tie."
"Further investigation is being conducted."
No other reports.
What of City Z?
I hear rumblings of a potential disaster
brewing in the abandoned area there.
No reports available.
However, two highly capable A-class heroes
have been sent to the area to investigate.
Here we are in City Z.
CLASS A, RANK 33
SPRING MUSTACHIO
Shall we begin our little inquiry?
CLASS A, RANK 29
GOLDEN BALL
Yeah, let's get on with it.
City Z is quite expansive, but further ahead
lies the uninhabited area we were told about.
Compared with other areas, City Z has an
abnormally high rate of monster-related incidents.
BEWARE OF
MONSTERS!!
The frequency has been gradually
increasing over the past ten years,
while the last few have seen more and more
highly advanced monsters appearing.
The residents have entirely
fled for the city center.
I know all that.
The place is a real ghost town,
just with the water and electricity still intact, yeah?
On the lookout for a cheap house?
Come off it.
People say something
real nasty's living 'round here.
Even you must've heard.
But of course.
I assume that's why we have
been assigned this investigation.
Once we hit the abandoned area,
we better be ready to fight.
Indeed, we mustn't let our guard down.
But, why here?
Why the increase in monsters here?
That's the mystery.
Many theories have been advanced, but my own is this:
A colony of monsters here
is naturally producing more of them.
Or perhaps a queen exists,
birthing more of her kind.
Of course I have no proof yet,
but there is something to this ghost town…
Or rather, something in it.
Of that you can be sure.
The proximity alarm?
If we can hunt down this mysterious being,
we'll go straight to the top of the rankings.
That's true.
We can't let Mr. Sweet Mask remain first for—
Something's there?!
Was that a monster?
No way to be sure…
But it's hard to imagine a human
still living in these conditions.
Let's pursue it!
Seems they are not after us.
Could this be the place I heard about?
Sure don't seem like it…
Aw man, I came all this way.
Isn't anyone around?
A monster.
It popped up out of nowhere.
Golden Ball, are you ready?
Hell yeah!
Victory to the swift!
Hey, people!
I can blast through a 20mm steel plate
with one of my shape-memory golden bullets!
Eat this!
He flicked it away like nothing.
Golden Ball!
Wow!
Tomboy…
…thrust!
It slipped past my Tomboy?
Not bad.
Those tentacles…
From the way they react,
they're tough as steel.
A monster that can use its infinite
number of tentacles like steel whips…
Such power!
I must call in reinforcements
from the Association.
May I ask if you were born
in this neighborhood?
Nah, I'm from out of town.
I heard a bunch of crazy strong monsters
were all getting together here.
Looks like it was just a rumor though.
But now,
I feel like it'd be kinda fun to
stick around and make the rumor true.
"The Ghost Town Monster…"
It's got a nice ring to it!
We have a backup request
from the heroes dispatched to City Z.
Class A rank 29, Golden Ball,
has been knocked out.
Class A rank 33, Spring Mustachio, is in trouble.
They're in the abandoned city.
Call in all nearby heroes
for immediate assistance!
A-class or stronger!
See the monster alert for City Z?
The threat level seems to be Tiger or higher.
Is it the ghost town monster?
They're not sure yet.
I'll go…
I want to catch the tiger by its tail.
Now I see…
If it means running into monsters
like this all the time
I wouldn't want to live here either.
Man, boring.
This is boring me!
I finally kick a hero's butt
and I don't get even a single scream.
Now that I think about it,
even if I start living here,
I'll never be famous if there's no people.
Guess I'll keep going.
Gotta find where they live.
There's somebody.
Another hero?
Or a regular guy?
I thought all the humans cleared out.
If all those monsters were really around,
there's no way he could live here…
I guess that means it was just a rumor.
Shoot…
I forgot to buy kelp soup stock.
Master, I saw a lot of kelp
right outside the door.
Oh yeah, I just…
Just happened… to get it for cheap.
Yes, people say that kelp
is good for hair growth,
but since there is no real scientific proof,
its real effects are yet to be confirmed.
I did some research, so I am sure, Master.
For example, according to this site—
No one said anything about hair!
City Z Investigative Report.
"Nothing noteworthy about
the downtown or residential areas."
"During our investigation, we encountered
a ferocious monster in the abandoned area,
but were unable to exterminate it."
"We escaped death,
but the monster we encountered disappeared
and it is possible that it still roams the area."
"Also, according to this monster, there's a rumor that…
…powerful monsters already exist in this area."
Sounds like it was pretty brutal.
A monster?
Y-Yes.
I think I'll pass this time.
See?
I told you I should have gone!
But…
faced with this,
I'm sure even you would
have had a tough time.
I would have been fine, idiot!
The rumor has not been confirmed,
but the reinforcements saw signs that point
to the existence of some horrible monstrosity.
Holy crap, what is this?
What kind of monster
could cause such violence?
I'd hate to face off against this thing.
Hey, what's this?
Is it a part of the monster
Spring Mustachio fought?
There may have been a territorial
dispute between the monsters…
Seems like there's definitely "something" here.
We must continue our investigation
and maintain vigilance over City Z.
Hey, did you hear?
There are monsters living
in the City Z ghost town.
Yeah, rumor has it the toughest ones
are secretly plotting something.
No, no. Not that rumor.
It's about a more dangerous monster.
What's that?
You didn't hear?
I hear the place has now become
terrifying for both humans and monsters.
THE TERRIFYING CITY
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Master, I filled in the holes in front of the house.
Oh, thanks!
Also, your rank has gone up
from last place, 388th, to 342nd.
Oh? Because of that Panic guy?
He boosted my ranking.
So it's been a week now.
Have you done anything?
No, not yet.
I guess it has only been a week.
I'm still ranked last in Class S
for ability… in 17th place.
Sounds like you've still got
a lot of training to do, Genos.
But in the public polls,
for popularity I rank number six.
Why?!
"A genius who, at the tender age of 19,
made his debut in Class S."
"He'll do great."
"He's so handsome."
"Love how he refuses to
do media interviews. Very cool."
Those kinds of comments.
You're not embarrassed
to read those out loud?
These comments are based on
impressions from my photo,
not evaluations of me.
I think nothing of them.
Oh yeah?
They continue.
"The Cyborg Prince."
"Behind the steely exterior,
I feel his fragile self."
"Among the top five handsomest—
Enough already!
Next
Time
The
Ultimate
Disciple
This is Blizzard.
Perhaps you know me better
as "Blizzard from Hell"?
Well, I only had a bit part this episode.
Next time on One-Punch Man episode seven,
"The Ultimate Disciple."
The Blizzard Bunch will finally
make its appearance.
Miss Blizzard, we're not scheduled
to go on next week!
That can't be right!