Haruka's Room
Number 2
Haruka's Room!
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Our guest for today...
"All the women of the world belong to me. Inside my mind, that is!"
The famous sex-crazed youth,
please welcome, Manabe Yoshihisa-san!
I'm Manabe Yoshihisa. Nice to meet you!
We're both first-year students and are in the same class at Midorigaoka High School.
We are also in love with each other!
I always have Kotoura on my mind!
We're lovey-dovey!
Yahoo!
I'm sorry. I got carried away.
Manabe-san, what do you think about your habit of
having more than a normal amount of erotic fantasies,
and troubling those around you?
Excuse me?
I know you were fantasizing about big-breasted women just now.
If you like big breasts so much, become a citizen of a country that's full of big-breasted women.
A country full of... big breasted women?!
Stop it! Stop imagining a country full of big-breasted women!
We're on camera!
That's not... My breasts aren't that big...
S-Stop it!
The End