No matter how far away we are
We can come together
La la la la
One Two Three Four Fly
Fly
Okay, good!
Good job!
Good work!
Good work. You were great.
Thank you.
Makoto, is something wrong?
I'm the same as ever.
No problems.
Will all my singing ever reach that person?
What should I...
Hey, Makoto,
we have another job offer.
You'd visit a restaurant and experience cooking first hand.
Not every job has to be about singing, right?
Fine.
But I have one condition.
A condition?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Hold The Phone!
Makopi's Coming to My House?!
Huh?
What's this?
A TV shoot?
Wow!
That's what I said!
I hear they were dead set on our shop,
so they picked it right away!
As the Pig Tail's second generation chef,
I've gotta keep a steady hand!
Don't worry!
Your cooking's the best in Japan!
Well, not on my watch.
Come on, Dad.
You know an idol's coming,
so greet her with a smile!
An idol?
Who's coming?
Hm, I think it was...
Hello.
Good morning.
Makopi!
This is great!
I had no clue you were visiting my house!
I only came for business.
Is this your house?
Yeah!
I'm Aida Mana!
Just call me Mana!
I'm Hishikawa Rikka.
All right then,
we'll start filming tomorrow,
so we're gonna rehearse it today!
R-Right!
I hope we work well together.
You can do it, Daddy!
Uh, now then,
today's challenge is our famous omelette rice!
First, we have to prep.
Dice the onions and carrots,
and thinly slice the bacon and mushrooms.
So, can you wash the carrots for me?
Sure!
D-Don't use detergent!
Please?
Huh?
I'm terribly sorry!
Makoto has never cooked before...
Well, that's just how first timers are.
So, how about cutting the bacon next?
Cutting?
Let's begin.
Makoto, you're not a samurai...
Huh?
I'm terribly sorry!
Makoto has truly never cooked before!
Well, that's just how first timers are.
Let's move on!
Oh yeah!
How about we crack the eggs!
Lower the difficulty!
Oh, then...
I'll crack them.
That couldn't have been on purpose.
No, it was.
Makoto's eyes are dead serious.
Makopi,
you've gotta handle food with lots of love!
Huh?
This is food?
What did you think it was?
What kinda chef doesn't know you can eat an egg?
Start over!
Grandpa!
Dad!
Well, that's enough for today,
so we'll start filming tomorrow.
What a mess.
Will Makopi even come tomorrow?
Should we start thinking up a backup plan?
Well that was unexpected!
Didn't think she was that bad at cooking.
It's not a matter of skill.
Dad likes to put his heart into his cooking.
His heart?
When you face the cutting board, you cook with the person eating it in mind.
That's what cooking is.
I'm sorry about that.
Lately, you've been singing non-stop,
so I thought it might be a nice change of pace.
It was my fault.
I should have studied cooking more.
Why did you pick that restaurant?
You knew that Mana girl lived there, didn't you?
I just wanted to see how those girls lived.
Is that really it?
That's it.
So, what about the job?
We can still cancel.
Wow!
Makoto visited your home?
What a surprise.
She definitely came to investigate us!
I don't think so...
Will Makopi be all right?
She messed up a little...
I'd call it more than a little.
And she got sad after hearing what Grandpa said...
You must really like Makopi, huh?
I'm going to see Makopi!
Wait, Mana!
Stop!
You want to see her,
but do you even know where she is?
Well I guess... I don't.
Oh, but that letter we got from her manager had a business card!
Then perhaps we should try the phone first.
Yeah.
Guess so.
I was about to do something dumb again.
Huh?
Makopi!
I'm glad you came back!
What?
Hey,
do you want to practice making omelette rice together?
I know a lot of tricks!
Practice?
I came back because I wanted to learn to cook right.
Could you help me?
Sure!
Honestly, I'm so happy you came back!
Mana was waiting in worry for you, Makoto.
I just don't want to abandon a job before it's through.
Fine,
but I'm still really happy!
Go ahead.
Okay, I'll crack it.
I think you're putting too much force into it.
Force?
Watch me.
You can break eggs without a lot of force.
Tap, tap, crack is the rhythm!
Tap, tap, crack?
Yeah!
You did it!
I did it!
Excellent work!
One more time, Makopi!
Go ahead.
You did it!
It's perfect!
With carrots, you go tap, tap, tiptiptap.
Tip, tap, tiptiptap.
With onions, you go tac, tac, tictictac.
Tac tac, tictictac.
Yeah, that was good!
You learn quickly!
She's gotta be Cure Sword!
So, they're connected?
Here.
Use this.
Thank you.
Next, we're gonna cut the bacon!
I'll wash the rice.
Then I shall prepare the seasoning.
No matter what you do, you always fail when it counts.
Sounds like you!
Who lost to them last time?
Oh yeah, you!
Oh, I didn't lose.
I only let them win.
It's rotten.
This is rotten?
Not that.
King Selfish'll be pissed.
The time we've got left
isn't too much.
Put some effort in!
How about you, huh?
What are you saying?
Good grief.
Guess it's my turn.
And we're filming!
Action!
Let's begin.
Tap, tap, tiptiptap.
Tac, tac, tictictac.
Tap, tap,
crack.
crack!
Great, Makopi!
You've improved a lot overnight.
Thank you very much.
All right,
let's get to the end in one take!
Right.
All that's left is to wrap the chicken rice in the egg, correct?
But that's the hardest part!
Stay strong, Makopi!
I'll show them.
Those girls practiced so much with me last night,
so I owe it to them.
Nice!
How impressive!
You did it, Makopi!
It's huge!
Sorry!
I got the ingredients to feed four on accident!
Aw, it doesn't matter.
We're finally done,
so lets get some shots of you all eating it.
Well, Makopi, let's put on the finishing touch!
Here you go.
What's this?
Use it like this.
Like a smooch...
That's Mana for you.
It's quite lovely!
This makes it even tastier!
Rikka, Alice, help me!
Sure!
Good.
Makoto's smile has returned.
Dig in!
Yummy!
It's quite tasty!
It really is good!
And it's her first time cooking, too.
Those girls put their hearts into that omelette rice.
'Course it's gonna be good.
My heart...
Come to think of it,
didn't I use to put my heart into my songs?
I wanted to see that person smile.
But lately...
I haven't been able to find that person,
and in my haste,
I forgot to put my heart into my singing.
Makopi?
Is something wrong?
I remembered something important.
Something important?
It's thanks to you three.
Makopi!
Oh, to be young.
But that omelette rice looks tasty!
Man, I could go for some fresh, homemade omelette rice.
I oughta ditch this job and get me some of that.
Nah, work's work.
Just gotta deal.
Aw, just eat it.
Who's there?
I will grant...
your desire.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Oink!
I wanna pig out!
What's that?
A dark heartbeat!
It's from the kitchen.
What the?!
Everyone, it is dangerous here.
Hurry outside.
But the girls are still inside!
Worry not, they are safe.
Now hurry.
Right!
Let's go, Charles!
Gotcha!
Us too, Rachel.
Roger that!
Are you prepared, Lance?
Of course!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Rachel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
Lance!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
Oh poor pig who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Today's the day...
that I kick all your butts!
It's you again?
You're really persistent.
Well, right back at you.
Whoop 'em, Selfish!
This too!
Quit eating and get 'em!
The restaurant...
It's eating it!
Such poor manners!
You'll get a stomachache if you eat that!
It's getting bigger!
Well fed children really do grow up bigger!
This is no time for admiration!
Ooooomelette rice!
I want that omelette rice!
Omelette rice!
Davi!
I've waited...
for that look.
Davi!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Makopi is Cure Sword!
I, Cure Sword,
shall sever your ambitions with the blade of love!
It's her!
She finally showed us her identity!
Davi!
Glitter!
Holy Sword!
Oink?!
Love love looooove!
Huh?
I remember bein' hungry, then what?
I'll remember this!
Makopi!
So you really are Cure Sword!
I'm all choked up!
I couldn't quite do it in secret.
We've been waiting for this moment!
Yeah!
We want you to join us!
I feel the same way...
That's why I came here...
Thank you.
I've been waiting...
for you four to be under one roof.
Who are you?
You don't need my name.
This'll be the last time we meet.
Farewell, Precure!
This world won't see your light ever again.
It belongs to the Selfish now.
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
What's that shadow?
It's King Selfish.
I'll tell you what happened to this country.
Dokidoki Precure:
An Intense Battle!
Farewell, Precure!!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!