Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
What kind of job do you think I can do?
Are there any other good places to work?
It appears to be blood...
"Jumbo Dumplings" "5,000 Yen Prize" "If you eat in 30 minutes."
Come again soon...
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
Oh, Yamaji. Are you making sure
Yoko's doors are secure?
Ah, good morning. How has
your back been lately?
Miss Yoko!
Morning!
Hayama, Futaba. Good morning!
The weather's great again.
Yes, it is.
I heard there's a typhoon coming, though.
What's this? I have a bad feeling...
"A Taste of Maid"
Last week's typhoon was pretty bad, huh.
It is delightful to eat outdoors again.
Futaba?
What's wrong? It's lunch time.
How rare. Futaba, you brought your lunch today?
Yup, I used up all my lunch
allowance for the month.
Oh? For what?
Man, I shouldn't have gotten
hooked on them... Grilled sea urchin.
Sea--
Most people don't get hooked on them.
Aw, I'm broke. Maybe I should
get a part-time job.
You mean you want to work?
That's what it normally means.
I wonder if there are any nice jobs out there,
like a cake shop, or a bakery, or a boxed lunch shop...
Are you working for money or food?
I'll make the most of it.
A part-time job. I have been
thinking of getting one myself.
What kind of job do you think I can do?
Miss Yoko wants to work?
I have brought your menu.
Excuse me?! Who do you think
you are, ordering me around?
You can get your own coffee refill!
Like a...
A themed restaurant?
Oh, I know! Yamaji would
know about part-time jobs.
Hm?
He usually comes out on his own...
Saying, "My poor Miss Yoko!"
Futaba?
What's this?
"Now Hiring" "Let's work together" "No experience required!!"
Wow, we're super lucky.
This shop opened recently,
and I've been wanting to go.
It's a small and cute cake shop.
I can make money and eat all the cake I want.
That's not how it works.
I-I wonder if I can work properly.
You wanted to try working, right?
And I'll be with you, too.
Hello!
They look delicious.
Cakes! It has been a while
since I have even seen them.
Excuse me!
What's this?
It appears to be blood...
Don't say anymore!
It leads inside.
Is anyone here?
Let's go back.
It leads behind this door.
What is this?!
A murder?!
Is that...?
Did the hand just move?
No, stop!
Phew. How careless of me.
I thought to recover by eating some sweets,
so I ate jam made from seasonal fruits,
but ended up falling asleep.
Sleeping?
Your eyes were open, though!
Sonobe, it is you!
Ah, Miss Yoko. Long time no see.
Wait, you know her?
Yes, she used to work for my family.
My name is Shino Sonobe. I'm the
Nishikawa family's former maid.
A maid?!
I enjoy making sweets--no, it's the only thing
I can do. So when I could not work as a maid,
I took the chance to start over and learn a
new trade, and now I'm able to open this store.
I see now.
I didn't know there were maids in Japan.
So that means this is the
cake shop of a former maid?
I believe we haven't been introduced.
They are my friends!
I'm Hayama.
I'm Futaba Odagiri.
Sonobe?
Wh-What's wrong?!
Oh my. That was surprising.
All people associated with
Miss Yoko give a strong reaction.
Wait, so that was surprise?
Isn't it more reassuring to work at
a place owned by someone you know?
That is true.
Miss Yoko? Work at my shop?!
Yes, if it is something I am capable of.
But of course. I'm counting on you, Miss Yoko!
She is counting on me?
Oh, yes! Me, too!
Of course! A schoolmate of
Miss Yoko's would be most amusin--
I mean, dependable.
--You should join, too!
--What? Oh, I...
What?!
"Milk"
Milk bottle caps?!
What is the meaning of this, Sonobe?
Yamaji!
Oh, it's the milkman. The fresh cream
goes in the refrigerator.
You have not answered my question.
Making Miss Yoko work? I'm getting
stomach pains just thinking about it.
Yamaji...
I would be worrying, too.
To make matters worse, I've had to
change shifts for other jobs,
and it's been hard finding people to cover me!
Thanks for helping me
find this property, Mitsugu.
What? You found this place for her?
Indeed. I happened to be working
at a real-estate agency--
Anyway, please do not make Miss Yoko work!
Sonobe is counting on me, though!
No! For you to work at a place
owned by a shady character...
Wh-What is the meaning of this, Sonobe?
I was just swatting at a fly.
I see.
Oh, there's a fly there, too!
Stop this at once, Sonobe, Yamaji!
Get on your knees!
Man, that scared me.
I wouldn't want to work there...
I apologize that you had to see that.
Are there any other good places to work?
There might be other places
more suited for you... Oh!
"Jumbo Dumplings" "5,000 Yen Prize"
"If you eat in 30 minutes"
"Stuffed Hut"
"5,000 Yen Prize" "If you eat in 30 minutes"
Come again soon...
Ah, that was delicious.
"Stuffed Hut"
I ate dumplings and got five thousand yen. That's the best!
Maybe I'll make it through this month.
"Stuffed Hut"
I thought you could do it, but you did it so easily.
I am jealous. As for me,
there is nothing I am good at.
That's not true.
Yeah, you have things you're good at.
You think so? What are they?
Huh?
Er, um...
Oh, a themed restaurant!
A cafe with mean girls with a soft side.
What is that?
"Central Shopping Arcade"
But for Miss Yoko, she wouldn't show her soft side to strangers,
even if it was for work.
"Central Shopping Arcade"
A mean girls cafe for masochists?
One that targets gentler customers.
"Central Shopping Arcade"
Mean girl with a soft side?
"Tonkatsu"
"Tonkatsu"                                                "Ramen"
Man, that was delicious.
"Stuffed Hut"
Come again soon...
She's at it again.
Oh, Hayama.
Being a glutton on the weekends, too?
I got the prize money again!
"Money Envelope"
Now, I'll use this to buy something yummy.
You're going to eat more?!
Oh, let's go to the maid's castle.
You mean Miss Sonobe's shop.
The cakes she gave us were pretty good.
They were, right?
They were like... a taste of maid!
There is no such thing.
Hello!
Welcome!
Oh my, what are you two doing here?
Wh--
Why aren't you wearing a maid outfit?
That's the first thing you ask?!
Wearing this is just my hobby.
It really is more comfortable
working at a friend's place,
and Yamaji is working here with me,
so I decided to take the job.
Yamaji...
Is his stomach okay?
But, it's true that working at a
friend's place is more comfortable.
Sonobe is still young, but she's reliable enough
to have her own shop. She's in her teens?
Oh, despite her appearance,
she is well past her teens.
I think she is in her early thirties.
In her thirties?!
Excuse me.
I will be eating my lunch soon, too.
E-Er...
--Miss Sonobe, are you in your thirties--
--I-Is Miss Yoko doing okay?
Yes.
It is a small shop with a
small selection, so I am managing.
Also, most of the customers are women.
Okay, I will return now.
Thank you.
Miss Yoko is amazing.
She's doing a good job.
For me to hire someone who once
hired me. It's really quite thrilling.
I wonder what the other two think
of me when they see me working.
Well, we should get going...
Please, take your time.
You can stay as I eat lunch.
I also have some sweets fresh from the oven.
Oh, okay.
Yay, I'll have some!
I can eat much more when I'm with two
young girls. Your young essence soaks into me.
Oh, really?
Wh-What does that mean?
I can't tell if she's joking.
Oh, you two are here?
Yamaji! You're working here, too, right?
Where have you been this whole time?
Oh, I only help make the cakes in the morning.
Oh, I see.
I had some free time, so I came
to see how things are going.
Miss Yoko, can I be of assistance to you?
Yeah, he does have other part-time jobs.
He came briefly in the morning and easily
finished after a little explanation.
Yeah, that's Yamaji...
He's always been a repulsive man
who finished jobs flawlessly.
But, how nice to be in high school.
You must have fun every day.
I go to school looking forward to lunch.
We do work hard in our studies, too.
I see.
Miss Yoko. It's a little early,
but it's okay if you leave now.
I can?
Mitsugu is here, too.
Didn't I say I only work here in the mornings?
Let's go home together then!
Okay!
It gets tiring standing all day.
Talking to customers also takes up energy.
Isn't it hard for you to bow to people?
W-Well, they are customers.
I manage somehow!
Your livelihood depends on it, huh, Miss Yoko?
Are you striving to escape
living on a bread crust diet?
Why would I want to?
They are so cheap and plentiful!
Miss Yoko...
Please come again!
I'm so hungry.
Just one more class until lunch.
Futaba! Hayama!
--Hm? Is someone calling?
--Futaba! Hayama!
--This voice... Is it...?
Here, over here. I'm over here.
Do you have a minute?
Wh-Wh-Wh--
What are you doing?!
Did I surprise you?
It doesn't matter. That uniform...
Oh, this?
I quickly made this after you all left yesterday.
I made it myself, pattern and all.
That really doesn't matter right now.
What are you doing here?!
That's right. You should be
wearing a maid outfit.
That's not it!
I wanted see what it's like.
That's it?! That's not the problem here.
What will you do if you're found out?
It's my heart of service.
You mean fan service?!
Fan service should be with the maid outfit!
Stop talking about that!
Ah, yes. I had something for Miss Yoko.
For Miss Yoko?
I made too much food, so I packed
some for Miss Yoko to eat.
Oh, lunch?
It might seem like an excuse, but it's true.
No matter the reason, there's nothing
that would explain this situation.
Oh, class is starting.
Miss Sonobe, what will you do--
She disappeared!
A poltergeist...
I won't be able to give Miss Yoko
her lunch until lunch time.
Linoleum-floored hallway.
Oh, the fragrance of youth!
My, what a lovely view.
It feels good to be up so high.
It's a view that really stirs up
my love for school uniforms.
You use a subject after "if."
After the subject, you use a verb--
Huh? What's that voice that sounds like
it would come out of a jungle?
The poltergeist...
C'mon, hurry up and get into pairs!
Start stretching!
C'mon, get a move on!
This is just...
Where did Miss Sonobe go?
It's her!
So you're not classmates with Miss Yoko.
What?
What are you doing here, Sonobe?
I wanted to eat lunch with you.
Wait, but...
You're not surprised, Miss Yoko?
Things just happen when you work with Sonobe.
Miss Yoko...
There is plenty, so please have some.
Thank you!
It's potato salad, with a
generous amount of mayonnaise.
You know what I like, Sonobe.
I knew it. She was planning on
coming here all along.
Thanks, Sonobe.
Miss Yoko, it's from your father.
Wow, did you draw this?
Indeed. I thought it would brighten up
a letter that only had words.
Thanks, Sonobe!
You shouldn't. You need to have balanced meals.
I don't want to hear that from you.
I eat plenty of bread, rice,
meat, and vegetables!
You eat too much.
--I don't eat that much.
--Miss Yoko.
I will take my leave soon.
You're going already?
Hayama, Futaba, please take care of Miss Yoko.
Sonobe...
I've found you, Sonobe!
Yamaji!
What are you doing,
walking around in that uniform?
Sonobe!
Maybe she was just worried about Miss Yoko.
Yeah. She's a little weird,
but she seems like a good person.
Sonobe...
Here you go. Here you go.
"Today's Recommendations and New Cakes!"
Here you go. Please take one, here.
It's a yummy cake shop. Yes, here you go.
Sonobe.
Oh, Miss Yoko.
What are you doing, first thing in the morning?!
You can have one, too.
That is not what I was talking about.
Hey, now...
Miss Yoko, calm down.
You think this is okay?
Yes. I'm confident nobody can tell.
Can tell what? That you're passing out fliers?
That you're not a student here?!
Although I made this myself,
I made it carefully.
I am not talking about that right now!
Oh, wait! So-no-be!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life
is so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
This is Maid Angel Super Shino!
I'm so happy you enjoyed this!
From this week on, I'll be here
to put a smile on your faces!
Please support me! You will, right?
"Arrogantly"
I will fight with what I have!
Perish! Unpaid overtime! Illegal uploading!
What year are you in?
2016...
"Next time: Actually, This Is What I Live For"
"I feel like someone's watching me."