Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
You've been messing around there for a while...
...but can you even tell?
Aren't they all the same?
Isn't it common sense to do this?
Otherwise, you could spend all the money
in the world and never get what you want.
Your common sense has very little practical application.
At the very least, normal people wouldn't do it.
How
to
Spend
Summer
It isn't just about figures...
Some people are after the cards.
How can you distinguish between cards?
Don't they all weigh the same?
There have been many legends and rumors about this.
Like where to find good cards...
Or special marks or patterns to look for.
By the way, I can usually get the special cards I want.
There's a pattern to it...
...if the box was just opened.
That's pretty insane if you think about it...
...but I really don't feel like praising her!
If people know these things...
...don't the good ones get taken in no time?
That's true...
If you live in an area with experts...
...rare cards and secret figures are gone in a flash.
When I go to a shop and see all these gaps in a box...
...I'm left in despair.
But then I end up falling for that faint glimmer of hope.
It's such a problem.
You definitely have a problematic nature.
I heard some collectors...
...go out and buy a whole bunch at once?
Yeah.
Some do.
It's faster to complete a set if you buy a bunch at once...
...and it's easier to read distribution patterns that way.
Oh, really.
Well, they call it the adult purchasing
method since it's a strain on your budget.
Gotta work part-time to support it.
Adult purchasing method, huh...
They might call it an adult method...
...but they sure act immature.
It signifies a really possessive nature...
...or selfish behavior.
Maybe the young adult purchasing method would be better.
Am I the only one who thinks that
spending the effort on something else...
...would be more meaningful?
These days...
Akihabara gets a lot more media attention.
And they're obnoxious about it.
They can do stories if they want...
...but I have yet to see anything based on factual evidence.
Well, they probably exaggerate some stuff...
...but isn't that because of their audience?
But that doesn't explain how TV shows and songs...
...which were big in otaku culture first became popular.
News programs and variety shows
use anime and game music all the time.
Well...
Maybe that's because normal people wouldn't recognize it?
Speaking of otakus...
Male otakus...
...are always talking about how they want an
otaku with the same interests for a girlfriend...
...on forums and stuff.
But you never hear a female otaku
wanting to go out with another otaku.
I wonder why.
Maybe girls are more susceptible to the charms of 2-D.
Maybe they're worried about the future?
I'm sure most of them are working though...
And like, don't ask me this stuff.
They showed up as soon as it got hot.
Can't stand how they're noisy and quick to escape.
And they're dirty.
They say that Musashi Miyamoto...
...could catch flies using chopsticks.
For real?!
I can't believe he was willing to
touch those things with eating utensils.
Makes me sick.
That's your concern?
Well, I know what you mean...
Abeshi!
Wow!
I could never smack a mosquito.
Why's that?
It'd be all gross when blood got
over your hand when you crushed it.
That's true...
That's my blood.
But what if a mosquito lands on your arm?
I go, "Shoo! Shoo!"
Or I blow on it.
Did you know?
If you clench your arm when a mosquito lands on it...
...it can't pull its stinger out.
No way!
Just watch.
You are already dead.
You've already been bitten.
If you clench even harder...
...the mosquito will explode.
Stop! Stop!
It itches!
Should have just smacked it in the first place.
Itches so much!
Are you going overseas again this summer, Miyuki-san?
No.
Not this year.
However...
...we will probably visit relatives in the country.
I also often go to the summer festival
with the neighbor's daughter from Ryouou.
She's like a younger sister.
So you're going to a summer festival, Iwasaki-san.
You'd probably look great in a yukata.
Not at all...
I know that you're complimenting me...
...but for some reason, I can't appreciate it.
It's like you're saying I don't have any...
Izumi
Be right there...
Yo...
Morning...
You just woke up?!
What a slob.
Well...
Something's really been bothering me lately.
What?
Like, did my alarm clock ring?
Or like, did somebody else turn it off?
I know what you mean!
When you look, the switch is off.
But then again, it gets hot in the afternoon...
...so I can't really keep sleeping.
We're well into the afternoon.
Kona-chan.
It's morning.
Wake up.
Izumi-kun.
Let's eat lunch together.
I thought I might go home with you, Konata-kun.
Hey, Konata.
Why are the main characters in those games...
...so unconditionally popular?
Beats me...
Maybe 'cause it wouldn't be a game otherwise?
Geez!
You have to do your homework!
I-It's not like I'm worried or anything.
Fine.
I'll do it if you say so.
Hey, Konata.
Why are the heroines in those games...
...always cute with great personalities yet unattached?
You can just pick and choose.
Beats me...
Maybe 'cause it wouldn't be a game otherwise?
Yo, Konata!
I'm here to play!
While checking on Yutaka.
Good evening, Cousin Yui.
Konata?
Your father's calling for you.
Okay.
Yutaka started on her homework, so let me borrow some manga.
Er...
Don't you need to study, Konata?
Haven't you been playing this whole time?
No!
You've got it wrong!
You just have bad timing and enter whenever I'm taking a break!
GRIN
But that just means you take a lot of breaks.
And so...
...I'm concerned about my image at home...
I try to stay at my desk...
...but I end up taking a break.
Honestly...
It's because you usually don't work hard.
But well...
It's not like I don't understand how you feel.
You've had a similar experience?
Well...
If I pick up a book I really want to read during a break...
...I end up wanting to take another
break as soon as I start studying again.
It's hard to put those down in the middle.
It's the same with manga.
You say you'll stop after one more volume...
...but then you end up reading dozens more.
When you borrow the DVDs for a TV series you missed...
...you always have to watch one more episode.
But the follow-up tends to be trash.
I see.
Director, about this doll...
Big Sister.
Can I change the channel?
Sure.
I wasn't really watching.
Is there something you want to watch?
There's going to be a special on sweets from around the country.
You love sweets, right?
I bet Kagami and Tsukasa will watch, too.
It's like the Hare Hare Dance of sweets!
That looks great!
With these shows...
...even if you find something good...
...it ends up being sold somewhere far
away and you're left disappointed, right?
We live in Saitama, so Nagoya's kinda...
That always happens...
...but I still end up watching.
Too bad.
Summer Classes ————
Good morning, Yuki-chan.
Um, what's wrong?
I went to the dentist's yesterday.
You're still going?
I ran away halfway through...
Let me know if it hurts.
It'll be over soon.
Something like that...
That's right!
They never stop!
It hurts to just hear about it!
We already have summer classes...
...but homework on top of that?
Screw that.
It's summer vacation.
It's not like you do it yourself anyway.
Besides...
...unlike grade school and middle school...
...we don't have independent projects or book reports.
Isn't this easier?
You just have to answer questions.
We made crafts and posters, too.
With that stuff...
...you end up getting your parents' help.
And then they get so into it that they finish it, right?
I won a prize off of that once.
With a poster or something.
I remember that.
I was like, "It's all thanks to you, Dad.
I think you're even cooler now!"
And Dad was all happy about it.
Shouldn't a parent be mad about that?
Buy at least five at once!
Whenever I see this commercial...
...I always get jealous.
When I was little...
...and read that fairy tale about a gingerbread house...
...I wanted to try eating all the candy I could!
I know what you mean...
...but when you actually get a lot of what you want...
...you tend to lose interest.
Really...
Yeah.
It stinks the whole year.
So I was thinking...
About summer homework...
I'm always in trouble 'cause I plan
to do it in one go in the latter half.
That came out of nowhere.
And I didn't need you to tell me that.
If I worked at it little by little...
...I might not have to scramble at the end.
You just realized that?
You're a third-year already.
Don't burn yourself out.
Which means I'll be coming over tomorrow so thanks.
I'll bring a present.
So that's what you meant by little by little?
Are you going to come over all summer?
Probably every week.
Shut up!
Yo...
It's hot...
Yo.
Sure is.
The A/C's on in my room.
So comfortable!
You sure are making yourself at home...
It's like this every year.
Summer always passes without me wanting to do anything.
Before I know it, summer vacation's over.
Stop sounding so lazy.
Set milestones this year...
...and get your homework done.
Well...
I plan on working hard before summer vacation begins every year.
Really?
In manga...
You see the whole "I didn't do my homework!" gag used a lot...
...this time of year.
That's true.
When you look at that...
...don't you think that in theory, you don't need to do it?
If that's what everybody else is doing...
Of course not!
Do it.
Besides, if you're gonna be like this, don't come to copy!
I'm thirsty.
I'll go get some barley tea.
Sis!
Sorry...
Could you also get the math problem set from my room?
Pretty please.
Yeah, yeah.
So hot!
You don't want to leave an air conditioned room...
...so you ask someone else to do it when they leave...
...but nobody else wants to leave, huh?
In winter, you don't want to leave the kotatsu...
...so you ask someone else to do stuff for you when they get up.
Hey.
Yo!
Sure is hot.
Yo.
Welcome.
I brought ice cream.
Take whichever one you want.
Since I won't be much help with homework.
And the Marimokkori's eyes...
In these situations...
...why is it that you always want the ones other people chose?
I'm reading this manga about getting into Tokyo U.
That one, huh?
When you read that...
...don't you start thinking that you
might have a chance to get into Tokyo U?
If you work hard like them!
You sure are simple.
Even if that method could get you into Tokyo U...
You'd need friends who abandon their regular classes to join in...
Teachers who hold class like that...
Someone to take charge.
And all kinds of other things for it to work, right?
You're right...
It's not that easy...
Too many people...
...get influenced by manga or TV shows
and think they can change themselves.
Well...
I plan on working hard and studying...
...but I always get sleepy.
Is there a good way to stay awake?
I think it's better to take a little nap...
...than to force yourself to stay awake.
Oh, really?
I heard that before, so I gave it a try...
But my little nap ended up being a lot longer...
...yeah?
No willpower...
Hello!
Hello, Yutaka-chan.
Hello.
Um, do you have a minute?
What's up, Yu-chan?
You can ask us anything.
A friend from middle school apparently got a boyfriend...
...and she asked me what she should give him for his birthday.
I have no idea...
What do I do...
It got really awkward...
A-Anyway, Yu-chan...
They have web sites that discuss this stuff...
...so you should take a look.
There might be a thread about it.
You can use my computer.
I-I'll do that.
I know about Tra** Man...
...but you can even ask questions about this stuff.
It's pretty common these days.
Anything goes, huh?
That's right.
They probably have the answers for math problems, too.
It makes me think how kids these days have it so easy.
As technology and the community advance...
...the users' mindsets and willpower are getting worse.
Just look at her.
Huh?
That's odd...
I'm just copying homework...
...but unlike usual...
...the presence of an audience creates this pride-like feeling...
Oh, yeah.
What about the festival at your place?
What are you talking about?
It's already over.
Wha—
Same as last year.
Why didn't you tell me?!
We have to study for exams.
If we told you, you'd definitely want to go.
We didn't go either.
Doesn't have to be ours...
Just go to the one where you live.
Is it already over?
Where I live...?
Yeah, I wonder when that is...
Yeah...
Some people go to festivals in other places...
...but don't even care about the ones where they live.
Are you the type who avoids friends from back home?
Even college applicants can't go on studying forever.
That's right...
There's going to be a fireworks display near my home tomorrow.
That's it!
Let's all go have fun for once!
Guess so.
We could use a break.
That's right.
There's going to be a fireworks display
near your home tomorrow, Minami-chan.
I'd like to see Japanese fireworks.
Then let's all go together, Minami.
Minami-chan.
Are you free tomorrow?
I'm good.
Then it's decided, Minami.
Let's go, Iwasaki-san.
Huh?
Iwasaki-san?
It's a pretty famous fireworks display...
...Mi—
Iwasaki-san.
It's hard to change how you call
someone once you've gotten used to it.
But it's far away and famous, so it'll be crowded, right?
Will you be okay, Yu-chan?
Weren't you sick a while back?
It's going to be hot tomorrow so should we wait for the next one?
You don't have to worry about me.
It happens all the time.
I'm the class health officer, and I'll be coming...
...so it'll be okay...
...Yutaka.
That's right.
You're right.
Thanks, Minami-chan!
So we're going to see fireworks...
...but otherwise, it's college application and study time.
It sucks how I have less time to play.
'Cause Kagami and the others are all serious.
Well, I can understand.
You should just do what you want.
I used to drag Kanata around...
...and made lots of memories.
I got in trouble...
...but adolescence doesn't wait!
Then maybe I should get a boyfriend and make some memories.
Absolutely not!
I won't accept a boyfriend!
Well, Dad...
You're not making sense.
That's right.
Wanna come watch fireworks with us, Yu-chan?
Actually, I'm also going.
We're meeting up at Minami-chan's place.
Really...
We're leaving!
Have fun!
The train's here!
You're late.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yutaka-chan came along.
Um...
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Over here!
Hello.
Hey.
Hiya.
Patricia-san.
Are you also here for the fireworks?
You look good in a yukata.
What the heck?!
Iwasaki
Huh?
So Miyuki-san's neighbor was Minami-chan.
What a coincidence.
What a surprise.
Welcome.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Oh?
Not enough?
There should be enough...
Mom.
Did you count yourself?
You're right.
Now I get it.
Thanks for having us!
So this is Minami-chan's house.
Scary big dog...
Don't worry.
It doesn't bark.
And it's really friendly.
I see.
When they're big and friendly...
...it's actually kinda cute.
Huh?
It's growling at me...
Maybe she's the type who tends to get barked at.
When I was little...
...I would wonder if fireworks were still round from the side.
Huh?
So they don't look flat?
Hey now...
They show firework displays on TV occassionally...
...but there's a better atmosphere when you watch the real thing.
You're right.
But you know...
I've been thinking...
Every time they launch a big one...
...and announce that this was
sponsored by some business or other...
...doesn't that ruin the mood?
Th-That's true.
Huh?
Yu-chan.
You look a little pale.
I'm okay.
It's okay...
...so go watch.
But...
I'll...
...stay here.
Minami-chan.
That was wonderful.
Yeah.
This is what summer's all about.
But you know...
It never ends up being a beautiful memory like in manga.
I got bitten everywhere.
So itchy!
They say that it itches more if you scratch.
And when you take off the yukata, it itches under the belt.
That's right.
Beautiful.
It really was.
But sorry for causing you trouble.
There you are.
Hey.
Were you guys bitten by bugs, too?
We weren't bitten at all.
So some people are easily bitten and some aren't.
So lucky.
Nah.
Maybe the mosquitos read the mood.
Good lucky!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
I'm the assistant...
Daisuke Ono.
We're already on the twentieth episode of Lucky Channel!
You're not a crow today.
You're not a dog today.
Then let's have a look at the live feed.
Forest
Studio
I wonder where he is right now.
That Shiroishi-kun.
Mt. Fuji's so pretty!
Whatever.
Then bye-bee!
Bye-bee!
Shiraishi-kun?
Shiraishi-kun?!
Ma'am!
This is what you wanted, right?
Hello, Minoru Shiraishi here!
Now, please listen to me!
Bridegroom Rumba!
One, two, three, four!
Merry voices ring through the air...
...at a church in June.
The phrase "happiest moment of my life" was...
...made for such a time.
If I'd known this would happen...
...I wouldn't have bought that new house.
Getting jilted by the bride...
...is like something out of manga.
All worked up, I break into the Bridegroom Rumba.
Somebody save me.
Oh, my god!
What am I going to do now?!
Even my boss is here!
One, two, three! Two, Two, three!
Bridegroom Rumba!
Cha-la!
Cha-la-la!
Cha!
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Misao here.
Ayano here.
Hey, Ayano.
Isn't Hiiragi so heartless?
She always runs off to the midget's class.
There, there.
Does our love not reach Hiiragi?!
「Pandora's Box」
Next time:
Pandora's Box.
Ayano's heartless, too...