Where should I go... when I don't even know where I came from...
When I don't even have memories?
What do I have to do to become free?
What is freedom when you have to kill people for it?
Smile... Please smile... Elen...
Succession
Give this to the police. That's all. Please!
Ah! Wait!
I have to escape or I'm going to be killed.
I can't escape from those black eyes.
If you don't want to die...
come at me with all you've got.
You have natural talents.
The talent to kill... the talent to survive...
The talents of an assassin.
If you want to live, you have to be reborn.
You are now only allowed to exist for the purpose of killing people.
What is our way of existing?
Be an instrument. Be a tool.
All we need to do is just function.
Don't think about unnecessary things.
Taking away the memories of an outsider boy,
and training him to be an assassin...
I went along with Scythe's suggestion, which some might consider reckless...
because I needed it at any cost.
I needed Phantom's power.
Phantom... the strongest assassin in Inferno...
the title given to the top sniper in the organization...
My masterpiece... Ein.
And Zwei... He is also...
But...
she's a human who's just being used by the organization.
Both Phantom and I have no choice but to live like slaves, right?
It's true that we're forcing you two to live this way,
but you're not slaves.
Even you have freedom.
Speed.
Speed?
Even when your course is set,
you can keep picking up speed for as long as you want,
so long as you have the desire and put effort into it.
You may even be able to reach the top of the organization.
How you dash through it... is up to you.
Say, Lizzie...
Would you agree to anything if it's an order?
I wouldn't work under someone for so long if I couldn't.
That just sounds like you.
Say, Clo...
What is it?
I've been wanting to apologize to you all this time.
Four years ago, I couldn't do anything because I was in jail.
During that time, your organization was crushed by Wisemel.
And Romero, too, was...
If only I had been...
That was in the past.
The weak get taken in by the strong.
That's just natural.
That's why... I became a member of Inferno.
Clo...
That which I lost... Which was taken from me...
I can take them back someday.
I want you to carry out one more task in LA sometime soon.
So you want to make an unexpected contribution
and let your seniors owe you one, huh?
Yeah. So we need to carry this out secretly.
I rather like that sort of scheming myself.
I no longer need this man.
I'll take Zwei...
I'll take Phantom.
Don't tell me...
That's right. This is your passport.
Your true self... your past is in this.
Read the name out loud.
Azuma...
Reiji...
That's right... I... was traveling.
This is the Azuma residence.
Hello? Hello?
There's no way... I could go back.
Tsk! Who are those guys?!
Phantom?!
That damn Scythe!
You idiot! Why the hell are you shooting your own people?
I don't care if Scythe ordered you to do this. Stop being his puppet!
You can't escape! Think about it carefully!
Ein...!
There's no other option.
Ein... I'm the only one... who can protect you now.
I won't abandon you. I'll never let the organization take you.
Let's escape together... from this town...
from Inferno!
Why? Why do you care about me? You won't gain anything.
I don't want you to die. I don't want to see you die without trying to help you.
It's for no one. This is my own will.
You need a new name.
Name?
A name that's not Phantom or some number...
A name for you to live as yourself...
Elen... It's Elen.
I'll call you Elen from now on.
Why Elen?
What does it matter? I decided that name.
It's a name for you to live as yourself, not as a killer or a puppet.
Elen...
Elen... It feels kinda strange.
Elen. Let's search for the past you lost.
Together...
It's not like you, Ein.
Overcome pain with your inner strength.
Master...
Phantom went back to Scythe.
That's a lie!
You're such a fool. You helped the traitor.
You're considered suspect.
Going back to Japan is the last thing you should be worried about now.
But you still have one great option left.
A way to prove your innocence and get Ein back...
What... is it?
You know how to use this, right?
I will kill Scythe.
Scythe!
Rei... ji!
An interesting outcome.
Suitable for the finale.
Among the major organizations that control the East Coast,
we succeeded in making contact with the Renato Family in Boston and
The Baldino Family in Philadelphia over the past three months.
We've started negotiating with their second in commands
on the conditions for joining us.
Our policy always stays the same.
We'll bring prosperity to those who show their allegiance.
We'll bring death to those who defy us.
Destruction and creation...
Everything in this country will change...
It'll be our era... Inferno's era.
Is it really okay to let that woman run everything?
She's excellent. Inferno is growing rapidly now.
She is absolutely essential to us as a coordinator. In addition...
you have a following called the Bloodies.
I have my own as well.
Because she doesn't have any backing like we do,
she can remain neutral to the various interests within the organization.
She's got Phantom.
It's true that Phantom is excellent.
But Phantom alone isn't enough for her to take on the organization...
just like Scythe Master failed to do three months ago.
True.
He's such a fool. Now that he lost Phantom...
he's worthless.
Thank you for waiting, Mr. Giuseppe.
If Claudia gets a swollen head and pulls a stupid stunt like that,
we'll just eliminate her. That's all.
Go ahead and play with this car a little longer.
Come back within an hour.
You think this is fishy?
It's just that I can't see it, Ms. McCunnen.
What would you gain by suggesting such good terms for us?
I want to do you, the Godo Family, a favor for something in return.
The Godo Family's principle is loyalty. So I'm trying to have you owe me one.
So you want backing, huh?
Yes.
I'll give you that 200 million dollars.
But I'll gain something that's worth more than that.
It's true that it makes sense as a business deal.
Then we'll give you a report each time we make a profit.
We're gonna make a killing...
although that means we'll owe you big.
This is just the beginning.
Isn't that right, Romero?
Can't be... He killed this many men by himself?
Who the hell... is he?
Zwei! To acknowledge your loyalty and contributions to the organization,
we'll bestow a glorious title upon you.
We will approve your succession.
From today on, stand at the top and let your name resound...
in the underworld... with fear...
Phantom!
From this moment on, you are Phantom of Inferno.
I will gain everything.
In order to achieve it, I need you, Reiji.
I need a Phantom of my own.
Apparition
Next episode
Okay, Reiji!
Well then, you and I are partners from now on!