It's the first time I've ever worn something this light and cool!
Cal...
This concludes all of Claudia McCunnen's conspiracies.
She trapped me in order to take away my command.
Then she used Zwei, who eventually became Phantom, as a toy...
...and eliminated Wisemel's power.
Her modus operandi is something to be praised.
We received a call from Lizzie Garland.
Claudia McCunnen has gone into hiding.
It seems like she doesn't plan to give us excuses.
Even though it is unbelievable, Scythe Master,
you can think of it as a corroboration for your story.
According to your suggestion,
we must retain the cooperative route with the Godoh Group, which sided with Claudia.
Yes.
Last year's cocaine robbery was surely a painful memory for Inferno.
However...
The profit from the Far Eastern market which the Godoh Group makes...
...is infinitely higher than the sustained losses.
Plus, if you apply the "emotional theory,"
I hope you will be much more considerate when it comes to Mr. Shiga's decision...
...to purge Godoh Daisuke as soon as the truth was revealed.
I see.
This is certainly a logical suggestion.
However...
Of course, the profit that the Godoh Group demands this time will be reduced as a penalty.
I hope you don't mind.
Very well.
Mr. Shiga,
for agitating your men, I assure a most cruel end to Claudia McCunnen.
Thank you, Mr. McGuire.
We are investigating Claudia's whereabouts,
but Phantom is the real problem.
We don't know what he'll do.
If you don't mind, Mr. McGuire,
may I send out Ein to track him down?
A duel between the old and the new Phantom, eh?
Interesting...
You want to work under the Bloodies?
Don't joke around!
Isaac was the one who killed Romero!
A new, strong organization is backing the Bloodies now.
So what?
One day, Inferno's time will come.
You...
Do you want to climb up the ranks that much?
Even by working under your little brother's murderer?
I'll reach where Romero couldn't.
I believe that's the best way to pay my respects to him.
At this point, I don't want to give up.
Come with me, Lizzie Garland.
I need you.
Even though I am part of the Mafia,
I have no intention of becoming a human slave.
There's a righteousness which is above simple loss and profit.
If you promise not to violate this, then...
Very well, Clau.
I'll follow you.
I promise.
You stupid moron.
To go on ahead like that.
You're such a complete imbecile.
It's no good! Nothing is coming out of this!
Fuck.
Call Ms. Lizzie!
There's nothing here.
I found it.
Her car key.
The more I look at it, the more awesome it is!
I'd love to ride the car owner as well.
No doubt.
Reiji.
Thank goodness.
It seems like you're all right.
I hope you at least have a gist of what's going on.
Claudia...
You...
I have no excuses.
I simply did what I had to do
in order to survive in the organization.
I've been deceiving you as well.
I don't plan on giving up just yet.
I can still win.
Reiji,
with you...
I'm going to escape from L.A. and join the East Coast Organization.
But in order to protect myself from Inferno's agents,
I need your help.
I'll wait for you at the 39th Drive Inn.
This time, I'll put my life in your hands.
Cal...
Scars like that can be removed at any time.
But I intentionally did nothing.
Do you know why?
Yes, Master.
What does that scar symbolize?
Insult and downfall.
That is correct.
Ein.
In the past, you were my best achievement.
But you were soiled by that man twice.
Your current self is far from perfection.
You're just like garbage.
But still...
I am right beside garbage like you.
This is because I believe that the time for renewal will come someday.
Kill Zwei.
Cleanse your disgrace with your own hands.
Reclaim yourself and recover that light that was within you.
Then I shall remove that scar from you.
I shall love you as my creation once more.
Thank you, Master.
Can Ein win against Azuma Reiji?
In the worst-case scenario,
she'll sacrifice herself in order to kill Zwei.
Sacrificing her own life...
You're just going to use her and then throw her away?
Thanks to an excellent creation known as Ein,
my art is about to reach a new level.
Even though she is the first full creation that is worth celebrating,
I don't put that much worth into souvenirs.
But this is the final stage.
There must have been a better method.
Sometimes, actors overact in plays
and the brush moves to an unexpected location.
It's the Muse's prank which surprises both the artist and the audience.
Will the final stage be a tragedy?
Or will it be a happy ending?
To leave the finale's joy to fate.
Isn't that something to be thrilled about?
Would her disposal be too much for you to handle, Lizzie Garland?
Don't underestimate me!
Who the hell do you think I am?
You and Claudia are old friends.
Due to your feelings, you might have difficulties pulling the trigger.
Shut the fuck up, you bastard!
A man who has no sense of time will become hated, Reiji.
This is where it all began.
Zwei.
I am...
...not Zwei!
I...
What was I doing until now...?
I've always wanted to race just like this.
Driving at an uncatchable speed, leaving everything behind.
You might end up flying to the sky.
That would be wonderful.
That's true freedom.
Where were you planning to go with all that?
I have no goal.
I just go wherever I can.
That's stupid.
One day, you'll just get tired and stop.
At that point, what will you do when you don't have your legs on the ground anymore?
There are stones which can't be left unturned.
That's true...
But it's okay.
Some scenes can only be seen when you race at this speed.
I just wanted to chase that to the end.
Till the very end...
Idiot...
...I'm sorry.
Do you want to die like this? Without doing anything?
If you're my opponent, then I'm like a rat in a trap.
That's a problem.
I was told to win in a proper fight.
Only the best shall survive.
To prove worthy of being a true Phantom.
I see.
If that's the case, then I'll play with you.
Strong...
Even now,
you are given reasons to fight this badly...
...by that Scythe.
Elen...
Why?
I can't win.
I don't want to win either.
I'm tired of this.
To kill you, and run away from this place...
Then what?
What would change?
To get deceived, played with,
and never be able to protect the one that you love.
There is no exit.
I hate this endless loop.
So please, finish me off this time.
With your hand.
That's right.
I won't blame you.
Nothing could have been done.
Even I can't endure this.
But you are still alive and can fight your way through.
Even now... for that Scythe.
No.
The reason I live is...
...this.
You told me to survive.
I swore to fight for my own will.
This is the scar that you made that time.
I admired you.
Even though it was just a short moment,
your strength that day...
...the proof of your oath that day...
...lives on in this body.
That's why I couldn't throw my life away.
That can't be...
You are another form of myself.
You fought through the path that I gave up myself.
You struggled and fought through.
That is why I lived dreaming about you,
believing that another me is living on freely somewhere.
This scar has always reminded me of that.
But I can no longer endure this pain.
If you give up,
no one can blame you for it.
So please,
if you are going to break that day's oath...
...kill me first.
And end everything once and for all.
I can't do something like that.
Don't worry.
I am Master's failure.
I'm just a doll that's waiting to be disposed of.
Elen...
If this world wasn't a complete hell for for me,
that's because you were alive.
So please, kill me.
I don't want to live in a world without you.
Until now, I couldn't keep any promises.
I thought I had lost everything.
Reiji...
But if I still have a promise I must keep, I'd like to keep it.
This is definitely my last one.
I'll take you away from Scythe.
Looks like the ending wasn't so pleasing.
I wouldn't be too quick to judge.
Perhaps this was really just one act of the show.
Bro!
Thanks, Reiji.
I'll treasure it.
I'll treasure it...
...forever.
Cal.
Cal...
It seems like I can't go to where you are for a while.
I still have an unfinished job that I must do.
Reiji?
Let's go.
Liar.
You said that we wouldn't get separated.
You said that we would be together...