[whispering]
[SOLDIER 1] I think
that's Roy Mustang.
[Soldier 2] The big, bad
Flame Alchemist himself, huh?
[SOLDIER 3] He must have
some serious connections
to have made it
this far at his age.
[SOLDIER 4] Yeah, well
you can't climb to the top
that quickly without
falling just as fast.
[knock knock]
[SECRETARY]
Come in.
[ROY]
Good morning...
Colonel Roy Mustang.
[SECRETARY] Oh, yes,
Colonel Mustang...
I'm terribly sorry, but your
transfer was poorly timed.
His Excellency
the Fuhrer is away.
[ROY]
Where is he?
[SECRETARY] Conducting an
inspection at Southern HQ.
[ROY]
He's in the South?
[sniff sniff]
[DOLCETTO] Something
doesn't smell right to me.
[ROA] Y'know what it
feels like to me...?
Old times.
[BRADLEY] What an
interesting discovery
for such a routine inspection.
[BRADLEY]
Move in!
[GREED]
Hahaha!
A housewife and
a hotheaded brat.
What a team...!
Though to be honest,
it's not one I'm particularly
interested in fighting...
[GREED] I'll just
be on my way now.
[ED]
What?
[IZUMI]
You coward-- Blerggh...
[ED]
Aaahh!
[ED] Teacher!
What's wrong?!
[IZUMI] He ran away...
how pathetic.
[ED]
You okay now?
[IZUMI]
Blergh.
[ED]
Ahh!
[ED] Teacher!
Just hang on!
[MARTEL]
Will you staay put...
Quit struggling, you oaf!
[AL]
I... don't... wanna!
[MARTEL]
Greed!
[GREED] Ah, Martel. I'm glad
to see that you're safe.
[MARTEL] What's
going on up there...?
No one else has
made it back yet.
[GREED]
Yeeahh.
Things have gotten
a little out of hand,
so we need to figure
a way outta here.
[BRADLEY] I can't
let you do that.
[GREED] Just what
do you want, old man?
[AL] It's the Fuhrer...!
Why is he here?
[MARTEL]
King Bradley?!
[GREED] What's the most
powerful man in the land
doing down here?
[BRADLEY]
Not that you'd know,
but growing
old isn't easy.
[GREED]
Huh?
[BRADLEY] This year marks
my sixtieth birthday.
[BRADLEY] It's frustrating
how your body stops moving
the way you want it to...
So I'd like to finish this
job as quickly as possible
and return home...
[GREED] I've got
an idea... Retire.
[splash]
[GREED]
Well look at this!
The old man's
got some moves!
[MARTEL]
Greed!
[AL]
Shhh!
[ARMSTRONG]
Behold...!
You have just had
the rare pleasure
of witnessing the famous
Armstrong statuary technique!
[ROA]
Well then.
I guess my ordinary
methods aren't gonna work.
[ARMSTRONG] Now that's
certainly peculiar.
[gunshots]
[SOLDIER 6] We've secured
the boy and the woman...
Now eliminate every
last one of these freaks...
Those are the
Fuhrer's direct orders!
[ARMSTRONG] You are a most
commendable adversary, sir.
[ROA] And you're just as
tough as ever, Major Armstrong.
[ROA] The last time
I saw you in action
was the Ishvalan Civil War.
[ARMSTRONG]
A former ally, eh...?
Even more reason
to end this...
No need for such
bloodshed... Surrender.
[ROA] And just let
myself be killed?
[SOLDIER 7]
Major!
[DOLCETTO]
Roa!
[GREED]
Urggh!! Hhhhggghh...
[BRADLEY] I understand
why you'd think
you have an advantage
over a man like me
since I possess neither your
impenetrable Ultimate Shield,
nor an Ultimate Spear that
can pierce any substance...
[BRADLEY]
But I'll tell you a secret.
Do you know how I managed
to distinguish myself
amongst the
storms of bullets
on the battlefield
time after time...
to rise to my
current position?
[GREED]
Y-You're...
[BRADLEY] I may not
have the protection
of your Ultimate Shield...
but I clearly see your
weakness with my Ultimate Eye.
[BRADLEY]
Now then, Greed...
How many times am
I going to have to kill you
before you stay dead?
[MARTEL]
Where the hell is Greed?
[AL] I don't know...
It's too dark to see anything.
[MARTEL]
No, Greed!
[AL]
Quiet!
[MARTEL] Let me out...!
C'mon, dammit!
[AL]
No way!
[MARTEL]
I said open up!
[AL] I can't!
He'll kill you!
[BRADELY] That makes fifteen
times you've died now...
How many lives have
you got left? Hmm?
[GREED]
Ahh, damn you...
[DOLCETTO]
Ahhh, crap.
[DOLCETTO] I kinda wish
we'd died back there.
[ROA] There's still plenty
of time to tuck your tail
and run away.
[DOLCETTO]
Trust me, I'd love to...
But I've got this obnoxious
canine sense of loyalty.
[DOLCETTO] Do us a favor
kid and get her out of here.
[ROA]
Protect her.
[MARTEL]
Roa...! Dolcetto!
[MARTEL] Hey...!
Quit trying to stop me!
Let me out!
[AL]
I can't!
[MARTEL] I don't have time
to argue, now open up...!
They need my
help, dammit...!
[AL] I said no!
I can't let you out!
[MARTEL] Just shut up!
I need out of here!
[MARTEL] You're not
gonna make me sit here
and watch my friends
get killed, are you?!
[AL] They asked me
to protect you...!
So quit struggling
and be quiet!
[MARTEL]
Dolcetto! No!
Rooooaaa!
[MARTEL] Please.
I'm begging you.
[AL]
I'm sorry... I can't.
[GREED] Whoa, that was
a little excessive...
Killing me is one thing,
but they're not coming back.
[BRADLEY] Pitying the lost lives
of your pawns...? Pathetic.
[GREED] Excuse me...?
Are you senile...?
Did you forget who
I am, old man...?
I'm the living
incarnation of greed...
Those weren't my
friends, Bradley,
they were my possessions...
Money! Women! Henchmen!
They're all possessions!
[GREED]
So killing my henchmen
is the same as
stealing from me...!
And I don't let people
take what's mine!
[BRADLEY]
Greed...
You grow more
pathetic by the second.
[BRADLEY] Now you stay put.
I'll be right back.
[AL]
We've gotta run.
[BRADLEY]
Not so fast.
[BRADLEY] Aren't you
the younger brother
of Edward Elric...?
They didn't hurt
you, did they...?
Can I help you at all?
[AL] Uh, sure...
I mean no, no, I'm fine...!
Thanks, but I'm alright.
[AL]
Martel!
Don't do this!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[AL] Stop it,
Martel! Please!
[MARTEL]
Die, Bradleyyy!
[splash]
[YOUNG ED]
Aaaalllll!
[AL] It's Mom...!
Wait, Mom! Wait...!
Mommm...! Mommmm...!
[ED] Al...!
Wake up...! Al...!
Say something...! Al!
[AL]
Brother?
[ED]
You okay?
[AL]
Are you okay?
You're covered in blood.
[ARMSTRONG] We thought
it best to open you
and remove her
before you awoke.
[AL sobbing]
I couldn't save her.
[ED] You can't blame
yourself, Al...
Come on.
Let's go home, 'kay.
[ED]
Al?
[BRADLEY]
Hold it, you two.
[BRADLEY] There are
a few questions
I need to ask both of
you before you can leave.
[BRADLEY] Have either of
you had any previous dealings
with the man who referred
to himself as Greed?
[ED]
'Course not.
[BRADLEY] Did you happen
to trade any manner
of information with him?
[ED]
None at all...
And the military wasn't
even mentioned, not once.
[BRADLEY]
That isn't my concern...
Let me be more specific...
If you arranged a deal or
shared any knowledge with him...
Then I'll execute
both of you right now.
[BRADLEY] I'll ask again,
did you share any knowledge
that might affect
the military?
[ED] No...
Can we go now?
[BRADLEY] I am curious
about your steel arm
and leg and your
brother's armor body...
Is there any connection
between the two?
[BRADLEY] You really
are an honest kid.
[BRADLEY]
Alright, men, pull out.
[BRADLEY] And you make
sure to take good care
of your younger
brother, Edward.
[IZUMI] I appreciate
everything you've done
for the Elric brothers.
[BRADLEY] Oh no,
it's nothing at all.
It's simply one of the
many duties of the military
to protect our
State Alchemists...
But what about you?
I'm sure you could use a
little extra protection.
[IZUMI] You mean as
a State Alchemist?
[BRADLEY]
Why yes, exactly.
[IZUMI] You're asking
a bedridden housewife
to join the military...?
You can't be serious.
Is the country really
in so much trouble
that you'd need the
help of someone like me?
[BRADLEY] There's
no need to be harsh.
[BRADLEY]
Well. I will be back.
[BRADLEY] I'll keep
my fingers crossed
that when I do return,
perhaps you'll have
had a change of heart.
[ED] There's something
I forgot to mention...
Greed had an
Uroboros tattoo.
[ARMSTRONG]
I'm not sure I follow.
[ED] Think back...
The fifth laboratory?
The Philosopher's Stone?
Remember the guys I told
you and Colonel Hughes about?
[ARMSTRONG]
Colonel Hughes? I...
Listen, Edward Elric.
[ARMSTRONG] Do not...
do anything rash.
[ED]
Sure.
[ARMSTRONG]
Well then... Goodnight.
[AL]
Brother?
They're back...
All the memories of when
my body was taken away...?
I remember.
[ED]
What'd you see?
[AL] Well it was
definitely weird.
[AL] But unfortunately,
I didn't find out anything
about how to get
our bodies back.
[ED]
That's okay.
[AL] So I guess we
haven't made any progress.
[ED] No. That's
not entirely true.
[ED] You remember
what the Fuhrer told us
back in Central?
About the unrest amongst
the ranks of the military?
[AL] And it all
had something to do
with the
Philosopher's Stone
and those Uroboros guys...
He said he was trying
to gather info on them.
[ED] Well Greed was
obviously connected
to them somehow...
But if so... why'd the
Fuhrer slaughter everyone?
[ED] If he was trying to
figure out what they're up to,
why didn't he catch
them and make them talk?
[AL] Yeah,
good point...
It also seems a little
weird that the Fuhrer himself
would lead an attack
against such a small group.
[ED]
Sure does...
No matter how you look at it,
none of this adds up.
[ED] We've been warned...
but we need to get closer.
[LUST]
Welcome back, Fuhrer...
How was your
inspection of the South?
[BRADLEY]
To say the least,
it was a very
productive visit...
It seems both
Fullmetal's younger brother
and their teacher are worthy
candidates for human sacrifice.
[BRADLEY] Oh and
one other thing...
I made an
unexpected catch.
[LUST] Talk about a
blast from the past...
It's been a century
since I've seen that face.
[LUST]
Rise and shine, Greed,
you can't
sleep all day.
[GREED] Well, well.
The gang's all here.
[LUST] Looks like
your Ultimate Shield
let you down after all.
[GREED] Maybe,
but you never do,
Lust the Lascivious...
Feel free to pierce me
with your Ultimate Spear
anytime you want.
[GREED] Hello,
Gluttony the Voracious.
Still haven't found the
right diet for you yet, huh?
[GREED] And little
Envy the Jealous.
Please! For the last
time, get a new outfit.
[GREED] And where is Sloth
the Indolent these days?
[LUST] I'm sure he'd love
to be here slacking off...
but we have to
keep him working.
[GREED] Sorry to say it,
but it's kind of depressing
that none of
you have changed
in the past one
hundred years... So...
[GREED]
Who's the new addition?
[BRADLEY] I am
Wrath the Furious.
[GREED] Fuhrer King
Bradley and Wrath,
one and the same.
[LUST]
Indeed...
The humans know him as
the leader of Amestris...
But the truth is that
he was created by Father
for the final
stage of the plan.
[GREED] A Homunculus
that can grow older...?
That's impossible.
[ENVY]
Oh really?
I thought nothing
was impossible...
You used to toss
that one around
like it was your
catch phrase...
you change your
mind or something?
[GREED] Shut your
worthless trap, ugly.
[GREED] Uh-oh.
That's a scary face.
Go on and let it out...
Why don't you show us what
you really look like...?
You hideous freak.
[ENVY] You scum...
call me that again
and I will destroy you.
[FATHER] Stop your
nonsense. Both of you.
[FATHER] It's time you
resolve this sibling rivalry.
Your father does not wish
to see such ugly behavior.
[GREED]
Hey, Pops, long time...
I know it's been a
hundred years and all,
but you sure
do look decrepit.
[FATHER]
Greed...
You are both my son and
you are a piece of my soul...
So why would you
betray your loving father?
[GREED]
I'm surprised you ask...
I mean, you know the answer
to that better than anyone, Dad.
I'm Greed the Avaricious...
You were the one that
made me this way, after all.
I'm just being myself.
[GREED] I simply
had larger ambitions
than spending my
life working for you.
[FATHER] And if I were
to ask you to return
and work for me again?
[GREED]
Never!
[FATHER]
As you wish.
[gears turning]
Geez, talk about cheesy.
[splash]
Ahhhhh!!
Hahaha!
Why don'tcha
come on in, kids,
the water's fine!
[GREED]
Nice and hot!
Just like the
flames in hell...!
I'll send you a postcard,
let you know what
they're like...!
And when the rest
of you get there--
I'll be waiting for you!
[FATHER] Now return from
whence you were born...
Return to my depths
and rejoin my soul...
Return, Greed!
[GREED] If that's
what you want, Dad...!
Just don't blame me when
I give you a stomach-ache!
You did it to yourself!
[FATHER] I propose a
toast, my children...
I shall drink to
the promised day.
And to your
undying loyalty.
[SELIM]
Father!
[SELIM] Welcome
home, Father!
I'm so glad you're back!
[BRADLEY] And it's
good to be back, Selim.
[SELIM] Did you
have a good trip?
[BRADLEY]
Why yes,
I'd say it was productive
at the very least.
[BRADLEY'S WIFE]
I do wish
you would act
your age, darling.
Why couldn't
you just retire
and try to enjoy some peace
and quiet for a change.
[BRADLEY] Hey... now,
I'm not quite that old yet...
Oh Selim, you'll never guess
who I ran into down south.
The Fullmetal Alchemist!
[SELIM] You saw the
little alchemist...?
Can I meet him
sometime Father?
[BRADLEY'S WIFE]
You sure do like
to hear about Edward,
don't you, Selim?
[SELIM] Well, he is the youngest
State Alchemist ever, right?
That's so cool!
I mean, he's not
much older than me!
[SELIM] And If he can
learn alchemy at his age,
then maybe I can to!
[BRADLEY'S WIFE] Why
would you want to learn
something like that?
[SELIM] So I can get my
state license, of course!
And then I could
help Father!
[BRADLEY]
You never know, Selim...
Maybe you will help
me out someday.
[NARRATOR] Like pebbles
tossed into a pond,
a handful of outsiders are
scattered throughout Amestris.
The ripples each one
creates roll inward,
until they collide
and form a whirlpool.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode fifteen.
Envoy From the East.
Behind this innocent
smile, I hide a blade.
And I will find my way
to the Philosopher's Stone.