When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
My dear Hayate, are you all right?
Of course, I am all right!
C-Counting the stitches of the tatami
mat is a piece of cake for me!
My! That is so impressive
One, two, three, four, five...
He's pretty far gone.
Yeah...
123,600. 123,601. 123,602.
My dear Hayate?
What is it? I'm on the
123,602nd stitch right now.
123,603. 123,604.
He's got it bad.
Yeah, bad...
123,605...
Someone like me deserves to
get abandoned by the Miss.
Um...
Being allowed to work in a
grand mansion like that...
It was like a dream to begin with.
Um...
I've just woken from the dream, that's
all. Nothing to be sad about...
Um, my dear Hayate?
Shove!
I-Isumi?!
Oh, pardon me!
You seem so down. That is...
I was trying to cheer you up...
Pardon me for doing something
I am unaccustomed to.
But I did not know what to do...
N-No, you must not laugh!
Oh, no. I feel better now, thanks to that!
What?
So I am fine now!
That's right! I have no choice
but to do my best here!
So, I will work hard and count every
last tatami stitch in this house!
My! That is so impressive!
1! 2! 3! 4! 5! 6! 7! 8! 9! 10!
He really has lost it.
11! 12! 13! 14!
He might be beyond help at this point...
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Hi! Do you know who I am?! Yes! It's Gilbert!
Now, another "Hayate the Combat
Butler" is about to start!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
And hunkering down is no fun
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Hearts Wavering
Video Rental
V Tachibana
Honestly!
Selling Hayate to the Saginomiyas?
What a child you are!
It cannot be helped. Things
just ended up that way!
Do you plan to keep losing the important
things in your life like that?
Shut up! Why are you here anyway?!
The members of the SP were
kind enough to tell me.
Aren't you guys supposed to be on my side?!
O-Of course, we are on your side, Miss Nagi!
Oh, is that right?
I see.
So you are on Nagi's side...
Traitors!
People will not follow your lead
with just your blustering whims.
Maria is so impressive!
Commanding those big men so easily!
She's not on the same level
as some rinky-dink maid.
Rinky-dink?! Who are you
calling a rinky-dink maid?!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
But I just hope he isn't crying.
What?
I mean, if you sold him for 150 million,
it's not much different than what
his terrible parents did to him.
Hayate certainly seems like a
very sensitive person, so...
He is a boy who puts a smile on his
face and cries in his heart, after all.
And if he's always being yelled at
by an insensitive girl like Nagi,
I wouldn't be surprised if he wanted to cry.
C-Could it be...
that I've done something awful to Hayate?
Needless to say, everyone thought,
"You just realized that now?!"
I... I...
Nagi?
Video Rental
(V Tachibana)
What're you crying for?!
I'm not really crying!
Hayate might hate me now.
Y-You need not worry!
The Young Sir will do
something about it, Miss!
Me?! I'm technically depressed
about Isumi here, too!
It will be fine!
The power of your love will surely
capture Isumi's attention!
Oh, you think?
But Wataru's not popular...
Bastard! You picking a fight?!
Miss Nagi!
Fine, whatever. I'll do something
about it, so wait here!
What?! O-Oh, Young Sir?!
But how are you going to bring him back?
Oh, that will be easy.
Hayate probably thinks
that Nagi hates him now,
so if I tell him that Nagi is in
tears and wants him to come home...
But Isumi...
My instinct tells me that she does
not love him so terribly much.
Well, everything will be fine if
you just leave it to those two.
But Hayate probably hates me now...
Then why don't you just test it?
Uh, who?
More like, test what?
I mean, why don't you just test his love?
Um, Miss, do you know this man?
Yeah, I'm ashamed to say we're related.
But we are not just related.
I'm a candidate to be heir
of the Sanzenin fortune
and my name's Gilbert!
Um, are you two really related?
I would sever the tie if I could.
So? What's this about testing his love?
In other words, if there is love
between you and that butler,
he should be able to overcome any obstacle.
For example, if we say
that I've kidnapped you,
he may or may not come for
you faster than anyone else!
Are you planning to fake a kidnapping?!
You should not do that!
Yeah, I'll decline.
Why?!
Hayate probably won't come!
Actually, he might come, but I think
that would be like out of sympathy...
Is that so?
What a cowardly brat you are.
To think such a sissy with no
stomach to face a challenge
is the Sanzenin family heir!
Our modern-day society has
truly gone to the dogs!
Fine!
Fake a kidnapping or whatever you want to do!
Miss!
But I will be the one who wins!
That's what I like to hear!
Meanwhile, at the Saginomiya residence...
Are you all right with leaving
things as they are, Hayate?
All right or not, there's nothing
I can do about it anyway...
That child says and does things
on the spur of the moment.
It would be endless if you
took it all seriously.
Yes, well, that's true, but...
Talk about harsh...
Besides, don't you want to come back, Hayate?
Don't you feel any attachment towards
Nagi and the Sanzenin estate?
No... attachment... or memories...
Wow! The Tokyo underground
never fails to impress!
But why come all this way to such a place?
The obstacles must be large
in order to measure love.
Don't tell me you plan to fight Hayate again.
Yes!
No matter how strong that butler is,
it will be impossible for
him to win against this!
Wh-What are you going to
do if Hayate gets injured?!
There is no need to worry.
The scientist who built this is a genius.
So the specs are fully human-friendly!
Hey, Eight, what's this part for again?
Oh, that's the control
chip for the giant robot
that you made yesterday
at a friend's request.
Huh... So I made a giant robot...
What?!
I was nodding off, so I don't remember much.
B-But that's impressive!
What?
Because you made that incredible thing,
even when you were nodding off.
Really? Do you think so?
But it's not that big a deal.
I just put your Version 8.1 system
in your prototype body. That's all.
Th-That's the data from when
I was the most reckless!
Isn't that really dangerous?
Oh, please, Eight!
That's why I made the control chip!
I-I see...
Aw, man, I'm so bored.
I wish something good would happen.
Osaka Specialty Twirly Octopus Balls
No way! They're freshly made!
It's probably a present from God!
Do you like sushi?!
(Sushi suki ka?!)
Please open up the country.
(Kaikoku shite kudasai.)
Will Hayate come for me?
No, even if he does come,
Hayate may no longer...
Man, it's so comfortable
here at Isumi's place!
She's quiet and kind, unlike
that spoiled little miss.
Man, getting sold was the way to go!
Hey, now, that's your own wild imagination.
Th-That's right! It all began
because Hayate cheated on me!
Who cheated on ya?
Sakuya! What are you doing here?!
What am I doin'? I thought I'd
watch over what my bro's doin'.
What?! G-Gilbert is your big brother?!
I didn't know until recently myself,
but it's 'cause he's a love
child born to another mother.
But we look alike, don't we?
And that makes you happy?
But how'd things end up this way?
That's because... Hayate cheated
on me with Isumi and...
Huh?!
It wasn't just Isumi!
Hayate said he plays with you often, too!
Sure, we play often.
Doin' slapstick comedy routines.
Like I said, doin' slapstick comedy routines.
Ah-ha! So, what, Little Nagi?
Yer only 13 and ya thought "play"
meant somethin' like that?
No, you idiot! You're wrong!
Of course, it's slapstick comedy
routines! I didn't have the wrong idea!
Don't ya worry. I know, I know.
Precocious brat.
But man, that's a terrible story.
That butler-in-debt did nothin'
wrong and ya sold him off.
He'll never come.
Hayate will never come to rescue me.
Little missy, it's by overcoming
such misunderstandings and conflicts
that trust grows stronger between people!
So you mustn't fear misunderstandings!
"Love" is coming in spite of such things!
What? The machine just...
Bro!
Kill.
Kill the stinking brat with
blonde pigtails and her butler.
My life is in a shambles
because of those two!
So it's saying. What shall we do?
What to do? I'm not going to sit
around listening to a loser gripe.
Yeah, why don't we just leave it and run?
We'll just say my bro is deadmeat
in there and that should do it.
Please don't abandon me, my sister!
Besides, this thing is out
to get the little miss Nagi!
I don't think you'll be able
to run from it so easily!
That's right! I'm not forgiving
that girl with the blonde pigtails!
Huh? Where did she go?
Where did that little girl go?
Ya really should pay good money for CPUs.
But I am glad that it seems like this
situation will not get out of control.
The Young Sir may be worried,
so I will give him a call.
Good idea.
What's up, Saki? What is it?
Don't tell me Nagi's been
kidnapped or something.
What? No, um, it is not a kidnapping, but...
Damn you, Nagi Sanzenin!
I'll friggin' roll you!
H-Hey, don't tell me we're talking murder!
N-No, that is not it!
It's not just a kidnapping, but
it's about to become a murder?!
It is all right. She has yet to be killed.
Then, Nagi's on the verge of being killed?!
What?!
Oh! Hey, Saki! Saki!
Um, Wataru, the phone
call you just received...
I-I don't really get it,
but Saki's screwed up and Nagi's been
kidnapped and about to get killed...
What?!
I-It can't be... Nagi...
Hayate!
Uh, what? Hayate?
Aw... No helpin' it, I guess.
I'll call 'em back.
'Cause I bet they totally got the wrong idea.
Oh, I know!
Oh, hello? Is this Wataru?
If I take out all of them,
This is Sakuya. So, anyway...
one of them would be the little girl!
We're in a real bad
situation, so come save us.
What?!
Hey!
This is bad. They really are in big trouble!
What?!
It will be all right.
Because my dear Hayate has gone to save Nagi.
Misses!
That thing's comin' after us!
What?!
How dare you go after
our precious Miss Nagi?!
Even another Sanzenin family member
will not be forgiven for that!
Shut up!
If you don't want to get hurt, hurry
up and hand over that pigtail girl!
We can't have you underestimating
the power of the Sanzenin family SP!
What?!
Behold! You damn piece of
Andro Army scrap metal!
This is what the Sanzenin
family SP is made of!
Found you, pigtails!
Now, that solves everything.
Like hell it does!
That is right! This is too much!
I've got you cornered, little girl!
No, no, no!
What are you going to do now
that you have me cornered?!
What?
What am I going to do?
Blush.
Then, I think it's time for...
What was that "blush" about?!
And the way your hands are
moving is extremely lewd!
Shut up, little girl!
Dodge, you idiot!
Young Sir!
Sheesh! Quit giving me so much trouble!
What are you doing here, Young Sir?
Oh, this place is right under Isumi's house.
Wh-What?
Young Sir!
You dummy!
I've always thought of him as a child,
but somewhere along the way,
he's become all grown up!
DX Animation
Tama's Sinister Design!!
All grown up...
And will he be watching videos like that?
You must not!
Huh?!
It is still too early for
you to watch pervy videos!
Wha?! I-I don't watch stuff like that!
Hey, you people! You need
to hurry up and run!
You won't get away from me this time!
That's enough, you junkyard robot!
Didn't you hear me, you piece of junk?!
You defective crab bastard!
Wh-Why you!
I swear! Your design is even
worse than fake Gundam models!
How dare you make trouble for us?!
That's why you're not popular!
Crushed!
I, Nagi Sanzenin, will be your opponent!
Then let's see you do just that!
Watch out, Miss!
Where's Hayate?!
He should've headed over here before me!
Oh, I see.
So Hayate really isn't coming for me...
Miss Nagi!
He probably won't come for me.
He probably hates me.
Run, Nagi!
Die!
Hayate...
HAYATE!
You called, Miss?
Hayate, why are you...
Why? Because you called my name.
The bitterness you carved into me...
You better not tell me you've forgotten!
Are you hurt or injured anywhere, Miss?
I'll tear you and the little girl apart!
No, I'm perfectly fine.
Wait... Hey, you! Don't ignore me!
I see. I'm glad to hear that!
No need to be impatient.
I fully intend to hold you responsible
for putting Miss in danger!
What?!
Could it be that he's mad?
More like, when a guy who usually
doesn't get mad gets mad...
It's scary!
Hey, boy, please don't forget about me!
I, Gilbert, am on board this mecha!
I see, so you're the culprit behind
the Miss's attempted kidnapping.
Th-That's not quite right...
You see, I conspired with the
Miss and the others to...
Conspired with them, you say?!
Then are you claiming
that Saki and the others
came up with the idiotic idea
of faking a kidnapping?!
How about it, Saki?
That's not true! My bro Gilbert
kidnapped her for her fortune!
See?! I knew it!
My sister!
So, in the end, all you can trust is money!
In that case, I will meet
the condition that was set
and make the Sanzenin family fortune mine!
Or rather... Destroy everyone!
I will not let you!
I will not allow the Miss to
be endangered any further!
Hayate?!
Tell this to the other
potential heirs as well!
If you want the Sanzenin fortune,
first, defeat their butler, Hayate Ayasaki!
Y-You idiot! Do you have any
idea how dangerous that is?!
I do know!
Besides, there's no way that old
geezer Mikado will accept that...
She might come to hate ya over
some other misunderstandin'
and kick ya out again!
It doesn't really matter.
Even if the Miss comes to hate me...
It won't change the fact
that I care about the Miss.
Quit the romantic comedy thing!
No matter how cool you act,
you cannot win against this
robot, Hayate Ayasaki!
You will be the one to fall victim to me!
Hayate, watch out!
There's no need to worry!
I prepared all kinds of things in
anticipation of just such a situation!
What?!
Wait, that's against the Firearms
and Swords Control Law!
Not to worry.
I'm thoroughly familiar with
how to operate this thing.
From where?!
Besides, this Firearms and
Swords Control Law thing...
When it comes to protecting the Miss,
I really couldn't care
less about such things.
Do you still want to continue this?
You can defeat me, but a second
and a third Gilbert will surely...
What demon king do you think you are?!
Sorry! Sorry! I surrender! I surrender!
The furious gunfight came to an end...
Hayate...
What is it, Miss?
And the girl and the butler
gazed at one another...
No... That is...
"I'm sorry I fired you on
the spur of the moment!
"I apologize, so come back
with me to the mansion,"
is what Nagi wants to say, but...
Come to think of it,
I changed the condition for the
inheritance on the spur of the moment,
so it may actually be more
dangerous for me to be near you.
Oh, but never mind that.
I'm Isumi's butler now, aren't I?
B-But that's...!
But I abandoned my duties when I came here,
so I may have been fired by now.
In that case, I will be out on the
streets again with my 150 million debt.
I wish there was a cute girl somewhere,
who would find me a new job.
Th-Then...
Why don't you be my butler?
I will, Miss!
Are you all right with this, Isumi?
It is not good to buy or
sell a person for money.
Besides...
Besides?
Those two are very
well-suited to one another.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful, it'll
be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
I have a good idea! I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I'm Sakuya Aizawa.
Well, Miss Aizawa, this
is an awfully sober song.
The cry of my soul's in this song, after all.
It's the pensive song of a woman
who lives for duty and compassion.
It just sounds old fogy to me.
Nagi, yer still a kid, so ya can't
understand how good this song is yet.
I don't care if I never do!
Next time, we'll have a special
edition. Please look forward to it!
Bye-bye!
Preview
Hey, Hayate, what is the meaning of this?!
The next episode of "Hayate
the Combat Butler" is...
Enough of this weird joke!
What? Um...
I-I won't let you have Hayate!
Because he's...
Because he's my precious butler!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"The Delivery Was Made in 29 Minutes,
So Please Pay the Stipulated Fee...
"Is a Thing of the Distant Past".
Hayate has amnesia?!
That's impossible!
The Delivery Was Made in 29 Minutes,
So Please Pay the Stipulated Fee...
Is a Thing of the Distant Past
Next time, you'll be
thrilled by Hayate in drag!