No, no, no, no, no!
It's okay! Really!
People are trying to eat lunch,
so please stop...!
Seeing is believing.
Come!
Bear witness!
Big relief, huh?
Aisaka being back.
Yeah...
Sure is.
Hey, what's all the fuss about?
Oh, right, Valentine's Day is coming up.
These giddy youngsters
won't hear a word I say.
Oh, Valentine's Day.
Come to think of it, I forgot.
- You can't fool me!
- Teach...?
You'll start fawning over each other
the second my back is turned!
Public displays of affection at school...!
Man, there's no point in giving or
getting chocolates at school...
School is for learning.
W-We're being lectured by Haruta?
I say something wrong again?
What's school for, then?
Health and gym?
Oh, oops.
Takasu-kun, Aisaka-san.
Please come to the reception
office after school.
(My Silky Love)
Every time I think of you
MY SILKY LOVE nijuu yojikan zutto
(My Silky Love)
for 24 hours straight,
MY SILKY LOVE kimino koto omoutabi
(My Silky Love)
It only makes me feel
MY SILKY LOVE modokashii kono kimochi
(My Silky Love)
that much more impatient.
MY SILKY LOVE tada afure kaetteku
It's so simple just to say I love you.
But when you come close to me,
sukito ieba kantan nanoni
kimiga maeni kichauto
my own emotions go awry
and get in my way.
kyaraga sobie watashino
koto wo jamashiteru
I can bring myself to do anything.
That's who I'm supposed to be.
itsumonaraba tsuyoki de ikeru
sonna seikakunanoni
But I just can't break this
wall down no matter what.
donna ganbatte mitemo kabewa kuzusenai
Please understand these feelings for you.
sasshite hoshii kono kimoch iwo
That's why these gazes of mine,
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimini
they tell my love for you.
daisuki dayoto okuru shisen
Now gather up my courage!
saidaino yuukide
A fragile heart made of silk,
yabure souna shirukuno haato
I realized that by meeting you,
kimini atte kizuita yatto
I was so clumsy when it comes to love.
ainiwa bukiyou dattan datte
A forgotten scar left in my heart,
wasure kaketa koino kizuato
and I suddenly felt it sting deep inside.
kyuuni uzuki dashitano kyunto
I have to say that I love you someday...
itsukawa watashi rashiku sukito iwanakya
Or it'll keep making me weaker.
imayori yowaku nacchauyo
Path to Take
Takasu-kun, you still haven't
finalized your career plan.
And Aisaka-san, you never turned one
in at the beginning of the school year.
Sorry, I'm still talking it over with my mother.
How does she feel? She wants
you to go to college, right?
Yasuko...
My mother has been pushing herself
too hard for too many years.
I don't want her to suffer anymore,
so I'm not going to college.
That's my plan.
And why haven't you turned
in yours, Aisaka-san?
I'm rich, so I'll never need to work.
Meaning there's no need to study.
There's nothing I even want to do.
Why are the two of you so...
Not going to college isn't that—
I know.
It's just, what you do with your lives
is completely up to you now.
No more blaming others for what happens.
The responsibility is all yours.
That's why I want you to give
this careful consideration.
Takasu-kun...
You've never gone against your
mother's wishes before, have you?
Bring your career plans to the
faculty office when you're done.
Reception Office
The rest of my life, huh...?
What are you—?
Ta-da!
Hey, wait!
That's the form we're supposed to turn in!
Hey!
I don't need that crap.
There's no way I can think about the future.
I have enough problems as it is.
I've always, always denied who I am,
and wondered why I turned out this way...
What could I have done differently?
I can't even figure out what
I want to do right now.
There is one thing.
I want to experience a normal love.
What are you doing?
B-But don't you have someone...?
E-Er...
I do?
Can't think of anybody off the top of my head.
I wanted to be born into a normal household,
and grow up to be a normal girl.
Then meet and get to know
a guy in a normal fashion.
That's the kind of love
I wanted to experience.
Why past tense?
Like I said. It's impossible.
Everything was wrong from the beginning.
I'm not normal.
What do you mean by normal?
Is there even a right way?
A wrong way?
Who decides that anyway?
Hold on...
Why are you suddenly lecturing me?
Oh, uh...
That wasn't my intention...
Where are you going?
What about your career plan?
I'm going home!
I don't give a damn about that crap!
Taiga...
Hello...
Like, seriously!
I already said I won't do it!
How many times do I have to...
Please, Kawashima.
Won't you reconsider?
I don't have time to deal with this.
If you'll excuse me, sir, I must go.
Wait, Kawashima-kun!
Why are you just standing there!?
Go after her!
Now! Hurry!
What are you going to do with my shoe?
Give it back.
Got a shoe fetish?
Sick.
Oh, wait...
I can't believe this!
Were you trying to set a record
in shoe throwing?
I already apologized.
Hey.
Why were you called to the faculty office?
I refused a request to model our school
uniform for next year's brochure.
Why'd you refuse?
Isn't that your thing?
Because I don't want to.
I mean, who knows how long
I'll be at this school?
Don't tell me you're still hung
up on your fight with Kushi—
No.
A peon like Kushieda Minori
could never affect my life.
Then why did you say that?
I'd originally planned to leave
this school after the first term.
Since the mess with the
stalker had died down.
You never mentioned anything...
I decided I'd like to stay a bit longer.
If I could, I'd stay here
with everyone forever...
Then why...?
I saw Taiga getting hurt.
If I was the only one who understood her,
then I had to be the one to save her.
Or so I thought...
But...
I now see that everything would've
worked out just fine without me.
Kawashima, you...
Wait!
Why now...?
Taiga?
I'm busy—
Will the bar be fine without me?
And my shift at the bakery...
They even had a cute uniform for me...
I called both. Don't worry about a thing.
Just get some rest.
Okay...
H-H-How i-is...
Ya-chan's sleeping, so shush.
Sh-Shh...
Ryuji, how is she?
She'll be just fine.
Whew...
It scared me so much when I looked through
the window and saw her collapse...
Ryuji?
Hey, where are you going?
To buy something for Yasuko to eat.
Wait!
What about your jacket?
Ryuji?
You didn't bring your wallet, keys, phone,
or even your dumb grocery bag!
Keep it together, idiot!
Hurry up and put this on!
What about you...?
Look at yourself.
You should take it.
No way!
I'm fine! You wear it!
Ryuji?
Hey...
Go home.
No.
Go home. I'm serious.
No!
You're acting weird!
Just go home, okay!?
Ryu—
What are you doing?
It's my fault.
Yasuko collapsed because of me...
I'm to blame...
It's all my fault...
What are you talking about?
She's anemic.
She wasn't feeling well.
- It's not your fault!
- If I were more responsible...
If Yasuko were willing to trust me...
If she would just rely on me...
This never would've happened...
Ryuji!
Ryuji...
What...am I supposed to—?
It'll be okay!
It'll be...okay?
Yes, it will!
It'll be okay!
Because I'm a super mommy!
Ryuji?
What's wrong?
Stay...
I'll be okay.
There's somewhere I need to go.
Oh, that's a problem.
We'll be swamped the next couple days on
account of it being Valentine's and all.
I'm very sorry. She won't be able to make it.
Doubt I'll be able to find someone
to cover her shift...
I'm very sorry!
I'll do it.
Really? Are you sure?
- Man, you're a lifesaver!
- Taiga...
I'm not doing this for you.
I want to help Ya-chan.
Please let me work too!
What?
I was fired from my job at the bakery?
But—
Oh well. These things happen.
I'll find another job.
Wh-Why am I the one being consoled?
W-Wel-c-co—
Welcome!
Nothing's selling...
You need to be louder.
You have to compensate for a face that
was never meant for customer service.
Hey, now...
Whoa, you're actually working!
Yo, Taka-chan.
What are you—?
Haruta-kun, which one do you want?
They say that if you get greedy and buy
a big one, something bad will happen.
I don't think that's true.
Okay then, I'll take the big one.
May I please have this one?
Th-That'll be 580 yen.
You have an older sister?
She's not my sister.
Girlfriend.
What!?
Well, have fun working.
Sure is cold outside.
Why don't we go someplace warm?
- Good plan.
- Why...?
There is seriously something
wrong with this world.
Noto!
What are you doing here?
No reason. Just happened
to be in the area...
Oh, hey.
Have you seen anyone else around?
Like Ami-chan, or the lovely Nanako...?
No, I haven't seen Kihara.
Huh!?
I don't give a damn about her!
I just, y'know...
Wondered if she's going nuts about
giving Kitamura chocolate!
So, you know anything?
Not that I personally care!
I don't! But Tiger, you're worried, yeah?
About, y'know...
Why would I be worried?
And why do you care if Kihara Maya
gives Kitamura-kun chocolate?
Oh, I see.
You're in love with her.
So after all those fights, you suddenly
found yourself attracted to her...
Heh, didn't think that actually happened.
What are you saying!?
That's just wrong, Tiger!
Nothing wrong about it.
It's perfectly natural.
When a male stamen and a female pistil—
Idiot!
You're messed up!
What's up with him?
Crap...
We better sell some stuff
before we get yelled at.
Guess we don't have a choice.
Time to summon the lethal weapon.
Ew.
I thought you were alone.
Y-Yo...
I'm leaving.
Come on.
You're already here!
I'll even let you hold this.
What? Screw that.
Don't make me do weird things.
I'm gorgeous, so I'm bound
to attract attention.
Yes, yes. You're positively stunning.
The center of attention.
So take it.
And say, "I love the chocolate here!"
as loud as you can.
Come again?
You want me to advertise?
Uh-huh.
Forget that.
Why would I do something so stupid?
Be nice, Dumb-chi.
Or, I know. Buy another one
with your own money.
And give it to Minorin to make up.
I've been watching you a lot
more closely than you think.
You're having a difficult time
making up with Minorin.
Your Chihuahua heart quivers.
Hey.
Don't make stuff up!
If it makes you uncomfortable,
I'll call Minorin for you.
Man, Valentine's Day came
at such a perfect time.
You...!
Huh? Is that Kawashima Ami-chan?
You're right!
She's adorable! Look at that cute face!
It really is Ami-chan!
Is she buying chocolates from here?
I love these chocolates!
My model friends all rave about them.
I'm gonna buy some!
The same kind as Ami-chan!
Huh, she knows what she's doing.
Excuse me.
Huh? Yes!
I-I'll be right with you!
Ryuji, what are you...?
Excuse me, I'd like this one!
Y-Yes!
Hey, Kawashima!
You really like to chase people around.
You have stalker potential.
And you really like to run away.
You're running from a lot more than just me.
Just to be clear!
I've never wanted you gone or anything.
Besides...
Everyone will be disappointed if you leave.
Everyone likes you.
"Everyone"?
Yeah, everyone!
You really don't get it, do you?
Look, Taiga's getting overwhelmed.
Crap!
But I don't want everyone to like me...
I guess...I don't get it, either.
Thanks a lot!
See you two tomorrow!
We reached our quota, you know.
You didn't have to buy the rest...
It's fine.
I'm gonna pass them out as gifts.
Gifts?
Uh-huh.
Since I ruined the trip for everyone.
Kitamura-kun, Minorin,
and Dumb-chi, I guess.
And...
If I were to give you chocolates,
would you be happy?
I'm just not sure.
Wh-What do you mean by that?
I'd have to be a heartless bastard to not be
happy about you giving me chocolates.
Fine.
Then I'll do it.
I don't want to hand them out as-is.
Maybe I'll try to make them special.
I just hope everyone likes them...
Something smells good!
You're going back to work already?
Don't you worry. I'm in tip-top shape!
I need to thank Taiga-chan!
Hey...
What are you planning,
gathering us all here like this?
It's Valentine's Day today, so I made
chocolates to show my appreciation!
Made? By yourself?
That's amazing!
Wow, it'd be a shame to eat them.
Aren't those the chocolates
you were selling yesterday?
So you've finally learned to lie—
No!
I reused the boxes because they're pretty,
but I made the chocolates myself!
Here, Dumb-chi, this one's for you.
Thanks for your help yesterday.
It'll never happen again.
Yesterday was a special case.
Next is Minorin.
I heard you came to save
me during the class trip.
Thank you!
Jeez, what's with all the formality?
I'll always be there to help!
Minorin!
Ryuji.
Same deal.
Thanks.
Share with Ya-chan.
Right.
And Kitamura-kun.
I'm giving you the one that turned out best.
Ooh, you sure?
Of course!
You're the one who carried me up the cliff!
Crap, I didn't tell Kushieda...
Oh, man!
Were my eyes rolled back in my head?
I had absolutely no idea what
was going to happen!
I kept rolling and rolling until I hit my
head and there was this whoosh!
That must be how it feels to get knocked out.
It's feels almost like a dream.
For a while, I thought I'd blurted
out all kinds of things.
I totally panicked when I came to.
What exactly do you think you said?
I could never tell you! Never, ever!
Not even you!
Come on, spill!
I can't! I mean, it was just my imagination!
Just tell us.
I can never let anyone find out!
If they ever knew, I'd be ruined!
So completely I could no longer live!
Or not...
Y-You didn't hear me, right?
Nope, I didn't hear a thing.
Right, Takasu?
Nobody heard a thing.
You're safe.
What...?
Liar.
You're going to pretend you didn't hear her?
Wh-What are you saying, Minorin?
Taiga!
Are you going to blindly accept this!?
Takasu-kun was the one who saved you!
But he didn't tell you!
Because of whatever it is that you're hiding!
Why, Taiga!?
- Why can't you just be honest and admit it!?
- Let...
...me go!
Kitamura-kun?
- Man, that's one sorry face.
- Dumb-chi...
Hey, Takasu.
Are you fine with letting
Aisaka go right now?
Are you sure?
Look at me, Taiga!
Look at me!
- No!
- What do you see!?
- No! No! No! No! No!
- I'm Minori! Your best friend!
Isn't that right!?
You said you love me, right!?
- Let me go! Let me go!
- Then trust me!
- Let me go!
- I trust you, Taiga!
You keep going on and on about me...
But you're not so weak you'd blame
others for giving up on what you want!
Or am I wrong!?
That's not it...
I just want you to be happy...
I want my best friend to be happy...
Don't give me that garbage!
The responsibility for my happiness
lies with me and me only!
I won't let anyone else decide
what makes me happy!
We've done all we can.
Pretty much.
Taiga!
Amin, you sellout!
Better chase her down.
If you're up to the task.
Takasu-kun, I'm going after Taiga.
I'm not done talking to her.
What will you do?
What...What should I do?
Find out how Taiga feels...?
But, then what?
Taiga wanted to hide her feelings...
Takasu-kun!
I'm...
In those sleepless nights,
nemurenai yoruni wa
I lay there sighing all alone.
hitoride tameiki
What about everyone else?
minna wa dounano
It just feels so lonely.
nandaka samishii
A tiny little seed in this huge Earth.
hiroi daichini hitotsubu no tane
Stretch out those roots,
nekko nobashite
and bear a fruit that's still unripe.
mada aoi miwo tsuketa
The fruit that wants to hurry and turn orange.
orenji ironi hayaku naritai kajitsu
Showering in your light
kimino hikari wo abite
only nurtures bigger ideals and dreams.
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
Why won't you notice?
kizuiteyo nee
I ate the orange today but cried
because it was still too sour.
orenji kyoumo tabete mitakedo
mada suppakute naita
It reminded too much of me,
watashi mitaide nokosenai kara
so I finished the whole thing.
zenbu tabeta
I love you. It makes me cry.
sukidayo nakeruyo
I love you. I love you.
sukidayo sukidayo
Hey, Taiga.
Looks like snow.
I left the laundry hanging outside...
That's not all.
I've left a lot of things hanging.