Toru!
Wanna eat some ice cream?
Huh? She's not here.
Run-chan...
What are you doing over there?
I was sleeping and I fell off.
I can't move. Help me.
Coochy coochy coochy coo!
Stop it! Stop it!
What are you doing?
I followed my impulse.
Saved
I'll take one more!
Stop it.
Nice shot!
Fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
Kirameku tooku no sora to hitotsu ni naru
Kazeyomi kimama na watashi no yukue wa kanata
Issho ni ikou
Shinkokyuu hazundeku, sekai no spring breath
Taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
Ohayou to sayounara no aida wa watashitachi dake
Nandemo dekiru ne
Sukitooru hizashi, umaretate no sora
Machiawaseta yakusoku no morning arch
Te o furu kimi e to totte oki no kyou o watasou
Oshaberi ga hajimaru
Okay, Toru.
Let's eat!
It's delicious!
Toru? Your bangs have gotten
longer, haven't they?
Yes. I haven't touched them at all
since summer vacation began.
I can cut them for you!
Huh?
Scissors!
Using THOSE scissors?
Don't move, okay?
Wait! You're going to cut straight across?!
Huh?
Um... You look younger now, huh?
A book bag would really suit you!
I didn't even use those in middle school.
It's no good. I can't go to school.
This is summer vacation.
We have an orientation day.
Don't worry. It's cute!
Forget it.
Well... Ah!
Put this like THIS...
Finished! Now we match.
We match.
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
...AT NIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE OF SUMMER
Yes!
Good morning.
Good morning, Toru-chan.
Sorry, Run's still asleep.
Would you wake her up for me?
Understood. Excuse me.
Run-chan. It's orientation day.
Run-chan. We're going to school.
It's summer, but you're wearing
long sleeves again.
I've told you, a summer sweater
would be cuter, haven't I?
Run-chan!
Okay, banzai!
Fine, I'll take it off! I'll take it off!
Banzai!
It's so hot!
I'm kinda lightheaded...
Run-chan! That's not the school.
Beware of
Gropers!
Run-chan! That's not the school.
Beware of
Gropers!
Eew, Summer brings out more
perverts and gropers, huh?
Beware of
Gropers!
Apparently, some of them even
call out while driving by.
Beware of
Gropers!
Ugh, how nasty. We have to be careful, huh?
Beware of
Gropers!
Hey, it's hot out. Want a ride to school?
Beware of
Gropers!
A groper!
Somebody! There's a pervert over here!
B-But I...
A pervert?
Should we call the police?
It's a misunderstanding!
I'm a teacher at their school.
Please don't call the police!
Okay, everyone take a printout
and pass it behind you.
You can take till the next semester
to fill out that survey.
Ma'am.
Everyone, listen up.
PLEASE CHECK YOUR DESIRED CAREER PATH
_Higher Education (University / Junior College / Vocational School)
_Employment
_Other (
If Higher Education, please list desired school,
college, department and courses.
In Order of Preference School Name
Everyone, listen up.
PLEASE CHECK YOUR DESIRED CAREER PATH
_Higher Education (University / Junior College / Vocational School)
_Employment
_Other (
If Higher Education, please list desired school,
college, department and courses.
In Order of Preference School Name
PLEASE CHECK YOUR DESIRED CAREER PATH
_Higher Education (University / Junior College / Vocational School)
_Employment
_Other (
If Higher Education, please list desired school,
college, department and courses.
In Order of Preference School Name
This is a career counseling survey.
PLEASE CHECK YOUR DESIRED CAREER PATH
_Higher Education (University / Junior College / Vocational School)
_Employment
_Other (
If Higher Education, please list desired school,
college, department and courses.
In Order of Preference School Name
Please take until the next semester
to really think about it.
PLEASE CHECK YOUR DESIRED CAREER PATH
_Higher Education (University / Junior College / Vocational School)
_Employment
_Other (
If Higher Education, please list desired school,
college, department and courses.
In Order of Preference School Name
You may still be freshmen, but make sure
not to fill this out carelessly.
Stay alert, or it will be entrance exam time
before you know it!
- Orientation
- Summer Homework
- New Semester,
Sept 4
- Orientation
- Summer Homework
- New Semester,
Sept 4
You're still on vacation, but starting tomorrow,
you need to face reality and study hard!
- Orientation
- Summer Homework
- New Semester,
Sept 4
- Orientation
- Summer Homework
- New Semester,
Sept 4
That's all.
See you next semester.
Miss Kito.
Toru-san!
Ma'am, you look pale today.
Do you feel all right?
Oh, my.
Such a nice girl.
She's one of my students, all right.
Yes, I've had something of a headache
since this morning.
They have medicine in the nurse's office.
My DRIVE can overcome some headache.
That just won't do, Miss Kito.
Wearing the doctor's whites again?
I wear those, so please stop that.
I'm allowed! I wore them
long before YOU got here!
But that is the gown of a doctor, is it not?
More importantly, please do something
about those ridiculous shirts, Mr. Sato!
What's that? You're saying I have bad taste?
I don't think you're in a position
to talk, Miss Kito.
Then let's have Toru-san decide!
Very well.
Huh? Toru-san?
Urchin-chan?
Toru-san!
Miss Kito, couldn't you have stepped on her?
What was that?! You mean YOU did, right?
No, it was you, wasn't it?
No, it was you!
No, it was you.
I'm not that small.
No!
No, it was you.
That's...
Could it be an SOS signal?
A freshman-year classroom? Hold on!
This way, you can clean up chalk dust
without going to the first floor.
How do you get blackboard erasers so dirty?
Right?
There's no "Right?" about it.
Is there a fire?!
Um, upperclassman?
What's the matter?
I totally misread this!
Um, that is...
I-I came to clean.
I wanna die!
I'm sorry, upperclassman.
This girl does so many dumb things!
No, it's fine. I always jump to
the wrong conclusion.
This just gives me another funny story.
Right, Toru?
If I had stopped Yutaka earlier, this would have
all ended without you getting embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
Stop that! Don't go apologizin'!
If you apologize, it just makes me
more embarrassed!
I'm sorry.
Stop it!
She sure gets flustered, huh?
Stop that!
It really was a distress signal.
Seein' that, all I could think
is that there was a fire.
If it were a fire, there'd be SMOKE, right?
You fly off the handle too easily.
Try and be a bit more calm.
Here, Nagi-chan.
That's hot! F-Fire!
So, getting all flustered like that is not good.
Wait, Run!
What's with that HOT drink in summer?
Oh.
I was in a hurry and chose the wrong one!
It's so hot!
Sure enough, it's not good for people
to get flustered, huh?
In my case, it couldn't be helped.
If it really was a fire, it would've been bad!
Same goes for me!
Drinking hot coffee in summer
defies common sense!
Oh! They should remove hot drinks
from vending machines for summer!
Oh.
That's not the point, is it?
Huh?
HOT
BLOODED
Has confidence in her fashion sense...
HOT
BLOODED
Has confidence in her fashion sense...
Maybe?
What should I do?!
Looks like I forgot the questionnaire at school!
Oh!
From Yuko, huh?
"I totally forgot my questionnaire at school.
"I wanna go get it, but I can't go alone
because it's too scary.
"Come with me."
Jeez. That's why I told her to be more calm!
There.
"Just leave it till the new semester."
No!
"I wanna put thought into it.
C'mon, please go with me."
Aah, jeez!
Received
Nagi
For real?
Received
Nagi
For real?
Go to school at night?
Text
Received
Yuko
Re: For real?
Please!!!!
It's too scary
by myself!!
Too scary, eh?
Oh, no! I ran late! I bet Nagi's already there.
There she is. Hey!
Huh? Why's everyone here?
I got a hold of these two.
The front gate ain't open?
We came in through the rear gate.
The rear gate's so far...
Yuko, race as fast as you can to get here.
Yeah, yeah. Okay, here goes...
Now, start!
You guys are kinda impatient.
Now listen! Do NOT look behind you.
C'mon, what gives?
That was a personal best, wasn't it?
Okay, let's go get your sheet.
Wait. I still can't move.
Oh. She's dead.
Sure enough, it's not open, huh?
Is the staff entrance locked, too?
It's impossible with this, isn't it?
What are you trying to use?
Dammit!
Sure enough, school at night is scary!
Well, a window just happened to be open!
Careless, but today it counts in our favor.
It sure did.
Yuko, you're sticking too close!
Well...
I get anxious if I don't stay close to someone.
Okay, fine.
I'll go to the chemistry lab and bring back
an anatomical model.
No! Don't!
If you don't like it, let go of me!
That's even worse!
Looks like fun, doesn't it?
I'm not so sure.
Please, just don't do it!
You really are scaredy cat, aren't you?
School is different at night! It's creepy!
Oh.
What?!
Look, we're at school at night, so...
Let's go expIoring!
Yeah!
Let's move out!
Kyoushitsu, shuppatsu shinkou desu
To the classroom, onward we go
Wait!
Kyoushitsu, shuppatsu shinkou desu
To the classroom, onward we go
Wasuremono wa, minasan, nai desu ka?
Everyone, you haven't forgotten anything, have you?
Mayonaka, narihibiku piano
Midnight, a piano rings out
Te-ri-ro-ri-ra-ra
Da-da-da-da-da
Nazomeku, nanafushigi
How mysterious, one of the Seven Wonders
Madogiwa, odoridasu gaikotsu ni aisatsu
By the windowsill
A greeting to a skeleton that starts dancing
Hora hora, kichinto escort shite!
Come on, escort him properly!
Saa, izayukan, omoshiroi jan, ushiro wa furikaeru na
Come on, let's go, it's fun, don't look back
Maa, ii jan, susumu dake, kowai mono nante nai sa
Well, it's fine, just going forward, there are no scary things
Da Vinci ya Mona Lisa mo
Da Vinci and the Mona Lisa too
Minna issho ni tanken shiyou
Let's everyone explore together
School sure is exciting at night, huh?
Yeah.
So scary!
Um...
What is it?
The bathroom...
Hey!
We're going to the bathroom.
Okay. We'll wait!
I'm not going in the stall with you.
I know that!
Um, the lights...
Hurry up and do it.
Okay.
What? What?
Um... THAT.
IT CAME OUT!
It came out! It came out, it came out!
No more constipation?
No, not that!
Th-There was a will-o'-the-wisp
at the gymnasium over there!
Is a will-o'-the-wisp that thing that appears
right after someone dies?
Then if we hurry and put it back,
the person might be saved!
What are you saying?!
Shh!
That will-o'-the-wisp grew legs!
Stay still!
I wanna see!
Footsteps... A thief?
It'll find us!
Jeez!
Footsteps... A thief?
Huh? Urchin-chan?
Jeez, it's Mr. Sato!
That was a waste of a surprise.
What are you doing here at this hour?
We came to clean.
Huh. You came to get
something you forgot, huh?
Yes, that's right.
Sir, what's with that candle?
Ah. I like candles.
This ephemeral flame is like my own life.
I feel a sense of kinship...
Oh, he fell.
Took that seriously, didn't he?
He's not moving.
So he fell over for real?
He had a fit!
Oh, no!
First off, we have to get him to the nurse's office!
Don't have him lying down!
You're scraping his face!
Damn, he's too heavy. We can't move him.
Oh, that's it! We should bring the bed HERE!
And then do what?!
We two will hold him from this end.
Run, you take his legs. Toru, you help. Got it?
Yeah.
Understood.
Here goes. One, two!
He's so heavy!
Heave-ho!
Huh? Now he's light.
Run! You left the rest of him behind!
Huh?
Nurse's
Office
Heave-ho!
How tiring.
He won't wake up, will he?
Don't do that.
Sir! Pull it together!
Slapping him like that...
Serves him right.
Did he wake up?
Sir! Sir! Please pull yourself together!
Sir! Can you hear me?
What's this? Run-chan?
Mr. Sato! You can't die!
Run-chan!
I won't die!
Snap.
Run-chan...
You think he's okay?
He said he wouldn't die.
Let's go.
Yeah, you're right.
That dog ain't out here, right?
No, it's not.
Man, I am SO tired!
Thank you for
the delivery
Okay, goodnight.
Goodnight.
The train will soon arrive at Platform 3.
For your safety, please stand and wait inside the white line.
Yuko-chan!
See you soon!
Okay. See you!
I'm sure glad everyone was there for me today.
I forgot it again!
Akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
Tanoshii ichinichi no owari
Tsukinai oshaberi mada mada aru keredo
Sorosoro o-uchi ni kaeranakucha
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Mail suru kara
Kyou no page ni minna osoroi no egao
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Itsumo arigato
Kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
Ru-ru-run, kaze to kokoro humming suru
Tsugi no kado de furimukinagara bye-bye
In the end, it was all a big waste.
And the memories are SUPER scary.
I can't sleep at all.
At my age, I can't tell my parents,
"Let's sleep together"...
Oh!
It's been a while since we've slept together, huh?
Goodnight.
yup!
Miporin, what about the
summer festivals is most fun for you?
More than anything, it's the fireworks.
Ah.
And takoyaki. Okonomiyaki.
Oh, and soft drinks, too!
Whoa, all very nice!
What do you like, Yutaka?
Me, well, I like the outdoor stalls where-
Hold on a second!
Next time, on A-Channel: "Summer Festival"
Next
Episode!
Next time, on A-Channel: "Summer Festival"
Next
Episode!
I like the outdoor stalls where you can eat
a whole BUNCH of oden stew!
You eat stew in the summer?!