If a monster really is out there,
we'll get permission to engage, right?
If this were a monster movie,
we'd be the first to go.
You know, the ones who make
the bad guy look tough
before the Giant of Light appears.
That's not funny, man.
Guess we'll find out in a minute.
No good... It's just regenerating.
It heals so quickly.
We're barely keeping it from reaching shore.
I can't get a clear shot at Caster this way.
So cool... This is so freaking cool!
You're awesome, man!
The Lord is with us!
What a disaster.
In the long history of the Grail Wars,
such a failure is unprecedented.
According to the observers,
the entire Mion River area is
blanketed in a thick fog.
But large numbers of onlookers
are starting to gather.
This is too much for us to deal with alone.
We shall have to request help
from the Mages Association.
And where is Tokiomi-kun?
My master and Archer are en route
to the battlefield.
Kirei,
I'll see to the cover-up.
You head out immediately,
and assist Tokiomi-kun.
Yes, Father.
What a nauseating scene this is...
Peons or not,
they are still supposedly warriors of renown.
Yet, even gathered together,
they cannot dispatch that abomination.
It's so pathetic, it's almost painful...
Don't you agree,
Tokiomi?
We must destroy that monster
before more witnesses arrive.
For the dignity of the Tohsaka family...
Your Majesty,
that beast is a wild animal that will
destroy your garden in its rampage.
I implore you to exterminate it.
Wild animals fall within
the gardener's domain.
Or, Tokiomi, do you equate
my Noble Phantasm with a
mere gardener’s shovel?
Certainly not!
But as you can see,
the others are no match for that monster.
Here is a chance for you
to display the power of a true hero.
I beg you...
It can't be.
We're leaving, Tokiomi.
I shall not look upon that vile thing anymore.
Please wait, King of Heroes...
Tokiomi,
I just sacrificed four of my
magnificent weapons for you.
Now they're so tainted by touching that foul thing,
I no longer even want them back.
Do not take my generosity for granted.
But you are the only hero strong enough
to defeat that monster!
The only way to overcome
its regenerative prowess
is to completely obliterate the
creature with one blow!
And, King of Heroes,
only your Sword of Rupture can—
Silence!
You wish me to draw Ea,
my greatest treasure, here?
You forget yourself, Tokiomi!
I should execute you
for allowing such an insult to pass your lips!
I could use a Command Spell,
but it would destroy any rapport I
have left with the King of Heroes.
Besides,
restoring my lost Command Spell
was the entire reason
Father Risei and I came up with this plan
involving Caster in the first place.
Why is everything backfiring?
Damn...
What the hell is that?
There's some kind of weird light
at six o'clock, too.
That's no helicopter.
What is it? A UFO?
Control to Diablo-1.
What is your situation?
The situation...
Uh... Well...
I'll drop down for a closer look.
W-Wait, Kobayashi!
Get back up here, Diablo-2!
If I just get a little closer, I'll be able
to see what this thing is—
Kobayashi?
Kobayashi!
W-What is that?
I-It ate it.
Control to Diablo-1!
What the hell is going on up there?!
Respond!
Eyes... It has eyes.
It's covered in eyes!
Eyes? What do you mean by eyes?
Is it trying to eat me, too?
Captain Ougi!
Diablo-1, engaging!
W-Wait, Ougi! What's—
I'll kill it before it swallows me.
This is for Kobayashi...
I'll hit it with everything I have!
Berserker?
What's he doing here?
Stay down, fool!
He had to pick now, of all times?
That's...
Ah, the mad dog again?
Interesting.
Your Majesty, I shall face his Master.
Very well.
Enjoy yourself.
I wish you good fortune.
Look at you, a cur that belongs on the ground,
somehow rising to the heavens,
the king's domain.
Learn your place, mongrel!
Impertinence.
Interesting, indeed.
I admit I have not been so
entertained in quite some time.
For a mindless animal,
you certainly do amuse me.
You're nearly unrecognizable,
Matou Kariya.
You once abandoned the path of a mage,
but you couldn't resist the lure of the Grail.
And now you return, in this wretched state.
The mere sight of you suffices to illustrate
how far the Matou family has fallen.
Tohsaka Tokiomi, I have only
one question for you.
Why did you entrust Sakura into
Zouken's custody?
What?
Is this truly the time to
be concerned with that?
Answer me, Tokiomi!
There is nothing to say.
I desired to secure a good future
for my daughter.
What?
Any mage with two children will
face an unfortunate dilemma.
Only one may inherit the family's secret magic.
The other is doomed to human mediocrity.
However, my wife was an
exceptional child bearer.
Both Rin and Sakura displayed
uncommon promise as mages.
Therefore, both required the protection
that only an established mage
family could offer.
How could I, their father,
sentence one of my daughters to failure,
to ensure the other's chances?
What father could act in such a way?
Mediocrity...
The happy family I saw that day...
He simply dismisses them as mediocrity?
For both to realize their potential,
I had no choice
but to give one up for adoption.
The Matou family's request was
an answer to my prayers.
With their knowledge of the Grail,
they have that much greater
a chance to reach the Root.
Mages are born with innate power.
And they eventually attain greater power.
This responsibility resides in their blood,
long before their brain
can comprehend it.
That is what it means to be a mage's child.
If I fail to reach it,
Rin will succeed.
And if Rin should fail,
Sakura will succeed.
They will fulfill the Tohsaka family's desire.
You bastard...
You would have them fight each other?
Sister against sister?
Even if that's what it comes to,
my descendants will still be happy.
What?
Glory and honor go to the winner.
The loser will have preserved
the honor of their ancestors.
One could not dream a happier conclusion.
You're insane!
Clearly, I've only wasted my breath.
None of this could be understood
by one oblivious
to the honor of magic, let alone a
traitor who turned his back on it.
Go to hell!
I'll never forgive you.
You unfeeling mages...
I'll slaughter you all.
Zouken... You...
I'll kill every last
one of you!
By severing ties with your father,
you ensured the Matou family's
magic would pass to Sakura.
Honestly, it may be that I should thank you.
And yet...
I cannot overlook your transgressions.
Not the weakness of running from
the responsibility of your blood.
Or the reprehensible lack of
remorse for doing so.
Matou Kariya, you shame
the name of magic itself.
And now that our paths have crossed again,
how could I but destroy you?
Screw you... You inhuman monster!
Wrong.
Taking responsibility for oneself is the
foremost part of being human.
Your inability to do even that
makes you less than human, a dog,
Kariya.
My insects, devour him...
Feast on his flesh!
Go get them, Sir Bluebeard!
Smash 'em! Kill 'em!
We stand within God's own toy box!
Saber!
Many thanks, Saber!
I'll never be bored again...
No need to bother with murder anymore.
I can watch them die in droves,
without lifting a finger.
Crushed...
Sliced...
Smashed...
Eaten.
They'll die and die and die!
Blood and guts I've never laid eyes on.
I'll get to see them all.
Every day... Every day...
Everywhere! All across the world!
Never ending! Never end—
It stopped?
What?
What's up?
It's so beautiful...
Of course...
I never noticed.
They say you can't see what's
right before you.
Everything I sought...
It was hiding right here.
Within my own guts...
this entire time.
Ryuunosuke!
I finally found it...
I've been looking for so long.
Sheesh.
I wish you'd just told me...
that it was inside me all along.
Ryuunosuke... My Master.
You have left this world before me.
But fear not, Ryuunosuke.
I, Gilles de Rais,
shall keep my promise to you...
Behold, Ryuunosuke!
A gift for your journey to the next world!
The coolest thing ever!
I shot the boy we thought
to be Caster's Master.
And it looks like we were right.
Should we move on to the next target,
while the Servants are occupied
with the monster?
Hold on, Maiya.
That's no ordinary monster.
It's an immortal monster that
can endlessly regenerate.
It will reach the shore before it vanishes.
If it finds a new food source,
it will mean the end.
Caster will have all the mana he
requires to maintain his incarnation.
That will lead to more casualties.
It may even endanger the
Holy Grail War itself.
Exactly.
But how do we defeat an immortal monster?
We must utterly annihilate it in a single attack.
One so massive, it destroys
every last particle of flesh.
Anti-unit or anti-army Noble Phantasms
won't be enough.
We need an anti-fortress one.
And Saber
possesses such an attack.
But she currently cannot use it,
due to Lancer's curse.
In the end,
I shall let them show us
what they call chivalry.
Episode 14:
Bloody Battle on the Mion River
This light...
You struggle, all for naught.
The undefeated king sings loud and clear
the name of the miracle she
holds in her hands.
This is painful to see.
He's going to sacrifice himself?
We must stop it now!
Next Time:
Golden Light
I shall put my trust in you, Saber.