Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Morning, you two.
Yo.
Good morning.
You remembered to wear your winter uniform.
Come on...
It's not like I'm Tsukasa.
What!?
But the hot weather isn't over yet...
They could let us wear our summer uniforms a little longer.
And when we have to wear summer uniforms, it gets cold sometimes...
They should just let us choose.
Right?
The switch is more to give students a change in pace.
Else there would be more slackers like you two.
Pandora's Box
This doesn't happen in our family,
but I've heard that some parents monitor their daughters' cell phones and e-mail.
I've heard that sometimes.
Is it like that for you?
Probably not.
Your dad's the type to smother,
but I guess he wouldn't do anything you wouldn't like.
That might be part of it...
My dad also uses the computer.
Maybe it's 'cause he knows how embarrassing it is when someone else looks at your D drive.
D...
What?
We've had all these classes and stuff this summer...
In the end,
I only got to have fun with the fireworks and Ariake.
So you still go to Comiket.
Comiket!?
Well, that's right...
As a result, my wallet's feeling pretty lonely.
How much did you spend?
You never know when to draw the line.
If you assume each book is a thousand yen...
Around forty to fifty thousand yen total?
Why you...
There's a limit to how clueless a person can be about the value of money!
Still, Kagami...
There's this thing called market price.
And it's pretty expensive to publish your own stuff.
That's not what I meant!
I'm talking about how you don't feel anything after spending so much!
It may be September, but it's still hot.
That's right.
It seems especially hot this year.
And there's talk about global warming.
Yu-chan can't put up with too much heat,
so she's been resting in an air-conditioned room most of the time.
That's what Tsukasa's been doing the whole time.
But she's just lazy.
Well...
Dad and I join in,
and we all lie around looking like a 小 character.
小?
Shouldn't it be 川?
Nah.
Dad's always in the middle.
Your family never changes.
And I guess Yutaka-chan's gotten used to it.
Hey, hey!
Doing good, Yutaka?
I'm here to play!
Onee-chan!
Oh?
Who's this?
My friend...
Iwasaki Minami-chan.
So this is the Minami-chan Yutaka's always talking about.
O-Onee-chan!
So she has a reason for hope right next to her...
I'm a little jealous.
Man...
I'd heard all the fuss,
but you sure are pretty.
You surprised me!
Want something to drink?
Beer then!
Huh!?
Didn't you drive here!?
Just kiddin'!
Barley tea's fine!
I see.
One absorbs from the other...
Absorption, is it...
Oh...
TL Note: Yassai Mossai: a Japanese folk dance.
It's the Yassai Mossai?
I always get sleepy at night.
Do you have any good ideas?
Instead of forcing yourself to stay up,
why don't you wake up early and work on it?
You'll probably feel better.
I see!
You're right!
I'll wake up early and work hard.
Huh?
Why do I always get up at the same time?
Come to think of it...
I vaguely remember turning something off at some point...
Even when I wake up early,
I just roll over and go back to sleep.
You have no will power...
Maybe I should just try harder and work on it at night.
I doubt rubbing your eyes while nodding off will improve the results.
Why don't you have someone wake you up?
Mom and the others wake up early.
Right, Mom?
Yes, yes.
I'll wake you up.
This can't fail.
Onee-chan is amazing.
Mom!
I told you to wake me up!
I did.
You even answered me back.
I don't know anything about that.
You don't remember?
Onee-chan forgot her lunch...
Thank you!
It feels kind of weird to walk through the hallway of a different grade.
You can feel a little pressure...
I know what you mean.
Yu-chan probably drew everybody's attention.
Being the way she is...
Usually, it's just your imagination,
but when you walk through a hallway for upperclassmen or underclassmen,
you get this feeling that everybody's looking at you, right?
I already tend to stand out 'cause I'm smaller,
but when they're upperclassmen, the pressure is more intense.
I enjoy receiving that kind of attention.
Really...
But I don't attract much attention when I'm in the first-year's area.
They don't realize I'm an upperclassman.
WIELDS NO PRESSURE AS AN UPPERCLASSMAN。
Patty-chan.
Hi!
Hello there.
Are you heading to work?
That's right.
I signed up for too many shifts this week.
Aren't you still working?
That's right.
We're pretty popular.
The A-boys are all over us.
A-boys?
It's what you call boys who look like they totally belong in Akiba.
But Narimiya-kun was a little different.
You're getting accustomed to Japan.
A little too accustomed, don't you think?
I just had a great idea!
I'll write it down once I'm done with my bath.
H-Huh?
I can't remember...
This is what happens when I don't jot it down immediately...
And it was funny...
Hilarious, even!
Another exhausting day...
That might be a funny idea.
I'll write it down when I wake up tomorrow.
Er...
That's weird...
What was it again?
I'm positive it was a good idea.
Should have just gotten out of bed and written it down.
Man!
I even got out of bed this time!
Why do you forget dreams so quickly?
I'm positive that it was hilarious!
Hotel Room Assignments
School Trip
Kyoto    .    Nara
So...
Make sure you all talk it over within your group.
Field   Trip
Kyoto     .     Nara
Since we're going all the way to Kyoto and Nara,
you better check up on all the hot tourist spots.
Trash Monitor ........ Minoru Shiraishi
Hotel Room Assignments
Free Time Team Assignments
School        Trip
Kyoto
Train Seating Assignment
What to Decide
Aren't we going through all the hot spots by bus?
Those will just be the typical places,
so they won't be that fun.
Well now...
That's a blunt way to put it...
So Iris came in here...
I will now guide you through the former capital of Nara.
Almost 1,300 years have passed since it became the capital in 710.
While in Nara,
I hope you enjoy my historical Nara narration.
Nara!
Nara narration!
Were we supposed to laugh?
Sorry for the wait!
This is the main body...
So the little things around it are options!
You're gonna get hit by lightning.
No!
I'm all sticky...
And stinky...
Here, here, here.
Indeed.
What's that supposed to mean?
Please, please.
They probably want you to take their picture.
Um... Um...
Click. Click.
Okay?
This is when you can tell how much somebody's been studying.
Like you're one to talk.
Um...
Onee-chan.
How do you say "cheese" in Indian?
You mean Hindi, right?
Um...
Uh...
Genius girl Kagami can't do any better.
Um...
I believe that Indians will understand English.
That's right!
"Say cheese!" should be fine, right?
Okay.
Say cheese!
You know how couples pop out of nowhere during school trips?
Can't miss the school trip event.
Perhaps, being away from school gives people a sense of freedom?
Kinda like a now or never thing.
I'm embarrassed to say that I'm unable to sleep with a different pillow.
I'm embarrassed to say that I can't sleep peacefully without this nearby.
I'm embarrassed to say that I can't sleep if I haven't turned this on at least once during the day.
Everyone.
The bus will soon pass Kiyomizu Temple.
The hill leading to Kiyomizu Temple is known as Three-year Hill.
Legend says that if you trip and fall here, you'll die in three years.
Three-year Hill will become your Boo-hoo Hill.
Does it count if you break down laughing?
Okay?
We'll be moving around in individual groups now.
Keep an eye out for traffic.
We'll regroup at 12:30 in front of Chion-in.
Don't be late.
Anybody who's late gets to write a happy 20-page report when we get back.
Sure about that?
Let's give it a try.
The Dragon Slayer's probably about this heavy.
We're really high up.
You know how the saying goes, "Like you're going to jump off Kiyomizu..."
...but if you really jumped, wouldn't you die?
Does it mean that you no longer care what happens?
You're so pragmatic, Kagami.
Look, look!
It says marriage.
This place seems to be famous for its god of marriage.
TL Note: Stone for Love Fortune Telling
They really spell it out for you.
Look.
You can draw love fortunes.
Let's all give it a try.
TL Note: Praying for a Good Marriage
Let's do it!
Guess I can't tell these apart...
Isn't that obvious?
This one!
Fulfill Love
Great Fortune
Great fortune!
Lucky you, Kona-chan.
My.
I drew good fortune.
That's fine.
Now what did I get...
Half Fortune
Half fortune?
What's this?
I-I guess you only get half a fortune.
Which means it's half bad.
Not like I care about love fortunes.
So cute!
That looks nice.
Nah.
Kagami would want this.
RECOMMENDED
What's that supposed to mean?
I'll get one of these.
Kagami! Kagami!
You forgot this!
I'm not buying it!
Then what about this?
No!
You should be careful.
Marriage Wishes
This one says, "Konata is my wife."
Okay.
Everyone's here, right?
We'll have lunch after we've gone in the hotel.
Let's get going.
Take us there please.
They said that Koizumi's character song was written in an IZAM style.
Sensei!
Someone's chasing us from behind!
What!?
This is like the Hokkaido shoot all over again!
Don't ditch me!
You have to go, "***tel!"
That idiot.
He's getting assigned a 50-page report!
Driver!
Sorry, could you stop for a second?
Hotel                     Honnoji
See you later.
To Hiiragi
I'd like to talk
Please meet me in front
of our hotel at 9 tonight
From
a certain boy
Doesn't even hurt!
The Golden Pavilion Temple is golden,
but the Silver Pavilion Temple isn't silver, huh?
They wanted to group it with the Golden Pavilion Temple,
Click.
so they named it silver to go along with golden.
It was never silver to begin with.
Click.
I wonder if it's like Poké***,
with Sapphire and Ruby and stuff.
No comment?
Our family's shrine was on the news.
We only have one day left.
Our plan for free time is all set.
Tomorrow is the beginning of our true school trip!
Off we go to the holy land!
Right...
D-Does this count as being in front of the hotel?
Did you wait long?
So...
What did you want to talk about?
You're the only person I can talk to about this.
Please give me that doll!
Doll?
You know...
The one you bought from the Kiyomizu Temple souvenir shop!
The Yatsuhashi character.
Y-Yatsuhashi-kun?
Yeah!
The one!
I really liked it and wanted one.
But if someone saw me buying one,
they'd probably all make fun of me!
I'm begging you!
Thank you!
I'm eternally in your debt!
Don't tell anybody about this!
Yes, yes.
I'm reading this book about four brothers.
****** of the Dragon Kings?
That's right.
I can't take it off!
Come to think of it...
The steam within cooled off,
That could make a pretty good anime.
and formed a vacuum.
They did an anime adaptation a while back.
If you press on the sides a little,
Really?
that should allow air to enter and make the lid easier to remove.
I had no idea!
I think they went up to the fourth volume of the original.
In that case...
But those books are...
I'm sorry!
So sorry!
Putting on a show till the very end.
I've already looked up the directions.
Is it really all right for us to visit?
We'll just be looking from the outside, so it's okay.
There's no need to go that far just 'cause we're in Kyoto.
Tsk. Tsk. Tsk.
You don't understand the otaku's idea of romance.
I don't want to.
Not much here.
It makes it easier to concentrate on their job, so this works.
It's a pretty ordinary-looking building.
They limit their workload, so this works.
Was it really necessary to buy these in Kyoto?
Princess Love
That's embarrassing!
Who cares?
It's a little something for remembering this day!
Onee-chan!
Let's take a picture together!
It's for commemorating this trip.
Since we came all the way to Kyoto...
What does this have to do with Kyoto?
Yeah, Tsukasa and I made it back in one piece.
Tsukasa's already asleep, though.
I figured you'd be sulking in bed.
Why would I be doing that?
Did you put up the sticker photo?
How could I put up something so embarrassing?
Something so embarrassing...
The school trip was this week...
I sure worked hard.
Okay.
Time to spend the weekend gaming online for once.
Emergency Maintenance Notice
Due to an unexplained server error at 20:30,
the server is currently undergoing emergency maintenance.
Good lucky!
Here's another crazy episode of Lucky Channel!
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
I'm the assistant,
Ono Daisuke.
Lucky Channel is already on the twenty-first episode!
That's right.
We're finally getting close to the end.
Well, then...
Let's get straight to this corner...
This Week's Bend
This week's...
...bend!
Who is it?
What?
I brought your water.
What is this!?
It's warm!
How am I supposed to drink this!?
I'd rather have something out of a vending machine.
Don't mess with me!
You...
Why, you...
What do you think I've had to put up with this whole time!?
All your damn selfish requests one after the next!
M-Minoru?
Well, I'm gonna speak my mind today!
Do you know how I felt when I was doing this corner!?
I'd have to work at CoCo**** every day!
That's better pay than my voice acting work!
Thanks to you, I'm working full-time now!
Before I come and kiss your ass here,
I'm over there frying cutlets!
Which means you're more suited for that work.
And what the hell!?
Why are you sitting there, Ono boy!?
That's my seat!
You were abandoned by the director and the producer.
What's that!?
They acted too quickly!
I'm a late bloomer!
I can go from here to Starga**r in no time!
You can?
Weally?
Sittin' there making fun of me...
Screw working with Hine**su...
Or Lo** and Be***...
I quit.
I quit this stupid show, damn it!
Take that!
Who gives a damn about Lucky Channel!?
Minoru Shiraishi-san!
What are you doing, morons!?
What are you filming there!?
What's with the Cape of Thirty Years!?
If you wanna play with that,
I'm gonna be thirty soon!
I'm talking about you...
Welcome to Idaho!
The belt isn't long enough so she's holding it up from behind.
Hello! Shiraishi Minoru here!
Okay!
Yeah.
Now please listen!
Don't wanna hear it.
The Dentistman Song!
What is this?
The sound of my drill rings through the universe!
Uchuu ni hibike doriru on!
What does that even mean?
Yeah, yeah.
Any enemy will fall after one hit!
Donna aite mo ichi geki da!
Stop moving.
Right.
Stop moving!
Striving to protect everyone's dreams...
Minna no negai mamoru tame...
I head forth giving my all!
Onore wo sutete tachi mukau
Wait, Akira-sama!
Th-The enemy is the cavity monster from hell!
Teki wa jigoku no mushibadosu!
Sheesh.
Right.
I'll show you my Drill of Justice!
Seigi no doriru wo misete yare!
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now is the time!
Ima da!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Eliminate them!
Kezure!
T-Twin drill!
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Stop moving!
Shatter them!
Kudake!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eradicate them!
Kezure!
For I am...
Ore wa...
I am...
I am Dentistman!
Ore wa Shikaider!
Can I let go?
Dentistman is...
Don't screw up your lines!
...is a cyborg.
He...
He will...
You can't be a hero like that.
...continue fighting to defeat the evil cavities!
You can't fight like that.
How was it?
No good.
Redo.
Yes, ma'am.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Kogami Akira!
I'm Ono Daisuke.
Okay.
That's it for the animal talk.
That was in animal, right?
Next time:
「 There Over Here 」
"There Over Here."
I can cross the goal line now, can't I?
Ramen set!