Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Morning, you two.
Yo!
Good morning.
I see you remembered to wear your winter uniform.
Come on, I'm not Tsukasa.
What!?
But the days are still quite hot.
I wouldn't mind wearing our summer uniform a little longer.
Conversely, it gets cold sometimes when we have to wear our summer uniform.
They should just let us have our choice year-round.
Right?
If you ask me, the switch is more to give the students a change of pace.
Otherwise I'm sure there would be a lot more people who would forget, just like you two.
Pandora's Box
It doesn't happen in our family,
but I heard that there are parents out there...
...who check their daughters' cell phones and e-mails.
Yes, I've heard of that on occasion.
Is it like that at your house?
Nope, I don't think so.
Your dad tends to be overprotective,
but I guess he wouldn't do anything his daughter wouldn't like.
I guess that's part of the reason,
but my dad uses a computer, too,
so he knows how embarrassing it is to have someone else look through your D: drive.
D? What?
We had to take so many classes this summer...
that in the end, the only fun we had,
was the fireworks festival and Ariake.
So you did go to Comiket.
Comiket!?
Well, yeah.
Thanks to that, my wallet's pretty lonely.
How much did you spend?
I know you don't have any concept of restraint.
Assuming that the books were about a thousand yen each...
I guess around forty to fifty thousand yen total?
Why you...
And here I thought there was a limit to how much a person could lose control!
It's easy for you to say that, Kagami,
but there's this thing called the "market price".
And publishing your own work can be quite expensive.
That's not what I meant!
I'm talking about how you don't feel any remorse after spending so much!
It may be September,
but it's still so hot.
You're right.
I hear it's especially hot this year.
And there's talk about global warming.
Yu-chan is pretty sensitive to the heat,
so she rests in an air-conditioned room most of the time.
Tsukasa's been in a room with constant air-conditioning, too.
But she's just lazy.
Well,
my dad and I join her and we all just lie around on the floor,
forming a 小 character.
Shou?
Shouldn't it be something more like a 川 character?
Nope.
My dad always has to be in the middle.
I guess your family never changes.
I'm surprised Yutaka-chan has gotten used to it.
Yahoo!
Yutaka, are you doing well?
I came to play!
Ah, Onee-chan!
Oh?
And who might this be?
This is my friend, Iwasaki Minami-chan.
Oh, you must be the Minami-chan that Yutaka-chan's always talking about!
Onee-chan!
She has a reason to hope so close to her.
I'm a little jealous.
Man, I've heard the rumors,
but you really are pretty.
I'm surprised!
Do you want something to drink?
I'll have a beer!
Huh!
Aren't you driving?
Just kidding!
Barely tea is fine!
Ah, I see.
One absorbs from the other.
Absorption, is it.
Oh!
It's the Yassai Mossai?
I always get sleepy at night.
Do you know of any good methods?
Instead of forcing yourself to stay up,
why don't you just sleep early and then wake up early to work on it?
You'll feel better, too.
Yeah, you're right!
I'll wake up early and work hard!
Huh?
Why is it the same time I always wake up at?
Come to think of it,
I kind of remember turning something off.
Even when I wake up earlier,
I just roll over and go back to sleep.
You have no willpower.
Maybe I should just tough it out...
...and stay up late working on it.
Though I doubt you'll really be all that productive...
...if you're so tired that you keep on rubbing your eyes and nodding off.
Why don't you have someone wake up you?
Mom and the others wake up really early.
Right, Mom?
Yes, yes.
I'll wake you up.
This should be fail-proof.
Great idea, Onee-chan.
Mom!
I told you to wake me up!
I did.
And you even replied.
Eh?
I don't remember anything about that.
You don't remember?
Onee-chan forgot her lunch.
Thank you!
It feels strange walking through the hallways of a different year.
Like it's somewhat controlling...
I know what you mean.
I bet you caught a lot of people's attention, Yu-chan.
Being the way you are...
Usually it's just the imagination of the person at hand,
but regardless of whether you go through the hallways of upperclassmen or underclassmen,
you're always going to get the feeling that everyone's looking at you, right?
I'm already very short, so I tend to stand out more.
But when it's the upperclassmen who stare at me, I really feel the pressure.
I actually sort of enjoy that kind of attention.
Really?
You do?
But I don't attract much attention when I'm in places where the first-years are.
They don't see me as an upperclassman.
WIELDS NO PRESSURE AS AN UPPERCLASSMAN。
Ah, Patty-chan.
Hi!
Hello there!
Are you on your way to work?
That's right.
I signed up for too many shifts this week.
Aren't you still working there?
Yeah, that's right.
We're pretty popular, you know.
The A-boys love us!
A-boys?
It's what you call the guys that you totally picture walking down Akiba.
But Narimiya-kun was a little different...
I see you're getting quite accustomed to Japan.
A little too accustomed, don't you think!
Ah, I just had a great idea!
I'll write it down after I'm done with my bath.
H-Huh?
I can't remember it now...
I knew this was gonna happen if I didn't write it down immediately.
And it was good...
Absolutely good!
Another exhausting day.
That might be a great idea!
I'll write it down when I wake up tomorrow.
Huh...?
That's strange...
What was it again?
I'm sure it was a good idea.
I shouldn't have been lazy and written it down.
Geez!
I even got out of bed this time!
Why do you forget dreams so quickly!
I'm definitely sure that it was hilarious, too!
Hotel Room Assignments
School Trip
Kyoto    .    Nara
So,
everyone talk it over with the members in your group and decide, okay?
Field   Trip
Kyoto     .     Nara
We'll be going all the way to Kyoto and Nara,
so be sure to look up all the tourist spots, okay?
Trash Monitor ........ Minoru Shiraishi
Hotel Room Assignments
Free Time Team Assignments
School        Trip
Kyoto
Train Seating Assignment
What to Decide
Aren't we going through all the sights together by bus?
The places we're going together are the typical spots,
so they won't be all that fun.
Well, that's certainly a blunt way of putting it...
So this is where Iris came in...
I will now be guiding you through the former capital, Nara.
It has been over 1300 years since the original city, Heijo-kyo, became the capital in 710.
While in Nara,
I hope you'll enjoy my historical narration of Nara.
Nara narration!
Were we supposed to laugh?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Hm.
So this is the main body,
and the small ones around it must be the options!
You're gonna get punished!
No!
I'm all sticky...
And stinky...
I'm all smelly now!
Here, here, here.
It appears so.
What are you trying to do?
Please, please.
H-Huh?
I think they want you to take their picture.
Um, um...
Okay?
This is where you can tell who's been studying.
Like you're one to talk.
Um...
Onee-chan, how do you say "cheese" in Indian?
You mean Hindi, right?
Um...
Uh...
Oh, even the genius Kagami hit a stump!
Um...
I believe that Indians would understand English.
That's right!
"Say cheese" should do it, I think!
Oh yeah!
Say cheese!
You know how, on school trips like this,
you start to notice couples everywhere?
Can't miss the school trip event.
Perhaps being in an outdoor environment away from school,
is making everyone feel a little more free.
You mean like a "now or never" thing?
It's quite embarrassing,
but I have a hard time sleeping on different pillows.
but I can't sleep peacefully without this at my side.
It's quite embarrassing,
but I can't go to sleep without turning this on at least once a day.
Everyone.
The bus will soon be stopping at Kiyomizu Temple.
The hill leading to Kiyomizu Temple is known as the Three-Year Hill.
Legend says that...
...if you fall from here, then you will die in three years.
Thus the Three-Year Hill becomes your Regretful-Tear Hill.
Are the jokes included with the trip?
Okay.
We'll be moving around in individual groups now.
Keep an eye out for traffic.
We'll regroup in front of Chion'in at 1230.
Don't be late!
Anyone who is late gets to turn in a 20-page report of gratefulness when we get back.
Are you sure?
You wanna try it?
The Dragon Slayer is probably about this heavy.
It's so high!
You know how the saying goes, "Jumping off the stage at Kiyomizu,"
but at this height, if you jumped, wouldn't you die?
Does it mean that you don't care anymore about happens from here on out?
You don't have any dreams, do you Kagami?
Hey, look.
It says marriage.
This place is apparently known for it's Goddess of Marriage.
They really spell it out for you.
Hey look, you can draw love fortunes.
Let's all give it a try.
Yeah, let's do it!
I guess I can't tell these apart...
Of course you can't.
This one!
Fulfill Love
Great Fortune
Oh, "great luck"!
Good for you, Kona-chan.
Alas.
I drew "good luck".
That's still pretty good.
I wonder what I got...
Half Fortune
"Half luck"?
What does that mean?
I-I guess it means you just get half the good luck.
Which means the other half must be bad luck.
I don't really care about love fortunes, anyway.
It's so cute!
It's pretty nice.
I think this suits you better, Kagami.
RECOMMENDED
What's that supposed to mean?
I think I'll get one of these.
Kagami, Kagami!
You forgot this!
I'm not buying it!
Then what about this?
Not buying!
You should be careful.
Marriage Wishes
This one says, "Konata is my wife."
All right.
Everyone's accounted for, right?
We're heading back to the hotel where we'll have lunch.
Let's go.
Take us there, please.
They said that Koizumi's character song was written in an IZAM-style.
Sensei!
We've got someone on our six!
What!?
It's me!
This is just like the Hokkaido shoot all over again!
You have to scream "***tel"!
Don't leave me!
That idiot!
One 50-page report for you, mister!
Driver, sorry,
could you pull over for a second?
Hotel                     Honnoji
See you later.
To Hiiragi
I'd like to talk
Please meet me in front
of our hotel at 9 tonight
From
a certain boy
Doesn't hurt at all!
Hurry up!
The Golden Pavilion is golden, but the Silver Pavilion isn't really silver...
They wanted to associate it with the Golden Pavilion,
so they named it the Silver Pavilion...
Click!
...to go along with the golden one.
It was never silver to begin with.
Click!
I wonder if they have a Sapphire and Ruby.
Like in Po*émon!
No interjection...?
Our family's shrine was on the news, and...
Tomorrow is the last day.
Our plan for free time is set, right?
Tomorrow is the beginning of our true school trip!
Now, off to the promised land!
Yeah...
Y-You said in front of the hotel.
Was this okay?
Yeah, did you wait long?
So...
What was it you wanted to tell me?
You're the only person I could talk to about this, Hiiragi.
Could you give me that doll?
Doll?
You know,
the one you bought from the souvenir shop at Kiyomizu Temple!
The Yatsuhashi character.
Y-Yatsuhashi-kun?
Yeah, that one!
I really liked it and wanted one for myself,
but if someone like me was caught buying one,
they'd all make fun of me!
So please!
O-Okay...
Thank you!
I owe you one!
Don't tell anyone else about this, okay?
And so, I'm reading this book about these four brothers...
Sohryu***?
I can't get it out.
Yeah, that one.
Come to think of it, that could make a pretty good anime.
The steam inside must have cooled down...
...and made a vacuum.
They did an adaptation a while back.
If you pull the edges a little bit,
Really... I had no idea!
that should allow the air to enter, and make the lid easier to open.
I see.
Though I think it only went up to the fourth volume of the original.
Okay then.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Putting on a show until the very end.
I've already looked up the directions.
Are you sure it's all right to go there?
We're just going to take a look from the outside, so it should be fine.
Just because we came to Kyoto doesn't mean we have to go that far.
You just don't understand the otaku's notion of romance, do you?
I don't want to.
Not much here.
It makes it easier for them to focus on their work.
It's a pretty ordinary-looking building.
They limit their works, so this is perfect.
Was it really necessary to buy these in Kyoto?
Princess Love
That's embarrassing!
Who cares?
It'll be our memory of this day!
Onee-chan, let's take one together!
It's a commemoration.
Since we came all the way to Kyoto.
What does this have to do with Kyoto at all?
Yeah, Tsukasa and I made it home safely.
Tsukasa's already asleep, though.
I figured you would have gone to bed out of spite.
Why would I do something like that?
Did you put the photo sticker on something?
How could I put up something so embarrassing!?
Something so embarrassing...
That sure was hard work.
With the school trip and all.
All right!
Time to top it all off with a weekend of online gaming for once!
Emergency Maintenance Notice
Due to an unexplained server error at 20:30,
the server is currently undergoing emergency maintenance.
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
We're coming at you full of energy today once again!
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
Piko!
I'm the assistant,
Ono Daisuke.
Time sure flies, we're already on our 21st episode!
That's right.
I think we're reaching the final stretch.
Now then,
let's get straight to the corner.
This Week's Bend
This week's...
Twist!
Who are you?
What?
I brought your water.
What is this!?
It's lukewarm!
How am I supposed to drink something like this!?
Even something out of the vending machine is better than this...
Don't screw with me!
Why you...
Why you!
How much do you think I've had to put up with this entire time!?
Always having to listen to your damn selfish requests!
M-Minoru?
Well, I'm gonna say what's on my mind today!
Do you have any idea how it feels, doing this corner every week!?
Every day I work at CoCo****!
With pay that's better than my voice acting work!
Thanks to you, I'm working full time now!
Before I come here to talk you up each day,
I'm over there deep-frying menchi katsu!
You do seem more suited for that kind of work.
And what the heck?
Why is Ono boy sitting there?
That's my designated seat!
You were cut.
By the producer and the director.
What's that!?
They decide too quickly!
I'm a late-bloomer!
I can go from here to Starga**r in no time!
Oh, can you...
...really?
Why you, making a fool of me...
Screw working with Hine**su,
or Lo** and Be**y.
I quit.
I quit this goddamn show!
Take that!
Who gives a damn about Lucky Channel!
Hold him down!
Let me go, morons!
What the heck do you think you're filming!
What's up with the Cape of Thirty Years?
If that makes a good plot...
I'm going to be thirty soon, too!
Yeah, I'm talking about you!
Welcome to Idaho!
The belt isn't long enough so she's holding it up from behind.
Hello! Shiraishi Minoru here!
Okay!
Yeah.
Now please listen!
Don't wanna hear it.
The Dentistman Song!
What is this?
The sound of my drill rings through the universe!
Uchuu ni hibike doriru on!
What does that even mean?
Yeah, yeah.
Any enemy will fall after one hit!
Donna aite mo ichi geki da!
Stop moving.
Right.
Stop moving!
Striving to protect everyone's dreams...
Minna no negai mamoru tame...
I head forth giving my all!
Onore wo sutete tachi mukau
Wait, Akira-sama!
Th-The enemy is the cavity monster from hell!
Teki wa jigoku no mushibadosu!
Sheesh.
Right.
I'll show you my Drill of Justice!
Seigi no doriru wo misete yare!
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now is the time!
Ima da!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Eliminate them!
Kezure!
T-Twin drill!
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Stop moving!
Shatter them!
Kudake!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eradicate them!
Kezure!
For I am...
Ore wa...
I am...
I am Dentistman!
Ore wa Shikaider!
Can I let go?
Dentistman is...
Don't screw up your lines!
...is a cyborg.
He...
He will...
You can't be a hero like that.
...continue fighting to defeat the evil cavities!
You can't fight like that.
How was it?
No good.
Redo.
Yes, ma'am.
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star:
Kogami Akira here!
Pika!
Ono Daisuke here.
Caw!
Piko? Piko.
Piko Piko Piko.
Caw.
Caw?
Piko?
Caw Caw!
Piko!
Caw!
Okay, that's enough animal talk.
So we were animals.
「 There Over Here 」
Next time: "There over here"
I can reach my goal now, right?
Pika!
Ramen set!