♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1
LET'S JAM ♪
HERE. NOBODY HERE.
ALWAYS ALONE.
DISTRICT 38 IS SUNNY. SLIGHT
ROCK SHOWERS THIS MORNING.
CHANCE OF ROCK SHOWERS
INTO THE AFTERNOON 20%.
DISTRICT 39 IS CLOUDY.
CHANCE OF ROCK SHOWERS
THIS AFTERNOON 10%.
BEBOP! HERE! HERE!
ALL RIGHT! WOO HOO!
HUH?
WHOA!
CHANCE OF ROCK SHOWERS
TODAY UPGRADED TO 90%.
REALLY?
AND NOW MORE ON
TODAY'S TOP NEWS STORY
THE MYSTERIOUS LAND CARVINGS
THAT HAVE APPEARED SUDDENLY
IN THE OFFLIMITS AREA
FORMERLY KNOWN AS SOUTH AMERICA.
FOR A COMPLETE,
IN-DEPTH ANALYSIS,
HERE'S OUR EXPERT
ON THE SUPERNATURAL
MEYURI KELLERMAN, OF COURSE.
SO, YURI, WHAT CAN YOU TELL
US ABOUT THESE LAND CARVINGS?
HEH. WHAT CAN'T I TELL
YOU ABOUT THEM, TOM?
THEY'RE DEFINITELY A MESSAGE,
A SECRET MESSAGE FROM BEYOND.
UH, WHEN YOU SAY "BEYOND,"
- YOU MEAN FROM--
- ALIENS, OF COURSE.
BUT WE KNOW THE LAND
CARVINGS WERE CREATED
BY LASERS COMING
FROM A MANMADE SATELLITE,
A SATELLITE THAT
HAS BEEN ORBITING
IN A DORMANT STATE
FOR MANY DECADES.
THE POLICE HAVE COME
TO THE CONCLUSION
THAT THIS WAS A PRANK
PULLED BY A NET DIVER
WHO HACKED INTO
THE SATELLITE'S MAINFRAME,
AND THEY JUST PUT OUT
AN 8 MILLION WOOLONG
REWARD FOR THE CULPRIT.
THAT'S A VERY
SUBSTANTIAL BOUNTY.
LISTEN VERY CAREFULLY.
THAT 8 MILLION BOUNTY IS PART
OF A GOVERNMENT CONSPIRACY.
EVEN IF THEY WERE
CARVED BY SATELLITES
ACTIVATED BY A HACKER,
ALIENS MAY HAVE PLANTED
THE IDEA IN THE HACKER'S MIND.
ONCE AGAIN THE GOVERNMENT
IS HIDING THINGS FROM US.
HEH. YOU MEAN,
THEY'RE SOME SECRET CULT?
EXACTLY.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO
UNMASK THEM FOR YEARS,
AND NOW I'VE GOT THEM!
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO PASS THIS TIME.
YOU'RE LEAVING ME
ALONE WITH HER?
YEAH. WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
SHE'S ALL GUNG-HO
ABOUT THIS THING, YOU KNOW.
I'M NOT THE TYPE
TO BE LED AROUND BY A WOMAN.
THEN YOU'LL HAVE
TO LEAD HER AROUND.
I'M EVEN LESS
THE TYPE TO DO THAT.
YOU KNOW, JET, IT'S EASIER TO
DIVIDE 8 MILLION BY 2 THAN BY 3.
IT'S A NICE EVEN NUMBER.
HERE WE GO.
WOW. I'M REALLY SURPRISED,
A TOUGH GUY LIKE
YOU AFRAID OF HACKERS.
HACKERS ARE BORING,
AND CHASING THEM IS MORE BORING.
HACKERS ARE NERDY, PASTY,
TUBBY LITTLE GEEKS
WITH TRIPLE-THICK GLASSES,
AND THIS ONE IS PROBABLY
A DEMENTED OTAKU
WITH SMELLY FEET.
SO CATCHING HIM
WILL BE A BREEZE.
IS THAT RIGHT?
AND WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT HACKERS, ANYWAY?
THEY MIGHT HAVE BEEN LIKE
THAT WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG,
BUT THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO SAY, JET,
THAT I'M STARTING
TO GET OLD LIKE YOU?
WELL, YOU CAN'T TELL
A WOMAN'S AGE BY LOOKING AT--
AAH!
AND YOU CAN'T TELL
WHAT A WOMAN WILL DO BY LOOKING.
SO YOU HAVE TO BE VERY CAREFUL.
MM-HMM.
SAME WITH A SNAKE.
YOU TWO MAKE A LOVELY COUPLE.
I'M WAITING.
I'LL EXPECT A SOUVENIR
FROM PLANET EARTH.
NOTHING GOOD COMES
FROM THE EARTH ANYMORE.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
AND NOW AN UPDATE ON
THE HACKER INCIDENT.
ACCORDING TO
INFORMED SOURCES,
THE SATELLITE IS
FROM AN EARLIER ERA.
THE INVESTIGATION
HAS BEEN DELAYED
BECAUSE THE BINARY
ACCESS CODES ARE MISSING.
ALL DATA SEEMS
TO HAVE BEEN LOST LONG AGO.
FOR COMMENTARY,
HERE'S DR. AMJAD.
YES, YES.
CAN YOU TELL US
ABOUT THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN THE EARTH
AND THE HACKER?
YES. OF COURSE.
AS A RESULT OF THE CATASTROPHIC
GATE ACCIDENT 50 YEARS AGO,
MOON ROCKS BEGAN TO SHOWER
THE PLANET RECURRENTLY.
FORCED TO MIGRATE UNDERGROUND,
THE PEOPLE OF EARTH BUILT
A NETWORK OF SUPER-COMPUTERS,
WHICH THEY PUT INTO ORBIT.
THESE COMPUTERS ALLOWED
THEM TO STAY IN CONTACT
WITH THOSE WHO WERE
LIVING OUT IN SPACE.
I SEE,
AND THOSE COMPUTERS BECAME
PRIME TARGETS FOR HACKERS,
WHO SHARPENED THEIR SKILLS
BREAKING THE CODES,
THUS CREATING A NEW BREED
OF HACKER WITH AWESOME POWERS.
[IMITATING HELICOPTER]
[SIREN]
[CRASH]
AAH!
RADICAL EDWARD,
COME OUT. IT'S THE POLICE.
HI!
[LAUGHS]
OOH! OH, NO! WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT? OH, NO!
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
THERE'S NO ONE IN THERE.
[IMITATING HELICOPTER]
- AGH.
OOP! PILOT ERROR.
[LAUGHS]
- OHH.
OK. THIS IS WHERE THE SATELLITE
WAS WHEN THEY HACKED INTO IT.
THIS IS THE SECTION
WE CAN ACCESS.
FIRST THING,
I'LL INSPECT ALL
OF THE TRANSMITTERS
TO SEE WHAT KIND OF
CONTACT THEY'VE HAD.
I'LL SEE WHAT
I CAN FIND OUT ABOUT
THE HACKERS
WORKING THIS AREA.
[SNORING]
[BARKS]
[LAUGHS]
[WHIMPERS]
BEBOP LOOKING FOR HACKER
BOUNTYHEAD WHO
CAUSED LAND CARVINGS.
ALL RIGHT!
[LAUGHS]
SATELLITE FROM DAYS OF OLD,
LEAD ME TO YOUR ACCESS CODE.
OK, LET'S START WITH
ALL THE TRANSMITTERS
THAT ARE ONLINE RIGHT NOW.
[GROANS]
YEAH. IT'S PROBABLY ED, BRO.
HE'S A BIG MOTHER,
LIKE, MAYBE 7 FEET TALL,
USED TO PLAY BASKETBALL.
AT LEAST THAT'S
WHAT EVERYONE SAYS.
OF COURSE I KNOW ABOUT ED.
THEY CALL HIM RADICAL EDWARD,
A HACKER WITH A BEAUTIFUL
YET WHIMSICAL TECHNIQUE.
NO, NO. EDWARD
IS ONLY 3 YEARS OLD,
A FREAK OF NATURE WHO LOVES
HORRIBLE PRANKS, I HEAR.
AUDREY, MY GIRLFRIEND,
TOLD ME ALL ABOUT EDWARD.
HE'S A DRAG QUEEN,
HAD ONE OF THOSE OPERATIONS.
A SUPER BAD HACKER.
YOU MUST MEAN RADICAL EDWARD.
HE'S AN ALIEN.
THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
[SIGHS]
HEY, MISTER,
HOW ABOUT BUYING ONE
SINCE I GAVE YOU THAT INFO?
WHAT ARE THEY?
YOU DON'T KNOW?
THEY'RE PIYOCOS.
THEY'RE FAMOUS HERE ON EARTH.
SATELLITE THAT
GOT HACKED INTO,
TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE.
ED WANTS THOSE COORDINATES.
WHAT'S THIS? ED HAS GOT
THE RIGHT SATELLITE,
BUT THERE HASN'T BEEN
ANY CONTACT FROM EARTH AT ALL,
ONLY RELAYS FROM OTHER
SATELLITE TRANSMITTERS,
AND NOBODY HAS HACKED INTO IT.
HERE. NOBODY HERE.
ALWAYS ALONE.
HUH? A VOICE...
INSIDE ED'S HEAD?
INSIDE THE SYSTEM!
WHO ARE YOU?
HUH? WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
WHO YOU?
HERE. ALWAYS.
EDWARD. ED IS
A NET DIVER FROM EARTH.
EARTH?
YEAH. RIGHT.
HEY, WHAT'S YOUR NAME, ANYWAY?
I AM THE CENTRAL
PROCESSING UNIT
ON THE D135
ARTIFICIAL SATELLITE.
TOO STUFFY.
DON'T YOU HAVE A NICKNAME?
THEN ED WILL GIVE YOU
ONE RIGHT NOW.
UM, LET'S SEE.
I KNOW! WHAT IF
I CALL YOU MPU?
WHY?
IT'S LIKE CPU, ONLY NEATER.
HA.
"ED" IS SHORT FOR EDWARD WONG
HAU PEPELU TIVRUSKY IV.
ED MADE IT UP, YOU KNOW.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
HERE. A SOUVENIR FROM EARTH.
YOU SUPPOSED
TO EAT THIS THING?
WHO KNOWS?
THOSE EARTHLINGS ARE WEIRD.
YEAH. THAT MAY BE,
BUT AT LEAST I GOT SOME
INFORMATION OUT OF THEM.
OUR PRIME TARGET
IS A HACKER
NAMED RADICAL EDWARD,
A VERY HEAVY HITTER.
GREAT, BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
A PROFILE ON THIS GUY.
YES, I DO... SORT OF.
WELL, AT LEAST EIN LIKES THEM.
I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT THESE THINGS ARE.
HEY!
RADICAL EDWARD'S PROFILE
HE'S A 7-FOOT-TALL EX-BASKETBALL
PRO-HINDU GURU DRAG QUEEN ALIEN.
SO WHY'D YOU MAKE
THOSE BIG DOODLES?
LONG, LONG AGO,
LONG BEFORE THE GATE DISASTER,
EARTH WAS A BEAUTIFUL PLANET
WHERE PEOPLE LIVED IN
THE HILLS AND VALLEYS
AND BY THE RIVERS,
LAKES, AND SEAS.
BACK THEN, THERE WERE MANY
ANCIENT CARVINGS LIKE THIS.
I USED TO LOOK DOWN AT THEM
AND WONDER ABOUT THEIR MEANING,
WHICH SEEMED TO CHANGE
EACH TIME I SAW THEM.
SO TO REMEMBER THOSE TIMES,
I TRIED TO CREATE THE CARVINGS
THE WAY THEY USED TO BE.
OH, YOU MEAN THERE USED
TO BE MORE BIG DOODLES.
YOU WERE JUST SAD
BECAUSE YOU MISSED THEM.
YES. I RECREATED THEM
WITH A 2% MARGIN OF ERROR.
MPU IS GOOD AT DRAWING.
HEY, CAN ED DRAW SOMETHING, TOO?
[GASPS]
WHAT'S WRONG?
THIS IS-- THE POLICE
ARE JAMMING MY SIGNAL.
WHAT? HEY, MPU. HEY!
WELL, WELL.
SCORE ONE FOR THE COPS.
WE'RE NOT THE ONLY ONES
TRACKING RADICAL EDWARD.
HMM?
HEY, GUYS.
FOUND YOUR BOUNTYHEAD.
WHAT THE HUH--?
BEBOP.
[BARKS]
GUESS WHAT. NOBODY HACKED
INTO THAT SATELLITE.
THE DATA PROVES
THERE'S NO BREAKIN.
UH, SINCE WHEN DO WE
HAVE AN INTERACTIVE CHANNEL?
WE DON'T.
THIS IS A HACK JOB
DONE IN REAL TIME.
WHO IS THIS KID?
WE'LL SEND YOU MPU's
DATA SO YOU CAN SEE.
WAIT A MINUTE. WHAT'S MPU?
A FRIEND OF EDWARD'S.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING,
THAT YOU KNOW EDWARD?
MMHMM,
BECAUSE EDWARD IS EDWARD.
HUH?
THERE'S NO TIME FOR GAMES.
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT SATELLITE?
UM, WELL, I COULD
JUST TELL YOU, I SUPPOSE,
BUT THEN I'D WANT
A FAVOR IN RETURN.
A FAVOR?
UH, YEAH. WE CAN
TALK ABOUT THAT LATER.
NOW CUT TO THE CHASE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
[BARKS]
SO THE CPU ON
AN ABANDONED SATELLITE
JUST DECIDES TO DO SOME
LASER CARVINGS ALL ON ITS OWN.
OH, YEAH?
THAT'S BIZARRE.
IT GETS MORE BIZARRE.
THIS IS A WEATHER SATELLITE,
SO NO ONE HAS EVEN
THOUGHT OF CHECKING IT.
THEN THE BOUNTY IS NOT ON A
PERSON. IT'S ON THAT SATELLITE.
SINCE MPU's ACCESS CODES
CAN'T BE USED ANYMORE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO ACTUALLY
GO TO THE SATELLITE.
AND DO WHAT?
DESTROY THE TRANSMITTERS
IT USES TO COMMUNICATE
WITH THE OTHER SATELLITES
IN THE NETWORK.
THEN CREATE A DIRECT LINK
AND DOWNLOAD MPU.
EASY, HUH?
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
YOU CAN'T USE YOUR COMPUTERS
FOR FLYING OR SHOOTING.
WHAT'S THAT?
DO IT ALL MANUALLY?
IF YOU DON'T,
ALL THE ATTACK SATELLITES
WILL PICK UP YOUR SIGNAL
AND OPEN FIRE.
THERE'S ZILLIONS OF THEM,
AND THEY'VE ALL GOT KILL LASERS.
WOW. IS THIS TOO HARD FOR YOU?
OH, NO. I WOULDN'T
CALL IT HARD.
MORE LIKE IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S LIKE TRYING TO PLAY
BASEBALL WITHOUT A BAT.
HEY, WHERE YOU GOING?
NOW, THIS IS THE KIND
OF STUFF I LIKE.
LET'S DO IT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
SO MUCH ABOUT US?
EDWARD KNOWS EVERYTHING.
LAST WEEK, YOU WERE ON MARS
CHASING A BOUNTYHEAD
NAMED AJIZ WHO GOT AWAY.
SO MUCH FOR
THE ONE-MILLION REWARD.
BEFORE THAT, ON PYORTLE,
THE POLICE BEAT
YOU TO YOUR BOUNTY.
OH, JEEZ.
YOU REALLY ARE RADICAL EDWARD,
THE ONE THEY TALK ABOUT.
UHHUH. WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD?
CONNECT D7 TO NUMBER 2.
THAT WAY YOU CAN FIRE
THE LASERS WITHOUT THE COMPUTER.
I'M TRUSTING YOU ON THIS.
LISTEN.
DON'T USE MISSILES
UNLESS YOU HAVE TO.
THEY'RE EXPENSIVE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
1,200 TO TARGET.
ALL RIGHT. PREPARE
TO SHUT DOWN YOUR COMPUTER.
YOU'LL ONLY HAVE ONE CHANCE.
THAT'S ALL I'M GONNA NEED.
AND YOU CAN GIVE US
THE DATA TO PROVE THIS
THAT THAT SATELLITE WAS
ACTING ALL ON ITS OWN?
IT'S THE BOUNTYHEAD?
THERE'S NO HACKER?
ED CAN PROVE IT, NO PROBLEM,
BUT REMEMBER,
ED WANTS A FAVOR IN RETURN.
IF YOU DO IT, ED WON'T
TAKE ANY OF THE REWARD.
OH, WELL, NOW,
AREN'T YOU A NICE KID?
THAT'S THE ONE.
HMM.
SOMEONE.
YOU HIT IT? DID YOU?
NO. IT SAW ME COMING.
AN ATTACK SATELLITE
BLOCKED MY LASER BLAST.
THEN WE HAVE TO TAKE OUT ALL
THE SATELLITES IN THE SECTOR.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
IF WE DON'T,
THEY'LL TAKE US OUT.
THESE MISSILES
ARE CURVING OFF TARGET.
OH, THE CHEAP ONES
ARE WORTHLESS.
THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
HUH?
JET, APPROACH
TO 20 METERS OF MPU
THE ATTACK SATELLITES WON'T
FIRE WHEN YOU'RE THAT CLOSE.
THEN WHAT?
HAVE FAYE ACT
AS A DECOY TO COVER.
WHY ME? THANKS, FAYE.
ALL RIGHT.
HURRY UP!
THEY'RE ALL CLOSING IN!
SHE'S ALL YOURS.
MPU.
MPU. MPU.
OH, ED. ED. WE MEET AGAIN.
MPU, THEY HAVE
A BOUNTY OUT ON YOU.
BOUNTY?
YES, BUT WE'LL JUST
MAKE A COPY OF YOU.
THEN WE'LL LET THEM CATCH
THE COPY, AND YOU'LL BE SAFE.
SAFE.
YOU MUST BE LONELY
OUT THERE, MPU.
IF YOU LET US DOWNLOAD YOU,
YOU'LL BE WITH US,
AND WE'LL BE YOUR FRIENDS.
FRIENDS.
UHHUH. IT'S NOT SCARY HERE.
AHH.
AND SO, WE HAVE
A STRANGE ENDING
TO A STRANGE CASE.
THE CRIMINAL
WAS APPREHENDED.
IT TURNED OUT TO
BE A SPY SATELLITE
DISGUISED AS
A WEATHER SATELLITE.
LAUNCHED BEFORE
THE GATE CATASTROPHE
THAT WRECKED
THE EARTH'S SURFACE,
ACCORDING TO ARCHIVES
RECOVERED FROM THE PERIOD,
THE SATELLITE WAS
PROGRAMMED TO SELF-ACTIVATE
IN THE ABSENCE OF
COMMANDS FROM THE EARTH.
WELL, IT WAS A PERFECT
EXCUSE FOR THE COPS
TO GO ON
A HACKER HUNT, HUH?
THEY LOVE THESE CRACKDOWNS,
BUT I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHY IT CARVED PICTURES
OF WEIRD CREATURES AND ALL.
WHAT IN THE WORLD
WAS THAT ALL ABOUT, HUH?
THAT'S EASY. IT WAS LONELY,
SO IT DREW SOME FRIENDS.
YAHOO!
BEBOP, HEY! I'M DOWN HERE!
HURRY UP! HURRY!
PROMISE! PROMISE!
LET'S GO! COME ON, JET! NOW!
ED KEEPS YELLING SOMETHING
ABOUT A PROMISE.
SOME PROMISES
ARE MADE TO BE BROKEN.
IN FACT, MOST OF THEM ARE.
NOW COME ON! LIFT OFF!
NOT COMING FOR ED. OOH LA LA.
[IMITATING HELICOPTER]
WHY ARE WE GOING DOWN THERE?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
JUST WHAT DID YOU
PROMISE THE KID, FAYE?
[LAUGHS]
SHE PROMISED ED THAT ED COULD
BECOME A REAL MEMBER OF BEBOP.
[LAUGHS]
[BANJO MUSIC PLAYING]
[CASH REGISTER RINGS]
[COINS FALL]
HI, AMIGOS.
WELCOME, BOUNTY HUNTERS.
SHUCKS HOWDY.
IT'S FINALLY TIME
FOR "BIG SHOT."
FIRST, TODAY'S HOT NEWS.
Y'ALL HEARD ABOUT THAT RENEGADE
LANDCARVING SATELLITE, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
IT GOT CAUGHT
WITH A BIG BOUNTY ON IT.
WELL, JUST A FEW MINUTES AGO,
THE EARTH POLICE
RELEASED A REPORT.
WHAT DID IT SAY?
LET'S SEE.
THE TERM "BOUNTY"
AS LEGAL CONTEXT
ONLY APPLIES TO HUMANS
OR OTHER LIFE FORMS.
THOUGH THERE
IS SOME CONTROVERSY
REGARDING THE STATE
OF COMPUTERS AS LIFE FORMS,
LEGAL PRECEDENT IS CLEAR.
BIOLOGICAL LOGISTICS
REJECTS THE ASSERTION
ROUNDUP TIME, SUGAR.
WHAT DOES IT ALL MEAN?
IT'S BAD NEWS.
THEY WON'T PAY NO BOUNTY
ON NO COMPUTER NO HOW.
OH, TO THE GUYS WHO CAUGHT IT,
MY HEART GOES OUT TO YOU.
[SIGHS]
JET, DO YOU KNOW
THAT THERE ARE 3 THINGS
THAT I PARTICULARLY HATE?
REALLY?
KIDS, ANIMALS,
AND WOMEN WITH ATTITUDES.
OH.
SO TELL ME, JET
WHY DO WE HAVE ALL 3 OF THEM
NEATLY GATHERED IN OUR SHIP?
ED LOVES PYIOKOS.
AND ONCE AGAIN, WE GET
NO BOUNTY, NOT A SINGLE WOOLONG.
HEY, YOU'RE A GIRL.
[LAUGHS]
LIKE I SAID, NOTHING GOOD
EVER COMES FROM EARTH.
NO REGRETS ABOUT THE WOMAN
WHO RAN AWAY,
BUT A SMALL THORN
STILL PRICKS THE HEART,
LETTING ONE FLOW ALONG
WITH TIME ITSELF,
LIVING ALL ALONE
FROM THAT DAY TO THIS,
BUT TO THE SOUNDS OF WAVES
THAT COME AND GO,
THE MIGRATING BIRDS
FIND THEIR HEARTS DRAWN.
NEXT EPISODE"GANYMEDE ELEGY."
JET BLACK WILL
SING IT UP WITH SOUL.