Safe!
Perf, you silly!
Ta-da! A party curl!
That settles that!
You seem excited!
I sure am!
Because tomorrow's Family Day!
Family Day?
It's a festival that we first years
set up and invite our families to.
It's been three months since I entered Noble Academy.
And tomorrow, I'll finally get some family bonding in!
I can hardly contain my excitement!
How much of your family's coming?
My mom, my dad, and my little sister!
Sister?
I didn't know you had one.
I do!
This is my sister, Momoka! She's a first grader!
Wow, she looks just like you!
So that's your sister!
She sure is!
She'd always tug my shirt and call me "Big sis! Big sis!"
When we walk, she always waddles a little behind me!
She's the cutest sister ever!
You sure sound affectionate.
Yeah!
'Cause we love each other!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
They're here!
Mom! Dad!
Haruka!
We missed you so much!
We really did!
Geez, Dad, you're embarrassing me!
Seems like you're doing well.
Yeah, I'm doing great!
How's Noble Academy? Fun?
Yeah! Every day's a full bloom of fun!
Noble Academy is the best!
Momoka!
Nice to see you!
Huh? Momoka?
C'mon and give your sister a hug!
So, this is your school?
Yeah, isn't it splendid?
Nope.
I hate this place.
The Form of Love!
The Haruno Family Dream!
Reception
Minami!
Let me introduce my mom and dad!
A pleasure to meet you.
My name is Kaidou Minami.
It's an honor to finally meet Haruka's mother and father.
Well, uh, thank you kindly!
Thanks for looking after our daughter.
Man, they don't call it "Noble Academy" for nothing!
All the kids here are so nice and polite!
I know, right?
Everyone here is simply splendid!
And this is my sister, Momoka!
Bonjour, Momoka.
The "bonjour" thing is how people
at Noble Academy greet each other!
You're weird.
Huh? Wait, Momoka!
I'm sorry, Minami!
That was so rude of her...
Don't worry.
She doesn't seem too happy to be here.
Is something the matter?
I don't know myself.
Did something happen?
No, Momoka was excited to see you the whole drive up.
She's been bragging to her friends
that you got into Noble Academy, too.
I can't imagine why she'd suddenly hate this school.
Take a look! Aren't they splendid?
I raised them myself!
My little girl's got herself a green thumb!
Hey, Momoka!
Haruno Flowerka!
Nothing?!
But how? That joke should've cracked her up!
Is this her rebellious phase?
Everyone!
Thanks for taking care of my daughter, Haruka!
Have a dorayaki!
You too!
Dad, you brought dorayaki?!
He wanted everyone in school to enjoy them.
He was up all night baking!
Something's written on this.
"Be nice to Haruka," huh?
Wait, is that Haruno's face?
It's a dead ringer!
No way!
Wow, it's totally her!
Take one! You too!
It's cute!
Dad, please!
Scrumptious!
I've never had a dorayaki this scrumptious!
Thanks...
I love them too.
Whoah, this is great!
Haruno, is your father a dorayaki baker?
He makes all kinds of sweets!
My family runs a confection shop called "Haruya."
All of our customers love the sweets Dad makes!
Huh, I never knew.
Well, it ain't bad.
You could just say it tastes good!
It's so yummy!
Thanks!
Dad, here are some cookies I baked!
You made them yourself?!
It's good! Unbelievably good!
Hold it together, Dear!
Oh, they grow up so fast...
Haruka!
Momoka, have some!
Don't want 'em.
C'mon, Momoka, you love cookies!
They're really yummy, so have as many as you want!
I'm fine!
Spurned by your sister, eh?
Uh, are you taking it personally?
Hey there, Momoka.
Amanogawa Kirara's the name!
Kirara's a fashion model!
She's famous!
Is she your friend?
Yeah!
That hairstyle looks great on you.
A ribbon might make it even better.
Huh?
Don't want one?
Too bad.
Momoka, would you like some juice?
I don't want any!
I'm so sorry, Minami!
It's fine. Don't worry.
Sorry...
Momoka!
Say what you want to me,
but I won't let you be rude to my friends!
Uh...
I...
I hate you, Sis!
Momoka!
Such peerless pulchritude upon a magnificent melody...
Princess Twilight, there is naught but one word to describe you...
Beautiful!
But of course.
It is a given for one as gorgeous and musically gifted as I.
For I was born a princess.
Indeed, Princess Twilight!
There is naught but you who are fit for that title!
Time for a stroll.
Princess Twilight, to where?
I shall accompany you!
The Key desires despair...
Cute Curls!
I don't think she's gone far, so let's split up and search.
Okay.
Sorry my daughter's putting you all through this.
Thanks for your help.
I hope you find her.
Haruka?
Oh, what?
Are you all right?
Having your sister hate you all of a sudden kinda stings.
You really think she hates you?
Huh?
I think I understand how Momoka feels a bit.
I had a hard time coping when my brothers first entered Noble Academy as well.
I was lonely, but I had trouble expressing it,
so I sometimes said things I didn't mean.
But even then...
I never once hated them.
A poodle?
Her name's Perf.
Looks like she's worried about you.
Haruharu's worried too, you know.
Let's head back.
Why not?
I made Sis mad...
and now she hates me...
You know, I don't get to see my mom a lot.
My mom's a supermodel, so she's always flying around the world.
She couldn't come today because of work.
Are you sad?
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't.
We're family, after all!
But I don't want to keep Mom from her dream.
Heck, I want to cheer her on!
I'm cheering Sis on, too...
Sis put in a lot of work to get into this school,
so I really, really want her to do well.
But...
when I saw how happy Sis was to be here,
I figured she didn't miss us...
Mom and Dad and I were so sad without her,
but she was totally fine...
and when that hit me...
You know, Haruharu was super excited to see you today.
She even showed us your picture.
Your smile in it was super cute.
I'm sure she missed you too.
So let's go back to her.
But I lost my present...
Your present?
I made it for Sis, but...
Momoka!
Was... this your present?
Sis!
I'm sorry!
I'm the one who should apologize!
I should have known how you felt!
I'm really sorry!
Momoka!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Mom, Dad!
We were all worried about you.
Sorry for making you worry.
Just don't do it again, okay?
I made this for you, Sis.
I hope your dream comes true.
Momoka...
thank yoooooou!
Hey, open it!
Sure! Thanks, Momoka!
The scent of dreams...
It's you!
Twilight!
Sealing that dream will bring forth despair.
There is naught but to leave it to me.
Now, show me your dreams!
Congrats
You're splendid, Haruka!
I'm so glad your dream came true!
Congrats, Sis!
Mom! Dad! Momoka!
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
How dare you!
Their dream is for their daughter's dream to come true?
Out of all the dreams I've seen, that is by far the most inane.
You just don't understand family bonds!
Family bonds?
How foolish.
Girls!
Let's go!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go! Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
I suggest you do the same.
Princess Precures, I shall defeat you here for the honor of Princess Twilight!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspaaaaairviiiiil!
You're helpless.
There is naught for you to do but flee and eventually fall!
Dyspairviiiil!
I thought dreams only came true through your own strength...
But it's the people that support you who give you that strength!
I have a family that supports me,
so I'll let nothing keep me from my dream!
How futile.
In the end, there is naught waiting for you but despair!
Dyspaaair!
Aroma, hold this!
You got it!
Viiiiiil!
Wow!
Way to go, Flora!
I can feel Cure Flora's spirits rising?
But why?
Dyspairvil!
This is no time to spectate. Let's join!
Dyspairviiiil!
What?!
Rose!
Dance, O roses!
Precure!
Rose Tourbillon!
Dyspaaair!
Curses!
Now!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rose!
Ice!
Luna!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Lumière!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Blast! But I've still—
That will do.
Shut, it's your loss. Withdraw.
Princess Twilight, I—
I despise such ignoble cowardice.
Particularly the cowardice of a sore loser.
Right!
This has grown dull.
Oh, do wait!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Congrats
Mom, Dad, Momoka...
I'm sure I do enough to worry you around the clock, so I'm sorry.
Momoka, I'm sorry I can't be by your side.
But more importantly, thanks for your support.
I'll dance as well as I can to thank you!
Haruka! Haruka!
Sis!
Momokaaaa!
S-Sorry!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Aaahh! There's a boy in the girl's dorm?!
Haruka, calm down. That's Aroma.
Wha? No way!
Uh, who was she, again?
That's Perf.
It appears they transformed.
Wh-What do you mean?!
This is a total mess!
Go! Princess Precure:
An Aromatic Transformation!
Aroma's Butler Test!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Niigata Prefecture - Yumeka (Age 6)
Aichi Prefecture - Mao (Age 11)