Winter has arrived.
With our little police incident safely behind us,
we've returned to our usual lives.
Outwardly, nothing has changed.
But perhaps something has shifted somewhere.
Regardless, the ESP Society is now and always shall be my home.
Research Society
Wassup!
Hello.
Good, everyone's here.
As of this moment, the ESP Research Society is officially disbanding!
What?!
One morning I realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
Don't fret now
Fret,
fret,
fret
Can't you smell my feelings on me?
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Is this love?
That's a really big secret, you know?
Yeah!
That's a really big secret,
isn't it?
The Things I Want
to Tell You
Pull yourself together, Kotoura!
My home...
It's no good. We've lost her!
What do I do?
Don't die, Kotoura!
I must give her mouth-to-mouth!
No...
I must perform chest compressions!
How am I supposed to choose?!
Wait! I can just choose both!
Kotoura.
Megoxhyef!
I can't let my guard down for a second around this Lothario.
Feels like it's been ages since you've called me that!
It kinda makes me tingle!
Ever the peerless lecher.
Are you quite finished with your little hymeneal comedy routine?
H-Hymeneal?
What?
What do you think that word means?
That is—
what do you mean, "disbanding," President Mifune?
Exactly what I mean.
The activities of the ESP Society,
directed at demonstrating scientifically
the existence of psychic powers and encouraging their acceptance
among the general populace, are ending as of today.
Are you serious about this?
No way.
Kotoura.
And, as of today,
I'm proudly announcing the foundation of the New ESP Research Society!
What?
You heard me. The New ESP Society!
Its primary aim will be to have fun with a psychic.
A psychic?
Me?!
We'll tease Kotoura and laugh at her ridiculous reactions.
Pretty much the same stuff we did before.
Why must everyone mock me?!
Wait, so this means it's okay for me to stay here?
Of course.
Your home isn't going away.
Oh, good grief.
You might've said so in the first place...
Hang on, couldn't you hear Yuriko thinking about it?
You know you can't trust what she actually says.
You've got quite the wicked tongue yourself.
I was so shocked, I didn't have time to check her thoughts.
It's not like you guys saw through her, right?
So it takes much lewder and lustier thoughts
to pique your interest, does it?
Oh, damn! My manly spirit is rising!
If I rig a hidden camera in that haunted house on Third Street
and lure Kotoura there...
I'm on the fire!
I knew I could trust you two to swiftly grasp the New ESP Society's objectives.
Hey! Stop picking on me!
You make a fine team, Manabe and Moritani.
You're getting along a lot better than you were.
It's like you've lost your hesitation.
I'm sorry. Kotoura has all my love.
I can't reciprocate your feelings.
What? Why?
I knew it would end this way.
And so, to celebrate the creation of the New ESP Society,
shall we sing some karaoke?
Yippee!
Oh yeah. You all went to karaoke before I joined the club.
Come with us, Moritani.
S-Sure. Let's sing together.
You'll regret those words.
You're horrible!
Oh, sorry. I need to finish something off here.
Kotoura, would you mind helping me?
Yeah, sure.
Then we'll head on over and reserve a room.
Let's scoot, you two.
What? I can help too.
Yeah, we should all...
Don't dawdle. Let's get moving, Moritani.
Hey, what are you doing? Stop shoving!
Don't go overboard, Yuriko.
President Mifune, everything's all right.
There was never any need for you to do this.
Please, no more apologizing.
In your every glance, I've heard an apology.
You apologized in tears, and apologized in laughter.
Enough. No more remorse.
But I've been trying to use you all along!
I know.
I pretended to be a good mentor,
but I only wanted to control you!
I know.
I showed you terrible things just to get your sympathy!
I put you in danger on my mother's account,
even though she had nothing to do with you!
Yes, I know all of that.
I am a psychic.
Then how can you say I needn't apologize?!
I've been a terrible friend!
I'm just a dirty selfish—
I have no right to condemn you.
After all, I was only using you too.
Kotoura.
Thank you for giving me
such a wonderful place to be myself.
Some president I am, letting you see me like that.
But are you really giving up on proving that psychic abilities exist?
I'd be lying if I said I had found some sort of catharsis.
But I can't let Muroto get hurt again.
I'll just take it slow and do what I can to—
What the heck is that look?
So that really was what was going on with you and Muroto!
What do you mean, "what was going on"?
Exactly what I mean.
So you wanna hear alllll about it?
Shoot! I'm in for it now!
It's okay. You can read my mind.
Go on. Look all you like.
U-Um.
Oh, that's right. We can't let Manabe and the other wai—
Do it.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Sorry you had to see me like that.
Nah, it's normal for you.
That was your cue to say something nice.
That aside,
You said that you'd stay with me until we reached port,
that you'd always be at my side.
Didn't you?
So how exactly did you mean that?
Well, we're childhood friends.
And I don't have any plans to move away just yet.
Um. I am truly sorry.
Yeah, that's right!
That lunkhead is genuinely clueless!
I've been subtly seducing him for frickin' years,
and he doesn't even notice!
Please calm down!
I guess I'm just used to it at this point.
I'll take this slow too.
You and Manabe, though!
You two are total lovebirds!
Huh?!
Please stop picking on me.
Knowing Manabe,
I'll bet he's constantly whispering amorous nothings in your ear.
Absolutely not!
Oh, come on.
Manabe's never—
He's never...
Wait.
What's wrong, Kotoura?
I've just realized Manabe
has never actually said "I love you."
Let's be off! Everyone is waiting!
That's just no fair!
Man, my throat is shot.
You sang too much.
And you're as tone deaf as ever.
Back then you taught me the strength to live
and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us
The flowers of hope may bloom,
What? What? Is this a joke?
We start our days together here
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?!
Absolutely unbearable!
Here you are. Chin up.
Oh. Thanks.
Welp, see ya tomorrow.
M-Manabe!
Um. Good night.
Night!
Why should he need to say it out loud?
I know how he feels, after all.
Huh?
I must have left the lights on this morning.
I'm gonna drive up my electricity bill.
Don't be stingy over stupid little things like that.
Well, I live on my own.
I need to economize wherever I can.
What? When did you start living like you're poor?
I'm not poor, simply prudent.
What?!
M-Mother?
So. Why are you here today?
How did you get into my room?
I came to eat at a restaurant by here, but it was closed. That's all.
I had the landlord unlock the door for me.
O-Oh.
You know you're a pretty crappy host?
At least offer me some food and booze.
But, well, I'm not old enough to drink, so I don't have any alcohol.
I'm sorry.
I'll go buy some right now. Please wait here.
Stop right there.
I'm coming too.
What are you doing?
You really are a damn idiot.
It's well after dark. She can't go out alone.
So how is it?
I guess it's not inedible.
When did you learn to make this?
I tried to make it how you used to.
Do you remember?
You used to cook it for me all the time.
Guess I forgot.
I see.
What's eating you?
Nothing. It's nothing.
My daughter, ever trying to avoid a conflict.
Pathetic.
And yet every time you open your mouth, you say something insensitive and piss people off.
You say you made friends, but that's got to be a bunch of bullshit.
It is not.
They've stayed by my side! Supported me!
They're true friends!
I am not lying!
Why, you—
You abandoned your own child in her greatest need!
You have no right to talk like you know me!
Wha?
What?! Like you're the only one capable of feeling pain!
Don't forget about those who were hurt just because they got close you!
If it was too much for you, why not ask for help?
Or could it be you didn't have any friends, Mother?
Wh—
What is this?!
I'm not like you!
You're just a naïve little girl with crappy taste in boys!
I know Manabe's a hopeless lecher!
But look who's talking!
I haven't forgotten that Tsuyama guy you were with!
What?!
You ignorant brat! Don't you take that tone with me!
Speak for yourself! Some adult you are!
That's it! Get over here!
Why I'll—
Mother, you nincompoop!
Hey—
Nincompoop! Nincompoop! Nincompoop!
You little...
Cut it out right now!
You cut it out!
You pelican daughter!
You nincompoop mother!
How did you turn out like this?!
It's all your fault!
Damn, you've really learned to dish it out.
My friends told me I shouldn't bottle up my feelings.
Friends, huh?
So what were you going to say about Tsuyama?
W-Well...
Hi there.
So you're Kumiko's daughter?
High school girl sighted!
That filthy pedophile!
Why didn't you tell me?
You're the one who told me to stay quiet.
Did I say that?
I guess we really do share a lousy taste in men.
I think you've still got me beat.
I gotta some more booze in me.
Haruka, clean up and get the sake ready.
You could help out too, you know.
Didn't you say you'd do all the cooking and cleaning when I left home?
I think that offer is no longer valid.
Okay, Mother, I'm finished cleaning.
Just give me—
Honestly, Mother.
I'm sorry, Haruka.
I'm so sorry.
If only you had never been born.
Wait, Kumiko!
K-Kumiko!
I'm sorry I was so weak, Haruka.
I'm so sorry I couldn't protect you.
I...
I was such a child.
My power didn't help me look inside.
I didn't even try to understand what my mother was really feeling.
Why did she put up that cold front?
I never knew.
I never knew there were things I couldn't understand without words.
Mama.
I'd like my eggs over easy.
Mother.
Mother?
I asked for over easy, Mother.
These are so overcooked they're bitter.
Sorry I'm late.
So I gather you told Kumiko about that incident with the criminal?
I haven't a clue what you mean.
I just got a message from Haruka.
From Haruka?
Well, look at that.
Haruka
Mom's fried eggs
Hmph. Her cooking used to be a lot better.
Haruka
Mom's fried eggs
That idiot daughter of mine.
Kotoura, let's head to club.
Manabe.
KotoUra!
For goodness' sakes open the door! He's right behind you!
Please stop casting me in your weird fantasies.
I've got something to do, so you go on ahead.
Understood.
So, Moritani, I wanted to talk to you.
I see. He hasn't actually told you himself, huh?
But don't you know what's in his heart?
I don't see any cause for worry.
That's why I thought it was okay.
But then I realized it:
sometimes I need people to tell me what they're thinking.
I want to hear it in Manabe's own words.
I see.
So you came to me for advice.
I know it's kind of awful for me to ask you of all people about this.
Don't worry about that. I'm over it.
Honestly, it'd just make me happy to help a friend.
Moritani.
Don't expect any stellar advice, though.
Manabe only gave me a serious answer because I confessed to him.
I think you'll have to put your own feelings into words first.
R-Right.
But I've never confessed to anyone before.
What do I do?
You'll just have to practice!
Imagine I'm Manabe and confess to me!
Y-Yes, sir!
I... I l-lo—
All finished, Kotoura?
I love you!
What?!
M-Manabe?!
N-No way!
Moritani, that was sinfully divine.
I'll make sure you can never so much as look at a mere boy again.
My woman's been stolen by another woman?
How can this simultaneously feel so unnatural
and yet so! Damn! Good!?
Don't worry, I get it.
Let me take care of him. Carry on.
Fight!
Kotoura, your attempts at
self-expression tend to backfire,
so I think you'll be better off saying
whatever comes to mind at the time.
Well, good luck.
How can you be so sharp when it comes to everyone but yourself?
Huh? Are you mad about something?
You tell me!
Sto-O-op!
So there you have it. What do you think?
I get the feeling it'll work out somehow.
Really?
I'll do my best.
That's my best friend!
Wait! We're best friends, aren't we?
Sorry. Not anymore.
Oh, sorry! Did I hurt you?
No.
Thank you, Moritani.
Score!
It's so pretty.
Christmas already? Time really flies.
Manabe, it's a white Christma—
Yippee! Snow! Snow!
Kotoura! You think it'll stick?
Let's have a snowball battle!
And then build a ginormous snowman!
You really follow your heart, don't you?
That's why I love you, Manabe.
I'm actually embarrassed.
I say it all the time, so that's only natural,
but this is the first time you've said it to me.
Huh?!
Huh?
You've never said it to me, Manabe.
I've never said it out loud?
I'm sorry, Kotoura. I'm thinking it every second of the day, so I had no idea.
Isn't life a funny thing?
Even you can't be thinking it every second!
Don't you get how much it's been bothering me?
But that's the way you are, Manabe.
That's the way I love you.
I love you, too.
I've always, always loved you.
I love you like crazy.
Did you hear what was in my heart that time?
I did. I heard everything.
Everything!
When something trips you up,
how do you stand again?
Can truth be found by thinking
about the days to come?
When we are born, we all come into this world alone,
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us
the flower of hope may bloom,
we start our days together here
We start our days together here
Kotoura!
Good morning, everyone!
Thank you for your support!