Why?!
The stage for Full Moon's first solo live concert...
All of a sudden, we couldn't use it!
Someone pretended to be
on the staff and canceled it!
Unfortunately, the live performance was to be postponed...
But...
...by using a boat as the stage...
...the live concert was a success!
Under the evening sky, on the last day of summer break...
...Full Moon  shone with all of her beauty!
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Doushite kimi wo suki ni nattandarou
Why is it that I've fallen in love with you?
Kantan sugite kotae ni naranai
I can't find an answer easily...
Isn't it over?!
Hurry! Hurry!
What's wrong with you two?
Bathroom?
Ah.
Okay.
Great job, Full Moon-san.
Ah. Yes.
Thank you very much!
Okay, it's over.
Thanks for your help!
Good work!
Good work!!
Ooshige-san, let's go back!
Eh... ah... w-wait!
What's going on?!
Tell me why!
Didn't we tell you?
They've been really strict as of late at her house.
Kouyama
You were out later than the curfew we agreed upon.
I'm sorry.
Even if you're visiting your friends' house...
...staying too long just troubles them even more.
That's all.
Be more careful.
Okay.
Moving Panic
Well, then... I have to go shopping...
Ah.
Dr. Wakaouji.
He's so wonderful.
Hello? Mitsuki?
Yes. Good morning!
Hey, Mitsuki. Whatcha up to?
Eh?
I'm playing with the accessory from the last concert.
Is there any work?
Not really, but...
...just a little something.
Eh?
What is it?
What do you think it is?
Come on!
What is it?
Can you come out right now?
I'll be in the area soon.
Oh... if possible, could you bring
Takuto-kun and Meroko-chan along?
See you later!
Ah!
Hello?
Hello? Ooshige-san?
Hello?!
You've moved here...?!
Yep!
If I live closer to you...
...it'll be easier for you to get out, right?
I see how it is.
Only the best from a manager!
I suppose so...
Uh... where do you want this?
Ah.
The room over there, please.
Put that in the corner over there, please.
Okay.
Quite a big place, isn't it?
A manager can afford something like this, huh?
Oh, the rent isn't that much...
...compared to living in the city.
Ah...
Is that so...
Now I can give you even more support than before, Mitsuki.
If the place is this big...
...we can even have a room just for you, Mitsuki.
For me?
Yep.
We can use this room for
singing lessons and such.
You can use this room to be alone while you're writing lyrics, too.
Wow!
Ah!
It's completely soundproof.
It's like a private studio for Full Moon !
Makes her look like a professional artist...!
Our girl here is a professional, you know...
I still have a ways to go though, right?
Ooshige-san.
Doing all this for me... thank you!
Oh come on... it's nothing... it's nothing...
This was my dream.
A room with an ocean view...
What... so it was for herself, after all.
Well, I guess that's how it is.
So this is why she actually bothered to invite us?
Geez, I wonder what she thinks Shinigami are?!
Crap!
Huh?
Excuse me.
You dropped something.
Huh?
That's...
Thank you for your help.
No problem.
I'll leave these in the cart.
That's Mitsuki-chan...
I wonder what she's doing here.
Anyways, I have to report this to the madam...
That's right.
You guys aren't the only ones...
I called someone else to come help, too.
Eh?
Who is it?
Ah.
He's here!
Hmm?
Ah!
Wakaouji-sensei!
By helper, she meant you, Wakaouji-sensei?
Helper?
Thanks for coming!
You can park in the back.
U-Um...
That important business you mentioned is...?
Sorry about that.
We need a man's help here.
Huh... sure...
She's a sly one, that woman...
If she wasn't so pushy...
...she wouldn't make it as a manager, right?
B-But... is this okay?
Being a guy, I'd probably mess up... moving a girl's belongings...
Wh-Why is Dr. Wakaouji here...?
My, my... please don't worry about that.
After all, we do have a relationship.
A-A relationship?!
Yeah...
I'm not sure if I'll be of much help, though.
Yay!
Wakaouji-sensei's helping out too!
I'll go park my car, then.
That woman...
Just how is she related to Dr. Wakaouji?
U-Um...
Do you need help with that?
I-I've got it covered!
There, see.
Let's see.
Shinigami-kun...
...I'd like to move this over there.
Ah... th-thanks...
Softly... softly...
Being so friendly with my Dr. Wakaouji...
I'm going to find out who she really is.
Man...
Looks like we managed to put everything in order.
Yep.
You were a huge help!
Really... thank you so much!
Not at all.
I'm glad I was able to help.
Why are they so close?
So those two really are...
Tanaka-san!
W-Why are you here..?
What is it, Mitsuki?
Who is this person?
Ah.
Tanaka-san!
Tanaka-san is...
The housekeeper at Mitsuki-chan's home.
This isn't good...
It's bad?
Of course it is!
If this girl's relationship with her manager is discovered...
I see.
Tanaka-san!
Um...
This is, well...
Dr. Wakaouji!
Y-Yes!
You had a fiancée?!
Fiancée?!
You mean me?
Huh?!
Dr. Wakaouji was who I longed for...
All I dreamed for...
All I hoped for...
U-Um... Tanaka-san?
Let's settle down here.
Ooshige-san is nothing of the sort.
Geez... what's going on..?
Is that so?
I understand.
To make up for this...
...I challenge you!
What?!
The one who suits Dr. Wakaouji...
...must cook... do laundry... clean...
A bride that can do everything perfectly!
To decide which one of us is more suitable...
...let us have a battle!
Dr. Wakaouji...
Do I have no other alternative but to accept this challenge?
If that will calm Tanaka-san down...
All right!
Things are starting to heat up!
This is getting out of hand again...
Come!
Let's settle this fair and square!
Fine... we'll do it your way!
What do I do...?
This has turned into something awful.
Tanaka-san?
Tanaka-san?!
That's strange...
She hasn't come back from shopping yet...
A requirement for being a good bride...
...is being able to make a delicious miso soup.
Here you go, Mitsuki.
Eh?
Ah.
Miso Showdown! Start!
Your miso!
How do you like that?!
You little...
More!
Had enough?
It's done.
Here you go.
Wow!
Let's eat!
It's delicious.
It's really good.
What is it?!
What's wrong, you guys?!
Well... you do live alone...
You probably can't win at cooking...
Next up is the Cleaning Battle!
Ready...
Start!
I'll be fine at this.
Huh?
Huh, huh?
Ah...
Okay.
I'm done.
Ah!
I'm not done yet!
All right!
Next up is the Laundry Royale!
And...
Start!
What is this?!
Why would anyone scrub clothes
in this day and age?!
There.
I'm finished.
Ooshige-san...
...are you okay?
My arms...
I can't lift them...
Ah! Okay!
I can't stand this any longer!
Take this!
Here I go!
What's with the wind all of a sudden?!
And it's so hot...!
Me-Meroko!
You're overdoing it!
I'll dry it faster for her this way.
Power up!
Ah!
The clothes I just washed...!
W-What?
How... what just happened?
I overdid it... maybe...
So...
...it is really impossible for me...
...to make delicious food for my husband...
...or iron shirts for him....
We'll have fun shopping on the weekends...
...a warm, pleasant atmosphere in our house...
...with lots of friends...
But... but...
It's hopeless!
Besides...
My purpose in life isn't to become a good bride!
That's okay!
So what if I live alone for the rest of my life...!
Even if I'm accused of failing
to carry on the family...!
Even if they say I'm weird at work...!
Even if I have to live a cruel life off a pension...!
Even if I end up as a plain old cranky woman...!
C-Calm down, Ooshige-san...
That's a roundabout way to put it, but...
...that means that you've given up, right?
If you'll accept that...
Hold on!
Is it okay to leave things like this?!
Isn't this mortifying?!
Excuse me for intruding...
Honestly, young people these days...
Their parents don't teach them anything.
How pathetic.
Hold it!
This has nothing to do with my parents, does it?!
Are you sure?
If your parents had brought you up properly...
...I'm sure this would have been more of a challenge.
Cooking!
Laundry!
Cleaning!
And not just those...
Sewing!
Evening drinks!
Taking a child to the park for the first time!
Can you handle all of those?!
Next match!
That's the spirit!
Ooshige-san...
Isn't this interesting?
In that case, if you win this time around...
...I'll give you four points.
She's so calm...
Like there's no way she'll lose...
But if she wins...
...it'll be a comeback victory for Ooshige-san!
I'll definitely show you that I can win!
The final one is a Shopping Contest.
A shopping contest?!
Ingredients for sukiyaki!
Whoever gets them cheaper within thirty minutes wins!
That's fine!
I'll show you...!
Which means...
The final round is a Sukiyaki Contest!
Ah... I need some sort of bell...
Ah... just leave it!
We're going too!
U-Um!
Sale
Bargain
Excuse me.
Welcome!
Could I have some sukiyaki meat, please?
Sukiyaki... that would be beef, right?
Coming right up!
Ah... Mister.
Could you knock a little off the price for me?
Of course, for a beautiful lady like yourself...
Really?
Thanks, Mister!
Hold it!
You!
You skipped work to play pachinko yesterday, didn't you?!
H-How do you..?
Don't underestimate me.
Last week, you made up a lie
about an appointment...
...and went to the races instead!
Your wife's going to find out.
Ah... um...
How does thirty percent off sound?
How about half off?
P-Please, come again!
Can't get anything past you, huh... Tanaka-san...
Ah!
This is cheap!
dd       Yummy                     Box Lunches
Excuse me
Yes ma'am!
What's she doing at a fish store?
Who knows...
Fish
House
Um... Ooshige-san?
Hmm?
Oh... what's up, Mitsuki?
House
Fish
For sukiyaki... fish is...
What?!
Fish
House
You don't need them?!
Of course you don't need them...
What are they doing playing around for?
There's no way she's never had sukiyaki before...
No way...
Ah.
She's going for the milk now.
After her!
Looks like I've won this one, too.
Ah?
They're here, they're here...
Dr. Wakaouji...
But... do we have enough eggs?
It feels like a fifteen-pack would have been better.
No.
Eggs are high in cholesterol.
Just one for each person is enough.
Just what a doctor would say.
Not at all...
Wha... what is... this...
I understand.
It's mortifying, but I must accept it.
Sorry I took so long.
You...
Eh?
But...
...I made it within the time limit.
I've lost.
Eh?
I concede.
This match...
...goes to you.
Eh?!
Ah... what do you mean?!
You can't cook...
Can't do laundry either...
Can't clean or shop at all, either...
Ooshige-san!
But... the two of you...
...look so good together...
Well, have a happy life together!
We'll be neighbors now.
Let's get along.
So what was the point again...
...of everything that happened today..?
Somehow...
It all worked out, didn't it...
Yes.
Ooshige-san will be Mitsuki-chan's neighbor now.
Ooshige-san.
Eh?!
Ah! Yes?
Mitsuki-chan...
I'm counting on you to take care of her.
S-Sure...
Let's do our best, Mitsuki!
Okay!
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
That place you had to leave for a while...
Sukoshi hanareta basho
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
This is great!
They're finally going to release
a second single for her!
Ah.
A lot's happened, but...
...everything's all good now.
So, what kind of song is it?
She wants to cover one of her father's songs.
Is that so?
Hope it's another hit.
What are you saying?
With Meroko taking care of things...
With Love! Love! Love!
It'll be a huge hit! No doubt about it!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
My Father's Song
Look forward to it!