Y'know how the air's totally dry now, right?
So Yumiko brought this little humidifier thing,
and it's all, like, puffing away during class.
The newer models are powered by, uh, USJ?
Ever since that day,
that smile's been frozen in place.
Or was it USA? You know what I mean.
Anyway, I wonder if we could
get one of those for this room.
And so has our everyday routine.
Thoughts, Hikki?
All we do is fight the desire to run away.
Hey, Hikki!
I'm listening.
You mean USB?
Why do we need something
so American to power us?
USB, that's it!
These days, you can even charge your cellphone via USB.
Yo, what's the plan for Christmas?
I'll be busy preparing for the end-of-year event.
In order to avoid crying over spilled milk,
But it's Christmas!
you try harder than ever to act the same as ever.
It gets so hectic.
Christmas, huh?
Ebina won't be free,
but what about everyone else?
I'll be a bit busy, too.
H-Hayato.
You got plans?
Hikki.
You're staring too much.
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something real
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
I-I wasn't staring or anything.
Uh, you totally were.
It was kinda freaking me out.
Oh? And why were you looking at me?
Huh? W-Well...
E-Er, I could feel your stare!
It burned a hole through me. Gave me chills.
Those two are polar opposites, you know?
Anyway, did you need something?
Nothing, really.
You just caught my eye, is all.
Oh?
Deep down, it suddenly hit me.
Why was I looking at them?
Morning.
Morning, Saika.
Yo. Morning.
What's up?
It's unusual to see you two talking in class.
R-Really?
Is something wrong?
Not at all!
W-We were just talking about the club, I guess?
Oh, the club.
But really, I'm glad to hear it's back to normal.
Y-Yeah.
Oh, right.
Feel free to drop by again if you need help.
Actually, scratch that.
Feel free to drop by even if you don't need help.
You're always welcome.
Extra motivated!
Later.
Oh yeah, Hikki.
Let's go to the clubroom together, okay?
Later!
Later.
Why'd you ditch me?!
But I didn't.
I waited for you.
Yeah, but...
Huh? I guess that's fine?
Let's go.
By the way, how's lunch break been lately?
Oh, uh, same as before.
That so.
Hey...
Forget it.
That so.
Yo, 'sup, Yukinon!
He said it was, like, super unusual
to see Hikki and me talking in class.
How long will this keep up?
That does sound rather unusual.
How long can we keep this up?
It's not, right, Hikki?
If we reach a point where we can't do it anymore, what happens then?
I don't remember us talking all that often.
It wore me out, quite frankly.
It wore you out?!
I was probably looking at Hayama and gang because I felt they'd show me the answer.
Show me how to paper over the cracks on something that had fallen apart.
Come in.
Help! I'm in big trouble!
Big, big,
big troubl—
A Christmas event?
Yes.
So that's the new student council's first job.
We have to work with people from Kaihin High or something
to organize an event for senior citizens and nursery kids and stuff.
Who came up with that proposal?
They did!
Why would I do it?
Figures.
Anyway, the obvious choice was to turn them down, right?
I mean, I've got Christmas plans too.
It was the obvious choice, huh?
Talk about a selfish reason.
But Ms. Hiratsuka insisted we take part.
I knew she'd be involved.
So we gave it a shot, but it's not really working out.
That's how it usually goes with other schools.
Don't let it bother you.
But really, you should've talked to Shiromeguri before coming to us.
U-Uh, well...
How should I say this?
Oh, yeah.
She's got entrance exams! I really
shouldn't be distracting her, right?
Uh, well...
You just find her really hard to deal with, right?
You guys are my only hope!
Let's see.
I believe we have a grasp on your situation.
Shall we?
Sounds good! Let's do it!
It's been, like, ages since we got a request.
Nothing's been happening lately,
so just like old times...
we could give it a shot...
I think...
Yes.
I don't see why not.
Nah, I think it's a bad idea.
This is the student council's problem.
Besides, Isshiki shouldn't be relying on people first thing after being elected president.
Wh-What's your problem?
We're not handymen.
We only lend a hand, at most.
Anyway, this is your job.
Now shoo.
I only became president
because you insisted, you know.
You gotta fix this!
She's got me there.
It's only natural that I'd need to do right by Isshiki.
That being the case,
there's one other person I need to do right by.
Instead of the club helping out with this event,
how about I do it?
Huh?
That's fine with me.
If it's just you, I'd find it much easier to manip—
I'd be much more at ease.
Woman, it's too late to correct yourself.
Actually, what about Hayama?
Isn't this the perfect time to ask him for help and take it from there?
It's really hard work, so I didn't want to bother him with it.
But I'm fair game?
I guess I am.
Look at her, talking about
not wanting to be a bother.
I guess she actually is a
lovestruck maiden at heart.
How praiseworthy.
Besides, the "adorably clumsy" act only works with simple tasks.
You know, making silly mistakes and all that.
Asking for help with a ton of work would just make me come across as a pain.
Is that so?
Could this girl be any more devilish?
Give it back!
Give me back my praise!
Well, let's meet up at the front gate later.
I have to start today?
We don't have much time.
Okay, but change the meeting place.
It'd be embarrassing if my friends saw us leaving together and started gossiping.
Am I not getting through to her because of the generation gap?
Where's the "but you don't have any friends" retort? She took me seriously!
Whatever.
Do you know where the community center is?
Let's meet up there.
Got it. I'll head there once I'm ready.
I'm counting on you, cap'n!
Enough with the foxiness already.
What'd she say?
She whined a lot, but it looks like she came to terms with it.
Oh.
I thought it'd be nice to do something for a change, though.
Something else will come up eventually.
Perhaps it might be better not to get any requests at all—
for time to pass without any trouble.
Maybe.
If so, what have I—
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
What have we been doing all this time?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I had to get some shopping done.
Phew.
Nah, don't worry about it.
What's with that annoying expression?
Wasn't that phew an implied
"this stuff is heavy, so carry it for me"?
Oh, no, that was just me being me.
Wait, were you trying to hit on me?
Sorry, that nearly made my heart skip a beat,
but now that I think about it, it's really not happening.
Is that so?
How many times do I have to be rejected by her?
Th-Thank you.
Don't mention it. Just doing my job.
My, how reliable.
In that case,
I hope you keep doing your best!
Seminar Hall 1
Good evening!
I'm Tamanawa, Kaihin High's
student council president.
Nice to meet you.
H-Hello.
I have to say...
I'm pleased to be able to push the envelope with my fellow up-and-comer.
I expect the emerging synergy from our partnership, based on mutual respect,
will be the game changer
this event needs to succeed.
Laying it on thick, isn't he?
Got a moment, Iroha?
Sure.
Huh? Hikigaya?
Hey...
You're in the student council?
Nah.
We're in the same boat, then.
A friend asked me to come along...
Wait, are you alone?
Yeah, I usually am.
What? That's hilarious!
It is not.
Later.
Wow, you knew someone?
That sounds less like "you knew someone here,"
and more "you actually knew someone," so let's not go there.
Also, you've met her before.
Who is that, anyway?
Yeah, well, she's a classmate from junior high.
Oh?
We're starting.
This way.
Hey, I'd rather sit in the corner.
Christmas Event
Let's pick up where we left off
and start brainstorming.
First on the agenda is the event concept and any ideas on what it'd entail.
Considering what's expected of us high school influencers,
I think we need groundbreaking innovation that'd disrupt the established thinking.
That said, a win-win for both us and the community is a critically important core deliverable.
We need to strategically evaluate the logistical efficiency, too.
What the hell's going on?
Beats me.
Well, they're throwing out a bunch of ideas.
Guys, shouldn't we be focusing on something more important?
We need to wear logical thinking hats
while adopting a logical mindset.
Aren't those the same thing?
How many times are you gonna think logically?
Consider the customer POV and envision
the endeavor from an end-user standpoint.
Seriously, those are the exact same thing.
How many times are you gonna become a customer?
Then we need to examine the pros and cons of outsourcing.
The current bizmeth doesn't meld
with our roadmap moving forward.
What do we do?
We might end up having to reschedule.
Shouldn't we shoot for a larger buffer?
Right. We have to take a more holistic approach.
Did that give you a decent idea of what it's about?
Nah, I didn't understand a thing.
Well, I guess they are talking about some complicated stuff.
But going "wow" or "I'll have to do my best too" works great.
Then just reply to their texts, and you're all set.
You're gonna get stabbed some day.
But you give off a similar aura sometimes.
You seem to have smarts or, well, a high level of awareness.
Don't lump us together.
I'm not highly aware.
I'm highly self-aware.
Not sure I follow.
Anyway, I put together the stuff we need to do, so let's get to it.
Oho?
What is it?
Guess you're getting on well with them.
I guess, yeah.
Wait, weren't you the one who taught me
that an eager-to-learn younger girl gets extra cute points?
I don't remember teaching you that.
But, hey, it looks like you
don't even need me here.
The thing is...
Iroha, could I ask you to take care of this?
Also, this, this, and this.
O-Okay.
If you have any questions, just ask.
I'm always willing to explain.
There you have it.
Looks like it's up to us to
organize the minutes too.
Please.
The student council doesn't appear to be functioning well.
While I'm sure they're still
feeling one another out,
I think that's hindering any meaningful discussion among them.
President, will this do?
I-I'll check.
Also, about our work procedures...
Yes?
Nah. Never mind.
That's the vice president.
You've got it rough, huh?
Guess I'm not thought of very highly.
But that's how it always is in the beginning.
It'll get better eventually.
Heya!
Yo.
What's with the lame reaction?
I'm just sick of you acting all foxy.
Puhleez, I was clearly being myself there.
You know, you're acting pretty foxy yourself.
Hold up.
Seminar Hall 1
We have yet to visualize all the action items integral to this project,
so let's reinitialize the brainstorm session.
I'd like for us to take this chance
to really make a mark.
Preach it!
Something big, or like,
you know, flashy!
Maybe we did decide on something too minor.
We decided things? When?
The minutes don't mention anything but crap like "logical thinking".
I have no idea what we're actually doing.
Well, we haven't decided on anything specific yet.
I think we need to go more large-scale.
What do you say?
Uh...
I guess.
We don't have enough time or people for a larger event.
Non, non. You've got it all wrong.
In a brainstorming session, you don't reject ideas that others bring to the table.
If time and personnel constraints make it hard to aim for a larger scale,
then we move on to discuss how to deal with those constraints.
Jumping to conclusions is taboo.
Thus, we can't accept your opinion.
R-Right.
But he seems awfully willing to shoot me down.
Let's talk about how to make this happen.
How about bringing in more high schools from the area?
Oh, come on. Why are these high-awareness types so keen to socialize?
There's nothing to be gained by getting more high schools to participate.
Sounds good.
We could involve the entire local community.
However, straightforward opposition will be shot down.
There's an idea!
When in Rome, you gotta do as the Romans do.
Shooting from the hip here,
but I'm not sure the earlier proposal is sustainable.
A more streamlined mindshare between our two high schools
would help us leverage the most synergy and organic growth.
Don't you agree?
Indeed.
We'd better avoid high schools, then.
Colleges, maybe?
No good, huh?
Wait a minute.
That'd mean we'd give up the initiative.
In order to gain more eyeballs
and a clear consensus,
we need a partnership where we can
transparently crystallize a manifesto...
What on Earth are you talking about?
Uh, I'm not too sure myself.
True.
He actually got that?
How about nearby grade schools, then?
I believe the word was Gameducation.
If we can empower them to have fun while being productive,
we should be able to get
local grade schoolers on board.
It's a win-win.
Win-win, huh?
Yeah!
Preach it!
Preach what?
Assuming we can reach out and
touch base with the grade schools,
it'd make us very happy if we can mobilize you to herd the cats.
Well...
Can we?
Sure thing.
Yo!
Were you in the student council in junior high or something?
You seemed at home back there.
You'd be surprised.
Did you break up with your girlfriend?
I mean, just wondering if you're going after Isshiki.
How can I break up with a
girlfriend that never existed?
Really?
I thought you were going out
with one of them.
Who's "them"?
Y'know, the ones that showed up that day.
They're...
We're just in the same club.
You're in a club?
Which one?
Volunteers Club.
I have no idea what that's supposed to be!
Hilarious!
It is not.
What do you even do?
Funniest thing I've heard today.
Yeah, it certainly is quite
the incomprehensible club.
Volunteers club!
Never heard that one before!
But that doesn't make it funny.
Safely,
The Congress Dances, But Does Not Progress.
Seriously, it's no laughing matter.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
However, That Room Continues to Portray an Endless Everyday Scene.
We should prioritize our tasks and decide what's mission critical.
There's an idea!
Aren't those the same thing?
How many times are you gonna prioritize?
Don't you think the flexibility and malleable thinking of youngsters is what's required of us right now?
Preach it!
Those mean the same thing.
How soft are you gonna get?
Great.
Now we've prepared a scheme to pool everyone's resources and dedicate them to the event.
I can't wait for the next brainstorming session!
All we've done is prepare.