[heavy metal music playing]
WORTHY OPPONENT
[intense operatic music]
[narrator] Thor and Lü Bu,
two beings born and raised
in different times.
One from the realm of mortals,
the other a god.
Linked by one simple truth,
they both live the experience
of being the strongest,
slaughtering all opponents
with a single blow.
They've stepped foot onto
thousands of battlefields,
laying waste to tens of thousands
of their enemies.
But now, they clash with a foe,
who can withstand their attack.
Who shall be victorious?
[Heimdall] It's an even match!
Neither can overpower the other.
Who could have predicted
such a shocking turn of events?
- [crowd cheering]
- You can do it, Lü Bu!
Amazing. He's holding his own.
[Zeus] A mere human
matching Thor's opening attack?
Rather impressive indeed.
I'll give the mortal that much.
They may have false hope of victory, as
they've yet to witness Thor's true power.
[both grunting]
[crackling]
Ah, yes. That's it, Thor!
- [Brünnhilde gasping]
- What now?
[Heimdall] Whoa, look at that lightning!
He started this fight with his guard down.
But now he's wielding Mjölnir
in both hands!
What's this? Is he losing his balance
and falling backwards?
No! That's not it at all!
He's winding up for a devastating attack!
What kind of technique is that?
Is he nuts?
Hm. We'll see. Yes.
[Liu Bei] Indeed.
[Muninn] Thor's going to
wipe this mortal off the map!
I suppose he's bored of him already.
No, you've misjudged him.
I deduce that this is his way of showing
he accepts this human
as a worthy opponent.
[Muninn] Seriously?
[Huginn] He wouldn't even allow a human
to behold this move if he wasn't serious.
- Yes! The almighty hammer of Thor!
- [crackling increases]
[Brünnhilde] A long time ago, the gods
built up high walls around Asgard,
the land of the gods,
to defend it from repeated attacks
from Jötunheimr,
the land of the Jötnar.
[guard 1 yawning]
This is so tiresome.
What? You're on duty right now.
Captain, I didn't become a guardian angel
just to stand around.
I hate being on watch all day long.
[guard 2] He's right.
It's far too quiet around here.
[captain] You fools! If things are
at peace, we're doing our job right.
We're the guardian angel corps.
Pathetic. You've never even been
in a real fight. Don't get cocky.
Hm.
[guard 1] But still,
if there was a battle to be won,
now that would be a job worth doing.
[guard 2] Isn't that the truth.
- [birds squawking]
- [captain] Hm?
- [rumbling]
- Earthquake?
[gasping]
No. They're coming!
Enemy attack!
The Jötnar are rushing the wall!
[Brünnhilde] The Jötunn army launched
a sudden, unexpected attack.
They rushed Asgard
with a band of 66 Jötnar.
A number that the Asgardians
could never have expected.
[Jötnar growling]
[guardian angels screaming]
[man] The Jötnar are attacking!
Will the walls and gates
hold against them?
[woman] It's going to be all right.
The guardian angels are fighting for us.
I'm sure that...
That everything's going to be okay.
TYR, GOD OF WAR
Hold! Don't let them inside.
[guard 3] I... I've never seen so many.
How are we supposed to fight them off?
[guard 4] They just keep on coming!
Hold them back, now!
If they get through the wall, it's over!
[gasping]
[growling]
- [people screaming]
- [Tyr] They've breached the wall!
It's only a matter of time
before they're in the city streets.
We have to stop them, men.
Don't let them near the civilians.
Remember your training!
We'll maintain an upper hand
if we attack from the sky.
[roaring]
[crunching]
[gasping]
- [male voice] It's over for you, Jötnar!
- Huh?
They're here! The guardian angel knights!
[slashing]
[knight] Taste our steel!
You may have made it through the wall,
but you won't get past us!
[crashing]
[screaming]
[people screaming]
[Brünnhilde] In the past, the Jötnar had
only ever attacked the city one at a time,
giving all a false sense of security.
The gods could not conceive
working together with them.
And their complacency
brought suffering to their people.
In turn, their defenses
became weak and useless.
- And the Jötnar...
- No!
...found their perfect time to strike.
[moaning] Stop!
[swallowing]
[Brünnhilde] Asgard was
on the brink of total destruction.
[all growling]
[pounding]
[Forseti whimpering]
- They're right outside the castle.
- [pounding continues]
[crying] No!
It's over.
This is the end. We're finished!
[sobbing]
Huh?
Hey, you, what are you doing?
We need to hide.
Wait.
Hold on. Are you crazy?
[gasping] No! You've doomed us all!
[roaring]
[crunching]
[splashing]
[bones crunching]
[Brünnhilde] One after another,
the knights all fell
to the jaws of the enemy.
But one warrior was unfazed.
[steaming]
[crackling]
Thor single-handedly annihilated
all 66 of the Jötnar!
[Thor] I'm so bored.
[Brünnhilde] The story of Thor's victory
was passed down generation to generation.
And to honor his actions,
the gods gave his attack a special name.
- What the...?
- What is that?
[whimpering]
Hm. Seems he's starting to get serious.
Finally.
A shame it's already over.
End it, Thor.
[narrator] The thunder mallet
of the god of combat,
Thor's Hammer!
THE THUNDER MALLET OF THE GOD OF COMBAT
[screaming]
[straining]
Oh!
Oh well. I guess
that's the end of that, huh?
[yawning]
Yes, it's Thor's Hammer!
You're the best, Thor!
[coughing] I got some sand in my mouth.
Whoa!
Hm.
This is the power of the gods.
There's no way that we can win.
Humans defeating gods...
We were totally delusional if we believed
there was any way
that could ever really happen.
[Brünnhilde] Göll, get up.
Brünnhilde, I can't.
It's hopeless.
I can't stand to watch this.
You must not turn away.
But why though?
You need to observe this closely.
Huh?
You must bear witness to this moment,
as history changes.
- [crunching]
- Hm?
Huh?
Hmm.
[crashing]
[whooshing]
Ah, I gotta admit, I'm impressed.
Wait, what?
Yeah, atta boy!
Just as expected.
Hm?
- All right!
- Ah!
- There's no way.
- My.
[laughing hysterically]
[Heimdall]
Blood is spilling from Thor's chest.
The human, Lü Bu,
has managed to injure a god!
[Chen Gong] Now do you all understand
the power of my liege?
Lü Bu was the strongest human
who ever lived!
His blade can pierce
even the skin of a god.
Hmm.
- [gods murmuring]
- How? Was Thor really injured by a mortal?
No way. No way!
[murmuring continues]
[narrator] It was in that moment,
that the strongest god, Thor,
and the strongest man, Lü Bu,
found themselves thinking alike.
"Had they walked the earth
at the same time,
and in the same place..."
Hmm.
You bastard.
What a waste it is that you
were born with the affliction of humanity.
[chuckles]
[narrator] "...they would have
considered each other comrades."
Ha!
[Brünnhilde] According to the official
history of the Three Kingdoms...
MONGOLIAN STEPPES
...Lü Bu was said to have come from
Wuyuan Commandery in Jiuyuan,
now a part of Inner Mongolia.
However, no one knows for sure
if this is even true.
But there is one thing that is certain.
Ever since he was a small child,
Lü Bu was on a journey
to become the strongest man alive.
He traveled across
the vast Eurasian continent
in search of any opponent
who could challenge his strength.
[roaring]
[bones crunching]
He cut down anyone and anything
who stood in the way of his goal.
As his tireless quest continued,
his name became commonplace
on the lips of everyone across China
for his fearsome abilities.
[all yelling]
In the end, no one dared
to stand in Lü Bu's way,
and instead,
an army grew, following at his back.
And then, at the end of his journey
of over 30 years,
Lü Bu finally realized the truth.
[screaming]
[Lü Bu] There's no one left in the world
who can defeat me now!
THERE'S NO ONE LEFT IN THE WORLD
WHO CAN DEFEAT ME NOW!
CAO CAO
No! My liege!
Bestow unto me an army.
And if you do then I shall deliver to you
the world and much more!
[Brünnhilde] They say that Lü Bu begged
for his life to escape execution.
However, is that the truth
behind his words?
No.
No!
[yawning]
The real reason that tears
stung his eyes that day...
Uh...
[Brünnhilde] He was bored.
[moaning]
The despair he felt at being
the strongest man in the world,
that not even an army
could hope to challenge,
was immeasurable.
[Lü Bu] Hey, hurry up and end it.
I'm so bored,
I could perish all on my own.
[crowd cheering]
[Lü Bu] I found you at last!
An opponent who I can have a battle with
using my entire body and soul!
I've never seen this before.
His expression.
Facing off against a god.
My liege, Lü Bu, looks...
happier than ever!
Uh, well now. How unusual.
- Hmm.
- Lord Zeus, what's wrong?
Uh...
[shouting] I said, is there something
that's troubling you, Lord Zeus?
No. But if I think about it,
this should be impossible.
Are you wondering how a human like him,
can hold his own in a fight against a god?
Is that what it is?
Quit your yelling!
I'm not deaf yet, Hermes, there's
no need to shout in my ear like that,
you blithering idiot!
[sighing] Anyway, if you must know,
there is something.
Human weapons can't withstand Mjölnir.
They should be shattered to pieces
merely by coming into contact with it.
What we're seeing here is impossible.
There's not a single armament
on the mortal plane
that can do what this one is doing.
Hmm...
There's no way.
Unless...
[chuckling]
Ah! Is that how you're playing it?
Well done, Valkyrie.
I couldn't have rigged it better myself.
[whimpering]
Uh, hey, Zeus is looking over at us
with a creepy smile on his face.
Yes. It seems he's finally noticed.
[narrator] However, before Ragnarok began...
[Göll] Lü Bu is first up for the humans?
You mean, the Lü Bu?
[Brünnhilde] Correct.
But, Brünnhilde,
that guy is way too dangerous.
He's the one who said that he was bored
after taking the lives
of countless others!
Listen, I know he's the strongest warrior
in the Three Kingdoms,
but is there even any possibility
he could defeat a god one-on-one?
Oh no. No, there isn't.
Ah! There isn't? Then why?
The source of each god's strength
is in their weapons.
Weapons which are all forged in heaven
to give them their absolute power.
Compared to what the gods produce,
mortal weapons are mere toys.
[whining]
The man who wields them matters not.
Göll, it's not possible for any human.
Their strength makes no difference.
There's no hope.
[crying] Why are we even trying?
[laughing] Your reaction's about right.
Anyone would assume
the mortals are doomed.
[sobbing]
But what if the humans
had a weapon of the gods.
[crying stops] Huh?
And, what if, blinded
by our choice of champion,
they simply failed to notice?
Does that mean...
Uh, isn't this...
[tinkling]
Eldest sister, did you summon us?
We 11 Valkyries have answered your call,
and by your wishes have assembled here.
What is it you need from us?
[Göll] Oh, our sisters.
This is the first time all 13 of us have
been gathered in one location, isn't it?
Brünnhilde, may I ask
what it is you're planning?
I don't understand.
How can the other Valkyries help?
Hm.
[clanging]
Huh?
All right, then. It's party time!
[Japanese pop ballad playing]