TLC
Tobikage
Timer
Floris257
Editor
Chippo
K-time
Floris257
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Logo AFX : KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter
Floris257
Kaitou[Kid]
QC
Robo731   Floris257
Encoder
Floris257
Changing World
Morning, Manabe-kun!
Mornin'.
Hey, Manabe!
'Sup?
This new ramen place just opened in front of the station.
I wanna go check it out, but...
Hey!
Uh, never mind..
I just can't forgive a place that markets
something made with margarine as miso butter ramen.
What's up with that?!
Yeah, that's just wrong!
Manabe's totally back to his old self.
That's a relief, right, Moritani?
Yeah...
Hey, do you think this could be your chance?
Yeah! No one is in your way now!
A week has passed since Kotoura disappeared.
Not a single thing in my life has changed.
It's almost as if there was never a girl named Haruka Kotoura here in the first place.
Kotoura Haruka
Dialing...
Talking...
The number you have dialed is not in service.
It must be nice to be you, Manabe-kun.
Aw, so close, yet so far.
President, you might as well take a step closer.
You're totally spineless now.
Look, just come to the club room.
I don't need to participate in the club anymore, do I?
I was just a bonus that came with Kotoura, anyway.
Shut up and come with me!
Hey! Wh-Whoa... That hurts!
What about the stairs?!
Like I care?!
I thought you were released from the hospital?
Oh, this is all the president's doing.
Straighten up!
Honestly, I misjudged you.
I can't believe you'd give up on Kotoura-chan so easily.
What exactly am I supposed to do about it?!
Everything has been taken from her apartment, and I can't reach her cell.
For some reason, even the teachers don't know where she moved or what school she transferred to.
After everything that's happened, I just don't feel like trying anymore.
Seriously, I've got nothing left.
Makes you laugh, doesn't it?
I don't even have a single picture of us together.
Is there really nothing left?
I don't think everything that gets left behind is visible.
What do you mean?
Oh, for crying out loud!
Try asking your own heart that question!
Manabe-kun!
Well?
I'm surprised.
You guys are right.
She appeared out of nowhere,
then strung me along for all that time.
And in the end, she left something unbelievable behind.
What would that be?
It's...
My burning rage!
How dare that little brat just disappear on me?!
Even if I have to uproot every blade of grass, I'll find her,
and give her a spanking!
You really are a funny guy.
Huh?
Well said, Manabe-kun!
I've been waiting for you to say that!
Together as the ESP society, we're all going to retrieve Kotoura-chan!
Yes!
Wait, retrieve her?
Yeah.
We've already ascertained the location where she's likely to be hiding.
What?!
What? I just took a peek at the data from some train station security cameras.
I've pretty much pinpointed Kotoura-kun's escape route.
Um, isn't that a crime...?
Uh, never mind. It's nothing.
On that note, the ESP Society's activity this weekend will be field work!
Whew... That was a long trip.
The sun has almost set.
There's nothing here at all.
Kotoura is here?
Yes.
There's no doubt that this was the last station she arrived at.
All that's left is...
I-It's pretty cold for May...
I've been wanting to ask...
Why are you dressed so lightly?
Well, when we left, my heart was still burning with passion...
Forget this idiot.
So what do we do now?
We collect information and use it to find Kotoura's location.
Fortunately, this isn't a big town.
I think we'll hear of a few sightings.
Okay! Then, we'll rest for the night and start looking for information tomorrow.
Right. Let's establish a base first.
So, where are we staying?
Where are we staying?
Why didn't you make reservations?!
I should be asking you the same thing!
I swear, Muroto-kun, you're the vice president, but you always screw up at the worst times!
Well, you're the president! You should be on top of things!
Hey, chill out, you guys...
You kids don't have anywhere to stay tonight?
Man, we're saved!
Who knew there'd be a temple nearby that would let us crash for the night?
You said it.
Next time, Muroto-kun, do your job!
Yeah, yeah.
Hello, welcome.
The station attendant told me about you.
I can't offer much, but please, come in.
We appreciate it!
Finally, a break!
We spent all day swaying back and forth on that train.
You're both showing such bad manners by lazing about like that.
Oh, no, please make yourselves at home.
More importantly, what did you come here for?
We're sort of on a club field trip.
Oh? What kind of club?
A secret society to prove the existence of psychic powers and protect those who have them,
the ESP Research Society!
E... ESP, you say?
I just love that stuff!
Oh, so you understand?
How would you like to discuss the topic till sunrise?
Count me in!
Ah-ha! I won't let you sleep tonight!
There's a reason why I took an interest in strange phenomena.
About ten years ago, I met a certain little girl.
Something evil has possessed my daughter!
Please, do something to exorcise it!
Oh...
Please, come in.
Wow, check this out!
Are all of these psychic-related texts?
That girl's strange power caused her great pain.
I wanted to do something for her,
and once I started hunting for books...
A girl with a power that caused her pain...
That sounds like...
What's wrong, President?!
Look at that!
At what?
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
It's all my fault. I'm sorry.
Haruka-chan, it's not your fault.
None of this is your fault.
Head Priest... How can I make my parents
and friends stay with me?
How can I make them smile at me?
I couldn't do anything for her.
I see... So you are her...
Why has she been carrying all of that by herself?!
You...
Please, tell me where Kotoura is!
I promised that I'd stay by her side!
That, no matter what happened, I wouldn't leave her!
And this time, I'm keeping that promise!
Her family's home is on the other side of the mountain.
I'll show you the way tomorrow.
Thank you very much!
Haruka-chan, it looks like you found some good friends.
You won't get away this time, Kotoura!
We'll grab her from behind and take her down!
I've got the capture net ready.
Okay, let's practice a bit before we use the baths!
Good friends... right?
Once you catch her, I'll tie her up!
Grandfather...
Um... Have you found my next place of admission yet?
Your new school?
You don't have to force yourself to go, you know.
No, I should at least go to school.
I'm causing you enough trouble...
Don't worry. I'm looking.
Sorry to make you do so much for me.
Not only school,
but you take care of all my rent and living expenses, as well.
I...
Never mind that.
Just come sit on your grandpa's lap every now and then.
Welcome, Granddaughter!
Um, I'm a high schooler now.
I'm so quick to forget things these days...
Place of admission? Oh...
Maybe some brief contact with my granddaughter would help jog my memory.
Fine.
Now, this brings back memories.
You really have grown up.
Grandfather...
Oh, Grandfather!
A granddaughter's butt and thighs are the best!
Living to such an old age has paid off!
What was that cackle?
As I believe you're aware, I can hear you.
You're just like Manabe-kun...
What?!
There's another lucky yet disgraceful man
who gets you to do such wanton things, besides me?!
Come on, Grandfather, just calm down...
My granddaughter's butt and thighs belong to me!
No matter what you say, they're mine! All mine!
Actually, they're mine, you pervert.
Right.
I guess there is a house here.
I can't even see any buildings from here.
Just how big is this property?
I guess she really is rich...
I bet we'll find a Kotoura-chan or two lurking around here.
Don't talk about her like she's a cockroach!
Her grandfather says he'll meet with you.
But he seems to already know you somehow, Manabe-kun.
He said, "Manabe's here?!"
Huh?
So, Zenzou-san, these are the friends of Haruka-chan I told you about last night.
Yeah. Nice of you to come.
Is he mad at us?
You should apologize quickly, Manabe-kun.
I have to do it?!
So you're Manabe-kun?
Y-Yes, I am...
I'll cut right to the chase.
What sort of sexual play have you indulged in with my granddaughter?
A bit of the sort where I imagine her in perverted situations and embarrass her.
Oh, is that all?
You're still quite the amateur, aint'cha, boy?
Just this morning, I enjoyed direct contact with her butt and thighs!
Well, I think there's more sexual appeal in a face flushed with shame than in physical actions like that!
Are you saying you don't want to touch those tiny breasts that Haruka may or may not even have?!
You bet I do!
Grandfather, I heard the head priest was... here...
Kotoura!
Get her!
Roger!
Wait!
Interesting kids, they are.
They seem to be enjoying themselves.
Why? Why are they all here?
Wait!
I'm scared! I'm so scared!
Damn, we lost her!
It's no use. This house is too big.
We'll have to split up to find her.
Damn it! Why are you running away?!
Sorry. I abandoned everything and ran away...
Now I'm too embarrassed to even face you.
But I'm glad. He looks well.
His injuries have healed.
I'd like to talk to him face to face.
But I'm sure he'll just get mad.
I'm sorry.
Kotoura, I'm sorry.
Why? It was my fault.
I couldn't... I couldn't protect you.
That's not true!
You did so much to protect me.
I promised that I'd be by your side.
That I'd never abandon you.
No.
That's not why!
I just want to be with you.
I don't want us to be apart!
I want to see you, Kotoura.
I finally found you.
Let's go home. Let's be together...
Let's...
Kotoura!
Manabe-kun... Manabe-kun...
I want to see you. I want to see you.
I want to see you!
Mana—
Crap. Now I'm getting mad again.
I guess I'll have to give her a spanking after all.
A spanking... A spanking... A spanking!
It should be obvious, after causing me so much worry.
But I'll be gentle.
Once I'm finished, I'll caress your swollen behind.
Kotoura!
Gotcha!
Let me go!
No!
Now, how about you explain yourself?
Why did you just disappear like that?
Because... it's my fault you were hospitalized.
I thought if I left, you could go back to your everyday life.
Oh? Hmm. I see.
Are you stupid?!
It's your fault I was attacked?
What a load of bull!
Besides, having you around already is a part of my everyday life!
In other words, you're saying you'd die for her?
I didn't say that!
But... Kotoura said something so stupid, I just...
I'm sorry. Please don't spank me.
So you did hear me!
And after I tried to fool you by being serious!
Of course, that was Haruka's fault.
Grandfather...
Forgive her, would you?
She hasn't had friends in a long time,
so she just doesn't know how to behave around them.
That's why she ran from you.
Still, it appears I can begin the preparations to re-enroll you in your old school.
I'm not going back! I won't!
I apologize for leaving without saying anything.
But I don't want anyone else to get hurt because of me...
So just leave me alone.
Go, Manabe-kun.
Just show her those tragic heroine acts
don't work on idiots.
Right!
Wait!
Let go!
No way.
If I leave you alone, you'll keep everything to yourself
and run off to hide again.
What choice do I have?
If something like this happens again, I...
What are you two doing?
Moritani-san?
What are you doing here, Manabe?
That's what I should be asking you!
Why are you here?!
I just... wanted to apologize.
I had a detective track you down.
Moritani-san...
I'm sorry.
My stupid jealousy caused a lot of trouble for you.
It even led to Manabe getting attacked.
What?!
Huh? You still didn't know?
That was your fault?!
Why didn't you tell him?
You really are full of surprises.
Why would you get someone to attack your classmate?
Are you into that stuff? Are you a pervert?
Oh, shut up! That's why I'm here to apologize!
You haven't apologized!
Why did you apologize to Kotoura and then treat me like that?!
Because of the way you treat me every day!
Moritani-san apologized, over and over.
Wh—
She said she couldn't be honest because she didn't know what to say.
Please don't talk about that!
It's like she said.
How do I apologize after what I did?
After she disappeared, you weren't yourself...
So I thought, if I brought her back, I could apologize to you.
But you're already here, and now I... I...
Oh, forget it. You're making me feel sick.
It's okay... It's okay!
He's so mean, right?
He's terrible. The worst man alive.
Wait, I'm the bad guy now?
You don't have to worry, Moritani-san. Okay?
Aren't I the victim here?
Are you okay?
Sent Away
Yeah.
It's funny. I came to apologize,
so why am I the one crying?
Pathetic, isn't it?
So... while I'm embarrassing myself, let me say this.
Thanks to you, I've realized a lot of things,
and I think I can change now.
Thanks, Kotoura-san.
Why did she come here?
She thanked me...
Then she said she'd see me at school.
Kotoura!
I want... to go back.
I want to go back with you... and everyone.
Yeah! We're going back!
H-Hey... Manabe-kun!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
I guess I was still just a child.
I thought I could read
people's minds and know everything about them.
But people can change.
Something so simple never even occurred to me.
I had turned my back not only on everyone, but myself as well.
I was an arrogant, selfish coward.
But I believe I can change, little by little.
Both myself, and the world I live in.
Because I'm not alone anymore...
A lot happened, but it looks like everything's back to normal.
That's not true.
Things have changed...
just a little.
Ungh!
Ah!
Hi-yah!
Eep!
Smack!
Eek!
Smack, smack!
No!
Oh, no! Seeing Kotoura trembling with fear at being spanked makes my heart race!
You special classification pervert!
Episode 5
School Paradise?