The treacherous sunset wipes away those annoying sweat drops.
As if it wanted to tear it apart,
the machine roars as if it's singing a song.
Selty
Sturluson
The quiet fairy is over here.
Yagiri
Seiji
Atonement is a piece of a broken love.
Yagiri
Namie
The morning sun rises, yeah!
Heiwajima Shizuo
Over the valley of buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't be meaningless.
Erika
Karisawa
The morning sun rises, yeah!
Yumasaki
Walker
Kyohei
Kadota
Coming out of the darkness!
As long as you feel it now,
Togusa
Saburo
you'll see that dream isn't meaningless.
There's surely something only we can see.
Mikado
Ryuugamine
Something that no one will snatch away from us.
Masaomi
Kida
The fact that this aim isn't meaningless!
Anri
Sonohara
What's this about an "urban legend"?!
The black motorcycle!
The headless rider!
The man on the black bike doesn't have a head.
He's headless, yet he still moves around.
Even though the job doesn't seem like it'll be too difficult... you should still be careful.
I didn't hear that you had become a hero of justice.
Because the world isn't
as terrible as you think.
Wh-what the fuck is that?
What the fuck  are you?!
The sun rises, yeah!
Brezhnev
Simon
Over the horizon, oh!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
that light won't be meaningless.
The headless rider? I've heard of it!
My friend said she saw it!
Well, I'm not really interested in that.
I managed to catch a picture of it.
Look!
The headless rider?
It's this guy, this guy!
You girls have heard of it before, right?
I think I probably saw it around the Sunshine building.
Seriously?
I'm not entirely sure, but since everyone was making such a huge scene about it, that just had to be it.
Everyone's so talkative.
I heard that the bike was spotted again.
Wow, looks like everyone's on pretty early this evening.
Good evening.
Evening.
Evening good~~
But, I wonder if the part about the rider being headless is true.
Good evening.
Evening
Evening good~~
I'm sure it's just an ugly rumor.
But, I heard that it's real, too!
Huh...?
It's just not possible not to have a head.
If it wasn't human...
then it would be possible, right?
I heard that people who come in contact with it become silent.
Sorry. I don't really know about that.
How about you?
What's your take on the legendary headless rider?
Scary? Cool?
Maybe it might be a good person?
As I thought...
you really don't know how you should react to it?
Today, I'll tell you what I know about the headless rider.
The story will be long and tedious, but I still want you to listen attentively.
Loneliness
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Kishitani Shinra, twenty four years old.
I work as an unlicensed doctor in this city.
In layman's terms that means that I work with various shady organizations.
I treat people that were injured from illegal weapons,
and whenever those people need their faces changed I perform cosmetic surgery.
I may not look it, but I am very talented at what I do. There are a lot of people who rely on me.
Now, to get straight to the point...
I'm home!
Oh, yeah...
I belong to the headless rider,
Selty Sturluson, we're living together.
I'm back, Selty.
Welcome
back
My job this time was simple.
What about you?
Don't peek.
Sorry, sorry.
I wasn't trying to be dirty or anything like that.
It's seems like something irritated you.
Maybe you need a calcium inoculation?
Are you telling me to eat an eggshell or something?
Hey, that sounds pretty good, doesn't it?
But you know,
I'm clueless when it comes to nutrition.
I have no idea how much calcium there is in an eggshell,
or how well the body handles the absorption of it.
Then as I think a little more on it, one can also wonder what calcium can actually do for you,
since we don't even know the location of your brain.
Be quiet!
Hey, Selty...
I know I've heard everything, but..
How does the world appear to you, as someone without eyes?
I can't really explain something that I don't fully comprehend myself.
Although she doesn't have a head,
she can see, hear, and also possesses a sense of smell.
Although, just because she doesn't have a head doesn't mean she can see in all directions.
She just possesses a slightly broader field of vision than the average person, or so it seems.
This is just a passing thought of mine,
but that shadowy mysterious Sci-Fi-like substance that's constantly released from your body...
Is it possible that those particles take the place of light
and gives you information about your surroundings due to the refraction and absorption?
Of course, objects that are too far away will be indistinct.
Not interested.
I can see and I can hear, I'm fine with just that.
Selty, you're always like this.
The difference between the way how you perceive the world and the way how I perceive the world...
is what I would like to know.
We're not just simply talking about vision in and of itself.
I'm also talking about our sense of values.
Not your sense of values as a human,
but the way that the one and only fairy that manifested itself in this city values the world...
The way how the Dullahan sees the world.
What's the matter?
If it's okay with you, would you please tell me what happened today?
Orihara said that your job today wasn't particularly difficult.
The job itself was finished quickly without any issues.
And?
Once again you've shown your prowess as a deliverer.
I can do what I have to do because you're here, and vice versa.
I don't see where the "vice versa" part fits into this.
Oh, come on, that's not very nice.
I'll be counting on you again from now on.
I want the two of us to get along.
From here on in...
Is it just my imagination or is there something ominous about you?
There's no doubt that it's just your imagination.
By the way, have you ever heard of a Dullahan?
It's a headless fairy in Ireland.
An old street artist who recently came to Yoyogi Park recently claims to have witnessed one.
I also heard that he was making a big scene saying "There's no head! There's no head!"
Maybe he's talking about the head of this "Dullahan."
Is he still around?
I don't really know.
I knew it was you.
Selty Sturluson isn't human.
She's actually a Dullahan, a fairy, famous in Celtic folklore.
Do you know of a street artist around here?
Oh, that person is no longer here.
Hey! Didn't that person say he was going to Yokohama?
Huh?
A Dullahan carries their severed head under their arm,
while riding the coach-a-bower which is a two-wheeled coach pulled by a headless horse.
They visit the homes of people who are close to their deaths.
If your not careful when you open the door...
you'll be greeted with a tub full of blood.
You can't really relate her appearance to such an ominous and deadly legend,
just because she doesn't have a head.
Why she came to Japan, to Tokyo, and to Ikebukuro,
and why she's so obsessed about her head...
is what I'll tell you about.
This story takes place twenty years ago.
When she suddenly woke up in the mountains,
she came to the realization that her head was missing.
At that moment she also realized that many of her memories were lost.
She lost her memories of who she was and what she did,
and she also realized that her memories only go back to a certain extent.
However, she knew that she was a Dullahan,
that her name was Selty Sturluson,
and she also knew how to use her powers.
And what surprised her first...
I must have never used my head to think in the first place...
Just as she said.
At that time she also realized that for some reason she can feel the presence of her head somewhere.
After thinking about it for a while, she came up with one explanation.
Her thoughts were originally shared between her body and her mind,
and the memories that she lost must have remained in her head.
And so she decided...
to recover her head, that contains the truth behind the meaning of her existence.
That in itself is what gave her existence meaning.
She thought that perhaps her head separated itself from her body of its own free will.
Even if that was the case, there wouldn't be any way to know for sure until she found her head.
He wasn't in Yokohama any longer.
After that, I went to Tama, then to Chiba...
I kept missing him no matter where I went.
You could have just waited until tomorrow.
I was desperate.
My head could have been right there.
I wanted to get it back, no matter what the cost.
As soon as possible.
I don't want to continue living with such a vague memory.
She made it to this location by following her head's presence in the area.
That was when she found out that her head was on its way to a foreign land.
The ship was on it's way to Japan.
She decided to stow away to go after her head, but first she had to figure out what to do with her horse.
Her horse is a type of a familiar used by Dullahans, it's a spirit that possesses a horse's corpse.
She could have ditched it if she needed to,
but then, where would it go from there?
The answer to that was probably also within her head.
When she thought about that she knew she couldn't just leave the horse behind.
That was the time...
she...
found it.
Ultimately, I wasn't able to find my head.
But...
Oh, I know that street artist.
He's been in South Ikebukuro Park since the day before yesterday?
Yup, that's it.
Want me to tag along?
Won't it be inconvenient trying
communicate with your phone?
Right?
Well, here it is.
Wow, this is amazing!
This makes you look prettier than you actually are.
Hold on!
I'd expect nothing less from you old man!
Oh, no.
Even now, I still can't quite draw the way I would like to.
Thank you very much!
You're very welcome.
Let's go.
Come again!
Okay!
Sorry, it's getting kind of dark.
That's it for today.
Is it true that you really witnessed a Dullahan?
Yes, I really did.
I saw in the Irish mountains when I was young. I witnessed her with these eyes.
What did you mean by, "I lost her head"?
"Lost her head"?
That's not it.
She didn't have a head.
I can't really picture her head to draw it.
Here.
The Dullahan was a woman. A very lovely looking one, at that.
She passed by a mountain trail on a misty night.
She ran past me at an incredible speed.
Her appearance was quite frightening, but beautiful at the same time.
I had a feeling she wasn't from this world.
When I went back to the inn and asked about it, someone told me that there was no doubt that I witnessed a Dullahan.
It seemed like she resided there for a very long time.
Why isn't the Dullahan in your drawing carrying a head?
I can't draw it.
The more I add to it, the more different it feels.
I remember that day so clearly, but I just can't fully picture that woman.
What was the color of her hair? Her eyes?
What was her face like?
If I were able to describe those features verbally, I wouldn't have attempted to draw her.
Come to think of it, recently a strange man came to see me.
He kept going on and on about how the drawing is perfect the way it is.
He said that it was alright that she didn't have a head.
He certainly was a strange one.
Why are you so obsessed with her?
That was the best experience of my life.
That night was my life.
I want to retrieve that moment. The memories from that night.
Old man, thanks.
I see.
You don't feel as if you've met that old man before, right?
Nope.
So that Dullahan may or may not be you.
He probably was mistaken.
That was me. I'm sure of it
I see...
I wonder where I was going?
What was I thinking? What were my intentions?
Do you really need to worry about it that much?
Huh?
You're definitely mysterious, just like a character from a novel.
But even with that, you've still got quite a ways to go until you reach your goal.
What do you mean by that?
To put it bluntly, just give up.
Maybe what that man said was true.
Maybe it's alright for you not to have a head.
Stop searching for your head and let's go somewhere together.
Anywhere is fine.
If you want to, I'll take you back to your homeland, no matter what the cost.
I'll go there, too.
And we can be together forever-
I don't dislike you, but being like this is already enough for me.
Don't say that...
It's enough!
Then could you at least try to act a bit more like a girl?
That's enough!
Is it as I suspected? Is there a difference between what we think is important?
Getting back on track, I'll tell you the rest of the story.
Her story after she got aboard the ship...
No, our story.
She was able to talk to one of the
crewman into letting her stow away,
but then she realized how much she stood out.
Now that I've known her for this long, it doesn't really matter to me anymore...
but when I first witnessed it I was shocked.
I was four at the time.
I was on my way back to Japan with my father.
Daddy! Daddy! There's a strange woman in the hold!
My father, Shingen, was completely out of the ordinary.
Hurry!
Come on, Daddy!
Wouldn't a parent's normal reaction to just laugh about it?
However, my father was different.
It was probably just his nature as a doctor, but he was suddenly interested in what I said.
Madam.
Pardon my asking, but is it true that you don't have a head?
My father said to her,
"If you let me perform an autopsy on you just once, I'll provide you with a place to stay."
She agreed to it.
Although it seemed like she had her own agenda, I'm sure she couldn't have been comfortable with the whole thing.
She doesn't remember too much about this ever happening.
The anesthetic for humans didn't work very well,
so I'm sure it was a huge shock for her psychologically.
It seems as though she has a sense of pain, but it's far less than that of a human.
She doesn't have a heart.
None of her organs are carrying out their functions; they're just sitting there doing nothing.
She has veins, but there isn't any blood flow.
She just has flesh.
She's almost like a living anatomy dummy.
However, take a look at this.
How is someone actually supposed to kill her?
He's a horrible father, isn't he?
Telling a four year old to dissect a woman.
Although, as a result of his upbringing, I was able to learn the skills it takes to become a doctor...
I don't really know what to say about it.
What's wrong?
Ever since I saw her, I was attracted to her.
Those feelings haven't changed at all during the twenty years we've spent together.
And she's been searching for her head as she works as a deliverer.
I wonder what she'll do once she recovers her head.
What's going to happen to her?
Are all of her thoughts coming from her head that's no longer there?
Or maybe...
What are you filming?
Well, how do I explain this...?
I wanted to talk a little bit about our sweet daily life for future generations.
Do what you want, just try to keep it down.
I can't sleep.
Sorry about that, Selty.
Well, I guess this story...
will have to be continued another time.
That's perfect, don't you think?!
What part of this is perfect?
Don't you know that Dullahans are supposed to be carrying their heads under their arms?
Maybe it's alright that she doesn't have a head.
There's nothing alright  about it.
The only reason you can say that is because you haven't witnessed the real thing.
She was absolutely stunning.
She is, isn't she?
But... I still think she looks fine without a head.
She looks more charming that way.
That's why your drawing is perfect the way it is.
So you don't need to keep worrying about it.
It's fine if you can't draw it.
She can stay like that forever...
Well, I'll still keep trying to draw it.
This is fine the way it is!
You know, you really are a strange man, right?
I don't think so.
I'm here
I'm right here.
Call me
I'm right by your side.
Trust me
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My dear
This invisible thread,
Trust me
exists because of our warm bond,
I feel so much warmth coming from it.
I hear the voice of your wonderful heart perfectly.
We're no longer kids, but love is still right here.
It's okay to try to cry. It's okay to try to depend on me.
It was then that I decided to take away your pain.
I'm here
Wherever you may be.
Call me
We'll become one.
Trust me
These feelings for you won't change.
My dear
Just put down
Trust me
those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
I'm here
I'm right here.
Call me
I'm right by your side.
Trust me
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My dear
This invisible thread,
Trust me
exists because of our bond,
I feel so much warmth coming from it.
This is a work of fiction.
Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Durarara!!
Next Time
Selling Dog Meat
as Lamb
Do you wanna know about my ~love love get you~ and heartbreaking life?
Then show me, the shy and cool Masaomi Kida, the channel of your heart!
Next time: Selling Dog Meat as Lamb.
Don't miss the chance that only comes around once every three hundred years!