I've finally found her.
If I can find out what she did during the summer festival—
No, what she's going to do!
If I learn that, I can stop her.
That form belongs to the person Hiruko first copied.
"Haine."
She prefers to be called by that name.
She is the God of Hitogashima, Hiruko no Mikoto.
The mother of Shadows.
This... This little girl is a god?
Lately, she's been too weak to walk.
She was in need of a replacement body.
How many times have we met so far,
Ajiro Shinpei?
You were alive?
It was you?
Ushio's killer.
Mio's killer.
This is the monster that swallowed the entire island.
That thing is the god of this island?
The whole time.
The whole damn time!
Y'were right in front of my eyes the whole damn time!
Shinpei, get back!
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Haine, ya mustn't!
Bloody Night
His voice is so loud.
It echoes painfully in my head.
I just might kill him at any moment.
I like to eat in silence.
Do not speak again.
Tokiko.
Negoro?
She works as a nurse for us.
On average, four people die on Hitogashima every year.
From sickness, accidents, and such.
Ya see where I'm going with this?
Our clinic has been feeding her the dead.
Our father.
Our grandfather and great grandfather as well.
All the way back as long as our family has existed.
What are those caskets for?
Yer not gonna feed that little girl humans, are ya?!
That's what I was waiting for!
Another feast today!
There will be even more tomorrow.
Remember how I said ya weren't capable of murder, Shinpei?
I, however, am prepared to be killed by ya.
W-Wait a sec, Toki.
Ya can't mean...
Come closer and look, Ushio.
This is your original that I failed to finish eating back then.
I-It can't be.
Ushio!
Is that really Ushio?
What happened to the body we cremated yesterday?
The bones we gathered?
My father replaced the body with a double.
Haine printed someone else's bones.
Why?
Why would ya do all that just to take care of that girl?
Toki, did ya know everything all along?
That they were after Shiori, and that Ushio would be killed?
Ushio's death came as a surprise to me.
I never expected her to team up with her own Shadow in order to save Shiori.
She died because she stuck her nose where it didn't belong in some misguided sense of justice.
What did you say?
Everything has been for Haine's sake.
Don't ya give me that!
Ain't no way y'all're gettin' of the hook that easy!
Where the hell is Dad?!
Quit flappin' yer gums like ya know everything, dummy!
It's because yer like this that I ended up havin' to shoulder everything!
It was the only choice!
My only choice!
If Haine dies, then so does Mom.
What?
Mom isn't alive because her disease was cured.
Dad asked Haine to turn her into a Shadow so she wouldn't die.
Huh?
Wait... What?
But I...
I don't understand.
Mom's... what?
You and Shinpei both treat Ushio like the real one, don't ya?
Toki.
No...
That thing's gonna eat her and make her disappear.
I won't let that happen!
Shadows can't move for a few seconds while they're scanning.
Haine's no exception!
Ushio, now!
Print!
I was waitin' for those words!
Eat this!
Ushio!
Are you hurt?
No fair! No fair!
They stole my food!
Thanks, Ushio.
You okay?
Here's my chance.
I should hurry and shoot—
Why?
Are you stupid, standing against the Shadows?
Yer just gonna die. Ya can't win.
Ever.
The Toki I knew wouldn't enjoy doing these things.
She's just using ya.
Taking advantage of yer weakness.
All to fill her own belly.
Ya toyed with Toki's feelings.
Ya think I could live with that?
Well yer dead wrong!
How dare ya treat my sister's dear friend like dirt.
I don't care if yer a god or Hiruko herself.
Don't look down on humans!
Ushio...
Boring.
What is that?
Does it no longer care about disguising itself as a human?
I wish to eat Ushio's memories until she's half-dead.
I should've prioritized
getting Ushio to break my neck so I could instantly restart the loop.
That was my plan initially.
After all, I couldn't allow Ushio to fight if it meant endangering her.
But...
I should have stopped her. But I couldn't.
Because I...
had the exact same thought...
There we go!
...as her running through my mind!
Don't look down on humans!
If I'm gonna die anyway,
then I might as well die fighting.
Shi—
Stop it, Haine.
That's enough.
You tried to eat Shinpei just now, didn't you?
But! But! They stole my food!
No buts.
It can't be...
How...
It's fine, Haine.
I'll be sure to retrieve Kofune Ushio's body later.
You mustn't eat this one.
She is an important hostage.
Mio!
Yer so annoying! I know that already.
Oh, don't worry. Mio is still alive.
But if any of you takes a single step,
I'll crush her skull like an egg.
Hey, what is this?
Ya weren't supposed to touch Mio!
That's what ya promised, innit?!
What a foolish question.
It's not like any of you are going to live past tomorrow, anyway.
What are ya talking about?
Tomorrow,
Haine was supposed to have her final meal at the summer festival to heal her body,
and then bring Mom back.
Do just as we'd been doing...
That was Dad's plan,
wasn't it?!
The Hishigata family has served us well.
But that's over now.
Ya traitor...
What are ya planning on doing with everyone—
Tokiko!
Wow!
Sou?
Your father already knows all of this.
Summer Time Rendering
Not good...
Consciousness fading...
Sis...
Hey, are ya okay, lady?
Yer really bleeding.
Totsumura...
Good. He's human.
This is it for me.
Sorry, Sis...
Ryuunosuke.
Hey, yer the H-cup that was at Ushio's funeral!
They're G's, idiot.
Where's Kofune Mio?
You were together, weren't you?
A monster took her.
So many of these baby monsters appeared, and...
What about your firearm?
I think I dropped it.
I pulled it out and tried to shoot them, but...
I tripped, and then I ran.
I don't remember a thing after that.
You made the right choice in running.
Huh?
I have a favor to ask.
I can't walk anymore.
So please carry me.
Oh! Right! I'll take ya to a hospital right away!
No.
Take me into the depths of this cave.
No...
I can't...
I can't let this become reality.
Ushio.
Come here.
Slowly, though.
Yer...
gonna pay for this!
Pay for what?
Mio's gonna die.
Come.
S-Stop!
Don't ya dare touch her!
Ya wanna eat humans?
Then eat me!
Don't try to die a hero.
Yer wasting yer time.
I revise my earlier statement.
Yer not an inferior stray.
Ya wouldn't have been able to defeat Negoro if ya were.
No, yer the opposite.
Yeh've grown to be superior.
Simply erasing ya would be a waste.
I'll reprogram yer brain instead.
We need all the help we can get for tomorrow.
No...
Shinpei!
Stop it!
So it's impossible to take away his power, eh?
Which came first, the chicken or the egg?
Cause and effect creates the ring!
No fair!
That right eye of yours.
It overlooks the flow of time from a higher dimension
and observes multiple parallel worlds.
And, Shinpei,
you have the power to make the world you observe into reality.
Right now, you are rendering this world.
A truly terrifying, godly power.
Luckily, you haven't mastered this power.
It is incomplete, only accessible when you lose sense of yourself in death.
So basically, we just have to keep you alive until the very end.
It's so simple.
You're going to stay here until tomorrow ends,
unable to do anything but breathe.
And fall into despair.
Mio...
I'm screwed.
If I can't loop, I can't ever redo things.
I broke my promise again.
I couldn't protect anyone.
I'm sorry, Mio.
I'm sorry, Ushio.
I-I hope I'm not interrupting anything!
Totsumu—
Miss Nagumo!
This is my last shot!
Too close, too close.
Shinpei almost died there.
Totsumura...
Miss Nagumo...
Now there's no one left to interfere.
Thank you...
What?
They bought me...
time to drink this!
You!
Shinpei!
Listen to me, y'all.
If one of us dies, or is injured with no hope of recovery,
I'm gonna loop immediately and redo things.
Ya mean yer gonna kill yerself? How?
I figured I'd use this.
Dude! That's mercuric chloride!
Ya brought it along?
What's the lethal dose?
Even a single drop is bad news.
Then if I drink the whole bottle, I'm sure to die?
Yeah, but it'll hurt like hell.
Right.
I'll just pray I don't have to use it.
Poison, huh?
You sure are used to dying, aren't you?
Don't tell me.
You've come this far multiple times before?
Not shocked, are ya?
Fuck-face.
Oh?
I didn't expect this much fortitude.
I'll keep doing this over and over as many times as it takes...
And in the end,
I'll defeat y'all!
I... I swear!
Hey!
There's no saving him.
Forgive me, Haine.
Forget him!
Look at her!
She's started to reverse my corrosion!
Shinpei's risking his life!
I don't have time to be sleeping now!
She's turning the corrosion back on me!
It can't be! Are ya...
Are ya the egg?!
Kill her!
And me if ya have to!
She vanished?
Curses!
He took her along.
Ushio!
Shinpei!
It's all right.
I got ya!
I'm sorry, Shinpei.
Because of me, everyone's...
Mio's...
Yer wrong!
It ain't time to cry over the past.
Just look at the present!
We'll defeat them, even if it costs me my life.
I'll go anywhere, as many times as it takes,
as long as we're together, Shinpei!
Which means you must be a time traveler.
Yes.
"Yes"?
We've just returned from the future.
July 22nd
(Fifth loop)
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Friend