It was a small incident that happened
to me, Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I accepted the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
As my beliefs became stronger,
the unyielding wishes
became stronger as well.
But I don't want to give up
on communicating,
because I don't want to end
without understanding anything.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin.
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
I've been thinking all this time.
About the girl who I'm sure
is close to me in age,
and has deep, pretty eyes.
I'm sure that we'll have another
fight if we see each other again.
But...
Episode é:
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?
That's enough!
Ever since that day, you always
space out when we're talking!
I'm sorry, Arisa.
Don't apologize!
If talking to us is that boring,
you can just sit by yourself and
space out as much as you want!
Let's go, Suzuka!
Arisa...
Nanoha...
It's all right, Suzuka.
That was all my fault, anyway.
I don't think that's the case.
I think Arisa said more
than she should have too.
I'll go talk to her for a bit.
I'm sorry...
I made her mad.
I'm sorry, Arisa.
Arisa! Arisa!
Arisa...
What is it?
I kind of understand
why you're so angry,
but you shouldn't have
gotten that mad.
I mean, it irritates me!
It's plain obvious that she's
worried about something.
It's plain obvious that she's in trouble!
But no matter what we ask her,
she won't tell us anything!
She's lying, saying she's not
confused or worried!
No matter how good friends we are,
there are things that we
can't tell each other.
If it's something that Nanoha
wants to keep a secret,
I think all we can do is
wait for her to tell us.
I'm telling you, that's
what irritates me!
I want to be of help to her,
even if only by a little bit!
I don't care what it's about.
I may not be able to do anything.
But at least we can
think it through with her!
Arisa, you really do care
about Nanoha a lot.
Of course I do!
Because she was here, I was
finally able to stop being all alone.
You're right. The same goes for me.
Because Nanoha was here,
we were able to become friends.
See you, Nanoha.
I'm sorry, we both have
lessons again today.
They last until late at night, right?
Take care, and do your best!
Arisa?!
It'll be all right, okay, Nanoha?
Yeah... Thanks, Suzuka...
You know, it's been a while since
I last walked home by myself.
I think I'll take a detour
on the way home.
Because I don't want anyone
to see how I look right now...
Do you remember when we first met?
I used to be much more timid,
and I couldn't say anything
that was on my mind,
and no matter what anyone said,
I couldn't argue back.
I hate to say it, but I think
I was a rotten kid.
Arrogant, selfish, boastful...
That's why I made fun
of my classmates.
Because I really had a weak will.
That's...
And because I had a weak will,
I couldn't say what I needed to say.
"That is something very dear
to me, so give it back."
Though people told me
to stop it, I didn't listen.
I felt that I would somehow lose,
if I honestly listened to what
someone else had to say.
What was it that Nanoha
said back then?
"Did that hurt?"
"But the heart of someone who got
something dear to her taken away"
"hurts much, much more than that."
That's right...
I think I ended up in a huge fight
with Arisa after that.
And the one that stopped us was...
..the very quiet girl that caused it all.
Stop it!
Because I was really
desperate right then...
And since then, we slowly started
to talk to each other, right?
Right. The three of us...
And so, Suzuka, bringing up
that old story,
what the heck do you want me to do?
As if you didn't know.
I know that she just doesn't want us
to worry about whatever it is.
And that we probably can't be
of any help to her, either.
If all we can do is to wait for her...
Then I'll just stay upset
while waiting for her!
At the loneliness from not
sharing our feelings,
and at myself for not being able
to help a friend!
You're so stubborn.
Hmph!
I see. So you guys got in a fight.
It's not like that.
Arisa just scolded me because
I kept blanking out.
You're close friends, right?
Yeah, ever since we
first entered school.
Here!
This is your share, Yuuno.
Since there's no cram school today,
we can take our time to search
for Jewel Seeds until dinnertime!
Let's do our best together!
Yeah... Let's do our best.
The food in this world...
Well, it's not that bad!
Now, where is my little princess?
Whoops, I forgot something!
Oh, you haven't eaten
your meal again!
That's not good! You have to eat.
I ate, just a little. I'm fine.
Let's get going soon.
I've determined the approximate
location of the next Jewel Seed.
I don't want to keep Mother waiting.
Well, Fate, you are my master,
and I am your familiar,
so if you're saying
we need to go, we'll go.
We can leave after you're done eating.
That's not what I mean!
I'm worried about you, Fate!
Wide-area search magic takes
a whole lot of stamina,
but you've barely been
eating or sleeping!
And those wounds aren't that
simple either, you know?
It's all right. I'm tough.
Fate...
Now, let's go.
Mother is waiting for us.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha!
Hey, Kyouya, about Nanoha...
Has she been worried
about something lately?
Even I think that when I look at her.
It's really worrying Suzuka.
Maybe...
She's going out more often in the
afternoons and evenings lately.
I don't want to meddle,
but should I try talking to her?
That would be great, but I don't
think she'll tell you anything.
You don't think I'm good enough?
No, no, that's not what I mean.
It's not that she won't tell
you personally, Shinobu.
I don't think she'd tell anyone.
She's always been like that when
something's bothering her,
or when she's trying to
decide on something.
Really?
Well, I don't think there's much
you need to worry about.
I'm sure she will reach
the answer on her own.
I see.
I think we're out of time.
We need to get home soon.
It's okay.
I'll stay here and search a bit more.
Yuuno, will you be
all right by yourself?
I'll be fine, so save me
some dinner, okay?
Okay.
Maybe Arisa and Suzuka
are done with their lessons
and are on their way home by now?
There is no new mail.
I think it's somewhere around here,
but I can only figure out
the approximate location.
Yeah. When things are this crowded,
it's a chore to find them.
It's a bit rough,
but I'm going to shower the area
with magical power,
and force it to execute.
Hey, hold on!
I'll do that!
Are you all right?
It's pretty tiring, you know.
Just whose familiar
do you think I am?
Then, please.
Here goes!
Forcing an execution in
the middle of the city?!
A barrier... Can I make it in time?!
Raising Heart, please!
Found it!
But they seem to be nearby too!
Let's get it over with
quickly. Bardiche!
Sealing form, set up.
Nanoha! Can you see the
executed Jewel Seed?
Yeah. It's right here!
Those guys are close by.
Seal it before they do!
Got it!
Lyrical, magical!
Jewel Seed Serial XIX...
Seal!
Device Mode.
Stop it!
Neither Arisa nor Suzuka were
friends with me when we first met.
Because we couldn't
talk to each other,
because we couldn't
understand each other.
The reason why I made Arisa mad
was because I couldn't
tell her how I really felt,
what I was really thinking.
All right! Nanoha, hurry up
and capture it!
I won't let you!
Because we both have an objective,
we probably can't help
clashing against each other.
But I still want to know!
I couldn't introduce myself
the other day.
I'm Nanoha.
Nanoha Takamachi.
A third grader at Seisho University
Magnet Elementary.
Scythe Form.
Why do you have such sad eyes?
Flier Fin.
Sending mail to Nanoha?
Yeah. Saying my lesson is over.
Now, let's go home.
Okay... Hold on a second!
I just got done with my lesson.
I'm going to go home and have dinner how.
Arisa isn't all too upset, so everything is fine.
Nanoha, I hope your worries are solved...
..your worries are solved soon.
Please do your best. I'll always be
cheering you on.
From Suzuka.
Sending mail
Flash Move.
Divine Shooter.
Defenser.
Fate!
You said that just talking it out,
mere words, won't get
the point across.
But I'm sure there are things out
there that don't make it across
unless you talk, unless you
put them into words!
Clashing with each other,
competing with each other,
maybe that can't be avoided...
But I don't want to keep fighting
without knowing anything at all!
I'm collecting Jewel Seeds because
Yuuno is looking for them.
Yuuno was the one that
found the Jewel Seeds,
and Yuuno is the one that needs
to collect them all back together.
I'm helping him out.
But even though it was coincidence
that I started helping him,
I'm now collecting the
Jewel Seeds of my own will.
Because I don't want to see
the city where I live in danger,
or all the people around me!
That's my reason!
L.
Fate, you don't have to answer that!
You don't have to tell
anything to a little brat
who's lived her life
surrounded by nice people!
Our primary objective is to
capture all the Jewel Seeds!
Nanoha!
I'm okay!
Suzuka, what's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
There is no new mail.
Man, I'm starving. Let's hurry home!
Okay!
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of cellophane
and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying inside
a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining
on the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something
I can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
For an explosion like that to occur...
That's just got to be bad!
But Mother is waiting.
What is the truth behind
the Jewel Seeds?
And a new mage appears?!
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 7:
Is This a Third Magician?
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 7:
Is This a Third Magician?
Episode 7: Is This a Third Magician?
Episode 7:
Is This a Third Magician?
Lyrical, magical, in hopes
that I won't lose!