Re-Opening Soon
Miura Ramen!
"A second branch will soon be opening in Kibougahana!"
Seriously?! That's awesome!
This place is seriously delicious!
But their first branch is in a neighboring town...
Soon I'll be able to eat here whenever I want!
Hey, Erika, you're drooling all over the place!
Oh, it's Miura!
Miura?
Congrats!
Why didn't you tell me you guys were opening a second branch?!
I'll come and dine here on opening day!
Don't.
Huh? What do you mean, "don't"?
Hey, why not?!
Oh, sir!
Good afternoon!
Hey, good afternoon.
Oh, Akira, you're heading back too?
Huh? Hey, come back, Miura!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Rejected Ramen!
Heal the Father-and-Son Bond!
Next! Third!
Nice job, Miura!
You're really giving it your all!
Of course I am! A regular isn't allowed to mess up!
Miura's on the baseball team, huh?
Yeah. He's been playing since he was in elementary school.
He's become a regular member of the team, huh?
That's amazing!
He hasn't had the time to play that often.
Back when he was a first year, he was just a backup player.
Oh, now that I think about it, that was the same year Miura Ramen's first branch opened.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Back then, he was advertising, telling everyone he met that his dad had opened a ramen store.
He was really rooting for him, saying, "My dad's ramen is seriously tasty!"
And then he just tells me not to come...
What's the matter with him?
I'm home!
Welcome back!
So which are we using?
If we're going for color coordination, we should really go with this, right?
But I think this one would be better...
Is that an opening present for Miura Ramen?
Yeah, but we're having trouble getting it just right...
We want it to give a real "Congrats on your opening!" feeling...
That's right. We need it to give off a really cheerful feeling...
Hey.
Hm?
Congratulations on your 2nd Branch!!
To everyone at Miura Ramen
Here!
Rapeseed blossoms?
Try putting them in!
Okay...
Wow! It gives off a "Spring has come!" effect!
Really makes you want to give it your all...
That's our daughter for you!
Thank you, Tsubomi!
All right! Let's start over with the rapeseed blossoms as our focus!
Right! Let's make this have a real uplifting, encouraging feel!
Miura...
Why can't you root for him...
Good afternoon...
Tsubomi, come out here for a sec!
Look at this! Something's happened to Coffret!
It's like he's totally worn out!
Me... too...
I'm... exhausted...
What's happened to you two?!
Well, we're...
...starviiiing.
Found it!
What is this?
It's the Cure Frumix!
First, press that button!
Um... this one?
Next you have to shake it!
Like this?
You need to do it harder!
Like this?!
That's totally no good!
Give it here.
How's thiiiiiis?!
That's okay!
This rich texture!
This addictive taste!
It's so delicious!
I'm so happy!
I totally get it!
Delicious things really do make you happy!
Miura Ramen embodies that perfectly!
The pork with just a hint of the bonito
flavoring—it's so rich, yet also refreshing...
Lord Coupe?
He's trying to encourage you to "Fight!"
Huh?
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
There's someone that you want to
encourage too, isn't there, Tsubomi?
Huh? I don't really...
Really?
This is delicious! What kind of tea is it?
It's a herbal tea made with thyme.
In the language of flowers, thyme means "courage."
Courage...
Oh, look, it's the horrible son.
I hope he's not going to damage the flowers.
Miura... and his father...
Fight!
Right!
Tsubomi?
U-Um...
Um, Miura?
Um...
U-Um...
Excuse me!
Tsubomi!
Are you okay, Tsubomi?
It hurts...
You're bleeding...
Here, have this.
Huh?
I'm on the baseball team, after all.
I always carry these around.
Thank you very much...
Bye.
Um!
Um... Well, you see...
Make sure you put that on, all right?
W-Wait! Miura, what is it you want from your father?!
Why can't you support his new store?!
Do you want your father to quit running his ramen store?!
Of course I don't!
That's way too high!
Nice catch!
All right, one more time!
A father and son playing catch, huh?
Miura, you used to play catch a lot with your dad too, didn't you?
Yeah, in the past.
Dad!
Look! I'm definitely gonna become a regular!
All right then!
I'll definitely come to cheer you on!
You'd better! That's a promise, okay?!
It wasn't just about playing catch...
He would always come to my games...
And then...
And then?
If you don't tell us, we won't understand!
Even if I did, it wouldn't do any good.
Sheesh! This pisses me off!
His Flower of the Heart seemed really dreary...
Miura...
First Sasorina, and now even you have been defeated by the Precure.
Would you like to explain yourself, Kumojacky?
I was merely attempting to measure their strength.
Next time, I'll surely...
Is that meant to be an excuse?
Lights!
You manage to be not only repugnant, but repulsive too, Kumojacky.
Flaunting yourself again, Kobraja?
You're not needed here.
Get lost!
Au contraire. I'm sure I'll perform much better than you.
Then go, Kobraja.
Defeat the Precure.
Leave it all to me.
Good morniiiiing!
How long are you gonna sleep?! Get up already!
But there's no school today...
It's the grand opening of Miura Ramen's second branch!
You can't just lie in bed all day!
But it doesn't open until 11...
If we get in line first, we'll be the first ones to eat!
Oh, Akira! Are you off to practice?
Yeah.
Good timing! Come in for a second.
Yo.
We just finished up the first batch.
If this second branch goes well,
there'll be a third branch before long!
We've got to work hard and make your dad's dream to let everyone experience Miura Ramen come true!
Right!
What's the matter?
It'll get cold.
I don't want to eat it!
What's the matter? Are you feeling sick?
Your dad's ramen is full of nutrients, so it'll perk you right up in no time!
I said I don't want it!
Non, non! That's no good!
None of these will do...
Ah, how long must I wander before I find a backdrop that suits me?
What's this? O-ho!
At first glance these flowers seem gaudy, yet they give the building this refined, elegant look...
This shall do nicely!
Camera!
C'était magnifique.
It's not that you don't like the ramen, right?
So if there's something you want to say, then say it.
Even if I did, it wouldn't make any difference!
After all, your ramen's the most important thing to you, right?!
Akira!
You there.
How your heart withers with such delicious suffering.
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
Now, let us begin the show!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Look over there!
Meeeeeeen!
A Desertrian!
Tsubomi!
Right!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
So you're here, Precures.
A new commander of the Desert Apostles...
Name yourself!
My name is Kobraja...
A pleasure to make your acquaintance!
Blossom!
Miura!
What on earth is this?!
You always came to cheer for me when I was in elementary school.
Huh?
But now, it's just ramen all day every day!
You don't care about me anymore!
Don't!
Men!
Leave this to us!
Men! Ramen!
Meeeeeeeeeen!
Dad cares more about his work than me.
That's not...
That's not true!
I hate ramen... and I hate you, Dad!
That ramen store should just disappear!
No!
Blossom!
Stop it...
You mustn't destroy the ramen store!
You mustn't destroy Dad's dream!
But just a second ago, he wanted to destroy it!
Both of them are part of his true feelings!
He's struggling with those two sets of conflicting emotions.
Miura...
Because you care about your father...
And you don't want to trouble him when he's working so hard...
You couldn't tell him how much you wanted him to cheer you on...
His Flower of the Heart was withering from something like that...
How weak and pathetic he is.
It's not weakness!
It's his kindness!
Manipulating and trampling on it like that is just cruel!
I've...
had it up to here with this!
Me too! I'm really annoyed and like...
Dang it, I can't think of a catchphrase!
I'll come up with something for next time!
Let's go!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
Safe!
Not bad at all.
I think we'll leave things here for today.
Adieu!
Thank you for the meal!
Thank you very much!
Ya know...
Shouldn't we tell them how Miura is feeling?
No.
These things are better coming from the source, I think.
It's the source!
Hey, the thing is...
Th-Th-Thanks for the food!
Dad... I...
Akira... let's go play catch.
Let's go.
Dad's been waiting with his glove for you.
You've got a match next week, right?
I'll come and cheer you on!
It doesn't matter, really.
You've got the shop to worry about, right?
That's no good.
Expanding Miura Ramen may be my dream...
but coming to cheer you on at your baseball games is also my dream!
I promised you back then, didn't I?
That when you became a regular, I'd come cheer you on, Akira.
You remembered... that promise?
Of course I did!
Like I'd forget a promise between us men!
Do your best! Cause your dad's gonna cheer with all he's got!
You too! Do your best with the second branch!
Right!
Dad!
I'm sorry...
I know!
Miura's Flower of the Heart is lively again!
In the language of flowers, sage means "familial love."
I think a Heart Seed is going to be born...
Playing catch sure is nice.
Isn't it?
We've done something good here.
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
There's some super in-depth reporting on the current Precure craze!
Kanae's journalist soul reveals the truth behind the Precure's identities...
Wait, what?!
If our identities are exposed, what'll happen?
Horrible, horrible things!
What horrible things?
Huh? Well... that's a secret!
Tch... Well, I don't mind if you want to keep it a secret.
HeartCatch Precure:
Scoop! The Precures'
Identities are Revealed?!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!