Arashigaoka Academy
LOCATION
Tsubaki Kureha
LILY
Look how beautifully they've blossomed, Kureha-chan.
Izumino Sumika
LILY
Nobody will see us all the way out here.
Don't be ashamed. We're not doing anything wrong.
But...
I want to be together with you.
Okay?
Sumika, I'll never back down on love.
Kureha-chan...
Yes, neither will I.
Bear shock!
Bears! There are bears!
Bears
Bear Alarm System
ALARM
The bears crossed the Severance Barrier?
Kureha-chan.
Don't worry.
I will protect you.
From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
That's why we wanted to become true friends.
To cross that barrier...
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Storm!
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shite
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so give me your approval
kaze ni notte ehon no page ga
As pages from a picture book flutter in the wind
kagirinaku kioku wo yurasu no
so sway my countless memories along with them
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
kurai kono sekai no naka
in this dark world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if the world would crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
Growl!
One day, an asteroid in the far reaches of the universe called Kumaria went kaboom.
A bunch'a the little bits fell to Earth as a meteor shower.
Kumaria Meteor Shower
HISTORY
Then all of a sudden, every bear on the planet rose to its feet!
We all came together and started attacking humans.
Like, I was totally shocked!
Severence Barrier
LOCATION
The humans built the Severance Barrier to keep us bears out
and tried to chase us away from their world.
But you know what?
We don't listen to those silly human rules! Growl!
We are bears!
Bears eat people. That's just how we are.
And now...
Ladies, today I shall introduce you to two new friends.
Yurishiro Ginko-san and Yurigasaki Lulu-san.
Yurishiro Ginko
Yurigasaki Lulu
Please give them a warm welcome.
Yurishiro Ginko
LILY
We've transformed into human forms and entered one of their schools.
Yurigasaki Lulu
LILY
Looks like they don't have a clue who we really are.
Each and every girl is the pick of the litter!
Sniff sniff.
Holy bear...
There are tantalizing scents from every direction!
It's settled!
I'm gonna do my best and eat them all up!
Right, Ginko?
Oh, and by the way, this girl over here,
Yurishiro Ginko, is also undoubtedly a bear.
She's my beloved, delightful little darling.
Hakonaka Yurika
LILY
And ladies, I do not believe that this bears repeating,
but a dreadful bear sighting occurred this morning on the road outside the academy.
A bear crossing the Severance Barrier and invading the human world is something that must be taken very seriously.
The alarm may have ceased, but be certain to keep your guard up.
When walking within the school, do not go alone.
Please use the buddy system.
There's one!
I've found you at last.
That girl simply reeks...
of a delicious meal.
Slurp.
Sumika?
Say, Kureha-chan. What dishes do you like to pack for lunch?
What dishes?
Yeah.
I happen to like fried fish tubes. What about you?
Let me think...
I guess Naporitan pasta and salted fish.
Salted fish? You eat it for lunch?
You don't?
What's so funny?
You're not aware?
Kureha-chan, you're like an old man.
An old man?
Yep.
How could you say that?
I mean, sure, it does smell a bit when I open the container...
But I love it.
I love you, even if you do act a bit like an old man.
I'm in love with you.
Sumika?!
Sumika!
Kureha-chan?
What's the matter?
Uh... well...
You haven't eaten yet?
N-No...
Here.
I'll share half of it with you. Let's eat together.
Okay?
There's a fish tube in this pastry.
Yeah, too bad it isn't fried though.
What is it?
Nothing at all.
How would you like to eat together up here every day?
But if we do that...
I want to eat with you.
It really does taste better when I'm with you.
It sure does.
Grind grind grind...
My stomach's growling too.
My delicious meal... I want to eat her.
Goodness, Ginko. You're such a little glutton.
I-If you really can't help yourself,
you can nibble a little bit of me here and there if you'd like!
Oh no, I said it! I really said it!
A storm has fallen upon us.
This was just a warning that everything we hold dear will be destroyed, one by one.
The Invisible Storm will engulf everything.
It will erode us until we are no more.
Kureha-chan, I'll also never back down on love.
Just as you've done for me,
no matter what may come of me,
I'll never back down on my love for you.
My stomach is growling even louder.
It smells. I can smell you, delicious meal.
I won't back down on my love.
I will protect you.
Kureha-chan.
As I suspected.
Tsubaki-san, to think that you have been swept into the Invisible Storm as well.
Yurizono-san.
Yurizono Mitsuko
LILY
How cruel.
It cut down these flowers at the peak of their bloom.
The Invisible Storm destroys what is pure and gentle first.
You're right.
But with this, I have steeled my resolve.
I won't allow for this to go on any longer.
Tsubaki-san. Izumino-san.
Let's stand against the Storm and stop it in its tracks.
I'm ashamed of my former conduct of turning a blind eye as the class representative.
My apologies, Izumino-san.
Can you find it in yourself to forgive me?
There's nothing you need to apologize for...
You know, I think we could be good friends.
If the three of us work together, we can surely halt the Invisible Storm.
Though given the alarm, we should probably return home for today.
Let's meet early in the morning to remake the flower beds.
I'll be there to help, of course.
Yurizono-san, your hands...
Not a problem. I see it as proof of being let into your ring of friends.
Who's there?!
The first lily I ate filled me up with happiness.
I want to eat that girl, but maybe she's not for me.
I want to eat this girl, but maybe she's not for me.
Let the judgement fall down all upon our heads!
Tsubaki Kureha's House
LOCATION
Beware
Kureha, did you play nicely with your friend today?
Yep! And we ate our snacks together today, Mom!
Really? Did you enjoy them?
Eating with her made them extra yummy!
You must really care for her, Kureha.
Yeah, I love her!
Yes, and that is why this time, I'll protect those I love
with my own two hands.
I shan't forgive the bears.
I will exterminate the bears!
Ichimashisa speaking.
Current location, the flower beds at Arashigaoka Academy.
Bear footprints confirmed.
Bloodstains present.
Casualties likely.
Personal belongings are strewn about.
The victim is possibly a student.
We are searching the premises.
Yes, we had planned to meet here.
We intended to come early and fix the flower beds.
The number you have dialed cannot be reached.
If necessary, you may leave a message after the beep.
I heard just her shoes were found.
That means the rumors about her were true.
She must've come early to fix the flower beds they were talking about.
It can't be. If that were true...
Akae Kachuusha
LILY
It's her fault for coming alone.
Kiyama Eriko
LILY
Friends are necessary for survival!
Yurikawa Konomi
LILY
Yeah, you're right.
This all but confirms the next Invisible Storm.
That's what happens when you're not invisible.
We're nothing more than feeble prey to the bears.
We need to stick together.
That's right, it's important to act as a group.
It's a lie...
It's a lie!
Sumika... Sumika can't have been eaten!
restricted number
Who is this?
Is that you, Sumika?
Is your love true?
Flashback
Tsubaki Kureha, this is a challenge from the Severance Barrier.
If your love is true,
then come to the rooftop at once.
The bears are awaiting you.
What do you mean? Is Sumika safe?
Entrust your body to the bears, and your love shall be approved.
Tsubaki Kureha
The time of judgement has come.
Grind grind grind...
Sumika!
Give Sumika... Give Sumika back to me!
I want to eat.
I want to eat that girl right now!
Enter!
Welcome to the Severance Court.
Severance Court
LOCATION
The gate has now been opened.
Let all living beings bear witness to this face off of man and bear.
Let us begin the judgement.
For man and for bear—
Life Sexy!
Judge
Life Sexy
JUDGEMENS
For man and for bear—
Life Cool!
Prosecutor
Life Cool
JUDGEMENS
For man and for bear—
Life Beauty!
Defense
Attorney
Life Beauty
JUDGEMENS
The Lily Court is now in session.
Lily Court in Session
TRIAL
Bearfendants, do you plead to be guilty bears?
Bearfendant
Yurigasaki Lulu
BEAR
Listen, our stomachs were growling so loudly.
Bearfendant
Yurishiro Ginko
BEAR
We will never back down on love.
Your Honor, there exists an insurmountable barrier of severance between man and bear.
The defendants have crossed it and invaded the world of man.
This is clearly an act of overeating.
I declare them guilty!
Shiny shine!
Your Honor, the prosecutor is clearly committing an ad ursam!
Defense, are you raising an objection?
Of course! Even bears will die if they don't eat.
Are you perhaps insinuating that these girls should've starved to death?
You must understand that if you allow their crimes to go unpunished, further victims will fall prey!
Objection! He is excessively supporting the human side!
Objection sustained.
We must be as scales, fairly judging the two worlds.
That is sexy!
Shabadadu.
Shiny shine!
Anyways, does that mean we can eat the girl?
Hold it!
Your Honor, please bestow your Love Judgement!
Very well. Then I shall ask the bearfendants.
Will you become invisible?
Or will you eat humans?
We will eat...
...humans!
Growl!
I shall hand down my sentence.
Lily, approved!
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily Instatement!
Kureha.
I am going to eat you.
Where is that which I desire?
I shall search for it from within the Invisible Storm.
Lick.
What are you searching for?
Where are you searching?
Bestow upon me the promised kiss!
Thank goodness, you've regained consciousness.
Yurizono-san...
Where am I?
The school infirmary.
Huh? Why?
We found you collapsed on the roof.
Sumika! Where's Sumika?!
We have yet to find her.
It can't be... but the bears on the roof...
They told me! They said they'd give Sumika back!
Calm down. You were the only one we found.
Just me? That can't...
I'll go buy you something warm to drink.
Was that a dream?
But I clearly remember...
Please be okay... Sumika.
What's that sound?
Don't tell me that someone brought another Storm to the flowers...
Grind... scrape... grind... scrape...
Human girls are just irresistibly delicious.
I'd eat them even if it was a crime.
I won't forgive those who destroy love.
Bears are eating a person!
Shock!
Bear shock!
Those are the transfer students...
I see now... those two were simply taking the form of humans. They're bears!
Slurp.
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger