Even if you ignore the uneasiness in your chest
Your heart Feels Blue
In the end, tomorrow comes even if you can't focus on it
Feelings can't go anywhere on their own
Change yourself, don't leave this in God's hands
Just find out that I have always
Been able to hear your sad voice
Shake hands with the courage to hold hands
The stars are turning into constellations
Shout friends, how you truly feel
So it echoes to the ends of the Earth
Dream bells, the sound of our bells
Shines peacefully tomorrow - True Story
Welcome to the Velvet Room.
I see you've made a great number of memories.
Along with your new bond, you've obtained the Hanged Man Arcana.
Your bonds will continue to strengthen through your encounters and conversations,
and as you gain a deeper understanding of one another.
Man, I get to see Risette!
Right! Okay, you got it!
Okay, I'm counting on you!
Schedule an interview with the magazine tomorrow at 11:30 PM at our office.
Okay.
It's been crazy since she got the lead role for that movie.
What's in two days?
A costume check for the movie at 2:00,
a recording for a radio talk show at 5:00,
filming for a commercial at 8:00, and we finish at 4:00 A.M.
Risette! Risette! Risette!
I quit.
Huh?
I'm going to resign.
Huh? Wha— Wait! Hey, Rise!
Here I go!
Even if you ignore the uneasiness in your chest, your heart will Feel Blue
In the end, tomorrow comes even if you don't think about it
Feelings can't go anywhere on their own
Change yourself, don't leave it in God's hands
Just find out that I have always
been able to hear your sad voice
Shake hands with the courage to hold hands
The stars are turning into constellations
Shout friends, how you truly feel
such that it echoes to the ends of the Earth
Dream bells, the sound of our bells
shine peacefully tomorrow - True Story
Press conference regarding Rise Kujikawa's hiatus
I imagine your fans must be worried because of your sudden hiatus.
Are you suffering from any health problems?
No, my health isn't an issue or anything.
Is it related to your mental health?
Huh? No, it's not.
Is it true that you'll be taking your break in Inaba?
Yes.
Excuse me, but why a break?
This means Risette is here for real!
Rise has no further comments.
I can't believe an idol's coming out here!
We'll be back after a quick commercial break.
This has everything I need.
Aqua Balance will revitalize your body.
Hello?
Yeah, it's Rise.
Milk? Okay.
Yeah, I don't mind.
Hey, isn't that her?
Grandma, you take it easy.
No way! Isn't that Risette?
You dropped this.
You should've said so sooner!
Oh, sorry.
You did give it back to me,
so thanks.
Oh, that strap...
Huh?
It looks tasty.
Press conference regarding Rise Kujikawa's hiatus
Doesn't your grandmother run a traditional tofu shop in Inaba?
Yeah.
Do you know when you'll return to work?
No, not yet.
Hey, think we'll run into Rise?
I did.
So are you looking to retire?
Big Bro, you saw her? You saw Rise?!
I don't know.
I think so.
That's so cool! Was she as cute as she is on TV?
How will you be spending your time?
I haven't decided yet.
Doesn't Inaba have those unresolved serial murders?
The best thing about this town was how quiet it was, but it's gotten crazy this past year.
Well, we're out of time,
but stay tuned for these commercials.
I know that I'm the only true you.
Aim for your true self!
For licensing, go to...
"Your Future"!
What? Amagi, you know Rise's family?
Marukyu is probably the traditional tofu shop they were referring to.
We carry their tofu.
Oh, that place!
So if we went by the tofu shop, we could see Rise?
Hold it! Now isn't the time for that!
If the cases are really linked with the TV, she might be targeted next.
But it's not like Rise's never been on TV before, right?
I looked into it,
but Rise's only connection with the late Ms. Yamano
was that they appeared on one or two shows together.
With all the fuss about her break, she's the talk of the town.
To top it all off, she's moving here!
Good point. If our assumptions are correct, she fits the criteria.
Whadduya mean?
If he goes after Rise,
then the killer is targeting people from this town who show up on TV.
It'll debunk the theory that he's targeting people related to Ms. Yamano's murder.
Hm... Oh, now I get it!
Are you sure?
But we still don't know the killer's motive.
Maybe he's got a grudge against us?
I mean, I got a shitload of people who hate my guts.
Amagi, what about you? You ever piss anyone off?
Nope.
C'mon, Yukiko! Everyone's done something bad without realizing it.
I-I guess not.
Uh, in any case, I have no idea what everyone's done to cause such animosity.
Well, we can ask him about his motives after we catch him!
For now, we should keep an eye on Rise.
I'm telling you, that's Rise!
You sure? Doesn't she seem kinda different?
I'm 100% sure!
That chest! Those hips! And her beautiful, thin legs!
Wh-What are you looking at me for?!
Narukami, what do you think?
They're fine.
Say what? I gotta disagree.
Jiraiya!
Chie, Jiraiya is Hanamura's Persona.
Yours is Tomoe.
Chie's is Tomoe.
Hey, are you guys taking this seriously?
We are.
What is Chie's? A "Chie Pet"!
Then should we check out the tofu shop?
Yukiko and I have to run by the Faculty Office,
Chie's is the Chie Pet Tomoe.
so we'll catch up later.
Okay, let's go!
Chie's so cute!
Just so you know, this is for our investigation.
This isn't about seeing Rise in the flesh.
Enough with the excuses already.
There are a bunch of weirdos hanging around.
Marukyu
Tofu Shop
Same goes for us.
Sold out
of tofu
Wh-What the hell?!
Sold out
of tofu
I can't go back now after coming all this way to see Risette!
Ex-excuse me!
Marukyu
Tofu Shop
Didn't you see the notice? We're out of tofu.
No way...
It-It's really R-Risette!
Are you Rise?
Why do you sound so lame?
Huh? You're the guy from yesterday...
Hello.
What?! You already know each other? No fair!
Didn't you come to get some tofu?
I certainly did!
And we're sold out.
Oh, um...
Six fried tofu fritters, please.
Nice ad lib!
Six fried tofu fritters it is.
She's got attitude problems.
You're one to talk.
Um...
Man, I'm glad we came. We've cleared our mission for today.
We still have a job to do.
A job? Come again?
Have you noticed anything strange lately?
Oh, yeah! That's right!
Anything strange? Like a stalker?
Have you ever heard of the Midnight Channel?
You mean that program last night?
Huh? Did you watch it?
Yeah, since I'd heard the rumors.
But the girl on TV wasn't me.
Huh?
I've never worn that swimsuit in a promotional video.
Besides, my chest isn't that big.
Yeah, so I see...
Down, boy!
The person on that show might get kidnapped.
Huh?
I know it's hard to believe, but we aren't lying or pulling your leg.
Hey! You're upsetting the neighbors, so beat it!
Excuse me... Whoa there.
H-Hey!
What are you doing here?
Tatsumi Kanji...
Uh, well, um... Oh right, we're here to get some fried tofu fritters!
Marukyu
Tofu Shop
Here!
Let's go, c'mon!
Later.
Thanks again.
Come again.
Do you have a moment?
I'm Adachi from the Inaba PD.
You guys are policemen?
I'm sure you've already heard, but this area has been dangerous as of late.
Why did you suddenly decide to take a break here?
I got tired.
And I don't mean to scare you, but...
But there's a chance I could get kidnapped, right?
Those three guys just warned me.
I'll be careful.
Did they now?
Well, I still have work to do.
H-Hey, just a sec!
Since she's in town anyway, she should've asked our chief to help for the day.
D-Dojima?
I only came to warn Kujikawa Rise based on my detective's intuition.
How could some high school kids who don't even know the situation beat me to it?
Courage
Fearless
Diligence
Staunch
Understanding
Generous
Expression
Eloquent
Knowledge
Informed
A
Courage
Fearless
Diligence
Staunch
Understanding
Generous
Expression
Eloquent
Knowledge
Informed
A
Yo, why are we stalking her?
We might find the guy who's after Rise if we trail her.
Keep your eyes peeled for any suspicious characters.
We're the ones who look suspicious.
What on Earth are you guys doing over there?
You look really suspicious.
Are you the killer?
Hey!
Thanks again!
You really do deliver everywhere, don't you?
Just leave the bowls.
I got the extra large.
Mine's roast pork.
I got Tokyo-style noodles.
Don't touch my steak over there.
The other noodles are mine.
Here, here, here! The set's mine.
What?! What's a detective doing out here?
Dojima ordered me to—
Oops!
Well, you see, I overheard you making an order while doing some legwork for Dojima.
Talk about timing, right?
Geez, why do we have to eat with a cop?
She's going.
Great, let's go.
But we haven't eaten yet!
C'mon.
At least let me eat my tofu.
Hey, look.
The killer?
What?
That hit the spot.
You bastard!
You little—
Hold it, punk!
Just leave Risette to me!
You're coming with me!
Ow, ow ow.
Narukami, you watch her!
Me?
Wait, dammit! I'm gonna pummel ya!
You can't! It'll be on the police if the suspect gets hurt!
What's going on?
Wh-What are you doing?!
I'm just your typical Risette-loving civilian.
You're hardly "typical" after murdering people!
Murder? What are you talking about?
Save it for the station!
I didn't...
Whoo! I've always wanted to say that!
Now get up!
I appreciate your help in apprehending the culprit!
Go on! Keep up the pace!
So, it's all over now?
The case is solved? Booyah!
Maybe he really was a fan.
Did I really get kidnapped by a wimp like him?
No way.
Is it safe here?
We can see if someone's coming from any direction.
I'm used to dealing with stalkers.
Wouldn't it be better if you weren't?
The girl everyone makes such a fuss over isn't the real me.
Risette, huh?
She's just a fictional character sold to the public.
No one sees the real me.
Impressive!
You suck.
That hurts!
Sorry.
Look! I can do it if I try.
That's cute!
From: Hanamura Yosuke
Subject: The killer? has been caught.
The killer? has been caught.
Hurry back with Risette.
Looks like the coast's clear.
Okay. It's getting dark out, so let's go.
You never told me your name.
Narukami Yu.
I'm Kujikawa Rise.
I heard on the news last night.
The Midnight Channel last night...
Yeah, I caught a glimpse of her in the store when I passed by this morning.
It seems like the variety show only starts up once they've entered the TV.
Didn't we discuss how the person inside the TV could be producing the show?
They could be subconsciously showing us their inner thoughts.
But then what's up with the fuzzy program that comes on before they go missing?
It could be the killer's warning.
But who is he warning? And why?
Ask the culprit.
Is it possible that we're seeing the killer's thoughts, so it looks like a warning?
So we're seeing who he's targeting next?
Are you saying it's his fantasies of "I'm gonna attack you"?
Wouldn't that mean the weirdo from earlier wasn't our guy?
All we know for sure is that Kujikawa Rise is in danger.
Kujikawa?
Oh, Narukami!
You're starting school today?
I'm transferring into one of the freshman classes.
I'm here to file the paperwork.
I see.
Is that your locker?
Yeah, it's for sophomores.
So you're my senior.
Be sure to show me the ropes, Narukami.
I just transferred here last April myself.
They weren't here when I arrived.
I wonder how they heard about this.
Let's take a different route.
This is like a TV drama.
Pretty cool, huh?
We can't sneak through.
Rise!
Mr. Inoue?
What brought you here?
As your manager, I simply can't accept your decision to quit.
I'm not an idol anymore!
I'm not some puppet who needs someone to micromanage her time.
But what about the movie you were just given the lead role for?
Are you trying to force me to come back?
Just go.
Kanami has taken your role.
Kanami? Mashita Kanami?
I'm going to support Kanami to the best of my abilities.
Are you okay?
Are you sure you aren't deceiving yourself?
What do you know?!
You don't know anything about me!
You're just like everyone else.
No time to waste
but make you pace
It's okay to remove, copy, and paste
I'm doing my way
You do it your way
Don't just follow your left, find the right way
Stereotypes
Too many hypes,
But I'm the epitome of new types
Having the fear is power to my soul
'Cause I overcome them
That's how I roll
Expose your thoughts
Don't be afraid of making mistakes
Rules prevailing in
That may be your greatest rival
Believe in faith and your heart
Your true soul stop being in the shades
Come on, out in the open sun
Beauty of the child of destiny
Delightful days
are with rich density of love
Thorny path
There's no easy way for real bliss
So I keep on fighting for
Beauty of destiny
Don't get involved just for the hell of it.
Huh?
If you aren't careful, you could get hurt.
If you're gonna play, do it elsewhere.
Okay.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you two fighting again?
It's nothing, don't worry about it.
Maru-Q!
There are a bunch of Risettes?
Why does this feel so strange?
No, you're wrong!
My glasses, my glasses?
What the heck?!
Goodbye... forever.