As much as I wished for the happiness of one...
Someone else must be equally cursed.
That's how the story of a magical girl goes...
I've been such a fool.
Sayaka!
What? What are you!?
What have you done to Sayaka!?
Stand back.
Hold on tight.
What?
Do it.
This is...
If you let go of my hand, time will stop for you.
Be careful.
What's going on!? What is that witch!?
What remains of Sayaka Miki.
You saw, didn't you?
And you're running away?
Would you prefer to discard that meaningless burden and kill the witch right now?
We could do that.
No way!
As you are now, you're only a burden.
We'll come back later.
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 9 I'll never forgive that
Sayaka!?
Sayaka! What's wrong!?
Where's her Soul Gem!? What happened to Sayaka!?
Her Soul Gem transformed to a Grief Seed, and gave birth to a witch.
No... Way...
It's true.
That's the final secret of the Soul Gem.
When our jewels are enveloped in black decay, we become Grief Seeds,
and are reborn as witches.
That is the doom of all who become magical girls.
No...
No, that can't be true!
But why?
Sayaka...
Sayaka just wanted to protect people from witches... She just wanted to be an ally of justice...
That's why she became a magical girl!
So why!?
Her curse shall counterbalance her wish.
She will live cursing as many as she saved.
What are you going to do!?
Are you just gonna shrug this off!?
Why do you sound so damn proud of that!?
She's Sayaka's—
Sayaka's best friend!
You finally understand.
The true form of what you long to be.
Take care with that corpse.
Taking it to the wrong places may raise some inconvenient questions.
And you call yourself human!?
Of course not.
Neither are you.
Can I come in? I'd like to talk.
So you're alive...
Is what Homura said true?
Nothing she said bears correcting.
So you really made them all into magical girls just to make them into witches?
Don't misunderstand. We bear no ill will toward mankind.
Everything is for the sake of extending the universe's life.
Madoka, have you ever heard the term "entropy"?
To put it simply, the energy produced by burning a log is less than that expended in growing a tree.
Changing forms of energy creates losses, and the amount of energy in the universe gradually diminishes.
Thus, we sought an energy source unbound by the laws of thermodynamics.
And what we found was the power of magical girls.
What are you—
Our culture developed technology capable of converting the emotions of sentient beings into raw energy.
Unfortunately, our race lacks emotion.
Thus, we studied many races throughout the stars, before finally settling on humanity.
Taking into account humanity's vast population and short generations, the emotional energy generated
by a single human is far in excess of what is necessary for their birth and maturation.
Thus, your souls suffice as a method to reverse entropy.
And especially effective are the hope-despair cycles of females developing secondary sex characteristics.
At the moment your soul, converted to a Soul Gem, burns out and becomes a Grief Seed,
a massive burst of energy is released.
And our role as Incubators is to harvest it.
We're nothing but raw materials?
And you expect us to die for you...
Do you realize how much energy is consumed every moment in this universe crowded with life?
Someday humanity, too, shall awaken from its Earthen cradle and join our ranks.
And we certainly can't leave you a withered, dead universe, can we?
Viewed over the long term, this is a profitable exchange for you as well.
That doesn't make any sense!
Are you telling me Mami died for that kind of incomprehensible reason?
And that's why Sayaka ended up how she did?
I can't stand it! That's just too cruel!
But we always form contracts with your consent.
Is that not sufficiently conscientious?
You just tricked them!
We do not understand the concept of deception.
Why do humans abhor others for their own lapses in judgment stemming from limited understanding?
I don't even understand what you're trying to say.
I can't comprehend it at all.
And we have difficulty understanding your human values.
There are 6.9 billion of you, and ten more born every four seconds.
Why is the life or death of a single human cause for such concern?
If you think of it like that, then you must be our enemies.
Still, I came to explain our actions.
I wish you'd understand how many wonderful things your sacrifice brings forth.
But it appears you can't,
Of course I can't...
Madoka. Someday, perhaps, you will become the greatest magical girl, and then the wickedest witch.
And then we will obtain unparalleled amounts of energy.
If you ever feel like dying for the sake of the universe, just ask me.
I'll be waiting.
You're going through a lot of trouble to keep that corpse fresh. What are you planning?
How do we get her Soul Gem back?
As far as I know, it's impossible.
And you're implying that there are ways you don't know?
Magical girls surpass all reason.
No matter which absurdities you commit, I would not be surprised.
So we can .
There are no previous examples, so I don't know how. Unfortunately, I can't even offer advice.
I don't want it.
Who the heck...
wants help...
anyway!?
You don't look well, Madoka.
Are you okay?
I'm just a little tired.
And Sayaka's taking the day off.
You should probably go visit her.
I don't know if I should come along, it's kind of awkward talking to her now.
Hitomi... Um...
Can you seriously just wake up the next morning and go to school after that?
Madoka?
We need to talk. Come see me.
Sorry, Hitomi.
I'm taking today off too.
Wait, Madoka...
What did you want to talk about?
Don't you want to save Sayaka Miki?
We can save her!?
Were you just going to write her off?
Sorry, that wasn't the right way to ask.
You might think I'm stupid for this,
but I don't want to give up as long as there's any hope of saving her.
Even if she's become a witch, she may still remember her friend's voice.
If you call out to her, she may remember her humanity.
And the only one who can do it... Is probably you.
Will it really work?
I don't know.
I'm trying it because I don't know.
Maybe, just maybe, I'll cleave that witch in half,
and rather than dropping a Grief Seed, Sayaka's Soul Gem will come rolling out.
Wouldn't that be great?
Love and courage triumphing in the end.
The more I think about it, the more I realize that's why I became a magical girl.
I'd forgotten, but Sayaka reminded me.
If you don't want to come along, I won't force you.
We'll be walking on thin ice.
I can't promise I'll be able to protect you no matter what.
I'll help.
Please let me help.
I'm Madoka Kaname.
Jeez, you're not listening to a thing I say, are ya?
I'm Kyoko Sakura. Happy to meet you.
Excuse me. I don't feel well. I'm going to the nurse's office.
Who's this class's monitor?
Kaname is absent today.
Then the class rep will accompany you.
Homura's not going to help, is she?
She's not that kind of person.
Aren't you friends?
Nope.
Well, I guess there was that one time, but...
We just team up to take out witches neither of us can handle alone.
In a few days, Walpurgisnacht will arrive in this city.
Walpurgis?
A Witch Queen, so to speak.
Neither of us would be able to defeat it alone.
So we join forces.
So I guess we at least have to get along for that.
Here we are.
Is it really Sayaka?
It's not another witch, is it?
The magic pattern is the same as yesterday.
It has to be her.
All right, I'll ask you one more time.
Are you prepared for this?
I've gotten used to it.
I'm always watching from behind...
Even though I've never been able to do anything to help...
Still, please. Take me along.
Man, you're weird.
Hey, Kyoko...
I always make other people fight for me, rather than doing anything myself...
I'm a coward, aren't I?
Why would you become a magical girl?
Why?
I mean, give me a break.
This job isn't for everyone.
But...
Every day you eat your fill surrounded by your happy family. Your life lacks nothing.
And you decide to become a magical girl on a whim?
I'll never forgive that.
You'd be my first target.
Risking your life is for people who have no other choice.
People who do have other options and still butt in just to entertain themselves...
That's just insulting.
I guess...
Someday, a time may come when you have to put your life on the line even though you don't want to.
You should only consider it then.
Kyoko, why do you—
She spotted us.
Here she comes!
Go ahead. Just how we planned.
Sayaka...
It's me! Madoka!
Can you hear me?
Can you recognize my voice!?
Don't hesitate. Keep calling out to her.
Sayaka... Please, remember me and stop this...
You would never want to do this, Sayaka!
You were supposed to be an ally of justice!
Please! Change back into the old Sayaka!
If you're not gonna listen, Sayaka, I've got another way!
Kyoko!
Don't worry... I can take this...
Keep calling out to Sayaka!
Stop it!
Please, stop it!
Sayaka! Recognize us!
Are you paying me back?
The first time we met was in mortal combat...
Back then, I thought you didn't have any determination, but no matter how many times
I beat you you just would've kept standing back up, right?
Are you angry? Will you never forgive me?
I understand.
Once you've had your revenge, you'll wake up.
Sayaka...
Please...
Sayaka!
You told me you believed!
You believed this power could be used to make people happy!
Please, God...
Just once in my life, show me a happy dream...
Kyoko...
Hey.
You...
Take care of her. This was all my bad idea.
You're all about fighting without burdens, right?
You were right.
Just as long as there's one thing you'd give anything to protect...
I always thought that was what I was doing, but...
Go.
I'll handle her.
Don't worry, Sayaka.
It hurts to be lonely, doesn't it.
Fine. I'll stay with you.
Sayaka.
Kyoko.
Kyoko Sakura truly hoped she could save Sayaka Miki.
Really? Wasn't it obviously impossible?
Then why didn't you stop her?
Of course I'd have stopped her if her sacrifice would have been in vain.
But her loss carries significant meaning.
With this, you are the only magical girl who will stand against Walpurgisnacht.
And of course, alone you cannot win.
The only way to protect this city is for Madoka to become a magical girl.
I won't let that happen. No matter what.
Illustration: Namaniku ATK (Nitroplus)
No one believes their future.
No one can accept their future.
Episode 10 I'll never rely on anyone again
Episode 10 I'll never rely on anyone again.
I'll never rely on anyone again.