Round, and round, and round, and round... There!
The sports showdown event is the 50 meter freestyle suggested by Kawashima-san!
Lucky!
What did you write?
If I win, we'll open an exhibition for those imitation videos.
And if I win, Takasu-kun will spend the summer with me at my mansion.
You'll be all alone during the summer...
If you know the answer, come up and write it on the board.
Yes!
As expected from the class representative.
Hey...
Dummy.
The first Takasu competition.
Ami-tan versus Tenori Taiga.
Bet in increments of 500 Tirol.
What the heck is this?
Will this even be a real competition?
When it comes to swimming, of course Ami-tan is going to win!
Taiga was sinking.
I wish I was in Takasu's position.
Bastards...
Ami is mine, sorry guys. Arl.
Was he trying to write "all"?
Isn't he in trouble if he can't even write "all"?
Haruta, you...
Never mind that, everyone is thinking only about themselves.
What?
W-What's wrong, Aisaka?
If you've figured it out, I'd like you to come to the front and answer it on the board.
A-Aisaka-san?
Don't be afraid, Taiga!
Do it as if you were washing your face.
C'mon, one more time!
Just because you say that...
She can't even get her face underwater?
She's way out-classed.
Is this even a competition? It's obvious who's going to win.
Just forget about what people say about your swimming skills.
I got it already!
She can't just give up. She's got to try hard for Takasu too.
Who does?!
Who does what?
Kitamura-kun!
You're doing great. Just keep working with Takasu and good luck on your competition.
What? Working?
Hey, Taiga!
No matter what happens, I won't practice during class anymore.
Image training is good enough!
Save lines like that after you can put your face underwater.
What's for dinner today?
Peas in eggs, tofu steak, miso soup, spinach, and deep-fried tofu...
I want meat, not all beans!
Don't complain. Beans are the meat of the fields!
Stingy.
More importantly, make sure you practice when we have time in the pool!
Once you've changed your mind.
I won't change my mind...
Kitamura-kun's watching.
All the more reason to try hard!
You...
Whose fault is it that I have to work so hard to fix this misunderstanding?
Who...?
Isn't it to keep Kitamura from going to Kawashima's mansion?
Ouch!
Enough! You just worry about making my food.
What is this...
Hey, hurry up and make it.
I'm going to get a lot of good food, then practice like crazy.
It keeps raining.
Looks like the pool will be closed today.
Just when I'm able to put my face underwater...
Why can't we use the pool?!
Don't get angry at me!
Swimming pool tickets?
Please use them!
I'm betting on Aisaka too.
Because Takasu bet on Aisaka so confidently when that paper went around, I thought, "Alright! Me too!"
On me?
Yeah.
B-B-But I can't swim!
Aisaka is the type that works hard under fire.
We don't know how the fight is going to go!
Can't we make the tickets like this?
What are you doing?
S-S-Shut up!
Well...
Keep working hard during practice!
Idiot.
Want to stop somewhere on the way home?
How about a cafe?
Sounds good.
What are you doing in a place like that?
So gloomy.
This narrow space is making me feel comfortable.
Alright...
Takasu-kun, in tired-mode?
Yeah, because of a certain someone, I've been pretty tired lately.
Who is that? Ami-chan doesn't know.
Hey, you...
It's cute. Taiga being jealous.
How is she jealous?
She just doesn't like you.
Takasu-kun, are you an idiot?
Look who's talking.
Anyway, don't provoke Taiga so much.
What's with this mansion plan?
It's not like you wanted to invite me in the first place.
I'm serious.
I seriously plan to win and spend my summer with you.
I'm really thinking about what will happen after I win fairly.
I think it'll be fun!
We're pretty compatible, aren't we?
We're not!
You got mad!
You...
Keep your teasing under control.
Okay...
Bye bye.
I know.
W-What? Who knows what?
The one who made Taiga's swimsuit so great was Takasu-kun!
That's...
You don't have to hide it, it was very easy to figure out, Akechi-kun.
Taiga told me about it before, "Ryuji is always there for me."
Cleaning, sewing buttons, ironing...
What, just that stuff?
That stuff is the most amazing.
Hey, Kushieda.
I believe in you.
I'm leaving Taiga to you.
O-Okay...
Because I'm the judge, I can't help, but my feelings are with you guys.
Leave it to me!
Alright!
Alright. Please let tomorrow be good weather, let tomorrow be good weather...
Thank you, Teruteru Bozu-san.
At least the weather is good.
Look, Ryuji.
It looks like I'm swimming, right?
It's about time we start practicing seriously.
What's with this?
The competition is tomorrow!
What's the point of practicing the crawl now?
You just have to use anything you can!
This is so uncool.
Alright, you're doing good. Try kicking.
I got it!
Hey!
T-Taiga!
That was amazing, Taiga!
Your kicking power really is something else!
You might be able to win!
Win? Me?
I wasn't doing anything special.
Of course you can't let down your guard, but...
I see.
I... Can win. I see.
Taiga?
I'll win.
R-Right! That's the spirit.
It doesn't look like it's going to stop anytime soon.
Just when you were getting into it.
What do you want to do?
Go home?
Keep at it?
Yeah?
That's right.
You don't want to waste the effort Kitamura went through giving us these tickets.
That's not it!
Not that...
The reason I'm trying hard is...
I know, I know! Let's show Kawashima too.
Nevermind. I'm wasting my breath.
What's that?
Is it for me?
I see!
If I'm not here, there won't be anyone to cook for you.
I keep telling you, it's not like...
But don't overdo it.
Even if you lose, it just means I can relax at Kawashima's mansion.
I'll ask her to leave Kitamura out of it.
I'll make all the food at once and put it in the fridge. You won't have to worry about that stuff.
Your true colors are showing!
You wanted to go from the start! To Ami-chan's mansion!
What's with that?
Well, it's not like it matters to me when, where, or who you're panting after!
What the hell's that?
When I'm trying to be really understanding here.
Who asked you to?!
You've been weird lately!
From that thing before with Kawashima...
You're still going on about that?!
You! What are you so mad about?!
What?
People who talk like they understand the feelings in my heart...
That's what I hate!
It makes me mad!
Why don't you get it?
Do you want me to understand or not? Which is it?
I don't know!
How can anyone understand what I'm feeling?
Even... Even...
Even I don't understand.
What did you say?
Hey!
I said that I won't compete, just how you wanted it.
Itchy.
I didn't do anything wrong, did I?
Huh?
Ryu-chan?
Why are you still awake?
I'm home!
Taiga-chan didn't come?
Why?
Did you have a fight with her?
Taiga said I didn't matter, and that irritated me. I think...
Is that so?
But, you understand, right?
Taiga-chan always says the opposite of what she feels.
It's not like it doesn’t matter anymore...
Yacchan thinks if she really hated you, no matter how hungry she was, she wouldn't eat the same food as you.
You haven't even taken off your makeup.
Come on, stand up.
You haven't eaten anything right?
Actually... I really wanted it to be sunny.
I hope you'll fight with everything you got...
Um, that is...
Whatever you may think, I wanted you to win and...
Win and I...?
I'll take the lunch, since it's just an innocent thing.
But...
It was raining for so long, my regular bathing suit wouldn't dry.
But I wonder if this is against the rules? I'm worried.
That gorgeous Ami-tan is going to swim in the pool, right?
That's so she can go with Takasu to her mansion, right?
Why is it always Takasu? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Why is it always Takasu?
Knock it off!
It's not like I'm going to the mansion for sure!
There's no way Taiga's going to win.
How can you tell...
When she hasn't even tried yet?
That idiot.
This time it's all meat.
Hey, hey!
How long are you going to make us wait?
It's hot!
Why isn't she coming? Tenori Taiga?
It's all good.
Just think of it as coming out to see that bikini.
Yeah.
Hey... Making people wait any longer in this heat...
Yeah...
What are you blabbering about all by yourselves?
Alright, let's have a fair fight, Stupid Chihuahua... Today, you're Stupid Bikini.
What's that?
Taiga!
You're going to swim like that?
For a second there I thought she was armed or something.
Isn't she kind of cool?
Let's begin!
The 50 meter freestyle competition!
On your mark!
Get set!
Hair.
Shi-
I can't believe it! I can't believe it! I can't believe it!
Tenori Taiga has used a frightening strategy to take the lead!
Damn you, you puny tiger!
Taiga!
Has something happened to Taiga?
Is this a chance for Ami? She's going!
Damn!
Are you okay? Did your leg cramp up?
Idiot! Let me go! I can still go!
It's impossible now!
I'm going!
But you...
You're happy, right?
Huh?
Not "Huh?"!
Your owner is fighting so hard for you, so be happier!
You spiteful dog.
You're doing great, Ami-chan!
Now the tables are turned!
Alright! Then go!
Use your tail or whatever to make it through this.
So...
Ami-chan!
Idiot! Don't push! That's dangerous!
Ryuji!
Huh?
Taiga?
Takasu! Hey, Takasu! Are you okay?
Alright, he's breathing.
Aisaka, hurry, to the nurse's office...
Don't touch him!
Taiga?
But, Aisaka...
Shut up!
You're all idiots!
Why didn't you notice? Why didn't you save him?
You were all so focused on that Stupid Bikini...
No one... Ryuji...
Ryuji is mine!
No one touch him!
Hey, I decided to go too, to your mansion.
I lost the fight, right?
Ryuji is going, right?
There won't be anyone to take care of me, right?
That's why I decided to go.
Wait a second.
Don't decide everything for yourself, Ami-chan is confused.
Why not?
It's more fun with everyone.
I see!
Aisaka-san, you're anxious about being separated from Takasu-kun.
After all, "Ryuji is mine!" right?
That's right.
I'll admit it.
That is...
After all...
He's my dog.
As an owner, I have the responsibility to watch over my dog and make sure he isn't panting after other people.
What? Were you expecting something else?
No...
Nothing.
Alright, let's decide on the schedule.
What, what?
I'm busy with my part time job around here...
It's too bad it can't just be the two of us.
But we still have more chances.
And this is how the curtain closed on the first term of Takasu Ryuji's second year of high school.
And the exciting beginning of summer vacation.
Going to the mansion with Kushieda!
Won't I get struck down for being so fortunate, Taiga?
Kitamura-kun's dim seaweed...