When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Milady!
Mi-la-dy!
She's nowhere to be found.
This is strange.
She's not even here.
Where did Milady go?
Senpai!
What's the matter, Milady?
Senpai. Please use this sports towel.
I'll be cheering for you during your game today!
Wh-What game?
This is so embarrassing!
Milady is broken!
Nagi is working on drawing a new manga.
Manga?
She's going to try a youth love story.
She's right. I thought my pen would move on its own if I acted the part, but...
No! I can't draw anything!
Are you all right, Milady?
I was able to do well until I was midway through, but...
"Well"?
Well, it is.
I can't get this important scene,
where the heroine of the story, Iglesias Nobue,
who loves Oosotogari Chadao, the captain of the prestigious Kabaddi club of St. Yamaimo Academy,
finally goes on a date with Chadao after many misunderstandings, to go anywhere, nowhere, and a bulldog goes "woof".
Is that really a youth love story?
It sounds very complicated.
Why? Why is it that such a prodigy as myself can't draw anymore?
You shouldn't get so worked up.
I know!
I can't draw because I don't have any references.
Huh?
That has to be it!
Therefore, Hayate!
Yes?
Go gather references for me at once!
References?
I want you to capture the trendy date spots teenagers nowadays like to go to!
What? But I don't have a clue about trendy date spots.
"Stop talking back! It's your master's crisis! Get going already."
Is that what you want to say?
Oh boy. I've never been on a date myself.
What a rare teenager.
Leave me alone!
All right, I shall.
Where should I even go?
Would Harajuku be a standard date spot?
I said leave me alone!
Harajuku...
Eh?!
Um... Ah... Ah...
W-W-W-Wou-Would... Would you be...
Maria-san?!
Yes.
You were in your casual clothes,
so I couldn't tell it was you for a second.
Y-You got me wondering who the pretty dresser was.
I do wear this kind of clothes from time to time.
Oh, by the way, may I accompany you?
Eh?
EH?!?!?!
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
A date with Maria-san?
I get it. This episode's punch line has to be that I'm dreaming.
That's right. That has to be it!
Oh, so Milady said she wants to be alone?
Yes, like this.
Going to a flashback?
Thank you for going through the trouble of filling me in.
It's... not... working...
I can't draw anything no matter what I do.
I get it!
I can't concentrate because there's a person!
Person?
Me?
Maria! I'll give you a day off today!
Relay that to Klaus, too! I want to be alone!
Okay...
Klaus-san! Nagi sai-
Various people work for the Sanzenin, but the mansion is empty.
It's because Nagi doesn't like having attendants.
That's how it went.
The last picture didn't make any sense.
So after demanding reference material, she started sending people away, heh?
It's as if she's a popular manga artist.
Even if she tells me to take a break, I don't have any immediate needs.
Therefore, I'll be going out with you today, Hayate-kun.
Going out?!
Go... Going...
Would I be in your way?
Nononononono. Well, um, you see...
For you and me to go out...
I thought I would go out with you
on your hunt for Nagi's references.
Oh, that's what you meant.
Of course.
Yes! Yes! I'm making great progress!
Milady!
Why the sudden break?!
An old man like me doesn't have anywhere to go.
Shut up!
It's just one day, so go waste your time at an arcade or internet cafe!
Don't cry, Klaus. Think of your age.
How unsightly.
Wow, so many couples.
Couples...
What's wrong, Hayate-kun?
No, I think I'm getting people sick because I got used to living in the mansion.
But, I must collect good references for Milady's sake!
Now, what else should I take pictures of?
We should go to Takeshita Street.
Takeshita Street?
Yes, if I'm correct, you'll see a House with ***** by the entrance.
And there are T***** Valentine House, ***zan, and Nori****.
Um, from how many years ago is that?
Oh, and that's the famous Ma-
NO! We can't say that even with bleeps!
But strange. They're all gone.
Yes, I think they disappeared quite a while ago.
As we've been saying several times,
Maria-san is a fresh seventeen year old.
I did bring the guidebook, so let's just walk around here.
Huh? Maria-san?
Maria-san, did you want to try on clothes?
No.
Oh please. I'm absolutely, negligibly, completely not thinking things like...
...I'm interested in the latest trends,
want to try current fashions, or love dressing up.
That so?
But, it looks like it'll be a good reference source for Milady, so let's go take a look around.
You're right. Can't avoid it if it's for her.
In that case, just a little.
Yes.
Hayate-kun, look at this! So many cute clothes!
This one-piece looks really nice.
Please take your time and enjoy.
Maria-san is a normal girl after all.
Um.
Yes?
Hayate-kun...
Can I... try it on?
Wow...
Nice.
Amazing!
Hey, you're in the way! Shoo!
They're all great. You look nice in everything.
Don't say that...
From now on, call me the Ebi-chan of the anime world.
You're being too full of yourself.
What's wrong with that?!
Nothing.
She looks good! She looks nice! She looks great!
Hey there, boyfriend.
B-B-Boyfriend?
You should try on some clothes, too.
I'll coordinate some good looking ones.
I meant it as a joke, but you guys look great.
Wonderful!
So good!
A nice couple!
It's a little embarrassing.
What should we do?
It's so good.
You can't miss this if you're at Harajuku.
But it's boring.
There's nothing else here that attracts me other than the crepes.
We came since Yukiji said there's a civilization that sells live bamboo shoots.
How strange.
She's thinking about Takenoko-zoku.
Takenoko = Bamboo shoot
And those of you who don't know what Takenoko-zoku is,
you should ask the adults around you or Maria-san.
Takenoko-zoku: 	Group of people who danced in streets of Harajuku to disco music in 1979 and 1980.
Oh well. Once we eat this, let's go back to school and take a nap.
What? We just got here!
And we've only been on screen for three scenes!
If only there was something exciting...
I found it!
I'm sorry. You even bought me clothes.
It's fine.
That newly formed looking couple is...
It's our best friend, Hayata-kun!
Who knew Hayata-kun had such a beautiful girlfriend?
No, that's Nagi-chan's maid.
Wow, I couldn't tell with her casual outfit.
So it's maid and butler love in Harajuku, eh?
All right then! Let us support their date!
It's part of a teacher's duty to teach students the correct way to date.
Work? You're just having fun.
But this is  interesting.
Hey, if the two get married,
do you think they'll let us make speeches?
Forget speeches! We'll be the guests of honor!
We'll take the lead in toasting!
We'll gulp down the Dom Pérignon.
Therefore, everyone go!
Aye, aye, yo!
The silence is getting awkward.
What should we talk about in these situations?
Th-The saleslady earlier said we were a couple, didn't she?
Yes, how strange of her to think that we're a couple.
As a matter of a fact...
Where's the need for us to feel so restless?
Um...
L-L-Let's take some pictures around here for Milady's sake.
Y-Y-Yes, you're right.
Want me to take the picture?
You think you're disguised just by wearing an afro?
It's afro people, destroying the Harajuku atmosphere.
Excuse me, who are you?
As you can see, I'm a genius photographer!
And her assistants!
The tension they're speaking with doesn't make me feel like it's our first time meeting.
Maybe someone you know from a past life?
Their hearts are throbbing so much,
they can't see through such simple disguises.
Afros are fearesome, indeed.
My blood as a photographer is boiling!
Please let me use you two as my models.
No, thank you.
Okay, let's publish a photo collection.
The title will be Love Diary 2007!
Decided!
Thank you very much.
Then will you-
What are you accepting?
But they're saying they would.
Absolutely not.
They're suspicious no matter how you look at them.
They're too suspicious.
You're too vulnerable.
Nice.
They talk you into taking more and more pictures. It's dangerous.
Nice!
Great!
These people pretend to take normal pictures and gradually move on to wilder pictures.
Get them closer!
Now the kiss!
STOP IT!
That's enough from Harajuku. Let's go somewhere else.
Ah, yes.
Why are they going away?
Didn't they seem bothered?
They're just embarrassed.
So cute!
And so they moved on to the next date spot.
Meanwhile...
Milday's pen was still not moving.
Hey, Hayate!
Maria! Tea!
Oh, right. I'm alone in this mansion right now.
Oh well. A little walk should refresh me.
Th-This is Hayate's room, isn't it?
And... the door is... left open.
No, I mustn't!
I can't enter someone else's room without permission!
Everyone has their privacy!
Yes. I won.
Is this a prank played by fate?
Or a result of passion?
The pen is...
In this situation, would I...
Boya boya shiteruto oitecchai masuyo.
Boya boya shiteruto oitecchai masuyo = I'll leave you behind if you lazzle dazzle.
Yorokonde tsuite mairimasu. Ha-to
Yorokonde tsuite mairimasu = I'll gladly follow you *heart*
I-It's because I don't have a choice.
About what?
It's because I have to pick up the pen I dropped.
So you did go in.
It's out of my control.
To whom are you making excuses?
Besides, it's Hayate's fault, too.
He should lock his door when he leaves.
I-It's his desk!
So, this is where Hayate always sits and studies.
Wh-What am I doing?!
Why am I making such a commotion over entering a boy's room?
B-But I'm not feeling well, so I'm going to take a little nap.
Only because I'm not feeling well!
You don't need to make excuses anymore.
What am I trying to do?!
Shoot, I'm starting to get dizzy.
I'll get out of here and continue with drawing my manga.
Where's my pen...
Wait, this is!
Could it be one of those books filled with naked females? Something all teenage boys are said to secretly own?
Hayate owned such a thing behind my back?
No, Hayate wouldn't!
But as his master and girlfriend, I must...
Attractive Bro?
He swings that way?!
She couldn't accept it.
The Lady found my secret fun reading.
So it was you who swings that way!
Oh, are we at Asakusa?
Yes. It's only thirty minutes away by subway.
I'm half lucky.
How about you?
Please don't ask.
Ah, it's hot.
Calm down and eat.
Hayate-kun!
Look at this!
Which one?
It's so cute.
I enjoyed it casually without thinking.
What was I thinking, grabbing on to Hayate-kun's sleeve.
Anyone want a ride?
It'll be cheap.
A rickshaw?
All the trendy date spots.
We'll show you everything.
Looks like it's perfect for the manga references.
You're right, then...
Give us a ride.
At your service.
Here we go!
We'll really get this going!
It's fast.
An amazing amount of G-force, too.
Off we go to the date course that will develop the two's love!
John-kun, living at the Tanakas at Higashi Koiwa, Edogawa-ku, is good at math problems.
This is a date spot?
And he got it wrong, too.
Next, Museum of Parasites.
What do you want us to do after coming here for a date?
This is a little...
Please live happily ever after like parasites.
This is a famous haunted area.
If you're lucky, you might get to see a woman hanging down from the ceiling.
Don't bring us to such a scary place.
Maybe this would work if it were summer.
Last stop is here.
It's a company that makes lots of fun anime.
The person acting Tsukishima ****o-chan came, too.
This is the end of the trip?
Please make sure to eat and sleep enough.
How was it? Did you enjoy the romantic moments?
We're back where we started.
But it was a rare experience.
Well, if you say so.
She took my digital camera!
Come on! Just hurry up and kiss already!
You're that phony photographer!
You're too persistent!
The Sumida is my ocean.
The ship's leaving!
We're getting on! We're getting on!
It's done!
It's pretty good.
Good thing I came to sweets class.
How wonderful!
It's nothing much.
It's about love.
Grazie to the how spectacular it is!
I've never seen a student make anything this amazing!
Thank you very much.
Grazie.
I lost...
Looks like we got away from that.
Yes.
Wait!
We're pumping up the date for you, so at least get a kiss in! A kiss!
Th-They're still coming after us.
What bothersome people.
At this rate, they're likely to chase us down to the ends of the Earth until they manage to take a picture of us kissing.
In order to... In order to protect Maria-san...
I'll show you that a difference in boat does not equal the difference in ability!
Go!
Jump out, youth!
Your head is mine!
Don't be hiding! It's useless! Useless! Useless!
Are you ready?
Don't come!
Stop that nonsense!
If you come any closer, I'll jump off of here!
Why? Why are you saying this all of a sudden?
What is this?
One of those lovers' quarrels?
I'm sorry. I have someone else I love other than you.
S-Someone you love?
He's a crewman on a tuna fishing boat.
I couldn't meet him over half the year, but...
It's better for you to forget about such a man!
I'll-
It's impossible!
Even if I can't see him...
I still...
Love him!
N-No!
I love him more than you, more than semi-fatty tuna, and more than fatty tuna.
So please forget about me.
Goodbye!
Wait.
Wait...
I...
You stupid ocean!
Did we just...
...witness the end of a love?
Poor Hayata-kun.
First loves are weak and sad.
Let's leave the boy with a broken heart alone.
You're right. Time shall cure him.
We'll leave what we saw today in our small memories.
So they locked the memory of the love in their heart.
Okay!
Let's go eat monjya at Tsukishima!
Agreed!
And they never recalled this day, ever.
Maria-san!
Hayate-kun.
We were able to get them off of us.
It was your amazing acting.
It really was nothing.
But, what could they have been?
Let's forget about them. I'm sure we'll never see them again.
How about we head home now?
I bet Milady is waiting-
Please wait.
Yes?
Hayate-kun, how about a ride on that before we go?
Thank you very much for today, Maria-san.
Oh, thank you, too.
But, next time, I hope you can go on a date with someone you really like.
Um, er...
What's the best way to answer this?
But before that, how about we bring Nagi along and go on a triple date?
Yes, I'd love to.
Oh, how about we take one for the end?
What do you think, Milady?
Isn't it well taken?
We also took pictures at Harajuku and Asakusa, so I'm sure you can draw a good manga.
I... think?
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
While I was having so much trouble, you were out enjoying yourself?!
So, how about you all ask out your boyfriend or girlfriend and go out on a romantic date?
Only if you have one to go with, that is.
If you do.
Stop picking fights with the viewers!
Next week, we'll fight against problems the elderly carry.
Wataru and...
Saki's...
Butler Network!
Hey. It's Tachibana Wataru.
I'm Kijima Saki.
The theme song for Rental Video Tachibana is finally complete, so we're here today to introduce it.
What? This song was the shop's theme song?
Yeah. You didn't know?
But there's not a single word of
"Rental Video Tachibana" in the lyrics.
Well, that's, you know, it's the shop's image song.
But don't rent the song, buy it!
Sir! Any more than that is-
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Bye.
I had a strange dream of being the owner of a coffee bean field in Brazil and doing nothing.
Sure. If you want to retire, go ahead.
What?!
I wonder what happened to Klaus-san. He looks so sad.
Nagi telling him to quit must have been a real shock.
I am the master's shadow.
When I realize I can no longer be of help to Milady, I just silently disappear.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Klaus is Japanese because the kanji is 倉臼.
Did you know? Saigou Takamori's real name is Takanaga.