Chestnut
mochi now
available
Hello. This is Tamaya.
Oh, Kanna!
Huh? Right now?
I'm helping out at the shop!
I guess it's going okay. How about you?
Superb!
Wow, really? Oh, right.
This chestnut mochi thing is just superb!
We've started making chestnut mochi, so why don't you come over and try some?
I shall have one more—
Yeah, that's right!
You're eating too much.
Huh? Business?
I'm so very sorry!
"Mister"?
Oh, you mean Dela?
He's here.
Got it. I'll be right there.
Stars and Clowns
Hello.
'Sup.
Oh, so it was you who wanted to see me.
'Sup, Mister.
Come back to your senses, little lass!
There. There!
Please, let's not get into this now.
So, what's up?
You have business with Dela?
I wanted to give this to him.
Ta-da!
Wow.
Is that supposed to be a house for Dela?
Mister
Yes.
I had some extra planks, so I decided to make something for Mister.
A tribute, huh? A tribute, isn't it?
I'll gladly accept it, my girl.
Wow, that's awesome!
Impressive as always, Kanna.
You're really skilled for someone so young.
She just acts coldly out of embarrassment, I suppose.
I guess I got a little serious this time.
Oh, you!
I am much obliged, little lass.
You needn't go so far for the likes of Dela.
I must object to that statement, even if it was one made by Lady Choi!
The populace has great confidence in me, Dela Mochidis Gusting.
This is all due to my virtues as a person—
No, as a bird—
Yeah, whatever you say.
Why don't you try getting in?
Very well then. One giant leap for birdkind...
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Well... This entrance is a bit cramped.
No way! It can't be!
One, two!
Ah, choo!
You're being quite intense, my girl.
Is this an expression of your love to me?
That was an utter failure.
Huh?
To think I'd get the size wrong...
Huh? What do you mean?
A carpenter getting measurements wrong is an inexcusable mistake.
A once-in-a-lifetime shame.
I'll reduce this to sawdust at once.
Mister
Don't!
It'd be a waste!
Wait, little lass.
The fault does not lie with you,
but with Dela.
He's put on even more weight.
In fact, he ate two chestnut mochi right before coming here.
Dela sure does love our mochi and steamed buns!
That doesn't mean—
You've got it wrong!
It's not that I love mochi.
Mochi loves me!
So what?
Huh?
You know what this calls for.
A diet.
Oh, yeah.
So, do we start off with exercise?
No. We need to limit his food intake.
Limit my...
food intake...
Until you can fit in here at the very least.
N-No! Please don't!
There are other ways to lose weight besides—
Do it.
Yes, ma'am.
In the fall, the sky grows clear and blue as horses grow stout.
A fall filled with appetite.
And yet, I am starving!
Saury Season
Come again!
Woe is me.
Welcome!
The saddest sight in the world is not a bird that cannot fly, but a bird that cannot eat!
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
Come again!
The bird?
O Mochi...
Can you see me?
I'm right here.
Do you wanna eat our mochi?
I'm right here!
Well, no wonder.
Compared to Mamedai's old-fashioned mochi,
our brand new avant-garde mochi is like a breath of fresh air!
Darkness closing in... but I see a light in the distance...
Here, have one!
It's our new Halloween mochi recipe!
Oh my!
Well, if you don't mind...
All this needs is some soy sauce, a dash of sweet wine, garlic and ginger to taste, and to be marinated in—
Wh-What's with that scary chant?
What's this all about?
Do not feed the bird.
Dela's on a diet now.
Here you go, Mister.
Do not feed the Mister
What's this?
Something I made.
For you.
Do not feed the Mister
Episode 8
I Won't Let Them Call Me a Chicken!
Yeah, now that you mention it...
He's looking a bit plumper than before.
I feel sorry for you, but as long as you're overweight...
See you once you've lost weight.
Soy pulp is low on calories.
Well, if you insist!
That negligent attitude will send you right back to being a chicken.
At least let me have this much!
Silence.
What?
Dela's on a diet?
Maybe I should go on one too.
What're ya talkin' 'bout? Yer just a child!
No, I'm not!
But yeah, getting too fat isn't good.
He overindulged himself on your kindness.
That's not true!
But Dela being that fat hinders your fortune-telling, doesn't it?
In that case, I feel a little sorry for him, but he's gotta get through this.
Huh? Grandpa?!
Grandpa?
Hey there.
We're doing this for Dela's sake.
You say that, but I feel so sorry for him.
I think hunger is the hardest thing in the world to endure.
Yeah. Dad's right.
I know what you mean, but...
Not now!
You can't sneak him food!
Tell me before you—
Hey, Grandpa!
Grandpa and Dad are the biggest dangers here.
Yeah. They're bound to try and feed him when no one's looking.
I'll keep an eye on Dela.
I'll make sure that no one feeds him any mochi.
What?!
No mochi?
No mochi.
Oh, I know. I'll take Dela to school!
That way I can keep watch on him from up close.
I'll go too.
I can't let you do all the work.
No, no, no, no, no! You needn't go that far!
You're thinking of getting Grandpa to feed you mochi while she's away, right?
I can see right through you.
B-But wait! You'll stick out like a sore thumb at school!
Besides, you don't seem to possess much knowledge of this place.
You need certain qualifications in order to gain entry into a "school."
What qualifications?
Huh?
Uh, um...
Uh...
You mean like passing an exam and having a uniform?
That's right!
Like passing an exam and having a uniform.
You needn't worry.
I'm smart.
An exam is nothing.
B-But what about the uniform?
Uniform?
That.
Oh, that outfit.
Indeed.
You can't go to school unless you wear those clothes.
Oh, no.
This is so unfortunate.
Don't worry.
Huh?
I've taken a liking to those clothes as well.
I'd wear them.
Really?
I'm happy to hear you like them too, Choi.
It's very nice indeed.
Everyone wears similar clothes.
It makes you all look like friends.
That's the first time I've heard it put that way.
That being said, we don't have any spare uniforms.
Oh, right.
What do we do?
Oh, well. That's too bad.
I've got a spare.
If you're okay with my cousin's uniform, that is.
Stars and Clowns
I'm looking forward to this!
Yeah.
Sorry to keep you.
Have these while you wait.
I could use some luck to start the day with.
Thanks!
Go ahead.
So these are supposed to bring good luck?
Yeah, like Ichiro's morning curry.
Oh, I see.
Ichiro's curry, huh?
My girls.
Can you find it in your hearts to give me a taste?
Yeah, I want to.
But I can't.
We're doing all this for your own good, Mister.
Really, now.
I guess I'll have to give up on that.
This is delicious!
But it makes me sad!
Yeah, it's great!
But it's so great that I can't bear it!
This is too much!
Are you done yet, Tamako?
Coming!
Is this really all right?
It's fine!
I have to say, this feels really weird.
It's not like me at all!
That's just your imagination.
You look great.
Thanks for waiting!
H-How do I look?
Totally cute!
I know, right?
I-I see.
I hope it doesn't smell too badly of mothballs.
It's been in our closet for ages.
It's okay!
I'm really grateful for all this.
Now I've caused trouble for you, just like Dela.
Don't mention it. Happy to be of service.
You can do it, Mister!
Do it for the house Kanna made for you!
Actually, while we're at it, why not keep up the diet until he's back to his former self?
Are you even human?!
Come on. Stop whining.
You'll get to see Shiori once you get to school!
Huh?
Shiori?
The girl Dela li—
What do you think you're saying?!
Finding a bride for the prince is our top priority,
and yet you've been wasting time on some infatuation?
I have not!
Just shut your beak and focus on your diet.
Yes, ma'am!
Tamako Market
Good morning!
Here. They're slippers.
Feel free to use these, Choi.
I will, thanks.
Oh, I'll go put my bag away.
We've got social studies first period.
Midori'll be with us too.
Heave-ho.
There we go.
Thanks, little lass.
No problem.
You must be a real prodigy to be here in the same class as Tamako and the others.
Uh, just to confirm...
...you don't think Kanna's younger than you or anything, do you?
Huh?
I—
I knew it.
I-I apologize!
It seems I've been operating under a grave misunderstanding.
This is quite shocking. I grew five centimeters taller last year, too.
Please forgive my terribly rude presump—
Don't worry, Choi.
Now that you're wearing that uniform, we're fellow students!
What she said.
Fellow students?
Yup!
Morning.
Huh?
And a very good morning to you too, Shiori.
Uh...
Allow me to introduce her.
This is the temporary exchange student who will be attending class with us,
Choi Mochidis Gusting.
And this is Mister, who will be pretending to be a stuffed toy.
Now that you mention it, I get the feeling that I didn't not hear about something like that...
No, I certainly did.
Uh...
Do you have a textbook?
She can share mine!
Feel free to ask me if you don't understand something.
Got it.
There are three important points that you need to remember.
My girl...
What do you want?
The first being Adam Smith's laissez-faire economy.
Could you move my leg for me, please?
The second being the collective capitalism that Japan follows.
I believe in you. You can get through this!
Well, of course.
As interim captain, I hereby declare that we'll be practicing with these members today.
Understood!
Interim captain?
What's that?
Imagine I put "aspiring" after it in brackets.
So it's not just a hope, but an aspiration?
She's so cute!
Nice to meet you!
Choi? That's quite an unusual name.
My girls. I must inform you that I am cute as well.
Where are you from?
You come over here.
What do you want, my—
We told you you're on a diet, didn't we?
Do I need to do even more?
You just need some soy sauce, a dash of sweet wine, garlic and ginger to taste, and to be marinated in—
Why, I've had a sudden change of heart!
Good.
I'm going to be especially hard on him, Choi.
Sure, go ahead.
All right. Everyone form a circle!
I've been meaning to ask for a while now,
but what's that stick supposed to be?
What do you think it is?
I haven't the faintest idea.
You will when I hit you with it.
Fare thee well, my girl.
I was just kidding.
Mister.
What?
I was kidding about kidding.
What?!
Watch out! These things hurt!
Hang in there, Dela!
I call violence! This is harassment, I say!
I call it "bird twirling."
This is too much! I'm going to die!
I'll be an ex-bird before I lose any weight!
Don't lie to me. I know you've got some more in you.
Lady Choi! My sides are aching!
Fine. I'll let you take a break...
Lady Choi!
...after we're done.
Good one, Choi.
I-I can't take this anymore!
Oh, Shiori!
Shiori.
I'm currently working as hard as I can to become a stronger man for you.
Wow, birdminton.
Come on. Time for another round.
Yes, ma'am.
Pose!
Dela, are you okay?
Throwing in the towel so early? You're pathetic.
Tomorrow will be more of the same, you hear me?
No way!
Lady Choi, could it be that seeing me in my weakened state has set your heart alig—
Certainly not.
Of course.
Choi grew up in the tropics, so maybe she's finding fall in Japan a bit too cold?
Especially in the evenings.
It's hot all year round where you live, isn't it, Choi?
Pretty much.
So this is your first fall?
First fall?
The first time she's experienced fall!
You're making it sound like it's the first time she's fallen in love.
How about you buy some new clothes, Choi?
I'm okay with just this uniform.
Uniforms don't count as fashion!
Choi, how does a knitted dress sound?
With some hand-knitted motifs!
No, I'd much rather see her in a frilly white dress.
I think she'll look cute no matter what she wears!
Come on. Let's get you something new to wear!
Count me in!
What should I go with? Bohemian? Military?
Trad? Fluffy stuff?
Dressing up, eh?
Hey, let's go check some out, Choi!
In that case, I'll let you pick something out for me as well.
Now that it's come to this, we've got no choice but to go.
Off we go, Choi!
Hm?
the british store
Hm...
We only have stuff like, uh,
this?
H-Hey! Are you threatening me?! I'm considering this a threat!
Not what you want, is it?
What about something like this, then?
Might make a nice carpet for my nest.
I'm fine with anything, rea—
No you're not!
I-I see.
Our main demographic's around fifty years old, so...
Oh, right. This is a place a friend of mine runs.
Go take a look.
Wow, a second-hand clothes store!
Looks like all kinds of things you wouldn't find in Usagiyama.
Huh? What's all this?
Customers?
That's right. Hello!
Welcome.
Wow!
Now this is more like it!
Choi.
Try this on!
Lookin' good!
Huh? Too hot for you?
Maybe it's because they traditionally wear light clothing back home?
How about this?
How is it?
Looks great on you, Choi!
I'm taking a picture!
When will you get around to picking clothes out for me, my girls?
Do it!
One, two...
No need. You look wonderful enough in that.
Say cheese!
That's Midori for you! The queen of fashion sense!
Of course I do.
Oh, please!
What?!
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to go shopping with you too!
This scent...
I'm sorry.
So, what kind of stuff did you buy?
Oh, we ended up not buying anything today.
Take me with you next time, okay?
Sure thing!
Battles are meant to be fought alone.
The radiance of victory shall arrive after a long, dark night.
Choi?
Dela?
We haven't spoken in a while.
Are you doing all right?
Choi?
Dela?
Huh?
What?!
Here I am at last, everyone.
How do you like my rippling muscles?
I won't let you call me a chicken anymore!
What happened to you, Dela?
I've remodeled the body that shamed me so.
Oh, my...
Be strong, okay?
Of course.
I am fully resolved to maintain this body shape forever.
Take this. It's mushroom extract.
Feed it to him gently. It's full of nutrients for the poor bird.
Tributes, huh? Tributes, aren't they?
More like get-well gifts.
How so?
Does that mean the people of this market only know Dela as a miniature blimp?
I will not accept that any longer.
'Sup.
Hm? Kanna and Midori?
Here you go, Choi.
Selection: Tokiwa Midori.
Measurement: Makino Kanna.
Open it up, Choi.
It's so cute!
And what are you offering in tribute to me?
Nothing.
You needn't hide it from me!
We're not.
Also, what's wrong with your body?
It's gross.
Gross?!
Can you not comprehend this beauty?
Oh, right. Where's my house?
Oops.
Sorry, Mister.
I didn't bring it today.
Huh?
How is it?
This is my first fall.
of autumn
How should I
fill in the blanks?
The seasons change, bringing fresh winds of clean air with them.
Let kindness be rewarded with warmth
and hearts be dyed an autumn red.
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
Tamako here. I think fried mochi's even better than potato chips!
If you've got leftover mochi, try letting it dry out and then deep frying it. It's really tasty!
Try it with salt, green laver, or black pepper!
Episode 9    Breaking Out Into a Love Song
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?