Big news!
Mitsuki's manager, Ms. Oshige, moved
into an apartment near Mitsuki's house!
As we were helping her out
with Dr. Wakaoji,
we were found out by
Tanaka the housekeeper.
But she mistakenly thought Ms. Oshige
was Dr. Wakaoji's fiancée,
so she didn't think twice about
Mitsuki's relationship with her.
That was just perfect, wasn't it?
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
You're really good at singing,
aren't you, Mitsuki?
What's that song?
It's a song my father
wrote for his work.
Oh, I see.
Yeah!
I'll teach it to you too, Eichi!
The reason I asked everyone
to gather here today
is to brainstorm Full Moon's
next single.
That's right.
Thanks to everyone,
"Myself" was received well.
I would like to thank you for
your support this time as well.
Last time, everything was left
in Takasu's hands.
But this time, I thought I'd solicit
ideas from everyone.
I see.
In that case,
I'd like to do something new.
Something new?
Hey!
Oh, yes?
Now then,
what are we gonna do?
I don't want Full Moon to be
just a one-hit wonder.
Okay then,
I'll leave the rest to you.
It sure is difficult to
do something totally new.
Don't...
Huh?
Don't you think we should ask
Full Moon for her opinion?
She sometimes comes up with ideas
that we wouldn't even guess.
And what is it that she wants
to express through the song?
I think it might give us
a key to hear her thoughts.
That makes sense.
Yeah... It would be meaningless
to continue this meeting.
That's true.
All right, I'll put all the information
together by the next meeting.
Huh? Me?!
Yes, it was decided that we would
incorporate your ideas too, Mitsuki.
I see. For some reason
that makes me excited!
It looks like it's finally Meroko's time
to come on the scene!
Leave everything to me!
Okay, without further delay...
Well, that's par for the course.
And, how about it?
What do you mean, "how about it"?
I mean do you have an idea
or a motif or something?
When you ask me that question,
I have no ideas.
You don't have to think
too seriously.
Let's think about it together
by the next meeting.
Huh? I have to attend too?
That's right!
That way the song will
bring you closer to Eichi, right?
Oh! I see.
That's true.
All everybody ever talks
about is Eichi.
Takuto...
How dare you!
- This ain't good!
- I'm not letting you get away!
Stop that, Meroko!
No way!
I won't forgive you!
- Oww!
- Take that!
Bring me closer to Eichi?
- That should teach you!
- Please stop!
Hmm... I wonder what should I do.
You don't have to make it so
difficult for yourself, do you?
Come on! How irritating!
You're gonna get closer to Eichi, right?!
If it's gonna be like this,
why don't you go on and just
sing the name "Eichi, Eichi"?!
Gimme a break,
what's that about?!
I mean, that's the fastest way
to make him take notice, right?!
Maybe so, but that kind of thing
- isn't very reasonable!
- What should I do?
This is difficult.
A song that will bring me
closer to Eichi.
Eichi!
Ms. Oshige, I've decided!
Oh, you've decided?
And? What kind of image do
you have for the song?
No, it's not really an image.
But there's a song that
I absolutely want to sing.
A song you want to sing?
Yes, but I don't know
the title of the song.
Huh?
Hey, you...
Umm... As I remember,
this is kind of how it sounds.
- Huh?
What was that song again?
Do you know it?
Yeah...
But, Mitsuki, why this song?
This song holds a place in
my memories of the times with Eichi.
When I was little
I often sang this song with Eichi.
So if I sang this song,
Eichi would know it too and
it might come to his attention.
That makes sense.
But what was that song anyway?
Don't you have any other
memories of Eichi?
Umm... I guess just the song
that my father wrote.
Huh?!
That's an extremely minor clue.
There's no way we can figure
out the name of the song.
But I've definitely heard
it before.
Hmm... Your father wrote it when
you were little, right, Mitsuki?
Huh? Wrote it?!
Mitsuki, the person who wrote it...
Your father...
What did he do?
Huh?
I don't really know because
he died when I was one,
but I understand he had a band.
Huh?!
So your father was
a musician too, Mitsuki?
Didn't you know that?
Which means that
that's a band tune from
about ten years ago.
Yeah.
I got it!
- Huh?
"Eternal Snow"!
That's that legendary song by Route L!
"Eternal Snow"?
That's right!
It was only performed live
and was never recorded on CD.
A rare piece that was
only known to serious fans.
- Wow...
- Oh...
Huh? Which means...
M-Mitsuki's father was
a member of Route L?!
P-Probably...
Are you serious?!
S-Seriously...
Oh my gosh!
I can't believe this!
Oh my goodness, I can't take it!
This isn't the time to
be saying this.
Okay, I guess we have
our plan in place then.
Now that we know that...
Let's go for it!
Hey!
Right, Mitsuki?!
Y-Yes...
I see.
"Eternal Snow," huh?
Yes!
Please. I want to sing
this song, no matter what!
What do you think?
I like it.
I'll go with that idea.
It's Route L's song, right?
- Yes!
- All right.
Let's come up with a plan
without any further delay!
All right then, Full Moon and I
will go ask for Mr. Takasu's approval.
All right, let's begin.
Yes.
Well, I'm heading out!
Hello, this is Takahashi.
It's been a long time.
How are you?
How am I?
Not good at all!
You're in your element as always,
aren't you, Mr. Takahashi.
I mean, nothing has happened
regarding your promise of
making up for the audition.
Oh, I'm sorry about that.
Please give me
a break on that, Madoka.
I'm up to my neck with
a new project.
Yeah...yeah...it's almost decided.
Yeah, I'm planning Full Moon's
second single.
Full Moon?
Oh, I see.
Yes.
Oh?
Producer Takasu's going to do
"Eternal Snow"?
Well, I'll treat you to dinner
sometime soon, Madoka.
Yeah...Yeah...
Okay, talk to you soon.
Okay!
Madoka!
Did you wait long?
That last commercial was
well received.
Just now in the meeting...
Ms. Sasaki!
Huh?
You said that after this commercial
you'd let me sing, right?
Yes, what about it?
There's a song that
I absolutely want to sing.
Good morning!
Ms. Oshige?
All right! Done!
All right.
All we have to do now is take
this along and ask Mr. Takasu.
See, Mitsuki.
It's a perfect project plan.
Ms. Oshige, is it possible that-
Of course, I haven't slept.
Awesome!
A-Are you all right?
No sweat!
Come on, let's hurry over to Takasu's.
Okay.
This will bring you closer
to Eichi, right?!
Yeah...
You're bringing up Eichi
first thing in the morning?!
Rubbing it in, aren't you?!
It's morning!
- It's morning!
- Sh-She's running at high tension.
Is she really all right?
Mr. Takasu's late, isn't he?
He's apparently running a little late
because of some urgent business.
Can't be helped,
he's sought after by everyone.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Sorry, sorry.
I suddenly had to attend
an urgent meeting.
And? I understand you brought along
a plan for the second single today.
Yes.
I've summed it up here.
Let me take a look at it.
This won't do.
Sorry but this isn't
possible for me to do.
Huh?
Why is that?!
What's the problem with it?
Well... This is a pure coincidence,
but I'm already doing a project
exactly like this one.
The reason I was late today
was because of a meeting
regarding that project.
In the near future, a girl by
the name of Madoka Wakamatsu
will be making her debut
with the song "Eternal Snow."
Eichi...
It's something that just sprung up,
so I'm sorry but the project
you proposed is impossible.
Please think of a different song
for your second single.
Gimme a break!
Ms. Wakamatsu, I understand that
you will be making your debut singing
a Route L song?
That's right!
I'm very happy because
it's a song I've always loved!
I understand that Mr. Takasu
will produce it.
That's right!
I am thrilled that he will be
overseeing the entire project!
I went to all that effort of staying up
all night to write this project plan.
Is that kind of coincidence
really possible?
Coincidence?
No way!
There's something fishy about
that Madoka Wakamatsu!
But nobody knew about it
except us, right?!
O-Of course!
There must be a spy
around or something.
Huh?
You're watching too much TV.
That's right.
I mean, it's impossible for
the information to get outside.
Still, that girl is definitely fishy!
Hey...
- Ms. Oshige?
- Hmm?
Will I ever be able to
sing "Eternal Snow"?
Mitsuki...
It'll be fine!
Don't worry.
I'll have you sing it,
no matter what!
Really?!
Yes! Let's go to
Seed Records again tomorrow
and ask a different producer
for his assistance, okay?
Now that it has come to this,
you and Madoka Wakamatsu can
battle it out with "Eternal Snow"!
- Wow...
See you next week.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Mr. Takasu...
What is it?
I'll do anything to make
"Eternal Snow" sell!
So...
What is it, all of a sudden?
I don't want to lose...to Full Moon!
Full Moon, huh?
Hey... Are you hiding
something from me?
To tell the truth, I had exactly
the same project proposal
from Full Moon.
She wanted to sing "Eternal Snow"
as her second single.
Isn't that strange?
Oh...
Wow, that's an amazing coincidence!
Hey!
You're hiding something,
aren't you?
Isn't this really
Full Moon's project plan?
And you knowingly asked me
to take on this project?
In order to win against Full Moon.
Am I wrong?
It pisses me off.
A newcomer suddenly gets
boosted up to the top of the ladder
and attention without
even having to work for it.
That pisses me off!
Well, whichever of you was first
really has nothing to do with me.
My job is to make a success of
the work that was designated to me.
However...
I won't work with someone who
doesn't believe in my talent.
That's all I want to say.
Mr. Takasu, I have only one goal!
I don't want to lose to Full Moon!
Please let me win against
Full Moon.
That's good!
That's the spirit!
All right!
You truly want to win against
Full Moon, right?!
Yes!
In that case, stop acting!
You need to do battle
as your real self.
Okay!
I will polish your talent thoroughly!
I won't lose.
I won't lose to Full Moon,
no matter what.
This is perfect.
All we need to do now is
negotiate left and right.
Thank you very much, Ms. Oshige!
Come on. A manager and the artist
work together for a single purpose, right?
And moreover, Mitsuki,
the bandleader's daughter,
will sing that rare Route L classic!
That's only right!
Ms. Oshige, what kind of a person
was my father?
Well...
Of course, his guitar technique
was fabulous too,
but he was a man who could
really write wonderful songs.
He had great chemistry with
Dr. Wakaoji on the keyboards.
When the singer came in
on their music,
it was totally out of this world.
Come to think of it,
I wonder what the kid on
vocals is doing now?
Anyways, the kid was a great vocalist
who wouldn't lose to you, Mitsuki.
Goodness, why did they break up?
If they were that famous,
there should be a video of
your father somewhere.
No, believe it or not,
there aren't any at all.
Huh? Why?
They were a band that
really hated appearing on TV.
"We'll battle it out on the
basis of our sound alone."
That was their policy and
I have to say that was really cool.
That was one of the great attributes
of that legendary band.
Hmm... I see.
Route L, huh?
Hmm...
Gimme a break, all you've said
is "hmm" for a while now.
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Okay, let's go!
- Okay!
- Please!
Well, I understand how you feel,
but with the other fellow being Takasu...
Would you please ask someone else?
Wow... That sounds like
an interesting project!
In that case, will you take it on?
Hmm... I would if I had time,
but right now I'm just too busy.
Sorry!
I'm not gonna handle that.
Please, isn't there some
way you would?
Even if you were to say that...
Then, is there someone who...
Whoever handles it would
just be crushed.
I'm saying this for your sake.
Just give up that project.
Other guys won't handle it either.
All right!
If things have come to this,
it's close to impossible but,
let's try overseas!
Huh? Can you speak English,
Ms. Oshige?
Hello?
Hello.
Takasu?! No!
Isn't this nice, Takuto?
Oh, how did it go?
It didn't go well.
When the other fellow
is Takasu, you know...
I see.
Goodness! I wish Mitsuki's father
were alive at a time like this.
I'd go right ahead and
ask him for help.
Oh! That's it!
Huh?
Hey, even if her father isn't here,
there's a father figure around!
Oh!
A father figure?
You know, the guy who used to
play in the same band
that played this song.
- Oh!
- Oji of Route L!
I wonder if I'm catching a cold?
How annoying!
What's the matter, Meroko?
They decided to ask Dr. Wakaoji
to produce her new single,
but he won't agree to it.
Moreover, Mitsuki is uncomfortable
because she said it would
be imposing on him.
That doctor once said that he had
given up the path of music.
That must have something to do
with his refusal.
Next time on Full Moon:
"Please Dr. Wakaoji?"
- Look forward to it!