You bastards!
What was that?! What happened?!
There's... one more.
What?!
No way...
Where? Where did the sniper shoot from?
Can't be!
Mission completed.
Good. Leave there immediately via route C and await your next instructions.
Yes... Master.
A suspicious bullet that didn't hit anyone...
Well, let's see how our heroine will improvice her way through this.
Confession
You summon me here and then shoot at me?! What's the meaning of this?!
You're going to take responsibility for this, aren't you?! Huh?!
What do you mean?! Isn't the shooter one of your guys?!
I see... Then...
We're gonna kill you all.
No, Mr. Godo!
Huh?
That surprised me...
Ray...
I... I...
W... wanted to...
Another sniper... but...
Reiji... Hey Reiji!
What's wrong?
Nothing... Let's get out of here.
I see. Okay.
My subordinate succeeded in eliminating the threat.
There won't be any more shooting.
What kind of charade is this, huh?!
Mr. Godo. I hereby present you Isaac Wisemel,
the ringleader of the plot that has endangered you over and over again.
What?
I punished the traitor who mislead our organization for his own purposes...
with my own hands.
Traitor?
You'd better be ready to explain...
the reason for killing one of our own.
To put it simply, Wisemel was responsible for this shooting.
If you check the sniper that was taken care of by my subordinate...
that should be hard evidence.
Humph. How very well prepared you are.
This is Inferno's way of taking responsibility.
The hotel shooting happened after I shot Randy.
It wasn't Wisemel's doing.
There was another sniper.
That was also Wisemel's henchman.
He was obstinate like that.
Then why did the shooter stop after one shot?
Wisemel's objective was supposedly to eliminate Daisuke Godo, right?
You sure talk like you're the only one who knows the truth.
Whether he killed Godo or not... didn't really matter...
The real goal of the sniper was...
to fill the minds of those at the meeting with doubts and fears
and ruffle Inferno from the inside.
The sniper might have even guessed that Claudia was going to shoot Wisemel.
Stop it.
The whole thing was Wisemel's plot.
That's why Clo decided to take care of him.
Don't fill your head with crazy ideas. We're just pawns.
We don't have to pry into things that much.
Lizzie's right.
We don't need to know the truth.
On top of that, if this series of murders was Wisemel's doing,
where that five million dollars should go is clear.
The Godo Family's stolen money is found in Wisemel's vacation home...
With that, everything will be settled.
The yakuza's murders... Judy's revenge...
and...
my own selfish speculation as well...
No...
It's not true.
There's no way...
she's alive.
Hey, I heard a rumor... that Isaac of the Bloodies died. Is that true?
Yes, it's true.
The sniper you shot was one of Isaac's henchmen
and it was him who killed Judy, right?
Yeah.
Then it's over... the revenge...
I see.
Ah... Uhm... How was my training to become an assassin?
If you like, shall I continue to help you with your assassinations?
Forget about being a killer.
What?
Forget about it.
Then... Then I'm no longer needed...
Am I?
But...
I'd hate to give up that cooking of yours.
What?
You can be my maid and do the cooking for a while.
Really?! All right! I'm going to be a maid!
I wanted to try being a maid once. The uniform is really cute, you know.
You don't have to wear it.
What?! No uniform?!
No uniform.
That's okay... as long as you let me stay by your side.
An excellent report.
This whole series of incidents was Isaac Wisemel's scheme...
With this, the Godo Family will have to accept that now.
However...
to think that you figured out all this in that chaos...
You're quite brilliant.
Now that Isaac is gone I'll have you take his place.
Well then...
Don't disappoint me, Claudia McCunnen.
I understand.
Potential?
That's right. She's got a rare quality.
You can even call it a talent.
Talent... Someone told me a similar thing in the past.
In other words, you're saying that you want to train that girl as an assassin?
Yes.
If you can't produce results...
You know the rest, right?
Yes.
Then, we shall see how you do.
I don't have to put her in any more danger.
I'll make up some excuses so she can...
And yet...
I'm feeling at peace these days.
Let me see...
Cal...
Hm?
I'm going out. I may not be able to come back until the day after tomorrow.
What?!
I should've told you this sooner.
No, that's okay. I'll see you then.
Be careful.
You too.
Looks like administrative work has become completely natural to you, huh?
No kidding!
Why don't you just settle where you are right now?
You're officially a senior member now. You no longer have to push too hard.
It's not over yet.
This is just the beginning.
What more do you need? Getting too greedy will ruin you.
Well, I know there's no way you'd stop no matter what I say.
But just make sure you watch your step.
Do I look like such a fool?
Let me at least give you advice. It's my hobby, you know.
Cal, I wasn't really sure, but is this the fermented tofu stuff you were talking...
Cal?
Ah... welcome home! You're already back?
Cal, where'd you go?
You remembered to buy it!
Ah...
Chicken marinated in this tastes good.
Is it okay... to go on like this?
Is it?
Reiji...
What is it?
I still want to become your assistant.
Cal, that's...
I know... that you don't want me to become an assassin.
You know the pain that comes with being an assassin, so...
But I want to be able to do something.
I'm weak and poor.
I can't do anything without depending on someone else.
I don't want to live like that any more.
Cal, you can take any path. You can become anything.
Of all things, why do you want to become an assassin?
You don't like assassins?
No, I don't.
Then you don't like yourself?
Right, I don't. I ended up becoming a killer and can't escape.
I hate myself.
But Reiji...
I'm already broken. Do you want to be like me?!
I... I'm sorry, Reiji... I...
Cal... I was too harsh.
I'm sorry.
But it's true. I don't know how many have people died because of me.
They would've been able to live on if it wasn't for me.
They would've been able to go back to their loved ones.
It wasn't your fault.
You're just doing the job that someone has to do.
That's just an excuse.
Then did you want to kill people?
Did you shoot those people because you wanted to kill them?
Do you like killing?
That's not true, right?
It's hard, stressful, sad...
You can't forgive yourself for doing such a thing...
so you're trying to kill yourself inside.
You're not a fool who fires away like those who killed Judy.
You live bearing the pain of what you've done.
So you don't make mistakes. You don't kill people for nothing.
If it were you in that alley that night,
Judy wouldn't have died.
But Cal...
once you kill, everything in the world changes.
The scenery you see, the sounds you hear...
Everything changes.
You won't be able to accept people with a kind heart like you're able to right now.
I don't want you to become like that.
This isn't a good place for you to stay.
You shouldn't come into the same world I'm in.
But...
But that's where you're always going to be, right?
If I go there, I'll be able to be with you forever.
Cal...
I don't want to be separated from you. I want to be with you forever.
I want to be of help to you.
I want to...
be with you.
That's right... I...
I wanted to go back.
I thought I could be with you if I did...
That's okay. I'll go there.
I'll come to your side.
No, I'll go. Let me go back... to the world you live in.
Cal... Before I met you, it was as if I were dead.
If I get separated from you, I'll go back to being that dead person.
You helped me remember... how to laugh... and to cry as well...
Can't be... This is...
You know him?
There's no mistake about it.
That brat!
I'm surprised, too.
I thought Ms. McCunnen was making every effort to get you to join Inferno.
I wonder when the plan was changed.
It's none of your business!
Contact bro immediately! Hurry!
Yes sir.
Your time on the stage will be over soon, Ms. McCunnen.
I'll send an appropriate bouquet for your finale.
Hello.
Phantom. Hey, can you take a job right now?
What's the matter all of a sudden?
There are some remnants of the Bloodies who're acting funny.
I'd like to take care of them without a big fuss.
Would you give me a hand?
Okay. Where do I have to go?
Let's meet up at the usual switchyard at 20 o'clock.
Got it.
Work?
Yeah.
I was hoping to be with you all day today.
What are you saying?
We'll always be together from now on, right?
What?
We have tons of time.
I'll get my old self back...
for Cal...
and...
for Elen as well...
Next episode
Truth
Don't call me Elen.
I'm Ein.
I'm just Ein... as I always was.