“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
There's been a lot more people in yellow recently, huh?
Oh, you mean the Kokinzoku?
Did you know? There's a rumor that the slasher is really one of the Dollars.
We really need you, man.
How's your boyfriend been?
He comes by sometimes. But only in front there.
The air in Tokyo is filthy. Don't you think so?
Pinworm! Pinworm! Pinworm!
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Did you hear?
A while ago, a student from Raira Academy got hit by the slasher!
Is that true?
How unsettling...
It's the biggest truth of all!
It was a freshman girl!
Excuse me.
I'm going to make a phone call. Gone for a bit.
Don't worry.
It doesn't sound like it was your girlfriend.
Thanks. But I'm still worried.
Do you know where it happened?
Let's see.
It happened not far from the East Ikebukuro Subway Station on the Shuto Expressway.
If you get close by, there'll be cop cars all over the place, so you can't miss it.
Is that so?
Excuse me for a moment. I'm signing off.
Setton-san, you wanna go see?
Oh come on!
Sorry.
I'm leaving too.
What?
Did your call go through?
She says she's with the police or something...
And she was there to see what happened...
I'll be back later.
Me too, then.
The slasher...
At the time, I hadn't the slightest clue that the source of these blood-stained incidents
was tied closely to the fate of a girl, and to my own past.
Unrest Prevails
I'm home!
I don't think... you heard...
Celty, I'm home!
Welcome home.
What's wrong?
I just saw something disgusting.
Disgusting?
Don't make me say it! I want to forget it.
Much better.
Shouldn't you at least take that white thing off when you're in the shower?
No. Tokyo's air is filthy, so I won't take it off at any time.
Oh, that's right. Thanks for what you did today, Celty-kun.
Although, do you know who those outrageous fellows in yellow were?
They're the Kokinzoku.
They're a gang that've been around since before you went to America.
After a dispute with the Blue Squares or whomever a while back, they've more or less settled down.
Better if they all crushed each other and died in the sewers.
Don't be absurd.
Anyway, Dad, since Celty brought you here in one piece, you should pay her for it.
I'll make the payment to you.
I refuse.
Then how about I just default on the payment?
I was just teasing you, Celty-kun.
If you let me go right now...
You're stabbing me, you're stabbing me!
The tip of your shadow's pricking my neck!
Shinra! I've fallen into a real-life crisis.
At a time like this, you know what to do, right?
My son should know that, right?
Of course.
Pleasure doing business with you.
Don't you dare think that I'm going to leave you any inheritance, because I don't think I will.
I don't really want one.
To think that I'd be so thoroughly fooled by a monster...
To be fooled by Celty and then to have your soul taken, that is true satisfaction.
Oh my, oh my, Celty-kun!
Could it be that you've fallen in love with Shinra?
I knew that there was something about you that Shinra was infatuated with,
but don't tell me you feel the same for Shinra?
That's right.
Celty! I never thought you would recognize our relationship so frankly!
Now that what once was nothing but an unrequited love,
has changed into an intimacy that shines for all to see,
I am filled with the urge to jump for joy!
Shut up! You're embarrassing me!
I'm full of joy knowing that you love me...
Do you think I will allow such a relationship?
What did you say?
Are you aware that you're an uninvited guest in our human society,
or to put it bluntly, a monster?
Of course.
"Of course," you say...
What about it? Is there a problem?
It seems my strategy of using your antisocial nature
to prove my point has failed miserably.
There's no way you can convince me by saying it like that.
Also...
Shinra says he loves me just the way I am.
It's no use. I must approve of your relationship.
In return, you must henceforth call me:
"Father-in-law-sama"!
Shut up!
That being said, Celty-kun,
as long as you have no head, your memories will never return.
That is, your memories of being a Dullahan, and carrying your head in your hometown in Ireland.
That's something that can't be helped.
In place of the memories you've lost,
let's make lots of good memories between the two of us.
Shinra...
For starters, let's plan our wedding!
We need to take your measurements for the wedding dress,
so why don't you take off those shadow clo–
Come to think of it, even when we were doing the autopsy on you,
he was smiling like a demented little child.
That's obviously due to your influence!
It's "Father-in-law-sama", not "you"!
Seriously, I just said it a moment ago. You're thoughtless as always, Celty-kun.
That's why you didn't even notice when I stole your head.
Crap!
W-W-Wha-W-What did you just say!?
What should I do? I just let a huge secret slip out of my mouth.
Well, it's okay though. Celty's a loser, so she won't notice.
Celty's a loser! Celty's a loser!
Shut up! Why are you saying it twice!?
The attacks of a distracted loser are easy to predict!
I won't let you ridicule Celty, even if you're my father.
I understand, I understand. I'll explain.
There's no use hiding it at this point.
Yes, the one who stole your head and handed it over to the drug company...
Was me!
Don't say it so defiantly!
Very well. Follow me. There's something I want to show you.
He ran away!
That sick bastard! He won't get away!
Is she gone?
At any rate, it seems my strategy of simply hitting the elevator button was successful.
I would have come back to get my luggage eventually, anyway.
Damn it. Where did he go?
Celty-san.
Is something the matter?
You're staring into space.
I was just thinking.
Tell me about it.
It looked like you had a dark mood.
It's about the slasher.
There are some strange rumors going around the internet and message boards.
Strange rumors?
Yeah. Like, the incidents might be the Dollars' doing.
That's absurd.
Do you believe those rumors?
Of course I don't, but if those rumors are left alone,
things might get dangerous.
Even without them, there's a growing tension between the Dollars and the Kokinzoku.
He's right. The balance in this city right now is poised precariously on the precipice.
Mikado. I'm also going to investigate the slasher.
Celty-san...
Hurry up and be on your way.
If you keep sitting here staring, you'll just get caught up in it.
You're right.
Thank you very much.
The slasher, huh?
Sorry, but I don't know anything about him.
Is that so?
There's no reason for you to stand up for the Dollars like this, is there?
It's not just for the Dollars.
He and I have a connection, too.
If I wasn't headless, I would have died back then.
Idiot.
Some people say that when a person calls someone else an idiot then they are the idiot instead,
but I don't care if I'm an idiot, so I'll say it.
Idiot! You should've said that sooner!
All right! I'll kill him! I'll kill him no matter what! I'll kill him for sure!
I'll kill him in flames!
No, wait...
I'm the headless rider, so I'll be okay.
No, no, no. That's no longer the problem.
To turn a blade on one of us equals certain death.
I'll kill him, I'll kill him, I'll kill him...
What about your job? You're just on a break, right?
I don't care about that.
Hey, hey. I'm not going to let you get fired because of me.
Plus, we need a lot more information if we're going to find the slasher.
I need to prepare first, so wait.
Got it.
Just try to be quick about it.
I'll kill him, I'll kill him, I'll kill him, I'll kill him, I'll kill him...
There was a reason why I left Shizuo temporarily.
I'm glad you came to see me.
How's it going? By the way, did you find your head yet?
I don't care about my head. I'll get right to the point.
I want to know more about the slasher.
That'll be three big ones.
Now that I think about it, your clothes and wallet are both made out of shadow, right?
If you were hit by a strong light,
I wonder if the shadow would disappear leaving you stark naked?
You want to see?
Not really. I don't have any desire for a headless person or a head,
unlike a certain perverted witch doctor and student I know.
Say what you will about me,
but the next time you insult Shinra, you won't get away unscathed.
You two must really love each other.
Still, if another Dullahan were to show up and seduce him,
and he suddenly had his heart stolen...
I'd like to think that wouldn't happen. But if it did, then in that case...
Would you kill him and then yourself?
No. I just wouldn't let her near him,
that other headless woman.
Because I already love him.
Wow, what a surprise! You've become even more like a human.
Be careful, though.
The closer you get to becoming a human,
the larger the gap may be when you finally find your head.
I can worry about that after I get it back.
Well, to be honest, I've actually thought that maybe I don't need my head.
More importantly, I need you to give me that information about the slasher.
Don't just take my money and say you don't have anything.
Don't worry.
There's still some information that I haven't given to the police or spread over the net.
Actually, I've been waiting for you to show up.
What do you mean?
This time, the world of evil-natured spirits are involved.
Have you heard of a sword called Saika?
Saika?
It's hard to believe, but Saika is a demon sword that was actually here in Shinjuku.
A demon sword? You mean like the Muramasa Blade?
Right. A sword that holds a mysterious power.
What's wrong?
I heard about a demon sword called "Saika" from Izaya.
Evidently, there's a legend about Saika capturing people's minds and taking over their bodies.
Also, all the slasher's victims say their attacker had red eyes.
And you think it was Saika's doing?
Yeah. The night the slasher showed up,
the screen name "Saika" started showing up on the Internet.
However, when I was attacked before, I didn't even notice it coming towards me.
Had Saika been human, I would have felt its presence in some way.
Since Saika is controlling the person's awareness,
all that's moving around is their body,
so you could say that the presence you'd normally sense wasn't even there.
Shinra... you sure know a lot about Saika.
Well, I mean, you did tell me to look it up earlier.
Anyway, hurry up and come to bed.
"Shinra's hiding something."
That is what I thought.
Hey, welcome back!
After Nebula took over Yagiri Drug Manufacturing,
I decided to investigate Miss Namie's whereabouts by myself,
and I discovered that she'd been coming to your place frequently.
Then, I took this model gun and threatened her into taking me in here.
A model gun!?
Didn't I tell you that?
Shouldn't we hand this guy over to the police?
Oh, I think it's you who would suffer if you did that.
What if they searched the place based on my testimony,
and found the living head of a young girl!?
Indeed, it would replace the slasher as the greatest sensation in town.
As I thought, Shinra gets his twisted nature from you.
Flattery will get you nowhere.
Well, honestly, I don't need to take that head back from you right now.
The upper division of our company was plenty surprised at the images of Celty-kun that were broadcasted recently,
and some are arguing that her body is worth researching more than her head.
That being said, I am currently searching for the whereabouts of the head on my own.
In any case, your approach with that head is quite an interesting one.
Going from the theory that Valkyries and Dullahan are one and the same,
you intend to put it in the middle of some sort of conflict and awaken it.
That's quite a unique idea.
Well, I've tried quite a few things.
If it comes down to it, I may have to take it to a conflict-ridden country.
Anyway, I'd be very appreciative if you considered cooperating.
Very well. I'm more interested in you anyway.
There's nobody, where I work, who wants to conduct experiments from a mythological standpoint.
Excluding me, that is.
I appreciate it.
Well then, let me give you a bit of advice.
If you want to stimulate Celty-kun's head, or her spirit,
by starting a mock conflict here in Tokyo.
Then perhaps, instead of bringing her into an external conflict,
you should throw her body's surroundings into calamity.
That's what I plan to do.
Or should I say, things are moving in that direction faster than I thought.
Anri.
Are you doing all right with the preparations for the sports festival?
Y-Yes.
I was worried.
Why were you with those students who were attacked?
Could it be that they were bullying you again?
I'm worried about you. I'm truly worried.
The slasher might target you again, so you're not safe alone.
Sexual harassment again?
That's not good, Sensei.
I'm worried about Anri.
No honorifics? Dangerous!
If you get too worried, Anri might just change schools like Niekawa-senpai did.
You were her homeroom teacher last year, right?
Niekawa Haruna's.
What?
You know about Niekawa?
Yeah, just the name.
Well, we students will be leaving now!
Just who is Niekawa Haruna-san?
Hey, Anri.
Mikado hasn't asked you out or anything, has he?
Didn't think so.
You do know that Mikado has a huge crush on you, right?
Ryugamine-kun is a good friend.
My best friend is really in love with you,
so I decided to take a look for him.
And then it turns out I have to be friendly towards one of the hottest girls in the world.
Masaomi!
Sonohara-san!
My, what a timid entrance.
Sorry. Were you waiting?
We waited so long I thought we were gonna turn into fossils.
Three points for the route.
Route? What do you mean, route?
At least say "minus 20 points" so I can understand your comeback!
Later!
See you tomorrow!
You finally came.
Celty.
It's about Saika.
My father had it at one point.
He sold it to an antique dealer years ago, though.
Shingen did? What for?
It's said that Saika is a sword that can cut souls.
You don't mean...
That's right. He used Saika to steal your head.
To sever the spirit connecting your head and your body.
You knew that, Shinra?
Yeah.
Of course, I didn't know about him using it to steal your head
until I pried into things afterward.
I thought it'd be all right to tell you now that you're trying to forget about your head. However...
Wait...
Let me think alone for a bit.
Of course.
Love gives birth to confusion.
That same night, the demon sword Saika was trying to make love to a girl.
A girl who couldn't find her place in this reality.
Sonohara Anri.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Wise Words from Fools
Durarara!!
Next time on
Ikebukuro...
I just wanted to find out...
About the source of the energy that packs this town of rubbish together.
The truth of this town where desires swell up every day.
Next time: Wise Words from Fools.