What's going on?
Even if you get five coins,
these battles don't end?
Five coins isn't the win condition?
Shock.
What does this mean?
No...
If it doesn't end after you get five coins,
then how can I get Chi-chan's memories back?
Tama?!
Where am I?
This is... Mayu's room?
Yes, this is the room of white windows.
Who are you?
Shiro.
Kuro is here, too.
The ones who left.
I know this voice!
The door will open soon.
The door...
The door will...
What is this?
Let me go!
Hey, let me go!
The girl of the beginning has returned.
The keyhole.
No! No! No!
Now all I need is the key...
I wonder how this will go.
There are five Selectors left in the game.
It's almost time for the climax.
I need to make the game more interesting.
Isn't that right, Eternal?
Ruuko
Where did you go, Tama?
That message from Mizushima-san...
If getting five coins isn't how you win,
does that mean there's no
way to recover lost memories?
Correct. We haven't been told how to win.
But we were told that if we win, it will be
possible in the end to alter memories.
Which means that to win this time,
you have to do something different?
Probably.
That message from Mizushima-san...
If getting five coins isn't how you win,
does that mean there's no way
to recover lost memories?
We don't know how to win yet,
but I'll keep winning battles and
get your memories back, Chi-chan.
That message from Mizushima-san...
If getting five coins isn't how you win,
does that mean there's no way
to recover lost memories?
We don't know how to win yet,
but I'll keep winning battles and
get your memories back, Chi-chan.
Unknown Caller
Yes?
Hi there.
Carnival...
Tama-chan's gone?
I didn't see it happen, either...
But why?
This is just a guess,
but Tama is a special LRIG,
so she may have been caught
up in something big.
What's going on?
I don't know.
But it looks like what's happening
here is totally different
than the Selector battles we know.
That message from Mizushima-san...
If getting five coins isn't how you win,
does that mean there's no way
to recover lost memories?
We don't know how to win yet,
but I'll keep winning battles and
get your memories back, Chi-chan.
Thanks.
I believe in you, Suzu.
Oh, hey!
How've you been?
I'm sorry, who are you again?
So you forgot about me, huh?
Is it because you lost your coins?
Can you tell me more about that?
How are you enjoying this
round of Selector battles?
Having fun?
These battles could never be fun.
Is all of this your doing?
It was Eternal who set it up.
Eternal?
The Room of White Windows itself.
The goal of these new battles is for
Eternal to pick itself a new master.
You can't be serious...
The Room of White Windows
summoned me personally
and gave me more information
than the other Selectors.
Looks like it wants me to mix things up.
Why are you telling me this?
You're the only Selector who defeated me.
If you're not taking this seriously,
it's not worth defeating you.
So I'm doing you a special favor.
There's a lot of stuff I forgot, too.
You were a Selector, too?
That's right.
When I was in trouble,
you told me about Satomi-oniichan.
And Satomi-oniichan found
me someone to fight.
Satomi...
Then, when I had one coin left...
Hey, are you okay?
What did I do?
I'm going to become the master of that room,
and make the world a lot more fun.
A world where the battles never end,
and their outcome determines everything.
A world where the battles
go on for eternity...
What could be better?
If you became the master of the room,
could you get other Selectors' memories back?
It was the master of the room who
invented the battles for memories.
They can probably do whatever they like
with the memories that were stolen.
If you want to make your wish come true,
you'll have to defeat all
the remaining Selectors.
I gave you the information.
Now get to work.
Right now, it's not even worth fighting you.
If you want to make your wish come true,
you'll have to defeat all
the remaining Selectors.
When I was Layla's LRIG,
I saw someone named Carnival.
They had information about the battles
that Selectors aren't supposed to know.
And you think they might know about Tama?
Yes, maybe.
This is the place.
Are you Kominato Ruuko?
Who are you?
That's him! Carnival!
You need something from me?
Do you know an LRIG named Tama?
Oh, I just heard that name.
What do you mean?
A Selector I just fought called
her LRIG by that name.
She should still be close.
I believe her name was... Homura Suzuko.
Homura Suzuko?
They can probably do whatever they like
with the memories that were stolen.
If you want to make your wish come true,
you'll have to defeat all
the remaining Selectors.
Homura Suzuko said there's a reason she
has to win the battles, no matter what.
And she stole Tama for that reason?
I'm going to get Chi-chan's memories back.
No matter what.
When humans get too attached to something,
it narrows their field of vision.
This should be a pretty
interesting development.
I hope I can find some kind of clue...
Confirmation.
Is Kurebayashi-san back?
Sorry.
It looks like she's left already.
She's near the street up ahead.
Got it!
Excuse me...
You're Kurebayashi-kun's friend, aren't you?
Yes...
Is she still sick?
Yeah, kind of...
We can't get a hold of her on the phone.
Do you know what's going on with her?
Um...
Could you tell her to call us?
Discovery.
There you are.
Late.
If we don't hurry, we won't
make it in time for the movie.
The movie? Wait... Huh?
I-I'm sorry... I think you have the wrong person.
I'm not going to any movies.
Blunt.
You're a Selector, aren't you?
Are you also a Selector, Hanna-san?
Affirmation.
Hypothesis.
Yuzuki-san is missing work because
she was caught up in the
Selector battles, right?
That's right.
Trade.
All right, Uemura-san, let's trade information.
We need allies.
I'd love to!
She's close.
Where?
That way!
Egg Tart
Yuzuki, which one is she?
I'm sorry. There are so many
people that I can't tell.
Understanding.
Your friend's LRIG is missing.
Unfortunately,
I have no information on
similar events occurring.
I see.
Shock.
I'm very surprised, though.
So you're friends with the legendary Selector
Kiyoi-san told me about, Kominato Ruuko-san.
Ruuko's just a normal girl.
Hunch.
I think something strange is going on
with these latest Selector battles.
Something...
I couldn't say anything about that.
But we need to stop that Carnival person.
I do agree with that.
Suggestion.
Then let's go meet my ally now.
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
She's on the platform.
Got it.
The train will be arriving
shortly on track 1.
Hanazono
Shrine
Here I am.
I see.
So you're Kominato Ruuko-san's friend.
Coincidence.
You know her?
When I was Aoi Akira's LRIG,
we battled once.
I remember you...
Understanding.
That's a bit of a curve ball,
but you've met before, I see.
Well, then, I'll introduce you again.
This is one of my allies,
Mizushima Kiyoi-san.
Mizushima...
Then you're the person who
gave that invitation to Ruuko.
Ruuko called you yesterday, actually.
I see.
I'm sorry. I was kind of busy yesterday.
Does that mean Kominato-san's
involved in these battles, as well?
Yes.
Then I'd like to ask for her help once more.
Naturally. That makes sense.
But she's busy finding Tama-chan now...
That's Ruuko's LRIG.
And she suddenly vanished...
Cooperation.
I think we could resolve that
faster if we all worked together.
That's right.
Suggestion.
Why don't we contact
Kominato-san immediately?
Yes.
Ruuko, hey...
Hitoe, sorry.
I'm a little busy now.
I might be able to get Tama back.
Really?
Yeah...
Yeah.
Ruuko says she's following the
Selector who stole Tama-chan.
Who?
She said her name is Homura Suzuko.
Stop her!
Homura Suzuko-san is on our side.
She wouldn't steal anyone's LRIG.
Ruuko!
She's getting on the train.
Sorry, I'm getting on a train, so I'm hanging up.
I'll call you back.
Ruuko, wait!
It's no good. I can't get through.
Roger.
I'll call Suzuko-san.
Failed.
Her voice mail picks up.
What do we do?
Impede.
We need to stop her somehow.
But we don't know which train she's on,
or how to find her...
Uncertainty...
At a time when we need to fight Carnival,
we can't let the two of them fight.
What do we do?
How can we stop them?
What can we do?
We don't have enough information...
The other.
The other girl.
Is this... the Room of White Windows?
I've been waiting.
Who's there?
I am Eternal.
Eternal?
Open the door.
Open the lock...
Who will win?
Who is the weak one?
Battle.
Battle, and risk your life.
Choose. You must do it.
Find the key.
The answer.
The law.
Me.
Find...
the key?
You?
Kiyoi-san!
Mizushima-san!
Are you okay?
Concern.
You just passed out...
I'm fine.
And I know where they are.
Let's go get them.
Kiyoi-san?
We'll talk later.
Mizushima Kiyoi...
So now she's been chosen?
I guess I'm just another pawn, too.
This will be fun.
I'll get Tama back, no matter what.
I decided I'd never be apart from her again.
Yuzuki...
It's so crowded that it's hard to tell,
but I'm sure she's on this train.
I'll know if you get close.
She's close. She's in this car.
Ikebukuro
The train will be arriving
shortly on track 7...
Here you go.
Thank you!
Ruuko, she got off the train.
Get off, quick!
There she is! That girl!
The one who just went down the stairs!
They should be in this area.
Homura Suzuko-san...
Who are you?
Give back Tama.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb.
Suzuko, she's a Selector.
You'll have to defeat all
the remaining Selectors.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But if you're a Selector...
I have to beat you!
Homura Suzuko, the one who defeated me,
and Kominato Ruuko,
the one who released Mayu.
This is a good match I set up.
Which one will win?
What did you say?!
I didn't see you there.
You asshole!
I'm the one who gets to fight Kominato Ruuko!
She's my prey!
The situation's changed.
Give up.
And there's no way you
can beat Kominato Ruuko.
What?!
Shut the hell up!
Fight me!
I'll take you down first!
Over there!
Open!
Contact / Key and Keyhole
I can't beat her with anything
less than my full strength.
Suzu is amazing...
That smirk of yours pisses me off.
Who is Eternal?
We all have a reason why we battle.
This is an audition for you all.
The Eve / Trust and Betrayal
"The Eve / Trust and Betrayal."