Band's Labyrinth (From Vol. 3 Chap. 21)
8th Street
“Full-auto Orchestra”
Lost Technologies.
The Great Pyramids of Egypt.
The Nazca Lines.
Machu Picchu, the city in the sky.
How and why these wonders were created remain a mystery to this day.
Time marches on, and they outlive their purposes.
Maruko Shopping District
These now meaningless monuments are doomed to obscurity.
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
“The All-In-One World”from Vol. dog-thing, Chapter ???
LAUNDROMAT
It's raining cats and dogs.
Of all the places to be stuck at...
I wonder if it's really worth it to just stay put?
It was so nice this afternoon, too.
‘Guess it's just abnormal weather.
Must be “Gang Rain”, huh?
Guerrilla Rain, stupid.
Well you're surrounded and can't get away, just like with gangs, right?
What kind of reasoning is that?
The forecast said it wouldn't rain today.
The one I saw said it would.
Huh? How's that possible?
Each weatherman's prediction is a little different.
So who's the genius weatherman you saw?
Like I’d remember!
Do weathermen have, like, batting averages or something?
“This guy's strong in the summer, but stinks at predicting snow” or something...
Then I'd watch the best one before I leave for school.
Sounds like the bookkeepers at horse races.
By the way, Kon.
Yeah?
If you knew it was gonna rain, where's your umbrella?
Forgot it at school.
It's coming down pretty hard considering it was unexpected.
Doesn't look like it'll clear up anytime soon.
I'm getting kinda chilly...
Yeah, our clothes are basically soaked.
Rain this time of year is pretty cold.
Hey, since we're right in front of the laundromat,
let's throw our clothes in the dryer real quick!
We're gonna catch a cold at this rate.
Hold it.
What're you planning on wearing while your clothes are drying?
Do you ever think before you speak?
We'll be fine.
Nobody's gonna come when it's pouring rain like this.
Come on, Tattsun, let's do it.
Huh!? No way!
Not happening!
You'll be fine!
Hurry, before you catch cold.
No! I'm not gonna do it!
If someone comes, you have to cover us.
Wouldn't it be more effective if Tattsun's smokin' bod was distracting them instead?
No way. I'm way to good to just let anyone see me like that.
You do it.
In that case, Kon's got nothing to worry about hiding.
That was a nice, clean hit.
Well, excuse me for not having anything.
That's his only option left.
I feel so icky wearing wet underwear.
How about borrowing those? They look pretty dry.
Not a chance! Who knows who they belong to?
We should have thrown our underwear in too.
If someone comes, we'd be in even more trouble.
Kon, what are you doing?
Feels kinda liberating, doesn't it?
They're still kinda damp though...
Still better than before.
A little warm, too.
I'm cold...
That warmth sure didn't last long.
Wet clothes really sap your body heat.
Why didn't you tell me that earlier?
Sure looks nice and warm inside there.
I won't stop you, so go ahead and make yourself a fried pervert.
That'd be great!
You love those weird murder cases, right?
I'm not in any hurry to become a corpse.
I've had it! I'll just drink something hot.
They're all cold drinks!
Guess they haven't stocked the warm stuff yet.
Quit goofing off, you piece of crap!
Make with the HOT coffee already!
A lazy employee like you shouldn’t talk.
They’ve got an udon machine here.
I'll take it!
As long as it's hot, I don't care what it is!
What exactly comes out of an udon machine?
Cup udon, of course.
But there's no hot water spout on this.
No hot water pots around, either.
Gimme back my 300 yen!
You're one unlucky customer.
Nothing's coming out at all...
My precious 300 yen...
Hey, sounds like something's moving inside it.
Maybe it got stuck or something.
What is it?
It's moving.
It's making the udon inside there.
What?
There it is!
What the heck?
Looks like Fox Udon.
This Fox Udon's piping hot.
This isn't cup udon.
And it's faster too!
You may think this looks old and crummy,
but maybe it's really a futuristic machine from outer space.
I'm gonna try it again.
How many do you plan on having?
I wanna watch the machine make it!
What is this, an arcade game?
It's cool, I'll have one myself.
I need something hot anyway.
Cooking
Time remaining
Seconds
Hey, there it is.
It's pouring the hot water.
It's even stopping at the right time.
There it goes again.
Wow, it steamed it twice!
Here comes the broth.
All done!
Hmm, that's pretty cool.
Ouch!
The taste is mediocre, though.
Hey, what about the hamburger machine?
I'll try it out!
Ooh, lemme see! Lemme see!
Well, is it making it inside there?
I can't see...
Rats. Pre-packaged, huh?
“Ready” just means it's warmed up.
Hot!
The box nearly burned me!
These future folk don't know how to tone it down.
I thought they were aliens.
This box looks kinda dodgy...
What's inside is the important part.
Looks more like a shamburger to me.
Who are you calling a shamburger!?
Why are you so mad?
I bet it's made with the finest ingredients!
Ingredients.
Meat: beef, pork, chicken, mutton, horse, rabbit, etc.
See? So many ingredients, it must be top-class!
What's that say about the places with 100% beef?
More importantly, since they wrote rabbit on there,
I'm kinda curious about what the “etc.” means.
You know, how at night when the workers sneak a peek inside the fridge...
I know, “Meowburger”, right?
You're kinda cat-like, so wouldn't it be cannibalism?
That's just an urban legend.
Cat's are actually more costly and troublesome to use.
There's the one about lizard parts too.
They’re considered high-quality ingredients in some places.
Which Iron Chef decided that?
Okay, I'll try a ham and cheese melt.
Toasting
Ow! Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Isn't all this stuff a bit too hot?
Those aliens need to take it down a notch.
Look, it says, “risk of burn, use caution" right there.
What, no Esperanto?
Esper-what?
The official language of Earth.
That was pretty yummy.
Sure does warm you up.
It tastes much better when you add a fun-factor to it, huh?
I don't think the guys who made this had entertainment in mind.
That's it!
What Seaside needs is that very same fun-factor!
If it’s got fun, then even that crappy, bland coffee would taste better!
Fun-factor or no, isn't figuring out how to improve the coffee more important?
Oh, I think it stopped.
This fresh laundry smells the best!
Arashiyama
I'm hungry.
Times like this are when this hidden little oasis really comes through.
The lost arts of ancient civilizations.
Monuments fated some day to be forgotten by man.
But until that day, they continue to thrive among society.
Just look at it simmer.
I can't get it open!
Hey Sanada...
Sorry, but could you open this for me?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks!
Even though you're a customer...
Thanks so much!
‘Gotta leave the tough work to the boys, right?
What's wrong?
A jar! Find me a jar!
A really hard to open one!
I'll make Sanada open it for me!
Found one!
JAR!
Wow, you're like a widow!
Don't talk like I'm some kind of butch!
Quit screwin' around!
Yes ma'am.
Head Maid, your stocking's torn.
Huh?
Oh dear.
Hey, what the heck?
Hustleryuki, don't tell me you're...
No! That's not-
No! Sanada's hot for the head maid!?
A nightmare engraved into my mind.
I have laid eyes upon that which isn’t to be witnessed.
Today, we mourn for Sanada.
Osaka's famous for its street food.
“Band’s Labyrinth”from Vol. 3, Chapter 21
With the change in the everyday drudgery, all students, without exception...
...gradually begin buzzing with excitement this time of year.
The season of the culture festival.
It's not even for a whole ‘nother month yet, but everyone's running around preparing for the festival.
Some people plan their whole year around the culture festival.
How childish.
Childish, huh?
Well, not really...
How come our class isn't doing anything?
I wanna be a part of the festivities!
A lot of our classmates are busy contributing to their clubs’ booths.
There's just not enough free hands.
Let's all do something next year. The whole class!
We only have so many chances to be a part of the culture festival.
You do have a point.
How about we put on a play?
I'll write the script.
I've got tons of great ideas.
Like “Murder on Jell-O Island”.
I bet you're gonna have me killed off, right?
Uncle! Uncle!
Hell yeah! Stage ticket!
Gimme some curry and coffee.
Yes'm.
It's “yes ma'am”, not “yes'm”.
Don't get sloppy just ‘cause she's our friend.
Yes'm.
So? You got what now?
You got a stagecoach or something?
Stage, not stagecoach, retard.
Kon made a pretty nice comeback, don't you think?
I didn't get it at all.
I won a stage spot on day three from the raffle.
Let's put together a band.
I'm kinda nervous singing in front of a crowd.
Who said you clowns would be singing?
Yeah, you're tone deaf anyway.
You've never even listened to me sing!
Don't need to. You can tell by your face.
Well, you're actually a little better than tone-deaf.
How do you know that!?
Have you been to karaoke with her before?
I've got vocals and bass under control.
You guys pick an instrument.
You can play guitar or keyboard, can't you?
Don't just assume everyone can play.
Yeah!
Hotori.
What about that one I taught you in grade school? You know...
Oh yeah! I can play something keyboard-like.
Come to think of it, I used to play something guitar-ish a while back.
For real?
I can't believe I found members this easily!
I got the drummer taken care of too.
K-ON
Club
You're a genius, Kon!
Haribara, you've got excessive lower-body movement,
so you tend to run outta steam in the second half.
So I've come up with a special training exercise to build up your lower body and your upper body strength at the same time.
Kon!
Sweet! We got us a band!
There's a catch, so this'll be fun.
I knew it was too good to be true.
Getting all excited without even seeing you in action.
Even by a loose...A VERY loose interpretation, an accordion's hardly like a keyboard.
Well, whatever.
You call that a guitar!?
See? It's got strings too.
If anything with strings is a guitar,
then a harp, koto, or even a triangle is a damn guitar!
They don't use strings, they're triangle-shaped.
Yeah, triangle.
You're just repeating me to sound smart, aren't you?
Ah, screw it.
I'm just thankful you're willing to perform with me.
Can't say we're not creative, I guess.
It's so tiring keeping up with Kon's selfishness.
You sure look like you're having fun, though.
Just the fact that this'll keep up until the festival is giving me a migraine.
Then again, it's good that they're giving it their all.
Hey, you running a dying cat-fé now?
It's a karaoke café.
Go on, belt one out.
— DAY OF THE CULTURE FESTIVAL —
Which one of you guys drew this?
He did.
You're pretty good!
T-Thanks...
What about this 4-panel one?
Oh, that was me.
This is really neat.
Thank you!
Oops, forgot I was going to buy some octopus balls and Korean pancakes.
Octopus, pancakes; 1, 2, 3!
You're not gonna buy it!?
Let's see...spring rolls are on the 3rd floor, gymnastics clubroom.
Oya
High
Culture
Festival
Guidebook
Oya
High
Culture
Festival
Guidebook
Oya
High
Culture
Festival
Guidebook
Oya
High
Culture
Festival
Guidebook
Oya
High
Culture
Festival
Guidebook
Oya
High
Culture
Festival
Guidebook
Tatsuno, the grilled chicken stand is out by the field.
Let's hurry up and buy some so we can eat.
Now, what was I supposed to get...
Umm...
Actually, I wanted to see the festival with you...
What?
I am NOT fat. I'm just growing.
I mean, I realize it myself,
that sometimes I'm being over-confident and egotistical.
And ‘cause of that, I get depressed.
So you see... umm...
I'll still try my very best to play tomorrow...
Umm...
You don't even have to ask. I'll come see you.
Ohmigod! I practically confessed to him!
Tatsuno's trying her hardest to beat her depression, huh?
I've gotta cheer her on.
What the heck are those two doing?
Can't even count on them to go on a food run.
The octopus balls and pancakes are gonna get cold!
— Final Day —
Full-volume lullaby!
Okay, last day!
Price down from 200 to 50 yen!
Sorry, sold out!
Gymnastics club is officially closed!
You don't even have to ask. I'll come see you.
Why did I have to ask him that?
You nervous or somethin', Tatsuno?
Don't sweat it. Just like we practiced.
The rest will come naturally!
I-I'm not nervous or anything!
Just keep your mouth shut, blowfish cheeks!
B-BLOWFISH CHEEKS!?
I've never been so insulted in all my life!
I'm not letting that one slide, you haughty four-eyed—
Knock it off, guys!
Even I got tricked into playing the drums!
Stupid fake training!
That's got nothing to do with this!
Dammit guys, quit bickering!
Don't pull this crap right before the show.
Kon!
We lose!
Whoa... déjà vu.
Okay, please get ready.
I practice my shuriken skills before bed.
All right, taking the stage next...!
...is a 4-girl band, “The Maids”!
After hours of debate, they chose to don their maid outfits,
thus, they have become “The Maids”.
Okay girls, take it away!
Don't believe what I say,
I'm leaving for good.
As clouds float across the southern skies,
farewell to those halcyon days.
Who's that singing?
That's Kon!
No way!
Go Maids!
It wasn't supposed to be like this!
I didn't mean to do it!
You call this rock!?
This ain't rock!
They're right, but it still has the same energy to it.
What's that say on her apron? Seaside?
I love you, Kon!
It's pretty catchy, don'tcha think?
This song's a little too hipster for me.
Careful, you'll piss off the hipsters!
But we don't care, we'll keep playing.
There's someone waiting for me at the edge of the world.
The winds may not carry our sound too far,
but it'll last through the Ides of March.
We're the world-famous sassy maids!
Sowing chaos and disorder through the universe.
We'll bop you one right here and now!
See ya later, alligator! Get lost Pluto!
“Oi”, not “hoi”, dammit!
And so...
After the cleanup, when we return to school,
there remains not even a trace of the vibrant festival that just took place.
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living for rock!
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
Living lonely, blasting my music.
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Kyou mo Kare ni wa Nasake Kokurezu
and I still have yet to tell him how I feel.
Toppuu ni Inochi wo Sasage Ashikoshi wo
Putting our lives in the hands of a tornado,
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
we train our legs by playing drums.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We're the Maids, yeah!
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Chiisai no wa Zessan Eigyou Chuu
The little one's working inside, making a profit!
Thank you very maid for coming!
Hey, get this!
After I ate this bean bun from the candy store, I won a freebie for the first time ever!
Where's it say you've won on a bean bun?
When you bite into it, instead of bean paste,
you get a ball that says “winner”!
Then you can turn it in an get another one!
So all you get is the bread?
You're right! You get hosed by the prize and forget about the important part!
Next time: 9th street.
Café Seaside
9th Street“Clash of the Buyitans!”
Clash of the Buytans!
Round and round, nice 'n soft.