- C'MON! JUST LET ME SEE IT!
- STOP!
- JERK. WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY DO YOU HAVE THIS?
- Minami: YOU KNOW, YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO BE ALL CREEPY ABOUT IT,
IF YOU WANTED TO SEE,
YOU COULD'VE JUST ASKED.
- ACTUALLY IT'S FUNNY, I THOUGHT
THIS WAS A PICTURE OF HIDEYOSHI!
YOU TWO LOOK SO MUCH A LIKE.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU CRUSH MY...
- TAKE IT BACK.
I SAID TAKE IT BACK!
ACKNOWLEDGE MY HOTNESS!
- THIS IS ABUSE! PEOPLE GO
TO JAIL FOR THIS, YOU KNOW!
- Minami: MR. NISHIMURA! MAY
WE HAVE YOUR PERMISSION
TO FIGHT A PRACTICE
ST WAR? PLEASE?
- Nishimura: YES! I APPROVE!
- SUMMONING AVATAR. SUMMON!
REALLY? SUMMON! I'M SUMMONING!
SUMMON! SUMMON!
I SAID, SUMMON!
OKAY, THAT WAS WEIRD.
LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN. SUMMON!
SUMMON! SUMMON! SUMMON
( shouts ) SUMMON!
- Nishimura: APPROVAL SUSPENDED!
THE... THE FIELD'S
OUT OF CONTROL!
- ( clamoring )
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: PROBLEMS ALWAYS
SEEM TO OCCUR
WHEN WE LEAST EXPECT THEM.
- Kouta: YOU READY?
WHAT'S THE SECRET PASS CODE?
- MAKES ME TOO FRISKY.
- OKAY.
- Akihisa: WHERE IS IT?
- HAND OVER THE CASH FIRST.
- Akihisa: OH! THERE'S HIDEYOSHI
AS A CUTE LITTLE WAITRESS!
HE MAKES LIFE SO DELICIOUS!
- Kouta: ( laughs )
I'VE GOT MORE IF YOU WANT.
HOW ABOUT A LOCKER ROOM SHOT?
COST YOU TWICE AS MUCH, THOUGH.
- ( exclaims ) DUDE, COME ON.
GIVE ME A DISCOUNT?
YOU KNOW I CAN BARELY EVEN
AFFORD TO EAT THESE DAYS!
- BUY IT AND I'LL THROW
THIS ONE IN FOR FREE.
- WOW, THAT IS PRETTY HOT.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
- Nemoto: COME ON. I GOTTA SAY,
EXPECTED IT TO BE EASIER.THERE.
OH, YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
THEY WANT ANOTHER PASSWORD?
DAMN IT!
( panting ) MAN,
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- ( Akihisa avatars laughing )
- Toudou: SOMETHING
IS NOT RIGHT HERE.
- EXCUSE ME, MA'AM!
WE HAVE A PROBLEM!
SOMETHING IS WRONG WITH
THE SUMMONER TEST SYSTEM!
- YES. I AM AWARE OF THAT.
- THIS IS CRAZY... I CAN'T
BELIEVE THEY'VE SPREAD THIS FAR.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
- Boy 1: OKAY, THAT'S ANNOYING.
- ( Akihisa screams)
- Boy 2: GET OFF ME!
- STOP IT!
- LISTEN UP.
I'M GETTING SICK AND TIRED
OF YOUR PRANKS, YOSHII!
- WHAT THE CRAP? WHY IS THIS
AUTOMATICALLY MY FAULT?
- WHY'D YOU HAVE TO BREAK IT?
YOU SUCK.
- IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT,
JUST TELL US HOW TO FIX IT.
- NO ONE WILL BE MAD
AT YOU, I PROMISE.
- GREAT. YOU GUYS, TOO?
- AKI, IT'S OBVIOUS IT'S YOU.
NO ONE ELSE'S AVATAR IS
ACTING LIKE THAT.
WHAT THE... WHERE'D SHE GO?
- INTERESTING.
I WONDER IF THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH THE SYSTEM.
- I'M GONNA TRY SUMMONING
MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
- THIS IS NOT APPROPRIATE.
- CLOSE YOUR EYES! PLEASE!
- MY EYES! I CAN'T SEE! HELP!
I'M BLIND! I'M BLIND!
- SHE ASKED US
TO CLOSE OUR EYES, YUUJI.
- IS THIS THE FUTURE?
ARE WE LOOKING AT GROWN-UP
HIMEJI RIGHT NOW?
- WE'RE LOOKING AT SOMETHING
GROWING UP, THAT'S FOR SURE.
- I'M GONNA SUMMON
MY AVATAR, TOO! SUMMON!
- Akihisa: FIGURES. WHY AM I NOT
SURPRISED MINAMI'S AVATAR GROWS
EVERYWHERE EXCEPT
IN THE... FRANKENSTINE!
- I'M A GENIUS.
- IF I ZOOM IN A BIT,
I CAN SEE EVERYTHING.
- PLEASE DON'T DO THAT! I'VE
NEVER BEEN MORE EMBARRASSED!
- OH YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT!
- PLEASE DON'T TAKE THAT
PICTURE! PLEASE!
FINE, THEN YOU LEAVE ME
NO CHOICE. STOP!
- ( exclaims )
- ( buzzing )
- Kouta: SKELETON?
- IT WORKED IN THEORY, KOUTA.
GOOD IDEA.
- MAYBE I JUST NEED TO
TRY A DIFFERENT ANGLE.
- IT'S KIND OF LIKE PLAYING
DRESS-UP, ISN'T IT?
I THINK I'LL TRY
SUMMONING MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
OH, NO! DON'T EAT ME,
MISTER BIG BAD WOLF!
STOP THAT, THOSE AREN'T FOR YOU!
- COULD'VE TOLD YOU
THIS WAS GONNA HAPPEN.
YOU MAKE A HOT GIRL, THOUGH.
IT HURTS TO LOOK AT YOU!
- WELL, THIS CLARIFIES
EVERYTHING.
THE WHOLE SYSTEM
IS OUT OF ORDER!
- WELL, THEN, BETTER GIVE IT
A SHOT BEFORE IT'S FIXED.
SUMMON!
- BEAUTIFUL.
I'VE GOTTA TRY IT. SUMMON!
- ( Boys exclaiming )
- THEY LOOK GREAT TOGETHER.
- HEY, MAN, LET'S SEE
WHAT YOURS LOOKS LIKE.
- SUMMON!
- ( breathing heavily )
- HEY, STOP.
- I KNOW YOU WANT IT.
- STOP. STOP.
- HOLD ON, I DIDN'T... I DON'T
HAVE CONTROL OVER WHAT HE DOES!
YOU KNOW THE
SYSTEM'S SCREWED UP.
- YOU'VE BETRAYED ME, YUUJI.
- YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO HASN'T DONE IT, YOSHII.
DON'T YOU WANT TO SEE WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE?
- I KNOW I DO!
- YEAH, ALL RIGHT. SUMMON!
- ( Akihisa avatars clamoring )
- THIS IS REALLY SUCKS.
WHY'S MY AVATAR THE ONLY ONE
THAT'S FREAKING OUT LIKE THIS?
- HUH, THEY'RE NORMAL AGAIN.
- WHAT'S GOING ON NOW?
- EVERYTHING! THEY'RE POSSESSED!
- Hideyoshi: WHERE ARE
THEY GOING?
- Akihisa: THIS IS INSANE.
- Takahashi: THE TEACHERS'
AVATARS ARE THE CLOSEST
TO THE CORE OF THE SYSTEM
BUT IT APPEARS
THEY ARE COMPLETELY FROZEN
AND CANNOT BE SUMMONED.
THE STUDENTS' AVATARS
ARE OBVIOUSLY OUT OF CONTROL.
- Toudou: I DON'T GET THIS.
THERE'S NO WAY TO ACCESS
THE CRIME PREVENTION SYSTEM
IN THE SERVER ROOM.
AS IT IS RIGHT NOW,
WE CAN'T EVEN OPEN THE DOOR,
MUCH LESS GO IN TO FIX IT.
- WHAT IF WE TURN OFF THE POWER
AND COMPLETELY
RESTART THE SYSTEM?
- THE POWER SUPPLY UNIT KEEPS
EVERYTHING FUNCTIONING
FOR AT LEAST A MONTH
IN CASE OF A SHUT DOWN.
- I SEE. THEN I GUESS
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
BREAK THROUGH THE WALL AND
ENTER THAT WAY.
- WE MUST REMEDY THIS BEFORE
PRESENTING THE SYSTEM
AT THE CONFERENCE TOMORROW.
SHOWING THEM A HUGE
HOLE IN THE WALL
WOULD BE TERRIBLY
EMBARRASSING.
- WELL, THEN WHAT DO YOU
PROPOSE THAT WE DO?
- HMM... PERFECT!
WE'LL GET ONE
OF THE IDIOT STUDENTS TO DO IT.
- Akihisa: HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO FIX IT?
- A PROBATIONARY
STUDENT'S AVATAR IS RUN
FROM A SEPARATE AREA
OF THE SYSTEM.
SO UNLIKE YOUR
CLASSMATES' AVATARS,
YOURS WILL NOT BE AFFECTED BY
THE MALFUNCTION.
- THAT MAKES SENSE.
EXPLAINS WHY AKIHISA'S
SECOND-SELF
IS THE ONLY ONE THAT WAS
BEHAVING NORMALLY.
- IT WASN'T NORMAL.
I COULDN'T EVEN SUMMON HIM.
- THAT'S BECAUSE THE
TEACHER'S FIELD YOU USED
HAD ALSO BEEN AFFECTED.
BUT IF I RECALL, YOU DO HAVE
YOUR OWN FIELD, DON'T YOU?
- OH, YEAH. I GUESS I COULD
USE MY IRON BRACELET!
- ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SEND
YOUR AVATAR INTO THE SERVER ROOM
AND RECONNECT THE CABLE.
WHEN THAT'S DONE, I'LL SHUT DOWN
THE CRIME PREVENTION SYSTEM
FROM THE TERMINAL
AND OPEN THE DOOR.
- ONLY A PROBATIONARY STUDENT'S
AVATAR CAN PULL THIS OFF,
THEIR ABILITY TO TOUCH OBJECTS
IS CRUCIAL HERE.
- YEAH, BUT HOW IS HE SUPPOSED
TO GET IN THERE?
HE CAN'T JUST BUST
THROUGH THE WALL.
- GOOD QUESTION. THE SYSTEM IS
EQUIPPED WITH A COOLING VENT,
I'M SURE HE'S SMALL ENOUGH
TO WALK THROUGH IT.
- YEAH, BUT IF AKI CAN'T
SEE INSIDE THE VENT,
HOW IS HE SUPPOSED TO CONTROL
THE LITTLE GUY?
- CHECK THIS OUT,
VIDEO CAMERA AND TRANSMITTER.
- IF WE HAVE HIS AVATAR
TAKE IT WITH HIM,
THEN WE CAN SEE EVERYTHING
THAT'S GOING ON!
- GOOD CALL! WE LOVE KOUTA,
YES, WE DO!
- YOU JUST CARRY
THOSE THINGS WITH YOU?
WHAT WERE YOU GOING
TO USE THEM FOR?
- DON'T JUDGE HIM!
HE'S JUST MISUNDERSTOOD!
AND BY "MISUNDERSTOOD" I MEAN
A LITTLE CREEPY AND PERVY...
- I WAS MERELY ASKING A
QUESTION. I WASN'T JUDGING HIM.
- AKIHISA'S AN EXTREMELY
LOYAL CUSTOMER.
- THE EFFECTIVE FIELD AREA FOR
THE IRON BRACELET IS SMALL.
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO TO THE
FRONT OF THE SERVER ROOM
TO CONTROL YOUR AVATAR.
WE'LL GUIDE YOU
FROM OUT HERE.
- I GUESS THAT'S WHERE
HE GOES IN.
- AWAKEN. NOW. SUMMON!
LET'S GO!
- Mizuki: LOOK, THERE HE IS!
HE'S INSIDE THE VENT!
- Minami: OKAY, IT'S CLEAR!
- Yuuji: YOU'RE ALL GOOD.
JUST KEEP GOING STRAIGHT.
- Akihisa: GOT IT.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
HE IS A PROBATIONARY STUDENT,
WHAT IF HE JUST CAUSES
MORE TROUBLE?
- THEN WE'LL HAVE
TO HOPE HE DOESN'T.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT
IDIOT'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN USE THE IRON BRACELET.
- COUNT THREE TURNS
AND MAKE A RIGHT.
THEN TAKE A LEFT AT THE
NEXT INTERSECTION
- AM I IN A LABYRINTH?
THERE IT IS. WHY'S IT HAVE TO BE
SO COMPLICATED?
- Toudou: IT'S JUST
A SECURITY MEASURE.
- OW! OW! EVERYTHING HURTS.
LIKE, BAD.
WHY'S MY SCORE GOING DOWN?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- Fukuhara: YOU WALKED
THROUGH A POISONOUS SWAMP.
- WHY THE HELL WOULD THERE
BE A SWAMP IN HERE?
- Toudou: IT'S JUST
A SECURITY MEASURE.
- DUDE, YOU CAN GO AROUND IT.
TURN RIGHT AT THE NEXT CORNER.
- Akihisa: I SEE A LIGHT!
- Yuuji: YOU'RE ALMOST THERE,
JUST KEEP GOING STRAIGHT.
- HUH! WONDER WHAT IT IS.
AVATARS?
- Minami: THE PSYCHO AVATARS
ARE IN THERE!
- Mizuki: THEY'RE ABOUT
TO ATTACK!
- ( screaming )
- KNOCK IT OFF, YUUJI!
- IT'S NOT ME, MAN!
THEY'RE OUT OF CONTROL!
- THEY'RE WHAT? NO THEY'RE NOT!
SHUT UP! NO, STOP! HELP!
YOU GUYS PLEASE MAKE THEM STOP!
YUUJI! HIDEYOSHI! MINAMI!
HIMEJI! MOMMY!
DON'T DO THIS! I'M BEGGING YOU!
- ( beeping )
- Nishimura: MEET ME
IN THE REMEDIAL CLASSROOM!
- Akihisa: NO!
- Yuuji: BAKA AND TEST!
- YOU OKAY, YOSHII?
WHAT HAPPENED?
- I JUST HUNG OUT
IN HELL FOR A BIT.
- WHAT KIND OF REMEDIAL CLASS
WAS IT?
- LET'S CONTINUE
MOVING FORWARD.
WE WILL NOW BE TAKING
THE RECOVERY TEST
TO HELP BRING UP YOUR SCORES.
- UNLESS HE MAKES
A REALLY GOOD SCORE,
HE'LL BE SCREWED IF HE RUNS
INTO ANY MORE OF OUR AVATARS.
- IF YOU WANT I CAN HELP YOU...
STUDY, I MEAN.
IT'LL BE FUN
IF WE DO IT TOGETHER.
- ( in seductive voice)
IF YOU WANT I CAN HELP YOU.
- WHAT?
- IT'LL BE FUN
IF WE DO IT TOGETHER.
- YES, I WANT TO DO IT WITH YOU
MORE THAN ANYONE IN THE WORLD.
STUDY, I MEAN.
- WHY DO I GET THE IMPRESSION
THAT YOUR TEST SCORES
ARE THE LAST THING ON YOUR MIND?
- THE ONLY METHOD THAT WILL
ACTUALLY WORK
IS ONE THAT PRODUCES
IMMEDIATE RESULTS.
- IN THAT CASE I THINK
I HAVE THE ANSWER.
- Minami: I GET IT.
YOU MAKE THE TEST LIKE,
BONE-HEAD EASY,
AND AKI CAN ACTUALLY
GET A GOOD GRADE.
- AND IT'S ONLY KINDA CHEATING.
- WOW! I'VE NEVER SEEN AKIHISA
DO SO WELL ON A TEST BEFORE.
- Mizuki: YOU'RE DOING
SUCH A GOOD JOB, YOSHII!
- Minami: DON'T MESS IT UP, AKI!
- ( buzzing )
- YOU HAVE GOT TO BE
KIDDING ME.
WHICH ONE DID YOU MISS?
YOU DIDN'T KNOW THE TAIKA
REFORMS TOOK PLACE IN 645?
HOW COULD YOU MISS THAT AFTER
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED?
- I'M UNDER A LOT OF PRESSURE
HERE. I GOT CONFUSED, OKAY!
- EVEN WITH THAT,
HE DID MANAGE TO BRING HIS SCORE
UP QUITE A BIT.
- SO HE'S NOT A TOTAL LOSER.
I MEAN, IF THOSE GUYS COME
BACK, HE SHOULD BE OKAY.
- HE'LL BE FINE. LET'S DO THIS.
- ALL RIGHT!
SUMMON!
I CAN CLEAR THIS THING FOR SURE.
JUST WAIT AND SEE!
- OKAY, LEFT TURN AT
THE NEXT INTERSECTION.
- ON IT! ( screams )
- Fukuhara: IT WAS
THE POISONOUS SWAMP.
- I GUESS WE NEED TO TEACH HIM
SOME TRICKS TO AVOID THAT.
- I AM NOT AN ANIMAL!
- OKAY, SO THIS TIME
TAKE A RIGHT.
- I KNOW. WHAT THE...
- ALL RIGHT, LISTEN,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO BE
REALLY CAREFUL HERE.
IF YOU TOUCH IT YOU'LL...
- ( Akihisa screaming )
- Mizuki: OH, MY GOSH!
- Minami: AKI!
- I CAN'T BREATHE!
- Yuuji: WHICH PART OF "BE
CAREFUL" DID YOU NOT UNDERSTAND?
- I COULDN'T HELP IT!
IT WAS HABIT!
WHAT'S THAT?
HEY, WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
I'M READY FOR YOU THIS TIME.
IN YOUR FACE!
- YOSHII, YOU HAVE
TO STAY FOCUSED!
- LOOK OUT! KOUTA'S
RIGHT BEHIND YOU!
- I GOT THIS. THE SUBJECT
WE'RE FIGHTING IS HISTORY.
IF THE MASKED PERV
ISN'T BATTLING
WITH HEALTH AND
PHYS. ED KNOWLEDGE,
HE'S DEAD BEFORE
HE EVEN ATTACKS!
- ( screaming )
- Fukuhara: IT WAS
THE POISONOUS SWAMP.
- THOSE WHO DIED, MEET ME
IN THE REMEDIAL CLASSROOM!
- Hideyoshi: HOW IS THAT FAIR?
- WE WEREN'T EVEN FIGHTING! OUR
AVATARS ARE POSSESSED, MAN!
- I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT!
- Kouta: YOU'RE
FREAKISHLY STRONG.
- I MADE IT!
- LOOK FOR A DISCONNECTED CABLE
AND WHEN YOU FIND
IT, CONNECT IT.
- OKAY!
HUH! I FOUND IT!
MINAMI?
- AKI?
- RUN!
- Akihisa: NOT YET!
- PLEASE HURRY!
IF YOU DON'T,
IT COULD GET WORSE.
- Akihisa: HIMEJI?
- ONE, TWO, THREE!
- HOLD ON, YOSHII!
- ( bell ringing )
- HE CAN'T WIN THIS ONE!
- AKI!
- ( Akihisa groaning ) NO!
( screams )
( gasps )
- Mizuki: SOMETHING'S COMING!
COME ON, SUMMONING
FIELD! PLEASE SYNC!
I THINK IT'S... IT'S
ANOTHER AVATAR!
- Miharu: HONEY BISCUIT!
- Minami: MIHARU?
- HELLO, SUGAR CUPS, YOU DIDN'T
THINK I'D LET YOU
OR YOUR HOLOGRAPH OF HOTNESS
FIGHT THAT THING ALONE, DID YOU?
BESIDES, IT'S MY DUTY
TO PROTECT YOU
FROM BREATHING GROSS BOY AIR.
- NOW!
- ( both screaming )
- TO THE REMEDIAL CLASSROOM!
- I DON'T WANNA!
- THIS IS GONNA BE SO FUN!
- Akihisa: HIMEJI, I'M SORRY!
- NOT TOO BAD.
- ( avatars screaming )
- Mizuki: YOSHII! PLEASE RUN!
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO BEAT HER!
- NO WAY. I'VE COME TOO FAR.
I'M NOT BACKING DOWN.
( screams )
- YOSHII, NO!
- COME ON, I'M SO CLOSE!
- HE WON'T BE ABLE TO FIGHT MUCH
LONGER. WE NEED TO STOP HIM!
AS EDUCATORS, IT'S OUR
FIRST RESPONSIBILITY
TO KEEP OUR STUDENTS SAFE.
- NO! I'M FINE!
I STILL HAVE SOME POINTS LEFT!
- THERE IS TOO BIG OF A GAP
BETWEEN THE SCORES RIGHT NOW.
AND YOUR ABILITY LEVEL
IS TOO LOW!
- I DON'T CARE. WAIT!
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU GUYS, I CAN RAISE MY ABILITY
LEVEL THE SAME WAY!
THE TEST DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
ABOUT MY OWN ACTUAL ABILITY.
HIMEJI, TAKE THE RECOVERY TEST!
JUST TAKE IT!
- OH, I GET IT NOW!
MS. TAKAHASHI, CAN I TAKE IT?
- IT'S RISKY. IF YOU RAISE
YOUR SCORE EVEN BY ONE POINT,
HE WON'T HAVE A CHANCE.
- ( screaming )
- I'M DONE! PLEASE GRADE IT!
YES! YOU DID IT!
- Takahashi: I DON'T
BELIEVE THIS.
ZERO POINTS!
- GOOD WORK, LITTLE GUY.
- Takahashi: IT WORKED,
THE SYSTEM HAS BEEN RECOVERED!
- AT LEAST FOR THE TIME BEING.
I'M IMPRESSED.
- ( theme song playing )
- YOU DID GREAT!
ARE YOU OKAY, YOSHII?
- YEAH. JUST ONE HANGING OUT'S
NOT GONNA HURT ME.
- THOSE WHO DIED WITH THE
PATHETIC SCORE OF ZERO,
MEET ME IN THE
REMEDIAL CLASSROOM!
- THAT'D ME,
GUESS I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
- OKAY.
THANKS A LOT, HIMEJI.
- WHAT'S WITH THE GLOOMY LOOK?
- OW! THAT HURT! WHY WOULD
YOU DO THAT?
MY POINTS! I'M LOSING THEM!
- IS SIX POINTS REALLY
SO IMPORTANT?
YOU SHOULD TAKE THE
REMEDIAL CLASS ANYWAY
WITH A SCORE LIKE THAT.
- LET'S GO, YOSHII!
- OKAY!
- I'D SAY THAT QUALIFIES
AS A DAY.
TALK ABOUT A GAMBLE, ENTRUSTING
SOMETHING SO IMPORTANT
TO A CLASS F STUDENT.
BUT I'M GLAD EVERYTHING
WORKED OUT IN THE END.
- ACTUALLY, NO. I DON'T THINK IT
WAS MUCH OF A GAMBLE AT ALL.
THERE'S A SPECIFIC WAY TO HANDLE
THE IDIOTS WE HAVE HERE.
YOU'LL LEARN, EVENTUALLY.
- I'M FINISHED.
WILL YOU PLEASE GRADE IT?
- Fukuhara: QUESTION NINE.
ONE OF THE UNITS USED TO
INDICATE BREAST SIZE IS "CUP".
EXPLAIN THE SIZE OF AN A CUP,
WHICH IS USED AS A BASIS.
- Akihisa: MINAMI SHIMADA.
- NO COMMENT.
- NEXT TIME! KISSES, BREASTS,
AND PONYTAILS!
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.