Fuck you!
I was wrong about you, traitor!
Richie, wait!
Listen to me!
Don't touch me!
I don't want to listen to you!
I don't need you anymore.
You changed me so much I don't remember what I was like before we met.
The breeze caresses our cheeks.
Lullaby of Birdland...
As we run down the slope,
our flimsy shadows extend.
It's like a neverending summer vacation.
It feels like when we snuck into the pool.
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
It's an intense spiral of temptation.
A beat pierces my heart. A strange one.
It vanishes after a quick spark.
Even on bad days, I dress up
and dance to some swing. The music quickly surrounds me.
What is this dance exactly? I can't stop it.
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
The melody...
is like love.
My feet feel heavy.
It's like I'm climbing this slope for the first time all over again.
Kaoru.
Would you like this onigiri?
Why? I'm fine.
I'm already stuffed.
A few bites of bread won't keep you goin'.
I guess I'll have one.
This is good.
What's in it?
Let's see. Clams boiled in soy sauce.
I shouldn't have said that!
I'm such an idiot!
Me and my big mouth!
Hey, Ri,
I can't help but notice that you're on really good terms with Nishimi lately!
Tell me the truth.
Are you two going steady?
N-No!
Look at her. She's blushing!
You don't have to hide it from us!
We're in your corner!
But we're not...
U-Um...
Honestly, we're not dating.
Mukae and I are just friends.
So...
please don't get the wrong idea.
Crap. What did I butt in for?
This is a surprise.
Nishimi, you hardly ever talk, so I've always thought you were kind of unapproachable.
I could've sworn you were going to blow your stack at us.
M-Me too.
Hey, tell us something.
What's the trick to getting good scores on tests?
Yeah, I wanted to ask the same thing.
Oh, I don't...
Oh, we've put him on the spot.
Huh? What do you know?
I don't feel sick at all.
Hey, Richie.
Don't ignore me!
Would you just listen to me, you blockhead?
Wow, what a pad, Yamaoka!
It's even separate from your house.
This is where we're gonna practice from now on!
Huh? Kawabuchi, you look kinda glum.
Are you having second thoughts?
Don't be stupid.
Once I decide I'm gonna do somethin', I see it through.
That's the way to be.
We better hurry up an' decide what songs we're gonna do. What's it gonna be?
Well, I wanna get The Spiders in there.
And The Ventures, of course. And then...
Hey, what about The Beatles?
What's with all the different genres?
I think the girls will dig it more if we play a variety.
Huh?
That isn't what you said before!
Ryunosuke.
We just got a roll cake.
Why don't you share it with your friends?
Mama! Don't bug us!
We'd love to have some roll cake, ma'am.
Let's discuss this over a snack, okay, Ryunosuke?
Kawabuchi, are you coming?
Nah. I'm gonna practice a little by myself.
Oh.
Pops.
What are you doin' wearin' a tie on a hot day like this?
Oh. I'm in mourning.
For who?
John Coltrane.
C-Coltrane died?!
You didn't know?
Well, I guess there's no way a rock and roller would know about it.
Please don't bust my chops about that, Pops.
That aside, have a look in the shop.
There's a familiar beauty inside.
Y-Yurika?
Oh, my. I haven't seen you in a while, Sentaro.
I heard that you're going to be in a rock band for the school festival.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yurika, Chet Baker...
If you're interested, wanna hear it?
Sentaro, I...
Please, don't say anything.
I can't.
Because... I...
Wh-Who's down there?!
Oh, sorry. Didn't mean to interrupt, Sen-boy.
Jun?
Don't pay no attention to me.
Go on with what you were doing.
Crap! I forgot to tell him about Junichi!
Yurika!
Hey, Sen-boy. Your woman forgot something.
Sen!
That packed quite a wallop.
What are you lookin' at me like that for?
You're not satisfied with one punch?
Wait, Sen.
Junichi kind of had a breakdown.
Jun?
What's wrong?
Hey, what happened, Sentaro?
Sentaro, wait!
Okay, everyone...
I'd like to decide on the festival committee members.
I'm open to volunteers or nominations.
Okay!
I nominate Nishimi and Mukae!
I'm sure those two would take
responsibility and do a good job!
I think that's a good idea too!
No objections here!
East High School Festival
Talent Show Sign-Up Reception
Oh, the brass band.
Could you write the representatives' names along with the program?
Um, could I have an application form?
Here you are.
You're good to go!
I'm sorry, Kaoru.
The new term's just begun, and you've been saddled with this busy job.
Actually, I've never had a chance to take on a responsibility like this because I transferred so often.
It's more fun than I thought.
Kaoru, have you talked to Sentaro recently?
No.
Then you wouldn't know about it.
He punched Jun a few days ago at the shop.
I didn't see it myself, and I
don't know what it was about,
but I heard Yurika was at the shop that day.
Could you two bring the completed
applications to the student council office?
Sure. I'll do it.
Kaoru, stay here at the reception desk.
Okay.
Oh, Ri'ko, good timing.
You're on the committee, right?
Do me a favor an' copy this info
onto the application, would ya?
Forget it! The reception desk is in the materials room.
Go up there, and fill out the form yourself.
I can't accept a scrap of paper.
Fill out a form.
Did he really hit Jun?
Is he taking it all on himself and suffering in silence?
Hey-
That band name... In katakana, it should be spelled
with a "Ji," not a "Za," for "The Olympus."
"Za" is fine.
No, it's not.
No, that isn't what I want to say.
Sen-
Excuse me! Is there still time to sign up?
Yes.
Whew! Good!
Za Olympus
The Olympus
Somewhere in my heart, there was still a little pain and regret.
As the festival drew closer,
I became busier with my committee duties, and before I knew it,
the distance between us had grown.
I even looked back fondly on our silly conversations,
but they seemed so long ago.
18th School Festival
And at last, the day of the festival arrived.
The Olympus is next!
I'm gonna go to the front!
I can't wait!
Are you ready, ladies?
One, two, three, four!
Look at him with that smile on his face.
Which girl is he gonna chase now?
Kaoru.
You two will go back to jamming at my place once this is over, right?
Um...
You're not going to listen from inside?
Things are... awkward between me and Sentaro right now.
It's my fault.
I gave in to my loneliness... and betrayed him in the worst of ways.
What the...?
You're on the committee, right? Follow me!
What happened?
The amps quit working all of a sudden!
Not good.
The electricity didn't go out.
Sorry, but could you help look for the problem? We'll split up.
Boy, what a bummer, huh?
Hey, second-year!
You can't do anythin' without electricity, so quit actin' big!
I bet you just wanted to show off
your fancy shmancy electric guitars!
Rub your money in our faces!
Why don't you get off the stage?
Th-That's not what...
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but him an' I are poor, and
the instruments are borrowed.
He may be a flashy guy, but he's got a real goal,
so I'll ask you upperclassmen
to stop interruptin' just to amuse yourselves.
Kawabuchi, you're actually a nice guy.
I'm seeing you in a new light.
"Actually," huh? I'm always nice!
Ow! Y-Yes, of course, of course you are!
B-But I really am surprised.
I never thought you would join the band.
Yeah. I was gonna refuse at first.
But I changed my mind after Matsuoka told me
he wanted to become a star so he could
support his parents and brothers.
I know how it feels to desperately want to be useful to your family.
U-Um... Kawabuchi, would you
consider staying with the band?
Nah. This was a one-shot deal for me.
Jazz is more up my alley.
Besides...
I'm keeping my important partner waiting.
They can't fix it, huh?
Guess I'll go.
No, don't leave!
Wait! Wait!
Please!
Don't panic.
I'll keep them occupied for a little while.
Be ready to go on as soon as the problem's fixed.
What's he doing all of a sudden?
He's wearing an armband.
He must be on the committee.
This song...
Can we get it all back?
Hey, what's goin' on?
Kawabuchi.
But... it sounds totally different than it did then.
It's like a friendly argument between two princes as they come back home.
Richie!
What the heck?!
They're running away?!
How cool.
My body feels light.
It's as if I've been reborn.
My feet...
feel like they have wings on them.
I was waiting for you on that slope.
We made a promise to meet after school.
The goodbye blurred into the distance.
So weak, so twisted, so fragile
had I been back then,
but you gave me a small pair of wings.
I'm searching the sky beyond the twilight
for the faint flicker of light
because I want to tell you I love you.
I wrote a letter to you in my textbook margins,
but I could never give it to you.
It's still just there.