Stomp!
Selfish!
Quit stalling and finish them off!
Self!
Found a puddle!
I said finish them off, not my makeup!
You must respect those around you when playing in puddles!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Love love loooooove!
I'll remember this!
Now girls, let us return home.
Aguri...
Grandmother?!
Did you... see that?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
To the Person I Love!
Aguri's Career Day!
I've come home...
Aguri.
Tomorrow is Career Day,
so shall we walk to school toge—
We'll discuss it later.
I let Grandmother see me...
How could I have been so careless?
Aguri.
Would you like to eat supper?
No, I'm fine.
Are you worried over what happened earlier?
I knew long ago...
that your destiny would be special.
I had planned to stay silent for a bit longer,
but I suppose now is the time.
We spoke before about how I took you in when you had no relatives.
Do you remember the day we met?
I don't remember perfectly.
I'd be surprised if you could.
Because at the time...
you were a newborn baby.
One year ago, as I was preparing a tea ceremony...
There, there...
Selfish!
Self!
This child is—
Cure Ace.
The legendary warrior of light.
Please, look after her.
I did as that mysterious voice asked and looked after of you.
The girls with you...
were Mana and her friends, correct?
Aguri?
It's really pouring.
Now that she's seen us transforming,
I think we should have a serious talk with Mari.
But Aguri said she didn't want to involve her in the Precure battles.
We simply must consider Aguri's feelings first.
Let's check up on her tomorrow.
Yeah.
Well, see y—
Aguri!
What happened?
Rikka!
Could you invent a machine to turn back time?
Huh?
The Yotsuba Conglomerate could fund it!
Well, uh...
Oh yeah!
Ai, use your magic!
Wait, calm down!
What?!
Mari knew about everything?
Yes, even things that I had not known.
She said I grew ten years in an instant!
Uhh...
That doesn't surprise you?
I thought it was the most shocking revelation, so I saved it for last...
Well, uh... you know?
You always use your emotions to grow older when you transform into a Precure, right?
Well, I suppose...
So, you were born in a bamboo field just like Princess Kaguya!
Princess Kaguya?
It's the story of a princess...
who was raised among humans, but returned to her home on the moon.
'Scuse me, I got a question!
Aguri, you once told us that you lost to a Selfish.
Just when did this happen?
That's what I'd like to know as well!
My loss to a Selfish happened before I met Grandmother...
It should be my oldest memory!
Your oldest memory?
I... don't have any memories before that.
I assumed it was due to the trauma of my defeat...
I'm sorry.
This story would have revealed the fact that I have no blood relation to Grandmother,
so I never told you.
You don't need to apologize.
It now seems strange that I could have battled a Selfish as a baby before meeting Grandmother.
A bit...
But lately, I've been having dreams of Princess Ann battling King Selfish!
What if the memory of being defeated by a Selfish is not my own?
I wonder who it was that entrusted you to Mari.
But the biggest mystery is...
Who I truly am, correct?
My head's spinnin'!
The plot keeps thickening!
Regardless,
I can no longer trouble Grandmother!
We can never be together again.
Mana?
Mari's on the phone.
Hi, we switched the phone.
Ah, so Aguri really is with you.
Yes.
I'm certain she's searching for you.
Aguri,
how about you stay over tonight?
Don't worry.
I asked Mari about it, and she gave her permission.
How much did you talk about?
About that Career Day you've got tomorrow, for starters.
Mari said she was looking forward to it!
Is that true?
Yes.
We're drawing a picture in front of our parents and then sharing it with them.
I told her we'd all be sure to drop you off at school.
We'd "all"?
Yep! You're all staying over, too!
We're having a pajama party tonight!
Why not?
It's quite a nice idea!
But...
You can't have a party...
Without sweets!
Sweets!
Th-That was just a reflex...
Aw, don't be shy!
All right girls, this night is gonna rule!
This one!
Hey!
You got any idea what time it is?!
Can't sleep?
You said earlier that you didn't want to trouble Mari anymore...
but I'm sure she doesn't think of you as a trouble at all.
What makes you say that?
Because she asked me to do something earlier.
To take care of you.
She wouldn't ask that if she didn't care about you.
People don't turn on the ones they love that quickly.
Emotional bonds are quite strong.
Cure Ace is Cure Ace,
and you are who you are.
You're a dear friend to us.
I'm sure Mari feels the same way.
What do you want to do?
Do you really want to run away from Mari?
I... want to stay with her.
Then how about you tell her that when you see her tomorrow?
I will!
Don't worry!
Oh, your grandma came!
Grandmother...
The person you love the most
Today, you're drawing pictures of the person you love the most.
When you're finished, share it with your mother or father.
Okay!
The person I love...
What's this picture?
57th Graduating Class, Friends Forever
"57th Graduating Class, Friends Forever"?
That's silly!
57th Graduating Class, Friends Forever
What'd they scribble this junk for?
It's worthless.
But they won't lose their love as long as they have their pictures.
So I'll erase them all from the world!
The person you love the most
So yeah, my dad's the person I love the most!
Your father seems quite elated.
Now, who wants to share their work next?
Has anyone else finished their drawings?
I'm gonna erase it!
Rub, rub, rub!
Keep it up! Erase every picture in school!
I wanna erase more!
Did a Selfish do that?
Erase it all!
Everyone, please come this way.
Aguri!
E-rase, e-rase, e-rase, e-rase!
E-rase!
Stop right there!
I will tolerate no further vandalism!
Regina!
Ai!
Kyupirappa!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor eraser who has lost its love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Could you quit being a pain for once?!
You're like roaches!
Stop this already!
Shaddup!
Shut uuuuup!
Erase those Precures!
Selfish!
E!
Rase!
No running in the halls!
Eraser Machine Gun!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Magical Lovely Pad!
Sword Hurricane!
Seeeeelf!
Ish...
We'll finish him in one strike.
Not happenin'.
There's still a lot of pictures left.
Those are...
the pictures we all drew for the people we loved!
People you love?
Yes!
We drew those priceless pictures to share them with those we care about!
You don't say?
Erase 'em, Selfish!
Don't do it!
I said to stop being a pain!
That's mine!
Gotcha, chief!
Eraseraserase...
C'mon, nobody would want that chicken-scratch.
You shouldn't have even drawn it in the first place.
That's not true.
Grandmother!
This picture was drawn for me by my dear granddaughter.
You can erase its colors,
but the shade of love it holds will never fade!
I accept your feelings.
Thank you, Aguri.
Grandmother...
Self?
Could it be?
This warm light...
My chest is tingling...
Selfish, destroy those two!
Erase!
You will not succeed.
Because I, Madoka Aguri, shall not allow you to lay one finger on Grandmother!
Grandmother, I may well continue to be a burden upon you,
but I will spare no effort to protect you!
So let me stay by your side, I beg of you!
I should ask the same to you!
Erase!
Let us go.
Kyupirappa!
Erase!
Precure Royal Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love loooooove!
I apologize for running away without a word!
In light of your picture, I'll forgive you if you weed the garden.
Is there anything you'd like for dinner?
I'd like your braised burdock and carrots!
All right, then.
Now let's return home.
Yes!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Student Council President Speech Contest?
It's to determine who the best Student Council Pres in Japan is.
Some past participants have gone on to become Prime Ministers!
This sounds like it was made for Mana!
I'm already there!
It seems this contest is only held on Christmas!
Huh? But we were all gonna hang out that day!
Dokidoki Precure:
A Selfish Trap!
A Christmas Without Mana!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!