Tsukuyomi
Shrine
Activity
Log
Scribe
Mickie
(Alias)
Tsukuyomi Shrine Activity Log,
Scribe,
Mickie.
Scribe
Mickie
(Alias)
The head of the family, Tsukuyomi Ruza,
has not left the home since the incident several days ago,
and now,
he mostly surfs channels,
nibbles on chips,
and moans about not wanting to work,
and now, he spends all day lying around the house.
I've been measuring,
and out of his commonly used phrases,
"I don't wanna work."
I don't wanna work
"I don't wanna try."
I don't wanna try
"I wanna die."
I wanna die
are his top three,
with "I don't wanna work" at 132 uses,
"I don't wanna try" at 1032 uses,
and "I wanna die" at an immeasurable count.
Ugh...
I wanna die.
I wanna die
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 8
Tactical Loneliness
I am no mere shut-in.
Those who dare invade
my lair shall be cursed.
Tsukuyomi Sasami
Those who dare invade
my lair shall be cursed.
Tsukuyomi Sasami
I am a barricade-in!
I can't allow anyone to invade my lair.
This is madness, Empress Sasami!
The Yagami sisters are mighty gods!
The odds of them breaking through are great!
Fear not, private.
I'm prepared to fight to the death!
I will use every ounce of my heretofore restrained Supreme God's Power!
They shall not pass!
Oh, finally!
I will not do a damn thing this Spring Break!
I'm going to lie in bed the whole time!
And nobody will bother me!
I'll do nothing...
even if it kills me!
Oh,
he died.
Are you okay, Paparin?
I haven't spoken to Sasami in 34 hours.
I haven't touched Sasami in 76 hours.
I haven't bathed with Sasami in 127 hours!
Teacher, you must stay strong!
Oh, Sasami?
Sasami!
Sasami, I've missed you!
GYAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
Oh, Sasami's scent.
Sasami's warmth!
Sasami's touch!
I love you, Sasami!
You're my everything!
T-Teacher, you dummy...
Currently, we have two problems.
The first is that Sister has fallen into the underworld and has yet to return.
The second
is the cause of Sasami's sudden fortification.
Take a look.
This is the house you and Sasami live in.
This black structure is the Heavenly Rock Door.
It is a manifestation of the Supreme God Amaterasu's desire to not see anything, meet anyone, or do anything,
and appears when she tries to shut herself off from the world.
It is a drastic barrier.
Wow! That's more important!
You understood unusually quickly, Tama.
Y-Yeah.
As usual, you understood nothing.
Y-Yeah!
At this rate, the world will be as though the Supreme God abandoned her post,
increasing the risk of an outbreak of unfavorable Transformations and plunging the world into chaos.
And this unnatural snowstorm would be one of those, yes?
Regardless, we must break through that rock door
and ascertain Sasami's status.
Everyone,
hold on to me.
Now, we shall leave.
One, two!
This seems somewhat dangerous!
Alert!
Sasami!
Any further advance shall be met with force!
Just leave me alone already!
I don't want to be separated from Sasami for even a second!
If I don't breathe your breath,
or absorb your sweat, tears, and other excretions like a Sasami stew, I'll die!
Shut it, creep!
Sasami, stop shutting yourself in!
Turn off the Heavenly Rock Door!
Just leave me alone!
It's not like I'm staying inside for my health!
Perhaps...
Sasami, do you have any troubles that make you want to run away from the world?
Are you hiding something?
If you are troubled, please talk to me.
I can help you!
I didn't ask for your meddling!
So just go away!
Otherwise, I'll shoot.
So be it.
We shall push on against all odds,
and make you regret your conceit.
We will spank you until you apologize in tears!
And then we will save you from your worries!
Just give up and leave!
The shallow tactics of a shut-in with no combat experience
will not work on me!
Wait, she plans to melt my clothing?
What horrors are you plotting?
No!
If you don't turn tail now,
I'll strip you and post pictures all over the internet!
I'll tag them as Excellent Kagami, the Unidentified Flying Nudist!
Do you have no soul?
That's mean, Mamarin!
Don't bully Kagami!
Please, I beg you,
if you strip anyone, strip me!
Keep it on!
I have already stripped!
Scram, creep.
I'll concentrate all of my power,
and make Excellent Kagami a worldwide idol,
Cover Story! Returning Home After A Month In LA
She won't retire!
KAGAMI's
comeback!
then a movie star, a nationwide craze,
and finally, a legend!
If you don't like it, leave!
You are a monster, Sasami.
And here I thought we were friends!
Kagami, I'm sorry!
Miss me?
Tsurugi!
It's hard to nullify divine attacks with the Supreme God's power alone,
but not with this sword!
The Heavenly Gathering of Clouds...
But how, Sister?
I tied my lifeline to this divine sword,
and got out of the underworld with it!
A god can't normally get past the Heavenly Rock Door,
but a new age god could eat it!
Tama, make a hole for us!
Gotcha, Tsurugi!
Kagami, bring us in close!
Understood.
Mow them down, Heavenly Gathering of Clouds!
Dinnertime!
They broke through!
Please excuse us.
Now then, would you like to explain yourself, Sasami?
We may forgive you based on what we hear.
Don't be so rough.
Sasami's got her reasons.
C'mon,
show us!
Um... well...
I didn't know what to do!
I had some tasty pizza yesterday,
and then I woke up and saw this!
I couldn't Transform my way out of it,
and I thought everyone would hate me,
maybe even my own brother,
so I sat here thinking and didn't talk to anyone,
but you guys couldn't take a hint and barged in!
You idiots!
Go away!
Just go away!
I... understand how you feel,
but we are friends.
I am happy you chose to share it with us.
Kagami...
No matter how much one overeats,
this could not happen in just one day.
It could be some form of supernatural affliction.
Allow me to explain.
The culprit is that Tsukuyomi priestess.
There's still some of her left.
So let me in,
Sasami.
Wh-What is this?
People from the Tsukuyomi Shrine?
What's wrong, Tsukuyomi Juju?
Your power is said to be the greatest of them all,
so please, show it to me.
Do not think that I am a mere decorative vessel for the Supreme God's power!
This is...
Me?
What?
What the heck is happening?
Where are the others?
And this... is my mother?
Am I in the past?
Tsukuyomi Juju,
I, the idle gravekeeper Baron Samedi,
shall dig your grave here!
Attack, zombies!
A living corpse is but dead.
And the dead belong...
That's the Incantation of Chigaeshi...
The god Chigaeshi
is the enormous boulder used to stop Izanami from escaping Hell!
Its effect on the dead is instant.
Repent, god of foreign lands!
And leave our lands at once!
What a waste of time.
Whoah!
But why did Tsurugi take me to the past?
What did she say was left?
Madam Juju!
Where are you?
Is that Mickie?
Oh, Madam Juju!
Madam Juju!
Mickie!
What a shock!
I thought I was going to die!
You were.
I'm deeply sorry, Madam Juju!
A god may bring your doom before a demon.
You must handle them with meticulous detail.
Right. I am deeply ashamed.
The Tsukuyomi Shrine is still all right.
So I really am...
in the past.
So, Mickie,
seeing as you searched for me,
you must have had some business, no?
Yes, Madam Juju.
You see, Sasami...
Huh?
Me?
This way, Madam Juju.
Sasami faints rather often.
It is no rare occurrence.
Perhaps she snuck out to the city again, and while there,
came down with a strange disease, no?
But we've tried doctors and priestesses alike,
and she still won't get better.
If it is some manner of curse,
your low spiritual power may put you in danger.
Stay back.
I will.
Be careful, Madam Juju.
Mom...
Are you awake?
I'm sorry, Mom...
Hush.
I may be a Tsukuyomi priestess,
but I am also your mother.
Now rest.
Grow up soon, Sasami.
That is the one thing you can do.
When you become an adult,
the times will be a bit better than they are now.
I'm sorry for burdening you...
I'm weak...
Do not apologize.
Being weak is not a sin.
The world is hurtful to ones as weak as you,
and it is my own foolishness for not changing it.
I will not apologize, either.
Instead...
I will try.
Mom!
Now, between Sasami growing up and me passing on,
which will occur sooner?
Mom...
But you've already...
Is that...
my brother?
Do not pace restlessly.
I know not your character,
and I understand you bear no ill intent.
But if, on slim chance, you bring misfortune,
I shall wring your neck myself.
I bear you no compassion.
Nor pity.
However...
it would be good for you to be saved.
I'm satisfied with my position, and my fate.
Is that so?
Then I will say nothing.
I'll return to nursing Sasami.
If that has shown itself,
then I suppose it has chosen Sasami.
What's that?!
My tummy is rumbling.
Oh, that was you?
Nay, a Tsukuyomi priestess has no need for selfishness!
I shall endure all desire,
and keep my mind and body pure...
Mickie.
Wh-What business do you have, Madam Juju?
Now now, be at ease.
Do you have any food?
The meals for the night guards will be finished soon.
Please wait a bit.
Right.
Oh yeah!
How about making rice porridge for Madam Sasami's dinner?
Yes, with Sasami as she is now,
something easily digestible would be easier to stomach.
Mom...
Yes, Mickie!
Create it!
Not that!
I meant that you should create it for Madam Sasami.
But I cannot cook.
Then I'll teach you.
Sasami is a real mother's girl,
so she'll be delighted to eat something her mother makes!
That said, I don't know much about parental relationships,
so I can't say for sure.
Because you were spirited away.
Spirited away?
You were born with too great a spiritual power,
so you were targeted and kidnapped by evil gods.
And then, all of your spiritual power was sucked away.
Along with the memories of your family, and even your name.
That's why...
as someone in a similar position, I understand how Madam Sasami feels.
Similar position?
Everyone around me is better than me,
so I worry and tell myself to work harder,
so I know how it feels to drive yourself into a corner.
But it's better if you have a family by your side to help.
My daughter must one day be thrust into a hellish fate,
and keeping her just a bit pure, neat, and secure
is the sole gift I can provide for my daughter.
Nay, even with that excuse,
I run from the daughter who grew so innocently attached to me.
But I am a Tsukuyomi priestess.
I cannot be a normal woman, much less a mother.
Mom...
Which path is correct?
Madam Juju...
Mom was always thinking about me...
She thought about when I'd inherit her duty,
and tried to make the world just a little better for me.
And despite all that, I betrayed her...
Madam Juju, get down!
Mickie!
You monster!
That's...
me?!
Release my daughter!
Oh, but I'm afraid I can't!
Oops, I cleared out all the guards, so nobody will come to help you!
This shrine is protected by a secure barrier!
How did you get in?
While Baron Samedi lured you out,
this girl was playing around in town.
That's when I caught her!
So, it was my fault?
No, wait. I don't remember this!
This isn't my past!
I hid myself inside the girl,
allowing me to slip inside without anyone noticing!
Even in the original timeline,
not a soul noticed my presence!
The original timeline?
What are you talking about?
Oops, I shouldn't be talking to you!
I know you're there, Tsukuyomi Sasami!
Huh? How?
Me?
I came to make a deal with you.
What about?
I'm an assassin from the corrupt occult society, Arahabaki,
a spirit living inside this Killing Stone golem!
And a fair skinned, golden haired nine tailed fox!
Nine tailed fox?
This country knows me as the playfully chaotic Tamamo-no-Mae!
Tamamo-no-Mae?
Hey there,
haven't you ever wanted to change the past?
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Sasami!
It's time for the ending!
Don't hide in your bed, come on out!
No matter how fat you might become,
your brother will always love you!
I want to cuddle with your softness!
I want to be crushed under the weight!
Please get a grip, Teacher.
You know how the Heavenly Rock Door story is.
According to the legend,
we should simply drag Sasami out.
I understand perfectly!
... How do we do it?
I will let that one slide.
Um, basically, we all surround her bed and make silly noises.
Once we do, curiosity should take Sasami, causing her to peek out of her covers.
I understand!
Let's combine our voices and sing with joy!
Join in, viewers!
I can hear your voice
everywhere like a resounding symphony
Huh? Mamarin didn't come out at all.
Perhaps she's asleep?
Sasami, if you fall asleep on air,
we could get pulled!
Looking closely, Sister appears to be asleep as well.
I wonder what kinda dreams she's having!
She grumbled about a nine tailed fox in her sleep.
Foxies, yip yip!
I have grown tired as well.
Next Episode
It's time for Sluggish Shopping.
Sluggish@Shopping
I'd like to introduce you to this product.
The Vain Vacuum Cleaner EX.
Vain Vacuum Cleaner EX
What part of it is in vain, you ask?
When you try to roll up the power cord,
the cord vainly stops halfway and dangles in vain.
Makes a great gift to those who like to be annoyed.
Sluggish@Shopping
Next time, on Episode 9.
Next Time, on Episode 9
I Totally Can.
I Totally Can