A month had passed since the six boys were sent to this school.
By then, they were all calling each other by nicknames.
Tuck your chin!
Elbows in!
Sakuragi Rokurouta （18）
Nickname: Bro
Punch like you're driving in a nail.
Faster!
Minakami Mario （17）
Nickname: Mario
Good!
You're so pathetic, Mario.
You're still a long way from being a boxer...
Tohyama Tadayoshi（17）
Nickname: Soldier
if that's enough to make you tired.
Shut up!
Hey, Soldier.
Matsu'ura Mansaku（17）
Nickname: Cabbage
I'm getting tired.
Can we stop now?
Are you kidding?
I got a hundred more!
When it comes down to it,
you need strength, Cabbage.
All right!
Maeda Noboru（16）
Nickname: Turtle
I win again.
Oh, guess so.
Sorry, Joe.
So you owe me 200 yen.
Yokosuka Jou（16）
Nickname: Joe
Turtle...
why don't you put some muscle on your bones?
I don't need to.
I got these teeth.
Though they didn't work on Bro.
No one can ever last more than three minutes under my teeth.
That's ridiculous.
What was that, Uncovered?
Nomoto Ryuji（17）
Nickname: Uncovered
Even if you have a strong jaw,
a slit on your neck will kill you anyway.
I'm surprised you're still alive with a brain like that.
Say that again, you bastard!
What the hell do you know about me?!
Hey, that's enough, Turtle!
Don't fight over some stupid little thing!
You don't understand the problems of living on the streets, Uncovered.
I've been living on my own for ten years now.
All alone.
This place is Heaven compared to the streets.
In fact, I wish they'd let me stay here forever.
You agree, Joe?
You're an orphan too, right?
You know how I feel, don't you?
Yeah.
But I'm not alone.
I have a little sister.
A sister?
Yeah, at the orphanage.
We're not full Japanese...
so we've gone through quite a lot.
But...
I think I got this far because of my sister Meg.
That's why... I want to get out of here.
And see my sister, I guess.
I see.
You have a visitor, Yokosuka.
Me?
Who'd come here to visit me?
Maybe it's Meg?
Just come with me.
He got a visitor.
Reunited siblings in tears.
It's not his sister.
Minors aren't allowed to visit here.
Get in.
Meg!
Hello.
It's been a while, Jou.
Have you been well?
Hey, Joe.
Who'd it turn out to be?
The director of the orphanage.
She said my sister will be getting a foster father.
Really?
That's great news!
Which rich bastard's adopting her?
Hey!
Shut it, Uncovered.
After his mother told them to wait there,
Joe and his sister knocked on the door of the orphanage.
He did not know it was the gate to Hell.
They knew nothing of parental love.
They had no one to rely on.
They were just two young siblings.
Whoa there!
Turtle.
Don't drift off into space while you work!
You're gonna hurt yourself!
Sorry.
Line up!
Okay, first twenty, get in the bath.
I'm here with the food supplies.
Thank you very much!
That was heavy.
Thank you.
You know, lately, I've...
Meg...
I'll let you see your sister.
Okay, next twenty, get in.
I'm hurt!
A snake bit me!
A snake!
There's a fucking snake!
Find it!
Now, Joe!
Turtle...
Go.
And don't you dare come back.
All right.
Bro, is he haring off?
I see the snake!
The snake's over here!
What?!
There it is!
Over there!
It's headed for the compounds!
It's poisonous!
It's a deadly snake!
No!
It's not over there!
It's over here!
It got me too!
Because escapees seemed to be "hopping" out,
breaking out was referred to as "haring."
If you were caught, you were finished.
They would beat you within an inch of your life.
Getting caught was not an option.
Joe kept running as hard as he could to find his sister.
We've got a hare, Ishihara!
Do you understand what that means?!
I'm terribly sorry, but-
Don't make excuses!
Listen, we only have forty-eight hours!
Bring him back within forty-eight hours!
If we don't, the police will get involved!
I don't know...
But he's a really nice man.
Why don't you just give him a chance?
But...
Damn it.
He's a fast runner.
Hey, over there!
Go look over there!
Sir!
Mommy didn't come for us today either.
If you're a good girl, she'll definitely come.
Yeah.
I'm going to be a good girl.
So sing me a song.
The usual song.
Okay.
I will.
When you can't sleep at night~
You begin to hear the rain making music~
You're good at singing, Jou.
Now, won't you sing me that song again tonight?
Come on, don't keep me waiting, Jou.
Damn it!
This is unreasonable!
Why did I have to take a beating for someone else?!
Uncovered, then...
why don't you tell me?
Why exactly did you help him?
Not just you.
All of us.
It wasn't for money.
There was nothing in it for us.
But we all diverted the guards' attention to help Joe escape,
and we were beaten and then placed in isolation for it.
W-Well...
Because we're friends.
Right?
That's why you helped him.
Isn't that right, Turtle?
I... had three other people in my family.
My alcoholic dad,
my mom who always just stood there,
and my little sister Tae.
When my dad got drunk and violent,
I'd always grab my sister and run out of the house.
But...
on that day in August...
I ran out of the house alone after my dad beat me.
That was the only time I ran off alone.
If only...
I had taken Tae with me like always.
A flash of light, the burning air,
the gigantic mushroom cloud that covered the summer sky...
Can you believe it?
There was nothing there.
No house, no city, no people.
In seconds, my sister had been turned into ash.
My parents were scum,
but I was sad when they were actually gone.
I... don't have anything left.
But Joe...
He has a sister.
His one and only sister.
So...
I don't know.
I couldn't just leave him alone.
Thank you.
That's all the paperwork I need.
Meg, he will be your father from now on.
N-Nice to meet you.
Starting today, you and I will be living together.
Good for you, Meg.
You'll definitely be happy with a father like him.
Meg!
Where are you, Meg?
Oh, Jou.
My, you're covered in dirt. Are you okay?
Shut up!
You're not taking Meg away from me!
Oh, no need to sound so mean.
I was waiting for you.
Don't try to fight back!
Thank you for your report.
Not at all.
This is all for Jou, after all.
You shouldn't do this, Jou.
Your adorable sister is finally going to find happiness.
Meg won't be happy if you do this.
Well then, we'll take our leave.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you, officers.
Wait right there, you hag!
Is Meg...
going to go through what you did to me?!
You use people for your own pleasure, and then you get rid of them for cash?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Hey, you perverted old hag!
How much more do I need to pleasure you before you'll let me see Meg?!
Director?
What are you talking about?
Hurry up and take him away!
Now, get up!
Hey, you hag!
How much more do I need to pleasure you before I can have my sister back?!
You...
ungrateful bastard!
I feed kids with nowhere to go, and this is how you repay me?
You fucking joke.
You're the one feeding off the kids.
You perverted old hag!
If you say any more, I won't let you off easy.
Do it.
Try it, you fucking bitch!
That's enough.
Meg!
I got a call from an orphanage.
They have Yokosuka Jou.
Apparently, he ran off to see his sister.
What an arrogant little maggot.
Why's scum like him trying to do something humane?
You all sit tight right there.
I'll give him back to you after I beat the crap out of him.
Damn it!
Meg...
Meg!
I came to get you.
Come on, let's get out of here together.
What did you come here for?
Hurry up and take him away.
Meg!
Don't you understand?
If that foster father takes you-
Director.
I'm deeply sorry for the bother.
Meg!
Don't go, Meg!
We need to be together!
Until Mom comes to pick us up!
I've had enough of your lies!
She's never coming for us.
She abandoned us.
Meg...
We have no relatives.
Our only choice is to be used by others.
I've long been prepared for anything.
M-Meg...
Don't... think about me anymore.
I can live on my own.
Come on, get moving!
Meg, what are you doing?
Let's go.
Thank you.
I'm so happy you came.
Goodbye, my dear brother.
Two siblings without a single relative...
became the puppets of adult greed.
Will they ever get another chance to see each other?
For us, the pouring rain signified the end of summer.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
Uncovered isolates himself from the group.
The serpent glares from the darkness.
The youngsters are enveloped in flames.
Then...
Hey everyone, this is Satake Uki.
Today, we're interviewing Mr. Oguri Shun, the voice actor for Murakami Mario.
Enjoy!
I believe that this series, RAINBOW,
is a story about people striving to survive...
during a rough period of Japanese history that we find difficult even to think about these days.
Personally, I find it an amazing work,
full of things that would touch anyone's heart.
I hope you enjoy watching it.