() Are notes/information for the timer/editor.
Hurry and get up!
You were up late again weren't you?
I can verify that the lights were on up until around 2:30,
you know!
Ryuji...
You... from your ears...
There's rice...
Rice is falling...
It's silver... and shiny...
Just cooked...
If it's breakfast, I already brought it.
I'll go warm it up for you. At least wash your face.
Breakfast...
Alright.
All that's left are the dishes and the laundry.
What a gloomy room.
A cardboard box?
What the heck is this?
An album?
This is...
What the hell are you looking at?!
Oh! Taiga this is!
Yeah, yeah, they're pictures of Kitamura-kun.
You got a problem with that?
Not that I'll accept it even if you do.
So these are Kitamura huh?
I-I-It can't be helped!
I don't know why but they end up kinda blurred--
Wh-When I try to take a picture of Kitamura-kun.
For some reason...
You want me to take some for you?
Some pictures.
I'll do it.
I'm not especially good at it, but it'll end up better than these--
Wait a second!
What's the limit?
Oh, what kind of pictures do I want?
A side-shot of his musing face during softball practice.
H-His face when he's eating lunch--
is hard to give up too.
Sheesh. I already told you that I'll take as much as you want.
You say "As much as you want", but there are limits you know!
Then, I want the 10,000 shots for free.
Good morning!
Hey, good morning.
You're pretty late today.
Yeah. I stopped by the student council room today.
Oh...
MORNIN'!
TL Note: Oha! Is a short way of saying Ohayou [Good morning] that was popular about 4 years ago.
That's old... It's way too old Taiga...
N-No, w-what I just did wasn't--
N-No, wh-what I just did wasn't--
Well... um--
Aisaka.
Mornin'!
Well, I'll be going ahead.
M-Mornin'?
Hey! Hey! Did you get it?
Get what?
The "Mornin'!" of course!
It happened all of a sudden.
How was I supposed to get that?
What a useless mutt...
Hey now...
Maruo, take a look at this.
Hey, this magazine model looks just like you Maruo!
Guys, the morning assembly's going to start soon.
Cut with the unnecessary chatter and move out to the front.
Aww, Maruo's so boring.
He doesn't have to be so serious just because he's the vice-chairman!
I wish I could get a reaction at least.
Yeah!
Kitamura's pretty popular with the girls.
What do you mean Maruo?!
How about I crush you into a ball with this hand?
TL Note: Maru means round or circular.
Stand at attention!
Hey you goons. It seems a lot of you have been forgetting your student planners lately.
We got the proof. According to the last week's report from the student council--
Eh, How much of them were there?
Fifty-nine.
Fifty-six people throughout the school were walking around without their student planners and--
Woah. My mistake there. It was fifty-nine people.
Well, who cares about the small stuff?
Anyway, to forget your student planner is the same as forgetting your pride as someone from Oohachi-High!
Got it you goons?!
Yeah!
You're one to talk.
You're forgetting something too.
A-Aisaka...
Hey, you small one over there.
You said somethin'?
You forgot to say "at ease".
SAY AT EASE!
Oh, I apologize for that.
Everyone at ease!
Sheesh! Why do we have to stand at attention when we're in high school anyway?
Having us standing in an idiotic position while listening to your worthless announcement--
Is it that big of a deal?
All you're doing is putting your hands on your hips.
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?!
Wait--Aisaka.
Fine by me.
You want to have a good sweat from early in the morning?
Chairman, you have to calm down too.
What do you know?!
Why do I have to put my hands to my hips like my back or stomach hurts?!
This--
Aisaka!
A-Aisaka. Please calm down a little bit.
I'm sorry about that chairman. Please continue the assembly.
R-Right.
What--What?
Palm-top tiger bit the chairman!
She's so…
Za pool dos... des?
TL Note: He is trying to read English
Dus... dees
She's depressed in a way that's easy to tell.
Is... wis...
Wait... is she actually happy?
Wes? Why... what... da.
Why, wisu man knowsu himself.
To--
Alright, alright.
That's enough Haruto-kun.
Next is...
Aisaka-san?
You seem to be in quite a good mood today.
Then I suppose I'll have you read it energetically.
S-Sike! Th-That was a feint attack. Actually--
Haruto-kun
!
Yuri-chan! Isn't that impossible?!
Go on; put your all into it.
Oh come on, listen to me!
Here. It's your lunch.
I don't need it. I'm not hungry anyway.
I got into a fight with the chairman and I ended up troubling Kitamura-kun too.
But he grabbed me from the behind.
It was a "Back-Tugging Carnival" for me.
Ta-Taiga?
But I do want to apologize!
Don't worry about that!
The chairman isn't someone who would worry over such a thing.
Oh, a boxed lunch?
Can I eat with you guys?
Hey now, that sounds good!
You'll have to let me join in too!
Isn't it nice to have this sort of thing once in a while?
Right?
Man, I'm hungry.
Thank you for the food~!
Thank you for the food.
Today's food~!
I wonder what today's food is~?
Why did it end up this way?
Woah! It's deep-fried chicken!
Ready-set, fried chicken!
Taiga?! You're getting way to nervous!
Woah! You've got a mountain of goodies don't you Taiga?
Crap! Now that I think about it... our lunches are--
I guess Aisaka's into boxed lunches lately huh?
Do you make them yourself?
Oh, Takasu does?
N-No. You got it wrong.
You know! Kushieda was doing it too!
She was working as a DecoDen.
I've been making boxed lunches to get some extra cash too.
Oh, is that so?
I wouldn't mind eating one of your boxed lunches once, Takasu.
Oh, me too!
That boxed lunch is really manly, being brownish everywhere.
It totally excites me.
Th-Then I'll make some for you guys next time.
Kitamura-senpai. Kusheida-senpai. It's about time for--
Ah oh. It's the manager for the softball team.
Oh, the meeting.
Sorry guys. Go ahead and eat without us.
R-Right.
That was bad.
I talked a bunch with Kitamura-kun...
Really bad.
With Kitamura-kun... Kitamura-kun...
Taiga?
Hey! You can't just reveal to Kitamura that I made that lunch for you!
Just when we finally settled the rumor about there being something between us.
What should we do?!
What should we do~?!
Hey, calm down!
Sheesh! Why do you get so weird when Kitamura is involved?
Be more careful from now on okay?
Huh?
What is it? If there's something you want to say, swallow your food first.
Hey, today's boxed lunch... there's no meat in it.
If you like households that always have meat in their meals, then go live with one of them.
As expected of mold from a public area--
Its roots are deep.
However!
Your fate has ended at the moment I found you.
Takasu-chan, lets call it quits.
Yeah, I'll handle the rest so you can go ahead and leave.
Oh? Lucky me. I'll leave the rest to ya.
Bring it on you black demon!
What's wrong? Giving up already?!
Alright. I'll use one of the forty-eight Takasu Style Chore Techniques on you.
The Takasu Mold-Killing Buster!
Ryuuji.
What are you mumbling about?
Hurry and get over here, you retarded dog!
Wha--Taiga?
You know this is the men's bathroo--
Who cares, just get over here!
What's the deal Taiga?
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh, that's it?
Kitamura huh?
Come on!
Hurry! Hurry and take it!
This girl...
Come on! Now! Now! Hurry!
I got it already.
The button for the shutter was...
Now! Right now!
Just hold on a second. I'm adjusting the settings right now.
Oh jeez! Fine! Give me that!
So this is how she mass produced those blurry photos.
You're so amazing! Kitamura-kun, right there.
Woah! Go!
Hey~!
Hey, he's waving like crazy.
Oh shut up...
You klutz.
Welcome to Sudoh-Bucks!
Manager, an American Napolitan please.
One Napolitan.
It's a miracle that these guys don't get sued.
Anyway... I don't think it was necessary to go through the trouble of developing those.
Hey you-you're drooling all over the place.
There are lots of Kitamura-kuns. It's a Kitamura Carnival.
What are you doing?!
There's limits to being a youth that's easily ticked off!
I'm here to help you... you mutt.
Huh?
I did have you take those pictures.
No, no thanks. I want to put the sheets out tomorrow anyway.
If you don't stop being a cliché, I'll butcher you.
Butcher? What are you--
Plus, you have to take some boxed lunches next time right?
For Minorin and Ki-Kitamura-kun...
Well then, can you peel a potato?
D-Don't insult me! I can do that--
All I have to do is peel this right?
Sheesh!
Hand-made cooking for Kitamura huh?
That's right.
Since Kushieda is going to be eating this--
I should put some spirit into--
Wha--?
What the hell are you do--
What?!
What? I got the skin off didn't I?
And, with this method, it's impossible to cut yourself.
Uh... Well... I suppose...
Wow! Rice balls for dinner? Kinda gives a picnic feeling.
Plus, this rice ball is so tiny and cute!
That?! I made that!
Oh my god?! Taiga-chan, are you a genius?!
Well, I suppose she could practice all she wants with this.
It doesn't require any peeling either.
I told you; swallow your food before you talk.
It's delicious! I can taste Taiga-chan's hands!
Here, I made you some tea.
They'll get damaged if you don't properly put them into an album.
Oh shut up. You sister-in-law.
What's your problem?
Just when I was thinking about securely laminating your favorite ones.
You can do that?
Hmph. I sure can.
Then, hold on a bit!
Um...
Once that's done, no matter how many times you fall over or drop it in water--
it'll be fine.
Taiga.
Is something wrong?
N-Not really.
If that's the case, it doesn't have to be just one.
Two or three or...
Shut up already! Just hold on a second!
Can't you see that I'm choosing right now?!
Wh-What's with you all of the sudden?
I just--
I'm going home.
What's with you?
I can't relax and choose here so I'm doing it at home.
Hey! Taiga! Wait a second!
What's with her?
I want pictures too…
Of Kushieda…
Look! Take a look at this!
T-This is...
Is it a dead light-yellow squid? Or slime?
Isn't it amazing? I made pudding, using a bucket!
T-This is?
How do I put this... it's mentally troubling--
A pudding with a bucket!
It's the manifestation of a woman's desire!
But it was so huge that it didn't go so well.
The gushy part and the pudgy were combined as one.
It was quite a--
Hey! You ladies over there!
Look at my wondrous bucket-pastime!
This is... a picture of... Kushieda.
And then, the gushy part and the pudgy are was all combined as one.
How should I put it? It was mysterious, yet beautiful--
It was different than what I was thinking of but I suppose it's alright.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Oh, it's just you Ryuuji.
You're still choosing?
Oh shut up... sheesh!
What's with you anyway?
You left so suddenly yesterday too.
I told you, if you're having trouble choosing, I can do as many as you want.
What'd you do that for?!
If you're going to say it so much, then why don't you choose it yourself?
I'll leave it to you then.
How can I choose something like this?
That Taiga...
Do those belong to Aisaka?
Yeah, they do.
Those are pictures of me aren't they?
Uh no... This is um--
How do I put it?
Oh yeah, I totally forgot about it but I had one that I left in too.
Wha--?!
It's so nostalgic.
You--Why do you have this picture?
Oh, the photo club used to do business way back.
So I got one of the--
That's not what I meant!
Why do you have a picture of Taiga?
I put it in because I liked Aisaka.
That's all.
Huh?
Although, I got reject swiftly, one second after I told her.
Oh no. Now I've gone and said it.
Please don't tell everyone okay?
Wha--Wha--
What's wrong Takasu?
Hey Takasu?
Wha--Wha--
What the hell?!
How could you do such a wasteful thing?
It couldn't be helped...
He told me he liked me and it just surprised me.
I rejected him then but...
I became conscious about him after that and...
After that I kind of... kind of started to like him
It was just around here.
Aisaka!
Your straight personality that doesn't hide your anger is just fine!
I've fallen for you!
Kitamura…
Wasn't that a strange way to say he like me?
I couldn't tell if he was complimenting me or talking bad about me.
But... it made me happy.
Someone who thought I was just fine.
Someone that needs me as I am.
To know that such a person exists.
I wonder why. It suddenly popped into my head.
That room that Taiga lives in.
There were so many pictures... but not a single one had it.
I want that expression.
The expression he made when he said that to me.
Just once more.
W-W-Why are you making me say such embarrassing things, you perverted dog!
W-Wh-Why are you making me say such embarrassing things, you perverted dog!
How is that my fault?!
And who else is there up here?!
To be needed by someone.
I wonder what that means to Taiga?
In any case... she really is one hell of a klutz.
If she thought she might start liking him, she should have waited on her response.
Right, Inko-chan?
Kitamura's, Kitamura too. If he liked her then he should of taken responsibility and went out with her.
Oh, you think so too, Inko-chan?
Yeah, go tell 'em Inko-chan!
I-I-Isn't it fine?
Kawashima Ami, the beautiful air-headed type of girl, suddenly makes her entrance.
The first thing I can say is that women are scary!
Hm? What's that mean?
I don't know what you're saying.