Takasu-kun, what would you do if I showed you the real me?
Huh?
Would you fall in love with me?
Would you?
W-Wait just a moment...
I...
Taiga? Were they there?
Taiga?
Huh? Are we in a bad situation?
Maybe Ami-chan's timing was really bad?
T-This is not what you think!
Ta
i
ga!
Minorin!
Looks like nobody's here!
Just where did they go?
My, why are you lying to her?
Could it be that you don't want to accept it?
That he let a girl other than you into his house.
Idi- Don't say it like that!
Aw, but...
No buts!
Come on, just tell her the truth!
Huh? The truth? No way! Takasu-kun, you're so...
H-Hey! Taiga!
Taiga!
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
Pool Opening Day
Good morning!
Huh? Taiga-chan, did anything happen?
No, I don't have anything any more.
I wonder what tonight's dinner is going to be?
We're having a rice bowl dish. You like those, right?
Is that so?
Shouldn't you have made red rice instead?
What?
Right, ugly bird?
Ugly?
Hey, Taiga. About what happened this evening...
Ugly... ugly... ugly...
Kawashima was just teasing me, and um...
It looks like it left a bad impression.
I'm sorry.
Exactly what might you be apologising for?
Ryuuji's a pretty weird guy, isn't he?
I-Inko-chan!
Hang in there, Inko-chan!
Get a hold of yourself!
Taiga! Wake up!
Oh man, it's so late...
That hurt.
Huh?
S-Sorry.
What?
I mean, we've overslept!
Hurry up and get ready as quickly as you can!
What's for breakfast?
Why did you wake me up like this today?
There's no breakfast or lunch box!
If we don't leave in five minutes, we'll be late!
Ah geez, if we don't go by a convenience store, we won't have any lunch!
Hey! Are you listening?
Taig-?!
I'm listening, perverted dog! The convenience store, right?!
What's up with you?!
Just because you haven't had any breakf-
Ow!
Made it!
Ah, he's finally here!
Thanks for everything you did for me yesterday.
No, um... Yeah.
What's that? Were you dazzled by my summer uniform?
Just kidding!
You're blocking traffic, Stupid Chihuahua.
O-Oh, you were here, Aisaka-san? Good morning.
Good morning, Kawashima-san.
I see that you're still in heat.
Hey, you two...
Oh, I see. My, how awful.
Don't get so jealous over such a trivial matter.
It was all Aisaka-san's misunderstanding, after all.
You're one dumb woman, aren't you?
What happened yesterday was just-
Forgotten!
Good morning, everyone!
Oh! I could tone my upper arms by doing this!
Minorin, don't use me for muscle training!
Information about the pool opening day
Okay! Tomorrow is our long-awaited pool opening day!
I'll explain the important points now.
Summer is the season for love. The final chance of my twenties!
Oh no, my stomach...
And my thighs...
My upper arms are even worse!
What the hell are you lot saying?
Just being young is enough, for crying out loud!
Really? Swimming classes at this school are co-ed?
Oh no, that's so embarrassing.
Why worry?!
You're super cute, and you're a model too!
What's so embarrassing, huh?!
Information about the pool opening day
Swimsuits can only be black or navy blue
Bikinis are not...
What is, huh?! What is so embarrassing, huh?!
Sensei, that's about it for homeroom.
All right, finish it!
Rise!
Taiga, come on!
No way! I don't need to buy a swimsuit!
Since last year's has already rotted, it can't be helped, right?!
You've got to wash and dry swimsuits right away, after all.
I said I don't want to!
And why is that here?
Because this is the only shop that sells swimsuits.
I-It's not like I invited her!
Hey, hey!
Wouldn't this look great on Aisaka-san?
Actually, it would fit her way too well!
Calm down, Taiga! We're in public!
Takasu-kun, what do you think about this one?
U-Um... I-It'd look great on you-
Hey.
How's this?
It's not weird, right? It's not too conspicuous, right?
What's up with the length of those legs?!
You're being really conspicuous!
Oh, really? I even went and picked a plain swimsuit too...
K-Kawashima-san! Which brand is that swimsuit?
Where did you find it?
Over there. You want to get matching ones?
Anything but that! Spare me from that!
Kushieda?
Hey, hey!
Ami-chan's super-duper-super cute in this! So cute that it's scary!
And in this plain swimsuit! How far can I go with it?
With this cuteness, this beauty, this body!
Hiding it is like some kind of crime!
You think so too, right, Takasu-kun?
Huh?
Hey! You okay in there, Tai-?
What are you do-?!
I don't know what to do any more.
Why? What's wrong?
No matter what I do, I can't decide.
What about them is bothering you?
You can't pick one in a colour other than navy blue or black.
That's not it!
I can't find one that fits!
Um, how about childrens?
Over my dead body!
Don't say what the Stupid Chihuahua said.
I-Isn't this one rather small?
It's not too expensive, and it's thick and sturdy.
You can even put it in a dryer.
Did you try it on?
I tried...
...putting that one on...
It was more or less okay...
But it was, um...
Then, this one will do, right?
Yeah, you're right.
Taiga, what do you want for dinner?
I'll make whatever you want.
Oh, yeah! Did you prepare for the pool tomorrow?
Don't forget a towel. A bath towel.
Shut up.
Why you...!
What are you so grumpy over?
The swimsuit?
Or are you still angry about last night?
No, that's not it!
Then, what is it?!
I can't swim! That's what's bothering me!
When you say it like that, there's no way that's the real reason!
Oh no, I'm going to be late!
Hey, wait up!
Drink this before you go.
Thank you, Ryuu-chan!
Ow, hot.
What's that?
Ryuu-chan's special soy milk!
He says that the soy beans and the isonobonbons or something that it has will make my breasts bigger!
Isoflavone.
I can't have them shrivelling up, so this is a precaution.
Ya-chan's so smart!
Taiga-chan's perverted, sketchy, one-touchy!
Don't sexually harass people's mothers!
I'm going out, then.
Sheesh, she's so noisy.
What's up with you?
You're acting weird.
Soy bean...
Hey!
That was horrible, give me more!
What the hell are you doing?
I want to stock up on isonobonbons too!
What? Why would you wan-?
The size of her swimsuit...
Isoflavone...
Taiga, could it be that you-?
No, don't say it! Don't say anything else!
You're...
...flat-chested?
Sheesh... why would you fret over that?
Just because your breasts are small...
Here I am.
Y-Yeah.
How is it?
It's flat, right? Really flat-chested?
No, w-well...
What about the cups?
They're in, but...
...t-they're collapsing.
This is why I don't like going to the pool.
E-Either way, go put something on.
You'll catch a cold otherwise.
What's this?
By looking at that, even you will be able to understand my grief.
Pitiful
Breasts
This is...
Pitiful
Breasts
...rather mean.
Pitiful
Breasts
"Pitiful breasts"? "Pitiful"?
I'm being pitied for the flatness of my breasts!
Pitiful
Breasts
No, well, that's only the opinion of the person who wrote this.
Pitiful
Breasts
Naturally, I made it rain blood over the photography club that I got it from.
Now that you mention it, the photography club did suddenly cease operations...
And now I've got to expose this pathetic form to Kitamura-kun... I don't want to...
I don't want to...
Hey, Taiga?
Okay. I'll do something about it.
Huh?
I'll make sure you'll be able to stand before Kitamura...
...with your chest out proud.
It's all right, you can go home and sleep.
No, I'll stay here and wait for you to finish.
I'll stay up until you're finished.
Hey.
Yeah?
Like, well...
I was being stubborn and moody, so...
...I'm sorry.
How is it?
When I become a bride, I will wear these with pride!
Maruo!
Maruo, you look better without glasses!
Switch to contact lenses!
Really?
For sure! Right?
I'm not wearing glasses either, you know...
Yes.
Girl's dressing room
Bye, then, Aisaka-san.
I'm going on ahead.
Taiga.
Hurry up! I'll do your hair for you.
O-Okay...
Maya-chan, I'm sorry!
I was having trouble getting my hair right!
Sorry for making you wait!
Ami-chan!
Wow, that's a model for you!
Your body sure is nice.
No, not at all.
I'm so moved!
No, really, you're completely different from us.
It's a goddess!
Again...
You're damn right I am!
Ami-chan's cute today too!
Behold, foolish mortals! I will allow you to
grovel in my angelic presence and worship me!
Come now, lick my shadow!
It's like the highest quality gourmet food to you, right?
Don't tease me like that, Maya-chan.
Aha! Takasu-kun!
Minorin, don't run! My hair will fall apart again!
Okay, it's time for warm-up exercises!
She's doing some running,
but it's a feint!
Minorin?
Kushieda?
I've figured it out!
Huh?
I figured that as long as I'm in the water,
I won't need to show my stomach to anyone.
And so, I'm going to do some swimming. Ciao!
Minorin...
My, Aisaka-san, you're finally here.
I was afraid your swimsuit might be so baggy that you'd be too ashamed to come out.
Huh? What are you saying, are you talking in your sleep?
Are you asleep?
Sheesh!
Man, I don't want to get sunburned.
It's perfect.
I'm so impressed she's come this far in one year!
I'm a fan of Taiga after all!
Oh, so you've got a normal figure.
The scale's completely off as always, though.
Success!
Yeah!
Fake breast special force.
She knows.
That's Minorin for you.
Aisaka?
Huh? You're Aisaka, right?
I can't see too well since I'm not wearing glasses,
but with that figure, you must be Aisaka!
Why are you hiding yourself?
Especially since you look great with that mouse hairstyle.
G-Go away!
Huh?
What?!
Did I say something wrong?
W-Who knows?
Hey, show us your biceps!
Like this?
Wow, amazing!
Being all...
...popular on his own!
We object to this unjust society!
"This is summer" drop!
Maruo!
Hey, are you all right?!
Hey.
Let's do it too!
Usually you're allowed to do whatever you want in this class, but...
...isn't this a little too dangerous?
Right, Tai-?
Kitamura-kun said my hair was cute...
No, he said it looked great...
Target spotted!
Let's go, softball club comrade!
Yeah!
All right! Next!
Acknowledged, Big Boss!
Yay, you got tossed in.
That looks like fun, right, Aisaka-san?
Y-You!
Let's play and have some fun!
Don't take this personally, now!
Whoa.
Hey, hold back a little!
Why should I? We're just playing!
Hey, Taiga! You okay?
Taiga?
She...!
I can't swim!
Don't tell me...
She really can't swim?!
You're kidding me!
Wai- Stop it!
Come now, come now!
Taiga!
Sensei!
N-No!
Calm down, Taiga!
What should I do?! The cup came off!
There's only one side left!
Wha-?!
Hey, isn't that bad?
Aisaka!
Taiga!
I'm coming now!
No, don't come!
Taiga!
Dammit!
Now that it's come down to this...!
Taiga!
The humiliation...
Look, I'm saying that I'm sorry!
I didn't know that you couldn't swim.
Everyone's gone home already, so just get over it.
This won't be settled with a mere apology.
Because you pulled that crap,
my b-breast-!
Either way!
Apologise! Apologise! Apologise!
At any rate, if Aisaka-san can't swim,
she can't go to the pool or the sea with us.
Hey, Takasu-kun, my vacation home is by the sea.
If you'd like, how about we spend the summer vacation together?
What?
Wait a second. Weren't you just apologising to Taiga?
Then, well, how about I bring Yuusaku along too? You'd come then, right?
Oh? Is something wrong, Aisaka-san?
If you keep this crap up,
I'll spread around the footage I took of you doing 100 different imitations in rapid succession.
Wait, it was 150, wasn't it?
If you do that, I might just sue you for infringing on portrait rights.
Not even a Palmtop Tiger can win against the hand of the law, right?
Hey, you two.
Stop this right now!
Your fists...
...will get hurt.
But listen, Minori-chan, Aisaka-san's been treating me-
It's this moronic chihuahua's fault!
Wha- What the hell are you saying?!
The one who started-
Shut up right this instant!
If you want to develop your friendship by fighting,
don't do it with your fists, but instead...
...fight it out with sports!
S...
Sports?
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
For whose sake?
Takasu competition!
Ami-tan vs. Taiga?!
Why is Takasu getting
all the good stuff?!
Waa, snatch me away
and mess me up too!