We're now on the last day of the Golden Week holidays!
How has everyone been?
I'm so bored that I could die...
Sheesh! All because the mongrel is so useless...
It's not my fault that you didn't get to meet Kitamura, right?
I said he'd be busy with the student council and club practice during the holidays, didn't I?
Doing something about that is a dog's job, right?
Even though if you met him, you couldn't properly hold a conversation with him in the first place.
I'll send you to hell!
It spilled on me!
What are you doing?!
Quickly! Something to wipe it with!
Sheesh...
It's because you're talking crap, isn't it?!
So noisy...
We woke her up...
Here. Wipe it off with this for now.
You two were planning to eat omelet-rice by yourselves while Yacchan was sleeping!
It's already wrapped up and in the fridge!
You properly wrote my name on it?
"Yasuko" with ketchup...
I'll write it! I'll write it! So don't cry anymore!
Sniff... I got it. I'll sleep some more.
What should I do? It's going to become a stain.
It'll come off if we treat it properly.
I'll make it come off properly, so in return...
Jonny's again?
It's fine, right? Please!
I can't go by myself!
You can at least help matters between me and Kushieda!
Ah, jeez! Shut up! I'll skin you!
What the...?!
Kawashima Ami
Kushieda... a day off...
Even a laboring girl will take some days off too.
It's punishment for going for just your own happiness, isn't it?
I'm different from you who's confessed and been confessed to. I've yet to—
My eyes...! My eyes...!
Don't say embarrassing things, horny mutt.
What are you doing?!
This is cute!
Which? Which?
For you to wear that is a bit—
What I want is the bag! The bag!
Y-Yeah...
Welcome!
After all, I'm tiny and have short legs.
But with that, I haven't had any trou—
What's—
Ryuuji, this!
...A bag, right?
Not that! The model!
The model?
Look! That person.
It's this person, right?
It's true!
She's Kawashima Ami.
She's the actress Kawashima Anna's daughter.
What's a girl like that doing here?
Sorry, Ami. I made you wait.
Ki-Ki-Kita-Kitamu—
Oh! Takasu and Aisaka, isn't it?
What a coincidence!
Why?!
H-Hey! They're coming over here!
Even if you say that...!
What are you getting entangled over?
As usual, you sure get along.
It's... it's not like that!
...It's not like that!
What's going on, Yuusaku?
Yeah, I was thinking of introducing you here.
"Yuusaku"?
She's Kawashima Ami. She used to live in my neighborhood.
I guess you can call us childhood friends.
And these two are Takasu Ryuuji and Aisaka Taiga.
Childhood... friends.
He-Hello.
Nice to meet you!
Is that...?
Eh?
Ah... y-yeah. We were just now looking at this... and—
Oh, no... You've seen an embarrassing side of me.
I should have put on some better clothes and make-up.
When not working, I just let my guard down...
No! Umm... that's not it at all!
Since we're all here, why don't the four of us chat?
That's fine, right, Ami?
Of course!
This place brings back memories!
We sure came here often in the past, huh.
Right! Right! With our families!
Here, Takasu-kun, have some too.
Would diet-sugar have been better?
Eh? No...
Rather... are you someone who drinks it black?
Hey, hey, you sure are careless.
I'm so sorry!
Since Yuusaku put some in, I just...
N... No, it's...
I did it again...
They always tell me... "Really, Ami, you sure are a klutzy airhead."
I'm sorry.
No. Not at all. I like sweet things.
Thanks! You're so kind.
Oh, no! What am I doing?
Ah... sorry.
Oh, no. Why are you apologizing?
I—
Well then... I'm off to the restroom for a bit.
...Wai—
Me too... restroom...
Jeez, I can't fill the time.
As expected, you left your seat, huh?
You! What about the rest—
Wh-What is it?
I want you to answer honestly.
Takasu, what did you think of Ami?
Forget what I thought! Since you suddenly brought such a cute girl, I got all nervous.
I'll admit that she's cute.
And she's a real nice girl too!
She's a bit of an airhead, but you could say she's innocent or...
Well, just have a look.
This is boring.
Hey, hey, Ami-chan's iced tea is all gone.
Go get some more.
Ignoring me, are you?
Speaking of which, hasn't your attitude been bad?
Ah, that's it! I'll have your boyfriend bring it.
Heh, if Ami-chan says it, seems he'll listen to anything.
Is it okay if Ami-chan steals him?
Though I don't really need him at all!
He's not my boyfriend.
I see. It's fine either way.
Precisely. That's Ami's true colors.
Spoiled, selfish, and tyrannical. Your typical princess.
I can't help but think she's been possessed by a demon.
Well, in a deserted town like this, there aren't any guys better than that.
Hey, hey, how many centimeters tall are you?
I just now noticed, but aren't your proportions strange?
Actually, I'm shocked that they even sell clothes that size!
But you know, when you buy things like denims, don't you have to cut the cuffs?
Even so, that Taiga can put up with tha—
Ami-chan's never had to, so—
Wha—
There was a mosquito on your face.
Ah. It was a fly.
Why, you—
Hey, hey, Ami, we're leaving already!
Yuusaku!
I get it. I get it.
I'm sorry, Aisaka. We'll leave here for today.
Seconds!
There's none left.
You've already gulped down two and a half bowls.
It's all her fault. That fickle woman... just remembering her makes me hungry.
You mean you get angry, right?
But he was troubled — Kitamura-kun.
Wh-What should I do? Doing that might have made Kitamura hate me...
Well, I don't think so.
Kitamura is aware of the whole story—
I hate... that woman!
Don't cry...
What about you?! Being so mushy around her!
I wasn't really—
You know, there really aren't any upright honest people who refer to themselves as airheads!
Huh?
Well, whatever. I won't ever meet her again.
I'll just be mature here and gulp down my hatred!
Hey! That's mine!
Thuddup!
Kawashima Ami
I'm transferring to this school starting today. I'm Kawashima Ami.
Please call me "Ami."
Kawashima Ami
Eh? Could she be...?
The girl who's modeling for Can Vi?
Too cute!
An angel has descended upon us!
I thank thee, God!
Kawashima Ami
Everyone! Let's all get along with our new friend, shall we?
Then first, let's decide on a seat.
Put her next to me!
No, next to me!
A big win!
I'm so glad that I'm in this class!
Standing out like this is kind of embarrassing.
Why? It looks good on you, so it's fine!
Yeah. You've got a really nice body.
I really want the same jersey as everyone else as soon as possible.
Ami-chan is certainly cute and has an exceptionally nice body, but...
my cute-girl-detecting Minorin Radar isn't reacting at all this time...
Minorin...?
Are you okay, Ami-chan?
Ah, jeez... why do I fall over in the middle of nowhere? So uncool...!
Ami-chan's pretty clumsy.
You're a bit air-headed, huh?
That's not it at all!
But... they sometimes tell me that... "Ami, you sure are an airhead."
As expected!
But that's really not it!
Yes, yes, we got it.
Jeez, even though it's true!
That's amazing.
Yeah. She's got a complete grasp of how to win people's hearts.
Why didn't you tell me? That she was transferring.
If I had, Ami wouldn't have shown her true colors, would she?
That wouldn't have worked.
What is that?
To be honest, I don't dislike Ami's true colors.
That's why I want everyone to know the true her, and like that Ami.
No. That's—
Even if they hate her, I'm sure she can cope.
I just don't want her to keep lying.
First!
So there was a vending machine here.
Why...?
Because you left the classroom just as the fourth period was about to start.
It piqued my interest, so I followed you.
Not good. Not good. Her true colors are...
Buying drinks outside lunch breaks is against school regulations, you know.
Then...
we're partners in crime, aren't we?
I'll pay for it.
It's fine!
That's an apology for yesterday.
An apology?
It really shocked me. That you were in the same school...
Aisaka-san too... Yuusaku didn't say anything.
Say, about yesterday... did you hear anything from Aisaka-san?
Yesterday...?
Yesterday, you see, was all my fault.
I'm somewhat of an airhead, so I think I ticked off Aisaka-san.
Even though I was just casually chatting... suddenly, she started calling me cheeky, saying that I was getting carried away...
and then... but Aisaka-san isn't bad!
If I were a more level-headed girl, things wouldn't have become like that...
It happens sometimes. After all, I get hated by other girls like this... so I'm not worried...
since I can keep going.
I get it.
So I don't want you to tell anyone about what happened yesterday.
I—
I understand what you're saying... so let's go back for now.
Thanks!
Let's hurry!
The sun was high when they, with no fanfare in their preparations, departed.
The Tale of Genji
The Carriage Competition
"The sun was high when they, with no fanfare in their preparations, departed."
The parts about the sun being high here explain how the sun is rising up by saying that it is climbing upwards.
It is simply pointing out that the sun is flourishing.
Why did you return to
the classroom barely in time
together with
Kawashima Ami?!
Taiga
"Why"...
Sheesh.
To Takasu-kun
From Minori
Takasu-kun. Minori is angry!
You're being somewhat suspicious together
with Transfer-Student-chan!
Is it cheating? Are you cheating?!
If you dump Taiga...
at that time...!
There will be punishment!
Minori
Takasu-kun. Minori is angry! You're being somewhat suspicious together with Transfer-Student-chan!
Is it cheating? Are you cheating?!
If you dump Taiga... at that time...!
There will be punishment!
Dammit! Why do I have to go through this?
From Takasu to Kushieda.
Sorry about the completely different subject,
but what do you think of people that
From Takasu to Kushieda.
Sorry about the completely different subject,
but what do you think of people that
refer to themselves as airheads?
From Takasu to Kushieda.
Sorry about the completely different subject,
but what do you think of people that
refer to themselves as airheads?
From Takasu to Kushieda.
Sorry about the completely different subject,
but what do you think of people that
refer to themselves as airheads?
From Takasu to Kushieda,
Sorry about the completely different subject, but
what do you think of people that refer to themselves as airheads?
Okay. Is there anything up to this point that you don't understand?
What's the matter, you guys?
Hey, Takasu.
Haruta says he'll introduce us to freshmen girls in the track club as a three-man set.
You'll go for sure, right?
Even If I went, I'd only scare them, right?
No way!
After all, we're just getting enough pe—
And besides...
The Palmtop Tiger...
That's how it is.
Just how did it become like this?
It wasn't on purpose!
I fell over, so I couldn't help it!
I'll go get some rags. Go on ahead.
It's fine. I'll wait in the classroom.
Ryuu—
Oh, no! Why are you here?
You're a real eyesore.
Don't come near me, damn kid.
Scary!
As expected of the Aisaka-san that even the teachers find annoying.
When I went to the teachers' office earlier, the teachers were all fawning over Ami-chan.
They were worried about whether Ami-chan was being bullied by Aisaka-san or not!
You're really hated around here.
I'm going to have a good time, seeing how long you can keep up that split-personality facade.
Revealing your true colors would be simple.
But that would be boring, right?
I'll keep watching you.
Even if we change classes. Even after we graduate.
Just like a stalker!
You're such an annoying runt!
It's because of that you don't have any friends, isn't it?
Just one: Takasu Ryuuji.
He looks like a delinquent, though he's entranced by me.
Gross!
But won't you really be all alone?
I really do pity you. To even be hated by humanitarians like Yuusaku...
What was that...?
Because I already told him all about what happened at the family restaurant.
I think he probably really hates you now.
It's really the end!
Kawashima?
Hey, move aside.
It's Ryuu-chan's pork cutlet!
Sheesh.
Even though I told her it's best when eaten right after it's cooked.
If you're worried...
go pick her up.
Aww, it fogged up...
Taiga, I'm coming in!
What? You're here after all, aren't you?
The lights aren't even on.
Hey, Tai—
What did you come for?
"What", you say?
It's about the food!
T... Taiga!
You all right?
She said Kitamura-kun...
hates me...
That woman said she told everything...
I... I...
It's all right.
What is?
Because Kitamura knows everything:
How she really is, what happened at the family restaurant, her lies... everything.
Really?
Really.
Also, Kitamura's not the kind of guy who starts hating people for something like that.
That's something you understand the most, right?
Then why am I tiny?
Huh?
Why do I have a weird name?
No. That's—
What?!
Just because she's 165 centimeters tall!
Just because her name looks just like Sailor Mercury's!
As a bonus, just because she's childhood friends with Kitamura—
Sorry. You all right?
Still, worrying about such useless thi—
Unlike you, I'm delicate!
You...!
Ryuu-chan...!
We're having pork cutlet, but there's no sauce. This is...
Pork cutlet...
Sauce! Ryuu-chan!
From a black pig.
Hey, what about pudding? Pudding!
Only sauce!
This is...?
Hey, let's get back. Yasuko will be late.
Ryuuji, look at this.
Notice
Kawashima Ami-chan will temporarily
be taking a break for her studies.
This is...?
That means she's on holiday, right?
Is there any worth in our school for taking a break from work?
Isn't that...?
That woman...!
That's really Kawashima Ami, huh.
What's up with that outfit?
And those bags are only filled with sweets.
Is she doing a home-party?
No, that's not it. That's...
I saw something interesting.
Next Episode Preview
True Colors
Ah, it's really annoying!
If you keep following me around like that...
Ami-chan will give you a swift death!
Named: Stupid Chihuahua!