"There are no good or bad customers.
The problem is always the good or bad of the store."
Note: There is no real quote from a Martin B. Stone; it's a fictional name
made up from the author's real name. (B. Stone = Black Stone = Kuro Ishi)
Martin B. Stone.
Welcome home, sir.
Street No. 01
"The Café of Ultimate Bliss, Before and After"
And Yet the Town Moves
A rainbow colored sunset falls
And the wind is a bit cool
Saturday night is bustling
Even the gloomy feeling
Brightens up right away
Everyone is in high spirits
In high spirits
Let's go downtown
MAID
Cafe
SEASIDE
The store of ultimate bliss.
That is where, even if it is shabby,
the customer can obtain what they desire.
No matter how beautiful it is, if what is desired
is not there, then it is the same as an empty shed.
Dear customer, what have you been doing up until now?
Homework...
For real?!
I only need math. Let me copy yours!
Math was the only subject with homework.
Whatever.
Here. Make some room!
H-hey!
Sit on the opposite side.
What? But if I looked at it upside-down, I'll copy it wrong.
You won't be wrong.
I will be wrong!
What am I going to do if the number "9" turns into a "6"?
Or the katakana character "yo" turns into the "E"?
Oh!
Maybe the reason why Europe starts with an "E"
is because someone copied wrong?!
Note: Europe in Japanese phonetics is ヨーロッパ (Yoroppa). This refers back
to the earlier bit about the katakana ヨ looking like an E flipped over.
If this deduction is true, then it could be
the biggest discovery of the century!
There is no katakana in foreign countries.
Okay, then. Copy already.
Thank you!
A store in which Arashiyama and I can be by ourselves...
...this is ultimate bliss!
Huh?
Ah, nothing.
People always seek the ultimate bliss,
but the ultimate bliss does not seek people.
That is because it is very rare when it comes on its own.
If you shake your head twice, it's a slider, poko.
Note: "Poko" is a nonsensical word, which stems from the
tanuki (raccoon-dog) character pictured here.
Oya High School
Arashiyama.
You've been copying other people's
homework, haven't you?
Uh, why?
Most of your answers are correct.
That's a false accusation!
When I do something, I do it!
However, you have copied the letter "I" as the number "1."
Even chalking this up to a transcription error,
were there no questions in your mind
when you wrote “I = 0” as “1 = 0”?
Oh... um...
Why?
After school, come to the Faculty Room!
Aw, man!
On a rare occasion you think
I'd do my homework, and this happens.
Isn't that what the teacher's supposed to say?
If he lectures me, then I'm going
to be late for my part-time job!
Oh. You have a part-time job?
Yeah, at the neighborhood cafe. I wear a maid outfit.
Is that what you call a maid cafe?!
Yeah, that's it, that's it.
I just started, though.
Well, that's hip. This area has become a place
for something like that to come about, huh?
English
Maid Cafe Uniforms
How nice... I've always admired maid cafes.
To chat and have tea with a cute maid.
Um, Arashiyama, may I come to the store to see?
Come, come! Customers rarely come,
so it's like the place is rented out!
Okay!
It's run by the neighborhood grandma,
so it might not be what you're imagining, though...
There are two ways that imagination can be cruel.
Imagination based on doubt
will cause fear in a person,
and imagination based on expectation
will cause pain from the disappointment.
Maid Cafe Seaside...
Cafe
SEASIDE
It seems there is no mistake that it's here.
Seaside
It's a bit different, or should I say...
It's a lot different from what I imagined.
YAKISOBA
Oh! Welcome!
Welcome!
Hotori, are these your friends?
They are!
Here, both of you sit, sit.
It's empty, so you can use any table you like.
Murakami Meats
What would you like for your menu?
I know, I bought some menchi cutlet,
so won't you eat that?
Murakami Meats
Tatsuno?
Th...
"Th"?
Th-this...
...isn't a maid cafe!
What's this "Welcome!" stuff?! You're not a sushi joint!
Did I say such a thing?!
Yes you did!
A maid cafe has a greeting typical
of a maid cafe, don't you see?!
Hmm?
Hey, welcome to the Maid Cafe!
Wrong! Wrong! Wrong!
Ready? You do it like this.
Not from the throat, but not from the belly...
As if you're projecting your voice from here...
Welcome home, Master!
Whoa!
This is what a maid is! I saw something like this on TV!
This is basic! You try it.
What? Me?
Don't "what" me!
Things like this would go "Bang!"
Straight into a man's heart.
You can't get away with only a maid outfit!
Can't I be a maid in outfit only?
You're good.
Won't you work here in place of Hotori?
I appreciate your offer, but I've
decided to join an after-school club,
so I won't have time for a job.
You're joining the Table Tennis club with me, right?
If I may be so bold, instead I would like
to train Arashiyama today.
Uh, no thank you.
I can't stand the thought of a store as crude
as this claiming to be a maid cafe.
Hotori. Here, for Granny's sake, ask her for advice.
But stuff like this isn't my cup of tea...
Then why are you doing the maid thing?!
Arai Cleaning
Hm. What great timing for a sucker to come along!
It's the Dry Cleaner...
In any case, training!
Shortest route to a Maid.
Course number one: Maid Greeting.
Here, do as I showed you just now!
Eh, for real?
There's no better training than the real thing!
Here!
Arai Cleaning
Now!
Go for it, Arashiyama!
Eek!
W-
Wha...?
We...
Welcome hoste, Mammer!
Tatsuno, that girl bit her words!
It's okay!
In fact, that newb-ness is a strike!
I'm home...
Daisy!
Who are you calling Daisy?!
There! A high inside pitch!
The old men around here aren't
immune to these things, are they?
Granny's favorite winning
mahjong hand is chitoitsu, poko.
Shortest route to a maid.
Course number 2: The Clumsy Maid.
But isn't Arashiyama clumsy
even if you leave her by herself?
You are absolutely right.
You guys, aren't you nonchalantly
saying something very rude?
Controlling that clumsiness
is what will make you a true Clumsy Maid!
You learn clumsiness with your body.
Ah, can you take my order?
One Guatemala, please.
Guatemala, hot.
There, it's showtime, Arashiyama!
But, how do I do clumsy?
It's okay. Leave it to me.
Here you go.
Haribara, now!
Got it!
Hot!
Hey... isn't this a bit too harsh?
The combo just fell into place by itself!
She's a natural clutz!
What are you doing, you...?!
You were wonderful, Arashiyama!
Don't pause, and go run with this bucket in your hands!
I'm sorry, let me wipe that up right away!
Then, immediately...
Trip!
This time it's a three-hit combo!
A god, a god descended upon her!
Although, it's not the God of Maids,
but the God of Laughs...
No... the God of Anger!
Do you have some sort of grudge
against me or something?!
It's your fault for piling on the unexpected clumsy!
How's that Guatemala coming?
What the...? it's unusually busy today...
Hotori, there's sucker number two.
Here, practice your greeting.
Sanada...?
Why are you all wet?
Because I'm such a fine woman
I'm just dripping with beauty!
Is the teacher done lecturing you?
Oh! I forgot!
Don't tell him you copied from me. I'll get scolded, too.
Arashiyama, have a second?
Huh? Wh-what?
If I am not seeing this incorrectly, just now...
Isn't he Sanada: attendance number nine?
That's right.
Well, I don't know his attendance number, though.
He... how does he know this store?
What is he doing here?
Does he come often?
Sanada is the son of the fishmonger in town,
so he comes fairly often.
Why?
This place...
Looking at it closely, it's a wonderful maid cafe.
Huh?
Head Maid...
Huh? I'm the store manager!
My name is Toshiko Tatsuno.
Please hire me as a maid!
What?!
Tatsuno, what are you going to do about the club?!
You said you would join the Table Tennis Club with me!
I have a bigger assignment than that.
This will make this place more like a maid cafe.
But there will be more employees
than customers, you know?
Seaside
The store of ultimate bliss.
Open
That is where, even if it is shabby,
the customer can obtain what they desire.
Faculty Room
What happened to Arashiyama...?
Now with
40% more
juice!     EGGPLANT
FLAVOR
Koala Ice
Oya High School
The words "after school" have a fun sort of ring to them,
but there is also a part that
gives the feeling of loneliness.
Because it signals that today is about to end.
Well, let's go for another day!
Your day starts now?
Oh yeah. Sanada.
Tatsuno is going to make a debut at my store.
Huh? She's still going through with that?
Yeah.
I'm just waiting for the maid outfit to be finished.
Granny said she'll finish sewing it today.
That was handmade?
Well, we'll be going ahead!
If you'd like, Sanada, come by later.
Uh... yeah.
Hey, you.
Aren't you working part-time
without permission from the school?
How'd the teacher find out about this?
I don't know.
For today...
...we'll have to shake him off.
Oh! Wait!
Crap!
I lost them!
I thought for certain they'd come this way...!
Are we really going to be able to get away with this?
It's fine! It's not unusual for temples to have
Deva king statues, so no one would take notice!
Note: "Deva kings" are Buddhist gods, and their statues
can be found in pairs in temple entrances.
This trick stabs at that mentality.
Where did they go?!
Must go buy some toilet paper soon, poko.
Seaside
Man! I'm late because of the teacher!
Is Sanada waiting?!
Closed
Sorry we're late, Head Maid!
Welcome.
"Welcome"? But Granny, it's us. You're going senile.
I am not senile.
I said it to the customer behind you.
Ow!
Customer? A customer...
...is here!
Really. You think you were able to shake me off
with that; that disgusts me.
Teacher.
As it states on page 14 line 8,
"Part-time work without permission
is prohibited by the school rules."
According to Article 21,
"If you do wish to work part-time you must
get your guardian's approval,
then submit a request to the homeroom teacher, and...
Ohhhh... My head hurts.
...if the content of the work poses no problem morally,
and the side job is financially necessary,
Big Brother...
...if the content of the work poses no problem morally,
and the side job is financially necessary,
Please stop, Sensei!
...if the content of the work poses no problem morally,
and the side job is financially necessary,
This is exceeding Arashiyama's brain capacity.
...if the content of the work poses no problem morally,
and the side job is financially necessary,
This is exceeding Arashiyama's brain capacity.
only then will you submit a request
to the school counselor, then the Principal..."
Help me, Mikuruya-sensei!
only then will you submit a request
to the school counselor, then the Principal..."
Who is this Mikuruya?! I am Moriaki!
In any case, part-time work that is not abiding
by the school rules will not be accepted!
Nobody follows that, though.
Now that I've found out, as your
homeroom teacher, I cannot let this pass.
What a hard head! No wonder you're a math teacher!
It's been bothering me for a while now...
But how does our teacher know about where we work?
Come to think of it... where did the information leak from?
Don't tell me there's a spy somewhere!
Oh yeah, Sanada.
Tatsuno is going to make a debut at my store.
That was the time!
It was totally leaking!
The information went through directly!
Was it me?!
You are so stupid. Really stupid.
Now that we've gotten to this point,
our only choice is to get permission to work part time.
Of course.
I didn't come here to make you quit.
But, will we ever get permission to work at a maid cafe?
We'll have to make him approve!
With our Maid-jutsu!
"Maid-jutsu"?!
Deluding a man by pretending to be serving
submissively and reaping the profits.
That is Maid-jutsu!
It's the basic philosophy as well!
Now isn't that the very content
that poses a problem morally?
Quiet, you!
This is a battle between a straight arrow
teacher's moral view versus the charm of a maid:
yin and yang, good versus evil,
white and black, monkey versus dog!
That's right...
There is no way I can lose.
For the teacher, this may look like
some part-time job I took on a whim,
but for me, this is the shop Sanada visits regularly!
Seaside
Cafe
SEASIDE
The place I found, the store of ultimate bliss!
Head Maid! Is my outfit finished?
Yeah. It's on the hanger in the back.
Arashiyama, we're going to change
into our battle uniforms!
Okay...
Salmon is actually a white-meat fish, poko.
It's been 22 minutes since they said that...
Girls take their time in getting dressed.
Thank you for waiting.
Starting today I'll be in your care.
I am Maid Number 2, Master!
I've been here a while: I'm Maid Number 1.
Please, let us know of anything you'd like, Master!
I've lost!
Arashiyama!
I lost in grades, I lost in looks, I lost in figure...
And now on top of that, I have totally lost
in how I look in a maid outfit!
Snap out of it, Arashiyama!
Right now, you're fighting the wrong opponent!
What... am I...?
Surprisingly, you might be oblivious of this, Arashiyama...
You have one thing that you would
never lose to Tatsuno in, don't you know?
Is that... if I read into this too far,
or I interpret it to my advantage,
my teacher thinks of me as...
Arashiyama. What you have that wins over Tatsuno...
...is eyesight.
That's brutal!
It's been declared by a third party that,
"Besides eyesight, you've lost in everything"...
Arashiyama, Arashiyama!
Before we could start our attack,
he shattered the most important thing
in Maid-jutsu: self-respect.
He is truly a Maid-killer!
This man...
...is tough!
Tatsuno...
Y-yes sir!
May I have some tea?
As you wish.
I've won!
You must think you're testing me,
but it has the opposite effect.
Tea is my absolute best skill!
I will make the perfect tea that won't
be a disgrace to the maid name!
Head Maid. What type of tea do you have?
Nah.
Huh? Nah?
Is there a kind of tea like that?
No, this store has no tea.
Wh-what?! No tea?!
When you say "maid cafe,"
tea and cake are basic essentials!
Even so, when you think maid you think England!
When you think England, then you think gentlemen!
Gentlemen then tea!
I don't like tea.
Tea's a pain to brew.
It's even in the word for cafe: "Tea House"!
It's tea, black tea!
The "Cafe" in "Maid Cafe" means coffee, right?
Man! When I say this, you say the other!
I don't know about tea either.
Is it the one that's Little Gray?
That's an alien!
Earl Gray...
Oh, I know one more: Notalin!
Note: Notalin (ノータリン) is "simpleton." Close (as in not really) to the
pronunciation of Darjiling (ダージリン) or "Darjeeling."
You're the notalin!
Did she mean to say Darjeeling?
Damn! The teacher has no weakness!
On the other hand, this store has
an overwhelming weakness...
I don't feel like we can win!
That's it.
If I can use this weakness to our advantage...
Arashiyama, whatever is fine; just go act out
one of your original clumsiness routines!
Wha...?!
Apply what you learned the last time!
It's okay, you can do it!
If Arashiyama's clumsiness can hit his soft spot...
We don't have tea, so please bear with coffee, okay?
If she can hit his soft spot,
then I can find a weakness to exploit!
Here you go.
Then, truly, truly he'll be within the palm of Maid-jutsu!
Whoa! The coffee exploded!
Oh no!
I made a mistake and brought you some cola!
Nice, Arashiyama!
Even I felt something in my
heart with that clumsy move! So cool!
I'll exchange it right away. Teh heh!
Wait, Arashiyama.
Coffee is made using a coffee syphon or coffee maker.
How on Earth can you make a mistake
and serve cola? Explain it to me.
Eh? Uh... Um... Wha...?
What?
Well... uh...
The color is similar...
Did you do it on purpose?
No... um...
Did you do it on purpose?!
I did do it on purpose... I'm sorry...
She's being lectured by that teacher...
Not even clumsy moves work on the teacher...?
Sit down right there, Arashiyama!
Yes, sir...
I don't understand why you do such things
that make no sense at all!
Your actions are absurd!
Yes, sir...
Do you even know what kind of job a maid does?
Where in the world would you find a servant
who is happy to play a prank on her customer?!
Yes, sir... there is no such servant...
Overseas, there was an incident where someone took
cola and candy and was rushed to the hospital.
Seems like permission for part-time work
and whatnot is going to be swept under the rug...
Overseas, there was an incident where someone took
cola and candy and was rushed to the hospital.
By the time the lecture started,
Arashiyama had already won...
Overseas, there was an incident where someone took
cola and candy and was rushed to the hospital.
By the time the lecture started,
Arashiyama had already won...
Even as a prank, it is truly thoughtless.
Come to think of it... Sanada is late...
Wh-why is even the teacher here?
YAKISOBA
You've got to be kidding me...
This was the store at which
I could be alone with Arashiyama...
My store of ultimate bliss... has changed.
You are always like that.
You write "1=0." Do you not even notice
that it doesn't make sense?!
Absurd. Truly absurd!
Yes, sir...
People always seek the ultimate bliss,
but the ultimate bliss does not seek people.
That is because it is very rare when it comes on its own.
Puppy poko poko 3 poko poko,
put them together poko poko 6 poko poko.
The store of ultimate bliss...
That is where, even if it is shabby,
the customer can obtain what they desire.
No matter how beautiful it is,
if what is desired is not there,
then it is the same as an empty shed.
Some tea.
Thank you for waiting.
What is this?!
Welcome back, Master.
My, my, this is your maid.
Once you've opened the door, we won't let you go.
What... did you say?!
Now, now, to the back, to the back.
Seaside
Welcome.
This is your store of ultimate bliss.
One, two, one, two, three, four!
I'm so bored, I have the heart of Rock n roll
Living alone a life of loud music
I'm oblivious with cheeks like a blowfish
Today again, the town to chaos will I drag into
Being tsundere is proof of my intelligence
Again today, I'm unable to confess my love to this man
I gave my life to table tennis
To strengthen my legs and hips when I play the drums
This band isn't a scam
This band isn't rock
We're not going for an ondo dance
We're not going to arrive in Nirvana
We are the Maids "Yeah!"
Dressed as maids we
Are here, we are here!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
This is Hell "Yeah!"
The crime scene is
A terrible sight, a terrible sight!
"Oh no!"
We are the invincible Maids "Yeah!"
Constipation is a difficult delivery
Enema, enema!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Pure and right and frank
Seaside is, with rave reviews, open for business!!
"Thank you always for your business!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
My boss at the office is the worst,
so I thought about framing him for
sexual harassment and killing him socially.
Isn't that going too far?
But he didn't budge even when I tried to seduce him,
so I put on some sexy underwear,
flipped my skirt up, and showed it to him.
You are bolder than I thought.
Then he sued me for sexual harassment.
You were the one sued?!
Cafe Seaside
Next episode, Street Number Two,
STREET NO. 02 "SEXUAL HARASSMENT LAWSUITS
ARE MAJORLY POPULAR"
"Sexual Harassment Lawsuits are Majorly Popular."
Today we're turning round and round, poko.
Cafe Seaside