Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
Each and every small thing is a thing of great beauty.
So cold!
Hey!
It's cold today, isn't it, Yuzu-chan?
Haruka, didn't you see the weather forecast?
Snow?!
A Snowy Day, Memories and a Shock
It almost never snows around here!
This is quite rare!
I wonder if we'll get a lot?!
It'll probably stop soon.
Yuu-chan's probably sleeping.
Yuu-chan, it's snowing!
She's awake!
Strange things are happening here, too!
Or not.
She was practically falling asleep.
Yuu-chan, it's lunch break!
It's snowing!
Look outside!
Poke
This is no time to sleep!
Wake up!
She's eating it!
What's with all the noise?
Sheesh, Haruka, you're acting like a kid.
Yuu-chan, it's snowing!
What?!
I'm not interested in snow!
Such a mature thing to say.
You can't do PE outside!
So you're a kid, too, huh?
I really like it, though.
I love it, too!
It's so magical, isn't it?
It really is!
As expected from Shizuku-chan!
I know!
Since we actually got snow,
let's eat lunch outside!
Harupoppo, are you out of your mind?
Rethink that.
Yeah.
I-I'm in!
Shizuku-chan!
All right, what's everyone going to choose?
No way, it's cold out.
Me neither.
Nope!
The only one left...
Stare
Kaede-chan, say something!
There are student council issues I need to attend to,
so I'll pass.
Ah, I see.
No way!
Three against two!
The inside faction wins!
We'll go by ourselves, then!
Shizuku-chan?
O-Okay.
She's quite stubborn.
Hold it.
Are you changing sides?
It may be cold out, but this is still nice, isn't it?
Yeah.
Are you all right?
I don't want you catching a cold.
I'm fine!
I have a hand warmer.
Want to use it?
So warm!
Yeah!
I-I can't eat my lunch like this.
Yeah...
H-Haruka-chan, I don't think we should overdo it.
T-That's right, but...
Shall we go in?
But...
We may not be able to see something like this...
...for another year or two.
Since this might be the last time we see snow,
I want to burn it into my memories.
We shouldn't be doing this!
Haruka-chan, sometimes you and Kotone say similar things.
Huh?
Like just now?
Yeah.
You're both determined.
She said that since three years is a short time, she wants to treasure them.
Kotone-chan said that to me, too.
That if I pass up this chance,
Yuu-chan will never get to be a cheerleader.
I see.
Now I understand why she's so determined.
That's right.
Kotone-chan is engaged.
And since there's only so much time she can spend with Shizuku-chan,
she's freeloading at Shizuku-chan's place even though her family's against it.
Wait here.
She left.
Even though I'm with Kotone-chan right now,
once we graduate, it won't be that way anymore.
I...
I don't want it to end at that.
When we graduate, and even after that...
I want to be with her forever.
Shizuku-chan, let's enjoy ourselves.
Let's make some memories.
And when we grow up,
we can talk about how we did this a long time ago.
So cold!
I said I don't want to!
You'll get used to it eventually!
What are you, a kid?
We're high schoolers!
Hey! You blockhead!
Yuu-chan!
Angry
Yuzu-chan, you didn't have to take it so seriously!
She called me a blockhead!
Direct hits on Shizuku-chan and Kotone-chan!
Yuu-chan, sheesh...
No!
My hair band got wet!
Shizuku-chan is yelling...
You're not even close.
All right, let's start!
Here comes!
Yuu-chan!
Kotone-chan, you're so mean!
What?
I think Yuu's the blockhead-
Now you've done it!
It's fun to play with everyone like this.
You're right.
Please don't forget about Kaede.
Student Council Room
That's all.
And with that, the Student Council's leadership has changed hands.
Since you'll only have second-years next year,
please do your best.
Sumi-chan, we'll leave the rest to you.
Got it!
Just leave everything to me!
Big
Sister
Thank you for your work this past year!
Thank you too!
President Mitsuki!
Kaede-san?
Thank you for everything.
Though, you're not President Mitsuki anymore, are you?
Ex-President Mitsuki!
Don't force yourself.
Well...
I've been worried about it for a while,
but I guess that just how you are, President Mitsuki.
I realise it's hard to talk about it,
but you can talk to me about it whenever you want.
Huh?
I'm sure Yuzu will be surprised too,
but I believe we're thinking the same thing...
Probably.
What are you going on about?
Haruka and Yuu are dating, aren't they?
A Snowy Day, Memories and a Shock                  The End
Yeah, that meat was totally out there!
I wonder what we're doing in PE today.
No idea.
I think the teacher said we're doing jump rope.
What?!
I would rather play volleyball!
Yuu-chan, won't you be cold?
I'll be fine!
They do say kids have vigorous legs!
I'm not fishy eggs!
Fish eggs, huh?
Kaede-chan, we're about to leave.
Sorry, I'm coming.
Kaede, your skirt!
That was close.
I almost wrinkled my skirt.
Geez.
We're going to be late for PE.
Huh
Huh?
Did you really forget to take it off?
Yeah.
Since it was you, I thought you did it on purpose,
and were just waiting for someone to take the bait.
Well, don't worry about it.
A Promise in the Gymnastics Storage
What's wrong with you today?
You've been weird all day.
I've just got something on my mind.
Kaede-chan's acting weird?
I didn't notice.
I thought she was the same as always.
Kotone, you didn't notice either?
Hm?
Haven't you known each other since middle school?
I've had my hands full with you, Shizuku-chan.
What?
W-What do you mean by that?
Oh you!
Shizuku-chan is so cute!
Isn't she?
Stop that!
You're messing up my hair!
Yuu-chan, save me!
Shizuku-chan!
It's hard to pinpoint what's odd about Kaede-chan.
She has quite the poker face.
I wonder if something is troubling her.
She's always odd!
After all, she carries a toy rat around with her!
If something's troubling her,
it's probably something along the lines of deciding who to scare today!
There's no need to be worried.
Paf
Oh no.
I accidentally threw my spider.
To think that we were worried!
Well, it was mostly just Shizuku-chan.
Where do you even buy something like that?
Not that I would buy one even if I found one!
But Haruka,
this is a stuffed toy.
Yuu-chan, don't touch it!
Spit now! Spit!
Is she supposed to spit it out?
*Grin*
I'll have to get my revenge during jump rope!
You should be more forgiving, Haruka.
Kaede-chan's toying with my forgiving heart!
Sheesh.
Since you're like that, Haruka, you're keeping your title of JHSG!
How is this related to jealousy?!
Juvenile High School Girl!
J
Juvenile
H
High
S
School
G
Girl
J
Juvenile
H
High
S
School
G
Girl
That's what it's short for!
No!
I got another weird trait!
The long ropes are ready, right?
Yes!
We'll be competing in groups for the highest jump count.
The lowest scoring group will be penalized,
so do your best, everyone!
What?
I don't like this.
I have no confidence.
*Grumble*
I won't lose to Kaede-chan!
Grumble
Oh!
Okay, ready...
Start!
Heave-ho!
One!
Geez, Haruka!
Four!
Five!
Here goes!
One!
Sorry...
Once more!
One!
Ouch!
It's fine.
One!
Haruka!
Just jump, Haruka!
I am jumping!
One more trait for the JHSG!
That was neither jealous nor juvenile!
J
Jaw-droppingly clumsy
Jaw-droppingly clumsy High School Girl!
H
High
S
School
G
Girl
J
H
S
G
Jaw-droppingly clumsy
High
School
Girl
Are you trying to make me mad?
I don't have anything to say to that.
Harupoppo, you tend to jump when the rope is going up,
But instead you should jump when the rope is coming down.
Let's rethink this and start again!
Okay!
Here comes!
One!
I did it!
I jumped over it!
Sorry, I screwed up.
I'll let it go if it's Shizuku-chan.
Yuu-chan!
Nine-hundred ninety eight!
Nine-hundred ninety nine!
One thousand!
Okay, that's it!
Ikeno's group did great!
And so...
Slump
We'll leave the cleaning to the lowest scoring group.
Pout
*Pout*
Haruka, you kept messing up the whole time!
I know that!
I'll do all the cleaning to make up for it!
Thank you, Harupoppo!
Are you sure about that?
It's okay!
It's just putting away the jump ropes.
Don't worry!
There are so many.
Hey, after all...
Silence
T-They left already...
Yuu-chan, what's wrong?
Nothing!
Should we wait for Haruka-chan?
Yeah!
Such a bright smile.
She's so easy to read!
Did they finish cleaning already?
That was quick.
There.
That's everything!
Huh?
Clang
I got locked in!
Hey, wait!
I'm still in here!
Someone open the door!
Ah!
M-My cell phone!
...is in my uniform's pocket.
Yuu-chan, I've been locked in.
This happened that one time...
...when we snuck into that empty classroom.
That time I wasn't scared since I was with Yuu-chan, though.
Yuu-chan!
Haruka sure is taking her time.
Maybe we should have helped her.
What are you doing?
Why haven't you returned to the classroom yet?
Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan, you know...
You cleaned up really quickly.
Thanks a lot!
Sensei?
What?!
Haruka's not coming back?!
Haruka got locked in the storage room!
S-Sensei, wait!
I'll go check from the back of the building.
Kotone, you go check from inside!
Okay.
She really is worried about her girlfriend.
Girl friend?
Actually, which one is the girlfriend in this case?
Hey, Haruka!
Are you in there?
Maybe she's not in there after all.
Maybe we just missed each other.
Haruka!
A hand!
She reacted to Yuu's voice.
It appears she really did get locked in.
I wonder if she's okay.
What if she's pinned under something?
It looks like she's fine.
Yeah.
But I'm so worried!
How about peeking in?
Yuzu-chan!
Please!
I don't want to carry you on my shoulders though.
Here, I found a ladder.
Thank you, Kaede-chan!
Haruka!
Yuu-chan!
Are you okay?
I can't get out!
Grab
Thank you!
Haruka! I'm going to fall!
I was thinking about you before you got here.
And then I wanted to do it...
B-But...
Yuzu-chan and Kaede-chan are below me!
That's right.
We can't do it here, can we?
I-If it's quick.
They won't notice, will they?
Don't worry.
It looks like Yuu is trying to pull Haruka out.
I don't think that's possible.
Hey, that's dangerous!
Haruka-chan!
Yuu-chan?
I was worried about what was going to happen to me!
It's because you're so clumsy.
You're quite the troublemaker.
Sorry for making you do it all.
Are you hurt?
I'm all fine!
It really looks like they are dating.
Contrary to what President Mitsuki said...
What are you saying?
Dating?
Well...
Do Mikan-san and the others know, too?
I'm starting to think she's doing this on purpose.
No.
I haven't actually asked them.
This is just a theory I have.
So they aren't actually dating, huh?
I mean, they're both girls and all.
Don't scare me like that.
You're right.
Don't worry.
Haruka-san is a normal girl who just goes overboard with physical contact.
That's
all
Big
Sister
That's all.
Haruka-san works hard so she can support Yuu.
I see.
Sorry for making you worry!
President Mitsuki was only talking about Haruka.
A Promise in the Gymnastics Storage               The End
Smile ♡  Rina-chan
Smile, Rina-chan!
Vice President Rina!
Good morning!
Do you have a moment?
Thank you!
H-Huh, what?
Next we have an announcement from Vice President Sakai Rina.
Thank you very much!
H-Hey...
What?!
Hey, Kaede!
What was that all about?!
I mean, the only thing Vice President Rina does is sm-
Yuzu!
I think that's enough.
But, Kaede...
Ah, well, that's...
Never mind.
Smile ♡ Rina-chan                                        The End
Yay
Won't you kiss
Kiss and love
futari dake no jikan ga
二人だけの時間が
Time for just the two of us
futari dake no himitsu ga
二人だけの秘密が
A secret for just the two of us
futari dake no yakusoku
二人だけの約束
A promise between just the two of us
aru kara ne
あるからね
We have all of them
yorokobi wakachiaete kanashimi wakeaetara
喜び分かち合えて 悲しみ分け合えたら
If we share our joys and split our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
一人より幸せに なれるように
We may be able to become happier than if we were alone
ashita mo omoide wo saa fuyasou
明日も思い出をさあ増やそう
Let's make more memories tomorrow as well
ippai ni shichaou ne
一杯にしちゃおうね
Let's make a lot of them!
Love you
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
この広い世界で 逢えた奇跡
I came across a miracle in this wide world
tokubetsu na no anata janai to dame dakara
特別なの あなたじゃないとだめだから
But it's no good if you're not special to me
futari janai to dekinai koto da yo
二人じゃないとできないことだよ
It's something we can't do if we're not together
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
いますぐに 大好き kiss and love
I love you now, kiss and love
Love
Preview
Hey, what's up with that mandarin orange?
I got it from mum.
It looks delicious.
It was a little sour.
But it was still sweeter than a lemon, wasn't it?
Speaking of which, one of my friends is called Yuzu-chan.
I see.
Onee-chan, it's not fair to eat so much of it!
But isn't it okay?
So, what is Mikan-san like?
Mikan-chan loves yakisoba!
Next time, Trick 11.
The President is Sumisumi!
The Sakura-coloured Truth
"The President is Sumisumi" and "The Sakura-coloured Truth".
Look forward to it!
Huh?