Damn, I'm tired.
School takes so much out of me.
I can't keep this up anymore.
Aokigahara
Enjoy nature
Mt. Fuji
Lost
A single flower signals
the coming of spring.
Onii-chan?
Top Secret
Let's see what kind of porn DVDs he's been watching.
I can't believe he's interested in other girls.
That's like cheating on me!
He's young, so I understand his libido can get out of control,
but he's dead if this isn't guys screwing their sisters!
I'm the one in charge of this project, Yagami Tsurugi.
Without further ado, let's begin the Sasami Watch Project.
Huh?
From a god's fingertips
The golden days of my life come
A long dream that took me beyond the starry sky
Is disturbed by a song
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
When I shut my ears and pretended to be a good girl
I felt as if I lost my identity
I was just trying to put up a facade
But I couldn't stop the noise from influencing me
Then I came across a lone flower
It was so scary yet so kind
The moment I touched it, even dioramas became real
From a god's frivolous thoughts
The course of my future is laid out
Thousands of tones resonate
Shattering the future coming after me
When we came together under the starry sky
I caught sight of warmth
A bond will form between us as we overcome hardships
That's the kind of bond I want to cherish
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode Four
Leeching Off Family
Testing, testing. One, two, three.
Do I look good on video, Tsukuyomi?
Yes, you look just fine.
What is this?
The goal of the Sasami Watch Project is
to support Tsukuyomi Sasami,
who has finally managed to rejoin society.
Support me?
Despite the power of the supreme god inside her,
she's trying to live an ordinary life.
If that's how she wants to live,
I want to help her in every way I can.
That's what we're here for.
Tsurugi...
To that end, we'll train Sasami how to deal with real life by giving her challenges to overcome.
The members of the Sasami Watch Project will
videotape this clueless girl and laugh at her when she struggles and screws up.
I should've known they were up to no good.
Sasami has already been assigned a challenging task,
and my capable little sisters are filming her.
Hey, Camera Two, give us an update.
That's too close! Get away from the camera!
This is Yagami Kagami with Camera Two.
I'm currently tailing Sasami-san at a distance of 30 meters.
Isn't that... me?
Sasami-san does not seem
to have noticed I'm following her.
When did they film this?
Did I ever go somewhere like that?
I don't remember being there.
What's going on?
Good work, Kagami.
Next up, Camera Three. How are things over there?
Oh, yeah. I became a presenter for our school's TV broadcasts!
But guess what?
I spoke too loudly on air,
so the headmaster, who has a weak heart—
A phone call!
Hello, Tama speaking!
Where are you right now?
Well, there was a bright flash from the sky,
then I found myself here.
Then these little gray people with big eyes, who are filming me right now, said to me,
"Intelligent Earth lifeform,
we have questions for you,"
in a really unnatural accent.
Don't trust strangers!
They might perform operations on you while you're still
conscious or plant mysterious pieces of metal inside you!
Anyway, get back to work!
Uh, Tsurugi-sensei, what was that just now?
Don't talk about it.
Pretend you never saw it!
Hey, Camera Two, I want another update.
What the hell are you doing?!
Nee-san, can we take it home with us?
Now's not the time for that. Where's Sasami?
Well...
I think I lost her.
Are you kidding me?
I will use something akin to a spiritual wave from a satellite in orbit to detect Sasami-san's location.
I know her location.
She seems to be at the other side
of the shopping mall.
H-Hey...
Don't dash on the rooftops!
What are you, a ninja?!
Tee-hee.
Don't "Tee-hee" me!
You're adorable!
Please marry me!
Sasami-san seems to be entering a drugstore.
Good, good.
She's on her way to buy what I asked her to get.
Oh? Sasami-san appears to be having trouble locating the item she's after.
Nee-san, what did you ask her to get?
Are you looking for something?
Um, this...
One box of prophylactics? Okay.
OFF
That's not something a minor should be buying!
A cute high school girl,
blushing, asks for prophylactics.
Isn't that just adorable?
Sorry, but it seems we don't carry that here.
I see.
My teacher told me it'd be at the drugstore, though.
By the way, what's a prophylactic?
Huh? You don't know what that is?
The sad truth is that young people these days don't use that term.
I'd say your attempt to sexually harass her failed.
No way!
People used to laugh out loud
when someone said "prophylactics"!
It seems Sasami-san is off to buy the next item on her list.
Oh, she entered a 100-yen store.
What would she go there for?
You didn't tell her to buy something from there?
Nope.
Oh, she came out.
It looks like she bought something.
Let me see what's inside the bag.
You can see through objects?!
Sunglasses and a knit hat.
I also see a sweatsuit.
Who cares about that? Use that power on Sasami!
What color are they?
What are you trying to see?!
I don't care what color Sasami-san's panties are.
That'd be nice to know,
but I'm talking about her nipples!
Stop it!
Oh?
What's wrong? She's not wearing any panties?!
She is about to enter a bath complex.
Bath
Complex
I wonder why.
Couldn't she just take a bath at home?
She might not want to because Tsukuyomi peeps on her.
I never peep.
We always enter the bathroom together.
You do what?!
Bath
Complex
She went inside.
I'll follow her.
Bath
Complex
Your Tickets Here
Coin Return
Bathing Tickets
One high school student.
I'm amazed they just let you in with that camera in your hand.
WO MEN
I had their perception undergo
a Transformation so that it wouldn't bother them.
That's my little sister!
I found Sasami-san!
Stop!
Stop filming!
I'm getting undressed!
Stop it!
No!
Okay, time for a commercial break!
Commercial
Break
B
It was a tranquil winter night, bathed in dazzling moonlight.
When did they...
No, that's not what it looks like!
Ah, jeez.
The hell is this footage?
Part of my treasured
Sasami-san's Sleeping Face collection!
You're supposed to say,
"Smile! You're on Candid Camera!"
Enough of that, back to Camera Two.
Kagami? What are you doing, Kagami?
Please leave me alone.
Why are you relaxing here?
What happened to the footage of Sasami getting in the bath?
If you're looking for Sasami-san,
all she did was change clothes and leave.
I'm sleepy now.
I regret to say this is as far as I go.
Hurry up and go after her!
Aren't you supposed to be in my debt?
As your big sister, changing your diapers and offering you a pacifier are things
I'd love to do as part of some ageplay, because I adore you so much!
I don't get what you're talking about, you sexual deviant.
Say it again!
Oh well. Tsukuyomi, we should take this into our own hands.
What's with this DVD?
I don't remember ever running this errand.
What's going on? I have a bad feeling about this.
This is bad.
Really bad.
Really bad!
All right, we're here!
Sasami is sure to come here!
Where are we?
This place is called Uzume no Ana.
With a focus on anime, game, and manga items,
it carries all sorts of goods
relevant to modern subcultures.
Novels
Manga
Think of it as a kind of department store.
So basically a shop for otaku.
You put it so bluntly.
So, where's Sasami-san?
On the third floor.
Let's go!
It says those under 18 are not allowed on the third floor.
Official Publications (Novels, Art Books, Technique Guides)
Mail Order Pick-up
Original Self-Published Works (General, Adult)
Goods for Adults
General Self-Published Works (Anime, Manga, Novels, Game...)
Adult Self-Published Works
Amateur-Produced Goods
Official Works
(Other manga, series with anime adaptations)
(New manga, magazines)
Where's Sasami?
Found her!
She's in disguise, but it doesn't fool me!
Let's see...
It's this one, right?
Yamato Chronicles
Taketake-run
Ibuki
Yen
Yamato Chronicles
Taketake-run
Kumaso
Yen
Let's check.
Ibuki-chan
from Yamato Chronicles
Taketake-run
Buy the limited edition
with detachable armor!!
The armor
can't be taken off
the standard model!
Ibuki-chan from Yamato Chronicles Taketake-run?
"Buy the limited edition with detachable armor."
"The armor can't be taken off the standard model."
Who gives a shit?
Yamato Chronicles
Taketake-run
Ibuki
Yen
Limited Edition Cast-Off
[QUANTITY LIMITED]
Yen
This costs 30,000 yen?!
Anyway, I'll have to get the store clerk.
Oh, she gave up.
Way to go, Sasami!
Welcome to my world.
I will give half of the world to you.
Stop! Don't go over there!
Little sister fetish?
Why am I being humiliated like this?
No way.
She's his little sister, right?
Why?
Oh, yeah. I can relate to that.
What?
What are they doing?
This is a man's...
Kill me! Just kill me now!
Um, do you have a moment?
You look like a high school student.
Well, I'm...
Are you here for the VA's performance on the fourth floor?
Huh? Y-Yes.
Sorry. I know it's hard to find your way around here.
The staircase is over here.
Let's follow them, Tsurugi-sensei!
Shut it, fuckwit!
I told you, I ain't no grade-schooler!
Huh?
Just sell it to me!
I'm sorry little girl, I can only sell manga like these to adults.
I told you already, I am an adult!
I'll just go on ahead.
Akihabara Branch
Event Hall
Adult Self-Published Works (Anime, Manga, Novels)
Self-Published
Works
for Women
Voice Actor Mini-Live!!
Thanks, everybody!
It's shaking, shaking, shaking
fuwa fuwa fuwa yureru
The fluffy, fluffy, fluffy ribbon
fuwa fuwa fuwa ribon
And I'm shaking, shaking, shaking
fuwa fuwa fuwa watashi
What are you doing?
Get in sync with everybody else!
Inside my maiden heart
chu chu chu otomegokoro
Huh? O-Okay.
Wrong!
We're using red for this song!
Huh? O-Okay.
The brilliant morning sunshine wakes me up
mabushii asahi mezamashi bari ni
I shouldn't just send you a text
meeru wa zurui (doki) kara (doki)
I'm excited to start a new day (surprise)
chotto ureshii sai start (surprise)
I feel like I can even fly right now
ima nara sora mo tobesou da yo
I hope I'll get to see you soon
sugu ni ai ni iketara ii na
Excuse me. Please let me through.
Excuse me, sir!
Video recording is prohibited.
Oh? U-Um, no. I'm not filming the VA, I'm videotaping Sasami-san.
K-Kamiomi-san?!
Why are you here?
Huh? Weren't you a shrine maiden at the Tsukuyomi Shrine?
I-I wasn't! I don't even know what Tsukuyomi Shrine is!
Please leave, Kamiomi-san!
If someone from the Tsukuyomi Shrine is here...
could this suspicious event be...
Now!
Congratulations are in order.
Father!
My dear daughter!
Leave the excess burden to your father!
Sasami-san!
Now the Sun will surrender its throne to the Moon,
and the human world will see a new reader!
What have you done, Father?!
This soul planned it all.
When the seal weakened and it regained its self-consciousness,
it made contact with us
and suggested we execute this plan.
Does that mean...
Indeed!
The power of the supreme god is right here!
Right in the palm of my hand!
Screw that guy. He wasted my time over nothing.
Huh?
What are you doing, Tsukuyomi?
Do as you wish.
So you were the source of the suspicious presence I sensed.
You'll pay a heavy price
for interrupting my Happy Nap time.
Out of my way!
Sorry!
The government was after us, so I ran away here.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
I won't hand over this marvel of the universe, Ntosmordent, to anyone!
Hey, you over there!
Hand that alien over to the United Earth Government!
This little one will be going back to his home planet!
Now we've got no choice.
Commence the attack!
What the hell?! What's going on?
This seems to be a drug for erasing memories.
Boys, get rid of those mischievous meddlers!
All units, charge!
Let's run away, Kyupi-chan!
I'll… be… free!
So that's what happened.
Huh?
I took down the grunts from the Tsukuyomi Shrine,
while Tsukuyomi called an ambulance and took Sasami to the hospital.
You inhaled that green gas and
were disorientated by the memory loss.
So I used Transformation to make a DVD that would give you the gist of what happened.
Do you remember who you are now...
Sarcoma-chan?
You were part of her body to begin with,
so it's no surprise you came home believing you're the real Sasami.
What are you going to do with me?
You're a part of Sasami.
I can't say what'll happen
when you're detached from her.
I'll use Transformation to change you back to a lump of flesh
then reattach it to Sasami so you can be reincorporated.
Then things will be back as they were.
Don't mess with me!
I'll be free!
She and I are different people!
Do you understand the pain of being trapped in someone else's body, unable to do anything?
I was finally torn off from her.
I'll live freely, any way I want!
That's right, I have power.
The power of the supreme god is within me.
I can do whatever I want to you!
I order in the name of the supreme god, you—
Give it back.
You can't handle this toy.
What...
I would've been nicer if you showed
some remorse and played along nicely.
Well, don't worry.
I do feel a little sorry for you.
I won't go so far as to say I'm a hard-working god,
but I still make miracles happen once in a while!
Are you awake?
What happened to me?
You are who you always have been.
Sarcoma's gone, though.
Oh.
She and you share the same body. You two are the same person.
You two had the same wish: to live freely,
and both of you make a lot of trouble for those around you.
But she committed a sin.
She attempted to sacrifice others for the sake of her own happiness.
You, on the other hand, are well aware of the trouble you cause others
and do what you can to try and minimize it.
You never abused the power of the supreme god.
In fact, you're rejecting it, saying you don't want it.
So being the mischievous god I am,
I'll leave it with you.
Keep working hard...
until the day you'll no longer have to.
Hello, Meat-chan! It's your big sister, Kagami.
Meat-chan?
That's the name I gave her.
I can't call her Sasami-san
just because she was a part of her, can I?
Meat is something you eat, though.
She's so cute that I want to gobble her up,
although since I'm not human, I don't eat food.
Right.
So where's Tama?
Goodbye!
There are some scientific fields humans aren't ready to explore yet.
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
What's up?
I'm your much-loved protagonist, Tsukuyomi Sasami!
I'll be singing a song for you all today!
So listen up, okay?
Tsukuyomi Sasami's "Osmotic Pressure Symphony!"
What?
We've only just said bye bye after school
mata ashita ne bye bye shitemo
But I'm already starting to miss you
nanka sugu ni aitaku naru
Until I get on the train home
densha ni noru made zutto
I want to listen to your voice
koe wo kiitetai yo
Why are you suddenly so motivated?
D-Do you have a fever or something, Sasami-san?
I look stunned, and you smile
akiregao kimi ga warau
Are you really Sasami-san?
Who are you?
Come on, I've always been like this, Onii-chan!
I love you! Kiss, kiss!
This feels so strange.
I can hear your voice
kikoeru yo kimi no koe ga
The symphony echoes off into the distance
doko made mo hibiku symphony
I'm doing pretty well, I think.
Did I manage to sing well?
Well, um… yes!
The singing itself was perfect.
Then I'll sing next time too!
I was driven out of the main episode, but there's still a place for me here!
I'll be happy here!
Okay, I'll sing even better next time!
You're definitely not Sasami-san!
Who are you?
It's time for Lazy Counseling.
We have a letter from Mr. A from Tokyo.
"Lately, I haven't been motivated to do anything."
"I feel like I've just been lazying around."
"I could do a good job if I tried, but I can't bring myself to."
"I think the world is to blame."
"You understand how I feel, don't you, Sasami-san?"
Stop being a baby. Get to work.
Next time, episode five:
"I Haven't Given It My All Yet."
Next time,
episode five
I Haven't Given It My All Yet