You sure are a cute little plushie...
Here, here.
Poke, poke!
This isn't good...
Excuse me...
Itsuki?
Is this yours, by any chance?
It really is cute. Where did you buy it?
Huh? Well, um...
I-I made it myself!
Really? I guess I should expect nothing less of the Fashion Club's leader.
It really is cute!
Huh? There's a leaf stuck in it.
There we go.
There.
All clean again.
I'm shure I felt it!
Potpourri?
Huh?
The Precure ish that girl! It has to be Ichuki!
Huh?! I-Itsuki?!
I've been looking for a girl like her!
She'sh kind, cool, and just really amazing!
I'm going to go and shtay with Ichuki!
Bye bye!
Stooooooop!
What are you doing this late at night?
What's going on?
Potpourri, are you sure Itsuki is a Precure?!
What?!
I felt it like a shudden shock! I'm shure it hash to be her!
Now I'll be able to shecure the Great Heart Tree!
Hooray!
Potpourri, you can't just choose a Precure based on what you want them to be!
You have to make sure they have the proper heart for—
I'm shure it has to be her! I want to be with Ichuki!
Potpourri!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Cure Sunshine
is Born!
Shtop holding me back!
Just sit still!
They're right.
Jeez... You were kicking up a fuss
all night, so why aren't you tired?
I didn't sleep at all...
She's here!
Ichuki!
Take care, then.
I'll see you later.
Could Itsuki really be a Precure?
Tsubomi, Erika, go and find out!
We're counting on you!
Right!
Huh?
Itsuki...
She seems kinda depressed.
How are we supposed to find out?
We can't just ask her, "Hey, are you a Precure?"
Oh, I've got it!
Before we became Precure, we had dreams about the Great Heart Tree and Cure Moonlight, right?
I see! So we just have to ask if she's had the same dreams!
Well then, hurry up and go ashk Ichuki if she's sheen them!
All right, all right!
Itsuki!
Huh?
The hospital?
Did something happen to her?
Big brother?
I'm coming in.
Oh, it's just you.
How are you feeling?
Oh!
I-I-Itsuki's mom?!
Good afternoon! Good afternoon! Good afternoon!
Sorry to make you go to all this trouble.
It's no bother, really.
The weather's nice outside, you know?
Let's let some light in.
Don't open them!
I-It's too bright for me.
Just leave it.
Big brother...
Oh, big brother!
Is there nothing I can do to help you?!
U-Um...
E-Excuse me...
G-Good afternoon...
You're worried about your brother's surgery, aren't you?
But it's the good kind of surgery, isn't it?
It'll help him get back on his feet!
The doctors all say it'll go smoothly.
However...
Even though he should be looking forward to it the most, my brother's been acting strangely.
He always has this pained expression,
and doesn't seem to be sleeping at night.
He always used to smile, no
matter how bad his illness got.
That's the kind of man he used to be.
Big brother?
Just look up at the Sun and do what I do.
Come on, follow my lead.
See? When you bathe in the Sun's rays,
your troubles just melt away, don't they?
Yeah!
Satsuki's a very kind person, isn't he?
Yeah...
But when I see my brother worrying
and suffering because of this surgery,
I want to give him strength.
I want to protect him!
They're back!
Potpourri!
What did she shay?!
Hash Ichuki had the dreamsh?!
Sorry, we forgot to ask.
Jusht what were you doing in there, then?!
Today really wasn't a good time to ask.
We'll ask once Satsuki's had his operation, okay?
That'sh no good! That'sh no good!
Potpourri?
We're going to go pay Satsuki a visit!
Stop sulking and come out of there!
Ichuki!
Huh? Isn't this the plushie that Kurumi and Hanasaki had?
Huh?
It spoke?!
Good morning!
We've been had!
I've been waiting to shee you, Ichuki!
Nishe to meet you! My name ish Potpourri!
It's... so cute...
No, what am I doing?!
There's a plushie walking around and talking.
That's not it either!
Oh, I know!
N-Nice to meet you. My name is Myoudouin Itsuki.
Nishe to meet you too!
Um...
I'm one of the Precures' fairies!
F-Fairies?
Ichuki, pleashe become my Precure!
Huh? You want me to be a Precure?
I can have a costume as cute as that too?
You can have one that'sh even cuter!
You'll look shimply fantastic!
You really think so?
I do!
Sho please, become a Precure and
help me protect the Great Heart Tree!
Protect... the Great Heart Tree?
Right!
Protect it?
What'sh the matter?
I don't think I have the right to be a Precure.
Whaaat?!
Wh-Wh-Why not?!
I already have so many things I want to protect.
I've been trying as hard as I can to do so,
but in the end, I don't think I have the strength for it.
Itsuki!
P-Potpourri?!
Shush!
Good morning!
G-Good morning!
What's with that bulge?!
Well, um... I ate too much last night, that's all!
What the heck did you eat?!
Is Potpourri nearby?
Not that I can see.
Itsuki, here. For your brother.
Thank you very much.
I hope your brother feels better soon.
We'll be hoping for the best.
Thank you.
It's not long now till the operation.
What should I do?
Itsuki...
That's right.
The Sun...
That's a nice look you have on your face.
Wh-Who are you?!
It just screams "I'm scared! I'm
so scared! I want to run away!"
Don't worry. I'll make all the pain go away.
Big brother!
Satsuki!
Chaaaaaaaaair!
Itsuki, please wait here!
Ichuki! Pleashe follow me!
Huh?
Chaaaaaaaaaaaaaaiiiiiiiiiiir!
Go wild to your heart's content!
Sasorina!
What?
You showed up pretty quickly this time, huh?
You're always just manipulating people's weaknesses like this!
We'll protect everyone's hearts from the likes of you!
Go forth, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
They're the Precure?!
Those two?!
Marine!
That trick... is from the School of Myoudouin!
Big brother!
Th-This Desertrian is unbelievably strong!
I'm scared... I'm scared of the operation...
When we found out they could
operate, everyone was so happy.
I can't tell them how scared I am now!
Satsuki...
My little sister is trying to help me as best as she can.
I don't want her taking pity on me just
because I'm worried about the operation!
Big brother...
I don't want her to see me like this!
I don't... I don't!
Precures!
Marine!
Blossom!
I'm free!
I don't have to have that operation anymore!
You're doing great!
Forget about all that bad stuff and go wild!
No!
Hrm?
What is it now?!
My brother doesn't want this at all!
He would never enjoy hurting anyone!
Big brother!
Big brother, please come to your senses!
Go back to being your usual kind-hearted self!
Big... brother?
Potpourri!
Potpourri! Potpourri!
Why would you be so reckless?!
Because I feel the shame way as you, Ichuki...
Huh?
I want to protect them...
I want to protect the Precure...
I want to protect the Great Heart Tree...
I want to protect you, Ichuki!
And even if I can't,
I'll try as hard as I posshibly can...
because I want to protect you all!
Ichuki, you feel the same way, don't you?
Potpourri...
Hrm?
There's one, there's two...
And there's three...
Hey! You must be the third fairy!
How lucky! If I take you back to Professor Sabark, I'll be the hero of the day!
What's with that look?
Hand it over!
You've got guts for a powerless whelp, but
you should keep your nose where it belongs!
I won't let you have Potpourri!
I might be powerless,
but I'll still protect them!
Potpourri...
My big brother...
I'll protect everyone who's precious to me!
What'sh going on?!
That's...
The transformation item is reacting to Itsuki's heart!
Ichuki!
Let'sh protect everyone together!
Take the Shiny Perfume!
Shiny Perfume?
Let's go, Potpourri!
Let'sh do it!
Sheed of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
This is...
me?
Now, think of a name for yourshelf!
A name?
I...
I want...
Yeah! I'd love to be named...
for that glorious Sun!
Itsuki really was...
...a Precure, after all!
The third Precure is born!
A third?!
That golden Precure is just an eyesore!
Go get her!
Chaaaaaaaair!
She's strong...
Big brother,
I shall bring the light back into your heart.
And I pray I can be like the Sun,
so that I become the light that
watches over everyone's hearts!
My name is...
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
Let me introduce myself properly! I'm Cure Sunshine!
Nice to meet you!
She seems really dependable!
The three of us are as unbreakable as three arrows together! The Desert Apostles stand no chance!
What's wrong, Potpourri?!
The Great Heart Tree is in sherious danger!
That figure looks like...
Speak of the devil!
Dark Precure?!
HeartCatch Precure:
Crisis at the Great Heart Tree!
The Precure Take Off!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!