Faint-hearted traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
On a spring night, Virgo is spread out widely.
My favorite star, Spica, is this Alpha star.
If you stretch this line from the Big
Dipper, there's the North Star.
And if you pull the handle of the ladle,
there's the star of the cow
herder, Arcturus, then Spica!
This line is called the Great Arc of Spring.
During the cherry blossom season,
try looking for it in the southern sky!
Survival Training
It's not here...
That's weird... Where did it go?
What are you looking for, little one?
Well, you see... I promised
to lend Kei-chan a book,
but I seem to have lost
it somewhere around here...
Oh... that sounds pretty troublesome.
Ah, that's it!
I was wondering where it was,
but you had it all this time, Lion-san!
Th-That's not it!
That girl from last week was reading this book.
Kei-chan?
Not her... the other person.
You mean Marika-chan?
Yeah... her.
I see.
Marika-chan was reading this back then...
How is she doing?
Huh?
Is she doing all right?
W-What is it?
So Lion-san only looks skin-deep!
Well, I guess since Marika-chan is so pretty...
I-It's nothing like that!
I was just... a bit concerned, that's all...
Yes, yes...
Let's just leave it as that.
No, you've got it wrong!
Asumi-chan!
What are you doing? You'll be late!
Huh? It's this late already?
I'm coming now!
Okay.
I'm confiscating this!
It is my book after all, right?
Huh?
It's Marika-chan!
I wonder if she used it as a bookmark.
Now that I think of it, I've never seen
Marika-chan laugh like this.
Come on, Asumi-chan!
Yes!
Well, I'm going!
I'm sorry, Ringo-san!
You're so slow!
It couldn't be... right?
What do you mean?
I don't want to.
I definitely don't want to!
Promise you'll quit if something happens.
Fainting at school is out of the question!
I told you I don't want to!
I won't ever quit.
I'm saying this because I'm worried about you.
Not taking your medicine, and
on top of all this, fainting...
There is no way I could let you out in the open.
You're worried about me?
Of course.
Isn't it because you'll be the one in trouble
if something happens to me?
If you have no intention of listening to me
then I have my own ideas
on what to do about this!
If you try to pull strings behind my back,
I'll leave this house.
You'd better think of what would
happen if I were to do that.
Is that the way you should
be speaking to your father?!
The real Marika would never have
taken an attitude like that.
Stop saying it like that.
Why are you always like that, doing these...
Stop it!
You're the one who keeps
saying the same things!
I'm myself!
Why... don't you understand?!
Marika!
She's here.
Safe!
Good morning.
How unusual for you to be rushing in
right at the last minute, Asumi.
Ah, I was looking for something, so...
Here, Kei-chan!
The book I promised to show you.
Ah! Thank you!
I really wanted to read this.
Someone for whom it's even
more unusual just came.
She's usually the first one here, too.
Ladies probably oversleep
sometimes, don't you think?
Good morning, Marika-chan.
Good morning.
Umm...
This...
It was in a book in the storage room at the dorm.
You must have forgotten it
when you came over last time.
It's a nice photo!
Let's see. Let's see.
It's taken very well.
Don't you think Marika-chan's smile is cute?
Don't just look at it as you please!
U-Umm... I'm sorry, Marika-chan.
But, I really thought it was a nice photo...
What would you know?
Quit meddling in my business.
Hey!
We were the ones that saw it without asking.
Asumi hasn't done anything!
Marika-chan...
Everyone, listen up!
Everyone get changed into your gym
clothes and meet in the study room.
Huh? Was first period Physical Education?
No, maybe there was a change in schedule...
What?! We're going to have to run again?
You're against running that much?
N-Not at all... how absurd of you to say.
Sadly, it isn't a marathon.
You can be at ease.
What is this?
Be quiet!
This is Nakazawa-san who belongs to
the JAMSF Development Department.
Nice to meet you.
Well then, please go ahead...
This is a one-man capsule
for an emergency escape.
In case there is a problem with
the space station or shuttle,
this has been created to provide a refuge
in space for a short period of time.
Within the capsule, there are approximately
18 hours worth of oxygen,
and though meager, some food and water.
Also, there is an assortment of tools.
To take them out, press this area
like this, and the cover will open.
Are there any questions?
Umm...
Yes, go on.
There's a little something that
I've been wondering about...
How do we get back to the space shuttle
after we escape with that?
You cannot go back.
You will have to wait until help arrives.
No way!
Seriously?
That sucks...
If you are placed in a situation
where you must use this,
you will need a certain amount of resignation.
Because there's also the chance that
you could be left behind in space.
No... I don't even want to think about that!
And so, you will all go into
the capsule to try it out.
It may be tough for those of you who
are slightly claustrophobic, but...
this is another part of your training.
Damn it, a test of endurance, huh?
The maximum length is 18 hours.
It'll end sometime before the
oxygen runs out, don't you think?
Hmpf, you sure are calm about this.
Understand, everyone?
Be sure you don't come out until the blue
lamp inside the capsule turns on.
Okay, okay... I understand...
I just have to do it, right?
Ah, wait, wait!
Everyone, before you go in, put this on.
Until the training ends,
absolutely do not drop this
or lose this.
Damn it...
Understand?
Hmm...
What is this?
If we lose it, will it really
be that much of a problem?
Lose it?
Inside this small capsule?
This might be...
It looks like it's not going to be claustrophobic
at all for you, huh, Kamogawa?
Huh?
Now everyone close your hatch!
Don't forget to engage the lock!
See you later, Asumi...
Yeah.
Marika-chan...
It's pitch black...
I don't know what's where with this darkness...
Status Display Light
Oh, it's on.
They said something about
the blue lamp turning on,
but I wonder how long I have to wait...
What is this? Geez!
We're being moved elsewhere?
Ow!
It seems to have been shaking for a while,
but is that the kind of
training it's supposed to be?
Ow...
The shaking stopped.
I feel nauseous...
I wonder how long it's been...
The blue lamp still hasn't turned on, either...
I'm falling?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Status Display Light
The blue lamp!
It's over at last!
Release the lock...
It's so bright...
Huh?
Why am I in a place like this?
Kei-chan!
Marika-chan!
Everyone!
No one's here...
I'm... all alone.
Could this be...?
"Survival Training Contents."
"Supposing that during lift-off, or when returning from
space, the rocket has made an emergency landing,"
"assemble within five days at location A
shown on the attached map."
This is the real training?
I see.
I guess they wouldn't make just staying
in the capsule the end of it.
If that's the case, why didn't
they tell us in the first place?!
Geez!
Ow...
They're checking our position using the signals
coming out from this device, aren't they?
You can't call this just training.
From here on in, everything will probably become
a criterion for selecting astronauts...
Promise you'll quit if something happens.
Fainting at school is out of the question!
I must reach the goal before anyone else!
I have to reach the goal...
There's no name plate, is there?
What's the use in checking?
What am I trying to check anyway?
What's left in the capsule is
a backpack, sleeping bag, vinyl sheet,
as well as...
a knife, pen-light, rope, toothpaste...
So there's no compass...
It looks as though the food and
water won't even last five days...
There are really only the minimum amount
of necessary things in here.
I have to hurry and pinpoint where I am,
or I won't be able to move forward.
But with this food situation, it would
be best not to move around so much.
I'll move in the morning tomorrow...
And for now, I'd better set up a
tent before the sun goes down.
If I could see the stars more clearly,
I'd be able to figure out my bearings...
I wonder if I've just gotten used to life in Tokyo...
It's so quiet that I can't sleep.
I wonder how everyone is doing...
When I'm like this, it reminds me of the day
I chased Lion-san deep into the forest...
That time, it was quiet and
completely dark just like this...
I don't know why, but I couldn't stop my tears...
I felt so lonely...
Scared, sad and all alone,
but I wanted to see him.
I just really wanted to see him...
While I was mulling things over,
it's already become morning.
I spent just one summer with her.
And I vaguely remembered her face too...
Even her name...
Now that I think about it,
what was her name anyway?
Didn't I ask her?
Well, even if their faces are alike, their
ages are just too different, right?
It's probably just me thinking too much.
Orion 2
Lion-san
Marika
Time to eat.
All done!
I have to brush my teeth after eating!
I'm fine.
I can do my best until I meet up
with everyone again.
Was that my imagination?
I thought I heard someone's voice...
Orion 2
Lion-san
Marika
Marika...
Marika?
To Space
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
Preview
One person is my classmate, Marika-chan.
The other is the Marika-chan that
Lion-san met when he was a child.
Ukita Marika
With the times so far apart,
what's their relationship?
Without knowing what that is,
we wander through the forest.
But during that time, Marika-chan
meets someone unexpected.
Next time on Twin Spica:
Marika and Marika.
Marika and Marika
End