Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression...asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Don't you think so?
Doesn't it stink?
It sure does.
Golden Week is almost over.
Have you two finished your homework?
Actually, I haven't yet...
For some reason, I always tend to play around when I have a long break.
It's so troublesome.
Don't you think so, onee-chan?
Sorry, but I finished most of mine.
Even though we both played around together?
Effort
&
Results
Thanks for the meal.
About this part...
How should I know something that you don't even know, Kagami?
You are a college student, right?
Can you go wake up Tsukasa already?
I don't wanna.
I know she's not going to wake up anyway.
Wake up!
I wonder what's keeping dad?
He went to the groundbreaking ceremony this morning.
What time is it right now?
I'm home.
It's past noon already.
Hey, welcome home.
Good morning.
It's already noon.
How can you possibly sleep so much?
Ehehe.
Did you watch the last episode of 'Koi no Apron' last night?
Nope.
I fell asleep halfway through.
Eh? You were asleep?
It was an amazing finish!
In the final scene, the guy with the red sink on his head was like...
Kagami?
Hm?
You have a phone call from Miyuki-chan.
Okay.
Would you like to have a study group together?
So we can check our answers with each other and stuff.
Oh! That's a great idea!
Let's go it!
Kagami.
You have a phone call from Konata-chan.
Umm... I was thinking about a study group to clean up all my homework.
Wait a sec!
Don't you mean you want to come over just to copy my homework!?
So, can I copy your homework?
You're so straightforward.
I really don't mind you copying my homework...
But if you don't study up...
You're gonna get really bad grades on the exams when we get back from break.
You're right... it's for our own good.
I'm good at cramming, so don't worry.
Can I see your homework now?
Shouldn't you be a little more stressed?
Sorry to intrude.
Welcome!
Oh, is Izumi-san here to study too?
No, she's just here to copy my homework.
Yup...
Despite that, you haven't done any homework yet.
What exactly have you been doing this whole break?
Umm...
First Day
23 pages of algebra.
20 pages of world history.
30 pages of English.
I've finally cleared this level.
I have five days of break.
So if I study 5... no 4 hours every day...
There we go.
1.5 pages per hour of math.
Second Day
Hmmm... this requires a lot
more experience than I thought.
Oh no! I haven't
studied at all today!
One more quest and I'll level up.
Let's see... I still have
three days left, so...
If I study 6 hours ever day...
We've been working together for 12 years now.
Third Day
Well, I guess it's almost time... yeah.
All I ask is for my senpai at work to remember my name...
Two more days...
I just have to really try hard for two days.
Fourth Day
Golden Week is almost over.
Have you two finished your homework?
Ah!
Ummm... I was thinking about a study group to clean up all my homework.
I tried to follow my plan, but...
It completely fell apart.
I guess it was futile.
You shouldn't be talking!
I guess she was trying hard by herself.
Even though she may not seem like the type, she can be pretty studious when need be.
But they're all wrong... I can't look at this.
Horrible... this is just too horrible.
Ussu!
I hope you guys enjoyed your holiday.
Then again, you kids did have quite a bit of homework.
Not to mention midterms are right around the corner.
So you probably didn't have much time to fool around.
It didn't feel like a break at all.
Well, I pity you kids, but I had a lot of run on this break, without a care in the world.
Sensei...
Oh?
I'm right with you on that!
Ugh!
Aren't these things designed so it's impossible to catch them?
It depends on the machine.
There are some that are designed that way.
Hmm...
Right?
That's why I never feel like wasting money on it.
Ah!
Amazing!
Well, I had my eye on this one.
Heh?
Maybe with this one, even if I tried, I could get it...
Really easily...
Is that what you're thinking?
Eh!?
I wasn't... not even close!
Smirk
But, I guess I'll give it a shot.
Onee-chan, do your best!
Smirk
Bah... I thought I had that one.
How unfortunate.
H-huh?
No way!
Why?
A wise person once said...
The UFO catcher is like a piggy bank.
That person was pretty good.
Konata
Tsukasa
Oh no!
Ahh!
Reporting the results!
I did so bad.
You are Taiko first-dan!
Kona-chan, you must have a really good sense of rhythm.
You are Taiko fifth-dan!
Well, I don't think rhythm has much to do with it.
I've leveled up my gaming skills, but surprisingly they're pretty useless in daily life.
Looking at you, that's really easy to see.
Kona-chan, you're so strong.
I guess...
How much time has she invested in this?
Izumi?
Hmm?
Is Izumi absent today?
Kuroi-sensei... a phone call from Izumi-san.
Yes?
I'm on the phone now.
Um... sensei, I'm really sorry.
But I would like to call in sick today.
Whoa Izumi... how rare.
Did you catch a cold?
W-well, I have a really bad case of May-sickness.
Eh?
I feel really tired.
Get your butt over here right now!
Hey!
Let's go home.
Hm?
Why's your bag so full?
Tests start tomorrow, so I have to bring everything home tonight and start cramming.
You mean you've been procrastinating all this time?
Geez...
Bringing your books home the night before a test...
There's no way you're gonna make it in time.
Um.
Well, I've always done it this way in the past.
You seem pretty confident.
I'd like to see how high you can actually score.
First Semester
Midterms
Modern Literature
Mathematics
English
All right!
I'm gonna return your tests from last week!
About so-so.
How'd you do?
I wouldn't ask if I were you.
But I did try my best...
Let's see how our crammer did.
Not bad. All thanks to you.
I won't accept this!!
I'm so tired.
I don't feel like doing anything at all.
C'mon, let's go home.
Even after all that, you still hang around to stop by some shops.
Ah!
Comp-Matsuri. Quo-card all service.
I must collect all of then.
All right... time to get a part-time job.
You're so easy to understand.
Geez... I've never heard of anyone trying to take the day off because of May-sickness.
I kind of understand how you feel.
Well, it's serious enough to have the word "sickness" in it, so isn't that pretty bad?
Are you being serious?
Yeah.
Speaking of which, what exactly is May-sickness again?
Miyuki...
Please enlighten them.
Ummm...
It usually occurs right after you achieve a big goal, such as making it into a new school or company.
Or when new interpersonal relationships around April don't go as you expect...
And you can't keep up with the image of your "new life."
It's the listlessness or lack of energy that comes from such things.
So, I'm not sure if you would consider 'just being tired' as a case of May-sickness.
First of all, high school juniors like ourselves don't even fit that description.
Well, every year when spring rolls around, I try my best to stay on top of things.
Is that so?
But, disregarding Konata, I think it's easy to get tired this season.
Even when I go home, I just don't feel like doing my homework.
Oh, I get that feeling too.
Ahhh!?
I'm so tired, I'm not even going to follow up on that one.
Sigh...
What's the matter, Yuki-chan?
Why are you sighing like that?
Like with contact lenses...
It's rather embarrassing at this age, but...
I don't like dentists, so I've been avoiding them.
However, lately I think my cavity's been getting worse.
Enough to hurt when I'm drinking water.
But...
Isn't that normal?
I'm scared of them too.
If it's become this bad, why did you wait until now to go the dentist?
It's really weird, but when my tooth starts to ache and even though I know that it's painful...
You just don't like the thought of going to the dentist, right?
Even when it just begins to ache, as long as I can withstand the pain...
I choose to not go to the dentist.
Are dentists that scary?
I've never been to one, so I don't know.
You've never gone?
I'm so jealous.
There's that scent that you only smell at the dentist's office.
And the tense atmosphere that comes from waiting for your turn.
And and... the sound of spinning drills above all.
Change Getter!
It's so scary.
But, don't you think guys would like the dentist?
Why?
You know how they say the drill is ever man's ultimate fantasy?
Dinosaur Empire!
I hear they love fights between two drill-wielding robots.
But, I don't think they'd like having their teeth drilled away.
I've always thought about it but...
Don't you think the receptionists and hygienists that work in dental offices are really pretty?
Now that you mention it...
I wonder why that is.
Perhaps it's the standards of those hiring them.
Pretty assistants and drills, huh...
So I guess it is kind of male-oriented.
Then, what would be a female-oriented dentist?
First, we have to get rid of this so-called 'smell.'
And their chair has to be a soft, reclining massage chair.
Don't forget the aromatherapy.
Or having them massage your feet as they treat your teeth.
That's really nice!
How about having the patients play games to forget about the pain?
It might be a little hard to play games...
But, it's a good idea to do something to keep your mind off the pain.
Having them play your favorite music on headphones?
I like that.
That sounds nice.
Yep!
But...
I'm still scared of the dentist.
I agree.
No Wai!
What's the matter?
Well, one of my favorite mangas is being adapted into an anime.
But the voice cast is completely different from the drama CD's.
I see...
Though I'm not too sure about what you're talking.
Maybe God's invisible hand is in motion again...
Is it politics?
Or money perhaps?
I don't buy drama CD's, so...
As long as the voices suit the characters from the manga, I'll be happy.
That's not enough, Kagami!
To a person who's used to listening to drama CD's...
There's just this inexplicable awkwardness when watching the anime.
And it takes time for that to go away.
I see...
But, there's also a flipside to this.
Eh? What's that?
With drama CD's and the anime, you can enjoy two different worlds with two different voice casts.
One grain of rice, but twice as delicious.
You're such an otaku customer.
Now, one of us is going to eat the fried chicken that Miyuki-san left behind.
So let's decided with a staring game.
Ugh... how puerile!
A staring game.
That sounds like fun.
Kagami might try to kick me under the table though.
Did you say something?
Here we go.
Niramekko shimasho Appu pu! And go!
That's too good.
It's almost dangerous.
Amazing.
That face isn't human!
I think you two are overreacting just a little bit.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The bathroom was pretty crowded.
What happened?
Hey, show that face to Miyuki too.
I don't wanna.
Miyuki, it was amazing.
I've never seen this face before.
Fine...
It's funny no matter how many times I look at it.
That face might come in handy to get on the good side of others.
Yeah, Konata!
You should apply to college with that.
I'm sure you'd pass.
That's not making me happy.
I saw a survey on TV about the number of books Japanese people read on average.
And they said, 'No manga please, just real books.'
Well, manga are...
How about light novels?
Huh?
I wonder...
I guess light novels are okay.
How about a picture book?
Um!?
Uh...
Well, it does have the word 'book' in it, but...
It's fantasy, but I betcha people would consider Harry Potter a book.
So I guess what I'm trying to ask is, 'What is a real book?'
Hmm...
On TV, they tried to wrap up the show saying today's youth don't read and write enough in their daily life.
But nowadays, I think kids post on blogs or surf the web and actually read more.
I guess I kind of understand how you feel.
Yo!
Let's go home, girls.
Gimme a sec.
Oh, I'm sorry, but I can't go home with you guys tonight.
Eh?
You actually have something to do?
How rare.
Yeah.
I started a part time job.
I see...
Whoa, I never thought she'd actually get a part time job.
Does Comp-Matsuri mean that much to her?
Still, I was pretty surprised with Konata.
Yeah, she actually started a part time job.
I thought she was joking all along.
Yeah, that's true too, but...
Hm?
I'm surprised someone actually hired her.
T-that's going a little too far.
I can't even picture her doing manual labor.
That, I agree with.
I wonder at where she's working.
Maybe a bookstore?
She really likes manga and stuff.
Excuse me, can I buy this?
Wait a bit.
My hands are tied up right now.
Eh?
Get!
I hope she doesn't get fired.
How about a convenience store then?
Excuse me, can I get this?
Fouwar hundreeed an' ninetee-ate yen desu~
Exact change.
Tank-yuu vry much.
I can't picture that either.
How about fast food?
Fresh Salad
Ice Cream Cone
Vanilla
Chocolate
Strawberry
Here is my smile... would you like anything else?
I don't see that happening.
For the same reason, I doubt she works at a family restaurant either.
Welcome.
I really wonder what she's doing.
Huh...
Working at a toll booth?
Nah.
A video rental shop?
I wonder...
A bar!
No, that's not it.
Pizza delivery?
She doesn't have a license.
A cashier at the supermarket?
Impossible.
A tutor.
I doubt that.
A coal mine.
Eh?
What else...
Let's just ask her tomorrow.
Hey, Konata, where are you working?
Yeah, tell us.
Hm?
Oh.
Just a cosplay café.
Uwa~
It's too perfect for her.
But is that legal?
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
Kogami Akira here.
This is our second Lucky Channel!
Akira's so excited about it!
And next to me is Akira's assistant and a handsome young man, Shiraishi Minoru-san!
Go ahead!
Wa Wa Wa Wa...
I am Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
I'm still a rookie, so if all of you could just remember my name that would be awesome.
Yes...
*clap clap clap*
Now, this program's just started but we're already overwhelmed with the questions from our viewers.
Akira's sooo happy!
*Thank you!*
It really is amazing.
I think this really shows your popularity.
H-huh?
I watched today's episode and...
Yes?
You were in it.
Eh?
In the episode!
You were in it, weren't you?
O-oh, yes... I was allowed to make a brief appearance.
Hmm...
Well, not that I care.
What was that?
What scene were you in again?
If I remember correctly...
Part A cut 45.
The classroom scene after break.
Oh oh oh... I remember now.
You didn't leave a strong impression at all, so I totally forgot about it.
Well, I only had one line this time.
What's this?
Now you're not content either?
T-that's not at all what I meant.
I wonder... having our rookies sayin' stuff like this.
When I first debuted...
Debuted...
How old were you again?
Three.
Back then, I was so happy just to get a line.
You know, Lines aren't all about how many you get.
Yes.
This time around I was surrounded by so many senpai, I was so nervous.
Thank you very much for your instruction!
Yeah, you were pretty stiff out there.
Eh?
You were so stiff that it was pretty obvious you were an amateur.
You know...
That scene in the actual episode was so bad...
Why don't you give it another shot right here?
Eh? R-right here?
You might be in more episodes in the future, right?
I-I suppose.
Then, you better practice!
I'm tellin' you, I'll help you out dammit!
O-okay I understand...
P-please go easy on me.
Gimme the script.
What cut was it again?
Cut 45.
Oh, this one.
Well, I'll play Kuroi-sensei's part.
Please.
Ready and...
Action!
Ussu.
I hope you guys enjoyed your holiday.
Then again, you kids did have a q-q-qui...
That's "quite."
...quite a bit of homework.
Not to mention midterms are right around the corner.
So you probably didn't have much time to fool around.
It didn't feel like a break at all.
What was that?
Eh?
Terrible.
Your lines aren't reaching me.
Reaching?
HERE!
I'm not feelin' it down here.
Uh...
I'm sorry...
Even monkeys can read their lines.
Eh?
I-I don't think monkeys could...
What was that!?
Ah!
Unnyu~
Ahh!
It's time to say goodbye again!
Time just flies when you're having fun, doesn't it?
So, if you have some questions, opinions, or comments you would like to make about the show...
Just send them to Akira, *puriizu*!
W-we'll see you again next time.
See you soon!
So how are the regulars?
W-what do you mean?
You know... like maybe someone's about to get kicked or something.
Don't those guys really hate each other's guts behind that cute facade?
I-I don't think that's true...
Then why the hell are you always humbling your-
Kona-chan, you're amazing.
That was so passionate.
W-wait a sec, Konata...
Do you mean you put two sings like these in already?
Yeah, I put some anime in too... not just special effects.
That's not what I meant!
Can't you sing a song that we all know?
Eh?
Isn't it up to me what I want to sing?
Umm, the remote...
Here you go, Tsukasa.
If you don't put something in quick, we'll have to listen to her anime theme medley.
I don't mind that.
I'm having fun like this.
N-not you too, Miyuki!
Oh, sorry about last time.
I'll stand and sing this time.
What do you have up your sleeve this time?
If you don't stand and sing, it's hard to get the sound coming from your stomach.
You mean you're gonna sing even louder than last time?
Oh!
It's actual footage from the series!
Whoa... amazing!
This looks like it was drawn before we were even born.
Zaraado Iraado Garaado
「ザラーど　イラード　ガラード」
Zaraado! Iraado! Garaado!
Kagayake Jyankeru (oo o oo)
輝けジャンケル（オーオオー）
Shine Jyankeru! (ooh ooh ooh)
Sora takaku (o oo)
空高く　（オオー）
High in the sky. (ooh ooh)
Waza to chikara to kokoro ga kayou
技と　力と　心がかよう
Techniques and strength. My heart wavering.
I've brought your drinks.
Thank you.
Zabitan (eei) Ibiru (eei)
ザビタン（エエイ）　イビル（エエイ）
Zabitan. Ibiru.
Oolong tea?
Gabura (oo o o o oo)
ガブラ（オーオオオオー）
Gabura
Oh, that's me.
Ice Lemon Tea?
Unare Jyankeru
うなれ　ジャンケル
Roar Jyankeru.
Oh, me.
Orange juice?
Akumaizaa THREE
アクマイザー　スリー
Aquamizer III
Ah, me.
Ginger ale.
Yuku michi hitotsu oo tada hitotsu
ゆくみちひとつ　オー　ただひとつ
There's one path to travel. One and only one.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just leave it right here.
Preview
Now, for next week's Lucky Star...
Kagami here.
When you buy a drink from the vending machine with 200 yen...
And your change is a 50-yen coin with some 10-yen pieces...
You get that "I win!" feeling.
On the other hand, when you try to buy a 150-yen ticket to board the train...
And you put a 100-yen coin in, thinking you have five 10-yen coins...
But you actually only had four, so left with no other option, you put that second 100-yen coin in...
And your change comes back as nine 10-yen coins...
You really feel a sense of utter defeat when that happens.
「All Kinds of People」
Next Week: Various People
Look forward to it.