ToraDora
Translation by Anisa
There's something that
not a single person in this world has seen.
This is a total lie.
This...
Why is there mold here!?
I just cleaned it the other day!
It's gentle, and very sweet.
Rag, rag...
Probably, if they ever had the chance to see it, anyone would want it.
That's why
the world hid it.
So that you couldn't get it easily.
Dammit! It won't come off!
But if I used the Takasu Rod...
But someday, someone will find it.
That one person who should have it will be able to find it.
And that is how we began.
Eco, eco, eco, ecology.
Inko-chan!
Are you still asleep?
It's morning.
I've caught you.
Ryu-chan, you're so mean.
I told you last night, I have school starting today.
Opening day ceremony?
Congratulations on moving up!
Is that what a mother's supposed to say to her son on his first day of school?
Hey, this room's so dark! Open the curtains.
They're open.
That's a big apartment building...
What kind of people live there?
Since that was built, it's blocked out all the sunlight.
The laundry doesn't dry anymore and each and every day, mold, mold, mold-
That cunning look in your eyes...
Ryu-chan, you look more and more like your papa.
Like your papa.
Don't compare me to that!
So cool! You're even more exactly like your papa!
Eh?
Ryu-chan, you're going already?
Where's my food?
Where it always is!
That...
That's the only thing I really didn't want to hear.
Because of this look that you like so much...
I... I...
Hey, wait up!
It's T-Takasu-kun!
What the hell are you doing?
Eh, wha, why-
I didn't do it on purpose!
Please forgive us!
This is all we have!
Really!
We wouldn't mess around about this!
It's okay...
We're sorry!
Scary!
He's got the eyes of a killer!
I...
Again?
You find a lot of wallets.
Well...
I hope we're in the same class!
Right?
I found it!
Yay, we're in the same class.
Dammit... again...
Hey.
We're in the same class again, Takasu.
Kitamura.
With this, we will end this year's opening ceremony.
Everyone should go to their classrooms and prepare for homeroom.
A new class.
I have to start by clearing up everyone's misunderstandings.
It's okay!
At least it's not everyone!
I get it.
Yeah. Thanks.
That's right.
There are people who get me.
And, in this class...
Hey, Kitamura-kun.
We're in the same class this year.
Kushieda, you're in C Class too?
You're Takasu-kun, right?
Do you remember me?
We always see each other around Kitamura-kun.
You're... Kushieda Minori, right?
Ah, you got it!
You remembered my whole name!
I'm happy!
Now! Refreshingly, brightly, let's enjoy life together!
Yeah.
Y-Yeah...
And then, that...
What's wrong, Takasu?
N-Nothing,
I just gotta go to the bathroom.
Gotcha. Then I'll go ahead.
Battle for the top spot!?
Ryuji vs. Aisaka Taiga, the best match is suddenly beginning!
The top place is going to be chosen now!?
What?
Her body's so small.
She's like a doll.
But, somehow...
I feel like if I let my guard down, she'll take advantage and devour me...
But what's this?
It's true!
Yankee Takasu-kun and Tenori Taiga!
TL Note- "Yankee" refers to a kind of gang. "Tenori" means "palm-sized".
Idiot!
Tenori... Taiga?
That makes sense!
Tenori Ta-
That's a perfect name.
Okay, that's all for today.
If you haven't filled out your career counseling survey, come to the teacher's room afterwards.
I-Is that alright, Takasu-kun?
Y-Yes.
Are you okay, Taiga?
You came in so late, too.
I went to see a doctor.
He said something about house dust...
A modern day cold.
That's pretty rough.
Tenori Taiga...
She's friends with Kushieda Minori.
I'm the one having a rough time.
Are you alright?
Oh, I guess.
But, look.
That was amazing! Aisaka-san and Takasu-kun.
That was one heck of a punch.
But they say Takasu just looks scary, he's not a yankee.
Really?
It looks like that misunderstanding is clearing up quickly.
Taiga?
What's wrong?
No-Nothing.
T-Takasu-kun, you aren't sure about what you want to do in the future?
B-But, you still have to turn in the career counseling survey. Everyone else has turned it in.
I'm sorry. I for-
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You don't want to be told that your path is wrong by an unmarried, going on 30, still wandering everywhere kind of woman.
I just don't know my place.
It's so late.
The limited time sale is going to end-
A-Are you okay?
Um...
B-Bag, bag.
I-I'll just leave her alone for now.
Y-You! W-What are you doing!?
What do you mean, what?
I just came back for my bag.
That was your bag? Your seat is the one next...
Y-You mean...
L-L-Let go!
Why my bag?
H-Hey, that's enough!
Hey!
Aisaka...
H-Hey!
Idiot!
She's crazy.
Crazy...
Papa is in heaven.
He was so cool!
He always hid a magazine under his shirt in case he ever got stabbed.
Groovy!
Just because I look like you,
I'm always in trouble.
If I didn't have this kind of face, no one would be scared of me, Tenori Taiga wouldn't bother me...
I would have had more confidence in myself.
And then...
The career counseling survey.
What's this?
To Kitamura Yusaka-sama.
Aisaka... Taiga.
I get it.
You put this in by mistake.
I haven't looked, so I have no idea what's inside.
Anyway, I'm returning it.
C-Crap...
I have to stick it back on.
She might be...
...an incredible klutz?
I'm going to sleep.
Huh? Yasuko?
She wouldn't be home yet.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Good going, Mirano-chan!
Alright, I'm going to drink some more!
He~y.
The window...
Ouch!
W-What the hell?
Huh? This size...
I've seen it somewhere...
Aisaka?
Use a tissue!
What?
Wha...
What...
are...
you...
doing?
Forget it!
Forget?
Ah, that let-
Gulp.
Since you've seen it, I can't keep living. I have to die!
Then don't try to kill me!
I don't want to die, so I have to kill you!
Or, forget everything!
I can't!
That's fine.
It's unheard of to die by a full force blow from a wooden sword, so your memories will certainly be blasted away.
Don't blast them!
Okay, listen! That letter...
Be quiet...
Be quiet, be quiet!
You saw it, right!? You read it, right!?
T-That's what I'm trying...
I won't listen...
So, that lo-lov-love letter, just forget about it!
It was empty!
Empty?
That's right.
There wasn't anything to read.
You're pretty lucky you didn't give it to Kitamura.
Otherwise, you would have embarassed yourself to him.
H-Hey.
How hungry are you?
I got tired of the convenience store.
Convenience store?
Why? Don't your parents feed-
Everyone has their own home life...
Here.
If you had just given up your bag back then, it wouldn't have come to this.
What are you going to do about it!?
There's still some left.
You're like a guy who was born to put the smell of garlic on fried rice oil.
Now, look here.
What's so embarrassing about a love letter?
Listen up! There's nothing embarrasing about something like that.
Just wait.
Look!
What's this?
Do you know what that is?
I bet you don't.
That's a list of songs I'd play if I were going to have a concert for the girl I like.
The poems I wrote for her.
MDs I'd play if we were out for a drive.
Of course, I don't have a driver's license.
I have everything for every kind of typical date.
How about it? It's pretty sick, isn't it?
I don't have the courage to tell her how I feel, so I can only sit here and fantasize about what it'd be like.
Of course, it's pathetic,
but even so, I don't think it's shameful!
You should have more confidence!
You didn't just stop at fantasy, you tried to do something about it.
Think positive!
Refreshingly, brightly...
"To give to Kushieda Minori."
Yeah! Just like Kushieda Minori-
You and Minori?
You're getting ahead of yourself.
She's way out of your league.
Be quiet!
Look who's talking!
What? I told you to forget!
Be quiet! Sabu, sabuibo.
I'm sorry, Inko-chan. Did we wake you up?
What's that!? It's disgusting!
What!? How dare you talk like that about my important family...
Good job, Inko-chan!
Introduce yourself to our guest.
Today's the day for you to finally say your own name!
W-Well... Today, Inko-chan isn't feeling well...
It's already this late?
Anyway, we're in the same tough spot.
I won't tell anyone about the letter. So please leave!
No.
Why not!?
Anyway, you already ate, so please go home!
Please go home. My mother's going to come home.
There's no way!
I can't trust you.
And...
Well, what do you think about love letters?
They're not kinda old fashioned, are they?
Even if you start acting fidgety now...!
I'll help you out with all your love problems,
but it's already late, so tomorrow, okay?
Really? You'll help me out?
I will, I will, I will, I'll do anything!
Anything, like a dog?
Anything, for me?
I will. I swear.
So, let's just call it a night.
Please, please?
How did she get in through the window?
Seeya.
I'll walk you home.
It's fine. It's near. And I have my wooden sword.
No, that's dangerous.
Hey, that hole...
Well, it's small enough to cover up with some paper or something.
Here.
Use it.
If it costs money, I'll pay you back later.
Seeya, Ryuji.
Y-Yeah...
Just now, did she talk down to me?
Yes, Taka-
Hurry up and come!
Yes?
You hung up!
Hurry up and come where?
Veranda? Why?
Why?
You said you'd do anything for me like a dog!
J-Just wait a minute.
Yesterday that was about helping you out with Kitamura-
You understand what will happen to you if you refuse, don't you?
I can make you understand...
No...
That's...
Just wait ten minutes!
The rice will be done in ten minutes.
Three?
You wanna eat too?
Wow.
E-Excuse me?
Huh?
It's open.
What's this smell?
Aisaka-san? I'm coming in.
There's an awful smell.
Aisaka!
For my sake, if only for my sake,
please let me clean up the kitchen properly!
What?
She's gone back to sleep.
It looks like someone made her.
Sleeping Aisaka really looked like a doll.
And this place, because it felt like no one lived here,
was like a child's play set.
But,
for a doll's house, the size was amazing.
About 15 minutes.
Alright!
What is... this?
Yo.
I'm not done, but it's gotten a lot cleaner, right?
It was amazing.
The water stuck up in the sink stunk, and the drain was a scene from hell, with all that raw garbage and mold.
And your place was full of dust.
Trespassing.
And pushy cleaning.
You're not marking this place, you dog!
Dog?
That would be rude to dogs.
Even if you're both dogs, you're a mongrel.
What an ungrateful brat! When I tried to...
Hey, what about "thanks for the food"?
God of Rice and the farmers, thank you for the food!
Why you...
Hey, your nose has stopped dripping.
That's probably because you cleaned the house.
What'd you say?
Be quiet!
A loose truce.
Emerging misunderstandings.
The power of genes.
Taiga, you really are deplorable, aren't you?
Be quiet and rot...