Nothing can stop us now that we
have the HeartCatch Mirage, huh?!
Marine!
That was close.
Jeez.
What other powers does the HeartCatch Mirage have?
It can warp you to the Great Heart Tree, or even let you see the Flowers of people's Hearts.
Really?
It's thanks to Yuri that we managed to obtain it, right?
Yeah!
Yuri, thank you so much!
I didn't...
I didn't really do anything to help.
You passed the trial with your strong bonds of friendship.
Rather than fighting alone like I did.
Yuri...
Grandma, can't we use the Mirage to turn Yuri back into a Precure?!
Well, that's...
...not even remotely possible!
Yuri...
Use the Mirage.
Look at the Flower of my Heart!
Do you understand now?
I can no longer be a Precure!
Cologne...
I'm so sorry.
Moonlight.
Please don't cry, Moonlight.
I'll be able to see you again soon.
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Cure Moonlight
is Finally Revived!
Yuri became a Precure
shortly after her father went missing.
"Missing"?
He was a botanical scientist who was searching for the Great Heart Tree.
His last known whereabouts were somewhere in France.
But then...
After Yuri was chosen by the Great Heart Tree, her fairy Cologne was there to encourage her.
With his help, she overcame her sadness over her father's disappearance,
and fought the Desert Apostles as Cure Moonlight.
Cologne was our mentor, and he was very kind!
That's right!
If Cologne... If Cologne hadn't died, then
Moonlight wouldn't have lost to Dark Precure!
Moonlight!
It's Professor Sabark!
Don't worry. I can handle them on my own!
Watch out!
C-Cologne!
Cologne!
Thank goodness you're safe.
Goodbye, Moonlight.
N-No...
Cologne!
Cologne sacrificed himself to save Moonlight.
Erika?!
Where are you going?!
To find Yuri!
She needs cheering up!
I just feel so sorry for her!
Erika.
Let's go!
Yuri!
Wh-What's the matter?
Don't hold back!
You can cry on my shoulder all you want!
Huh?!
Yuri.
We heard what happened to Cologne.
All about your tragic past.
We just... We want to make the Flower of your Heart bloom again, Yuri!
Like it used to!
Please let us help give your heart strength again!
You three...
really don't give up, do you?
Tsubomi! Erika!
Itsuki!
Good morning!
Morning!
Truth be told, I couldn't resist designing an outfit for Yuri to wear at the school festival, so...
You did too?!
Wait, "too"?
Ta-da! We drew some too!
Whoa!
I want Yuri to wear something beautiful and get some energy back again!
Looks like we all felt the same way, huh?
Yup!
All right then, show us your designs, Itsuki!
Sure!
Lord Coupe seems kinda tired.
Well, it must've been exhausting fighting them.
This light!
It is! It's just the same as when Potpourri was born!
Chypre, bring me the HeartCatch Mirage!
Okay!
You drew these for me?
Yes.
We'd like you to wear them at our fashion show.
We want you to find a new you, Yuri!
A new me?
It'll change you!
Fashion has magic power that'll make your heart shine again!
And if your heart shines again,
I know it'd make Cologne happy too!
You really think so?
Tsubomi!
Erika!
Ichuki!
Potpourri!
There, there.
Tsubomi, your grandma says you need to bring Yuri to see her as soon as possible!
What?
Speak, Dark Precure.
Thank you, Professor Sabark.
Look.
Cure Moonlight is...
No.
Something very strange is happening to Tsukikage Yuri!
Grandma!
Good work.
Yuri, come here.
The HeartCatch Mirage enables you to see the Great Heart Tree, no matter where it might be.
Cologne!
Huh?!
I think it's thanks to the Heart Pot.
Because Tsubomi and the others collected so many Heart Seeds, a miracle has happened!
Yuri.
Go to the Great Heart Tree.
You'll only get one chance.
Go and say the things you wanted to say to Cologne.
Just press the blue button,
and the HeartCatch Mirage will
take you to the Great Heart Tree.
To where Cologne is waiting for you.
What is it?
It's Dark Precure!
Yuri!
Yuri, go and see Cologne!
Leave this to us!
That's right!
What?!
Let's go!
Right!
Seeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Where is Tsukikage Yuri?
You're out of luck! She's not here anymore!
Hmph. In that case...
I'll stick around until I beat the answer out of you!
Cologne.
Cologne?!
Cologne! You're there, aren't you?!
Cologne!
Moonlight.
Hi there.
Cologne...
I'm sorry.
My body's long gone, I'm afraid.
It's because of all the Heart Seeds that Blossom and the others gathered that I'm here at all.
I'm sorry.
You died to save me.
I've always been watching over you, you know.
Ever since we first met.
You always overdid it, trying to do everything yourself.
Moonlight!
Don't you want us to find allies?!
Cure Flower defeated Dune on her own, didn't she?
But things are different now!
We have Professor Sabark and Dark Precure to deal with!
I'll be fine.
I have no intention of losing!
I was such a fool.
I thought I could do everything on my own.
I was so overconfident in my abilities!
Moonlight!
That's not true.
You risked your life to protect the Flowers in everyone's Hearts.
You knew the burden of being a Precure better than anyone.
That's why you took it all upon
yourself and decided to fight alone.
You didn't want anyone else to get hurt.
You thought you should suffer the pain on your own.
It was because you're kind.
I know that better than anyone.
Cologne...
You need to accept that, Moonlight.
You have to accept your kindness, and how you care for your friends.
Your new friends have taught you the importance of friendship, and to always be grateful for it, haven't they?
That's all you need if you want to fight the Desert Apostles again.
I can't!
Just look.
That is but a reflection of your heart.
Huh?
When you lost me, and were defeated by Dark Precure,
that's the shape your damaged heart took.
But if you truly wish to fight alongside them...
If you truly wish to protect this world,
then you can become Cure Moonlight again!
So make a wish to the Great Heart Tree.
That you wish to become a Precure again!
You really should just tell me where Tsukikage Yuri is.
Yuri has always been there to protect us!
Now it's our turn...
...to protect her!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Precure Shining Fortissimo!
Precure Dark Power Fortissimo!
Is this supposed to be the power of teamwork?!
If this goes on, they'll...
Please, Great Heart Tree!
Please make me a Precure again!
Tsukikage Yuri.
Yes!
Hold aloft your Seed of the Precure.
Focus into it your desire to
become a Precure once more.
What is this?!
Is this the Great Heart Tree's light?!
You...
Have you...
Courage, love, friendship, kindness, sadness, and joy.
Within all our hearts lie countless emotions.
I shall fight!
And I shall protect everyone's hearts!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, Cologne.
Thanks to you, my heart stands tall once more!
I am Cure Moonlight!
O power of the silver moon,
help me cast away my doubts and sadness,
and grant me the strength to defeat Dark Precure!
HeartCatch Precure:
What Incredible Power!
Cure Moonlight!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!