This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki, 12 years old.
Since "Myself"  is a big hit, she asked Dr. Wakaouji to listen to it...
...but he said that he didn't listen to music.
We tried very hard to make him listen...
...and somehow, we ended up at the grave site of Mitsuki's parents.
It was there that we found about his true feelings towards music.
It looks like that girl was moved by them.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Ah, found her!
This is her!
Eh?
Who is it?
I'll be on TV with her tomorrow.
Komaki Fuyuko, is she a geisha?
Komaki
Fuyuko
Stupid, not everyone who wears
a kimono is a geisha.
Komaki
Fuyuko
She's an Enka singer.
(Enka: Modern Japanese Ballad)
Komaki
Fuyuko
An Enka singer?
Why do you have to appear with her?
You are  an idol, aren't you?
I think it's because...
...Komaki-san has been hosting a show for new idols lately.
So, I'll be a guest on her show.
What's this?
"Do you want the next generation to live by strict rules?"
Looks like new idols have to go through this gateway for success.
"Gateway for success?"
What's that?
It means something like
the road to stardom.
You should have said so from the start.
"Gateway for success...", he said.
Old man Takuto... gross!
Haha, Meroko, you didn't
even know what it meant.
T-That's not true!
Besides, I'm older than you, Takuto!
Well, if I'm an old man, that makes Meroko an old hag, right?
What?!
Now you've done it!
What was that?
Stop it!
What was that about me being an old hag?!
I'm only a little bit older than you!
Komaki
Fuyuko
So, I have to at least try.
Komaki
Fuyuko
Eichi-kun, I will work hard.
The Law of Show Business!?
Wow, the TV station is so big!
I guess so.
Ah, my favorite weather woman!
Wah, so she's here too...
Ah, that guy... I saw him in a magazine!
Aww, If only I had some
papers for autographs...
Stop it, Mitsuki.
Eh?
You're already one of them.
Uh, s-sorry.
By the way, when we meet Komaki-san, make sure to greet her properly.
Komaki-san is really annoyed by small details.
Okay.
The proper greeting in showbiz is not "Good afternoon!", but
Good morning!
Nice to meet you today.
Ah, trouble!
Eh? "Good morning?"
But it's already afternoon...
Good morning, Komaki-san!
I'm the manager for your
guest Full Moon  today.
My name's Ooshige.
Pleasure.
And Full Moon-san is.. where?
Eh?
Mitsuki!
Let's go, Tadokoro.
Erm, um...
Well, we'll see you later.
It's Komaki-san! Greet her properly!
G-Good day!
Hey, wasn't that Komaki just now?
Eh? That was Komaki-san?
That's right!
I'm a failure.
Why didn't you come with me?
Eh?
You didn't know that was Komaki-san?
I'm sorry.
She wasn't wearing a kimono, so...
Enka singers wear jeans, too.
So, did you greet her properly?
Eh... sort of...
I'm kind of worried.
Komaki Fuyuko-sama's
Dressing Room
Listen!
Komaki Fuyuko-sama's
Dressing Room
This time, say "Good Morning!"
when you greet her.
Komaki Fuyuko-sama's
Dressing Room
Okay!
Komaki Fuyuko-sama's
Dressing Room
Here we go.
Excuse me, this is Ooshige.
I'm sorry about earlier.
Once more, seriously this time.
This is Full Moon,
and I'm her manager Ooshige.
Good morning!
I'm Full Moon.
I'm looking forward to working with you today.
How do you do? I'm Komaki.
I'm also looking forward to today.
She's still new, so I think she could have some problems...
Ah, how wonderful!
W-Wait, Mitsuki-chan!
Wow, the kimono is so pretty.
(Shichigosan: A visit to a shrine by children aged 7,5, and 3)
Komaki-san, it looks like
you're going to Shichigosan.
Komaki Fuyuko-sama's
Dressing Room
I really messed up...
And Ooshige-san doesn't
look too happy either...
What should I do?
It's all my fault.
Aside from that, that Komaki's a mean old hag.
Should you be saying that?
Shut it.
Man, that Komaki's a mean old hag, right?
Huh?
And that bald manager is
such a stick-in-the-mud.
Tadokoro, is it?
He sure is one.
He's such an ass kisser.
Weren't you doing that to Komaki as well?
Well, you have no choice in order to advance your career in showbiz.
There's no helping that.
Rehearsal is starting, we should get going.
Okay, okay.
What was that about?
It's so disgusting.
Should you be saying that?
She should have put it out properly.
You!
What are you doing with that cigarette?
You're still a teenager!
Eh?
Really... all the new talents these days...
Ah, you're mistaken.
The girl who just left
didn't put it out properly.
That's why I...
How dare you talk back...!
Man, kids these days...
In the old days, you wouldn't even think about doing that.
Eh?
Um...
That's not how it was...
She really is a mean old hag!
This girl would never smoke!
Ah, she's really pissing me off!
Hey, Meroko!
Where do you think you're going?
Eh... wait, you two!
Mitsuki!
Rehearsal is starting soon.
Do your best so Komaki-san
won't get mad at you.
Yes.
Test! Test!
A! A! A!
Mic check!
Whoa!
Check, one, two!
There's so many staff members here.
That's right.
They're working hard
to broadcast your song.
Well, Full Moon-san, we're on standby, so please go on.
See, now, good luck.
R-Right!
Okay, let's try it.
Well, we'll start in...
Five seconds...
Four.
Three.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afurete~
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Cut!
What is she doing?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
The camera appeared so suddenly...
I was surprised.
Ah, I see.
We're doing the same thing this time, so please don't be startled by it, okay?
Okay.
Alright, let's try again!
Five seconds...
Four.
Three.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
After the intro, start the lasers...
Ready and go!
Whoa, whoa!
Cut!
Does she think something will happen if the lasers touch her?
Let's clean up and start with Komaki-san.
Okay.
Alright then, let's get moving!
Excuse me, you can take a short break now, so if you could tell Full Moon-san...
Standby, and get ready!
Alright.
I'll try to calm her down.
Well, please do.
Take a break!
Well?
What exactly is your reason to fly out here, leaving her all alone?
There's the one.
Eh?
There! That guy!
Huh?
From that magazine she was reading last night... one of the band members!
I'll be on TV with her tomorrow.
He's so cool!
Hello?!
Weren't you looking for Komaki?!
Geez, you're so annoying.
A little distraction won't hurt.
Could it be...
Maybe you're jealous?
Huh?
Why should I be jealous?
Maybe because this is the date
that I've longed for?
Well, it's too bad that
I had to leave her by herself.
Oh, you're such a sinner, Meroko...
And to think you're a Shinigami...
Komaki Fuyuko is hard to deal with.
I was so tense the whole time, Takeda-san.
I never even knew you could think that way.
Please stop making fun of me.
Hey Meroko!
Those guys... weren't they reporters from "Monthly SuperStar"?
The ones who just passed by?
Don't be so weak, Nou-kun.
That Komaki-san must have a good side, too.
But there are so many rumors spreading.
That she's hard to deal with... and that she picks on the newcomers...
I heard those too. I'd hate to say
that those were true.
She probably does those things
because she cares.
To show that she's there to help them...
She was forced to be an idol, or so I heard.
Yeah.
She didn't like her debut song,
but she had to sing it.
She was depressed and
began to smoke and drink.
As a result, she ruined her voice.
Her attitude that we see now...
...is probably the result of that.
I see.
Even so, did she really have a good voice?
Yeah...
Of course.
Somehow, she could light up people's hearts.
Nowadays, you can't find
singers like that anymore.
Really?
So that's how it was...
That's why she got angry that time.
She might be a good person after all.
Komaki Fuyuko-sama's
Dressing Room
Let's see...
They took a break and
said that Sensei's turn is next.
Well, I said that we can't do that, but the director insisted.
I understand.
R-Really?
Well, thank you very much.
Honestly, what was that novice thinking?
She was rude to you, Sensei.
This time, she messed up the schedule.
She's a really rude person, isn't she, Sensei?
Sensei!
That's what we heard.
I see.
So that's why.
I must have sounded so rude
to Komaki-san earlier.
Well, I have to apologize to her properly.
Yes, you do.
Komaki-san's entering.
I'm going.
I'm really sorry, Komaki-san.
Alright, alright, stop playing around.
You should go outside.
But, I...
What's this about?
Eh? What's the meaning of this?
It's time for Sensei's recording.
If you do anything bad, it may throw off Sensei's performance.
Why did that guy throw Mitsuki out?
I'm sure it's because Komaki said so.
Just like I thought, she is a mean old hag!
She's really a troublesome novice, isn't she?
Oh yeah...
Let's take out Full Moon's  performance.
Just put Sensei's new single instead.
S-Sure.
Wait a sec! What is he saying?
Takuto, we have to tell her.
Okay!
Eh? They're not letting me sing?
Seems like it.
I knew it! She's definitely evil!
That's so... cruel.
What's the meaning of this?
Why are you canceling
Full Moon's  performance?
Can't help it.
She was so troublesome to Sensei.
That's why we're changing our schedule.
Sensei doesn't have free time like you do.
Hey!
Even so, that is too cruel.
Mitsuki?
Komaki-san?
Komaki-san, they said that they won't let me sing... is that true?
What are you talking about?
Eh? But Tadokoro-san said that...
Is she plotting something?
I know I've been in your way
many times, Komaki-san.
But not letting me sing is just too much!
It's my first time on TV.
I want to sing... quickly.
Quickly what?
To quickly become a big star that everyone idolizes about?
That's not true.
Well, what is it?
If that's not true, why else do you want to become a singer?
I promised...
I made a promise...
...to someone very dear to me.
Someone very dear to you?
Yes.
I don't know where he is now.
But we made a promise...
...that we'd both work hard
to achieve our dreams.
So, please, let me sing.
You're too naive.
That's just a dream.
Once you get into it,
the promise will be forgotten.
You will sing and sing because it is your job.
No, I won't!
Then...
Then Komaki-san is singing
because it's her job?
Of course.
That's what makes me a pro.
I don't think that way.
I don't think that way!
I want to sing with that
precious feeling inside me.
If I can't do that, then I'm fine
with not being a pro.
All I want is to touch people's
hearts with my songs!
Well, Full Moon-san, please.
Eh? But they said I wouldn't sing...
It's alright.
The idea was from this rotten bald guy.
So, you don't have to worry.
You can sing.
Okay!
We'll take it from the top!
Five seconds...
Four.
Three.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Promise me.
The next time we meet, we will be closer to reaching our dreams.
Sure.
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
I lost way too much back then
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Well, she has the potential to be an idol.
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Yeah, I think so too.
Wait, please.
I want to sing Enka!
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
On that day I could see...
Wait, please!
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I don't think that way!
I want to sing with that precious feeling inside me.
Futari niteru no kana
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
If I can't do that, then I'm fine with not being a pro.
fuu
All I want is to touch people's hearts with my songs!
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
She's wonderful.
She's just like a young Komaki Fuyuko.
Until we became so far apart...
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Sensei?
Why did you do such a thing?
Don't even bother to come
to work from tomorrow.
Sensei...
Sensei...!
Hey, look at this!
Ah, Komaki-san!
Eh, Takeda-san too?
You've been involved with new idols lately.
How are they?
The latest idol, in particular...
Let's see.
Today, the girl didn't greet me properly.
She looked at my kimono and said that it was like in a Shichigosan.
She even had enough energy
to mess up my schedule.
I couldn't even imagine that one person could mess up that badly.
That sounds so troublesome.
But...
She was different from all the newcomers I've come across.
She even dared to voice her opinions to me.
Oh...
I'm ashamed to admit it, but...
...that girl reminded me of what's important when you become a singer.
Once again, I want to go back
to my original intentions.
Well, Komaki-san, she seems to have left a deep impression on you.
Yes.
It's possible she made me realize my situation.
So, until we meet again,
do your best, Miss Newcomer.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
I will!
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Takuto, there's trouble!
The paparazzi are onto her!
At this rate, her secret will...
Damn it!
We can't let her secret get out!
Wait for me, Mitsuki!
I'm coming to help you!
Wait!
You can't do it alone!
Shut up!
I will...
I will always protect her!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Dangerous Lens
Look forward to it!