So Ra No Wo To
Ready, my little chickens?
Prepare to advance! Forward!
Forward!
Where are our allies?
Forty degrees, left.
Prepare to fire main cannon!
Range 400!
Load shell. Type: heat round!
On it!
Origa!
Don't worry.
I've been locked in this thing for three days.
I'm not dying till we can take a shower.
Main gun aimed!
Fire!
Direct hit!
Anna, report to the rear:
"One tank destroyed.
Continue the advance!"
Roger that!
Filicia, back her up.
Y-Yes!
I know it's flashing.
But it isn't lightning, so don't worry.
I know!
Th-Three o'clock!
No...
Lieutenant Anna!
Kamiya...
Higoya...
Chirping Crickets -
Spirits Down the River
Hey, Noël! Put your back into it,
or they won't get clean!
It's so hot out there...
It's cold in the winter, but I love how
cool this building is in the summer.
Huh? Aren't Filicia and Rio-sempai
on cleaning duty today?
They said they were busy,
and asked us to do it.
Whose is that?
That's Filicia-san's.
She said she wasn't hungry,
so we could eat it.
Then I guess I will!
What's that?
Are you preparing dinner?
Also...
What are you doing?
You'll be written up for
playing with the food!
I'm not playing!
It's almost time for Obon, isn't it?
Huh? What's Obon?
Fiesta des Lumières.
Fi...
Fiesta des Lumières is a holiday
unique to southern Helvetia.
It originated from a folk religion
that believed that,
for a specific period of time during the summer,
the dead return to the world of the living.
Floating paper lanterns down
the river sends them back.
In some places, this festival is called Obon.
Here you go!
Thanks.
Huh? So it's the same thing!
Spirits returning...
Wait! Wait!
What?
Does that mean we'll see ghosts?
In a way.
Paper lanterns... How wonderful!
We used to make fires and
stuff back home, but-
No!
The dead go to Heaven
and stay there forever.
Only bad things are stuck
wandering the earth!
That's not true!
But in church...
We're back!
Come and give us a hand!
Hey, when did you go shopping?
Those...
They looked tasty,
so we bought them.
This too.
Will this do?
No, Father!
Do it like this!
I'm done!
Your mom and dad?
I see.
They look great!
What? Even the church is in on it?
This Fie-thingy?
Yes.
The Central Orthodox Church
would be up in arms over it,
but we're in the middle
of nowhere.
They're not very serious.
In my town,
we would make horses and cows
out of cucumbers and eggplants
for our ancestors to ride.
And we all danced to
make them happy!
Are you going to make some, too?
Yeah. Last year, we just watched, but...
It's part of our job to maintain
good relations with the locals.
If you don't really think about it,
it's just a nice little festival.
Right, Filicia?
Filicia-san!
Are you OK?
Does it hurt?
No. I'm fine.
I just screwed up a bit.
But you don't make mistakes
like that often.
You're not Kanata.
You know how hot it's been
these last few days...
I haven't really been
able to sleep.
I'll go take a break.
Filicia-san...
She's acting kind of strange.
She didn't eat her lunch, and she
blew off work to buy watermelons...
She's got a lot on her mind.
I think I'll go talk to her...
Stop!
There are some things she
doesn't want anyone to know!
Leave her alone.
Noël.
Do you know about it, Rio?
I read the records.
I know about it first-hand.
So...
Filicia...
Keep it steady. Like that.
OK, there's a good girl.
And then there was a monster
that looked just like the captain!
It's hard to believe there used to be
all kinds of living things in this sea.
Did you ever hear...
That the world is slowly ending,
and someday there will be no humans.
That's just a rumor...
But if it's true, then what
are we fighting for?
I'm still alive...
Ideograms?
I'm sorry.
I wish I were able to read
your last words...
This equipment...
Is it from the old era?
Captain...
Lieutenant Origa.
Martina.
Anna-san...
Why am I the only one left...
Why... are you crying?
I see.
There are still survivors
in this world.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because we lost...
To them.
We couldn't protect you.
I'm truly sorry.
The world ended.
No...
You're just the last remnant.
A few remaining bubbles on
the surface of the water.
Humanity...
The world can never regain
the glory it once had.
Don't try to decide that for us!
But it's the truth.
So end it.
It must be far too painful, living a miserable
life in a world filled with despair.
No... No!
Why not?
Is there some meaning to survival
in a world like this?
I...
Save me...
I'm in here!
I'm alive!
Please!
Come save me!
You're...
I'm sorry.
If my squad had only arrived half a day earlier,
this never would have happened.
Your Highness, Princess Iria...
But I was surprised.
At what?
Last year, you ignored the
Fiesta des Lumières.
What changed?
Well...
Pretty colors, huh?
It's made in Treize.
I bought it at the last market.
Wow!
It's so wonderful!
Isn't it?
It's true. They used to
be everything to me.
I wanted to protect the country,
the people, like they did.
But sometimes, I think...
What's the point?
So if they've really come back,
I wanted them to tell me.
But what about you?
Everyone's worried.
That's true. I may have
made them worry.
I failed as a captain.
It's not just them!
I...
Uh...
You?
Anyway, don't try and carry
it all on your own!
At the least, even I can listen to you!
Thank you, Rio.
I'll honor that and tell you, then.
What is it?
You see...
I've gotten fatter this summer!
What?!
If I don't start losing weight, I won't be
able to fit into my winter clothes.
I heard that if you only eat watermelon,
you'll lose weight,
so I thought I'd try it.
What's wrong, Rio?
Stop it already!
What happened at
the Vingt front...
Oh! Did you think I was
remembering that?
You... You weren't?
It's so pretty!
Shall we go, too?
So you made one, too,
Kureha-chan?
I-I don't believe in
souls and stuff!
It's a mission.
Umm... Who are you sending, Filicia-san?
My old friends
and a soldier whose
name I don't know.
The people who made me realize
something important.
Could those people be...
Filicia-san,
if something's bothering
you or anything...
I...
I may not be able to help... But!
It looks like I worried you.
I'm sorry.
But I'm all right.
That's too sad.
I want to worry for you, too!
You always worry about me!
I always do things to
make you worry.
I want to worry about you!
I love you!
I love you too, Kana-chan.
Stay as you are. Won't you?
Filicia-san.
What you're always teaching me,
to not fear putting your
feelings into words...
I think that's wonderful.
Captain.
Filicia... Me, too.
Guys...
You're all so cute.
Come back next year, ancestors.
Dad... Mom...
Mother... Sister...
That girl is...
Hey, Rio. You were asking if there
was some meaning in this world.
Yeah.
When I was the only one who survived,
it was all I could think about.
Why had I, alone, survived?
What did it mean?
And I realized,
I'm sure there's no meaning
in this world.
But isn't that wonderful?
That means you can
find your own.
And I've found mine.
The meaning to my being here...
And then the priest...
What about him?
Well, he was super selfish,
so Yumina-neechan...
What?!
I don't want them to
suffer like I did.
Yeah...
Phone Duty - We Have an Emergency
Next time:
Phone Duty.
We Have an Emergency!
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.