Komachi-kun?
What's wrong? Get the hook in the middle...
Komachi-kun...
Like I could do that!
Komachi-kun!
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
A Man's Heart Wavers
Just as I thought, it's impossible to have a guy in the Underwear Appreciation Society.
Yako-chan!
Geez. If you can't touch a bra at all, we're not going to get anywhere.
Shut it, Monkey Forehead.
Did you say something, Cat-Eyes?!
C'mon you two, calm down!
I... kind of understand what Yako's getting at.
Boys really would... look at underwear in a dirty way...
G'morning, Keigo-san!
Hey!
Oh? So you're wearing the summer uniform now?
Does it look good?
Yup, yup.
Cute, cute.
So, how many fried eggs will you have?
Two! I'll go make toast.
Thanks...
Nayu.
Eh?
The colour of your bra lets the bra-line show through.
What?! No way! I'm going to change.
Well, if you leave it, the boys might be pleased.
You shouldn't look at girls in such a dirty way!
Puberty's pretty tough...
...and am I some sort of geezer?!
Isn't that girl's bra seriously showing?
She's completely showing it off!
Seriously? Oh man...
Will our classroom be like this from now on?!
That'll make lessons kind of awkward.
So, how about that sale next week.
Ah, that's been pushed back.
No way! Seriously?
Geez! All that nonsense back there was a nuisance.
It's enough having to think about that bad mock exam.
Why do I keep losing to a girl who
constantly thinks about underwear?
Hmm? My mock exam results?
Let me see 'em.
Sure.
Loser
Panties and bras, panties and bras, panties and bras, dammit!
Enough of that! Calm down.
I'm not calming down at all!
I just don't understand how boys feel.
What're we doing after this?
I just might understand how boys feel...
For here, I'll switch... on!
They're this spring's new product!
Nayu's Rant
They're for teens, but the slightly adult look is fabulous!
I wonder how they feel.
I believe they're made of summer-friendly cotton.
And yet it's got some of the most stylish adult decorations on it!
N-Nayu-chan?
Haruka-chan! Yako-chan!
G-Good morning.
What were you babbling about?
Um... I was thinking about stuff when underwear suddenly appeared!
I understand you wanting to discover how the mind of a boy works,
but you can't just peep up skirts for that!
There's no connection between them, anyway.
I was so into it...
But that's just Nayu-chan, right?
Is this one of those...
What? A letter?
I don't know.
Could it be a love letter?
Pretty old-fashioned.
It couldn't be!
I-It's not too strange for her to get a love letter.
She's cute, always doing her best,
isn't scared of her breasts being touched...
Er- what on Earth am I thinking?!
The one who wrote down his hidden feelings and secretly delivered it must be like...
Someone like this!
Yako-chan, that's a bit strange.
Wait, the sender might not be a guy!
Haha, Hayama-san...
It could have been a drag queen!
C'mon you two, we haven't even found out if it's a love letter.
"I'll be waiting for you in the courtyard after school."
Amahara-san!
Eh?
It would appear that there are actually people that would be interested in a childish girl like you.
Anyone who would become your boyfriend is
probably some wild underwear maniac, though.
That's not true!
Goodness, don't couples sometimes need excitement, too?
I wouldn't expect good children to understand, though.
It's only morning and she's already taunting us.
The memory of the worker from back then...
...was still strong somewhere in his mind.
Who could it be?
I wonder what he likes about me.
Now then,
based on what we've covered already,
you can apply this formula here.
Holy cow, they're enormous.
F? G?
You stay with B. Don't dream that you'll do better.
I think A's are more-
You people. Don't bring that kind of stuff into the classroom.
Tch, it's Komachi.
What a boring guy.
Take a break from studying and take a look at this too!
But then you've already seen stuff like this in your "Bra-Pan" club, haven't you?!
..."Bra-Pan" club?!
You know, the thing those girls from Class A put together for underwear...
You've got to be joking!
What's with this underwear?
If she wears this poorly fitting underwear,
it'll be bad for her body when the underwire starts digging in!
And yet you guys can just happily look at this?!
And I thought Komachi-kun was kind of nice...
But, he does seem to understand girls a bit...
Not girls, it's the underwear, isn't it?
He knows a bit too much, it seems.
Is he some sort of underwear maniac?
Curse you, Hayama...
Because of the weird stuff you've been teaching me, things have become...
What's the matter, Representative?
N-Nothing. Sorry.
Oh, the Appreciation Society might not gather today.
Huh? I didn't hear about that.
It's because someone is probably going to confess to Hayama-san after school.
She received a love letter.
She's more popular than we thought, hmm?
R-Really? Seems like there's someone out there with poor taste!
A love letter?!
Sensei, you're yelling!
I'm sorry.
Mizuno-sensei, as the adult here,
please tell Nayu how to mentally prepare for this.
Y-Yako-chan.
All right... A love letter, huh?
This bitter-sweetness is kind of nostalgic.
You could call it the first page of youth...
Right! The first love that tastes like lemon!
Isn't that great?!
H-Hey, don't react like you've asked the wrong person for advice.
Nayu-chan, you seem kind of happy.
She's got a love letter, doesn't she?
I'm not really...
I envy you.
Oh, nothing.
Hey, Nayu, your bra is showing through.
No matter how much you look, you're not going to see inside it.
Who's looking at it?!
It's because I want to wear cute underwear in the summer too!!
Um- I knew that dark beige would show through more than skin-coloured, but...
I was going to change, but...
Well, there wasn't anything really cute...
I knew that it would show through, but...
But, um...
If it shows through a bit, are you bothered by it?
How can you ask a male like myself about bras and panties with a straight face?
Because you're like that, people are
making weird assumptions about me!
Pardon, but you can't let this bother you, Hayama-san.
On the contrary, showing him a little would be perfectly fine, right?
Amahara-san, there's a guy in here too!
Sensei, don't you know about the "show-bra" too?
Eh? Show-bra?
Is that the bra they "show" on display in stores?
There are clothes with open chests or backs that allow such cute bras to be seen.
May I see for a-
Wow, it's cute!
There's rhinestone in the straps, huh?!
What is wrong with you?!
Enough already! I'm telling you that I'm going to quit this society!
Go ahead and compare underwear on your own!
Komachi-kun...
Hey, are those "show-bras"?
Yeah- isn't this laced part cute?
Actually, I have some...
Oh, how cute! It's covered in beads!
That's neat... I wish I could wear cute underwear too, but there are so many to choose from...
Then why don't you try consulting Hayama-san from Class A?
Oh, from the Underwear Appreciation Society, right?
First years, hurry up and change!
Ah, right!
Dammit, why does she always have to be like that?
Why haven't you noticed that showing me this kind of stuff isn't fine by me?
Hayama Nayu...
I didn't think that girl could be so out of it.
She's stood in my way as a nemesis and rival...
I always thought of her like that!
On top of that, after years of competing for first,
how could she not remember me?
It makes it look like I'm the only one...
She received a love letter.
She's more popular than we thought, hmm?
Like I'd care!
Dammit, now what...
What is it, bro?!
Uh yeah, do you think that you could do a bit of shopping for me?
No, I can't!
Get me fifty of the usual protein supplement.
Hey!
No matter how much they're on sale for,
what are you going to do with all this protein?!
Hmm? Komachi-kun?
How to Apologise to Komachi-kun
For now, how about emailing him an apology?
I didn't ask for his mail address...
Then how about calling him?
Um...
I called him once before about the Underwear Society, but...
...his older brother answered it.
You wanted Hiroki right? I'll go yell for him.
Hey, Hiroki! Your girlfriend's on the phone!
He got really angry and told me to never call again.
I guess I should apologise to him in person.
But Komachi-kun's so rough around you...
That's quite true. Take this with you.
Jinguuji-san, that'll add fuel to the fire.
Right, time's up.
Did you forget?
"I'll be waiting for you in the courtyard after school."
But we still haven't decided what to do about Komachi-kun!
It's fine for now, hurry.
I want to see what kind of person would confess to you.
Sorry for the wait.
Thank you very much.
Nah, it's fine.
There's something I wanted to talk to you about anyway.
Well? How have things been with Nayu...?
I told you this before, there's nothing going on between us.
Anyway, there's really no relationship between the two of us anymore.
I quit it- the Appreciation Society.
I see. Did you feel out of place, after all?
I'd expect so.
For men, lady's underwear is something that'll bring up all sorts of thoughts.
I didn't get any fantasies or anything from it...
But having that stuff suddenly show up in your face...
When it comes to underwear,
Hayama will generally ignore any given situation,
or forget that it's not normal to show off underwear...
All of that aside, you've got to ask why she checks everyone's underwear without shame!
Some men might be pleased with that, but I think that it's terrible!
When I get hot and bothered over it for only a second, I-
K-Komachi-kun, calm down a bit.
I do understand what you want to say.
It's because Nayu really doesn't understand the male mind, right?
But Nayu, in her own way, is looking out for you.
Why, just this morning...
Do boys really look at underwear in a dirty way?
Hmm... seems about right.
Think about it the other way round.
How do you feel when boys end up seeing your underwear?
You see?
If you're embarrassed when others see it,
surely the ones seeing it aren't fine, either.
I'm... totally a child, aren't I?
Nayu?
I was thinking so much about underwear,
and I didn't think at all about how Komachi-kun felt.
Komachi-kun, huh?
It's got to be tough for a boy at his age to be in the Underwear Appreciation Society.
But I don't want to give up so easily on the possibility of having boys in it...
Komachi-kun was the one who motivated me by telling me:
"If you can do what you love, go and make underwear."
After that, she asked me what kind of activities a boy could do in the Underwear Society.
Komachi-kun, if you change your mind about quitting,
I hope that you'll take care of Nayu.
Ah, miss! One avocado miso soup shake.
Certainly!
Hayama did all of that for me...
But around now she'd be...
What...?
He got the wrong shoe locker?
Correct. It seems that he mixed it up with the next class's row.
W-What's with that promised outcome?
Well, it's impossible to believe that someone would be interested in that girl,
who only thinks about underwear.
That's what you say, but actually, you're relieved.
Who's relieved?!
Anyway, I delivered the message,
so go and have your conversation together.
"Together"?
Ah, um...
I'm very sorry about yesterday!
Hey-
I'd like you to stay in the Underwear Society,
but if that's impossible, um...
I take back what I said about quitting...
...since you guys probably can't manage by yourselves.
Huh? Komachi-kun...
On one condition! I'll say at least this:
I am a man, so I will see underwear in a dirty way.
And one more thing.
The world of underwear you speak of
is incomprehensible and unreachable to me.
But, although it's simple to deny it,
even the weakest guy should be able to try and understand.
Komachi-kun...
The Forehead's taunting is annoying me,
and I said that I'd join the Underwear Society.
I'll try my best not to see underwear as something erotic.
Yes!
Damn Cat-Eyes, you're calling me Forehead again?
But this is good!
I guess it is.
It'd be sad to have someone like that disappear on us.
Oh, Komachi-kun!
Go and say something to the guys!
They brought another dirty magazine in.
What is it?
Just ignore them for me.
There's a lot to being a male.
Thanks for just now.
Even you're interested, right?
He is a man.
A man among men is in front of us!
This is also training...
For myself and for them, I have to be immune to this!
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
Three Will Be Cut Down!
Wear it
The Recommended Way to
Wear a Garter Belt
Model: Hayama-san
First, let's prepare the garter belt and stockings.
Once preparations are done, place the garter belt around the waist.
Next, pass the stocking clips through the underwear briefs.
It's easy to make a mistake here!
Once you've completed this, continue. Done.
Once you've finished them all, as you put on stockings,
roll them up snugly to the thighs.
Stockings that are worn with garter belts are not very elastic,
and will make your legs look better than tights would.
Finally, attach the stockings and the garter belt together.
And it's finished!
Preview
What kind of figure do you like on a woman, Keigo-san?
I suppose my ideal would be dainty, sexy, but potentially robust.
I might not have much sex appeal, but I'm very robust!
I'm not sure about that underwear, though.
It's underwear you're...
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra!
Underwear
Summer
Training
Camp!