Nice to meet you, Ein.
Or should I call you the Old Phantom?
But that's in the past.
At this moment,
Phantom is me.
The Scythe dude calls me Drei.
Ein, Zwei, Drei.
I don't think you need an explanation, right?
"Nice to meet you"? I see the title of Phantom has degraded.
You know, I could kill you whenever I want to.
But that wouldn't be fun, would it?
Finding you two. Driving you into a corner. Killing you.
These are the only things that have kept me alive for the past two years.
Being kept by that fucking Inferno.
So please let me enjoy myself.
I want to see you two being afraid and running for your lives.
And will that make you satisfied?
It would.
You should've seen Reiji's face when he saw me!
It was like he saw a ghost or something.
Next, hmm...
How about I kill you in front of Reiji?
What kind of face do you think he'll make?
Impossible.
Huh?
You met me first.
And I'll kill you right here.
You're well prepared.
Sacrificing yourself to protect Reiji?
That's so damn lovable!
You're the one that's lovable.
Huh?
You couldn't forget the fact that Reiji abandoned you, right?
You want to make him regret more. You want to bury him in sadness.
But he's not the Reiji you knew back then.
He threw away his past and lives for the present.
Your point?
You're just a ghost of the past.
If you stand in his way,
he will shoot you.
You talk as if you know him pretty well.
You just don't understand how strong-willed he is.
And the main character enters.
Elen, Cal, you have no reason to fight each other.
Did you hear that?
Ein, it seems like you're wrong.
Not yet.
The entire cast hasn't gathered yet.
Drive.
Yes, sir.
Shoot me, Reiji.
Stop it, Cal.
Didn't you already abandon me once?
One more time won't make a difference.
Cal...
Shoot.
However, I'll take this woman with me.
I'll take her with me to hell.
Cut it out, you idiot.
Jesus Christ, I knew this would happen.
Why are you in such a rush?
This doesn't concern you.
This is Japan, you dumbass.
Don't think you can just get away after shooting in broad daylight.
I don't give a shit.
Really?
Then shoot, Phantom.
But if you do that, I'll kill everyone in here including you.
Come on, you're first, Phantom.
Put down your gun and get the fuck out of here.
I have your back.
Bang!
Man, what a boring ending.
Cal...
She's your successor, Zwei.
And I'm her support.
Thanks to her, I don't feel alive every single day.
Thanks.
Indeed.
Anyway, the game of school is over.
The organization discovered your whereabouts.
Hurry up and go somewhere else.
And I'm sorry, but I don't have the confidence to stop that crazy bitch again.
All right. We'll hurry.
Lizzie...
Well, how should I put it...
Live in the present, Zwei.
For Clau's sake, too.
Were you going to shoot?
What about you?
I...
This girl and me... if you had to pick one of us...
When that happens...
There's no time left.
I'll secure the escape route.
During this period, we'll let Inferno handle Drei.
It's finally time to shuffle the deck.
Hurry up.
We're going to go without you.
I'm sorry!
Come in.
Excuse me.
Boss, you've got a call.
Who is it?
Well, he calls himself Claudia's confidant.
This is Shiga.
It's been two years, Shiga Toru.
Who are you?
I've already introduced myself.
Claudia McCunnen's confidant?
That Asian brat that was always by her side.
If I remember correctly, it's the assassin...
Phantom.
Correct.
I hear you're being hunted down by the organization.
What do you want?
Does Shinokura High School ring any bells?
Shinokura...
Correct.
The school that the daughter of Godoh Kaiten goes to.
Hey, you know what the fuck you're doing?
You're touching something that you're not supposed to!
Don't worry.
As long as nothing happens to us, we won't lay a hand on Mio.
As long as nothing happens to us that is.
What do you mean by that?
Inferno's assassin is after me right now.
And I want you to stop her, Shiga Toru.
Put pressure on the Inferno presence in Japan with your authority.
Stop messing around.
It's up to you whether you do it or not.
This has nothing to do with her!
Just do your best.
So you became an actor, too.
I'm nothing compared to you.
If this works out, we can gain enough time.
Shiga's a sharp guy.
It'll be fine.
He'll definitely do as we say.
If this doesn't work out...
If that happens, we'll think of other plans.
I don't want to endanger Mio.
Are you happy that Drei is still alive?
Yeah.
I thought she died on that day.
I thought I killed her by getting her involved with what happened back then.
But she's still alive.
Tomorrow, I'm going north at daybreak.
There's a smuggling freighter.
I'm going to go and negotiate.
Alone?
Yeah.
You stay with Mio.
Let's go home!
Look at the time.
I'll make dinner as soon as we get home!
Hey, Phantom!
I just received orders from the higher-ups.
Fuck off!
So it seems like you've heard about it already.
The Godoh Group's godfather - Godoh Kaiten's secret child.
It seems like those two didn't become students because they felt like it.
I don't give a fuck about Japan's yakuza!
Calm down, Phantom.
The Godoh Group is also an official part of Inferno.
That's right.
If the Godoh princess can't be safely secured,
there's no way to kill them.
We were deceived by Zwei.
I guess this is it for now.
We'll wait for the next chance.
Fuck!
Bodyguard for a high school student?
Yeah.
Who the hell is she?
You don't need to know.
But to me and to the Group,
she's an extremely important person.
Is there a need to deploy us?
Yeah.
Use your lives to protect her! Got it?!
Yes, sir.
Do you hate him that much?
No shit.
Why the fuck do you think I've been listening to the orders of this shitty organization?
It's because I want find and kill him.
That's all.
To be honest, I'm relieved.
Huh?
I don't think I can bear to watch you and Zwei fight, Cal.
So you're underestimating me.
You think I'd lose?
That's not it.
It's true that he lied to a lot of people two years ago and messed around with them.
I was also a victim.
That's because he's a fraud.
But you were the exception.
Zwei protected you.
He's been lying to me this whole time.
He never told me anything.
He covered up his lies with more lies.
He was just scared of the moment when he wouldn't be able to keep me in the dark anymore.
He lied in order to protect you.
Protect?
The only one he ever wanted to protect was himself.
See, he abandoned me in the end.
And ran away with another woman.
Even so, that can't be your reason to be an assassin.
You're not being one because you want to, right?
I am.
Right now, I'm the great Phantom who can even make a crying brat shut up.
Gangs who own the streets will shiver when they hear my name.
Feels good man.
Kicking those bastards around, tormenting them, killing them.
You can't have a better life than this.
He's afraid of me.
He realized that I would become too strong.
I'll definitely pay him back for lying to me and using me.
Cal, you're just like burnt-out fireworks.
Elen's absent today?
Yeah, she's had a fever since last night.
It might just be a cold though.
You should've told me that sooner!
I could've gone to your house and taken that cold away from her!
Sup!
I see you're talking about boring stuff as usual, you idiots.
Shut up.
By the way, we're going to a movie today and I'm allowing you guys to come too.
Is that how you invite someone?
Mio's coming, too.
Sorry, I'll pass.
I have something to do.
Could it be a date?
Good guess!
So, they ditched us.
It seems like it.
Why did Sanae say everyone's going?
What a way to beat around the bush.
Yeah.
I hope Elen gets better soon.
Let's go to a movie.
I'll just be a bother to Elen if I go home.
Sure!
This situation is convenient.
As long as I move around with Fujieda Mio,
Shiga will be pressured.
I was fooling around like a kid. It's embarrassing.
That movie was pretty good.
We should thank Sanae.
I think you're...
...a mysterious person.
How should I put it...
Your views are different from those of normal people.
What do you mean?
What's ordinary and normal to us...
...is something that you treasure dearly.
That's why when I look at you, I fall in love with the present.
Even if it's something boring, it has its own significance.
It's just that everyone has forgotten about it.
Am I intruding?
Reiji-san...
So she's Fujieda Mio.
Ein, me, and the princess of the Godoh Group.
You use each and every woman that gets close to you.
You don't even have any intentions of harming her.
Cal...
Now, let's continue our match.
There can be only one true Phantom.
You're Phantom, Cal.
Right now, I'm just a student.
Don't make me laugh, Zwei.
Are you that type of person?
If you want my life, then I'll give it to you.
Why were you escaping up until today?
You didn't want to die. You just wanted to keep living. Wasn't that it?
If you kill me, I'll gladly accept that as punishment.
I did something that merits you killing me.
However, I have a condition.
After taking my life, I want you stop hunting Elen-... Ein.
You want to be her scapegoat?
She won't be a threat to Scythe or Inferno anymore.
So...
You want to protect her even if you die.
After abandoning me...
I can't believe you have someone else that's so important to you.
No, Cal...
Back then, I was...
I'll kill you as you wish.
However, I'll continue to torture you and make you feel pain before I kill you.
Reiji-san...
We are...
...ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
We are phantoms with no identity.
If you can't shoot me here, you're too naïve.
It's only natural for you to die here.