Faint-hearted traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
On a spring night, Virgo is spread out widely.
My favorite star, Spica, is this Alpha star.
If you stretch this line from the Big
Dipper, there's the North Star.
And if you pull the handle of the ladle,
there's the star of the cow
herder, Arcturus, then Spica!
This line is called the Great Arc of Spring.
During the cherry blossom season,
try looking for it in the southern sky!
Alone
I'm finished.
Is that all?
Marika, it seems you haven't
been taking your medicine lately.
You don't have a normal body!
Take your medicine properly!
I'm going on ahead now!
The real Marika never had a
rebellious attitude like that...
I was always alone.
I am always alone.
Well, Miss...
The train has already made one full circuit.
Direct sunlight will be bad for your health.
Let us hurry and move on.
Are there any other places you want to go
or things you want to ride?
At long last, this is the first outing
your father has allowed since you were born, so...
Tell me without reservation, wherever it is.
Here, Miss, what about this place?
The Toritsu Zoo... or would
you like the aquarium?
That's why I thought I'd be
alone from here on as well.
I thought I would be all right with that.
I don't need any friends.
Miss?
Marika-chan!
Can I have a second?
W... what is it?
Well, you know, a new Space Observation Center
was finished in Chiba.
Yes, where Japan's largest observatory is, right?
Oh, come now.
I just read it in the papers.
From the perspective of someone who didn't read it,
that sounded just a tad spiteful.
Don't be jealous.
I'm not jealous!
And, well, we all decided to go to
the Space Observation Center together.
And we thought, "What about
Marika-chan as well...?"
I'm sorry, but I'll decline.
Eh? But it's close, so the
transportation fare would be cheap
and there's a discount on admission
to the observatory for Space School students...
It won't cost a lot of money...
I've told you before.
I hate friendly behavior like that.
Marika-chan!
Hey, wait!
Let go!
I'm sorry.
Umm...
Every person has their own concerns.
I'll say it directly, Kamogawa-san.
You're a nuisance!
Marika-chan!
Leave her alone, Asumi.
But...
That's why I told you it's useless to invite her.
Even when we call her over at lunch,
she never comes.
She must really like being alone.
Doesn't she get lonely?
Asumi...
I don't need any friends.
I forgot the meaning of loneliness long ago.
That's what I've always believed.
That's why...
I'll be leaving now!
I'll say it directly, Kamogawa-san.
You're a nuisance!
Little seagull!
Suzuki-kun.
Hey.
Those clothes... a part-time job?
Yeah.
I have the important job of providing
a moment of relaxation to an exhausted city.
I don't get much in return, though.
I see...
By the way, "little seagull" was...?
Don't worry about it.
Hey.
The vending machine over there's the last one,
so can you wait a bit?
When I'm done, let's go on a date.
Huh?
By "date", you mean here?
Yeah.
Emergency Exit
Little seagull!
This way.
I guess this year it'd be in this direction.
Hmm, let's see...
There it is.
Here.
It's Saturn!
Even though it's an older model,
you can see it quite clearly, huh?
Yeah, I can see the rings perfectly!
Pan, Atlas, Prometheus, Pandora...
Epimetheus, Janus, Mimas...
The moons of Saturn!
Long ago, I used to recite them by heart like this.
Enceladus, Tethys...
Telesto, Calypso, Dione, Helene...
Rhea, Titan, Hyperion, Iapetus, Phoebe.
Suzuki-kun, do you come here a lot?
Pretty much.
It's all right to walk into places like this?
It's all right. This is my dad's building, after all.
Huh?
Why don't you sit down, little seagull?
But it really is mysterious.
Despite being able to see all these stars,
it's possible that not one star
is really there anymore.
What is there is distant light
that's tens of thousands of years old.
In other words, we're looking at phantom light.
But it's like Fucchi said.
Huh?
You'll be smiling as long as you see the stars.
Suzuki-kun.
Thank you.
For what?
Nothing...
I'm back!
Welcome home.
Oh, he said to eat that.
See, that kid with the black-rimmed glasses
came and left those here.
Seems like he went out of his way to
buy it from the fruit shop on the corner.
Ah, and there were a lot of calls from Kei-chan.
Has something happened between you guys?
No...
Hey, why are you crying?
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
That's not it. I was just really happy.
Huh?
I won't allow it!
Why?
You don't even understand why?
Marika!
Marika, open this door right now!
You're different from normal people!
If you go that far, and something
happens, what will you do?
I'm a normal person!
The real Marika wouldn't say such things!
What's this "real Marika"?
I'm myself!
Marika!
I won't feel lonely.
I can live by myself.
At least, that's how it was supposed to be.
But then...
It's a promise.
I... promise.
Yeah!
I see, Fucchi's name is Shinnosuke?
Physics Report
About atmospheric resistance upon entering the Earth's atmosphere
Astronaut Course  Fuchuuya Shinnosuke
Don't look without asking.
It's all right, isn't it? It's a compliment.
I was thinking it wasn't really
a suitable name for you.
How's that supposed to be a compliment?
Fuchuuya-kun, you were named
after your great-grandfather, right?
Great-grandfather?
Yeah, he was a skilled fireworks craftsman.
I see, Fucchi comes from a
family of fireworks craftsmen.
And here you are taking the Astronaut Training Course
instead of following in their footsteps.
Quiet. I'm going to launch a
huge firework right into space.
Hey, what about your name, Kei-chan?
Does it have to do with
your family making Japanese sweets?
No way.
I'm told my grandmother took a character
from the name of a vocalist in a band she liked.
"Keisuke" if it was a boy. "Kei" if it was a girl.
I see...
What about you, Asumi?
Me?
My mother gave me my name.
She said it would let me become someone who
can look forward to tomorrow, no matter the situation.
I see. It suits you, it seems.
But my father's name is Tomorou
and my mother's name is Kyoko.
So don't you think it's
strange that I'm named Asumi?
It's really nice.
It seems like she thought
really hard about your name.
Yeah. They seem to be a happy family.
You think so?
It's true that...
You're different from normal people!
The real Marika wouldn't say such things!
Would you stop it?!
Marika-chan?
What is it all of a sudden?
Marika-chan, umm...
Don't come close!
Don't come pestering into everything like that!
You the one who's always being sheltered!
What?
Marika-chan! Wait a minute!
Marika-chan...
That is all for today.
Ah, I didn't understand anything today either.
Somehow, I'm depressed...
Eating a delicious lunch should
help at a time like this.
That's true! You say such nice things, Shuu.
Asumi, let's go!
If we don't hurry, the cafeteria'll get crowded!
Y-Yeah!
I wonder what today's lunch will be...
Marika-chan didn't even come back to class...
You sure are reading something difficult.
I see, you're interested in cytology?
Cytology
It has nothing to do with you.
Nothing to do with me, huh?
That's true. She's also a real meddler.
But it's not like she's been sheltered.
Well, it's true that her father is a good man.
But everyone has their own concerns.
We're all different, right?
I don't want to listen to a lecture.
If I said she and I were both born in Yuigahama,
would you understand a little better?
Keyword:
Yuigahama
All-Japanese Manned Space Rocket Fails to Launch
List of casualties (Unordered)
Kamogawa Kyoko  Critical
Kamogawa Kyoko
"After suffering extensive injuries
from the Shishigou accident,"
"Kamogawa Kyoko-san, who had
been in a coma for five years"
"has died without regaining consciousness
on the fifth day of her 33rd year."
"After that, the same..."
Don't drop your pace!
Yeah, yeah.
Geez, when are we going to be relieved
from this agonizing hell?
All right!
Now we can be released from hell!
All right, all of you finish up!
Marika-chan?
It's painful...
Miss...
It has become a downpour.
It is a pity, but let us go home.
I will get the car ready right away.
It's me. Please bring the car around.
There was no place I really wanted to go.
I just... wanted to run away.
Marika-chan!
I wanted to run away from that place.
To a faraway place... farthest from there.
To a faraway place...
No matter how much my legs hurt...
No matter how much my breath became short...
Even if no one noticed...
Even if I was alone...
But really...
The place I really wanted to go was...
What I really wanted was...
Oh my, you've woken up?
Let's see...
Do you feel any pain anywhere?
Do you feel sick?
I see. Well, there's nothing to worry about.
It seems like a light anemia.
Have you been eating properly?
You shouldn't miss meals for the sake of dieting.
The course you girls are in
is basically a test of physical strength.
Is it all right to go home?
I suppose. Be careful.
Oh, that's right.
A few girls have been anxiously
waiting outside for a while...
Friends of yours?
I told them, "She's still sleeping, and it's late,
so go home," many times, but they wouldn't listen.
Kids around your age are lucky.
Your feelings for others are
so pure and straightforward.
With me, I have to have a
reason to worry about someone.
Come in, come in!
I'll go get some tea ready,
so you can go ahead to my room upstairs.
Ah, I'll help!
A storage room?
Who's there?
My imagination?
But it's mysterious...
When I'm here, I feel calm.
There's a nostalgic smell.
I wonder where Marika-chan went...
Geez, she's annoying.
Kei-chan.
Good morning, Kei-chan.
Ah, 'morning.
I'm sleepy again today.
I hope I don't fall asleep during class...
Ah, Marika-chan, good morning!
Thank you for everything yesterday.
That surprised me...
Wait, Marika-chan!
Ah... hey, wait up!
Ah.
I wonder what kind of guy the little seagull likes.
What is it all of a sudden?
You like that kind of girl?
Bad taste.
You sure aren't honest.
Here.
Hey, you...!
In middle school, it seemed
like she liked someone.
He died from an illness.
You're no match for someone who died...
Yeah?
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
Preview
He was the first person that
I talked with about space.
First love? If that was my first love,
then it would be the second most
heart-breaking time of my life.
Who decided that spring is
the most beautiful season?
Even though spring comes every year,
the same cherry blossoms don't bloom twice.
Next time on Twin Spica:
Asumi's Cherry Blossom.
Asumi's Cherry Blossom
End