When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Miss, what is this?
It seems rather avant-garde...
Yeah, when I went
to rent videos from Wataru,
it looked interesting, so I couldn't
resist bringing it back.
You have to show it to
at least 2 people within a week
or you die.
Wait, what?! Isn't that the curse
from that loopish video?!
There's no way such
an unscientific thing could be true.
I guess even you have
a rather childlike side to you.
Oh, right. You're right.
Allow me to explain, just to be clear.
The loopish video refers
to the movie "Ring"...
No, no! Please don't say anything more!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Our theme may be horror,
which is typical for the Obon festival,
but perhaps I still acted too scared.
It's the Obon festival anyway.
No one's watching,
so we'll go with animated storyboards
for the rest of the episode!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Miss Saki's Little Preoccupation
(National Edition) 2007
Video Tachibana
What's with that damn Nagi?!
She's late again!
Sure, she probably can't understand Oshii's
work just watching it once, but still!
Huh?
That loopish video isn't here.
Summer Horror Fair
I had no idea there were people kooky enough
to rent a knockoff like that.
Oh, Saki,
Nagi's late again, so give her
a call to remind her for me.
What's with her?
It's been a week since then,
but nothing's happened.
I told you, didn't I?
There can't possibly be such
things as ghosts in this world.
You're right.
Maria sure is something, though.
She's so mature. I bet there's nothing
that she can't handle.
Oh, that reminds me. We received
a watermelon as a gift, didn't we?
How would you like some?
What? Then let us be sure
to serve it to the Miss as well.
Oh, no, that is...
I actually took some to Nagi earlier, but...
This is no good!
I need a better name
that reaches out and grabs people!
I'm going to incorporate horror
and develop a new genre!
I see.
When it comes to manga,
the Miss gets too absorbed in it.
Well, that's also one
of her good qualities, though.
Give me some, too.
Wataru, what brings you here?
Hmm, you know, well...
Stupid Nagi's late again, so I'm here
to give her a little reminder.
Oh, what was that weird video?
So that's it. I noticed it was
missing from the store.
I guess Nagi took it
without letting me know.
It was made right around
when the original became a hit.
The Loop
A knockoff and a pale imitation at that.
I never imagined anyone would want to
watch something so obviously lame.
I mean, if Sadako comes
out of it, that's one thing,
but as I recall, when you watch that video,
the thing that comes out is like this.
Hmm, something like that would
certainly be creepy, though...
Don't you think, Maria?
Oh? Is something the matter?
Saki's been acting strange.
It seems she's got something on her mind,
but she won't even talk to me about it.
I swear! Just because she's turned 20,
is she trying to tell me that she
can't turn to a 13-year-old for help?
Wow.
Saki doesn't look it, but I guess her
coming-of-age ceremony is next year.
Coming-of-age ceremony?
May of This Year
Wow, so you're turning 20 in June.
Yes.
Maybe I should get you something
to mark the occasion.
What do you want?
That sentiment alone is enough for me.
You're always wearing a maid uniform...
All right, want me to buy you
a long-sleeved kimono?
W-Would you really, Young Sir?!
If you're turning 20, you'll need one
for the ceremony and stuff, right?
What is it?
D-Don't you want one?
It's not that.
Then, I shall look forward to it
without getting my hopes up too much,
Young Sir.
Could it be because I forgot her birthday
and her long-sleeved kimono
for her coming-of-age ceremony?
Is that why she's depressed?
Hey, are birthdays and
coming-of-age ceremonies important?
Well, I imagine they're pretty important.
Incidentally, how was your
coming-of-age ceremony, Maria?
Huh?
What?!
Oh, r-right...
You're still 17, so your
ceremony's still a ways off...
That's right.
ROARRRR
I'm a young and fresh
17 years old, you know.
So why...
...did you think I'd already had
my coming-of-age ceremony?
M-Maria, you've been acting
strange for a while now!
I-I haven't been acting strange.
I just remembered something I have to do.
Uh... I really wonder
what's gotten into her.
Her coming-of-age ceremony...
I guess I'll just start
by asking Saki directly.
Video Rental
V Tachibana
Hey, Saki...
Were you sighing because
I'd forgotten your birthday present?
Come to think of it,
no one celebrated my birthday.
Well, not that it really matters.
I can't get back the time I've lost,
but I believe I can win back the trust!
Uh-huh... So what do you want from me?
I want to give a present!
No thanks.
Like hell I'd ever give you a damn present!
BA-BAM BAM BAM BAM
Can't show you!
When you're asking a favor of someone,
as Haman Khan said, you would do well
to watch your language.
Yessir...
Good grief.
In the end, it's better for her
to be playing nicely with her friends,
rather than working on manga by herself.
Let me go see about
getting these two some tea.
So? What's this about a present?
Oh, no, so...
I want to give someone
a long-sleeved kimono as a present,
but I don't know what kind to get her...
Oh-ho, a long-sleeved
kimono as a present, huh?
I see, so finally, you've...
Huh?
Go to this store.
It's pretty cheap and they have
the sort of kimono she'd like in stock.
R-Really?!
I'll owe you one, Nagi!
Then I'll head over there right away.
Oh, but don't buy anything too cheap!
Let me ask you, just so I know...
About how much does one
long-sleeved kimono cost?
Oh, it won't cost as much as 2 Ferraris.
How the hell does one outfit
cost more than a Ferrari?!
Don't mock the money sense
of the general public!
Would you shut up?
The chair I hit you with earlier
was even more expensive.
What kind of goods
are you using on a daily basis?
Besides, once a man's decided
to give a woman a present,
paying that kind of money...
...is a given! What's
the point if you can't?!
S-Sure, that may be true, but...
Where am I supposed to get
that kind of money?!
What?
It may be in name only,
but we're still betrothed.
No interest, pay it back
when you make it big.
What?
Now, what will it be?
So bright!
What?!
Roaches Come Come
Combat
Amazing! An Onmyou mystic!
What is all this?!
Maria, you're acting strange!
What? How do you mean?
There's nothing strange going on here.
Wh-What in the world...
Nooo!
What?
I-I... Anything but that! Anything but that!
I can handle anything but those
black things that go scurrying!
I had no idea Maria had
a side to her like this.
I'm sorry. For losing my composure...
But it's the one thing that I just can't...
It'll be all right.
Even if it were to show up,
I will protect you, without fail.
Y-You will? Really?
Yes!
Roach!
What's that?!
I-It can't be!
H-Hayate, was that...
It's going to be all right, Maria.
Roach!
Roach, roach, roach,
roach, roach, roach, roach!
I am coming to be with you.
(Ima ai ni ikimasu.)
I-I can feel a draft.
(Su-Suusuu surun desu.)
I had no idea the Young Sir
was so concerned about my birthday.
In contrast to that,
Granny hasn't even called me.
Let us explain this to you now.
Saki Kijima's grandmother is...
...the legendary house maid, Rei Kijima.
In search of her missing daughter
and her husband, i.e. Saki's parents,
Rei Kijima went traveling across the world
with her granddaughter, Saki.
At one time, she saved a president
from being assassinated.
At another time, she solved
a difficult cold case.
And on yet another occasion,
she found an oppressed people,
whom she frequently freed
with dishes that impressed the Emperor.
Uh, however, the legendary house maid
was already 62 years old.
Smack dab in the middle
of the Sahara Desert,
she was on the brink of death.
Granny! Granny!
Are you going to let your
exhaustion overcome you here?!
O Rei Kijima, legendary house maid?!
This man is none other than the
leader of the Tachibana Group,
Enkyou Tachibana himself!
Enkyou rescued Rei Kijima
and also Saki, while he was at it.
A soul-deep rapport grows
between Rei Kijima and Enkyou,
which is neither love nor friendship!
And to repay him, Rei fights!
Against evil! And against culprits!
In the midst of all this, there was
a new encounter for Saki, too.
Her encounter with Wataru.
Being too young, the mother showed
almost no interest in her own son.
Seeing him in profile,
looking so lonely, Saki swore...
...that in thanks for rescuing Rei Kijima,
she would repay them by raising
this child to be a fine adult.
There you are. Tea.
To Saki, it seemed as though their two
souls, abandoned by their mothers,
were calling to one another.
The tea I make tastes better.
However, Wataru turned out
to be an unexpectedly skillful boy,
capable of doing anything
and he was far better at things
than the naturally klutzy Saki.
Considering how the Young Sir is,
will I be able to guide him
so that he becomes a fine adult?
Incidentally, Saki's parents
live in Ueno even now,
so please rest assured
that they are not missing.
Sanzenin
A d-dead end!
Please hang on tight!
Hayate...
Really, such a beautiful day.
Oh?
On days like this,
there is no better pastime
than to go around giving new
meanings to the garden flowers.
Beep! Target sighted!
Security
Roach!
Jet Stream Attack!
Attack!
Roach!
We can get him! We'll do
the Jet Stream Attack one more time!
Roger!
Roach!
Jet Stream...
...Attack!
Roach!
Beep! He used me as a stepping stone!
We should be fine,
now that we've come this far.
Based on what evidence?
Hayate...
Oh, no, anyone would have
done the same in my place.
No, that!
Roach!
You're one persistent bastard!
I'll protect Maria!
Butler Kick!
BAM
Roach!
Roach?
You lay a hand on Hayate
and you will regret it!
R-Roach...
Roach!
Ow, that hurt...
Maria...
Hayate!
Are you all right?
I talked big, saying I would protect you,
but you ended up protecting me.
That's not true.
You did protect me, Hayate.
Maria...
Oh, no! If that thing goes after Nagi...
The Miss!
Here I was thinking I had arrived
without getting lost for once,
but I come to find a little one
who has become lost in here.
Roach!
Isumi, I had no idea you were here!
Oh, did you see a black
scurrying thing around here?!
Oh, that little one went home already.
Isumi defeated that thing...?!
What's this commotion about?
I didn't know you were here!
Did you hear from Wataru?
What?
That's not why?
I guess he's shy,
in spite of the way he acts.
When you get down to it, a present
has to come out of your own pocket.
Once I looked at what
my savings could buy me,
I ended up with a summer kimono.
My, what an adorable summer kimono.
Isumi!
Oh, sorry... But what are you doing here?
Um... Nagi said...
...that you had something important
to say to me and a wonderful present,
so I should come to your house right away.
Could the present be...
...that?
Oh, no! This is...
Then, what was the important
thing you had to say to me?
Damn Nagi and her meddlesome ways!
But this is a golden opportunity!
I can give this summer kimono to Isumi
and tell her how I feel...
How I feel...
Isumi!
Yes?
I was able to get two
of the "Changéríon" box sets,
so I'll give you one!
Oh, my!
So, what was the important
thing you want to say to me?
It was about the performance of
Mr. Hagino, who plays the lead!
It's different from Asakura
in "Masked Rider Ryuki",
and his cheerful performance
is a real highlight!
Well, take your time watching it
when you get back.
I will. Thank you, Wataru.
Young Sir?
What are you doing out here?
Uh, right...
Oh?
This is...
Well, you know,
I felt bad for forgetting, so...
I can smell another
woman's scent in this room!
Huh?!
Could it be that you brought home a girl
while I was gone and...
Uh... did pervy things...?!
No!
A present for you! This summer kimono!
What? Why did you get me a present?
Because... like...
I didn't have enough money
and I couldn't buy a long-sleeved kimono,
and this can't really take its place,
but I forgot to get you a birthday present
and I thought maybe that's why
you'd been so mopey lately, so...
Oh!
The thing that was bothering me...
...was what color I should get
for my new cell phone...
Huh?!
Well, that's okay...
Good grief.
So it seems that wasn't a present for Isumi.
I see.
So, did you end up lending him money?
No.
He said it was pointless
if he didn't pay for it himself,
so it seems he bought a cheap summer
kimono instead of a long-sleeved one.
Paid about 50,000.
F-Fifty thousand...
That is not cheap.
By the way, that loopish
thing hasn't shown up.
See? Stuff like that is superstition.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Wh-What was that?! Did a missile
come flying from somewhere?!
They started a fireworks show nearby.
Fireworks, huh? Nothing says
summer like fireworks.
All right, let's go out together, Hayate.
Yes, Miss.
Nothing says summer like grilled
squid from a street stall!
Y-You look good in that summer kimono.
Thank you very much, Young Sir.
It just may be that yet another
new misunderstanding has been born.
Hurry! Hurry!
Pretty, isn't it, Hayate?
Yes.
Roach.
Frozen!
Next time, a dragon and a hamster...
...will fight over the one they love
and their maidenly pride.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful,
it'll be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
SIGN: Butler Report
...Butler Report!
The Iron Cross Killer! I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
Man, it's really gotten hot lately.
The highs in Nerima surpassed
30 degrees Celsius today.
Please don't make such offhand remarks.
We won't know if it'll be hot
on the actual day this airs.
And depending on the region,
it'll air on different days, too.
Never mind that. What I want to say...
...is that when it's hot, stay
cooped up in a room with A/C blasting,
play some online game,
and listen to my character song!
You shouldn't spend your summer
in such an unhealthy way!
Bye-bye!
Preview
All right! Starting today,
it's summer break!
Starting today, I'm going to play
online games, watch anime, draw manga,
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
and have all the fun I want every day!
I feel like her life is pretty similar,
even when she has school...
Aw, man, summer break's here,
but I don't feel very happy somehow.
I wonder what Hayate's doing...
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"I Like Books, But Sing It
Great Palace of the Dragon King".
Oh, you're that thieving hamster!
I Like Books, But Sing It
Great Palace of the Dragon King
Wh-Who are you calling a thieving hamster?!
The Sign of the Guardian guides me.