The event for the sports contest will be...
...Kawashima-san's suggestion,
a 50 meter freestyle contest!
I'm so lucky!
What did you put down?
Note: Vale Tudo
If I win, I'm going to have an appreciation session for the video of your imitation medleys.
If I win, Takasu-kun will be coming over to my villa for the summer.
You're going to spend your entire summer by yourself.
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Preparation!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed there's nothing
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
For Whose Sake
If you can solve this, come up and do it.
Here.
As expected of the class rep.
No!
Hey.
Idiot!
Front Side: Pass it on to everyone in Class 2-C
Remember to skip Ami, Taiga and Takasu
The first round of the battle for Takasu has begun!
Ami-tan VS Palmtop Tiger.
One bet will be 500 tyrols!
What the heck is this?
Is this even a fight?
Ami-tan will win for sure if it's a swimming contest, because Taiga will sink.
I want to be fought over, too. What should I do?
Damnit... All of you...
Sorry, arl, Ami is mine.
Did you want write "all"?
Oh wow, he even spelt "all" wrong!
Bottom: Did you cheat to get admitted? >Haruta
Haruta, you...
That's not right.
Why is everyone scribbling stuff down?
What the hell...
Note: Palmtop Tiger: 3,000 tyrols! - Takasu Ryuuji
W-What is it, Aisaka?
I-If you understand how to do the problem, please go up and solve it...
A-Aisaka-san?
Don't be afraid, Taiga.
It's like washing your face.
Come on, one more time.
Even if you say that...
Is she afraid to put her face underwater?
She's pretty bad...
I think the winner is obvious.
Ignore them.
I know!
Well, she's trying her best for Takasu.
Who-
What do you mean by "who"?
Kitamura-
Do your best together with Takasu's support!
Eh? What? Support?
Hey, Taiga!
I'm not going to train during class ever again.
Image training is good enough!
Don't say that until you can put your face underwater.
What are we going to eat today?
String beans with egg, tofu steak and miso soup.
There's also spinach wi-
I don't want beans, I want meat!
Don't be so picky, beans are also meat for the fields!
Cheapass...
Putting that aside, you should use the class time wisely to practice.
First, correct your attitude.
I can't, because Kitamura-kun is watching...
That's why you should give it your best.
You know...
And just whose fault it is that I'm doing my best for a misunderstanding?
Whose?
I told you, in order to stop Kitamura from going to Kawashima's villa-
Ouch!
That's enough, just make my dinner.
Seriously, what's with you?
Hurry up and go make something.
I have to train hard after taking in a lot of nutrients!
It's raining pretty hard.
Today's swimming class is canceled.
Even though I wore my swimsuit today...
...why is the pool closed?!
Don't ask me.
Tickets to the public pool.
Use them.
I placed a bet on Aisaka, too.
You know, the paper that was passed around.
Since Takasu was so confident with his bet, I thought "Sure, I'll bet on you, too".
M-Me?
Yeah.
W-Why? You know I can't swim...
That's because you're the type with hidden potential.
We won't know who'll win until the end!
Can't we... do this?
What are you doing?!
S-S-S-S-Shut up!
Do your best to train!
Stupid.
Hey, do you want to go anywhere while we go home?
How about Sudohbucks?
Sounds good.
What are you doing?
Why are you in between there?
You're weird.
I can only feel peaceful in narrow spaces.
My gosh, you're going into your exhausted-mode, too?
Because of someone, I've always been like that recently.
Hmm? Someone's fault?
I don't understand.
You...
Isn't a jealous Taiga cute?
How is she jealous?
She just doesn't like you.
Are you stupid?
You're the stupid one.
Anyway, just stop picking on Taiga.
Why did you mention a villa?
You never planned to invite anyone in the first place.
I'm serious.
I'll win and spend my summer together with you.
I've been thinking of what to do after I win.
I think it would be fun!
See, we get along well.
No we don't!
You're mad!
You...
Seriously...
You should stop pulling pranks.
Fine~
Good bye.
I know already.
W-What do you know?
You're the one who "enhanced" Taiga's swimsuit.
Well, that's...
Don't hide it.
This is just simple reasoning, Akechi-kun.
Before, Taiga told me that you'll always help her.
With chores, sewing buttons, or even ironing.
Oh, that's nothing...
The "nothing" you talk about is the most amazing.
Hey, Kushie-
I believe in you.
I'll leave Taiga to you.
O-Oh...
I'm not allowed to help since I'm the judge, but I feel the same as you.
Just leave it to me!
All right.
Please don't rain tomorrow...
Thank you, weather-fortune doll.
Somehow, the weather is nice today.
Look, Ryuuji.
It's like I'm swimming, right?
It's about time we get started.
Ugh, what is this?
Tomorrow is the day of the contest! You have to practice the front crawl!
You just have to use whatever you have.
This is lame.
That's good.
Try kicking the water.
Fine!
Hey...
T-Taiga?
Taiga, you're amazing.
Your kicks are awesome!
You might be able to win!
I can win?
I just kicked normally.
Of course, we can't stop yet.
But-
I see.
I can win.
Taiga?
I'll win.
Yeah, just like that!
I don't think it'll stop anytime soon.
It wasn't easy to get you going...
Now what?
Do you want to go home?
You still want to continue?
I see.
That's right.
We can't waste Kitamura's effort. He was the one who gave us the tickets, after all.
That's not it!
It's not like that, I'm trying my best beca-
I know.
We'll give Kawashima a surprise, too!
Forget it. No matter what I say, it's pointless.
Why?
Oh, perhaps it's because of me?
I see, you won't have anything to eat if I'm not there.
I told you that's not the-
You don't have to push yourself.
Even if you lose, I'll go to Kawashima's villa by myself.
I'll ask her not to drag Kitamura along.
I'll prepare enough food for you.
So don't worry too much...
You've shown your true intentions.
You wanted to go to Ami-chan's villa from the very beginning, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you, I don't care what you do, where you do it, or who is involved!
What are you saying?
I'm doing this all for your sake!
Who told you to do these things?
You've been acting strange lately.
It's probably because of what happened last-
Are you going to bring that up again?
What are you unhappy about?!
What, huh?
When someone else thinks that they know me and act like they do...
I hate it! It pisses me off!
Why don't you understand?!
Do you want or not want others to understand you?
I don't know!
Huh?
No one will know what I'm thinking!
Because...
...I don't even know myself.
What did you just-
Hey!
As you wish, I won't be participating!
It's itchy...
Did I do something wrong?
Huh? Ryuu-chan?
Why are you still awake?
I'm back!
Didn't Taiga-chan come over?
How come?
Did you guys have a fight?
Taiga said whatever I do is not her concern, and got mad.
I think that's the reason.
Oh, I see.
Well, you understand, don't you?
Taiga-chan never says what she really wants to say...
As if it doesn't concern her...
If she really hates you...
It doesn't matter how hungry she is, I don't think she'll ever eat from the same dish as you...
Seriously, your make-up is still on.
Hey, wake up.
You probably didn't eat anything, right?
I really hoped for good weather.
I also hoped that you'd give it your best.
Well, in other words...
It doesn't matter what you think, I still...
...want you to win.
Win? I...
The boxed lunch is innocent, so I'll take it.
But...
Because of all the rain, my usual swimsuit is still wet...
But isn't this breaking the school rules?
I'm really worried...
The beautiful Ami-tan is going to swim in this pool!
That's because she wants to bring Takasu to her villa.
Why is it always you?! Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why? Why? Why? Why is it always you?!
Ouch! Ouch!
Cut it out, you guys!
It still isn't decided if I'm going or not.
It's impossible for Taiga to win-
You don't know unless you try!
Until you try...
...we still won't know...
That idiot...
It's all meat this time.
Hey, how long are you going to make us wait?
It's hot!
Why isn't the Palmtop Tiger coming?
Isn't that good?
We're here to see that bikini, after all.
Hey, if we continue to make them wait in such hot weather...
I guess...
What are you bitching about?
Bring it on.
You stupid Chihuahua with an even stupider bikini.
What is that?
Seriously?
Taiga!
Are you going to swim like that?
I thought she was armed for a second.
Don't you think she looks cool?
Now, the 50 meter freestyle contest is about to begin!
On your marks...
Get set...
I see hair.
Cra-
I can't believe this! I can't believe this! I can't believe this!
The Palmtop Tiger created a decoy; this is a really surprising tactic!
Damn you, you tiny bitch!
Taiga?
Did something happen to Taiga?
Ami-tan's chance is here!
Damn!
Are you all right?
Did you sprain your ankle?
Idiot, let go of-
I still can-
It's impossible!
I'm going!
But you're...
You're happy, aren't you?!
Wha-
Don't "what" me!
Be grateful that your master is doing this for your sake!
You slow dog!
All right, Ami-tan!
The tables have turned!
Yay!
All right, if that's the case, go!
Use your tail or whatever!
That's why...
Ami-tan!
Don't push!
Idiot, it's dangerous!
Ryuuji!
Huh?
Taiga?
Takasu!
Takasu, are you all right?!
Yes, he's still breathing.
Aisaka, take him to the nurse office!
Don't touch him!
Taiga?
But Aisaka...
Shut up, you're all idiots...
Why didn't you notice?
Why didn't you save him?
That Stupid Bikini won...
No one went to... save Ryuuji...
Ryuuji is mine!
No one touch him!
Well, I'm going to your villa, too.
Huh?
Didn't I lose?
Isn't Ryuuji going?
Doesn't that mean no one is going to take care of me?
That's why I'm going, too.
Wait a second.
You're confusing me now by deciding on your own.
Wouldn't that be better?
It'd be more fun if everyone went.
Oh, I see.
Perhaps Aisaka-san will feel insecure if she's separated from Takasu-kun.
After all, she said Ryuuji is hers.
That's right.
I acknowledge that.
Because...
Well...
He's my dog, after all.
It's a master's duty to restrain their own dog from messing around.
What?
Did you expect something else?
No, I didn't.
All right, let's plan our schedule.
Oh! Oh!
I've been working recently...
I'm also busy with club activities...
It's too bad we can't be alone.
But there are still chances.
Just like this, Takasu Ryuuji's first semester of his second year in high school has ended...
...and he is about to begin an exciting summer holiday.
banira saruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience.
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla
Next Episode Preview
You, Going to the Sea
I'm going to a villa with Kushieda!
Will I get punished for being so lucky, Taiga?
Kitamura-kun has some black seaweed...
Huh?