This is all I'll say: you are not fit to call yourself the legendary ninja's granddaughter!
What's wrong with everyone?
You're all so quiet.
K-Katsuragi! What are you doing this early in the morning?!
Are you still upset that those
Serpentine girls pounded us?
We just gotta beat 'em next time, right?
You don't seem to be bothered at all.
Who's the one bothered here?!
Good grief... That girl!
Not gonna beat them by being depressed.
Is that your letter of apology for the other day?
Please, just call it a report.
Even if it was without a doubt my fault.
Kiriya, from what I observed during the incident the other day,
the attackers had help from someone who knew the campus.
A traitor? Absolutely impossible.
Kiriya, you must at least consider the possibility it was her.
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't be strong
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Like a spiral, this red trap coils around us
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Dress yourself in the rampant shadows
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
I don't like this exercise.
This is a walk in the park compared to the other exercises, isn't it?
Yeah, but it ruined my hair! It took me two hours to set!
Who cares?
Oh right, did you hear?
Nope.
I haven't said anything yet!
It's about sprouts again, right?
I could talk about that too!
Yeah, I figured you would.
I heard that Master Suzune used to work for Hanzo Academy.
That's nothing but a rumor.
Hmph, there's no way one of them would become a Serpentine teacher.
Are you sure?
What are you trying to say, Mirai?
You can't categorically deny it, can you?
I mean, even you come from a line of virtuous ninjas, don't you, Homura?
Shut up!
I also come from a similar line.
If you say one more word about this...
Ooh, scary.
Master Suzune... Hanzo Academy?
Set up?
It pained me to do so without saying anything,
but I couldn't refuse a direct order from the headmaster.
Looks like I haven't earned his complete trust yet.
Why are you telling me, then?
This is a secret arrangement with him, right?
Well, I am your student, Master.
Besides, I am not against adding a few more puppets to my troupe.
You're as inscrutable as ever.
That isn't true. I'm quite simple.
I just want to enjoy myself, that's all.
You have my gratitude.
By the way, about combining spheres...
I heard that you came up with that when you were a student.
It's lucky that such an amazing technique didn't fall into the hands of Hanzo Academy.
Well then, if you'll excuse me.
Combining spheres, huh?
Its advantage is its degree of difficulty to perform,
but for a student to develop a new ninja art is unheard of.
Well, I'm going to be a super ninja!
I should at least be able to do something like this.
You make me proud. Well done, Rin.
Forget her. Rin is... dead.
Rin is dead.
She failed in her mission.
To fall in the course of one's duties is glory to a ninja.
But until I see her corpse with my own eyes, I shall not acknowledge it.
Also... I have found something.
Found something?
There was a dark ninja's presence in that piece of clothing.
A dark ninja's presence?
A wicked presence, in a different league from the other dark ninjas we fought.
Then that person back there...
As a teacher—in fact, precisely because you're a teacher—
you must know the abilities of the Serpentine Academy girls.
It is an application of the countless skills that girl used.
I've read reports, but I've never seen it myself.
Wait, are you saying that this plot was crafted specifically so that I would be blind to it?
Are you ready for this, Kiriya?
Are you ready to let your students be drawn into this fight?
We're going to climb this mountain?
Yeah.
I'd call this more of a dangerous exploration of the uncharted than an enjoyable hiking trip.
You may be pretty close to the mark.
Pretty close?
Could this, by any chance, be a part of that so-called "forbidden training"?
Good guess, Ikaruga.
I-I knew it!
What do you mean?
I heard that there was a training program
that was run a number of years ago, but stopped because it was too dangerous.
It was called...
HIKING
...hiking!
The hiking regimen: one of the most severe courses of ninja training.
They must survive in extreme conditions for at least two whole days,
and then fulfill the objective given to them.
It is used chiefly for strengthening survival skills.
Th-This is not the kind of hiking I'm familiar with.
Me neither.
I placed a scroll at the top of this mountain.
Whoever obtains this scroll will be the winner.
So we'll be competing with each other. Is that right?
Sounds like fun, doesn't it?
I wish this was regular hiking.
Don't worry, Hibari. I'll protect you.
G-Gotta do my best.
All right, go!
Right!
While we may not know their true intentions, it is evident that those five are the enemy's objective.
All five of them have their own special qualities.
To think that their development has stalled must eat at you, Kiriya.
The Terrors of Hiking
This is hard right from the start.
H-Here goes!
Ninja Art! Soaring Squirrel!
Ninja Art, Soaring Squirrel: a technique for getting to the ground from an elevated location
by gliding with a drape woven of special fibers.
Landing... failed.
I wonder if everyone else is all right.
Still a long way to go, huh?
It is impossible to reach the summit in one day.
If you fail to manage your stamina properly, it could cost you your life.
All right! I'm definitely gonna be first!
Be sure to get enough rest at night.
That hurt!
This is all part of your training.
I need to rendezvous with Hibari right away.
It's so hot...
Is this really Japan?
It's so cold!
Is this really Japan?!
Huh?!
I feel like I could be blown off at any time.
Hibari should be right around here.
Wha—
Oh no!
Devil's Peak is no ordinary mountain.
But knowing you all, you should be able to handle it.
Devil's Peak
Devil's Peak: a special training zone designed with countless hazards
to simulate extremely inhospitable conditions.
This snake's giving off such a creepy vibe!
A-A giant eel? Wait, no.
It has whiskers, so it's a giant loach!
Wait, as if that matters right now!
If that's how it's gonna be...
Sorry, Mr. Loach.
Th-That's...
How's that? Give up?
You bears better think twice about taking on Hanzo Academy's ace, Katsuragi!
I should probably transform into something warmer before I catch a cold or something...
The hell's this?
Well, as long as it's warm, who cares?
All right! Here I go!
Riding on my weapon was a bad choice. Now I can't fight back.
Yagyu!
Hibari, keep back!
Fishies?
These are piranhas!
Piranies?!
Hibari, don't worry about me. Keep on going.
No!
What?
I'm going to help you, Yagyu!
Hibari...
S-Secret Ninja Art!
Ninja Bunny Boom!
Yagyu!
Thank you, Mr. Bunny!
Yagyu, are you okay?
They only chewed on my clothes.
I thought the river would be safest, but apparently I was wrong.
Hibari...
What?
Nothing. I'm just grateful.
Oh, Yagyu!
Your breasts, your breasts!
You got careless, didn't you?
Time to get a move on.
Senran Kagura
I'll camp out around here until daybreak.
Who's there?!
Wait! It's me, it's me!
Katsuragi, is that you?
Is that right? That really happened?
This place is even crazier than I imagined.
It's all part of our training.
Yeah, yeah.
Ah, I'm hungry.
For heaven's sake.
I can't believe you didn't secure any food.
Here.
These are acorns, aren't they?!
I gathered them up along the way.
Are you sure about this?
Go ahead.
Thanks! Leave it to our class rep, eh?
Rubbing salt into an enemy's wounds... you shouldn't do that.
I think in this case you mean "offer salt to the enemy."
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Well, thank you, I'll help myself.
Oh, yeah, there's a hot spring up ahead.
A hot spring?!
I wonder if everyone else is all right.
I'm sure they'll manage.
What?
I was just remembering the past.
The past?
I was thinking, when we first enrolled at the school, it was only the two of us, just like this.
Yeah, you're right.
This sure takes me back.
Amazing!
Our very own hot spring.
It should be enough to wash away the sweat.
The river is too dangerous, after all.
We'd be attacked by those piranhas.
Thanks for earlier.
Huh?
I only thought of letting you get away, Hibari, and never imagined you'd end up saving me.
I didn't have enough faith in you.
I wasn't thinking about helping you either.
Before I knew it, my body just responded on its own.
You always think too much, Yagyu.
I'll give you that.
It sure is nice, not having anyone watching.
You are not fit to call yourself the legendary ninja's granddaughter!
Once we climb to the top of this, we'll be at the summit.
I'm not gonna lose!
There should be a shortcut if I go through here.
This is scary, all right.
I hope nothing pops out at me.
I can't let myself be spooked by this.
I am... the legendary ninja's granddaughter, after all.
That's a laugh.
Who's there?!
The legendary ninja?
What is it worth, being his granddaughter?
M-Monster!
Family legacies are nothing more than their memories.
It is foolish to tie yourself to one!
I'm not tied to it!
Does the legacy strengthen you?
If it doesn't, then what is it to you?
To me?
I...
It's no use...
You are not fit to call yourself the legendary ninja's granddaughter!
I knew it... I'm not fit at all.
You take after your father, huh?
Huh?
My dad? I do?
When I was fiercely opposed to him marrying your mom,
your dad gave up his dream of becoming a lawyer, and said he was starting a sushi shop.
He said, "I don't need dreams or wealth to live my life with the one I love."
He was determined to have his love.
And with that determination, he convinced me.
Your father is stronger than he looks.
And so is your mother, who fell in love with him at first sight.
It doesn't matter if I'm fit or not.
It's because of Grandpa, and because of Mom and Dad, that I'm here now!
And just for that, I'm...
Secret Ninja Art!
Twin Sword Slice!
The pressure of expectations,
and the feelings of inferiority that come from perceived failure to meet those expectations,
create shadows of doubt in the mind.
Do not fear these shadows!
It disappeared?
Pay heed.
What's truly fearsome is one's own weaknesses!
I think once we get through the jungle, we're just a hop away from the summit.
Yeah.
That's just my hunch though.
That's good enough. I believe in you, Hibari.
Gah! All at the same time?!
Who wins?
What becomes of first place?
Wh-Who's that?
I do not show myself voluntarily.
If thou wishes a testament of the victor, perform to the utmost of thy ability.
What does that mean?
I am the final obstacle of Devil's Peak, and the objective of this hike.
The scroll... Then, if we defeat her...
We're to take it from her, are we?
Who are you?
I am Daidoji.
Daidoji?!
You mean, you're the legendary... Daidoji?
You know who she is?
Only by name.
We'd heard there was an extraordinary student before us who,
despite having passed her graduation exams, volunteered to stay behind for many years.
Th-There's a person like that?
She's stayed here for so many years? That's truly extraordinary.
Then again, she's a woman?
Seems awfully manly to me.
Fighting one on one would be way too easy.
All of you, come at me together!
That was pathetic.
What power...
She's on a whole other level.
I didn't come this far to be beaten!
That was lamentable.
You shame the reputation of ninjas.
After all our attacks, and not even a scratch!
There's no way I'm a match for her...
Even so!
Running away means surrendering to my weaknesses!
Asuka!
Stay with us, Asuka!
Have the Academy's standards really sunk so low?
That's enough, Daidoji.
Mr. Kiriya!
What's going on here?
It was Daidoji here that planned this hiking excursion.
She wanted to play a part in her juniors' training.
Why would a legendary senior ninja...
You lack experience, but at least you put up a fight. That in itself is valuable.
Does that mean that Asuka won?
Well, I guess there's not much we can do, huh?
That girl has great potential.
She still hasn't realized it, though.
You can tell that, huh?
Latent strength is unconscious strength.
As such, she is a double-edged sword.
If she takes the wrong path, she could arrive at the same place as the other.
I won't let that happen. Not again.
I'm gonna be a super ninja, Teach!
What's it say? Hurry up and open it!
Katsuragi, you're being improper.
You're interested too, aren't you?
Well, sure...
What does it say on there?
"Strength is both a sword and a shield."
This is the greatest secret of the ninja,
written down by Master Hanzo himself.
You must learn to channel that strength as a sword and shield.
I'm not going to whine anymore.
Grandpa, I'll do my best!
This is how it should be, where my scattered wishes guide my heart
and drive me onward
At first I saw nothing
I didn't know what it meant to shine
I lay buried in the earth like a stone,
with eyes closed, and hid from the dawn
My feelings gave me a voice
and with breath held
I soar
I run forward because that makes me who I am
Nothing will stop me, not today, nor tomorrow
I run through time
This is how it should be, where my scattered wishes guide the children
and I smash their fear away
I run through the dream of my life
Next Episode Preview
Is it true that Ikaruga and Katsu didn't get along?
Yeah, they were quite cantankeriffic.
And when I came along?
You were quite fresharmonious.
And Yagyu and Hibari?
They were quite chumminacious.
Um...
A Ninja Classroom Retrospective
Next time, "A Ninja Classrom Retrospective."
Come get it like your life depended on it.