Last episode!
The rival that finally
showed up in front of me.
I'm Kaneru Nido.
Kaneru and I...
Whose dojinshi is going to sell?
A one-on-one female battle
with our spirit and pride on the line!
Let's stop!
No, I won't!
Which one did the
maiden of victory smile for?
Looking forward to it!
You're so mean...
The result is finally about to come up!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
You're not going to ask why
I'm in such a good mood?
Why are you in such a good mood?
You noticed?
You made me notice.
I won! I won!
Columbian Horned Frog
Is it like a Columbian
horned frog or something?
Not a pet! I'm saying I won a battle!
Even though you say you won,
you only sold one copy.
And it was only to Hoshi-kun.
To tell you the honest truth,
I'm jealous that you...
...can be happy about
selling just one copy.
Well, yeah...
6th Edition
I'm going to take one first.
I'm Kaneru Nido.
Age 24, second year
of joining the company.
Pretty much a common
employee to a company.
I'm home.
When I go home, what's
waiting for me are the manga drafts.
Yes. In a way,
dojin artist is my side job.
It was something I started
because I wanted to, but...
To tell you the truth,
it's not that easy.
It's well-drawn...
My books aren't selling,
but I have to live strong.
So that's when Tsuyuri said to me...
"It's too early to become a snob."
That's what she said.
Hey, are you listening?
Oh, sorry.
I was looking at Sora,
so I wasn't listening.
Gosh, Justice!
Poke, poke!
Sora!
Justice!
All is well because he is
back to the normal Justice.
Thanks to you.
I was able to give the
epic piece that I packed in...
...all the thoughts of my heart to him.
Take this!
Take this.
I wrote this manga
that might be good for you.
Read it and configure yourself!
Well, the reconfiguring manga that
you wrote became a waste, though.
Najimi, I'm going to ask
one more time, but...
...the reason you went into a love
hotel with him was for research, right?
That's exactly right.
But we can't let our
guard down with that guy.
I would like to continue to
be on high alert with him.
Are you still saying that?
Well, see you later.
The techniques to have
a lead on your rival...
This is it!
H-Hello, how are you?
T-Thank you about the other day.
But seriously this is a coincidence.
Looking for a certain book?
Yes, "The techniques to
have a lead on your rival."
Or should I say this.
This?
Can I have it?
No, there's only one copy...
Then all the more...
I found it first.
Please! I looked around for it
everywhere and finally found it!
Even though you say that...
Come on, you won the other day!
Well, even though you say I won...
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors?
I'm going to put a rock out.
What? Hey!
Rock, paper, scissors...
...shoot!
You're mean...
First off, choosing with
"rock, paper, scissors" is nonsense!
What's the matter, Najimi?
How embarrassing.
Why are you raising
your voice in a bookstore?
It's not my fault! She was...
And she is?
It's the girl competing against Najimi!
Um, we aren't competing or anything.
I see. You compete on how many copies
you sell and you boost each other up.
What a good relationship.
Thank you.
I'm Kaneru Nido.
Normally, I'm a company employee.
A company employee?
Is there something wrong?
Oh, no...
I'm Najimi Osana.
This is Justice.
And she is...
Justice of the major company?
Oh, you know me? What a pleasure.
I'm a big fan!
I'm Sora!
I always buy your books.
I cried so much with
the epic 500-page piece!
On top of that, on top of that...
I...
Thank you very much.
No!
Kaneru-san...
I guess I'll let you
have this book after all.
Really?
I'm going to have Justice
teach me how to draw.
From me?
From Justice-san?
Come on, as a
childhood friend's side benefit.
Lucky...
Well, I don't mind, but...
Me too, me too!
I want him to teach me too.
That's not possible at all.
If it's fine with me, I would love to.
Goody!
Hey! What are you saying okay for!
Why not, Najimi?
If you compete with
the same requirements...
...then you'd be able to compare
each other's strength, don't you think?
That might be true, but...
Well okay, I'm going to
show her my seriousness!
It's supposed to be here.
She's not here when
she's supposed to be.
Come on, let's leave!
Good morning.
Welcome.
Come in.
Thank you!
Those are cute pajamas.
The stuffed animal too!
I am Aioros the bear.
A brave warrior...
I'm a bear that doesn't like conflict.
Thanks in advance.
No, that's our line.
I'm so sorry for being half-awake.
I didn't say anything weird, did I?
Yes, of course.
I can't believe you said
such a vulgar thing like that.
Tsuyuri, stop it.
She's my friend Tsuyuri.
She writes dojinshi also.
Nice to meet you.
I heard you're competing
on your sales with Najimi.
Ah, no, it's not like that.
I will cheer you on because for me,
it would be more interesting if you win!
Please do your best!
Thank you!
Y-You...
This is...
If you stare at it too long,
your lifeline is going to get shorter.
What kind of drawing is that!
How is it?
Is there hope in my drawing?
Well, this is a common aspect to
the both of you, but you don't have...
...enough sense to make your
drawing more three-dimensional.
The drawing to be...
...three-dimensional.
That's new.
O-Okay...
Then let's actually draw it.
Just like this, as you make
a dimension in your paper...
Amazing!
I see.
Did you get it?
Then I'll give you advice
as you work on each page.
As I thought, living alone is nice.
N-No, not really...
Oh, I know!
If you live at your parent's house,
there's something I want you to have.
I was given this
from someone at work.
A Columbian horned frog!
I didn't think I was really
going to have one as a pet.
I don't want it! I don't
want it! I don't want it!
But, you can't have pets here...
...and at my house lives Aioros!
I don't care about such a thing!
Why don't you take it, Justice?
I had the harlequin snake
Guilty at my house just let out.
It's going to be eaten!
Then, Tsuyuri!
A frog skin bag.
You can't do that!
I'll take it!
Thank you so much!
Oh, I'll bring some tea or something.
Oh no, don't worry about it.
The tea that I made has a reputation
of being really good at work.
Amazing!
Hey, Sora-chan, you are
cute and I like you a lot!
Kaneru-chan, you are like
a child and cute too!
What? I'm not a child anymore!
More like you put "chan"
at the end of my name?
Kaneru-chan!
Bears...
Look, Aioros is right here.
No!
Baki-chan!
I'm really sorry...
I'm going to vacuum right away.
Ah, that feels good.
U-Um, I will make
some tea right away.
No, don't worry about it.
Don't change the channel!
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
It's already the halfway point.
I can hear everyone's voice
of being disappointed.
Those that didn't say it,
say it right now.
7th Edition
How wonderful the smell of BaLa.