It's summer already.
Loads of things have happened since I started doing love research here.
You went too far with the changes there!
Hell, it turned into pure fantasy somewhere in the middle!
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Love Lab?
A lot has changed since I started doing love research,
but there has been zero progress on the love front.
I still don't have any links with guys.
What are you up to, Riko?
Oh, my mom forced me to start going to cram school since my grades were truly awful.
And well, they give out too many assignments.
Cram school? The same one
the guy you rejected goes to?
What? Is that true?
Isn't it awkward for you?
You have other ex-boyfriends there, don't you?
That's all in the past, so it's all right!
It's also a lie.
But they might still like you!
What?
What if a war breaks out over Riko?
Must be a real bed of thorns, eh?
There's one
right here.
Ex-boyfriend?
Not him, surely?
I see your mental image of Jan keeps getting more and more beast-like.
No way!
He really helped me out, that's for sure.
It was my first time, you see.
Thank goodness he did it.
It was a bit too rough for me to handle, though.
Huh?
Why's he censored now?
Entrance exams were a piece of cake for Jan,
so I had him help me study.
Oh, hey, he's uncensored now.
I see he's also got a nice side to him.
A little                                       update
But I get the feeling he let me have a whole lifetime's worth of snarky remarks during our study session.
What?
Update
error
Hey...
Could you do some research for
this request at your cram school?
Which one?
The one we found in the south building.
Hairstyles that are popular with boys.
In particular, she wants to know what the guys in the nearby South Middle School think.
Fuji Girls' student council must live up to the faith the students put in it.
We have to get our hands on
information pertaining to every season.
So she says, but in truth...
I'm interested too!
Wait. Does anyone I know at cram school even go to South Middle School?
More importantly, when will people learn that everyone's got their own tastes?
But we might figure out what trends are popular.
If that's a no-go, ask the guy you rejected this for me.
Huh?
"How should I tell the guy I'm dating that I want us to go back to being just friends?"
Like hell I can ask him that!
South Middle School?
He goes there.
Um,
Satch...
Nagi!
That's what everyone calls me.
Naggy, then.
You want your ass kicked?!
How about Waggy, then?
Ew.
Why did your reaction get even worse? Explain yourself!
Just state your business already. You're annoying.
What kinda girls are popular at your school?
Th-The ones who don't punch guys.
What's the most common hairstyle among popular girls?
Is there a hairstyle that boys at your school like?
What?
They're all different, obviously.
Thought as much.
Why are you even investigating this?
There's a girl who wants to know.
You're still a busybody, I see.
Huh?
Let's see...
I think long and silky black hair's quite popular.
Apparently there's a real hottie at Fuji Girls'.
She's the heartthrob of all the guys at my school.
I've never seen her, though.
Do you know this girl?
Don't tell me...
My school's full of scary women,
so everyone's thirsting for the cute ones.
But you're cute.
M-My bad. Force of habit!
But I was complimenting you, you know?
Shaddup!
Going by how you're acting, I can tell you still haven't remembered my confession at all.
Why did I fall for a girl like this?
All right.
I forgot all about my history with you just now!
Huh? Wai—
If you don't remember it,
it might as well have not happened.
A dark chapter in my life has now been erased. That's a relief.
"Dark chapter"?
Oh, really?
Come to think of it,
there was something else I wanted to ask.
What is it?
How should I tell a guy who asked me out that I want us to go back to being just friends?
Huh?
Modified it a bit.
Something wrong?
Well...
An insensitive girl who doesn't stop to consider how guys feel
will eventually make the guy come to his senses and leave her, so she doesn't need to say anything.
That does make sense.
Long and straight black hair is popular?
Not fluffy confectionery hair,
but silky and shiny dark night hair?
Maki's probably the heartthrob Nagi was talking about, right?
An insensitive girl will eventually make the guy come to his senses and leave her.
Huh?
Wha—
Riko?
Why are you curling my hair?!
Didn't you once say you wanted to get a new hairdo?
Please stop!
Maki residence
If long and straight black hair is popular,
I should draw up an encounter strategy that utilizes this to the fullest
and let the girl who made the request know.
I need to take better care of my hair too.
Time for a bath.
All your pain will disappear.
The cold is the greatest enemy for both women and digestive organs.
Lend me a book, Natsuo.
Huh? Is she in the bath?
Oh, she was studying.
Let's take a sneak peek.
Operation: Showing Off Your Hair
"Operation: Showing Off Your Hair"?
Maki Natsuo's "Operation:
Showing Off Your Hair," part one!
Install a large fan at South Middle School's main gate.
Show off your wavy hair and become popular!
Wouldn't a large fan be a bit too much for the student council's budget?
Oh, right!
In the event of a typhoon,
you can become popular for free!
Operation part two!
Wet your hair for a sexy look.
It wouldn't look unnatural during pool season.
South Middle School is a ten-minute walk from Fuji Girls'.
Taking drying speed into consideration,
it might be a good idea to start off dripping wet.
The light reflecting off the drops in your hair will form the perfect synergy!
The next day
Rejected!
Why?
Maki Natsuo's "Operation:
Showing Off Your Hair (Revised)"!
Part one!
Dance near the school!
Part two!
Hold a concert near the school!
Part three!
Do some fishing near the school!
Part four!
Cram school?
You know how your tutor, Matsubara,
is quitting because she's getting married, right?
Well, one of my friends is running a
cram school with a good reputation.
But you once said that I couldn't go to a
cram school because there'd be guys there.
Father!
Natsuo's in big trouble!
What's wrong?
It might be due to her lack of interaction with boys,
but her desire for love seems to be
growing in a very eccentric manner.
A smooth-talking guy could deceive her in an instant.
Your overprotective nature is also to blame!
What?
Natsuo needs to learn about reality!
Don't you go to a girls' high school and have no interaction with them either?
Currently attending Fujisaki Girls' High School
Why does it sound like you know what reality's like?
I'm shocked.
The advanced classes seem quite difficult,
so I won't force you—
I'll go!
Let me go!
I can finally display the fruits of my training!
I'm talking about my studies, of course.
Oh, really?
Came face-to-face
with reality
Now I can interact with boys too.
I might happen across the prince of my dreams!
We're here, Natsuo.
Okay.
Masaomi!
The girl who's joining the advanced class is coming to check the place out, apparently.
Mr. Irikimi, could you call me by my last name, please?
But I wanted to show my affection by calling you that.
It actually feels strangely distant to me.
Should I call you Jan like Riko does, then?
I'm fine with Masaomi.
Anyway, once the new student shows up, I'd like it if you could be friends with her.
I hope this one doesn't quit because she can't keep up.
Two people quit just the other day.
It'll be all right. She's a talented kid.
Oh, speak of the devil.
That's Maki, your new classmate.
I need to speak with her father, so show her around, will you?
Right this way.
It's just the two of them?!
This isn't what we agreed upon!
A few students quit the other day, you see.
There'll be more joining soon.
Don't just say she's Maki and run off.
What's her last name?
What's your name?
The teacher just told him what my last name was.
It's Natsuo.
Natsuo...
So she's Natsuo Maki, huh?
Okay then, Ms. Natsuo...
Ms. Natsuo
H-How could you address me like that?!
What?
M-Miss? Wh-What are you...
S-S-Stop it!
What, so she doesn't like being called Miss?
Then how about Natsuo?
Natsuo
I don't have my digital voice recorder with me!
Wait, that's not the issue here!
I-I'm sure I just heard it wrong—
Are you okay in the head, Natsuo?
Riko!
It's a hottie!
A real hottie!
M-Maki?!
Riko!
Wh-What's wrong? Calm down!
Wait, why are you here?
There she is.
What was with that weird noise just now?
Jan took another one of my firsts!
Y-You've got it all wrong!
What's all this racket about?
G-Gosh, what have I done? I completely lost my cool.
Sorry for kicking up a fuss.
If I were as popular as Riko,
I wouldn't get flustered by just this much.
I'm pathetic.
Popular?
Don't you know?
She's always been very...
Hey, we're leaving.
See you tomorrow at school!
Popular?
Wait, are you putting on airs and lying to your friends?
I-I'm not, you oaf!
You don't even know anything.
This feels awful!
Yeah, for me!
This feels awful.
The
one
feeling
the
most
awful...
...has gotta be me.
Riko!
Maki.
Did you hear?
The school rules changed from "No relationships allowed" to "Relationships endorsed."
What?!
We don't have to research love in secret anymore.
Let's assemble the whole school and have you,
the love expert, run a course on love techniques!
Wait, I can't!
Why not?
Is it because you're putting on airs and
lying to your friends about being popular?
No!
I have my reasons!
Let's hear it, then.
In the faculty lounge after school, that is.
For now, stand.
Huh?!
Faculty Lounge
You're slacking too much.
You're a member of the student council,
so act like one and focus.
Come on, tighten up your necktie too.
Maki, the president, is always on her toes.
Well, yeah, Maki's perfect,
but here, she's...
'Sup.
What's wrong, Maki?!
Goodbye, pure girl memories.
Are you talking about what happened at cram school yesterday?
You said Jan took your first time.
Yes.
He's a monster.
I lost it.
L-Lost what?
The memory of being called "Natsuo" for the first time!
He suddenly called me by my first name!
Twice, even!
Wait, was Jan that kinda guy?
Oh, but that's not a big deal.
Not a big deal?
Well, yeah, you're popular and have a wealth of experience,
so you probably don't understand how those of us with zero experience feel!
Totally
gets it
I'm sure it's not something to get up in arms about,
but I've always dreamed about being called by my first name.
I even imagined an ideal situation.
days    hours    minutes  seconds
A boyfriend who still won't call me by my first name.
It's been 86 days, 9 hours, 27 minutes, and three...
four...
five...
six...
A passionate count!
Terrifying!
The weather's clear-turned-typhoon.
Go home.
It's just like my heart.
Too volatile!
Ramen
That's when a sign flies toward me!
You should really go home!
Look out, Natsuo!
Did you just call me "Natsuo"?
This is absurd!
Say it again.
Some other time.
Seriously, go home!
Yet, it happened just like that...
What's important to you?
Having the guy you love call you that, right?
So don't let this bother you.
You're right.
That guy you rejected is calling you by your first name too,
but you don't let it bother you at all.
That's a load off my mind.
Thanks, Riko.
Wait, are you putting on airs and lying to your friends?
And now I've got a load on mine...
Wh-What's wrong?
The next day
Look, it's President Maki.
She's always so prim and proper.
Her wavy hair is so pretty.
But there's no breeze blowing right now.
The beauty of Fuji's Princess can manipulate nature itself!
What amazing girl power!
Superhuman
power
Are you a love expert?!
I-I guess?
I do have a few guys wrapped around my fingers and all...
Why the hell did I say that back then?
If I hadn't, things would never have ended up like this.
Quiet!
Huh? Are you in a bad mood?
Did something happen?
Huh?
No, nothing.
How'd you like it?
It was my production of
"Pretty Hair Flowing in the Wind."
I thought it was an eel.
There's no guarantee that there'll always be a breeze.
If I have my own breeze,
then I won't let an opportunity slip!
You do it from the shadows, like so.
That's terrifying!
At least use a portable fan or something.
But taking the lazy route to success doesn't seem that satisfying.
Don't worry. You'll never succeed.
The shadows are dark, which makes it scary, huh?
I'm not sure you understand what's scary.
Oh, right.
I could use the lighting and...
It's so hot today.
The hallway's seriously hot and humid.
Oh my.
Did I look so wonderful your jaws hit the floor?
The lighting doubles the hair's beauty in what I call...
"Operation: Backlit Goddess"!
That's one evil goddess!
I see it even makes me seem
a little devilish and attractive.
You're one optimistic devil.
Yo! You're an eco-friendly goddess who needs no A/C!
Don't egg her on!
It's suddenly gotten a lot chillier.
A production of hair flowing?
Are you dumb?
I'm amazed you can come up with such worthless ideas.
Wait, no! This is an old habit!
You shouldn't overdo it when you're using a fan.
Just do it normally.
I-I see.
But it's kinda heavy to walk around with, isn't it?
That's where the portable slapstick comes into play!
Why a slapstick?
You can slap people and fan yourself!
That looks pretty damn weird!
This way, your guy will consider you the perfect straight man!
Why does she get so self-confident when slapsticks are involved?
That reminds me of when I went to a public school.
I used my desk pad as a fan.
Me too!
I'd fan under my clothes that way.
And play with static electricity using it.
Or even throw it!
Huggy!
This is it!
What is?
Take out a desk pad in front of
South Middle School and fan yourself!
Totally natural.
Nope.
It's a bit embarrassing, but fan under your clothes.
It'll be simply fantastic!
You think you cracked a good one, don't you?
Attract attention to your hair by playing with static electricity,
and show off your innocence!
At the same time, single out one of the guys around you.
Looks like a specter's drifting about.
And then you throw it at a guy of your type!
It'll give you an opportunity to talk to him.
What is this, a full course desk pad menu?!
All done.
The answer's complete.
As the representative of girls with long and straight black hair,
I'll also pass on my techniques to effectively show it off.
I really hope you're not talking about the desk pad thing.
But we might get even more
requests if we reply to this one.
We'll never run out of love research topics!
That's nothing to be delighted about!
There'll be more events from now on. We'll be busy!
What if you push yourself too hard and fall ill again?
Yeah, we can't go around
answering every request we get.
We went and did all that crazy stuff the other day, so we should keep a low profile for the time being.
That said, we can't just ignore them.
What about picking only the easy ones?
I think it'd cause real problems if the
student council got picky and choosy.
We might get accused of playing favorites.
This is such a pain in the ass.
Do you want me to use this to tell them, then?
Oh yeah, the newspaper association.
What?
Yeah, well—
It felt like we were being called, so we rushed here.
Pull the other one!
We brought our new edition.
We're really proud of this one.
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
It's great to have friends!
Mizushima Sayori's rare smile.
A notice from all clubs
A smile of
friendship!
How mean!
This is a special two-sided edition, you know?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
Has the Princess
boom arrived
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
Has the Princess
boom arrived
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Fuji Girls' News (Trial Ed.)
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
A Mysterious Princess (lol) shows up!
Has the Princess
boom arrived
in the
student
council?
in the
student
council?
Well, isn't this a nice newspaper.
Quit with that reaction!
It really is a great newspaper.
Quit with that reaction too!
Aren't Nana's pictures wonderful?
I'm not sure if it's good enough to go with Momo's article.
Your pictures are really wonderful!
Way to go!
R-Really?
It certainly is a nice newspaper.
Nice and harsh.
Hilarious!
I know, right?
But what we want you to pay attention to...
...is this bit under the main article.
Right here!
Love Lab News
Love Laboratory News?
Call it the Love Lab News.
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
Maki's being pushed around.
It's kind of refreshing, though.
Don't act unconcerned just because it doesn't affect you.
Huh?
Letting my hair flow while I'm being
pushed around seems like a good tactic.
Do you want someone to grab
your legs and spin you around?
That's just a giant swing.
What are you, a wrestler?
Love truly is war.
How deep.
Love isn't scripted, though.
Please Be My Friend Forever
Don't say something so dangerous!