Summer Time Rendering
I really thought I was screwed for a moment there, Shinpei.
Shide...
Haine...
No.
Hiruko.
You're disposable now.
Ya got so small.
Ain't a chance in hell ya recover now.
Her eyes are destroyed too.
This couldn't be more disappointing.
And yet, what is that right eye?
The observer's right eye!
You're the egg like I thought!
And now you've awoken!
But it doesn't add up!
Haine's scan said you were mostly corrupted data.
So it was that?
I knew ya were growing faster than expected.
But is that the reason y'were able to be restored?
So this is the power of love, eh?
All I have to do is steal that eye from ya,
and my wish can still be granted!
During the fourth loop,
I wasn't able to steal it from Shinpei,
but the egg has yet to come in this timeline!
I should be able to steal it from Ushio before she gives it to him this time around!
Shide's desire...
If what I read in his mind back then was truly his desire, then...
I won't let ya!
Shide... Wait...
I can still do it!
I just gotta eat lotsa people!
And I'll recover!
Then we can go home together?
O-Or maybe give me Ushio's eye...
I ain't got no more use for ya, girl.
What the heck?
Haine's yer mother, ain't she?
And yer point is?
I have no interest in the past.
Shide!
And ya call yerself human?!
And yet, I require Hiruko to live.
If she dies, my armor will vanish.
As ya wish, then.
I'll take ya home!
N-No!
Not in this body!
Come, observer.
Let's settle this on the other side.
Ushio, give me the shotgun!
Shide!
Shinpei!
Thanks!
This is bad.
Shinpei, we're getting sucked in!
I'm weak...
Too weak!
Humans can't go beyond this portal!
If ya do, you'll never come back out!
You'll be lost forever, unable to even die!
But!
I'll go alone!
Idiot!
I'm never leaving ya alone again!
Did ya even hear me, ya bull-headed dummy?
Can ya hear me, Ryuu?
Take control of Shinpei's body and get him outta here!
And if I abandon her now,
Sis will punch me when I see her in the next life.
Ryuu!
I decided to fulfill the promise Sis made
to save her!
I'll support you, Shinpei!
I won't let you get lost!
I'll follow yer presence.
I'll always...
be by yer side.
I love ya, Ushio.
And I wanna be with ya.
Got a problem with that?
Idjit.
Shinpei!
Sou!
Take care of everyone!
Ushio!
So this is Haine's home?
Right. Where's Ushio?
Tokoyo
So this is the cut-off for the flow of time.
It's just as Dr. Hishigata said.
Time doesn't flow here.
It's like it's stagnant.
I doubt my looping would work here.
If I die, that's it.
This isn't good.
Ushio!
I was just holding her with my own hands!
I'm sure she made it over.
The shotgun she printed hasn't disappeared at all.
That's right. She's gotta be within 50 meters!
I feel her presence too, albeit slightly.
She appears to be on the move.
We gotta catch up to her!
Shinpei!
Sorry, that jump was too much for you!
I-It's fine!
I told ya to go after Shide with all ya had!
Compared to what Miss Nagumo went through, this is nothing!
Please give me total control of your body.
That way, I'll be able to take the pain from you.
But then ya'd be—
I'll be fine.
I'm a Shadow, after all.
Just let me lower the amount of pain you have to bear.
And I'm not only talking about your foot.
Your body's beginning to break down.
If I don't support you from the inside,
your human body won't be able to survive in this place.
How is it? I'm going to start moving.
What an odd sensation.
My physical feelings are paralyzed,
so I can't feel anything, but my mind feels so clear.
That's what it's usually like for me.
You'll have to get used to being nothing but a formless consciousness for your own sanity.
Right.
It's kinda like when I do my take a step back thing, so I can do it.
Ushio!
Please answer me!
Ryuunosuke, could this be Hitogashima?
It's quite similar.
I can see Wakayama on the other side of the sea.
Right.
Hey, Shinpei.
I've been meaning to say something to you.
What is it?
You don't have to be so formal with me.
Huh?
You're older than me, Shinpei.
No, no!
Ain't ya the same age as Miss Nagumo?
You're an adult!
Nah, I died when I was in middle school.
Look at Ushio. She started calling me Ryuu right off the bat!
Well, she's just a crazy extrovert.
I'm more the type to stick to myself.
In fact, I hardly ever open up, even to my juniors.
So you maintain this with everyone?
Yeah.
Well, I'm a little better with people my own age.
What about Mio, then?
You two seemed pretty close.
It took a long time to get there.
That's kinda frustrating.
'Kay! I'm gonna stop hidin' my accent!
Huh?!
So feel free ta treat me like an equal, Shinpei!
It's my way of showing respect.
And healthy, respectful distance doesn't mean you're enemies.
No! It's important to get into the spirit of things!
So don't hold back. C—
Come at me, bro!
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Ya just made me interested in getting to know ya more, Ryuunosuke.
Forreal?!
Hold up...
What's that?
A ball?
I recognize this.
It's Haine's ball.
Let's go after it!
Roger!
Ryuunosuke, look at that sign.
Tekram?
Oh, Kobayakawa Market?
What's their deal?
Are they Shadows?
Dunno.
But they don't seem hostile.
Ushio!
Get it together!
What happened?
Shinpei...
My head!
That aura...
Haine?!
I made a promise with Ushio.
The mud that makes up her body is split off from Haine's.
If in the future, Ushio's personality is eliminated and Haine reappears,
I'll kill her.
But if I'm not there anymore, then, Ryuunosuke...
You will have to fulfill my promise for me.
Shinpei, I'm shooting!
I'm shooting!
Okay?
Shinpei...
Wait, Ryuunosuke.
She's saying something.
It's okay now...
It's okay now, Ryuu.
This Haine ain't the bad Haine that killed ya.
Back then, Haine's personality split.
It split into the human girl, Haine, and the Shadow, Hiruko.
Then who's inside ya right now?
Just a little girl who loves sweets.
The girl Miss Nagumo befriended.
Her friend...
Right.
And this girl is...
I.
Haine wants to talk to ya.
Will ya listen?
Thanks.
Nice to meet you.
Summer Time Rendering
You're...
Don't be scared!
We're all Hizuru's friends.
I had the longest dream.
Now I know it was Ushio's memories.
I'm sorry, Shinpei, Ryuunosuke.
Getting involved with me led to so many deaths.
Yers, Hizuru's, Ushio's...
It's all my fault.
Ya don't have to apologize.
It was Hiruko that ate me.
And that's just the sort of being she is.
The one who's really to blame for all of it is Shide.
You're gonna fight with Shide, aren't ya?
This is Tokoyo.
A plane of existence above the world we came from.
Time stands still in Tokoyo.
Shinpei, Ushio, I'm sure the two of ya can see it.
Yeah.
Look at Ryuunosuke.
Ryuu's not shifted ahead in time!
She's right!
And we've been conversing like normal this whole time.
So this was Shide's goal?
Time stands still here, which means I can't loop.
And we can't look two seconds ahead, either.
He wants to use this place to steal Ushio's eye.
The possessor of this awakened eye is able to ascend to a higher dimension.
If he does that, time and space will be at his command.
It's like how us humans,
who live in three dimensions,
can easily pick up, flip, and burn manga,
a world of two dimensions.
Wow!
Whoa, seriously?
It doesn't feel like I can do that at all!
It's only just awakened, and it seems to be unstable.
Y'all are also in Tokoyo.
Only in the mortal realm can its full power be realized.
The ending...
When I scanned Shide's inner body,
his thoughts flew into me.
He wants to destroy the world.
Like pulling the plug on a game console.
Then the world will cease to exist.
A true end...
Th-This sound!
This is the Central District Army.
A large formation of B-29 aircrafts is heading north from the Kii Strait.
Enemy formation is approximately 250 in size.
They have split into five separate units and are headed north.
Currently circling Awaji Island,
one group reportedly went southeast.
To the citizens of Wakayama Prefecture,
we pray for your safety.
It's an air raid siren!
Ushio!
Get down, Ryuu!
Ushio, don't let your shadow touch the ground!
Fire's bad!
Make yer real body as small as possible!
I'm fine. Shadows cant die in Tokoyo.
This ain't nothin'.
Shide.
Struggle all you like, slugs.
Y'all will never reach me.
Ushio.
I'll burn ya to a crisp, then rip that eye from ya.
Getting back on track...
Shide's planning on going back to our world after he takes yer eye, isn't he?
Then that means there's a way to get back!
Makes sense, Shinpei!
Erase Hiruko.
Even with Tokoyo, as long as Ushio holds out, we should be able to do it!
If both Hiruko and Tokoyo are erased,
we can return to your world!
I like the sound of that!
But how?
Shide's so far up.
Leave it to me.
This raid is from Hiruko's memories.
Stop...
Hot...
Body... burning...
Don't... m-make
me r-remember this...
Her memories?
Tokoyo is connected to Hiruko's memories.
Although, this ought to be a day she'd rather forget.
Deal with it.
The pain won't kill ya.
Yer pain will become their pain.
It's Shide! He's forcing her!
Ushio, jump on my signal.
Huh?
I have memories of this day too.
I can at least suppress the memory for a few moments.
But Shide's armor is able to reflect any force directed at it back at the opponent like an echo.
To defeat Shide, we have to hack him,
erase his armor, then kill what's inside.
But erasing the armor will kill Ushio!
No, I ain't dying.
Mio gave me a gift!
No matter what happens,
I'll end this in two blows!
I'll end everything!
Before the last of my hair burns away!
Okay.
It'll only be a few seconds,
but I'll carve a path for ya!
Will you trust me?
I will.
A friend of my sister is a friend of mine.
Ryuunosuke!
Right, Shinpei?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Ready when ya are.
All right.
Now!
I see.
Ya got Haine on yer side, do ya?
I'm counting on ya, Ushio.
Please stop Shide!
Please let Hiruko finally be at peace!
Leave it ta me!
I can't get to Ushio's main body at this altitude.
So fast and heavy!
I can't block them all with my hair!
I'm takin' ya down even if it kills me!
Huh?
What?
He's...
Even if it kills ya, huh?
...completely empty inside!
Shoot!
This ain't gonna be a tie at all!
Did ya figure out my secret, then?
He's gonna bounce back my hack—
She recovered?!
She ate something!
Probably a piece of the original Ushio!
Then, at least...
What did she do to me?!
The air raid stopped.
Wh-What happened?
That one moment of contact erased the memories of the air raid!
Shinpei, can ya hear me?
Ushio?!
I've got it!
Shide's body is in our world!
Our world?!
Shide is controlling that armor remotely through Hiruko!
There's nothing I can do if he's empty inside!
What's going on with Shide's armor right now?
The left half of him I erased is still gone!
Then if ya erase the entire armor, ya win!
Ushio?
Ushio!
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time