SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
Rio-senpai!
Good work!
And the parts?
I got them here in one piece!
They're there if we look for them!
It's so warm.
I feel much better now.
Huh?
Was it your turn to clean the yard today?
I had something I wanted to burn.
Huh?
It's been half a year since Kanata came to this fortress, huh?
She plays well now.
It's because she has a good teacher.
Hot!
Seems I won't be needing my earplugs anymore.
Hey, Madam.
Isn't it a better idea to stay in town this winter?
I'm all right.
I won't die that easily.
I've been living alone on this mountain for 50 years.
DEPARTURE
THE FIRST SNOW
Steady, steady...
Steady... Stop!
It's finally coming together, isn't it?
Can you handle the rest, Noel?
Yeah. I'm happy now.
Let's have some tea, then.
Okay.
Hey, Kureha-chan.
Wait...
Where did it go?
It's supposed to be here...
Hm? Is something wrong?
This is where we keep the army's roster, isn't it?
Kanata said she wanted to know about Her Highness Princess Iliya.
I'm sorry.
If it's not there, I don't know where it could be.
Bummer.
Ah! Naomi-san might have it.
I'll ask her next time.
Okay.
Her Highness Princess Iliya is the eldest daughter of the current Arkadian Archduke.
I think I've told you about this before,
but anyway, she was a very famous tanker.
Claus-san said, "if only she was alive," the other day.
Yeah.
She passed away.
About two years ago, I think.
In the war?
No.
Her Highness was assigned to the Royal Guard division,
but they also put her in charge of boosting national morale,
so she traveled around the country a lot.
And then, as she was returning from a certain town,
she tried to save a child who was drowning in the river.
But, I'm a bit glad...
This is just a rumor, but...
Iliya...
Kanata-san.
Yumina-san,
and, um...
It's me, Kanata.
Um...
Yumina-san...
She brought Yuuko-chan with her...
Ah, Yuuko-chan is Martin-san's daughter.
But, um, old lady Jacott was...
Jacott-san is an old lady living alone in the mountains.
I sometimes buy vegetables from her at the morning market...
Ah, you said the pickles the other day were delicious, right?
She was the one who grew them.
And, um... Jacott-san hasn't been around lately...
She has a weak body, so they're worried about her...
She seems to live deep in the mountains.
And, um-
Jeez, alright already.
I'll hear you out. Wait a bit.
Okay!
In order to improve our relations with the holy city of Rome, Her Highness Princess Iliya...
was to be wed to the emperor.
That's what people were saying.
But that would've made her his third Empress.
The third! His third one, you know?
That's just ridiculous!
She'd be nothing but a hostage.
But then Her Highness passed away, and it all stopped.
In the end, we were still at war until the armistice this year.
Jeez.
We're finally here, huh?
An unfinished house?
Didn't you say she lives by herself?
That's what I heard...
Madam!
I see.
So Yuuko sent you?
Yes.
She's a sweet girl.
She's too good to be that bratty Martin's daughter.
This is a pretty house.
Thank you.
I built this house myself.
Really? That's amazing!
But wait...
What about that house over there?
That house is for my son.
Is he here?
He lives in a faraway town right now.
I'm preparing it so he can come home anytime.
My son and he might have use for it at any given time,
so I need to prepare it properly for them.
When will that son of yours be back, Madam?
He'll be here soon.
Winter will be here soon.
You should get off the mountain before the snow arrives.
That I cannot do.
You see, I must complete that house.
I won't leave this place before it's done,
even if it costs me my life.
But-
Stop this nonsense!
How are your preparations for winter?
Where are your firewood and food stocks?
You haven't prepared any of it, have you?!
I'll get through it somehow.
Thank you for worrying about me, both of you girls.
Madam!
Seriously, she's a hardheaded old lady.
It seems the both of you are similar.
Gimme a break.
How am I-
Well, sometimes, you aren't honest with yourself as well.
Shut up!
Hey, about that letter,
why did you show it to me?
I was informed in last week's scheduled communication,
that the Roman armies along the eastern border
have started to mobilize.
Oh?
It's for old lady Jacott?
Alright then, take these too!
Thank you very much!
By the way,
do you know anything about the peace conference?
I, um...
I'm sorry.
If only Princess Iliya was still alive.
Now that you mention it, Martin,
didn't Princess Iliya have a little sister?
Your change, four million yen!
Hadn't heard that.
Well, she's the Archduke and his mistress's daughter,
so she wasn't talked about much.
She's the third in line for the throne or something like that.
Um, about her sister...
Okay then!
Thank you, come again!
I'm sorry.
Why don't we take a walk?
Say, Kanata.
What kind of place is your hometown?
It's a typical country town.
We have fields, and lots of cattle and goats.
But there aren't many people there.
I think it feels a bit different from this town.
But it's a nice place, isn't it?
I bet your parents were nice, too.
I can tell by looking at you.
What kind of environment were you raised in?
I was raised in a place away from the government complex,
with a beautiful forest and lake.
It was a small town.
I lived there with my mother.
The days we spent were boring,
and nothing special would happen.
The only comfort I looked forward to was my loving sister.
We had different mothers, but she sometimes came to visit us.
She was someone I looked up to.
She was so dignified and kind,
accepting her destiny as a blessing.
She was the one who taught me the trumpet.
But, she was too kind.
She was too kind, and because of it, she lost her life.
At first, I only thought this town was simply inconvenient.
I got lost and ended up here,
and I thought I had finally reached my goal.
But, later I realized something.
This was just another dead end.
That's not true!
I lose my way quite often.
But, I like getting lost.
There's nothing wrong with getting lost!
Or reaching a dead end!
Since, because of that, I met you!
I really envy you sometimes, Kanata.
If only I was as honest with myself as you.
This'll do it.
Why do you care so much about someone like me?
You remind me of my mother.
I don't remember giving birth to someone as pretty as you.
I was born from a forbidden love.
She was always waiting.
Each year, she would wait for him,
without knowing if he was coming or not.
She died living an unfulfilled life.
Why did you decide it was unfulfilled?
Well, that's-!
I'm happy now.
You see, he promised me he'd come back someday.
He'd come take me away someday.
I'm happy with just that promise.
But, that's-
What else do you think I could do?
That's right.
If there was something I could do, I might have done it.
But still...
Are you really okay like that?
Do you truly feel happy with that?
Because I have memories of my love for him.
Because I have memories of him.
Because I have hope that I can meet him again someday.
That's more than enough for me.
I had a feeling it'd snow.
The first time I met you, it was a snowy day like today, wasn't it?
Back when Madam was still young,
Seize was prospering as a resort town.
She fell in love with a young merchant.
Soon afterwards, she gave birth to his child.
But, he already had a family.
It was a blessing for him,
since his legal wife couldn't bear a child.
He took their child and returned to his hometown.
He promised her he'd come back someday and take her away.
Madam!
At this age, I think back at times.
"What if, back then..."
Jacott-san!
You know, life consists of losing something again and again.
But you must gain something first, before you can lose it.
The greater the happiness gained,
the greater the suffering when lost.
But, as long as we have memories of that happiness...
It's because of those memories that we can continue living.
Oh, yeah.
I know this isn't the best time,
but I found Princess Iliya's picture.
Naomi-san!
It's okay, Filicia.
I think it was about five years ago when the Princess visited Seize.
Isn't this Shuko?
Rio-senpai!
The truth is, my parents wanted to marry me off,
so that someone could inherit the family business.
But then, I heard that trumpet's melody.
I couldn't forget it, no matter what.
She was...
Iliya-san, wasn't she?
So you've met her too, after all.
How wonderful is this?
Iliya-san's note resounds within me.
And then, we met each other.
Maybe I was running away by coming to this town,
so I didn't think about it too much in the beginning.
I thought that I'd leave this town eventually anyway.
But now, I honestly don't want to leave this place.
I guess that's why I must go.
I can do it.
Because, there's something only I can do.
This isn't farewell.
Because no matter how far apart we are...
The note will resound.
The note will resound, and...
It will connect us.
Kanata, was I a good senior to you?
Yes!
And so, that's how Senpai came to leave us.
She left behind a very beautiful sound of the sky
that will resound in my heart, forever.
Resonate the feelings of love and friendship
Let's perform the important things
I cried when I was happy
I laughed when I was hurt
But, they're all proof that I'm alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me what you truly want
You're just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I know, You know little happy
I want them to echo forever
Can you hear my precious note?
Speaking endless words touched by love
This is our harmony
I can hear our harmony
A VISITOR - A BURNING FIELD OF SNOW
Next episode: A Visitor - A Burning Field of Snow
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.