Hey! Are you seriously
never going to sing again?
I'll transform you as many
times as you want!
She's not transforming!
Why?
Unless Mitsuki has the desire,
we won't be able to transform her
with our Death Spirit powers.
No way.
Mitsuki...
IS FULL MOON RETIRING AT LAST?!
Full Moon...
What in the world is up with her?
Madoka, it's time for rehearsal.
Okay!
- Good morning!
Good morning!
Hey, hey, have you heard the news?
Full Moon is finally retiring.
Yeah, I heard that the record company
is already searching for a new artist.
Really? Maybe I'll bring
them a demo tape!
What? Now?!
Hey!
Do me a favor and stop
spreading random rumors!
There's no way she'd retire!
Full Moon isn't the kind of girl
who would give up that easily!
Got it?!
Oh... Yes.
Madoka...
Gimme a break!
Running off their mouths like that!
I don't know what
it is with you,
but I suggest you do something about
that strong-headed manner of speaking.
I take after you in strong-headedness.
Oh, Ms. Oshige!
Oh, Ms. Imamura.
What are you doing here today?
Full Moon is off, right?
Yes. I came to pick up the fan letters
that were sent here to the program.
Oh, I see.
- If I remember correctly,
- Please give her my best regards too.
that woman is
Full Moon's manager.
Thank you.
Well, see you.
Ms. Imamura...
Yes? What is it?
What's my schedule for today?
You're free for
the rest of the day.
Great!
Huh?
Nothing. Thank you!
If I trail her, I might be
able to find out something.
Hey! If you don't hurry,
I'll leave you behind!
Yes?
It's Oshige.
Kamiyama?
This is Full Moon's house?
I see, so they've
gone to the hospital.
I'm sorry that you went
out of your way to visit.
It's no problem.
I'll come by again another day.
She still has the fan letters.
Maybe it wasn't here after all.
Huh?
That's that girl from back then.
So this is that girl's house?
Are you tired?
Yes.
Mitsuki, you must eat for
the sake of your health.
Okay.
Do you think you can
eat something today?
I'll bring you some fruit later.
Ms. Tanaka.
Yes?
Please bring Mitsuki
some fruit later.
Yes.
Umm... Ma'am?
What is it?
How was the hospital?
M-Ma'am?
Did you find it?
Who are those guys?
Hey!
Oh, Takuto! Where were you,
slacking off like that?
More importantly, look at that.
Hey, hey.
Madoka Wakamatsu? Why?!
Hey, you!
Madoka?
Can I come in?
I can, right?
Sorry!
I was so surprised to see you here!
I couldn't help but say hello!
Are you not feeling well?
Do you have a fever?
Oh, you don't have a fever!
Am I bothering you?
Do you want me to leave?
No.
I didn't think so! After all,
you're a fan of mine, right?
You must be thrilled because I came
to visit you when you're sick, right?
Dear Grandma, I met with
Dr. Herberd the other day.
I was very happy to hear that
I might recover from my illness.
The landscape here in America
is very expansive
and it makes me
feel very small.
Next time, I'd like to come
here with you, Grandma.
Mitsuki.
That song...
That's my song!
Well, I guess Full Moon
sings it too.
Speaking of, Full Moon's manager
dropped by this house.
How do you know her?
You don't feel well, do you?
What happened to all that energy
you had that last time
when you were talking
so big to me?
But it's really weird, isn't it?
That Full Moon has suddenly
taken time off from work.
You and Full Moon...
I was thinking that I wouldn't
be where I am today
if it hadn't been
for both of you.
You probably wouldn't
understand this,
but Full Moon is a girl
who really pisses me off.
She seems to be
so full of confidence.
I'm looking forward to
knocking her down someday.
Do you understand
what I mean?
What I'm saying is that if
Full Moon weren't around,
I would lose sight of what
I'm aspiring to right now.
So that's how Madoka
sees Full Moon.
So it seems. In those days this girl
was so strong it even surprised us.
And moreover,
I'd really be depressed
if a cheeky girl like you who told me
that I have my own song lost her vitality.
Madoka...
Huh? What? What?
Full Moon...no longer exists.
Huh?
Come on... Don't talk nonsense!
Hurry up and get well.
Is there anything I can do?
Shall I sing you a song?
Mitsuki!
What's the matter?
Are you all right?
Mitsuki, are you all right?
I'm so sorry!
I invited myself in.
Hey, hang in there!
Mitsuki, be strong!
Ma'am?
U-Umm...
They're asking whether
you have a regular hospital.
A regular hospital?
Dr. Wakaoji, I cannot entrust her
to you any longer.
From now on, please stay
out of our family's affairs.
Of course,
I will switch hospitals as well!
Please take us to
Dr. Wakaoji's hospital!
Mitsuki, you'll be all right now!
You're at the hospital now!
Doctor,
we're ready for her now.
All right.
Mitsuki...
I am not in that girl's heart.
Isn't there anything I can do?
We must have Mitsuki
live out her life span!
But it would be cruel to force her
to continue living in this state.
This is the first time I've had to
deal with...such an exhausting case.
That's not true!
Even if her life is short,
making her feel that it was worth living
is part of our job too, right?!
That hurts, Takuto!
Don't say such
irresponsible things!
That's impossible.
We're Death Spirits! There's no way
we would be able to do that!
Takuto, you idiot!
Ma'am, I will go get
her clothes and things.
All right.
Oh?
Umm... How is she?
It seems her condition
has stabilized.
What a relief.
Well, I better go now.
You there.
I'm sorry about inviting myself in
to see your granddaughter.
I had no idea that
she was that ill.
Are you a friend of
Mitsuki's from before?
Mitsuki?
I didn't know her name was Mitsuki.
I see. Is that what happened?
Yes. Thanks to Mitsuki,
I was inspired to persevere.
Until then I thought
I would quit singing, but...
I think...that everyone
has a unique song.
There's a song for Full Moon.
But I think that there's also
a song that only you can sing.
I want to hear your song.
It made me think that if there is
somebody out there who says
they want to hear my song,
I should sing.
It made me think that I should try
and persevere just a little longer.
Mitsuki's passion for song...
is what gave this girl strength.
Grandma...
Please listen to
my songs someday!
I've never properly listened
to Mitsuki's singing.
Dr. Wakaoji.
Mrs. Koyama...
Mitsuki... I beg you,
please help Mitsuki.
I will, with my body and soul.
I will do everything within
my power to help her.
Please, grant my request!
If you are going to that extent
to ask me, Wakaoji,
it will be risky for the hospital.
But let me try
to do something.
Thank you very much.
However,
there is one problem.
Our job is to cure people's
illnesses and save lives.
But unless the patient has
the desire to live or to get better
no matter how much effort we put into it
or how expensive our facilities are,
we will not be able to
cure their illness.
Yes.
I will exert every possible effort
to give Mitsuki hope.
I do understand what
Meroko is saying.
There's no meaning in giving her
hope to live at this point,
when the span of her life
is almost up.
But still, continuing this way
won't do either!
This is...
But...that girl's smiles
were all for Eichi.
She was overflowing with
the desire to see Eichi.
That idiot! He should have stayed alive
until he and Mitsuki reunited!
All those smiles were for you, Eichi.
So you... You can't die!
Damn it!
Jeez... Why in the world did I
become a Death Spirit!
Th-There it is again!
What was that just now?
What happened to me?
What lovely flowers.
I'm so sorry.
She just fell asleep.
Don't worry about it.
I just dropped by to see how she was.
I'm so relieved to see that
her condition has stabilized.
Get better soon, okay?
Well, I'll drop by again.
If you're leaving,
let me show you to the door.
Don't worry about it!
That's the least I can do.
The two that you
were concerned about...
It looks like they're
doing all right now.
But...where did your heart go?
Did it freeze up in that snow?
Don't my words reach you?
Mitsuki... Wake up!
Please wake up and sing!
Let's sing together again
one more time, okay?
Okay, Mitsuki?!
W-Was that just now...
a memory of when I was alive?
You understand what will
happen to you if you recover
your memory in this state,
don't you?
You will become a ghost
who wanders all alone.
Why am I remembering this
all of a sudden?
I didn't want to die!
I really didn't want to die!
Why is it?
Why am I feeling these things?
Why am I crying?
Why am I so sad?
What exactly did I do
when I was alive?!
Takuto?
What's the matter, Takuto?
Shut up!
Please leave me alone!
Takuto!
What is...Takuto thinking?
I don't understand
what he's thinking.
That's a lie.
I do understand.
Even I know that
Takuto loves Mitsuki.
It's so painful.
What don't you like about me?
Somebody tell me. Please!
You're late, Mero.
I thought you would come sooner.
I don't know
what's what anymore.
Izumi, will you hear me out?
Of course, Mero.
I never thought it would be so
painful to keep that girl alive
for the duration
of her life span.
But Takuto doesn't understand
how I feel at all.
And...why are you hesitating?
That's not like you, Mero.
What do you mean?
Well, it's our job to adhere
to the schedule.
But if it's for you, Mero,
I wouldn't mind reaping that girl's life.
Meroko! What in the world
were you thinking?
I can't believe you
would ask Izumi!
Then what should I have done?!
I don't know what to do anymore.
Meroko...
At this rate,
everyone is going to be unhappy.
I can't stand by and watch anymore!
I hate it! It's all so painful!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Izumi's Temptation."
- Look forward to it!