I'll rely on others!
There it is!
So this is...
the Dollars?
What the hell?!
Don't tell me they're all...
For example...
Marrying me.
You're still keeping our secret.
Celty.
This is more fun than I expected.
Screaming even louder!
I was born here!
Give Celty back!
I have to thank you.
If it weren't for you, my sister probably would've locked her in a tiny research lab again.
Yagiri-kun...
Are you okay?
Anyway, return Celty to me.
We need to escape before the cops come.
That doesn't justify your actions!
What do you know about me?
I've been watching her ever since I was a child.
I wanted to liberate her,
give her freedom in this vast world,
and then live together with her.
That's all I've thought about.
It's been the only thing on my mind.
Oh, man...
No one can stop the power of love.
And what's up with you?
You've always relied on the masses.
My love won't be crushed by something like this!
It's futile!
I feel pain, but I choose to ignore it.
My life with Celty has no use for pain!
That's how I can ignore the pain you inflict!
You're nuts!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
Seiji-san can be strict, violent, and strange,
but he's definitely not a bad person!
He already has someone he loves.
No...
It can't be.
So... don't kill him.
No, no, it can't be!
Wait, she's...
That's not my head!
This girl... Her name is...
Harima Mika-san.
Right?
You're the Harima Mika-san that Yagiri-kun supposedly killed, aren't you?
You're kidding me.
Hey...
That's a lie, isn't it?
I'm so sorry!
Hey, hey! You're in there, aren't you, Seiji-san?
I'm here as well today!
Oh, gosh, your door's locked.
How am I supposed to come in?
Hey, are you sleeping?
Say, do you remember?
I sat next to you during the exam.
The guy next to me had a pretty cool name, "Ryuugamine."
Then, when I looked to see who was on my left,
I fell in love with you at first sight!
And you smiled when our eyes met!
So please let me see you!
Pretty, pretty please!
Oh, are you feeling sick?
Is that why you won't open the door?
Then I'll open it for you!
Hang on a moment!
And here we go!
I've investigated you ever since that day.
Your birthday, your family...
S-Seiji-san...
You saw it.
U-Um... I...
I won't tell anyone about this.
U-Um...
I swear!
I'll get in sync with your hobbies, no matter what they are!
S-So...
It's okay.
Seiji-san...
Seiji-san?
It's okay.
I'm sorry!
I wasn't dead!
And then your sister...
Do you want Seiji to love you?
Good girl.
Then...
Then there was this doctor.
He said, "With some plastic surgery and makeup, you can look like that head—
exactly like the head Seiji-san loves."
"Your name is Celty,
because that's the name of the head."
That's why I tried to become Celty for you.
But then, Namie-san said that wasn't enough.
She said that you'd figure it out quickly,
so I had to take pills and undergo surgery to erase my emotions and memories.
But I didn't want to forget anything about you!
Someone who knows my name...
A doctor that knows that I'm a Dullahan...
There's only one person in this city!
I just wanted to be with you!
That's why I went through all this!
No way. You're lying...
Then I'm...
Well, you weren't even capable of telling her apart from the real one.
So much for your love.
Nice going.
Seiji-san!
Um...
I think it's pretty amazing that you put your life on the line to get her back.
I misunderstood you.
It's true that her personality has some problems,
but she's not a stalker after all.
You risked your life for her, Yagiri-kun.
I don't think an egotistical person would do that.
It's really amazing to love someone who tried to kill you.
In many ways...
I think you two are really similar.
Welcome back.
"What's the meaning of this?"
And then you'd say,
"You knew my head was in that research lab.
You and your father have been helping Yagiri Pharmaceuticals from the very start.
Perhaps your father was the one who stole my head!
You hid that from me, and even performed plastic surgery on that severely injured girl.
I may be a monster, but you're a monster that feasts on others!"
Something along those lines?
I'll say this now to avoid any misunderstandings:
I don't know if my father stole your head, and I'm not interested in knowing.
And I only performed plastic surgery on her because she wanted it.
Maybe the people working for Yagiri forced her into it.
Either way, it's none of my business.
"Can you read my mind?"
Yes, I can.
I've loved you for twenty years.
Of course I can do that much.
What the hell?
Then why didn't you ever tell me about this?
Because I love you.
That's why I kept quiet.
If you found your head, you'd go somewhere else.
I couldn't bear that.
I'd never say something like, "I'll just give up to make you happy."
This is a war with our love at stake.
I'll never let go of you.
To keep you, I'll use the love and death of others.
And even my own.
This might sound like an oxymoron, but I'll even use your feelings.
Even if I get my head back, I won't leave you.
You may think that,
but that doesn't mean your head will too.
I've thought about this.
Why are you, a fairy, revealing herself to humans?
Didn't you reincarnate into this world because you lost your head?
Then, when you regain your head and your memories,
the time we've spent together will dissolve like smoke, like a mirage.
I'm afraid of that.
Will you believe me?
I will.
To be exact, you're the only one I can believe.
I'm scared too.
I'm scared of death.
I'm aware that no one can kill me right now.
I'm not boasting.
I've accepted this as a simple fact.
I'm not happy or thrilled about it.
But...
No, that's precisely why I'm scared.
There's no core in me that governs my death.
My head is that core.
If someone destroys my head,
then I will, regardless of the situation and any decision I'd like to make...
Do you believe me?
Although I lack eyes and a brain, I have nightmares.
Do you believe that I tremble in fear after those nightmares?
Because I'm afraid of that, and because I want to have some control over my death,
I've been searching for my head.
Would you believe me if I said that?
Didn't I tell you?
You're the only one I believe.
I'm totally confused.
We were just being stubborn because of stupid assumptions.
That's so dumb.
Say, Shinra.
Yes?
Let me punch you.
Sure.
Then let me hit you as well.
See.
You're prettiest without your helmet.
That punch was my pledge of a marriage kiss.
Are you crying?
That was really unexpected.
Hey, Izaya.
'Sup, Dotachin. Fancy seeing you here.
Stop calling me that.
Hey, do you know where the name "Dollars" came from?
Something like, "Give me your money"?
Nope.
This organization doesn't really do anything.
It comes from the laziness of a "doll," hence "Dollars."
That's it.
Dotachin! Did you see that?!
The black bike!
Man, was that for real?!
So I wasn't hallucinating!
Does that mean it was CG?
That CG is part of the Dollars.
Wowzers!
Really?
Wowzers! Wowzers!
To be honest, I'm really surprised.
I knew a lot of people on the Internet claimed to be part of the Dollars.
But I didn't expect so many of them to gather just because someone said to.
Humans never cease to amaze me.
Oh, you might dream about escaping your ordinary life,
but life here in Tokyo becomes ordinary after about six months.
If you want more excitement, you could try wandering off to some other country,
or get involved with something underground.
But even that would probably become ordinary after three days.
If you truly want to escape your ordinary life, you have to continue evolving.
Whether your goal is is above you or below you.
Just enjoy your days.
Oh...
To show my respect, I'll give you Yagiri Namie's phone number as a freebie.
And I won't sell the information that you're the founder of the Dollars.
It's your organization.
You should use it whenever you want.
Izaya!
It's time to go.
Good luck, Tanaka Tarou-kun!
Wait, you punkass!
Izaya!
Huh? It couldn't be.
The next day was painfully ordinary.
For him...
and for him...
and for that boy as well.
Hey, Mikado.
I saw it on the Net.
The Dollars gathered last night!
And... and... Shizuo and Simon are both members of the Dollars!
And the rider of the black bike has no head and drove down a building.
Then she hocus-pocused a scythe and boom, there was black fog everywhere!
It was so frickin' awesome, man!
You're not making any sense.
And for them as well.
I don't love you.
But as long as I see your face, I won't forget that I love her.
That's why I'll accept your love...
until I get her back.
'Sup, guys.
Hey! I've been waiting.
Ah, thanks.
I'm kind of sleepy tonight, so I'll pass out a bit early.
Not enough sleep? How come? Did you pull an all-nighter?
Yeah, something like that.
Looks like Kanra-san isn't here yet.
I wonder if he'll come.
Argh, something came up.
I see.
Sorry, I've got to go.
Later.
Sorry for being a party pooper.
There's an urgent job.
No problem.
And so, my life went back to normal.
As always, I still run into people I don't want to see.
You seem relieved.
People are afraid of ghosts because they sneak around and stuff.
But you gave such a fancy performance there.
No one will fear you anymore.
Oh yeah, you ended up not killing anyone.
What's with that scythe? It can't cut anything?
Or are you still looking for that girl?
Let me know when you need my help.
Just give me a call.
Bye.
I don't know where Yagiri Namie is.
Not that I care.
I'm me.
There's nothing I need.
The days have returned to normal.
Normal days without hope or despair.
The same old thing.
Yet, I feel so... full.
I'm here.
And you're there.
If I'm your salvation, then you're mine.
And the boy falls into deep thought about Orihara Izaya's words.
Would he, who wishes for an impossible reality, be able to find a new reality that lasts forever?
More so, would that eternity just become part of his everyday life again?
I'm sorry for what I did.
Thanks.
Hey! That's my place.
There's an empty seat behind the class rep.
What the hell?
You come out of nowhere and take my seat.
She most likely won't hang out with Harima Mika anymore.
Only she knows whether that's good or bad.
But is it true?
Is it true that people don't understand their own feelings?
"You have to continue to evolve."
That man's words still echo in his head.
The boy thought he was capable of anything after such a bold act.
But he didn't know...
how much courage he needed to ask his female classmate out.
Thirty seconds till he sees her.
Thirty-five seconds till he sees his best friend hitting on her.
Forty-five seconds till he kicks his best friend away.
Seventy-four seconds till the girl declines his offer.
Seventy-eight seconds till the girl asks him to join her for lunch on the roof.
How long will it take for him to fall in love with her?
How long will it take for him to confess?
You sure did something silly there, huh?
You sacrificed everything for your brother's twisted love.
Oh, or should I say, your twisted love for your brother?
Anyway, don't things look grim for you?
Nebula is merging with your company.
You know, if you leave with that,
the mafia, or some skilled sniper, will put a hole between your eyebrows.
Checkmate!
A garbage truck?
Yes, the usual collectors.
Roger.
Hello?
Things got a bit complicated.
Can you leave that room?
Can't they make a rule where the kings fight one-on-one?
I think your uncle was like me.
Not believing in the next world, fearing death more than anyone else,
and thirsting for Heaven.
However, I'm certain now:
The next world exists.
Let's leave it at that.
Usually Dullahans are female.
Do you know why?
No.
The researchers were looking into it,
but I thought it was a complete waste of time.
So you're a rationalist.
Anyway, putting that aside,
there's a heaven called "Valhalla."
Well, not exactly.
In Norse mythology, armored female angels called Valkyries
guide the souls of gallant warriors to Valhalla.
A woman comes to pick up the dead.
Doesn't that sound familiar?
They say that Valkyries are Dullahans.
If that's true, I'm sure this is waiting for it.
For its awakening.
For the clocks to sound war.
To find the sacred warrior she'll invite to Valhalla.
The reason it doesn't open its eyes, even though it's alive, is because this isn't a battlefield.
I'd love to be chosen, if possible.
What should I do if Valhalla, the afterlife, really exists?
I doubt I'd excel on the battlefield.
Then maybe I'll start a war that only I can fight.
Right?
Man, I'm such a lucky bastard.
Without believing in Heaven, I've lived a life equivalent to it.
And I even met the fallen Angel of Death too.
These are merely your deductions.
"Believe, and thou shalt be saved."
And this is just for insurance.
Even if it's Hell, where only torment awaits me...
I don't care as long as I can live there.
But if possible, I'd love to go to Heaven.
So Namie-san,
let's all go to Heaven!
I'll keep this as a member of the Dollars.
Hide a tree in the forest.
I doubt Celty would think that her head is in the same organization as she is.
Oh, hey. Why don't you join the Dollars too?
Our leader is like, "Invite whoever comes near you."
Though I was the one who started recruiting people halfway through.
Let's make the fallen angel fly again.
Right?
Nothing happens in her ordinary life.
Nothing changes.
Even though something new is born in the city every day,
while something else disappears.
Next time: Sudden Turn.