Because your echoing voice
will stir up the wind
When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Miss.
Come on a date with me.
April 30, 2008
Night Duty Room – Hakuou Academy Noon
What with it being Golden Week and
all, the Academy sure is quiet.
It's great that I got my own homeroom,
but I need a pay raise to go with it.
Man, what a drag!
I can't even get into the
mood to grade the tests!
Well, guess I'll have a drink.
Cheers!
For Golden Week, ya gotta go to Hawaii!
Gardens of the Saginomiya Residence 1:00pm
What the heck?! I was puttin' up with
the chill and buildin' up the mood here!
Now, now, Nagi and the others are going
to the Aegean Sea this year, after all.
Why didn't ya go with 'em?
Well, I felt I should not
intrude on those two...
Uh-huh, I suppose that makes sense.
We're gonna get every volume of the
shows the boss said he wanted to watch!
Rental Video Tachibana 1:30pm
Yes, sir!
Wh-What do they want?
The "Godfather" series maybe?
Or "Battles Without Honor and Humanity"?
If it's direct-to-video V-Cinema
stuff, getting it all will be tough.
Do you have all the for-rental
videos of "Brave Exkaiser"?
Half won't do.
Huh?
Is that all?
We've got it.
Then, what 'bout videos of
"Superhuman-Machine Metalder"?
We've got it!
Yer good.
If you want, we've got all
of "Fight!! Ramenman", too.
We'll be back.
Sanzenin Residence 2:00pm
So, the main stage today will be Mykonos
Island, where the Miss is vacationing.
Which means those of us stuck at
home will have no more scenes.
Well, a nice long break for
once might not be so bad...
I thought I just heard someone talking...
Oh, crap.
I must be hearing things.
But what's a nice long break when
it comes in the final episode?
What?! For real?!
I'm hearing things again.
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
Wow! So this is the Aegean Sea!
Come, Miss, you hurry up, too!
Mykonos Island, Greece
Come to think of it, this is your
first time on Mykonos, isn't it?
Yes! I often used to go deep-sea
fishing in the cold seas,
so I've been to Iturup Island and
those kinds of places, though.
I'm surprised you didn't get arrested.
Miss, the ocean is incredibly beautiful!
The Clear Black LCD of the TV
is beautiful, too, so I'm fine.
When did the Miss become like that?
Who knows? She has always been like that.
Though, some of it really can't be helped.
Isn't there anything we could do for her?
Cappadocia, Turkey
Wow, so this is Cappadocia!
I think this is what they mean when
they talk about magnificent views!
Wow, so people used to
live among those rocks.
Hey, look, look, Hina, that sort
of looks like a camel's hump.
Wow, it really does look like a camel's hump!
Huh?
That's a real camel!
Honestly! Enough with the jokes!
Come enjoy the scenery from this
high vantage point a little.
I'm fine! I'm fine right here!
Hina?
You know I don't like high places, Ayumu!
You say you don't like high places,
but you were able to get on the plane.
But I was totally asleep before we took off!
I'm not getting up until we
land, no matter what happens!
Now that you mention it, you didn't
have anything to eat on the flight.
Even though it was 13 hours long...
Anyway, scenery is something you
enjoy from a lower altitude!
Oh, you're hopeless.
We came all the way here on vacation,
but you don't seem very excited.
There's no reason to get excited.
Then let's go outside. Outside!
You'll get more excited under the blue sky!
It's hot.
Then are you going to stay
inside for the whole trip?
Yeah.
I see.
There, there. We can go shopping
together or something later.
But, but, the Miss...
Uh, that's not something I can change...
It's fine. I'll stay here
the whole time, too.
Oh, dear...
Oh, sheesh! Fine!
Tomorrow, I'll go out in the morning for you!
What?
R-Really?!
Yes. But just for a bit, all right?
Just for a bit.
Yes, Miss!
I'm sorry you always have
to go to such trouble.
Not at all.
Time flies. It's already
a month into the new term.
Please take care of Nagi for me.
I will.
And the Miss is becoming
more used to the new class.
I see.
I would like for her to finally
properly attend school this year.
Y-Yes, well...
The developmental technology
for UFOs got sold!
We're back!
We're back.
Welcome back! How was Cappadocia?
It had long lashes, a split
nose, and it spit on me.
That was the real camel.
Onto Greece tomorrow, huh?
I'm looking forward to the Parthenon.
It's a one-story building.
But it's built on top of the Acropolis.
But we'll be going to
Mykonos Island after that.
Yeah, Hayata and the others
are there, too, right?
What?
Ooh, so this is Athens!
This is incredible! You can see
the whole city from the Parthenon!
The Parthenon, Greece
I think this view definitely
deserves to be a World Heritage!
Wait...
Hina, why are you intently
looking only at the temple?
This temple is the World Heritage!
The view has nothing to do with it!
Sheesh, there you go again.
You're missing out if you
don't enjoy this view.
I'm fine! I told you, I'm fine!
Hina...
I don't need to see views from high places!
Where are Miki and the others
anyway?! Where are they?!
If it's sightseeing, you could
just bring them instead.
All three of them said they got tired of
sights like this back in kindergarten.
Those damn bourgeois girls...
And they partied hard yesterday,
so they asked to be left
at the hotel to sleep
until it's time to take the
ship to Mykonos Island.
As for that, you were
partying hard, too, Ayumu.
So why are you so energetic?
Because this is my first trip with you.
This is a trip to deepen
our friendship, right?
What?
Why is it?
For some reason, I always end
up in high places with Ayumu.
A-About Hayate?
What's wrong?
So? Where's the view good from?
Huh?
Oh, um... The view in this direction is...
D-Don't let go of my hand! Don't let go!
I won't.
Wow!
It's like we've come to a magical land, Miss.
Well, it's true that this view
hasn't changed in a long time.
It's as if time has stopped for this town.
What? Does that mean you've been here before?
More like, we used to live here.
Both Maria and I have spent
more time abroad than in Japan.
Though, no matter where we
went, you were always shut-in.
Shut up!
But you really should stop being so withdrawn
and become a child who plays
under the sun as children should.
What?
Huh? I-Is something the matter?
No, just thinking there was a guy who
once said something like that, too.
I don't even remember what he looked like,
but he was a thief and a liar, and
a guy who couldn't keep a promise.
My hat...
Please leave it to me, Miss!
Here you are, Miss. As you
can see, your hat is safe...
Miss...?
Um...
Have you shrunk, Miss?
What a thing to say to
someone you've just met!
I may not look it, but I am
growing swiftly every day!
P-Pardon me. I mistook you for someone else.
I swear! Give that back!
This is my hat!
Y-You cannot take that!
Because that hat belongs to Miss Nagi.
So it is mine!
So this hat belongs to me,
Nagi Sanzenin, right?!
What?!
It can't be! This bitsy kid is Miss Nagi?!
Don't call me bitsy!
Which means... No... Just because
anything can happen in this anime...
Surely not!
I've suddenly time traveled to the past?!
No, no matter what, that can't possibly be!
No, there's just no way!
P-Please excuse me.
What is today's date?
Peperoncino?
Neapolitan, spaghettino carbonara?
Ack! He's a foreigner, so
I can't understand him!
So long, commoner.
I am in a hurry. Do not make any
more trouble for anyone else.
Oh, wait!
Please wait!
What are you doing?! Are
you a kidnapper, too?!
I-I'm not! I'm no kidnapper...
I swear! Let go!
I swear, it's because of people like you...
At any rate... At any rate, why
did I travel into the past?
If I can figure that out...
This is why I do not want to go outside!
What?!
Oh! Miss!
P-Please wait!
Please wait, Miss.
I need to switch up my thinking.
If this is the past and this child
is the Miss as a little girl...
If I start now...
If I start now, I can fix
that super-indoor lifestyle!
And if I do, she might
be able to become a girl,
who genuinely feels moved by
the blue oceans and skies!
Hey, commoner, what are you
smirking about all on your own?
I'll do it! It'll be fine!
I know I can do it!
I will use my abilities to change the Miss!
So, Miss...
Come on a date with me.
Huh?
In the end, a first class lady should be a
child who plays under the sun as children should.
So please come spend a little time with me.
W-Well, I won't mind, but...
Will you be all right?
With what?
Well, how to put it...
I'm being targeted by Mafia
kidnappers right now.
What are you doing being targeted
by bona fide Sicilian Mafia?!
Easy for you to ask! It's
a problem for me, too!
Barbeque, hotcake, soft serve ice cream!
"I've lost visual on target!"
"Send the next assassin."
Italian stallion.
I swear...
This is why I do not like going outside!
I see!
It's because she's had experiences
like this since she was little...
That's why she stays indoors like that.
I know, Miss! Let us go to the
ocean together to go stargazing!
Huh?
Fool.
These things always happen to me.
I do not wish to go outside.
It'll be fine.
In the past or the future,
I will always protect you.
So let us go together...
Come with me to go stargazing.
All right! Then it is a promise!
It will be all right.
How about we take those guys
out before we go stargazing?
Take those guys out?
How in the world will you do that?
You have nothing to worry about.
Now, call the police!
For all the cool posturing, you're
awfully reliant on others.
Pacific saury are cheap today!
"Not so fast!"
Miss!
Ich liebe dich!
"We're going after them!"
Comment allez-vous!
"They're not getting away!"
It will be all right!
I will protect you, without fail!
"Where did they go?!"
Lady Erika!
"Find them!"
Ebi-chan!
Leah Dizon!
"Don't let them get away!"
You're pretty good.
What?
I have faith in you!
Miss...
Yes, Miss!
"Prepare to meet your fate!"
Cabaret club!
I'm going to borrow this!
Nabeshin, Nabeshin?!
"Uh, where did they disappear to?!"
Goddamn!
"What has my life been..."
It is all over, Miss.
I am sorry.
I have put holes in your precious hat.
That's fine. It's a testament
to how you protected me.
If you had not saved me,
I may have died here.
Could it be... The reason I was
summoned to the past was...
Then, as promised, shall we do
some stargazing here together?
My hat...
Call my name so that it reaches me
Because your echoing voice
will stir up the wind
Liar...
Liar
Reach out that hand to hold mine
It'll bring a smile to my face
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Hayate!
Miss?
What happened? Where did you go?
...look at the present and start walking
Both Maria and I have been
worried for you all this time.
And what are you doing here, Miss?
Huh?
Uh... W-Well, what does it matter?
Liar
I was just getting back at
that idiot, who made me cry.
At a brisk pace, all alone
Without even noticing what color the sky was
The time difference between Mykonos
Island and Japan is minus 7 hours.
I simply walked
Right about now, they are probably gazing
upon the beautiful starry sky of the Aegean Sea.
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
And yet, we alone must remain at home...
Are you trying to comfort me, Tama?
Well, thanks to that, I have
this quality time with you now.
The sense of continually seeking
We have never gone stargazing
just the two of us.
Used to darken my days
Not that I want to gaze up at
Nerima's murky night sky with you.
I see, I see, so you're lonely, too!
Until the day I met you
Aw, there, there! There, there!
These children are my life. Just kidding...
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
What the heck? Yer still up?
Yes.
Do you suppose Hayate is also gazing upon
the same starry night sky on Mykonos Island?
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Maybe. But the sky over there's
probably filled with more stars.
Yes...
When we start walking, the
world will come to our side
That is the constellation Boötes.
Next to it is the Big Dipper.
And beyond that is...
Oh? There is a leak in the roof there.
Darn it.
Someday, I'll take you to see the
starry night sky of the Aegean Sea.
Morning will come
And we'll feel the wind...
Yes, I will be looking forward to it.
What were you thinking about, Hina?
Just wondering if Nagi and the others
are looking at the same stars, too.
I was, too!
For you, I will remain by your side
Oh, Nagi. She said she was going to look
for Hayate and that was the last...
All through the flowering season
And for all time beyond that
Goodness, the stars certainly are
beautiful, aren't they, Miss?
Going stargazing outside once
in a while isn't so bad.
It's my wish to stay with you
Thank you... for protecting me.
What?
I mean...
I'll be counting on you in the future, too.
Yes, I look forward to it!
Namae yonde boku ni todoku-youmi
Call my name so that it reaches me
Hibiku koe wa kaze o okosu kara
Because your echoing voice will stir up the wind
Daijoubu
It'll be okay
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Arukidasu toki sekai ga mikata ni kawaru
When we start walking, the world will come to our side
Asa ga kuru
Morning will come
Bokura wa kaze o kanjite...
And we'll feel the wind...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
See you!