Huh?
The Mirror Lovies!
Give it a try!
The princess!
Princess Ann!
It has been some time, Cure Sword.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Ai's Being Stubborn!
Begin Operation Brush Those Teeth!
Even now, I am yet unable to awaken from my icy prison.
I may have little power left in me,
but there is one thing that I simply must tell you.
What is it that you must tell us, Princess?
It's about the infant you're raising, Ai.
Princess, it's an honor to meet you!
I'm Oogai First Middle School's student council president, Aida Mana!
Princess, you're familiar with Ai?
But your fiancé, Jonathan Klondike,
told us he had found Ai's egg by a river!
Shh!
You could wake Ai!
She has two duties to fulfill.
Her first is to act as a fairy to grant the Precures power.
And her second...
is to act as a shield to repel the power of darkness.
A shield?
The Selfish can take hold of any human.
By expanding the self-centered, egotistical part of their hearts,
they can increase their numbers, as I'm sure you're aware.
Yes... Charles told us.
Kyupirappa!
Ai can use the power of light to repel the source of the Selfish's power, Egogy.
Ai has such a wondrous power?
I can't believe it!
Should that shield's power deteriorate,
the Selfishes would attack with ever-increasing vigor!
I believe you've already seen the effects yourself.
We did!
So that was why Ira and Mammo grew so powerful!
But why did Ai's power deteriorate all of a sudden?
Because she's entered her grumpy phase.
Her grumpy phase?
When babies first begin to assert themselves.
"I hate this, I hate that," they selfishly cry, bringing much grief to their parents.
But it's an essential step towards adulthood that all babies must take.
True, my mother said something like that...
The deciding factor between her growing to be a happy, energetic child,
or a self-centered, egotistical one...
will be how you raise her.
Please, wait!
What'll happen if Ai turns into a selfish child?
Her mysterious power will vanish, and the shield will be no more.
Oh no!
Please...
Please, raise Ai with...
She is the world's final h...
Wait, Princess!
There's more I want to ask you!
She's gone...
Princess...
L-Lemme go!
Lance!
What happened?!
I need help!
C'mon, why're you all shaken up over a little nibble?
That was no nibble!
That hurt way more than normal!
Don't tell me...
So she is!
What is it?
Look here...
Is that a...
Ah! Ai grew a tooth!
How cute!
Hey, how 'bout stoppin' to breathe?
But I'm still hungry no matter how much I eat!
It must be because of this ring.
Thanks to all the power it saps,
I feel like I need to stuff myself to compensate!
That Blood Ring of yours had to be made from Gula's Egogy.
Oh no, it won't come off!
But man, that power we got was something else.
Doubt it came from this.
Maybe Bel was right about it coming from the baby?
You're still eating?
There's always room for dessert!
Don't come cryin' to me when you get Gula's gut.
... You're right.
Then perhaps I should burn some calories.
A match against the Precures...
sounds like excellent cardio.
Look, Ai.
Solitaire
After you eat, you're supposed to brush your teeth like this.
Now you try too, Ai!
Now say "Aaah."
Naw.
If you don't brush your teeth, you'll get cavities!
Naw, naw!
Um, what's a cavity?
You... don't know?
Cavities happen when bacteria in your mouth form tooth-dissolving plaque.
They're a nightmare!
It melts your teeth?
The human world has such terrifying illnesses...
If you only eat sweets, you're bound to get them.
Are your teeth fine, Aguri?
You've no need to worry.
I brush my teeth every day!
Brush your teeth?
You'll be refreshed with one brush!
Royal White will make your teeth feel brand new!
Royal White
New
You brush your teeth to prevent cavities?
You shot that commercial without knowing?
It's no biggie.
If you just brush your teeth every day, you won't get them.
Thank goodness.
What's wrong, Makoto?
It hurts...
Huh?
My tooth hurts!
What?!
Solitaire
No doubt about it.
It's definitely a cavity.
Why...
You haven't been keeping up with your tooth brushing!
A performer's teeth are her life!
You'll be fired from being an idol!
You jerks!
I've been brushing!
There are right and wrong ways to brush your teeth, you know.
If you miss a spot, you'll get cavities.
Really?
Though there's no point in fussing now that you already have one.
We'll simply go to the dentist and have him fix you.
Dentist?
We'll have Ai watch along.
Naw, naw!
Times like these...
Call for this!
Lancece!
Here, Ai!
This'll make you feel better!
So, cavities are curable.
That's a relief.
I don't think I could deal with this pain forever.
It's too early to relax.
The true terror of cavities...
lies in that office.
Wh-What's he doing?
He's drilling his tooth.
Drilling his tooth?!
What's that?
Pliers.
I can see that they're pliers!
I'm asking what he's gonna use them for!
If the pain doesn't go away, they have to remove your wisdom teeth.
Remove your teeth?!
Hello.
Hello!
Now, we'll begin treating your cavity.
Open your mouth wide and show us your teeth.
Tell me if it hurts.
I'm fine, really!
Wha...
Makopi!
Makopi...
Why did you run away?
Doesn't your tooth hurt?
Cavities don't heal when left alone.
Now, let's return and have your cavity treated.
No!
Makopi...
I'm scared...
My knees start shaking as soon as I hear that drill rev up!
There, there...
How unbecoming, Makoto.
You're no different from a selfish baby.
The princess entrusted Ai to us, making us nothing short of mothers!
And what kind of mother sets a poor example for her child?
We're Ai's mothers?
Just as Aguri said.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree, you know.
Let's go back to the dentist.
And let's show Ai the importance of dental hygiene!
I'm sorry, girls...
You're right, Aguri.
If I can't conquer a cavity, I can't call myself Ai's mother.
And I can't let the princess down, either!
I'll get my cavity treated!
You go, Makopi!
Then let's go back to the dentist!
Makopi?
But it's really scary!
It's so empty here...
If only more people had cavities, I'd get more business.
Wait, I shouldn't even think that!
I'm a doctor!
I should always hope for my patients' health!
Oh, don't be so stiff...
W-Who's there?
I'll turn your desire into a dream come true.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Cavity Selfish!
Cavity!
Dentine hypersensitivity!
Periodontitis!
Mana, I felt a dark heartbeat!
What?
It came from the dentist's!
Selfish!
Is that...
A Selfish!
Girls, let's go!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki—
Huh?
Makopi?
What's wrong?
Well... look!
When I hear that sound, I get scared stiff!
Aww, looks like I'll barely work up a sweat.
Get them, Selfish!
I'll make those teeth of yours clatter!
Drill!
Self?
Self!
Seeeelf!
Get offa me!
Ow!
Makoto!
It's resonating with her cavity!
Ai started crying!
That's not a good sign!
Selfish!
Now this, I don't mind!
Selfish, destroy them!
Light Arm!
It's bright!
Water Arm!
Dryer Arm!
Not your best look.
Selfish, turn them into Swiss cheese!
Drill Arm!
Why did she get so ludicrously strong?
Because Ai's shield disappeared.
It's my fault.
All because I got this stupid cavity...
Makoto...
Stay strong!
Do you not have a duty to restore Trump Kingdom?
You must not give in now!
Plant your feet on the ground and take a stand!
Princess!
Grit those teeth!
Davi, if you'd please.
Thought you'd never ask!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Drill!
Cure Sword!
You're kidding!
The blade of courage, Cure Sword!
I shall sever your ambitions with the blade of love!
Ai.
I won't lose to a silly cavity anymore!
So let's fight together!
Self...
Wait, what now?
Eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth!
Magical Lovely Pad!
Sword Hurricane!
Let's go, everyone!
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Precure Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love looooove!
I'll remember this!
Cure Sword, excellent work!
It's all thanks to you.
To me?
Your words made me feel as though the princess herself was encouraging me.
That's what let me fight with all I had.
Thank you!
How curious.
When I saw Princess Ann reflected in the mirror,
I felt as though it wasn't our first meeting...
As though I had known her long ago...
Really?
It's but a feeling.
Let's restore Trump Kingdom ourselves!
I don't want you laughing at me, so I got my cavity fixed!
Look!
Let's brush our teeth to make sure we never get cavities again!
Could that light be...
Pajama Lovies!
Let's use it right away!
Dibbity dobbity Davi!
Look at that!
It's a pajama toothbrush set made just for Ai!
Ai!
She seems to like it!
Great!
I'll finish it for you.
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Ah, my heart just won't stop racing...
You okay? Can fairies catch colds?
Maybe. It's like there's a knot in my chest!
Your heart is racing?
A knot in your chest?
Could that be...
Lovesickness, perhaps?
No way, couldn't— whaaaa?!
Rachel, you've got a crush?!
Dokidoki Precure:
Rachel's on Cloud Nine!
A Full Throttle First Love!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!