In the year 845,
two terrifying new breeds of Titan appeared:
the Colossal and the Armored,
barreling through the outer walls as if
wholesale destruction was child's play.
The territory couched within the
circle of Wall Maria was abandoned.
Twenty percent of the human race perished.
As the Titan onslaught advanced,
our only choice was to withdrawal behind Wall Rose.
In the year 850, the Colossal Titan again appeared
and decimated yet another barrier between us and them.
Once more, mankind retreated in panic
before the advance of its greatest foe.
Brave soul after brave soul perished.
Eaten alive.
Eren! No!
Cadet Eren Jaeger, tragically
consumed early on in the battle...
later emerged miraculously from
the fallen body of an Abnormal.
Attention!
Dot Pyxis, unconventional commander
of the entire Southern Territory,
witnessed firsthand Eren's Titan form in action.
Taking note of the boy's incredible strength,
a plan worthy of the commander's
fabled eccentricity was hatched.
Recall the massive boulder roughly a league from the gate.
Having assumed Titan form, Cadet Jaeger
will hoist said boulder on his back,
schlep it to the hole, and voila!
Should we succeed, history will be made!
Today is the day!
Trost regain shall stand as a reclamation
of pride and hope beyond measure!
A leap greater than we have ever taken!
And yet, despite Eren's ironclad resolve,
the plan teetered on the brink
of collapse even as it began.
We've managed to corral most of the
Titans in the corner furthest from the breach.
Combat has been avoided as much as possible.
But still, 20% of our forces are lost.
Not lost.
They did not die of losing their way.
They were sent to their deaths. By me.
This is the threshold of our extinction, soldiers.
If my actions ensure mankind's survival,
history may call me "butcher" all it wants.
Ackerman, look out!
Hey! Ackerman! Stand down! Now!
Get away from him. That's an order!
Eren! I know you're in there somewhere.
I know you recognize me!
That's right! Come on!
Snap the hell out of it! We've got a breach to seal up!
We've failed.
It was foolish to pin our hopes on
something we didn't fully understand.
Eren! Listen to me! You're human!
Get out of there!
What the hell?
You tellin' me the kid was a regular Titan all along?
Eren!
Captain!
We've got two Titans bearing down on us
from the front; a 10-meter and a 6-meter!
Heads up! There's a 12-meter
closing in on us from the rear!
Ian, that's it. Please. Just look at him.
We need to get out of here; the plan's a bust.
Agreed. Full withdrawal.
We have to leave him as he is.
Red smoke. That's not good.
Sir, at best I'm afraid it means
the elite squad hit quite a snag.
This was pointless.
My friends died like animals.
No! Look! Over there!
What? What's happening?
It's over.
They failed.
But, how?
Whoa! Armin! Where are you going?
Commander.
I recommend we revert back to defending the gate.
Just give the word, sir.
Denied.
Sir, shall I order a retreat?
Absolutely not.
Continue luring the enemy to the edge of town.
The Elite Squad is well-helmed;
they have leave to make their own decisions.
We proceed as planned.
This was an all-or-nothing proposition.
I will allow those at the vanguard
to determine if and when we deviate.
We are not in a position to deliver a verdict of defeat.
But, we are in a position to fight to the last breath.
It's humanity's debt. It's what we owe the fallen.
Ian! Snap out of it! What are you waiting for?
Give the order!
Hey, it's not like this is your fault!
Come on! Look, this plan was doomed from the start!
We all get that. Was it worth a shot? Sure, whatever!
We did the best with what we had!
But all we've got left now is going back over the wall.
Stop!
Easy. Now's not the time.
Team Rico, take out the 12-meter approaching from behind.
Team Mitabi and I will handle the two front-runners.
Are you nuts?
In case you've forgotten, I'm the one in charge!
Now do as you're ordered, soldier!
We are not leaving Jaeger defenseless, period.
Change of plans. Our job now is to keep
the others off him until he can be recovered.
Whether we like it or not,
he's still our last best chance.
We're not about to abandon him.
We're expendable; he isn't.
He can't just be replaced.
Please! Don't talk to me about our last best chance!
He's a failure countless soldiers have died because of!
Just look at him, Ian! Are you saying
you want more of us to die saving that?
That's right. Down to the last man!
If that's what it takes, so be it!
What the hell's up with the red smoke.
What happened to him?
I don't know, but Armin's gone to see.
But I... I think it'll be alright.
Yeah?
Of course! I mean...
this is Eren we're talkin' about.
Right.
I don't wanna be that guy, but this
whole thing feels kind of pointless.
Hell, when's the last time a fight
against the Titans didn't feel like that, huh?
The best thing now?
Do what we can from losing any more.
I don't like the idea of so
many of us being dead for nothing.
We have to pick our battles.
If we want to wage all-out war someday,
we have to conserve all the manpower we can.
This was the right call.
Just be patient.
Was it the right call, though?
Yes! Of course it was!
Live to fight another day, is that it?
Right. I'm in.
Ian, you can't be serious!
What other hope against the Titans do we have?
You know something I don't?
This is it. This is all we've
got, and you damn-well know it!
I am making a judgment call here.
If you have a better plan, speak up!
How else are we ever going to get out
from under their feet? I'm all ears here!
If you're asking me how else we'll
defeat the Titans, obviously I have no idea.
See? That's why we can't afford to beat a retreat.
Not just yet.
We may not know what else is in there, but there's hope.
And as long as that's the case.
We're gonna fight to the bitter end.
Look at us. Always scraping by.
Always on the run.
Don't you... Don't you want it to be over?
Don't you want to make a stand?
Well, this is how it's done!
This is just... This is madness.
Hey!
I think you're right.
If we're to stand, this is the only way.
Just this once.
Let's fight a fight that's not just a battle of attrition.
Let the bastards taste humanity's wrath.
Right. My team will address the
12-meter Titan coming from the rear.
Well? We got the two in front or don't we?
Right.
Thank you, Captain.
That was brave.
No, it wasn't. There's no thanks needed.
Fact of the matter is I was petrified
of the mess you were about to get into.
But you're free now. So do your thing.
Make good use of that inborn skill.
Sir.
Go save the man you love.
It's not like that.
What? Why haven't his injuries repaired themselves?
Did the earlier damage compromise him?
Oh, Eren. What is this doing to you?
Oh god, what if you won't be able to change back?
No, I've got to stop.
I'm thinking about it too much, that's all.
I need to focus on doing.
Eren. Misaka. What's going on?
What's... Where am I?
What am... What am I doing?
Am I sitting?
I can't see.
What day is it?
Wait.
Oh. That's right, of course.
Weird.
Eren.
Come on, what are you doing? Wake up!
Here's the plan:
we don't let a single one of these
ugly S.O.B.'s wander outta this corner.
Focus on luring them here and
keeping them here, understood?
Do not, I repeat, do not engage them
in combat unless you absolutely have to.
I want you on the ground, three cadets per team.
When you reach the wall, jump. That clear?
Die, and you'll piss me off.
If a Titan goes astray, we'll put him down.
Whaddya mean "if"? It's not like we
can count on them to follow protocol.
What if our situation gets risky?
Are we free to act at our own discretion or what?
Whatever'll make it easier on you.
Team Kirschtein, move out!
Yes, sir!
Son of a bitch... Behind us!
It's a 13-meter! And from the looks
of it, he's about to pounce on Jaeger!
Heads up! We've got four more coming through the gate!
All of them 10-meters at least!
Right. Rear! Ackerman! Yours!
Sir!
Keep it away from him at all costs!
Hold the rest off here!
Will do!
Elite or not, two teams can't take on four Titans at once.
What's going on?
Where are they coming from all of a sudden?
There aren't enough of us to attract this many.
Unless... Unless they're coming for Eren!
Mikasa!
Why'd the plan go belly-up?
Armin?
Why on earth is he just slumped here like this?
Get away. It's dangerous!
Something went wrong. He lost
control and wound up like that!
I tried to snap him out of it,
but I couldn't get him to respond.
He's been out like this for the past few minutes.
But the plan?
We've had to shift tac. Right now all we
can do is protect him. He's defenseless.
And there's... There's just so many.
I don't know how much longer we can keep this up!
From the back of the head to the nape of the neck,
one meter high and ten centimeters across!
Armin!
I'm pulling him out of here!
You just hold off the other Titans as long as you can!
But...
When Eren first emerged from this
form, it was from the weak spot.
I dunno. But something tells me
that's a big part of the picture.
How these damn things work.
It'll be alright. As long as I don't hit the center.
This won't kill him.
But, well, it is going to hurt.
A lot.
No!
Stop it! You'll get yourself killed!
I'm fine! Just do what you can to keep the rest at bay!
Trust me, there's tons of other
people you should be worried about!
Now leave Eren to me and go do what you do best!
Eren! Can you hear me?
You've got to pull it together!
If you stay like this, we're all going to die!
Whatever this body's doing to you, fight it!
You're Eren Jaeger, damn it!
What's this steaming lump of flesh have on you, huh?
What is he talking about?
Fight it? What?
I'm tired.
Come on. Damn it!
Wake up! Get out of there!
We need you! Eren!
Your mom, remember?
Remember what they did to her?
You were bent on avenging her death!
You swore to massacre the Titans!
You're not making any sense, Armin.
Open your eyes. Mom's not dead.
Eren! Eren, please! You have to push through it!
I know you're in there! Listen to me!
If you don't get a move on, the Titans are
going to kill us! It'll all end right here!
Armin. Seriously, what the hell's gotten into you?
What's this "get a move on" crap?
I don't wanna "move" anything.
This right here's good enough for me.
It's not like I want to be a Scout.
Fantastic. Well, like it or not we're on our own now.
Die!
Yeah! That's what I thought, you bastard!
Get some distance!
I've got this, Captain!
I'll help Team Mitabi!
What the...?
Jean!
Get up the wall!
I'm sick and tired of people dying because of me!
You malfunction now?
Jean!
What's he doing?
And why the hell isn't he using his gear?
Hang on!
Don't tell me it's not working!
I am not going to die today!
Way to go. Draggin' everybody down. Great job.
Maybe I won't die today.
Eren. Please. For me.
Wake up.
Remember when we were kids?
All we could talk about was the world outside.
You know, beyond the walls.
Frozen tundra that stretches to the skies.
Sand dunes.
Oceans.
Forests.
The world my parents wanted to see.
I'd always thought you'd outgrown that dream.
I was kind of sad it didn't come up anymore.
But then I realized you let it go because
you didn't want me to join the Scouts.
No, I... just...
Tell me. Honestly.
Even though your first step beyond the wall meant
the difference between a warm hearth and hell on earth.
Even though it meant risking your life.
Gambling against the possibility of dying like my parents.
Why? Why throw caution to the wind and venture outside?
What kind of question is that?
Don't play dumb. You know damn well why.
Because the world beyond the wall is my birthright!
Run like hell. Stay alive.
Words run in circles;
lives end in blood and ear-piercing screams.
But Eren soldiers on, a beacon of hope.