If this is posted here
this early in the morning,
The mysterious figure making a
stir at Kanyasai Phantom Thief Jumoji
they must be in high gear.
Well, they can't top me when it
comes to being geared up.
Global Act Club
Yo, Fukube! You're late!
Hey, good morning.
Aw, man.
It's going to be hard to keep
Jumoji at large like this.
You know,
you're really making an effort,
staking out so early in the morning.
As are you.
If there are this many aspiring
detectives waiting around here,
it looks like the crime
hasn't happened yet.
Okay, Jumoji,
if you're going to come, then come!
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
The Final Target
It's the final
day at last. The moment of truth.
Indeed...
It seems like I've met that
lady somewhere before...
The idea of using the
Jumoji incident as bait
to sell our volumes of
Hyouka isn't a bad one.
But even so, it won't be enough
for us to sell out of them.
Let's think about this.
I'm not sure it will work, though.
Nothing's happening.
He's right about that.
Is Jumoji's target the
Quiz Club? No, it couldn't be.
What could he steal from the Quiz Club
once the event is already over?
I'm tired of this. I'm leaving.
I think I've had enough, too.
What happened, Phantom Thief Jumoji?
Well, if anything happens, text me.
Scared off by too many people here?
What?!
Did something happen?
Hmph! Lousy Jumoji! He put on a feint!
A feint? You mean, the Quiz Club?
No, the Keion [Light Music] Club.
One of their gen [strings] is missing.
Light Music Club? The Light Music Club?!
You're sure about this, right?!
If that's what you think,
go ahead and check for yourself.
See you.
Wait!
It's no use.
It looks like the
Light Music Club got hit.
For real?
Jumoji's flexibility is far greater
than I anticipated, or can handle.
The frontal approach didn't work.
I have to rethink this.
What else can I do besides
catch him in the act?
Goal: Sell out all 200 copies!
Oh...
When they sell, they sell well.
The 20 that we relegated away sold out
and Chitanda took ten more
of them down there.
Add to that nine more this morning.
Now I have some hope for the future.
That's Saturday for you.
Hey there!
I see you've devoted yourself to the
energy-conserving work, as usual.
Sis? You really did come, huh?
You should be grateful that
your big sister came to see
how her dear younger
brother was doing.
Here.
Thank you very much.
Hm? What's that?
It doesn't suit you very well.
Oh...
This is the Warashibe Protocol.
Your fountain pen became a hand mirror.
Huh? So in other words,
you exchanged stuff for that?
More or less.
Oh, yeah? Well then...
I'll take this. In return...
Here.
What is it?
A Corpse By Evening?
It's a manga?
It's up to you whether or not
you pass the time with that.
What's that supposed to mean?
Okay, I'm going.
Hey!
"Anshinin Takuha"?
"What did you think of A Corpse By Evening?
I thought it turned out
quite well, if I do say so myself.
Of course, I just helped out
with the backgrounds
and didn't have much
to do with it at all.
If you enjoyed reading this manga,
the credit goes to the author
and the artist, not me."
I guess "Anshinin Takuha" must
be like the name of their team.
"It's not as though all of us
are in the Manga Club.
We just liked manga, seemed to
hit it off while talking to each other,
and when we decided that we
would try drawing something up,
this is the story that came about.
I think it's quite extraordinary
for a maiden effort,
but it wouldn't be right for me
to blow their horn for them.
I will leave it in your hands
to judge its worth.
Now, we have no intention of
splitting up after just one work.
We have already started something
new with next year's Kanyasai in mind.
Our writer, A, is thinking of turning
the writing style on its ear
and is talking about tackling
some kind of mystery.
I hear the plan is a take on one
of Christie's ultra-famous works
while seeing if a twist or two
can't be added to it.
The title has already been chosen,
so I'll announce it here.
The next story's title will be
The Kudryavka Sequence.
Yet another foreboding name.
Okay, see you next year
during Kanyasai season again.
Anshinin Takuha."
"The Kudryavka Sequence"?
I don't know what "Kudryavka" means,
but that word "Sequence"
there catches my attention.
Also Christie's ultra-famous work?
See you next year
It's up to you whether
or not you pass the time with that.
Damn it, Sis. I hope you haven't
laid more trouble at my doorstep.
Broadcasting Studio
Excuse me! Um, you are the
Broadcasting Club's president,
Yoshino-san, right?
Yes, I am. Who are you?
Hello.
I am Chitanda Eru, president of
the Classic Lit Club. Yoshino-san...
You're the president of
the Classic Lit Club?!
Perfect timing! I was just
about to come see you!
Would you like to be our guest
on the radio at lunchtime?
Huh?
I think having the president
of Jumoji's final target on
will be a huge hit.
Well?
I couldn't ask for a better chance!
It would be my pleasure to be on your show!
Okay, 12:00 here at the studio, okay?
The broadcast starts
at 12:30! See you then!
Right!
I'm back.
Hey, Chitanda-san.
Thanks for being here. Have there
been any new developments?
"Ku" has been skipped over;
a gen [string] from the Keion
[Light Music] Club was stolen.
We have to rethink this from scratch.
What do you think, Oreki-san?
Mmm...
He's all wrapped up in that doujin manga
and has been like this for a while.
Oh...
This is good.
Oh, yeah?
Huh?
What's the matter?
That picture... it feels like
I've seen it somewhere before.
Your eyes are fooling you.
My sister brought this here.
No, there's no doubt about it.
Chitanda, this isn't the time for this.
I-I...
I am curious!
There it is.
It's on the tip of my tongue.
Swallow it again.
I can't!
Can't you do something?
Let me see another page.
Here.
Thank you very much!
This picture looks just like the poster
outside the conference room.
Mm-hm, it sure does.
Oreki-san, let me borrow
this manga for a bit!
I want to go compare the two!
All right. But bring it right
back here. I kind of need it.
Right!
Welcome to the Manga Club
This is the artwork, here, all right.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you very much.
Sorry, it's not for sale.
All finished.
What's next?
Miss, could I take a picture?
Just draw whatever.
Okay.
No.
Let's see, the color should be...
I'm going to go change your water.
Oh, mm-hm. Thanks.
I said no pictures!
Whoops!
Nice!
I-I'm sorry, Ibara!
This isn't what I intended...
Mm. It's okay. It's khaki to
begin with. This won't stand out.
More than likely.
Ibara...
Sorry, President. I hope
you can do without me.
You need to change out of your
Rainbow Parakeet outfit, though.
Please don't worry about me.
Mayaka-san!
Chi-chan?
Do you have a moment
right now? Huh?
Gym clothes?
Mm-hm, I changed clothes.
So, what's going on?
Oh, it's this!
W-Why do you have this, Chi-chan?!
It isn't mine... it belongs to Oreki-san.
Why does Oreki have it?
He said his sister brought it.
Mayaka-san, do you know this manga?
Hm, well, yes, I do.
You know what?!
There's a poster promoting
the culture festival
and I'm curious as to whether
whoever drew that poster
and whoever drew this
manga are the same person!
Where is this poster?!
Next to the conference room!
All right, let's go!
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light
findeth equal measure with darkness.
Hyouka
54th Kanyasai
What do you think?
Ninety-nine percent it's the same person. The
way the ears are handled is exactly the same.
Is that right? Thank you very much.
I'm glad to get that off my chest.
You were curious, right?
Yes.
Say, you want to ask who drew it?
Yes, I'm curious about that.
Yes?
Hello, Tanabe-san.
Yeah. You're, um...
From the Classic Lit Club.
Ah, yes. So, did you
need something else?
Forgive us for asking,
but do you know who drew the poster
that's pinned up right there?
Ah, that would be Kugayama.
Huh? Kugayama Muneyoshi-san?
The student council president?
Yeah. I badgered him
to draw something, too.
It turned out nicely, didn't it?
Yes! I think it looks very pretty.
He'll be tickled to hear that.
First I find out the author,
now I learn who the artist is!
Maybe I'll ask him about it personally.
Who knows? Maybe this golden
combo will keep on rolling.
Earth Science Prep Room
We found out!
So, was it the same person? Wait, huh?
Mayaka, gym clothes?
What about the Manga Club?
Mm-hm, I switched out.
It is the same person!
We even found out his name!
Ho, good for you.
It was Kugayama Muneyoshi-san!
What a surprise!
Is he famous?
H-Hotaro, you're messing with us, right?
You know who he is?
Kugayama Muneyoshi (Student
Council President)
The student council president.
Ah, yes, of course...
I thought it was pronounced
"Rikuyama" this whole time.
Which means that among
this Anshinin Takuha group,
this Kugayama guy drew the pictures?
What do you mean, "Anshinin"?
You read that as "Ajimu."
It's a location in Kyushu.
Is that vital knowledge
for getting through life?
Um...
The reading for this is written in
small Roman letters next to it.
The artwork was done
by Kugayama-senpai,
but the story was written by
someone named Anjo Haruna.
Oh, you know about this, do you?
I love that manga. I bought it
at last year's culture festival.
For Ibara to come out and say
she loves something, it must be...
Listen, Oreki,
could I borrow that for a little bit?
It's fine with me, but in a
little while. I still need to use it.
Use it?
Oh, yeah!
As it happens, I'm appearing on the
Broadcasting Club's lunchtime show!
She's what?!
Chi-chan, that's amazing, isn't it?
Nice going. You even managed
to score an appearance.
The goal of selling out of
Hyouka is now within sight.
Okay, I'll teach you the secrets
to being a good guest.
Really?
First and foremost, a guest
only gets about five minutes.
So the question is, how much can
you stand out in that short time?
Getting Around at Kanyasai,
That follows.
And the second thing is, keep
saying "The Classic Lit Club."
the Gardening Club, the Cooking Club,
Right! You can count on me!
the Light Music Club,
Christie's ultra-famous work,
Yes, we'll be doing that, Chitanda-san.
"The Kudryavka Sequence"...
What?
How about it?
How about what?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, well. My thinking was
coming to a standstill anyway.
Normally, I'd move my thinking
forward by talking to these guys...
but Chitanda would hamper that.
If she knew what I was trying to do,
I'm positive that she'd be against it.
Satoshi...
Hm?
Sorry, but could you come
with me for a second?
You've figured something out,
haven't you, Hotaro?!
Is that true, Oreki-san?!
No one asked you to
exercise your instincts!
Now Chitanda's got that
look in her eye, you know!
Have you realized something?
No, I haven't, I haven't!
Then, this isn't about the Jumoji matter?
Well, um...
Come on, Oreki.
You know, I'm...
I'm very curious about this, too,
so why will you only
talk to Fukube-san?
Aw, man... Well, I guess at this point...
It does indeed have to do
with the Jumoji matter.
Then, include us, as well!
It's of an incredibly obscene
nature. Are you sure?
So tell me what this
"obscene" story of yours is.
Sorry to have to drag
you out here like this.
Hey, it doesn't bother me.
It's not like I had any
earth-shattering thoughts.
It's just that there are a number
of things I can't get my head around.
It seems to me like they
ought to be significant.
Is there some hidden link between
the clubs that fell victim?
No, it's not that, really.
Then, did you find some tiny mistake
the phantom thief Jumoji made?
It's not quite that, either.
What?
It's neither one?
There are over 1,000 suspects.
Are we really supposed
to identify the culprit
without finding any leads or mistakes?
Well, yeah.
But how?!
Look, it's not as though I
have anything on the culprit.
I just want to gather
my thoughts a little more.
Mm-hm? Let's hear it.
I'm looking forward to this, Hotaro.
First off,
why is Jumoji stealing ten different
things from ten different clubs?
It's just something we assumed from
reading the way he signed his notes.
An assumption that now
seems to be in doubt.
Second, why is he leaving greeting
cards at the scene of his crimes?
Yeah...
You mean these.
Third, why is he using the word "lost"?
lost
Wouldn't one normally say "taken," instead?
Fourth, why leave behind a
"Getting Around at Kanyasai" book?
It's not the only thing that
has a list of all the clubs.
Why choose that in particular?
By the way, I have that, too...
The one from the Cooking Club.
Fifth, why the Gardening Club
and the Cooking Club?
There are a number of other clubs
that begin with "E" and "O."
Especially with the Oryori [Cooking] Club.
Normally, you'd just consider
that the Ryori Club.
That directly touches on the question
of whether the Classic Lit Club or
the Industrial Arts Club will be hit.
Sixth... and this is the weirdest one...
Why did he skip "Ku"
and steal from "Ke" next?
That was to get by without being noticed.
The Global Act Club was in
no condition to steal from.
Seventh, there's this.
Christie's ultra-famous work
The manga has nothing
to do with this, right?
That may not necessarily be true.
Satoshi, what do you think of when you
hear "Christie's ultra-famous work"?
Let's see... And Then There Were None,
Murder On the Orient Express,
The Murder of Roger Ackroyd,
and The A.B.C. Murders.
Those four, I'd say.
If someone were going to work
one of them into a manga,
and give it the title
The Kudryavka Sequence,
I think it would be The A.B.C. Murders.
Kudryavka was the dog they put in
a rocket as an experiment long ago,
but then she never made it back, right?
If it were me, given the
image of a violent death,
I'd guess And Then There Were None.
Well, since this is just supposition,
we don't have to pin it down.
I think I'm starting to figure out
what you're trying to say, Hotaro.
Satoshi, is there a manga called
The Kudryavka Sequence
being sold at the culture festival?
No. The Executive Committee
wasn't told of it.
If it was coming out
through the Manga Club,
Mayaka would have mentioned it.
"If," you say.
At last year's culture festival,
A Corpse By Evening came out.
In the afterword, it announced that
there would be a manga next year
that was a twist on Christie's
ultra-famous work.
We guessed that that work was
And Then There Were None
or The A.B.C. Murders.
Now, this year, when it was
announced for, there are incidents
which clearly seem to be lifted from
The A.B.C. Murders taking place.
Is this a coincidence?
In other words, Hotaro, you're
saying that these Jumoji incidents
were announced at the end of
A Corpse By Evening, right?
Well, enough that I'm not willing
to say they're completely unrelated.
Hm...
I even get the feeling that
with Jumoji, it's more like
he wants to carry out this Jumoji
caper while causing as little trouble
and while being hindered
as little as possible.
I don't think it's being
done for the fun of it.
So then, why did he skip over "Ku"?
There were any number
of ways to pull it off.
Satoshi, there's some reason
behind these incidents.
I'm heading back.
I'm concerned about Chitanda-san.
Yeah, okay. Go on. I'm going to
look over this stuff you gave me.
Oh, Satoshi!
Tell Chitanda to have some
"Ko" items ready to go.
Bait to lure the culprit in with,
right? I was thinking of that.
I'll get some koryogenko
[proofed manuscripts] ready.
I have high hopes, Hotaro.
On Air
We'll start when we get our cue, okay?
Y-Yes!
Five seconds.
4... 3...
This is a special edition of
Yoshino Yasukuni's Radio Beat!
Hi, hello there! This is radio
personality Yoshino Yasukuni.
Our guest for the final day is
the Classic Lit Club's president
from Class 1-A, Chitanda Eru-san.
Oh, right! I-It's a
pleasure to talk to you...
Ow!
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "The Kudryavka Sequence."
The Kudryavka Sequence