Where... am I?
I can't remember anything.
Are you awake now?
Who—
Welcome to...
the I-Ain't-Dead-Yet Battlefront.
I know this is out of the blue, but could you join our force?
Huh?  "Join"?
If you're here, then that means you're dead.
Huh?
Um, I'm not following you well—
This is the world of the afterlife.
If you don't act, you'll be obliterated.
"Obliterated"?
By whom?
By God, I imagine.
Then what's this about joining your force?
I'm asking you to join the I-Ain't-Dead-Yet Battlefront.
The name of the force changes often.
First, it was the Afterlife Battlefront.
But that name kind of admits that you're dead, doesn't it?
As such, we pitched it.
Ever since, we've been changing the name around.
Right now, we're the I-Ain't-Dead-Yet Battlefront.
The one before that was the It-Doesn't-Feel-
Like-I'm-Alive Battlefront.
Now that was a real joke, so we changed it within a day.
Um, is that a real gun?
Everyone who comes here has the same reaction.
Be more adaptive.
Accept things how they are.
Okay "accept," and then what happens?
You'll fight.
Against what?
That down there.
The enemy here on the I-Ain't-
Dead-Yet Battlefront.
Tenshi.
I'd really like to hurry and rename this from the
I-Ain't-Dead-Yet Battlefront.
You.  Come up with a name.
Hey, hey.  That's an ordinary girl there no matter how you look at it.
What's she talking about?
Hey, mind if I go over there?
Huh?!
What for?!  I don't get you!
How did you come up with that?!
You must be an idiot!
You should die once!
By the way, that's a cliché joke in this world where no one can die.
So, was it funny?
P-Putting my thoughts on the joke aside...
I thought I might have a better conversation with her than with a person who points a gun at a girl.
I'm on your side.
If you don't want me pointing guns, then I won't.
Trust me.
Hey, Yurippe!
What happened to recruiting the new guy?
We're short on people right now.
We need to resort to every dirty trick we have—
What?
I'm going over there.
I failed to recruit him!
I don't get this.
What was up with them?
Excuse me.
Ah, good evening.
You know, you were being targeted by a gun.
She was calling you an angel or whatnot.
I'm not an angel.
Obviously.
Then—
I'm the Student Council President.
What an idiot I am.  That girl was playing around with me.
Damn it!  And I don't even know who I am.
I guess I'll go to the hospital or something.
There are no hospitals.
Why not?
Because no one gets sick.
"No one gets sick"?
Because we're all dead.
Oh, I get it!  You're in on this, too!
You're trying to trick me, aren't you?
Is this amnesia of mine your doing, also?
Amnesia is a common thing here.
If one dies from an accident, they frequently hit their head.
Then prove it!
Prove to me that I won't die since I'm already dead...
Hand Sonic.
Where is...
I'm alive...
But it hurt so much...
Damn it!  Damn it!  I don't understand what's going on, but I shouldn't be here!
What's this guy's problem...
So you're the punk who insulted Yurippe and declined to join the force?!
Hey, hold on.  Hold your horses.
You wanna die?
Oh?  Oh, that.
You mean...
Yeah, that's hilarious.
That's the joke in this world where no one dies, right?
Great sense of humor there.
Die 100 times.
Die, die, die, die, die!
DIE!
Insult Yurippe again, and you'll be back in the air, punk.
Are you trying to kill me?!
Oh, right, like that works as a come-back here...
At any rate, what kinda sick joke is that?!
It hurts like hell, yet you can't die?
This sucks!
This is the world of the afterlife.
If you don't act, you'll be obliterated.
That's right!  I can just be obliterated!
Then I can get out of this world.
B-But how exactly do I do that?
I'm on your side.
Trust me.
Is there anyone who looks trustworthy out there?
That's right!  Start by looking for an adult!
And where are the adults?
Any teachers?
Maybe I'll ask the headmaster.
Okay, how does this sound?
You're-the-One-Who's-Gonna-Die Battlefront.
That sounds like I'm gonna die.
No, of course we'd be targeting it at that woman.
Then look at me.
Where am I?
You're-the-One-Who's-Gonna-Die Battlefront.
Whoa, crap!
Yeah, sounds like I'm gonna get killed.
Anything else?  Any other suggestions?
How's this?
Flashback Battlefront!
You're on the verge of death.
How about this, then?
Obliterate Battlefront!
You're pretty much asking to die.
Driven-to-the-Wall Battlefront.
Oh, yeah.  That's right!  Oh, yeah.
Death's cornering you!
How about Invincible Force?
Now we're missing the "Battlefront."
Suicidal Rangers!
Nice.
Want me to punch you?
Wright Brothers!
Shut up!
I said it needs to end in "battlefront"!
That's a must, no questions!
We're standing on the frontline of this war.
Doesn't anyone have a better idea?
Hey, isn't he awake now?
Ah, so you've come to.
That's right.  I told him to think up a name, too.
You've had plenty of time.
So let's hear it.
Hear what?
A new team name that will replace the I-Ain't-Dead-Yet Battlefront.
I-Don't-Care Battlefront.
You got some real nerve to defy Yurippe.
I said I don't care what you guys do!
What did you say?!
What are you guys?!
Don't drag me into this!
I'm gonna go get obliterated!
You want to be obliterated?  Even though you exist here?
Yeah, that's right!
I already explained that bit to him.
So you wish to be obliterated without even putting up a fight?
Yeah!
So you choose to turn into a water flea without even putting up a fight?
What?  "Water flea"?
You thought only humans have souls, punk?
How unwise.
You might even turn into a barnacle next time.
Or maybe a hermit crab.
Or even a wharf roach!
You've gotta be kidding!
And you're not even asking why the choice is limited to aquatic creatures.
For the record, there is no reason.
So, come on.  Get outta here, already.
You're gonna become Tenshi's pet and go "rest in peace," right?
Go become a barnacle and get eaten by humans, already.
Wouldn't that be such a pleasant new life?
A barnacle...
What?  Barnacles are edible?
There are some that are edible.
I never knew that.
How unwise.
Easy now, everyone.  Don't be so mean and force him out.
The poor thing.
We the...
Um... what were we right now, again?
Barnacle Battlefront.
Right!  We of the Barnacle Battlefront will—
I'm reverting it!
We're the Afterlife Battlefront!
That was a good kick.
While you remain in the Battlefront's Headquarters here, you're safe.
You came here knowing that, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Besides, the moment I tried to enter, I was knocked away.
But anyway, assuming that there really is reincarnation, you're just joking about not being human, right?
We're not joking.
How would one confirm such a thing?
Has anyone seen it themselves?
Of course nobody has!
But in Buddhism, it's thought possible to reincarnate into something other than a human.
But still... a barnacle?
Well, religions are all created by humans, but listen closely.  This here's the critical part.
In the world where we once lived, death came indiscriminately and randomly.
As such, there was no way for us to fight against it.
But that's not true in this world.
You can continue to survive as long as you keep fighting against Tenshi.
You can rebel!
But wait, what lies beyond that?
What do you all hope to accomplish?
Our objective is to obliterate Tenshi.
And to seize this world!
You've just come here, so it's no surprise that you're totally confused.
Be more adaptive.
Just accept things how they are.
So we fight?  Against Tenshi?
That's right.
Together.
Not so fast, Yurip—!
What an idiot.
He fell for the trap he set himself.
So that's what I looked like, too.
To enter here safely, you need a passphrase.
This is the Headquarters for anti-Tenshi forces.
There are no other places we can talk safely.
Could you give me some time?
Sure, but you can't spend it here.
Fine, I'll join!
What's the passphrase?
"No God, no Buddha, nor angels exist."
I'm Yuri.
I'm the leader on this battlefront.
He's Hinata-kun.
As you can see, he's quite lax, but he'll do what's necessary at times.
Hi—
Hey, you're not giving me enough credit!
He's Matsushita-kun.
Totally ignoring me...
He's a 5th degree black belt in judo,
so everyone calls him Matsushita Fifth, with respect.
Nice to meet you.
He's Ooyama-kun.
His lack of character is his defining characteristic.
Welcome to the Battlefront.
C'mon , let's dance!
No, I don't think I will.
Okay... don't be afraid.
That's his way of saying hello.
Feel the groove, man.
Everyone calls him T.K.
He's a mystery man.  No one knows his real name.
Yeah, nice and slow.
Are you sure about keeping someone like that as an ally?
Yeah, step on!
The one who's always lifting his glasses to speak intelligently is Takamatsu-kun.
He's actually an idiot.
Pleased to meet you.
And he's Fujimaki-kun.
Remember, it's Fujimaki, you brat.
I'm not a brat.
Oh, and the one who flew out just now is Noda-kun.
The one who keeps saying "How unwise" is Shiina-san.
And the one sitting here is Iwasawa-san.
She's the leader of the Diversion Division.
Besides us, there are dozens of other Battlefront members within the school.
Well, let's see.
Come to think of it, what's your name?
Huh?  Oh, um...
O... O, Oto... Otonashi.
What's your given name?
I can't remember.
Ah, it's amnesia.
Don't worry!  You'll remember things soon enough.
Hey, shouldn't you give him the school uniform?
Oh yeah, I forgot.
Right...
Why is my uniform different from everyone else's?
It's not that you're any different.
We are different.
You're dressed in what honor students wear.
Whereas what we wear are the SSS uniforms.
[ Note: The SSS, short for Shinda Sekai Sensen,
aka the Afterlife Battlefront. ]
This is a pretty big school.
A little over 2,000 students.
It's a mammoth all-boarding school.
I don't know who—
Hey, is it all right to be talking at a place like this?
Yeah, so long as it's not battle plans.
I feel like I've been tricked.
What?
Nothing.
Hey, is that canned coffee?
It's Key Coffee.  It's good, you know?
That's what you wanted to ask?
Ah, well...
Who are they?
Right now is when people are either busy with clubs or heading home.
You guys don't do either?
We'll be obliterated if we do.
We humans would be obliterated if we participate in clubs, as Tenshi says.
"Humans"?
From how you talk, sounds like they're not human.
Let's go grab some food.
You're right.  They're NPCs.
"NPCs"?
Never heard?  It stands for non-player character.
Are you talking about a game world?
It's just an example.  They're honor students who exist in this world to begin with.
Then they don't have any self-awareness?
Would they only return the same answer no matter how many times we talk to them?
Try it for yourself.
As a newcomer to this world, it can be hard to tell the difference between us and them.
So we can actually facilitate a conversation?
Go shove a finger up a girl's ass.
Say what?
She'll either run away or you'll get kicked.
S-So they're well-made...
And the teachers?
The same.  And just so you know, NPCs never age.
That applies to us, too.
Any other questions?
How violent is Tenshi?
She stabbed me the moment we met.
I was watching, but really, you brought that upon yourself.
If you ask Tenshi to prove that you can't die,
then of course she'll skewer you right through your heart.
To her, that was no different than answering where the Faculty Lounge is.
So Tenshi strictly obeys this world's rules.
She's just clumsy.
She has self-awareness?
Dunno.  It's a mystery.
How she's emotionless, unsociable, and speaks minimally makes her unique compared to NPCs.
So normally, we aren't killed—
Well, aren't beaten so easily.
Those who don't fit themselves to the honor student role will first be given a verbal warning.
If you run away, she'll chase you and even get in your way.
Does it ever get physical?
Eye for an eye!
Only when we start the fight, though.
So there are times when you'll get beaten up like I did.
Of course.
And you shouldn't even pretend to be an honor student.  There are those who were obliterated for that.
Okay.  Then here's the last question.
Regarding God.
Does He exist?
I believe in Him, though I've haven't met Him, yet.
You've never asked Tenshi about it?
She doesn't answer questions that touch upon the foundations of this world.
And that concludes Lecture Hour.
To be honest, I haven't united with them, yet.
What I should be focusing on now is to buy the time necessary to get my memory back.
That's all.
After that!
After that...
I don't know.
Here, Otonashi-kun.
This should work, even if it's your first time.
Is it effective?
Aim for her foot.  That'll at least stop her from chasing after you.
Firing a gun on a girl?
Will the wound heal fast?
You should learn those things through experience.
That's how we learned.
Fine.
Good answer, Otonashi-kun.
To get you started and familiar with your surroundings, I'll have you take part in the daily operation.
Code name: Operation Tornado.
Ah, this is big.
"T-Tornado"?
We'll sweep away lunch tickets from the students!
That's what you meant by "tornado"?!
And that's not big at all!  It's basically bullying!
I've totally lost faith in you guys!  All you have are weapons and your numbers!
You punk!  That's an insult to Yurippe.
I'll have you take that back.
Why?!
We of the Barnacle-Extinction-Prevention Battlefront would never threaten students with numbers or violence.
They're on the verge of extinction?!
I'm sure they will be someday.
But you just said you're sweeping them away!
Yes, and we will, literally.
Listen.  You'll be part of the barricade group that will inhibit Tenshi's interference.
You'll be on standby with a weapon at designated locations around the cafeteria, the area of operations.
And relax, I'll drop you at an easy point.
Ask for details from Takamatsu-kun or Ooyama-kun later.
Iwasawa-san, I look forward to your hard work today, too.
Yeah.
When Tenshi appears, open fire.
That will be the signal to request reinforcements.
If you hear gunfire, you go running there, too.
The operation start time is 18:30.
Operation start!
How's this operation going to peacefully sweep away lunch tickets?
This is Yusa.
The Light and Sound Staffs are on standby.
I believe it's about time.
The fans are starting to gather.
Okay.
So, shall we get started?
Hey, there's GDM!
The live concert's started!
She's there.
She's right there.
She's right in front of me.
So I'm the weakest link on the current battlefront, eh?
She's totally underestimating me.
Damn it!  I'll shoot!
But, if a bullet goes through that frail body...
If I don't shoot, she'll get me.
She won't show any mercy.
It hit!
But, the leg was all I needed to hit.
That's enough...
It's...
Guard Skill: Hand Sonic.
No way...  No way!
Why?  Why won't she stop?!
W-What's that supposed to be?!
Damn it!
Crap, I missed.
Sorry to make you wait.
Give you a little kiss!
I'd say she came after the weakest link, yo!
She's only using Hand Sonic right now.
Head to a place that's more open!
We'll fire as we fall back!
Roger.
Ready?
Guard Skill: Distortion.
Fire!
Goddamn it!
We were too late.
My God!
This is why I hate guns!
Goddamn!
What's taking the tornado so long?!
I never thought buying time would end up meaning something like this.
Seems we're at the climax.
Spin it.
Spin it, please.
That what you want?  Let's go!
Here's your beef udon.
Mmm, this is super-delicious.  Oh, yeah.
Is it all right for us to be eating here so carelessly?
Won't she come after us?
We're only eating.
So that's how it works, huh?
With this much insight and power, they should be capable of doing anything.
And yet, they're leading a plain life right now, eating like everyone else.
Could you pass me the pepper?
Here.
There's really only one enemy.
Just Tenshi.
They're really only fighting against her.
But, will I somehow justify this behavior?
No.  It's too early for that.
After all...
I don't remember anything.
Parachute operation...
We call it the Guild.
You're gonna be next.
It seems you still do not understand.
Run for it!
The traps weren't disarmed?!
Shoot, I forgot!
Because I was the first to rebel.
I don't know...   I don't know of anything like that!
Tenshi's getting up!
Fire!!
What the heck am I doing?
I can't forgive being given such a life.