After careful consideration of the times, we feel that intense scenes in this show are important to the story.
-Rainbow Production Staff
Sign: Shonon Hospital
Hey, did you hear? Some boys broke out of the Shonan Reformatory!
What?! Seriously?!
Yes, four of them! Apparently they've all been patients here, too!
But they're only kids. It won't be long until they're caught.
I was hoping you could be there to see Bro!
Setsuko had prepared herself to keep her promise to Mario.
Setsuko! Setsuko!
Who's there?
It's me.
Maeda?
Y-Yeah...
So he not only wasted away, but his hand's really hurt now...
He's really hurt?!
Anyway, we need to let Bro rest somewhere!
But we have nowhere to go...
I know just the place!
Hold on while I draw a map.
Setsuko...!
It's a farmhouse my relatives used to live in, but nobody uses it now.
There are no other houses nearby,
so you won't need to worry about being seen.
Thank you, Setsuko!
We managed to stop the bleeding, but he's still unconscious.
And this is the last of the medicine and bandages...
He also needs nutrition of some sort...
All right! Hang on, Bro! I'll get some good food for you!
Setsuko!
Just where are you going, Maeda?
You'll get spotted if you don't stay put!
I brought medicine, food and a change of clothes.
I want to help, too.
Setsuko...
Plus, I promised I'd be there to greet Sakuragi. Didn't I, Minakami?
Thank you, Setsuko...
I feel relieved.
We wouldn't have been able to do this much on our own.
Yeah...
That's right.
It's great that Setsuko came for you, Bro...
You're so emaciated... What in the world happened to you?
I refuse... to die...
I won't let you die.
I'll - we'll - save you!
On the faces of the three sleeping boys were peaceful, proud expressions.
Scam and the others hadn't killed anyone,
so they woudln't have to go to juvenile prison.
"Whatever wind blows tomorrow, we'll do our very best!"
The boys were prepared for the worst from the very start.
Sakuragi remained in a deep sleep.
Hey, where's Turtle anyway?
I dunno. He left early this morning.
Huh? Let's just hope he doesn't swipe anything weird again.
Check it out!
Whadya think?! Nice and lively, huh?!
I'm gonna feed it to Bro!
Oww! "I wanna get eaten!" was written all over its face, so...!
How do we explain this to Setsuko?
We'll have to keep getting physical until you tell us where they are!
Soldier...
Scam?
Yeah. You didn't talk, did you?
Talk about what? I wish I knew where they went...
Anyway, how's Cabbage?
Hear for yourself.
Snoring so loudly with all we're going through?
Dunno if he's just carefree or if he's got thick skin...
All we gotta do now is put up
with one more year of Ishihara and Sasaki's abuse.
Do you regret it?
That's a stupid question.
I was prepared for this.
Still, a year without Bro...
It's going to be one long year...
"They'll beat us and they'll kick us, but they won't kill us..."
They were prepared for abuse and harassment.
The thought of all seven of them reuniting under the tree
the summer after next was enough to fill their hearts with warm hope.
Those damn kids!
What do I do about them?!
Kill 'em.
Just kill 'em.
I- Ishihara! You're already up and about?!
Get three death certificates ready.
Every who defies me will die!
Everyone! Sakuragi is awake!
He is?!
He says he has something important to tell you.
Something important?
What do you need to tell us, Bro?
Guys...
Go back to the reformatory.
Bro?
C'mon, what's wrong with you guys?
Sakuragi gave me a lot more fun than this!
Don't think you can defy me and get out of here alive!
This bastard... is serious...
He's serious about killing us...!
Ishihara! It's me!
What do you want, Doc?
He's back!
He came back!
Jo Yokosuka came back, all alone!
I dunno why you came back, but don't think you'll get off easy.
Though, if you tell us where the other three are,
I'll consider letting you off the hook.
But if you give us some fake info, you're as good as dead!
Can you take my life?
Don't get a big head, turnkey.
Yokosuka! You little...!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Just cut the crap and put Soldier and the others back in Cell 6.
Don't screw with me! Do you want to be thrown into solitary?!
Are you really sure you can talk to me that way?
What?!
You killed Eiichi Hagino.
It was all written in Hagino's suicide note.
S-suicide note?!
One he signed with his own blood.
And Bro still has it!
If the cops and the press get ahold of it,
You'll be sentenced for sure and sent straight to prison.
I'm sure you'll have fun living in hell.
So, what'll it be?
Sign: Block 2, Cell 6
J- Joe! What are you doing here?
Bro sent me!
He did?
Take it easy. I'll explain everything.
Go back to the reformatory.
Bro?
Please!
Go and help Soldier, Scam and Cabbage...
Please...
That's so stupid...
Worrying about us when you can barely even move yourself...
But why did you come alone, Joe?
One was enough. So we played rock-paper-scissors to choose.
That's how you chose?
And you lost, huh? You got no luck!
That's for sure!
No...
I didn't come here because I lost.
I came because I won.
Bro taught them to be men who can suffer a loss in stride.
In rock-paper-scissors, it's easiest to throw a forceful "rock".
So Mario and Turtle woudln't hesitate to throw "paper" to win.
Joe saw through that.
Shit!
It's over. The evidence is in Sakuragi's hands.
There's nothing you can do now.
Maybe you should submit a transfer request.
I'm going to stay away from here for a while myself.
Sakuragi!
New Year's Day, 1956
1956...
Sign: "Shonan Special Reformatory"
Sasaki had disappeared from the reformatory
and Ishihara was no longer in charge of Block 2.
The boys in Cell 6 also enjoyed a peaceful New Years season.
At their hideout, Bro had recovered somewhat,
but it still took everything he had to get up.
With so much spare time,
Mario hit his handmade punching bag day in day out.
They depended entirely on Setsuko for medicine and food.
We can't rely on Setsuko forever.
Yeah.
I'll check out the black market tomorrow.
Maybe I can find out something good.
I'll go with you.
Yum!
Hey, Mister! Feel like earning some money boxing?!
Twenty dollars if you win by knockout, ten by decision!
You even get five if you lose! What do you say?!
Damn, where did Turtle run off to?
Hey, Mario! Mario!
I got some great news!
Oh? You box, kid?
Are you any good?
Are you kidding, lady?!
He's the Shonan Reformatory's best fighter!
What?
He's practically in a league all his own!
Shonan Reformatory...
Hey! Don't say things like that!
Shut up! You be quiet!
Sure.
Okey! You're in!
Come to the American army base in Tachikawa this Saturday!
All right! We did it, Mario!
Wait, is your right hand gonna be okay?
Yeah, it healed a long time ago.
I haven't used it in so long that I've been iching to try it out again.
Oh! That's great, then!
I have no choice...
America had won the war and Japan had lost.
Stemming from this, American versus Japanese boxing matches
took place weekly on the U.S. Amry base in Tachikawa.
In the red corner were specially-selected American Soldiers.
In the blue corner would be a mishmash group of Japanese people.
Let's see.
Twenty dollars for a win by knockout, ten by decision, five if you lose.
Okay! No mistake about it!
I'm going home with twenty dollars.
Yeah! Make sure you win, Mario!
Mr. Mario Minakami.
Oh, yes, yes! I'm the manager!
Your game is winner-takes-all, okay?
Okay! Okay! It's all okay!
Right. Come on.
Okay! Let's go, Mario!
I'm gonna come home with a lot of money!
Hang on, Bro!
Letter: Bro: We went out to earn us lots of money, so don't worry.
Guys...
Mario! Mario!
One! Two! Three!
What? What the hell?
What am I doing?
Damn it...
I've come so far...
I can't lose now...!
Fight!
C'mon, Mario! Don't you dare lose!
Mario!
Shit! Our twenty dollars is gonna turn into five!
I guess you didn't understand...
...what "winner-takes-all" means...
W- What are you talking about, Mister?
Winner-takes-all means the winner gets all the prize money.
In other words, the loser won't even get one cent.
Wh-what?! You gotta be kidding me!
We don't even got the bus fare to get back home!
Mario!
Hey, stop already! Stop!
The fight's already over! Ref!
Damn it! You're gonna kill Mario!
Don't kid! You'll get killed!
That's enough!
Is it really that fun to bully weaker people?!
In that case, why don't you fight me?!
Sorry, Mario... It's my fault...
I couldn't even land one good punch...
It's wasn't your fault.
Licking each others wounds, losers?
You said he was in a league of his own at the reformatory
so I had high hopes... How pathetic.
And you call yourself a Japanese man?
Did you really think you could beat that GI
when you can barely use your right hand?
What?! Mario, you said...!
Quit trying to act tough, kid!
What would you know?!
What would a filthy American whore like you know?!
Take it and go.
What?!
Men always think acting tough makes them real men.
I'm sick of it...
I'm sick of seeing Japanese men lose to America...
Get stronger...
Get stronger and then come try again.
Damn it!
I won't let myself be indebted to you! I will pay this money back!
I expect you to.
I'm Lilly. Bring it back to me ten-fold.
It was an utter defeat.
Mario wasn't the only one hurt.
The woman named Lilly also felt as if she had been hit.
The one-sided defeat multiplied their sadness and pain
by four, even eight times.
It was now that Mario learned the big difference
between fighting and boxing.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
A demon is revived.
Mario and Sakuragi head to the ring.
The poisonous snake smiles.
The bell rings.