Fumizuki Academy is a new school that has
implemented a special system for the first time.
All right, please begin.
The first part of this system is the Exam Summoning Battle.
Battles are waged between
Summoned Beings of different classes,
which are given form by the latest technology.
The other key element of the system is classroom
facilities which directly correspond to one's ability.
Students take a placement exam at the end of each school year,
and are then divided into six classes
from A through F based on their scores.
Finally time to take the placement exam...
This ain't gonna be a walk in the park, but I can handle it.
Himeji!
Are you okay? Pull yourself together!
Leaving the room during the exam will result in a zero. Am I clear?
But teach!
What is it, Yoshii?
She's sick!
Yoshii...
You're late, Yoshii.
Ironman...
My name is Mr. Nishimura, not Ironman.
Here you go. You're the last one.
These are the results of your placement exam.
You'll be assigned to whatever class is written in there.
All right.
I guess I might as well tell you this now.
After everything you showed me last year, I had my suspicions that you were an idiot.
However, after I saw your score, I realized that I was mistaken.
I have to apologize for doubting you, Yoshii. You're not an idiot.
You're one hell of an idiot!
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Fly! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
First Period
Idiots and Tests and Summoning Wars
Fumizuki Academy is a new school that has
implemented a special system for the first time.
What the hell? Class F?
Akihisa Yoshii
That's the worst class.
And I thought I was gonna do well, too.
I mean, I have to have at least gotten 10% right...
Fumizuki Academy is a new school that takes pride in the fact that it uses only the latest study materials.
Wow!
System desks and reclining seats!
They even have laptops!?
Dear lord, a self-serving bar! Class A
can have snacks whenever they want!
Straw floors... Floor cushions... Coffee tables...
This is my classroom!?
Reality is a harsh mistress at Fumizuki Academy.
If one wishes to have a more comfortable educational experience, he or she must make better grades.
That is the academy's central tenet.
God damn... So I guess this is a caste system, huh?
Yoshii, hurry up and sit down.
Fine. Where do I sit?
Wherever you like.
There's no seating chart!?
Excuse me, my cushion doesn't have any stuffing in it.
Just deal with it.
Excuse me, but there's wind blowing in from the crack in the window. It's quite chilly.
Excuse me, my table broke.
Just deal with it.
What the hell!?
Just kidding.
Yes, reality is truly cruel at Fumizuki Academy.
I'm Fukuhara, the teacher for this class.
I hope we'll have a-
I'm going to go get this fixed. You
can study whatever in the meantime.
Man, this place sucks.
We're supposed to spend the entire year here?
Hey, man, you shoulda scored better on the test if you were gonna bitch.
Yuuji! You're in this class too?
Sakamoto
Yuuji
Look who else is here.
Yo! Looks like I'm stuck here too.
Shimada
Minami
Shimada!
Yeah, I'm not surprised you're in F.
Are you calling me an idiot?
Owowowowow! This shit hurts when chicks without any tits do it!
N-Nearly there...
Kouta Tsychiya
I haven't lived in Japan for a while,
so I couldn't read the questions, that's all.
Looks like it's pretty lively in here.
Hideyoshi?
Kinoshita
Hideyoshi
I'm in this class too.
Hopefully this won't suck too much.
I can drink to that.
Anyway, yeah, this is the worst class in the entire school.
All of the guys in here look retarded.
That includes you.
Thank goodness we have a cute girl like Hideyoshi!
I'm a guy.
Male
I'm a girl.
Female
You guys don't get it.
Girls are beings who are so gentle and
kind that they can mend a broken heart...
Shimada, on the other hand,
is rough, frightening, and flat...
Jesus Christ, my spine!
Ow...
Excuse me, I'm sorry I'm late.
I was in the nurse's office.
Himeji
Mizuki
Himeji...
Yoshii!
What's the matter?
Doesn't that hurt?
You're gonna snap my spine into two!
It's gonna break... You bitch...
Nearly there...
Don't leave us, Voyeur!
Li... Li...
Don't talk! I'll call an ambulance.
Light blue...
Voyeur!
Well, at least I'm not the only girl here.
Voyeur! I'll save you!
There's no seating chart, so sit wherever you want.
Save him! Somebody save him!
Okay, thank you.
Umm, is that seat free?
Yeah.
Oh, so you got placed into class F...
Well, let's make the best of it-
You're still sick?
Yeah, a little...
This place is worn out as hell.
Like, the cushions might as well be rocks.
The floor's a veritable breeding ground for mold.
This isn't somewhere a sick person should be!
What's up?
I've been thinking about something.
Isn't school, like, a microcosm of society?
How dare they segregate us like this!?
And they'll treat us like dogs if we complain about it.
As such, we'll simply have to challenge them fair and square.
Once we come into power and gain the right to speak up, we'll tell the world about-
In other words, you want somewhere more amenable to Himeji, yeah?
Hey, come on! I was trying to make it sound all noble!
Why'd you have to ruin it?
To be honest, I was thinking the same thing.
Really?
I want to prove to the world that grades aren't everything.
I'm pretty confident, at least.
Wanna try it, Akihisa?
Yeah, let's try out an Exam Summoning Battle!
Exam Summoning Battle
Listen up, guys.
I'd like to propose something as your class representative.
I want us to engage in an Exam Summoning Battle!
What!?
An Exam Summoning Battle? What the...
Fumizuki Academy has a system called the Exam Summoning Battle, also known as the ESB.
Under the supervision of a teacher,
students can summon a Being with attack power proportional to their grades in a given subject.
They can challenge other classes using these Beings.
If a lower level class defeats a higher level
one, they will swap facilities and classrooms.
Guys, are you happy with this crappy room?
Hell no!
If we win an ESB,
we'll be able to get class A's fabulous room!
We're the lowest class.
The bottom of this school.
We're nothing but a bunch of garbage!
And that means that we have nothing to lose.
So why don't we give it a shot?
And we have him!
Yoshii Akihisa is a legendary Punishment Inspector.
PUNISHMENT INSPECTOR
Seriously!?
Wow! I've never seen one before!
Amazing! He's left me in despair!
Well, uh, not really...
Yes, Himeji?
Are Punishment Inspectors strong?
Yeah. Only very special people can be one.
It's a title given to mentally
disabled kids who get bad grades.
It translates to "Idiot".
In other words, a worthless piece of crap.
Wow! That's amazing!
Just take me now!
If we win an ESB, we can kiss this classroom goodbye.
What say we give it a try?
We need to start with the class directly above us - class E.
Akihisa, you're now class F's ambassador.
Go and declare war on class E.
Me?
Don't bad things happen to ambassadors from weaker countries when they declare war?
Nah, only in movies and novels.
Come on, who on Earth would mess with an ambassador?
But...
Akihisa, you're the only one who can do this for us.
Pretend that I tricked you or something. Hop to it!
You tricked me!
Yeah, this is about what I thought would happen.
You predicted this!?
Duh. I'm the rep for a reason.
At least act like you're sorry!
We can no longer turn back, Akihisa.
Are you prepared?
Isn't this what you wanted?
Yeah. Don't worry, I'm ready.
Oh? The sophomores have declared an ESB during the first semester?
Interesting.
They have my permission.
Understood.
Put on a nice show for me.
Our supervisor is Mr. Hasegawa.
Seize him right before fifth period, while he's walking to class E.
Mr. Hasegawa, the math teacher?
Math is my thing.
All right, Shimada will be our
mainline, since she's good at math.
Himeji, are you good at math?
I'm not bad.
Then team up with me.
No.
Why?
Your attack points are equal to the
grade you received on your last test.
Our last test was...
The placement exam.
I had to leave during the exam, so I got a 0.
You can take a recovery exam once the ESB begins.
If Himeji takes it, she'll be able to join us when she finishes.
Okay...
Good luck.
Thanks.
We've seized Mr. Hasegawa!
It's time for war, people! Let's go!
For crying out loud... these guys are friggin' morons.
Guys, it's time to sortie.
Go teach those failures a lesson!
Minami Shimada, reporting in.
Hideyoshi Kinoshita, ready to go.
Kouta Tsychiya, same here!
Permitted.
Summoning Being!
Summon!
Name:
Subject:          Math
Points:
Summon!
Name:
Subject:          Math
Points:
Summon!
Name:
Subject:          Math
Points:
Why was I the only one with a transformation sequence?
Here they come.
Be careful. Living flesh can't cross that barrier.
If you wanna get past here, you're gonna have to beat us first.
Yoshiko Mika, I accept.
Summon!
Name:
Subject:          Math
Points:
You brat...
You're finished!
That's my line!
You're kidding...
There's no way class E can beat me at math!
Those who were KIA, meet in the detention room.
That's...
Ironman!
Acording to ESB rules, those whose points reach zero must receive supplementary lessons.
Save me! I don't want to have detention with this monster!
If you want to pass, then you have to defeat us.
Very well, then.
Summon!
Let's go!
Supply Room
Hurry up and get started.
What's our plan, Yuuji?
We don't have one.
It's like tug-of-war - whichever class gets
pushed back will have their classroom invaded.
And if their rep gets defeated, that side loses.
That won't happen to us, right?
Dammit! They're pushing us back!
Class E has better grades overall.
If we go head to head, it's only a matter of time before we lose.
You're kidding me.
Still, they are only class E. It'll take them a while to make it all the way here.
And the time it'll take them to do that is the key to our victory.
My points...
They're gonna murder us at this rate!
Go on standby and recover your points.
All right.
I want to take the recovery test!
Whatever you recieve on this test will become your Being's attack points the next time you summon it.
If you score low, then your Being will become weak.
Are you all right with that?
Yes.
Which subject?
Math, please.
I need to answer as much as I can to recover my points...
Oh, no!
Voyeur!
Retreat!
This is our victory.
Shit!
Assault them.
Our defensive line is down.
This is bad, Yuuji!
Numbers are just numbers... they're not Japanese.
Oh god, kanji!
I'll skip this question.
Those who were KIA, meet in the detention room!
What should we do, Yuuji?
Are you guys finished?
Sorry, but it looks like it's about time for us to end this.
My, my, coming here yourself, eh? Don't underestimate us.
Are you guys idiots? You declared an ESB as soon as school began.
We just finished taking the placement exam.
Our differences in class are equivalent to our differences in points.
Did you really think you'd win?
Beats me.
I see.
You guys are in class F because you're so stupid, I guess.
Yuuji, we're not going to be able to beat the classes above us without a plan...
Oh yeah, I do have a plan.
Know why I kept you with me?
I see.
Don't tell me...
Correct! He's Akihisa Yoshii, the Punishment Inspector.
Akihisa, show them your true power!
Guess I've got no choice... It always comes down to me in the end.
Summon.
The Punishment Inspector's Being has special powers.
Because it has to assist teachers with their chores as punishment,
it's corporeal, unlike the rest.
Also, any pain it feels will be felt by its summoner as well.
Isn't it cool?
That's all?
Fine.
I'll take care of that small fry first.
Summon!
You won't take me down that easily!
Charge!
Owowowowowow!
It makes sense that you're the rep for E class.
Your bodyguard's pretty damn useless.
Nah, he's good enough.
I'll finish you off personally.
Get ready.
I, Hiromi Nakabayashi, challenge you, Yuuji Sakamoto, to-
Please wait!
Mizuki Himeji, I accept!
Summoning Being.
Summon!
Here I go!
Why are her points so high!?
This is class A level!
Why is a student like that...
There she is.
Himeji!
Mizuki Himeji... Don't tell me... you're...
Yoshii!
Shinada?
She's totally awesome!
No wonder she was a candidate for class A...
That's Himeji's score?
In Fumizuki Academy, you can take as many tests as you wish during the testing period.
As such, you can acquire as points as you are capable of.
So, your plan was...
to buy time while she took the test.
No one told me she was in class F!
It's my turn. I'm sorry.
N-No way...
This Exam Summoning Battle ends in class F's victory.
Wow, you're amazing, Himeji!
This is all thanks to you.
Oh, you're just saying that...
Now we can switch classrooms and facilities with class E!
Well, it's better, at least...
No, we're not switching facilities.
We'll keep what we have now.
Hey, don't you think it's a good idea, Nakabayashi?
Wait, why?
Why, Yuuji? I mean, we won!
So it's over?
Hideyoshi, why are you dressed like that?
Ahh, that's it. You've finally understood the calling in your heart.
I'm over here, Akihisa.
There are two of you?
That's my sister.
Hideyoshi is my twin brother.
I'm the ambassador from class 2A, Yuuko Kinoshita.
We, class A, declare war on you, class F.
Why is class A declaring war on us!?
Don't think we'll go easy on you just because you're the lowest class.
We're going to obliterate you.
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
Question 2:
Please answer the following question:
This plant has roots which can be eaten. In English, it is known as a "lily".
Yam! Potato! Sweet potato!
Please also pay attention to the second part of the question.
Next episode: Lilies and Roses and PE.
This will be on your test.