Rider, look.
You scared, boy?
Yeah. I'm scared.
Or, as you might put it, my heart is dancing.
Looks like you're starting to understand.
The enemy is within?
Berserker?
You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
So that nobody would have to cry ever again
we all scream and pray on fields stained red with blood
yet our pleas reach no one
I will be able to leave my solace behind
The moon's beautiful light
shines on all that makes up
the beginning
With eyes kept barely open I still see you far away
and trust your grief
They're going to have a drink here?
What has become of your little chariot?
Well...
I'm embarrassed to say that I lost it to Saber.
Did you forget my decision?
I'm certain I told you that I would defeat you at your full strength.
True, my weapons are not what they might be.
However...
Iskandar tonight is less than perfect,
and thus, is greater than perfection.
So I see.
Indeed, the aura that overflows from you...
It is unusually potent.
It appears you do believe you can defeat me.
King of Babylonia, a final word.
A question with which to conclude our banquet.
I shall allow it.
Speak.
Purely hypothetically,
were my Ionian Hetairoi armed with your Gate of Babylon,
it would create the most powerful army imaginable.
And?
Would you not ally yourself with me?
Together, the two of us could conquer the very stars.
You never cease to amuse me.
It has been aeons since I laughed so hard at anyone but a fool.
But unfortunately,
I have had but one comrade, and he is all I shall ever have.
And there is no need for two kings.
A lonely path of kingship...
I shall challenge your unwavering spirit with respect.
Very well.
Show me what you can do, King of Conquerors.
You are an usurper worthy of my judgment.
Are you guys really friends?
I could hardly be unfriendly to him.
He may well be the last person I ever see.
Don't be stupid.
You can't die here!
I won't allow it!
Have you forgotten my Command Seal?
You're right...
You're exactly right!
Gather, my comrades!
Tonight, we become the greatest legend in history!
Our enemy is the mighty King of Heroes,
a truly worthy opponent!
My warriors, let us show the first Heroic Spirit
our path of conquest!
Come to me, lord of conquering armies.
Now you will behold the form of a true king.
Why must you suffer so?
Because Berserker...
must fight.
Why?
Because the priest said so.
Priest?
Yeah...
He promised me.
That he'd give me the Grail.
If I have the Grail,
I can save you.
You're going to save me?
Yeah. I promised you...
that we'd all play together like we used to.
Then...
I'll be able to see Mom again, right?
Mom...
Now!
It didn't hurt him?
Can he see it?
He knows the length of this blade...
Could he be some knight I once knew?
I ask this,
assuming you to be a skilled knight.
If you know me to be Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
give me your name,
as a knight's pride demands!
To attack with one's identity shrouded is worthy only of an assassin!
You are...
N-No...
Arondight?
You can't be...
Arthur...
Sir Lancelot...
Why, my friend?
You were the first among the Knights of the Round Table! So, why?
How could you become Berserker—
Lancelot?
Lancelot...
You saved them, but you never led them.
Because I never led them...
Enraptured by a false idol, the king who serves others...
My ideals...
My kingship...
Only a little girl.
Did they push you to do this?!
Arthur!
Lancelot...
To unite your dreams beneath a banner of conquest.
I praise your efforts.
But, warriors...
Do you not understand?
All dreams must disappear when the dreamer wakes.
Every last one of them.
Therefore,
it was inevitable that I would stand in your way.
King of Conquerors,
know the end of your eternal dream.
I, myself, shall show you harsh reality.
Here it comes!
Now awaken, Ea!
A worthy stage has been set for you!
Look up and behold...
Enuma Elish!
Hang on, boy!
That...
Is that sword really
the anti-planet Noble Phantasm that can destroy anything?
Rider...
Come to think of it,
there was something I wanted to ask of you.
Waver Velvet,
would you serve as my retainer?
You...
You are my king...
I will serve you, and only you.
Please lead me...
Let me dream your dream!
Very well.
As king, my duty is to inspire others to dream.
And as my retainer, it is your task to see my dream to the end,
and to speak of it to future generations.
Live, Waver.
See all of this to the end.
And when it is done, speak of it.
Of your king...
Of Iskandar's glorious charge!
Now...
Let us go, Bucephalus!
Rider!
Glory lies beyond the horizon...
Challenge it because you know you cannot reach it.
Speak of conquest, and make it real.
For my men, who watch behind me!
As I thought...
Your bag of strange tricks is endless indeed.
Have you awakened from your dream,
King of Conquerors?
Indeed.
My heart danced a great deal...
during this campaign.
Challenge me again, as many times as you like,
King of Conquerors.
This world will remain my garden until the end of time.
Thus, I can guarantee this:
It will never bore you.
I am glad to hear that.
I see...
The beating of my heart...
was the sound of Okeanos' waves...
Child...
Are you Rider's Master?
No.
I am his retainer.
I see.
But then, child, if you are truly loyal,
your duty is to avenge your fallen king.
If I challenge you, I will die.
Of course.
I can't do that.
I was ordered to survive.
Your loyalty is splendid!
Never tarnish it.
He restores my soul.
He leads me down paths of righteousness for his name's sake.
Even though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for you are with me;
your rod and your staff—
they comfort me.
You prepare a table before me in the presence of my enemies;
you anoint my head with oil.
My cup overflows.
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me all the days of my life.
Episode 23:
The Sea at the End of the World
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
You would steal the Holy Grail from me?!
What are you doing, Saber?!
Such a troublesome person.
Impossible!
It longs for its own life! For its own birth!
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
I knew you'd come.
Next Time:
The Last Command Seal