Hello, Renji-kun.
Ah, hello. You look relaxed today.
Here. I've finished my novel.
I finished the end by myself.
I-Is that so?
What's wrong?
Congratulations on finishing it.
Thank you.
But I don't think it's quite finished yet.
I want Renji-kun to read it. After he reads and checks for any problems, then it will be finished.
What did you do for the last part?
Eh?
Will you have the girl enter the painting as the ending?
Or will you have the boy leave the painting as the ending?
You've already decided on which one you'd use, right?
Well... you'll know when you read it.
Yeah, you're right.
Wait, please.
Eh?
Please, read it after I leave. It's embarrassing.
I should do something in order to thank you.
To thank me?
It wouldn't have been possible for me to finish this novel by myself.
This was all thanks to you, Renji-kun.
I didn't do anything. It was all thanks to Chihiro's determination to write.
No.
If it wasn't for you, Renji-kun, I wouldn't have been able to do anything.
Renji-kun, it was because of you that my one dream was granted.
Yes, the way I am now...
Please let me do something to repay you. I want to express my gratitude to you, Renji-kun.
Chihiro...
Whatever I can do, please let me know.
Well, how about you and I go on a date?
Eh? A date?
It's not possible?
A date is something that lovers would do.
Would it be wrong if we became lovers?
I guess not. I suppose it wouldn't work if it was with me.
That isn't...! That's not what I mean.
I understand. Let's become lovers.
But, only for a day.
Only for a day?
Yes.
Tomorrow, Renji-kun and I will become lovers for a day.
Then let's go on a date.
Just for tomorrow?
You might say that it's a test.
Well, what about tomorrow then?
Why don't we think about tomorrow instead?
Could I have you read that novel the next time we meet?
Eh?
Please read it after tomorrow's date.
It's amazing how similar the two of you are.
Who am I similar to?
Who knows... I've long forgotten about it.
Is it the person that's waiting for you, Himura-san?
I've forgotten that as well.
Umm...
Hmm?
What kind of feeling is it when you fall in love?
A good question.
It's something that's uncontrollable.
Uncontrollable?
When you get hurt, it's already too late.
Whatever this feeling may be is something that comes far too late.
Is that so? In that case I might be too late myself.
I see.
Umm... I want to thank you for everything up to now.
Why are you saying that now?
I had a feeling... that if I didn't express my feelings before it was too late, I'd forget it all.
I didn't do anything at all.
That's the same thing that Renji-kun said.
We're the same too I suppose.
Give this to him.
What is it?
Just a simple custom.
Good morning.
G-Good morning.
What's wrong?
Umm, well that dress...
Since it's a date, I decided to dress appropriately for it.
Onee-chan bought this for me, but I've never had a chance to wear it.
Wonderful. It looks really cute on you.
Thank you.
Did you have anything planned?
I was thinking that maybe we could go watch a film. What do you think?
That sounds good.
What would be a good one to watch?
Perhaps for this situation... maybe something romantic?
If it's something that isn't sad...
Something that isn't sad?
I might break down into tears for something like that.
Well, how about a comedy then?
That sounds good. I'd like that.
Ah... I'm sorry.
Well, I didn't think the end would be a tearjerker like that.
I guess I failed, huh?
I'm sorry.
I-I'm going... to go wash my face.
Do you have a tissue?
I didn't bring any.
Sorry about that.
Welcome back.
Well, it was a great story.
It was interesting having the story develop that way.
I thought it'd be a slapstick comedy, but instead it had a heartfelt development.
It did, didn't it?
I didn't think the end would be a tearjerker.
I was glad that it ended with a happy ending.
I-I'm really... glad...
I'm... going to go wash my face...
Umm... do you need a tissue?
You're mean!
Where do you want to go next?
Good question. It probably wouldn't be good to go somewhere crowded.
A game center might be out of the question too.
Want to give it a shot?
That was a bit tricky, huh?
The crane was weak too.
And the material easily slips away too.
Maybe we should go next door where it might be easier to get it.
Wait, I know...
Next time, I'll get one for you. I know a place that sells them.
The one I wanted...
The one I wanted was in there...
Let's go back!
That was the one, right? I'll get it no matter what!
I've got it... I've got it...This time I've got it!
Go!
Got it!
It'd better not drop!
Just like that... like that... like that...
Alright!
I finally got it!
Here you go!
Thank you very much!
Poyo.
Poyo?
I have one at home called Puyo-chan. This one is called Poyo-chan.
A-Ah, okay.
Could we do that too?
Eh?
I'd like one, please.
There's plenty. Would you like half of them?
One is fine.
Really?
Thank you, Renji-kun.
Sure.
Today has been a lot of fun.
That's good.
Umm, Renji-kun...
Yes?
Could we hold hands?
Huh? S-Sure.
Thank you.
We're lovers after all, right?
That's true.
I feel that if I'm with you like this, that I'll become more carefree.
What should we do now?
If it's all right with you, I'd like to go to the sea.
The sea?
It seems that the sea is where lovers would go.
Really?
Yes. I read that in a book.
What do lovers do when they come here?
Well, if we were to just be like this and not do anything, it wouldn't be a bad idea either.
That's true.
In the past, we've been here before, right?
Yeah.
Many things happened, didn't they?
That's right.
Many things did happen.
I've reread all of it. But I don't remember any of it.
But if what happens today...
will then turn into tomorrow...
Wouldn't it be better if we didn't meet tomorrow?
I would never say something like that.
Perhaps tomorrow will be even better than today?
You're right.
Ah, I totally forgot.
Himura-san told me to give this to you.
He said it's the key to the school rooftop.
Huh? Why?
He said that watching the sunset from the rooftop of the school is very beautiful.
That's not what I mean. Why does Himura-san have something like that?
Hmm, why does he have this?
He's a real enigma, isn't he?
At that school, it is a custom for someone to hand it down to someone else, he said.
Well, shall we give it a shot?
Yes!
Amazing...
I should thank Himura-san after this.
Yes.
Wow! It's amazing!
Be careful running around like that!
It's okay!
This really is something.
Yeah...
Chihiro...
Yes?
I love you.
Tomorrow, the day after, and always... I will love you, Chihiro.
That didn't really fit my character, did it?
That probably wasn't a good one.
I love you.
May I kiss you?
Kissing is something that lovers do.
I am Chihiro's lover.
At a time like this, you should just say nothing and kiss me.
You're right.
Yes.
You hit my teeth.
Well then, let's try that again.
Ah!
S-Sorry!
I guess I was getting carried away.
Please don't stop.
The me of today finally came this far; I don't want to be treated distantly again.
Chihiro...
I really want to become lovers with you, Renji-kun. So please...
Why me?
I don't know.
What about you, Chihiro?
Why me?
I don't know.
It's just...
Just...?
...that I love Renji-kun as well.
Chihiro.
What is it?
I love you.
Eh?
I really love you.
I know.
Renji-kun.
Yes?
W-Wait a minute...
No, don't.
Geez...
You mean about today?
Yes. Where you said I love you.
What did you write?
I can't say that in front of someone.
Well, the parts you can say, then.
Okay. You hit my teeth.
Uhh, well I guess the rest you aren't going to tell me then.
I can't say.
10 p.m.
In other words, the Chihiro that I met at the train station at 9 a.m. up to now... will begin to fade.
From now, every hour that passes...
The things that happened today by the hour...
will disappear within Chihiro.
Everything will disappear.
What's wrong, Renji-kun?
Nothing. It's nothing.
Okay.
It's nothing, then.
Today I went over the limit.
We've gone past the test's length, right?
You brought it with you?
Yes.
Please read it.
After that, it's complete.
Chihiro?
I guess I really am embarrassed to be next to someone reading it.
I'm going up to the rooftop to read this.
I want to read again about when I first met Renji-kun up to now.
Please let me know when you finish reading the novel.
Okay.
See you in a bit.
"The girl is only one in the world. That made her the god of this world."
"Something mysterious happened."
"The two in those paintings had moved."
"She looked closely at the paintings."
"The two in the pictures seemed to be doing something, smiling at each other."
"But the paintings were blurred. The world itself appeared blurred, giving her no clue to see what they were doing."
"'Why?' the girl thought."
"A strange feeling developed in her mind."
"She could not describe what it was."
"Why did the paintings become so blurred even though she had painted them so clearly?"
"But the two in the paintings were smiling at each other. That was what she felt."
"She repainted them over and over. But the results were exactly the same."
"She was at a loss. She began to be unsure about everything."
"The girl is only one in the world. That made her the god of this world."
"So the god thought she should make her world cleaner."
"She burned all the pictures."
"She set fire to the old castle."
"She burned all her memories."
"Lastly, the god...
...the only trash left in the world,
...off the cliff."
Renji-kun.
I finished reading your novel.
How was it?
Well, I was a bit surprised.
A sad way to end it, huh?
That isn't true.
To the girl, that was the happiest ending.
Of course, it wasn't good for the girl to have come into contact with anyone... since she'd understand the feeling of loneliness.
Chihiro...
That girl was me.
Renji-kun, this is goodbye.
No.
This is the reason why I brought you to the school rooftop.
No...
I'm sorry...
No!
Do you remember the story about the sheep?
Tied to a chain, it ate only the grass and died. That sheep story.
I feel like I've been chained with the length of twelve years.
And regardless of what day it was, I couldn't go to the outside world.
Only if I was escorted, then I could be out for thirteen hours at a time.
The point of writing the story was the dream I've had these past twelve years.
That is why when I finished it, that would be the end for me.
I decided upon this from the beginning.
When I finished this novel, I wanted to disappear from Renji-kun's eyes...
so that there wouldn't be any memories.
Very silently much like the mermaid princess, I thought I would disappear just like that.
But, since I'm weak, this way I'm not a mermaid princess, but a Cinderella.
But that's fine.
It's childish to say I'm the prince, but still-
No, that's not it, Renji-kun.
I was happy. I was very, very happy.
I love you, Renji-kun.
But the way I am, I don't want you to ever disappear from my heart!
I want us to part ways knowing that you love me.
That... reason... doesn't make sense.
You lent me your story about your will to never give up.
I put on my uniform and was able to go to school.
From that abandoned station, you picked me up and showed me the way.
Before that, I would never look up while I stood at that train station.
I always felt like I wanted to cry.
Every time I looked up, tears would come out.
Even like that, you embraced me.
For me you felt pain; for me you cried...
That is why I want you to be happy as well.
I don't want you to be sad.
Chihiro...
If you were to stay with me, I think that you will always be in pain.
I don't want that to happen.
I'm not disappearing because I'm angry.
I wanted to think of a way to not let you feel sad.
For someone like me who can't do anything, I was able to find a solution.
No!
Please feel proud of me.
I love you, Chihiro!
For something that foolish, I can't be proud of it!
Please smile.
No!
Like you always do, please smile as we part ways.
No...
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
Chihiro!
This is...!
I chose to do this.
This is my diary from when I first met you up to now.
Now I have disappeared from your memory.
And now, I will no longer have any memories of you.
Thus, this is our true parting.
The end of the season.
The beginning of time.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
Love.
Are there memories you don't want to forget?