That's right. Ginko committed a grave crime.
Ginko was Sumika's--
I'll...
...never forgive bears!
I'll ruin bears!
Growl!
We hated you from the beginning--
and loved you from the beginning, too.
And so we wanted to become
true friends with you. To cross the wall...
Yurikumaaaaaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
"THE FUTURE OF THE GIRLS"
Viens avec moi
Church chimes echo in the distance
Offer up a prayer and betray today
Wander in a dark forest, then become
the morning moon at the Wall of Severance
I won't join the Invisible Storm
Once I've made you stickier
with sweet, thin honey
Please, approve me, I'll be a good girl
Picture-book pages dancing on
the breeze shake up shadowy memories
Always
I'll be waiting you-know-where,
in an empty world
Even if everything falls apart
Even if you have to gracefully writhe,
even if you have to bend space-time
Find me
Flower petals will slowly
enfold us on a starry night
Come on...
J'ai besoin de toi
Girls, this is way bad! People are
saying another bear was here yesterday.
But I heard it was exterminated right away!
That same girl shot it, right?
The Invisible Storm one?
Yeah, but--and this is way secret--
apparently that bear's still alive.
Welcome to the Door to Friendship, you silly girl.
"Door to Friendship・(Place)"
Now I've gotten rid of the nuisance.
Ginko Yurishiro... You're the girl Reia
gave her pendant to on that stormy night.
The foolish girl.
Instead of getting love,
you fell into the abyss.
It's your own fault, you know.
You knew Lulu Yurigasaki loved you,
but you pretended not to see.
And then you tried to abandon her.
You're paying the price of that sin.
Guess what, Reia?
Your daughter Kureha Tsubaki
is about to be my bride-in-the-box.
Yes, today...
Shock!
Bear shock!
...I'm going to eat Kureha Tsubaki! Purrowr!
I...
Yes, you're alive. For now.
Oh, did I surprise you?
You're... supposed to be dead, growl.
That's right, I died.
You're the only one who can see me now.
Let's say I'm a ghost named "Desire,"
dwelling inside you right... here...
That'll do for an explanation.
Where are we?
The Door to Friendship.
The center of the sky that divides
the worlds of moon and forest.
The place where true love is tested.
So, tell me--how did you kill Sumika Izumino?
"Flashback"
I say we come early tomorrow
morning and fix the flowerbed.
I'll help, of course.
Thank you, Yurizono!
Let's do it, okay? You, too, Tsubaki.
A-All right.
Who did that?!
I sensed it then.
I had a rival at this school
who was after Kureha Tsubaki.
Another bear in human form
besides Konomi and me.
If I didn't hurry,
another bear would beat me to her.
So...
"Flashback"
Well, I'm headed this way.
See you tomorrow!
Listen, Izumino, about tomorrow...
Why don't the two of us arrange a surprise?
A surprise?
I know someone with young lilies
in bloom who'd probably give us some.
I bet we can have them by tonight!
Really?!
Yes. So let's beat Tsubaki
to school tomorrow morning,
and fill the flowerbed with lots of new lilies!
What? But that would...
It'll be just like magic!
I'm sure Tsubaki will be thrilled!
That girl would've done anything
if I said it was for Kureha Tsubaki.
Now come on, be honest.
You found out that I was
targeting Sumika Izumino.
"Flashback"
I knew all along that you were following her.
Do you like those flowers?
What?
You're the exchange student...
Sniff, sniff.
They smell nice, don't they?
Do you like lilies, too?
Lilies remind me of a special memory.
A special memory with a friend I love.
I won't back down on love.
Because the love she gave me,
no one can take away from me.
I-I'm sorry!
It was probably weird for me to tell
you that when we've only just met...
You were jealous of her, weren't you?
The love you wanted so badly from Kureha
had already been given to another girl.
"That Fateful Morning・(History)"
And yet you went to her again,
without even telling your partner your intentions.
Why, to warn her about me?
Yes. That was my plan.
Oh no, I can't believe I lost it again...
Here.
Thank you for finding it!
I'm so glad! You know, this is the second time
someone's found this for me.
I lost it the day of the entrance ceremony, too.
It was the friend I told you
about yesterday who found it.
She... found...
Yep. This pin brought me friendship and love.
It's my special charm.
Thank you so much, Yurishiro!
Now, I've got to hurry, or I'll be late!
Wait--
I was the one she found first, growl...
That's right, if you'd stopped her then,
Sumika Izumino wouldn't have had to die.
Kureha Tsubaki wouldn't
have had to lose a dear friend!
To me...
Sumika was in the way.
We exclude those in our way.
We ought to be honest about what we want.
So that's it... I wanted Sumika to die.
"Flashback"
Good morning, Izumino!
Shock!
Bear shock!
It's such a nice morning. And I'm starving!
Chomp, chomp, grawr.
You witnessed me attacking
Sumika Izumino, and you just let her die.
You could've saved her, but you didn't.
I'm the one who ate her.
But the one who killed her...
...was me.
That's right! In that moment,
you were a slave of desire.
Jealousy drove you to a terrible crime.
I'm a criminal-bear, growl.
Yes. But is there any creature
who doesn't sin in order to live?
Kureha Tsubaki forgot you, her friend,
and gave her love to Sumika Izumino.
Now listen closely: Only one thing
is certain in this world, and it's not friends.
It's me--desire.
Love is a savage emotion.
To love someone is to rule them.
To want to become one with them
so badly that you consume them.
I'll tell you something you'll want to know--
There's another bear at that school besides us.
A very cunning bear, too.
She got Kureha to kill me,
and she got Lulu Yurigasaki to betray you.
I hate to admit it, but that bitch-bear
had all of us dancing to her tune.
--She's after Kureha Tsubaki right now.
--Chomp, chomp, purrowr. Chomp, chomp, purrowr.
If you don't hurry,
you'll lose her forever this time.
Now, become one with me.
It's time to prove your love!
Grawr grawr grawr, graw-ha-ha-ha-ha!
The bear opens!
I'm going to eat her, growl.
These photos were discovered
in the locker of Kaoru Harishima,
who recently died in a bear attack.
As you can see, Konomi Yurikawa
was actually a bear disguised as a human.
"Chouko Oki・(Yuri)"
This is way scary. Bears got across
the wall pretending to be human,
and they've eaten our friends one after another!
We all see what this means, agreed?
That's right, there is a bear
in this class--a bear among us!
Bears way stick out from our crowd!
Bears refuse to fit in with us.
Bears are evil, unable to follow social cues!
"Can't Follow Social Cues = Evil = Bear・(Exclusion)"
It's started up again.
Yep. But Kureha Tsubaki is attending this time!
They make her a friend at this late date?
Have they canceled her exclusion?
Who knows?
Those girls are always looking
for some "evil" to exclude.
It doesn't matter to them whether
the evil is a person or a bear.
The ritual of banding
together to exclude someone
makes the invisible connection
called "us" feel real to them.
It looks like they're almost there.
That's the sexy way. Shaba-da-doo--
Shall I put in another coin?
Yeah.
Shaba-da-doo...
Let us begin the Exclusion Ceremony.
"Exclusion Ceremony・(Exclusion)"
Please name the bear lurking among us.
Let's search bear!
"The Invisible Storm・(Exclusion)"
"Ginko Yurishiro"
People who shelter bears are accomplices!
Tell me, Mom...
...what should I have done that day?
"Flashback"
Lulu...
Kure-chin, I know what Ginko did to Sumika.
What?
That's right. Ginko committed a grave crime.
Ginko was Sumika's killer's accomplice!
Is that true?
It's true, growl.
I killed Sumika Izumino.
Mitsuko Yurizono killed Sumika.
I know that for sure, so...
Why would Ginko say that?
What's the truth, and what's a lie?
"Incoming Call: Blocked Number"
Hello?
Is your love the real thing?
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance.
Kureha Tsubaki, if your
love is true, go to the lily bed.
The bear is waiting for you.
So she's there? Ginko's there?
Give yourself over to the bears,
and your love will be approved.
I'll going to go talk to Ginko.
I'll find out the truth this time!
To think she masqueraded as us
to make a prank call to Kureha Tsubaki...
Yuriika Hakonaka is guilty.
Well, today was the whole
reason for her contract with us,
so she's probably ready for
the consequences. Sparkle!
All shall be as Kumaria wills it.
That's the sexy way!
Shaba-da-doo.
Ginko, what happened between us?!
I want to know the truth!
Reia, do you remember that stormy night?
I ate you.
To put you in the box of myself.
But I wasn't fulfilled. I was still empty.
After all, all your love had been given to her.
So I decided to wait.
Wait until that girl who stole
your love from me grew up...
Wait as your love
gradually blossomed inside her.
And I did, in a blank world robbed of all color.
I waited, and waited, and waited.
And at last...
The flower bloomed. Today, I eat your daughter.
Today I eat Kureha Tsubaki. Purrowr!
Ginko! Where are you?!
Pant, pant, purrowr...
Purrowrrrrr.
This is wrong. This bear isn't Ginko.
Oh, Reia, she looks just like you!
Her eyes, her hair... She even has your smell.
Kureha Tsubaki, give your love to me! Purrowr!
You and I are going to become one!
Now take my kiss, Kureha.
This is a kiss for the bride-in-the-box.
Pur-ro-rowrrrr!
That was a way close call.
You're... Oki?
The bear ran away! After it!
This is...!
Yuriika.
Yuriika... Yuriika...
Yuriika? Yuriika!
Reia... you found me.
I missed you.
This day is all I've thought of,
ever since that night I ate you!
There's something I have to return to you...
In a box in the middle of my drawers...
The Moon Girl and the Forest Girl...
The box has the rest of that picture book in it.
It was the dream of our love
that never materialized.
So I wanted it so desperately, I stole it!
I'm sorry.
Yes, you're right. That's their destiny...
Their rightful future...
Say, Reia... I really... really...
We'll be friends forever, won't we?
Yes. Friends forever.
Love you...
On the boundary that severed
ripe moon from sleeping forest
Break the law God shackles us with and smile
I turned away from the bleating flock
of shadows and howled my bloodthirsty ego
Here amidst the Invisible Storm
Overflowing honey and soul
I want to rend silk with my fangs
I'm afraid you'll vanish
like the world's last ray of hope
The savage beast inside me
tore out the throat of innocence
Come on, shoot me through the heart
with your sweet-scented Barrett of love
I can't believe Miss Yuriika
was the bear who killed Mom...
It's their destiny... Their rightful future...
This is Ginko's and my future?
No... that's impossible!