Oh, are you a visitor for Kamijou-kun?
Y–Yes...
I'm sorry... the date of his examination was moved up, so right now he's in rehabilitation.
Ah, is that so... thanks.
That girl comes frequently, doesn't she?
It's a big help. He's a difficult patient, after all.
It'd be nice if she could encourage him, but...
Before the incident, he was a child prodigy, right? At the violin.
Even if he were able to walk again, his fingers are, you know...
It'd be impossible for him to ever play an instrument again, wouldn't it?
Why was it Kyousuke?
As for things like my own fingers, no matter how much I move them, they aren't useful at all.
Why wasn't it me instead of Kyousuke?
If I used my wish to heal Kyousuke's body, how would he feel about it?
Would he just say thank you, and nothing more?
Or do I want to be told something more than that?
I'm a...
detestable girl.
When I think about it, at that time... I still didn't understand anything at all.
About the meaning of miracles and desires... or their compensation.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 4
Miracles and Magic Do Exist
A mole?
Ah, got it off.
Madoka?
Oh, if you don't eat quickly, you'll be late.
Y–Yeah...
Nee-cha, what's wrong?
I–Is it unappetizing?
No... it's delicious.
Really delicious.
I'm living, and Papa's meal...
is this delicious...
"But like, you know, Yuuka... you said that much and still haven't noticed?"
She was like, "Eh? What? Did I really say something weird again!?", and made half a crying face!
I couldn't bear it anymore and laughed until I was about to die!
(Sayaka-chan, about yesterday...)
That Yuuka-san is a truly mysterious person, you know...
(Sorry. Not right now. Try again later.)
Right, that's right, isn't it?
I wonder what's up that!?
As expected, going that far is...
Ehh, certainly... the best childbearing age is something that medical science has found...
Past subjunctive
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
When the past tense is used subjunctively, it is described as a counterfactual condition in the present. This is the past subjunctive.
The past subjunctive with present meaning can be distinguished from the past indicative with past meaning based on if the verb in the main clause takes the conditional would form or not.
iii)        's other meaning implies that "preparation is not complete, therefore we cannot go," which is a hidden meaning of the current fact.
◆ Past tense which can also express the future
◆ Subjunctive mood is not connected to a subject, 'were' is usable
◆「・・・When xxxxxxx then you insert an auxiliary verb in the past tense
But calculating a marriageable age based on that is a huge mistake, you see!
In short, the fact that women past the age of 30 also have a chance at a loving marriage is something very obvious!
Therefore, this shouldn't be past perfect, but instead, using the present progressive tense is correct—
It's sort of like... we've gone to a different country, isn't it...?
School and Hitomi-chan... nothing has changed at all since yesterday, and yet...
Somehow, it's like... there are nothing but strangers in there, it seems...
No one knows.
About witches, or about Mami-san...
We know, and everyone else knows nothing.
So now, we're already living in a different world where we see different things, aren't we?
Sayaka-chan?
It changed a very long time ago.
We should have noticed it sooner.
As for you, Madoka...
Even now, do you still think, "I want to become a magical girl"?
That's right, isn't it...
Yeah... it can't be helped.
I understand that it's unfair...
After all this time, I'm asking for too much...
But... I can't...
The way she died... When I think about it now, I can't even breathe...
It's scary...
I hate it...
Mami-san was a truly kind person.
In order to teach us a lesson about what kind of mental preparation is necessary to fight for an objective...
That person has...
Hey, Kyubey... what'll become of this city?
In Mami-san's place, I wonder who will give everyone protection from witches from now on?
This was Mami's territory for a long time, but now that there's a vacancy, other magical girls won't be silent.
Without delay, other girls will come for the purpose of hunting witches.
But that means those girls are just aiming for Grief Seeds, right?
Like that transfer student...
Certainly, a type like Mami is rare.
Normally, the pros and cons are properly considered.
Everybody wants a reward, you know.
Then...
But, if you want to criticize that...
You can only do that from the viewpoint of a girl who's equally fated to carry the burden of being a magical girl, can't you?
I understand both of your feelings.
It's regrettable, but I can't pressure you.
This is farewell.
I have to go and resume searching for girls who require a contract with me.
I'm sorry, Kyubey.
Same here. I apologize for involving you.
It was a short relationship, but thank you.
It was fun being together, Madoka.
I'm sorry.
Tomoe
Mami
Koucha Living
A modern adult's tea magazine
Fastidious
Tea
Set
A modern adult's tea magazine
Fastidious
Tea
Set
I'm so sorry...
For being a weak girl...
I'm so sorry.
Homura-chan...
You are placing too much blame on yourself, Kaname Madoka.
Eh?
A person who can do something like criticize you... doesn't exist.
If they do, I won't forgive them.
I see that you complied with my warning.
Yeah.
If I had more quickly listened to what you said, Homura-chan...
That would not have changed the fate of Tomoe Mami.
However, your fate has changed.
Rescuing even just a single person... makes me happy.
H–Homura-chan, you know...
Somehow, you give off the impression that you're a veteran in a different way than Mami-san.
That may be. I won't deny it.
Have you seen a number of people die, like yesterday?
That's right.
About how many people?
Enough to give up on counting.
I wonder if that room... will stay like that forever?
Tomoe Mami had no relatives except distant ones.
I believe it will take a while before she's reported missing.
No one... will notice the fact that Mami-san has died?
There's no helping it.
If you die on the other side, you don't leave a corpse.
In this world, she will continue to be a missing person for all of eternity.
Something like a magical girl's end... is that sort of thing.
That's awful...
She was someone who always fought alone for everyone's sake...
Something like no one ever giving her attention...
Such a thing... is just too lonely...
By that sort of contract, we received this power into our hands.
It isn't for anyone's sake.
You continue fighting for the sake of your own prayer.
Even if no one notices you, even if you're completely forgotten...
Those are just inevitable things.
I'll remember.
I won't forget... about Mami-san.
Absolutely not!
I see.
Just to receive those words... Tomoe Mami is fortunate.
Enough to make me envious.
Even Homura-chan...
Even if it's about you, Homura-chan, I won't forget!
I absolutely won't forget that you're the one who saved us yesterday!
Homura-chan?
You are too kind...
Eh?
Don't forget...
There are also times when that kindness can call forth an even greater sorrow.
What are you listening to?
"The Girl with the Flaxen Hair."
Ah, Debussy?
That's a wonderful song, isn't it.
Y–You know, since I'm like this, it seems that everyone thinks I wouldn't listen to anything like classical music.
Now and then, people get really surprised if I guess the name of a song and stuff, you know.
I get respect for it since it's too unexpected, or something...
It's because you taught me about it, Kyousuke.
If you didn't, I... probably never would have properly appreciated this type of music in my whole life, I think.
Sayaka, you...
What is it?
Sayaka, are you teasing me?
How come after all this time, you're still making me listen to something like music?
Do you intend to harass me?
Because you like music, Kyousuke, so...
I don't want to listen to it anymore!
Something like just merely listening to songs that I can't play myself...
I... I...
It can't move.
It can't even feel pain anymore...
With a hand like this...!
It's all right.
I'm sure it'll work out somehow.
If you don't give up, I'm sure someday...
I was told to give up.
I was told to give up on performing already.
Sensei told me personally... that with current medical science, it's impossible.
My hand will never move again.
Unless there's a miracle or magic, it will never heal.
They exist!
Miracles... and magic... do exist!
Homura-chan... we'd become friends if we properly talked, and yet...
I wonder why she ended up fighting with Mami-san...
Hitomi-chan...?
Hitomi-chan!
What about today's enrichment lessons?
That's... the same as the person from that time!
Hitomi-chan!
Hey, Hitomi-chan, come on!
My, Kaname-san, good day to you!
W–What's wrong?
Hey, where are you trying to go?
"Where?" That's...
It's a place that is much nicer than here, yes...
Hitomi-chan...
Ah, that's right... Kaname-san should certainly come along with me.
Yes, that's right, that would be just wonderful!
What should I do?
This couldn't possibly be...
If I contact Homura-chan...
Ah, it's no good! I don't know her cell phone number...
That's right... I'm... a failure.
Only one small workshop like this, and I couldn't even satisfactorily manage it...
In an age like this, there's absolutely no place where I belong, is there...?
Listen, Madoka.
If you make a mistake with the treatment of these two items in my hand, an unthinkable thing will happen.
Our entire family will leave this world.
Absolutely do not make a mistake, okay?
No good...
That's no good!
You mustn't be a hindrance.
That's a divine ceremony, you know.
But... that's dangerous, isn't it!?
The people inside here... Everyone will die!
Right! From now on, we're all going on a journey to a wonderful world!
Do you understand just how lovely of a thing that is?
Things like living bodies are just a hindrance.
Kaname-san... soon you'll understand too!
Let go!
W–What should I do...
What should I do!?
IT WAS VERY FUN LETS GO AGAIN NEXT TIME WITH A BENTOU
N–No!
This is...
No! Help me! Someone!
I wonder, is this punishment?
Surely, because I'm... a coward... and a liar.
I'm receiving...
...punishment for it...
Sayaka-chan!?
This is the finishing blow!
Man, sorry, sorry.
That was a close call, wasn't it?
Sayaka-chan... those clothes...
Huh?
Well, what is it... You could say I changed my mind, I guess.
I said it's all right!
I did really well for my first time, didn't I?
But...
You've...
Hmph.
Aren't you late, transfer student?
You know, I didn't think you'd come...
I heard that Mami girl dropped dead, y'know.
So I took the trouble to come all the way out here.
What's the deal? Isn't this a bit different from what you said?
Sorry, but there's already a new magical girl on this soil.
She only just formed a contract a short time ago, though.
What's that? Super pisses me off.
But, y'know... it'd be annoying to let such an ideal turf get stolen from right under my nose by a little rookie chicken, wouldn't it...
What do you intend to do, Kyouko?
It's settled.
After all... it's fine to just beat her to a pulp, right?
That girl.
Someday, the light of love that has lit within your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
(will pass through time)
(時を超えて)
A single dream belonging to the ruined world will certainly
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ
(be destroyed, I hope)
(壊すだろう)
Drinking every last drop of hesitation, what is the thing that you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Does such a greedy aspiration have course in an evanescent tomorrow?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
Like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was a child
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
I want to meet you, with the power to crush even darkness with a smile
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Inside these frightened hands lies the courage of a plucked flower
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
I rely only on my emotions for everything
想いだけが頼る全て
The light will awaken the wish.
光を呼び覚ます願い
I'm soaring high, you know!
Because from now on, Mitakihara City's peace...
will be passionately protected by this "Magical Girl Sayaka-chan" here, after all!
Episode 5
There's No Way I'd Have Something Like a Regret
There's no way I'd have something like a regret.
Subtitle notes, runes, and extras @ http://tri4.net