WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is the script writer:
虚淵玄(Urobuchi Gen).
Okay! Well then, let's start, Mahou Shoujo☆Madoka Magika episode four commen—um,
"Miracles and Magic Do Exist" commentary host, with the role of Madoka, I am Yuuki Aoi!
Yes.
Yup, continuing, with the role of Akemi Homura, I'm Saitou Chiwa.
And this time—this time!
Sorry for intruding. I'm the mastermind, Urobuchi Gen.
Yaaaay!
(lol)
Yaaaay.
There's a lot of things I want to say here!
Nah, nah. How exciting.
That's right, you certainly are the mastermind.
That's right, truly.
Yes.
No, no, no.
Right! First off, this time it seems we'll have a small discussion about Kyousuke.
Ahhaha.
Right.
From Ao-chan:
Right—
Actually, in episode two's commentary, I had specifically asked Ume-sensei about our beloved Kyousuke-kun's hair color...
We had a conversation like "Is it white? Is it light brown?"
But actually, the color that was in the version we used for commentary was something like a prototype, and um, what is it...
When you see it on DVD, there isn't really a way it could be white,
but there was a time when it was white, and then they added the light brown color later.
Right, it was a mistake.
Right! On the DVD it's light brown.
It was for internal use.
Right, right, right.
No, wait a second please, because when you see it in the volume, it was re-applied.
Right, so you might have felt like "Huh?", but... it's fixed!
Ne?
All traces have been completely removed!
After all this time.
Yes!
Now our uniforming of our good name is complete!
Now our  uniforming! of our good name is complete!
Yes.
Now our uniforming of our good name is complete!
Now then, Urobuchi-san has come, what to do~?
What to do~?
What were you thinking when you wrote this story?
(lol) That's...
Ehh, so that's it?
Uhh, well... Right, as you might think...
Originally the basis was a mahou shoujo thing, and...
Well, that certainly isn't a genre that I've written for up until now, so it was odd to be entrusted with such a thing...
The starting point was SHAFT-san?
Right, um, Producer Iwakami-san had said, um...
"We're going back to mahou shoujo... Furthermore, it's with Shinbou-san and Ume-sensei."
"Well, we're being a bit deceitful, you know."
I was like "Just what the hell are you guys doing?" (lol)
At that time, were there any more bright choices, or was it already decided that this time a serious work will be made?
Well, right, pretty much from the start it was going to be serious.
Yeah... well, yeah, this is commentary, so I can just be frank, right?
Yup, yup.
Well, in the very beginning, it was a mahou shoujo, and it was something like Battle Royale.
Ehhhh?
Ahhh.
Yeah.
And, that would be, um...
Each and every time, starting after episode 1, a girl would die. Seems that would have been fine.
Ah, ahhh.
I see...
"Nah, as you might think, every episode is a bit too cruel."
"Since we're doing it, let's just do from episode three or so."
There was that conversation. (lol)
(lol)
In its own way, that's even more cruel...
That's right, it kind of leaves a huge impression on you when there's that gap.
Well, you know.
Well, that was the intention.
And the number of characters, too.
Yeah.
About how many characters did you want to have?
Ah, I lent a hand in figuring that out.
Ahhh.
Yeah.
Well, twelve episodes was decided from the onset, after all. Yeah.
That's right.
If we had more characters than this, we wouldn't be able to properly "biograph" them. Yeah.
Ohhh.
I see.
I see... Really, you know...
There are really so many things I want to ask!
Since I have the chance, I'd like to ask...
Urobuchi-san, you were at the auditions, so I'd like to hear a little bit about that...
Ah, yes, yeah. I was there. Yeah.
Yeah.
I mentioned this once before certainly, but Ao-chan and I had coincidentally run into each other at auditions...
We were together coincidentally!
There were so many girls that seemed younger than Ao-chan, and then I was there...
Right.
AHhahahaha.
Then, you know, the fact there were so many characters was another amazing part.
(lol)
Thanks to you, there are a lot. So then, what is it...
The auditions were held while allowing us to pick a character we'd like, and such...
That's correct.
Yeah.
That's right, um... that's a considerably rare style, isn't it?
Yes.
It's very rare.
AHhaha.
Mm!
This is the first time I've overseen such a thing, personally.
Yeah. I usually see them on tapes and such. Yeah.
"Ah I see, I can't decide on a tone of voice that I like." Yeah.
Urobuchi-san, you were really the one who said, "Please try Homura," to me when I was doing a different role.
Ah, um, yeah.
That's right. Yeah. Yeah.
You really have that, what is it, "dark beauty" feeling. (lol)
Ahh!
So I requested that.
During the audition phase, did you already know the entire scenario?
Ah, that.
Ah, yes. That's right.
To be frank, I was the only one who knew.
So...
Even if there weren't details, you knew about things such as episode 10.
Well, that was there too. Yeah.
تشان، الثابتة والمتنقلة نقاش
How did Madoka go? Actually, I believe she's the hardest character.
That's right...
We asked everyone to feel a bit hazy and gloomy. Yeah.
In the end, really, um... right,
we thought you were the most "unadulterated" if you will.
Ahhhh.
Yeah.
Umm... you possessed something like a cute girl, that worked in pleasant way and felt like a girly protagonist.
It didn't come off like you were forcing an act.
What is it, umm... well, see,
umm...
That scene where she has a conversation with Kyubey by her bedside,
Ah, yes yes.
to an extent, while it isn't bad, she gives you an impression of being half asleep, or like...
Umm, it feels a bit like a natural airhead.
Umm, it gives off an air like "This is nice." Yeah.
Ohhh.
Ahhhh.
Yeah. Umm... What is it... umm...
thank you very much.
It's like an "absent-minded" feeling. Yeah.
(lol)
Feel like can't converse!
"With no boys [in the cast], there will be conversations like this." I like that feeling. It's nice, I think.
I get it, I get it.
She might be the most difficult character, and she runs away from her situations a lot, like she isn't sure where to go,
but, she's a good girl, isn't she?
Yeah.
mmm...
But, it's different from the good girls you'd usually see in anime.
Really, she's the type of girl who, if she was real,
everyone would say "She's such a good girl, isn't she?"
If you look closely, I think the real person is a good girl, too.
She tries her best, huh? In the real world too.
(lol)
That's right, huh?
Right. Actually, before this, we had this conversation with Mizuhashi Kaori-san in episode 3's commentary, but...
When we were talking about characters, it was said that girls' and guys' viewpoints change a bit.
Ah, right.
AHhahaha.
We had that conversation.
Well, when you look at the story as a whole, it really changes with each individual person, so I didn't get into that,
but we were talking about how the characters give off different impressions between men and women.
But Urobuchi-san is a guy, right?
So, why do you understand that!?
Nah, that's–
You're a girl?
Ehhhh, reallyyyy...
You're really a girl?
Well, nah, what to say... If I didn't understand that, I couldn't work, you know (lol)
In these icy waters.
So are you constantly observing humans?
Well, right... Well, that's something to take into concern, you know.
He can see through...
He can see through us!
I was had!
Ah, I see...
No, no, no, no.
Well, when we first heard that discussion, we thought "Hee~?"
Kaori-san, too, thought "Ah, that might be true~"
But, guys...
Well, since we consisted of nothing but women in the booth, we had no second opinions, but do you think the viewpoints differ?
Right, well, really, umm...
Ahh, well certainly, as for what was paid attention to this time...
This wasn't really made with appeal to guys in mind.
Ahhh, really?
Mmmm.
If you were a boy watching, you would simply want to see nothing but pretty girls talking, anyway.
From a girl's perspective, it's really like "Ahhhh!"
Yeah, that's right.
No, this connects with the audition conversation from before, too...
Really, for the person you call a "protagonist," everyone stays aware of them...
For example, when there is a scene where she's alone in her own room...
From a male's viewpoint, what he'd feel is the acting.
You know, that's natural, since the male viewers are watching something "distant" on TV.
Um... we went without that feeling.
Yeah.
I see, I get it...
Unintentionally, even for scenes that are acted out by a single person, cute acting will come out.
Yeah.
So it's very much like, when there's a girl alone in a room... what kind of acting will there be, or what kind of words will be spoken?
Ahhh, you were able to see such a thing!
Ne~
A part that was very much on my mind regarding the situation of the characters: Well, they're really cute, very natural as well,
which is especially true since they're children. I find their childish qualities extremely cute.
But even if you don't keep in mind that they're children, it's cute.
That's right.
Still, they've got a relatively "cute, cute!" childish presentation to them.
This scene where Madoka is crying is true for that too, a very cute crying presentation...
From the viewpoint of an actor, that's one part of drama,
but that's different from the true meaning of the tears—sadness and hardship.
Right...
That's right.
That's right... Homura has come.
Yes...
I really love conversation scenes between these two!
Uwaah~
Somehow, you know...
Mou... I really feel that way, but...
Ne~
There's a reason, isn't there?
S–She's finally speaking kind words.
Isn't that right?
That's right, yeah.
She's always been tsun up until now.
All the way until the end of episode 3, she tried REALLY hard!
(lol)
Homura tried hard to be tsundere! Or well, tsun.
She stayed cool!
In order to understand all of that, you have to watch episode ten.
Yeah. It hasn't come yet.
But actually in episode four...
Yeah.
There's a part to be a bit aware of...
AHhahaha.
Yeah.
Ahh.
Well, that's right. Yeah.
The lines a little bit after this, right?
Yeah.
Somehow...
This is another part that really hurts to act!
Like right here.
Yeah.
I felt very mindful of this, and I thought it was a display of her kindness...
Now and then—I suppose that after episode three, she becomes a little dere here and there.
The air around Homura is completely different when she's alone with Madoka, compared to when other characters are with them...
That's right.
It's like the guard she puts up is much different.
That's right, right now she's a bit more soft.
Ne? You have the ability to soften or harden a girl, Madoka.
(lol) Right, right, right
Like "This time too, I'll soften you up!"
(lol) Right, right!
Then if Sayaka-chan is like "Hey!", she'll be like "Tsk."
She'll get mad and go "Ahhhh!"
This is kind of like her "Desperate" guard-style, isn't it? This commonly talking Homura.
She's so tender, isn't she? Really, I can't say it! She's so patient.
But you know, for the Madoka who won't go as far as completely accepting that, she isn't just being kind.
But that's very realistic, isn't it? Usually, the protagonist would get tougher and take on everything by now...
Taking on Homura's pain too, but Madoka hasn't taken on anything yet.
Well, that's true.
She hasn't saved anyone yet.
(lol)
No, no, no.
But because of that, I believe that everyone feels like they're in the center [of the story].
Ahhh!
But, what it is it, it feels like she carries the most sympathy for other girls.
Ah, is that so?
When I took the auditions and was told to do the most sympathetic Madoka,
I thought, "Ah, this person is shaken up. She's very close to me."
You know, all the characters fit themselves in reality, too.
That's right, actually!
Ahhh.
Is that how it is? I see.
Mou, Kitamura Eri doing Miki Sayaka is just perfect!
(lol) Really?
Mou, it's truly perfect.
Uwaa!
Uwaah!
She's really a good girl...
Yeah.
But then, she has that cheerful, joking feeling to her... and then more than anyone else, she's uneasy... she's such a nice girl...
Uwaah
Uwaaaah~
Saying that now... (lol)
That's right.
Right.
You'd say it's rather unexpected, though, ne?
Right, like it just happened right before your eyes...
I wrote that story, but it's still hard to watch.
(lol)
Yeah.
Yaaaa...
Really...
Right.
Really, somehow, when I tried Homura out, my heart was going "de-de-de-de-de-de, de-de-de-de!"
(lol)
Zoku・Satsuriku no Django -Jigoku no Shoukinkubi- (2007)
A nitroplus game featuring a fully female cast written by Urobuchi Gen.
Well, this is the first time I've wrote anything so full of girls.
Yeah.
In the past, all the stories I've written have had guys in higher positions.
But this time it's basically just Kyousuke and the father, huh?
Right, and the little brother. Then, Beh-san! Where's Beh-san?
Hang on, Beh-san?
Where is Beh-san's position?
Beh-san doesn't have a gender, right?
Ah, so that's it? It's like a gender-bending QB.
Yeah, if Urobuchi-san says it, I believe it has to be the case.
Right!
In many different places, many different staff-san...
Whether or not Urobuchi-san regards QB to be a male animal has probably bugged people in various interviews and such.
It has bugged us as well!
It has  bugged us! as well!
Well, I guess I haven't said it too many times.
Well, I guess I haven't s s(lol) too many times.
Not too many!
Yaaa...
わけがわからないよ(wake ga wakaranai yo) - I don't get the reason.
This is a line QB says in ep6. It's become a pretty famous line.
I don't get the reason.
(lol) Ah!
There it is!!!
There it is.!!
There it is...
But if you look at the most calm one, QB is the one who's never shaken up at all.
Well, that's right.
Actually.
He certainly says some righteous things.
That's right, right right right.
Mm.
Well you know, more than anyone else, he's thinking in the long term.
That's right, isn't it?
When you think about the continuance of everything, really, you know.
mm...
ahhhh.
Right, rather than thinking about the happiness of himself or someone that he likes, it's much bigger.
QB is talking about something closer to the scale of world peace.
It's kind of like... "What to do?"
Right? I see that.
No, but in the first place humans aren't righteous, so you can think of him of as a wonderful animal.
Since he's purely righteous and just, he's an animal that doesn't need people or love.
Yeah.
Amazing, you know. Why is it so... I believe each character has their very own situations...
It's like there's no way this was written by one person. Who's in your head? Where are you looking from, really?
How many people are up there?
Ahh, well, that's right... Umm, you could say that in that regard, a writer, and the acting that plays out that writing, are different.
Really, this is my first time writing while commanding a view of so many different characters.
Actually, when I focused myself in on writing a single character intently,
all the way until the core, there were many parts that I thought would need to be given an awesome performance. Yeah.
There are parts where it was like "Oh, I didn't think so far into it."
When polishing them up to be performed, it was like "Ah, we don't really need this line."
Ehhh?
If you want to have this sort of feeling, then you don't need to use a lot of words to explain many of the scenes.
Yeah.
But this piece of work has a few things that are like that?
It has them, yeah.
Ohhh.
Well, like, earlier, regarding Madoka's mother.
Like where?
Ah, ahhh.
She's scary enough, now.
(lol)
If she didn't say "Mama, you have scary eyes" then it'd have just been "Mama, you're scary."
Mama is scary. (lol) That's right.
Well for that, if it wasn't said, an assumption regarding that may have not been formed at first.
So really, "Your eyes are scary" should be written. Yeah.
For those who aren't aware, Urobuchi Gen-san normally writes text/narration heavy game scripts or light novels, which may be a part of why the relatively thin writing style suited for an anime may have slipped his mind.
That sort of minimal explanation style is something I'm not well acquainted with.
I see.
But regarding that point, for something that starts out as anime, if you say something too much...
You could say it'd be too much explanation through their lines. Yeah.
If you keep firmly planting lines, it'll make people think "Ah, they're still saying that..."
It's difficult, isn't it?
Ehhh, I never once thought that! (lol)
Yaa, really...
Regarding that, it's really something you could say there was guidance on... or you could say it's something everyone created.
Before this, I had really developed a habit of not putting any weight on seiyuu when writing.
Yeah.
Are there any characters whose impression changed a lot when everyone began acting them out?
Right, really... Mami-san was quite... yeah.
I didn't think she'd become such a fleshed-out character after only 3 episodes. Yeah.
That's right, ne... it was a bit like she had more of an impact on the distance of those other two, and it gave it a lot more meaning later.
To Mizuhashi Kaori-san: GJ.
Compared to when I wrote it myself, the sense of loss went way beyond my expectations.
And after that, Madoka and Sayaka's relationship was getting pulled apart by Mami-san's existence.
That's something I believe was a really straightforward setup.
When doing this piece of work, the thoughts for us who are actors, doing things inside of a booth... It's really like...
So far, everything has been... Extremely interesting.
I'd say.
(lol)
Ne~
Well, for other pieces of work, of course there's a lot to get involved in, and lots of people...
But this time, it's like everyone really carved or engraved themselves into this. (lol)
Somehow, it's really like... everyone had a lot of trust placed in them.
I feel like it was very worth doing...
Then, I think it leaves a staggeringly large impression on your consciousness.
Somehow, if I'm not in the company of people I can completely trust...
I'm not able to do this kind of "I can put anything out there" acting.
It's really scary.
I see.
And then they have to see the entire vocabulary within you, including things you don't want them to...
Yeah.
When I watch this kind of "I can't run away from here" part, I definitely couldn't do this without these kind of members.
That's right. And it's true for the staff-san as well, this is my first time working with Urobuchi-san, but for SHAFT-san...
Somehow, the people are very familiar, and for the actors as well, no one was like "Hello, nice to meet you,"
it's like we didn't start from zero... Well, this piece of work probably began at stage zero...
But in terms of trustworthy relationships, we've started together around 5 or 6 times now, and things have steadily increased.
Somehow, I feel extremely grateful for that.
For you to say that makes me extremely happy, yeah.
And then it was like, "After coming this far, there's no way things won't be fun!"
It's always like "What'll happen next week, what'll happen next week?"
"Why don't we get to see the full script?"
(lol)
Like "Why do we get the script on the same day we have to act?"
Well, well, that's a bit of trouble.
That's right!
That sort of thing is really how the feeling is.
Right. This much you really want to push through.
Like "I WANT TO KNOW THIS!"
But it's like intense polishing of the script, up until the very last moments.
Right, right, right.
And because of that, it is fine.
Ne?
Then for one week, you're thinking about things, which steadily increased the impact.
Right.
Because of that it had more impact in the end, I feel like one week is around the perfect amount [of time].
It certainly pulls you in when you put thought into it. Yeah. Yeah.
And since everyone is trustworthy, as soon as we start fixing things, we can instantly make corrections.
Mm, that's right.
Ah, this is Inu Curry-san's directing here...
This is another amazing thing, isn't it?
You know, these never were present once in the scenario.
Ah, what was it like?
No, really, it was many lines. There was a bit of line revision.
And after these lines, they jumped in. Inu Curry-san made everything related to the barriers.
Like the part with Madoka being pulled or getting killed?
(lol)
For that area, right, you could say it's completely an original from the minds of Inu Curry-san.
Yeah.
During the script-writing stages, monster designs weren't made.
And it wasn't clear exactly what kind of action there would be.
So there were no lines or anything for that.
Yeah.
Right, somehow since the script's stage directing was torn apart and scattered around to different people's presentations,
I really think, "It can be done,"
Then it's like, "GROW!" That's right.
It'd be called "going beyond your imagination," right?
Right, I think going beyond your imagination is scary!
That's right, really, you know~
I see, so things were really entrusted to everyone.
That's right, really, that's... Well,
That was there.
I haven't written many stories like this before, yet.
For that point, really, what words should be spoken or what kind of air should be held...
Right, you could say I would have needed a bit of help from the onset.
And after that, there's the topic of relying on actors.
But somehow with that, it's just become better.
It's got amazing endurance.
That's right, really... there are parts that I just couldn't have made by myself.
Here's the new character!
I love her~
♥ I love her～♥
Kyouko-tan~
She's the best!♥
This is a scene I like, myself.
Ah, that's right, isn't it.
I see... Cute—
A new character has finally come.
That's right.
She was in the opening, and here she is for real.
It's like "Who's that rival girl? Who is she?"
*giggle*
You know, Ume-sensei has never really made any characters that have her sort of "bad-style" before.
Right, and then Ai-chan's play of her is super cute, too...
Ne~!
Right...
Yeah.
That unbalance is unbearable!
That's right, huh?
Unbearable!
Yeah.
I feel like this is another girl's "something"!
That's an original part, too, and I feel like the bad-girl acting was pleasant.
Yeah.
Well, I think that's great. And it's a bit unpredictable, too, according to Shinbou-san's guidance.
I see, from now on, Kyouko will be there.
That's right, it'll be exciting, won't it?
It gets so amazing from here!!!
There are so many things I want to ask, why are we so close to ending?
To be honest, in this phase we know a lot, but we don't know the finale.
We haven't done after recording for episode twelve yet, and we haven't read the script.
Ah, that's right.
That's right.
So there's no choice but to ask Urobuchi-san, what's going to happen!?
Umm, right, well without spoilers I can't really say too much, but...
Yes.
Umm... regarding the ending, it wasn't to be in complete despair.
Yeah.
Is there salvation? Is there? Um, salvation!?
Umm, there is a little bit of salvation intended...
Yes.
Yes!
Roger.
Yeah...
Just umm, it won't be perfect salvation, perhaps?
*giggle*
Ohhh...
There might be some distress?
Yeah...
Ahh...
But that's right.
Mm.
Mmm.
Then we'll believe in that, too!
Yeah.
That's right.
Well, with the script covered in smoke.
Yes!
Thank you very much for coming here!
Um, Yuuki Aoi and—Saitou Chiwa, and—Urobuchi Gen.
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye.