brothas, dat wuz uh nice practice peep this shit
Damn Strayt, nigga
Yo ah can just feel muh motha fuckin skill level rising! slap mah fro!
Yo Summer vacation iz 'boutto end, Ya' know what I'm sayin'?
Yo but ah wants ta werk even harder on muh motha fuckin hoops just like mammy.
SHIT NIGGA
gotta werk hard all ye damn hood ratz..
huehuehuehuehue
Yo brothas's so pumped up! sho 'nuff!
Yo iz brothas ready fo' da hoe down?
Shit yeah, son
I got muh threads good, ya dig?
My mommy said I's good to go
Yeah dawg? I'ma catch me a goldfish
Yeah nigs, dis be our last shindig of da summer
Dis party gon' be off DA HOOK
We gon' have a ballin' time, son!
I wanna eat candied watermelums!
Oh!
I wanna eat some fryed chikken!
I wanna catch some cotton!
We gon' be rememberin' dis 5-ever
Shit yeah!
NBA Allstars - Wo~rld!
I've been a coach for these five niglets at Lebron's Ballin' Academy for the last three months.
We've accomplished a lot during this period of time.
The five of them taught me a lot, too.
This period of time has been extremly precious.
YO!
Shooting Guard - Kobe Bryant
Point Guard - Chris Paul
Center - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar
Small Forward - Lebron James
Here! Dirk!
Power Forward - Dirk Nowitzki
They have been maturing every single day.
Gather around children!
I got us sum KFC
RUB A DUB DUB THANKS FOR THE GRUB
FUCK YES
HOLY SHIT MY TASTEBUDS
FUCKING EAT MORE YA CUNTS
Yess'um
Yep. Now it seems like you're a good guy now, Phil Jackson.
Dis b natural, yo, I'm the head honcho 'round here now
HOLY SHIT IS DAT A GLAZED DONUT? GIMME DAT SHIT
Screw that mang, wutever
Kareem's not afraid anymore
Thanks, mang
Chris and Kobe pair up with each other quite well.
Yall're bangin' those threes
Chris, you went a bit easy on Kareem, right?
Yeah mang, I found me in front of Kareem,
but, mang, I sho' wanted to see Chris and Kareem hit dat shit
Izzat so?
Yah mang. 1v1 sounds ballin'
I'll fite u next time, Kareem
Yeah mang? King me
You're quite perceptive as usual, Le-a.
Yeah mang, some things r girl 2 girl, y'hear?
You're really a great help.
Yeah. Wutever, I's think it's prudent
Kobe in da house!
Sup?
Yo babby daddy needs a word wit u
Yo mah nigga, what's cracka-lackin'?
Kobe sit the fuck down
K
I see u out there playin'  ape-hoop
Cotton-picking, art of rap, and African Traditional twerking...
y u do dis
Two misses in a row?
Did something happen?
Big daddy got pissed, yo
Huh!? You made your father angry!?
I don' give a fuck
I-I see.
He said I gotsa stay home and work on da farm
there be a rave this saterday, daddy said I can't go!
No way... Why?
Daddy says ape-hoops no good for me
I been trainin' hard like Usain Bolt for it
He not happy at all, mang
I feel SORRY, mang
but this can't be helped, we'll have to use 'that'
Word?!
Kobe ain't coming?
Damn son!
Fool! U no Kobe wants 2 come
sorry m8
we all got plans, son
workin' hard in da hood
Sheeeit, you work da hardest,  Kobe
I'm gonna go 2 ur daddy 'n talk sum cents into him!
u stay da HECK away from me
Juss enjoy da show, kay?
dis gon be okay?
OUCH!
2tight4my child bearin' hips
Shaniqua!
dis be 2 short?
So Kobe really ain't coming?
I cry ever tim
I don't wanna start nuthin, but
Did Kobe hit you up?
nah mang, I'ma drive 2 her hood, tho
Peace
kay
Subaru! There's a phone call for you! From Kobe's mom!
Name: Kobe Bryant
Birthday: 9/9 Blood Type: A Class: 6-C Height: 142 cm (4' 8") Bust: Tiny (She's very concerned about this.) Words to Subaru: I respect you from the bottom of my heart!
Kobe!
Subaru!
It's nice being young.
wassup, Subaru.
Thanks, mang
I be feelin' blue when Kobe's all alone
S'good to know u'll b here with her
Smell ya later, homes!
Damn son, I didn't think she'd be that chill
Yep. That's great.
I see u, Subaro
That yukata fits you really nicely.
Aw damn, we here too soon?
Where are we supposed to meet?
In front of the candied watermelum stall
Don't worry.
We'll meet up with them soon.
Let's take this chance to have a look around.
Oh? What's that?
Ape-Hoop Game
Free throw, huh?
Want to try it out?
I dunno mang, this yoo-kat-ah is tighter than a 12 year old
Okay, how about this?
If you can make two out of three, then I'll do anything for you.
A-Anything?
Yep. Anything.
How about it?
You got it! Three out of three! Perfect!
Free Throw GAME Perfect Award - Suzuran Item Certificate
You're amazing, Kobe!
Back in the day they called me KOBE BRYANT
Yo, Subaru...
uhhh
What?
muh dick mutha fucka
oh yeah, my reward
Oh yeah, your ''reward.''
yeah son
Well y'see
Will you take responsibility for 'lil Kobe?
Damnit Kobe, you said you were on the pill!
Let's get freaky
Okay, let's go see the fireworks together.
I wish this were a dick
Yo! It's from Kobe!.
Oh! Is Kobe in da hood?
Shit yeah, she's chillin' like a villain with Hasegawa
No shit? Let's blow this popsicle stand!
Nah son.
Lets go hit up some niggas over here
Gotta get me sum goldfish
Yeah son, me too
I wanna eat some choco banananas, ya dig?
Lets bounce
yeah dude
I wanna eat some fryed chikken!
Yeah, yeah.
Huh? Weren't we supposed to meet up here?
Are they not here yet?
Kobe?
What's the matter?
Um...
Do you need to use the restroom?
Yeah son, I gotta piss like a race horse
You can't walk?
Do I look like I have polio?
Okay! I get it!
Um... Well then!
Let's go.
Thank Black Jesus we made it.
Get the fuck out, old man
Um, are you okay?
Yes... But I dropped the bass
Are you Skrillex?
Excuse me!
He dropped his bass! Can you help us look for them?
Wub Wub Wub!
Is this it?
Yes, it is. Thank you very much.
It's fine. Thank  Black Jesus we found it.
I'm here to see my lil badonkadonk, but I guess I'm not used to the crowd.
I understand. I'm not good with crowds, either.
Thank you. You've been a great help.
Go for itadakimasu, Trayvon!
Cut it out, nigga
Yo is dat Kevin Garnet?
What's good in the hood?
Look's like a ballin' time!
Is that a FAMAS?
Huh?
Get outta here Crips!
lolwat?
You're on my TURF, son!
niggas please
Blaze it up, nigga
You got no aim
Let's go.
Wait, Trayvon!
These bitches givin' me a hard time
S'all good!
Can't Corner the Dorner!
You'll fall if you keep on leaning like that!
Yo! Dirk! Chris!
Oh? Shootin' whiteys?
Dirk!
Your Hanes!
Get a good look Subaru!
Itadakimasu!
You're so mean, Subaru!
Whack
It's yo own damn fault, nigga
Give it a shot, Chris
Make sure he gets a bangin' look at yer badonkadonk
He ain't seein' nothin!
y this happen 2 me?
You should tighten up your asshole a bit.
Okay!
So close!
That was close.
Yes, but thanks for the tip ;)
Ah, I wanna taste a dick
Off da heezy!
yeah son
Yo!
I can see the hood from here!
This ghetto is unexpectedly nice.
The fireworks are about to happen.
Shit yes!
Kobe!
Sup dad?
I told you, the hood is very dangerous!
Fuck that
We're going home.
Stop right there criminal scum!
You're...
I'm the coach for the Lebron's Ballin' Academy's basketball team, Hasegawa Subaru.
I'm sorry for taking Kobe here.
Nah son, moms said I's cool
No, I broke her hyemn promise in the end.
I'm sorry.
But Kobe ain't no sleeze!
She gots skills and doens't afraid of anything
Subaru...
Oh, it seems like you're mackin' with my niglet?
I didn't bring her here because I wanted to break her promise with you.
I just want her to be with her homies
They're her precious homies
Homies, you say?
Kobe does not need friends who play ape-hoop!
Yo dads, cut it out!
Oh?
You're that guy...
You're Kobe's coach?
Yes, I coach these niggas
We need Kobe!
Yeah!
I wouldn't be a sick baller without Kobe!
I love Kobe, too! I love being with all mah negroes
Kobe is the glue that keeps dis hood 2gether
Yo dads, my B
It's cause of Subaru I'm havin' a bangin' time playin' hoop
That's why...
You can take Kobe outta the hood but you can't take the hood outta Kobe
Please!
Don't bother coming home tonight, son
Daddy.....
Hey!
I think you know already.
Ape-hoop had left Kobe a terrible memory before.
But it seems like she found some great friends through ape-hoop this time.
This is unbefitting of me to say.
But please take care of my daughter.
Yes!
A'ight
Let's continue with our promise. ya dig?
Okay!
You look bangin' today.
Yo word?
Did something good happen?
Pops said to hit some young jeezy's in B-ball!
She's so pretty
Gud 1 m8!
Who the HECK are you?
Wanna fite m8?
It's starting!
HOLD ONTO YOUR BUTTS
Chill out, Dirk!