When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Miss! Miss!
MISSSSSSS!
She's not here.
That's strange.
She's not over here, either.
Where could the Miss have...
Senpai!
Wh-What has gotten into you, Miss?
Senpai, please use this sports towel!
I'll be cheering for you
during today's match!
Huh?
Wh-What match?
It's so embarrassing!
The Miss has lost it!
Nagi is currently writing a new manga.
A m-manga?
She's apparently trying her hand
at a lighthearted teenage love story.
Yes, that's right.
I thought if I put myself
in my character's shoes,
the pages would just draw themselves, but...
It's no good! I can't draw!
Are you all right, Miss?
It was going well up to a point, but...
Going well?
Yes, it was going well.
I have Chadao Ohsotogari,
captain of the kabaddi team,
an institution at Saint Yam Academy.
And our heroine, Nobue
Iglesias, is in love with him
and after numerous lame near-misses,
she finally get to go on a date with Chadao,
but this crucial scene isn't going anywhere
and it's just a bulldog, wow!
Uh, is that really
a lighthearted teenage love story?
It's completely cliché...
Why?!
I'm supposed to be a genius,
so why can't I draw?!
Now, don't get so hung up on that.
I got it!
I can't draw, because
I have no reference material!
Huh?
That must be it!
So, you heard me, Hayate!
Yes?
I want you to go immediately
and gather reference material!
R-Reference material?
I want you to go to the date spots
that young people favor these days
and capture it on that camera!
W-Well, but...
I have absolutely no idea
about trendy date spots.
Oh, "Quit arguing! Your mistress
is in dire straits! Hurry up and go!"
Is that it?
Yeah, yeah.
Tokyo Date Spots
Oh, man...
I've never gone on a date before.
A rare modern youth indeed.
Please leave it.
Alrighty. Leaving it.
Let's see, where in the world should I go?
When it comes to dates,
shouldn't you look at Harajuku?
I said, leave it!
Harajuku...
Wait, what?!
Um... Um... Um, um, um, um...
I-I-I-I-Is... Is... Is that you, Maria?!
Yes.
I didn't recognize your for a moment
without your uniform.
I was wondering who this
fashionable young lady was!
I wear clothes like this once
in a while, too, you know.
Oh, by the way, would you mind
if I came along with you?
What?
Wh-What?!
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
A date with Maria?!
Ah-ha, I get it.
The punch line to this episode will be
that it was all a dream.
Yeah! That's got to be it!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Must-See! Complete Autumn 2007 Guide of the
Latest Fashionable Date Spots for the Young and Hip
I see.
So, the Miss asked to be left alone?
Yes, it went like this...
Oh, a flashback? I appreciate you
taking the trouble to do it.
It's... no... good...
I just can't draw!
I know!
I can't concentrate
because there are people around!
"People"? D-Do you mean me?
Maria, I will give you the day off today!
Tell Klaus the same thing!
I want to be alone!
I see...
Mr. Klaus! She actually...
What?!
There are various people working
at the Sanzenin estate,
but there are no people
in the main building,
because Nagi dislikes servants.
So, that's what happened.
That last image was
a total mystery, though...
First, an order to collect reference
material, and now sending people away?
She's acting like some popular manga author.
She suddenly tells me to take time off,
but I don't especially
have anything to do...
And so,
I will go out with you today.
Go out with me?!
Go... Go...
Would it be a bother?
No, no, no, no, no, that is, uh, well...
For you to go out with someone like me is...
I thought I would go with you
to help gather Nagi's reference material.
What?!
Oh, that's what you meant.
Of course!
Ooh! Smooth sailing! Smooth sailing!
How are you doing?!
Miss!
You are so cruel to suddenly
make me take the day off!
This decrepit old man has nowhere to go!
Shut up!
Go to an arcade or an internet café!
Surely, you can kill a day's worth of time!
Don't cry, Klaus. It's disgraceful
for a man of your age!
Whoa... Couples...
Couples...
What is the matter?
Uh, no, perhaps it's because
I've gotten used to life on the estate,
I felt a bit dizzy.
But I must make sure I collect good
reference material for the Miss!
Shonen Yonday
Let's see... What else should I photograph?
I would say you absolutely
cannot miss Takeshita Street.
Takeshita Street?
Yes, as I recall,
first, at the entrance
is "The Energizer House".
There is also the Tunnels' Valentine House,
Mr. Tokoro and Nori-P...
Um, what era are we talking about?
And that's the famous Mar...
N-No! Even with it bleeped,
that's just no good!
How strange. They're all gone.
Yes... I imagine they closed up
shop quite a while ago.
As we have repeatedly noted,
Maria is a young and fresh 17-year-old.
Well, you know,
I did bring a guidebook, so...
Shall we try walking around this area?
Huh? Maria?
Maria, could it be that you want
to check out those clothes?
What? Uh, n-no!
Oh, please! I don't care
about the latest fashion
I want to look
or have any desire to try on trendy outfits
or love getting dressed up!
I totally, absolutely don't! Not one bit!
Are you sure about that?
But I think it might help
with the Miss's reference materials,
so let's check it out.
Y-You have a point!
I guess we have no choice!
Then, just for a bit!
Über Beauty
Y-Yes.
Hayate, look! So many cute outfits!
Oh, this one-piece is cool, too!
Please feel free to take
your time looking around.
Maria's still just a normal girl.
Um...
Y-Yes?
Hayate, would it be all right
if I maybe tried some things on?
Well, now!
Incredible!
Yay!
Hey, you're in the way! Shoo! Shoo!
But you're amazing.
Everything looks really good on you.
Oh, please.
Starting now, please call me
the Ebi-chan of the anime world.
You're letting it go to your head.
Who cares?!
Okay, okay.
She looks good! She's fantastic!
She's being Ebi-ish!
Oh, are you the boyfriend?!
What?
B-B-B-Boyfriend?!
The boyfriend should try
things on, too! Yup, yup!
I'll coordinate a cool outfit
for you guys! Yup, yup!
I put you in those as a joke,
but you look really good in them!
Yup, yup, yup, yup!
You look fabulous! Yup, yup, yup!
You're awesome! Yup, yup!
You make a nice couple!
It's kind of embarrassing, isn't it?
O-Oh, man...
Ah! So delicious!
When you come to Harajuku,
you just have to get this!
But it's boring. Nothing except
the crêpe interests me.
I came because Yukiji said
an ethnic group that dances and sells
bamboo shoots lives in Harajuku.
It's weird...
They are referring to the Bamboo Shoot Kids.
Incidentally, if you
don't know what that is,
ask an adult you know or ask Maria.
Well, no helping it.
Once we finish eating,
let's go back to school and take a nap.
What?! We just got here!
And we've only been in 3 scenes!
If only there were something
to get excited about...
Oh, wait! There it is!
I-I feel bad about this.
You ended up buying
clothes for me as well...
N-Not at all.
Ooh!
That clearly dewy-eyed couple!
If it isn't our good friend, Hayata!
I had no idea Hayata had such
a beauty for a girlfriend!
Wait, that's Little Nagi's maid!
Ooh! Hard to tell when she's out of uniform!
In other words, this is the butler
and maid's "love in Harajuku"!
All right! Since we're here,
let's liven up their date for them!
Part of a teacher's job is to lecture
about the pure and righteous
ABCs of dating to one's pupils!
Job? She's just having fun.
But this is pretty interesting!
Hey, hey, if they get married,
do you think we'll get to deliver a speech?!
A speech?! We'll be the guests of honor!
We'll be leading the toasts!
Swallowing Dom Pérignon whole!
So! Get them!
Off we go!
Uh, the silence is kind of awkward...
What should I talk about at times like this?
Th-That store attendant called us a couple.
It's odd, isn't it? A couple?
Actually, when you get down to it...
Why am I feeling so nervous?
Um...
What?
Oh, I should get some ph-ph-photos
of this area for the M-Miss, too!
Y-Y-Y-Yes, I agree. I agree!
I'll take it for you, if you'd like.
What?
Is that supposed to be a disguise?
It's just some afro wigs...
What afro-ish people, ruining the
fashionable atmosphere of Harajuku.
Um, who might you be?
Exactly who I look like!
A super genius photographer!
And her assistants!
This enthusiasm... I don't feel like this
is the first time I've met them.
Are they people you knew in a past life?
Both of them were feeling so nervous,
they weren't even able to
see through these simple disguises.
The afro is to be feared!
Ah! The photographer in me
is itching to get to work!
Please let me photograph you guys!
No, thank you.
All right! Let's put out
a photographic collection!
The title will be "Journal
of Love 2007"! It's settled!
Settled!
Thank you very much. Then, please...
Wait, why are you going along with this?!
But since they offered...
No!
They're suspicious, no matter how
you look at them! Too suspicious!
You are too unguarded!
That's good.
You'd let them take tons of photos once
they're got you going, wouldn't you?!
That's good! That's good!
It's dangerous!
These types of people pretend
to take normal photos
Get closer together! Closer!
and gradually move on to more extreme...
Okay, let's go for a smooch!
Hey, please stop!
I swear!
We're going to call it quits for Harajuku
now and go somewhere else!
A-All right.
Why would they leave?
Is it just me, or do they seem
to find us annoying?
They're just being shy.
So cute!
And so, the two moved on
to the next date spot.
In the meantime...
The Miss's pen was still at a standstill.
Hey, Hayate!
Maria! Tea!
Oh, right. I'm all alone
at the residence right now, aren't I?
Well, maybe a little walk will be
a nice change of scenery.
Th-This is Hayate's room...
And the door has been... left ajar...
No, I shouldn't!
Entering his room without his permission?!
Every person is entitled
to their own privacy!
Whew. I shook off the urge.
Oh! Is this a trick of fate?!
Or is it the deed of a passionate heart?!
M-My pen...
I-In this case, as I expect...
Keep dawdling and I'm leaving you behind.
(Boyya-boya-shiteru to oitecchaimasu yo.)
I will happily accompany you. Heart.
(Yorokonde tsuite mairimasu. Haato.)
Th-There was no helping it, all right?
With what?
To go get the pen I dropped,
I had no choice.
So you went in.
It was beyond my control.
Who are you making excuses to?
B-Besides, it's Hayate's fault, too.
When you go out, you should
at least lock your door...
H-H-His desk!
S-So, this is where Hayate...
...always sits and studies...
Wh-What am I doing?!
I can't believe myself.
Why am I so worked up over a little
thing like going into a boy's room?
B-But I feel a bit sick,
so I guess I'll try lying down...
It's only because I feel sick, all right?!
You don't need to keep making excuses.
Wait! What's the point
of doing this anyway?!
This is bad! I'm starting
to feel sort of dizzy!
I'm going back to draw my manga.
Let's see... my pen... my pen...
My pen...?!
Th-This is!
Could this be the thing
every teenage boy hides?!
Full of women's bodies...?!
Hayate's keeping stuff like
that behind my back?!
No, knowing Hayate, surely not!
But as his mistress,
and his girlfriend, I...
Wonderful Big Brother
"Wonderful Big Brother"!
He swings that way?!
She wasn't able to accept it.
Oh!
The Miss has found my favorite reading
material that I had stashed away!
So you're the one that swings
that way? Bastard.
Kaminarimon
Oh, my!
Are we in Asakusa?
Yes, just 30 minutes by subway.
Fortunes 100 yen
Medium Luck. What about you, Hayate?
Please don't ask.
Big Misfortune
Hot! That's hot! Hot!
Please settle down before eating.
Hayate!
Huh?
Please look at this!
Let me see.
Oh, that's cute!
Wh-Whoa, I forgot and
I've been enjoying myself normally!
I can't believe myself!
Grabbing Hayate's sleeve?!
How could I act so boldly?!
Sir? Ma'am? How'd you like a ride?
We'll make it cheap for you!
A r-rickshaw?
The newest date spots in season right now!
We'll guide you to them all!
This is perfect for the
manga reference material.
Th-That's true.
Then...
Please take us for a ride.
Just leave it to me.
Here we go!
We're totally going!
Th-This is fast!
What incredible G-force!
On to a date course that'll cement
their love in one fell swoop!
Onward!
The Tanaka family's Jon, living in
East Koiwa of the Edogawa Ward,
is good at calculating!
This is... a date spot?
Not only that, but he's cheerfully
getting the answer wrong.
Next up, the Parasitological Museum!
Wh-What's the point of looking
at this during a date?
This is a bit...
May you have a long
and happy life like a parasite!
This is the most prominent haunted
spot in the Metropolitan area.
If you're lucky, you'll see the ghost
of a woman hanging from the ceiling.
D-D-D-Don't bring us around scary places!
This might be good in the summer...
SynergySP
And the last spot is this! A company
that makes lots of interesting anime!
The person who plays Kirari
Tsukishima is here, too.
This is the finale?
Please be sure to eat properly
and get good sleep.
Kaminarimon
How about it? Were you able to
immerse yourself in romance?
Uh, we're back to where we started...
But that was quite a valuable experience.
Well, if you say so, Maria.
Oh! My digital camera!
Come on! Come on!
Get that smooch on already!
Whoa! You're that fake photographer!
Smooch on!
So persistent!
The sea of Sumida is my sea!
We're setting sail!
We're getting on! We're getting on!
Dessert Making Class
Instructor: Grazie Maki
27th Cake made with love
It's done!
It came out fantastic,
if I do say so myself.
I'm so glad I took the plunge
and came to this dessert making class!
My! This is fantabulous!
You're too kind.
Hayate Love
All it takes is love.
It's superb, grazie!
I have never had a student
make such a magnificent cake!
How very kind of you. Grazie.
I've lost...
Looks like we managed to get away.
Yes.
Wait, hey!
Hey, wait!
We've put all this effort
into livening up your date,
so the least you could do
is smooch! One smooch!
Th-They're still coming after us.
What tiresome people.
The way things are going,
I have a feeling they'll chase us
to the ends of the earth
until they get a photo of us k-k-kissing.
If I'm to... If I'm to protect Maria...!
The ship's power doesn't
decide how well we can fight!
I'll show you!
Boom!
Leap out, youth!
Your head is mine!
I mean, where are you?!
Hiding is no use! No use! No use!
Ready or not...
Stay back!
D-Don't do anything stupid!
Come any closer and I'll jump!
Wh-Why?!
Why are you suddenly saying this?!
What's this? What's this?
Is this what they commonly
call "the lovers' quarrel"?
I'm sorry. There's someone else that I love.
S-Someone... you love?
He's a crew member on a tuna fishing boat.
I don't get to see him
for over half of the year, but...
Y-You should forget
about a guy like that! I'll...
I can't!
Even if I can't see him...
Even then, I love him!
Y-You can't mean that!
I love him more than you,
more than medium fatty tuna,
more than the fattiest part of tuna!
So please forget about me!
Good-bye!
Wait!
W-Wait...
I... I...
I...
Ocean, you jerk!
Could it be... that we just...
Maybe we just witnessed
the death of a romance...
Poor Hayata...
Such is how fleeting and
heartrending first loves tend to be...
Let's leave the brokenhearted
boy alone for now.
Agreed.
Time will surely heal all wounds.
Let us keep what we saw
today stored in our memories
in the depths of our hearts.
Having stored away the end of
a romance in the depths of their hearts...
Now, then!
Let's go to Tsukishima to eat monjayaki!
Yeah!
It is said that after this,
they never again recalled the events
that transpired today.
Maria!
Hayate!
We managed to drive them away!
Thanks to your passionate performance.
Oh, no, it was nothing so great.
But I wonder what in the world
those people were up to.
Let's forget about them.
We'll probably never see them again anyway.
Now, shall we head home soon?
The Miss is sure to be waiting eagerly...
Please wait.
What is it?
Hayate...
How about going for a ride
in that to end the day?
Maria, thank you very much for today.
Not at all. I should
be the one thanking you.
But...
What?
Next time, I hope you get to go on a date
with someone you really love.
What? Well...
H-How should I respond here?
But before that happens...
Shall we bring Nagi along next time
and go on a date, the three of us?
Oh, yes! I'd love to!
Oh, then, let's take one last photo.
What do you think, Miss?
Don't you think the photos
turned out quite well?
We also went to places
like Harajuku and Asakusa
and got good reference photos,
so I'm sure you'll be able to...
...draw... a great manga...
Don't give me that crap!
Here I was, agonizing my head off
and you were enjoying yourself like a fool!
So, why don't you go out
first thing this morning
and invite your boyfriend
or girlfriend on a romantic date?
Well, assuming you have someone, that is.
If you have someone...
Hey, don't say potentially
offensive things to the audience!
Next time, they'll be fighting
the troubles of an aging man.
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
Wataru...
Wataru & Saki's
Illustration by Marina Inoue
And Saki's...
Butler Report
Butler Report!
Hey! I'm Wataru Tachibana.
And I'm Saki Kijima.
Since the theme song for Rental Video Tachibana is finally ready,
we're here to let you hear it!
Wait, is this the shop's theme song?
That's right. Did you not know?
But it doesn't mention "Rental Video Tachibana" at all.
Well, you know how it is. It's one of those "image songs."
But don't just rent this song! Head out to the store and—
Young sir, wait! That's going too far!
Yeah, I guess you're right.
See you next time!
Preview
Goodness! To think I had become a coffee
plantation owner, comfortably retired.
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
What a strange dream I had.
Go ahead. If you want to
retire, why don't you?
What?!
What could have gotten into Mr. Klaus?
He seems so depressed.
Nagi telling him to quit must have come as quite a shock.
I am my mistress's shadow.
If I feel I am no longer of any use to her
then I will simply fade away!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
Klaus Is Japanese Because
His Name Is Written "Kurausu"
"Klaus Is Japanese Because
His Name Is Written 'Kurausu'".
Did you know?
Takamori Saigo's real name is Takenaga!