If I showed you my true self, what would you do?
Would you fall in love with me?
Hey...
W-Wait a minute, I...
Taiga! Are they inside?
Taiga?
Huh? Seems like it's looking bad.
Was Ami-chan's timing bad?
T-this isn't what...
Ta-i-ga~
Minorin!
Looks like no one's here.
Where did they go?
I wonder?
Why do you have to lie?
Could it be that...
You don't want to admit it?
That another girl other than Aisaka is in his room.
Idiot! Don't spout nonsense!
Eh? But...
It's not "but", right? Hurry up and tell the truth.
The "truth" is?
Oh Takasu-kun, you naughty dog!
T-Taiga.
Taiga!
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, yet complicated and mysterious
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
onkou tokujitsu ECCENTRIC na anata
You, who's gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PURE PARAATO
A naive preparation
atama no naka wa junjou PURE PAREEDO
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
Pool Opening
Good morning.
Did something happen, Taiga-chan?
Nothing happened, at least not to me.
I wonder what's for dinner today.
Seasoned rice, you like that right?
Can't you just make red bean rice?
Right, ugly bird?
Ugly!
H-Hey, Taiga... about what happened last night...
That was just Kawashima playing around.
It can be considered... how do I put it...
She doesn't seem to be feeling well.
Sorry for that.
Oh? Why are you apologizing?
Ryuuji sure is a weird guy.
I-Inko-chan?
Pull yourself together, Inko-chan! Wake up!
Taiga! Wake up!
Ah, there's no time left...
That hurts...
Huh?
S-Sorry...
What?
We overslept!
Anyway, hurry up and get ready!
Where's breakfast? Why did you wake me like this today?
There's no breakfast or lunch box.
We'll be late if we don't leave within five minutes.
Geez, we'll have no lunch if we don't go to the convenience store.
Hey, are you listening, Tai... ga!
Are you listening, you perverted dog? The convenience store, right?
What's with you? Being like this just because of food...
Ouch!
We made it!
They're finally here.
Thank you very much for your help yesterday.
No... ah... y-yeah...
What's that?
Ah, could it be that you're mesmerized by my summer attire?
Just kidding...
You're in the way, stupid Chihuahua.
Ah, you're here, Aisaka-san. Good morning.
Good morning, Kawashima-san.
Thanks for your work, being in "heat" so early in the morning.
Hey, you guys...
Ah, is that so? Come on, really.
Don't get jealous over something that trivial.
That's just you misunderstanding.
You don't get it at all, do you?
The incident yesterday...
Good morning, everyone!
This might just slim the biceps down!
Minorin, don't use me for weightlifting.
About the pool's opening.
Okay, it's the long-awaited pool opening day tomorrow.
Now, let me brief you on the things you should take note of.
Summer has the risk of love and is the key to victory for people in their twenties.
Ah, no way... my stomach.
That's right, it's my thighs for me.
My arms are worse.
What are you guys talking about?
Isn't being young good enough?
Are the swimming lessons in this school held together with the boys?
Oh no, how embarrassing.
Why?
Aren't you super cute? Aren't you a model?
What's there to be embarrassed about?
Eh, what?
What, what, what? I said, you punks!
Sensei, homeroom's ending here.
Okay, class dismissed.
Stand.
Taiga, come on, hurry up!
No way, I'm not buying a swimsuit.
It can't be helped since the one from last year rotted away.
That won't happen if you wash and dry your swimsuit quickly.
Didn't I say no already, geez!
Why is that person here too?
Because this is the only shop that sells swimsuits.
I-I wasn't the one who invited her.
Hey, hey.
This looks suitable for Aisaka-san.
It's a little too suitable.
Calm down Taiga! Others are watching!
Takasu-kun, what do you think about this?
Eh... um... very suitable...
Hey.
How's this?
Does it look weird? Is it too conspicuous?
What's with those long legs! You're far too striking!
Is that so? I chose a normal swimsuit though...
Ka-Kawashima-san!
What's the brand of that swimsuit? Where can I find it?
Over there.
Ah, let's buy the same one.
J-Just this! Spare me that!
Kushieda...
Hey, hey.
Although Ami-chan's super-super cute...
this is scary, this is just a normal swimsuit.
I wonder how good this body can get. This cuteness, this beauty and this style!
Isn't hiding it the same as committing a crime?
Hey, don't you think so too?
Huh?
Hey, are you all right, Tai-
What are you doing...
I don't know what to do anymore.
What is it? What's wrong?
I can't decide at all.
What aren't you satisfied with? The only colors are indigo and black.
It's not that, it's just the sizes don't fit.
How about child sized?
Over my dead body!
Don't say the same things as that stupid Chihuahua.
I-Isn't this pretty small?
The price's good, the material's durable and it can be dry cleaned too.
Try putting it on?
I tried that on... but...
I thought it was just okay...
How should I put it, that...
Then, isn't this okay?
Yeah, you're right.
Taiga, what should we have for dinner?
I'll make whatever you want to eat.
That's right. Have you prepared for the pool lesson?
Don't forget your towel, it's the bath towel.
Shut up.
You...
What's bothering you?
Is it the swimsuit? Or are you still angry about last night?
No!
What is it then!?
I don't know how to swim...
I hate that!
Saying that so easily, that's not the real reason at all.
Ah, I'm late, I'm late.
Oh, wait.
Drink this before you go.
Thank you, Ryuu-chan.
It's hot.
What's that?
It's Ryuu-chan's special soy milk.
It seems that the beans contain some sort of Iso, Vonvon thing, which can enlarge the breasts.
It's Isoflavone.
It would be troublesome if they shrunk, so this must be prevented.
Ya-chan's so smart!
Taiga-chan's so perverted, touching others!
Don't sexually harass other people's mothers!
I'll be going.
Good grief, what a mess.
What's wrong with you? You're acting weird.
Beans...
Hey!
It tastes bad, give me another one!
What are you doing?
I want Isoflavone too!
Huh?
Why do you want something like that?
The swimsuit's size and the Isoflavone are...
Taiga, could it be that you...
No, don't say it!
Don't say anymore...
Are you flat-chested?
Geez, is breast size something to worry so much about?
The size of breasts is such a trivial thing.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Y-Yeah...
How is it?
It's flat, right? Flat-chested, right?
No... w-well...
What about the pads?
I put them in, but...
They caved in.
That's why I hate the pool.
In any case, put something on. You'll catch a cold.
What's this?
After seeing it, you should be able to understand my tragedy.
This is...
Pitiful breasts
That's mean.
Pitiful breasts, pitiful...
I'm being pitied because of my breasts.
No...
Well, this is simply just the thoughts of the writer...
Of course, I've already caused some bloodshed in the photography club that published this.
Speaking of which, the photography club was suddenly abolished.
I actually have to present such a tragic side of me in front of Kitamura-kun...
I don't want that...
Hey, Taiga.
All right, I'll think of something.
Eh?
So that you are able to show your breasts in front of Kitamura.
I'll take care of it.
Enough already, you should go to sleep.
No, I want to wait here till you finish it.
I want to be awake before you complete it too.
Hey.
You know, about my...
Acting so stubborn.
Well...
Sorry for that.
How is it?
I'll definitely bring it along when I get married.
Maruo!
You look better when not wearing your glasses!
Change to contact lens instead.
Is that so?
Definitely so.
I don't wear glasses either.
Female changing room
See you later, Aisaka-san.
I'll go on ahead.
Taiga.
Come on, hurry up. I'll help you with your hair.
Y-Yeah.
Sorry, Maya-chan!
I couldn't fix my hair properly.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ami-chan!
Whoa, as expected of a model!
What a great figure.
How do I put it...
I'm so touched!
She's a goddess!
You're different from us after all.
You're at it again...
Of course! Ami-chan's really cute today.
So, I'll allow you to worship an angel, commoners!
Come, follow in my shadow. This can be considered my greatest gift to you.
Geez, don't tease me, Maya-chan.
Ah, Takasu-kun!
Minorin, don't run!
My hair will get messed up again.
All right! We'll do the warm-up like this.
Let's run around...
...facade!
Minorin?
Kushieda.
I've just realized.
As long as I'm in the pool, no one will see my tummy.
That being said, I'll swim for a while.
Later!
Minorin.
Ah, Aisaka-san. You've finally come out?
I was thinking that you would be too embarrassed to come out wearing a loose swimsuit.
Huh, what are you talking about?
Are you still asleep?
Good grief.
I really don't want to get a suntan.
Perfect.
They've grown so much in the last year.
I'll be in Taiga's faction after all!
What, how ordinary. It's unusual.
We did it!
Ginyu Special Force!
We're exposed.
As expected of Minorin.
Aisaka?
Huh? Aisaka... right?
Although I can't see very well without my glasses,
you're Taiga's size, right?
Why do you have to hide yourself?
That hairstyle isn't bad at all, it's just like Mickey Mouse.
S-She went that way!
What?
Did I say something wrong?
W-Who knows...
Hey, let us see your muscles.
Like this?
Whoa, awesome!
Just by himself...
He's so popular!
We'd like to question the hierarchal society!
This is the Summer Back Toss!
Maruo!
Hey.
Want to do it?
Although it's a free period...
Isn't this a little dangerous?
Hey, Tai-
Kitamura-kun said my hairstyle was cute...
No, although he said so...
Prey discovered!
Let's go, softball club union!
Well done! Next!
Okay boss!
You were thrown in.
How fun, Aisaka-san.
You...
Let's play, let's play.
Don't get mad, okay?
Hey, go easy on her.
No way, we're just playing.
Hey, Taiga, are you all right?
Taiga?
That girl...
I don't know how to swim...
Don't tell me that she really doesn't know how to swim?!
No way!
Spare me!
Taiga!
Sensei!
You can't!
Calm down, Taiga!
No way, a bra pad dropped out!
There's only one left!
What...
Hey, something looks wrong.
Aisaka!
Taiga!
Don't come here!
I'll go over right now!
Taiga!
Damn, if it comes to this...
Humiliation...
Like I already said, I'm sorry.
I didn't know that you can't swim.
Look, everyone's gone home.
Isn't it about time that you get back to normal?
This isn't a problem that can be solved by an apology.
It's all because you did something so meaningless.
M-My... b-breast... b-b...
In any case, apologise, apologise, apologise...
Even so, if Aisaka-san can't swim,
you won't have any affinity with the sea or pool for your whole life.
Hey, Takasu-kun. I've got a villa located near the seaside.
If you don't mind, how about going together during the summer break?
Wait, weren't you apologising to Taiga just now?
Then, it's fine if Yuusaku comes?
Huh?
What's wrong, Aisaka-san?
If you make any more decisions on your own,
I'll leak the photographs of the 100 rapid-fire impressions from the other day.
Ah, it's 150.
If you do that, I'll sue you for violation of privacy.
Even the palmtop tiger won't be able to get past the arms of the law, right?
Hey, you guys...
Stop it!
You'll get hurt if you get violent.
Ah, however Minori-chan,
it's all because Aisaka-san wanted me...
It's all the fault of this stupid Chihuahua!
What are you saying?
In the first place...
Silence!
Unless you wish to nurture your friendship with your fists...
Don't fight!
Let's decide the victory through sports!
S-Sports...?
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru mono to wa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
Unable to be honest, I'm just rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
For Whose Sake
Battle for Takasu.
Ami versus Taiga?
Why is Takasu taking all the good stuff!
Please fight for me and treat me harshly after that!