Question 11
Yuuji, and Shouko, and Their Childhood Memories
Where did I go wrong?
When did I have this resolve?
If I had the chance...
to redo all of this...
Was it back then...
in that room...
the time you stood before me?
I want her to be free.
I don't want to hold her heart captive like this!
No, that's not it.
It's because I know the real you!
That's even more precious to me!
That's why...
Hi! Question: Being single or a couple, which one is more...
FABULOUS?
My future slowly cycles
through a rainbow of colors
Can I talk about it as much as I want?
Will you ignore me?
Oh, the wide world fills my heart with new feelings
I love you today, too
I really love you!
I'm an idiot... More idiotic than there are stars in the sky
I had a dream of walking with you
but I wasn't being honest with myself
I'm sorry! After all...
I didn't realize I was in love with you
Answer me. What do you, me and something unknown add up to?
An infinite jump!
"There's a genius in Minazuki Elementary School."
That's how the rumor went many years ago.
Indeed, he was a tad smarter than the other kids.
Plus, he was serious and hard working.
The adults praised him and expected great things from him.
And yet...
Minazuki Elementary School
You're really amazing, Yuuji!
At what?
School trip
Contents
Purpose of the trip
Rules of the trip
Schedule
I heard the teacher praising you about the mock exam.
He called you a prodigy.
That was no big deal.
But didn't you do better than even the middle school kids?
I sure did.
See? You're amazing!
The sixth graders who took the test with you were so mad.
I made a mistake in the civics test. Otherwise, I would've ranked first.
Back then, I set my sights high.
I heard you're going to get a recommendation for Shimozuchi Middle School!
It was a piece of cake for me.
Can't say the same for the other chumps.
Honestly, I was just avoiding reality by saying that.
You're too slow, Shouko.
Hurry up, so we can go home.
But I wanna talk to you some more.
Nope. I wanna go home.
I wanna talk to you.
Nope.
I wanna.
No!
Hey, Yuuji.
My boobs got a lot bigger recently.
Are you all right, Yuuji?
What the hell did you just say?!
You weren't listening to me, so I thought I'd say something to catch your attention.
I don't care about that!
Well, maybe a little.
Never mind. Let's just get this over with.
Okay, but I still wanna talk to you some more.
Why don't you just go talk to your friends?
Exactly! That's why I'm talking to you!
Oh, for God's sake!
Shouko was quite above the rest of the class.
She had a good family, earned excellent grades, excelled at sports, and was beautiful to boot.
She was almost too perfect.
Kirishima
Shouko
My name is Kirishima Shouko.
She's so pretty! Wow!
Hey! Go talk to her!
Ah, why don't you go?
You like her, don't you?
I don't!
Hey, don't you think Kirishima acts a little too cute?
Her family's rich, right?
She must be one of those rich bitch types.
It's kinda hard to talk to her.
Fabre
Souvenirs
entomologiques
I know, right?
Maybe that was why Shouko became close to me.
I treated everyone the same, after all.
It's been two years since you transferred in.
Yeah. I made a few friends too.
That's why I kinda look forward to coming to school.
Huh? You like coming to school?
Well, no one plays with me at home.
There's no one to talk to,
and it's so big that it gets lonely.
Minazuki Elementary School
I have much more fun at school.
Well, isn't that nice?
I'd prefer to have the big house.
Then do you wanna come play at my house?
No way.
It's a hundred times more fun to read a book than play with you.
"You meanie."
You meanie.
Sticks and stones...
"You bully."
You bully.
may break my bones...
"You dummy."
You dummy.
but words will never hurt me.
Yuuji...
You're in love with me, aren't you?
That's why you're too embarrassed to come play with me.
Do you really want me to play with you that much?
Um...
What? I can't hear you.
My grandfather mentions Seiryou Girls' Academy a lot.
That famous school for rich ladies?
You're gonna transfer again?
Probably, yeah.
He keeps asking me if I'm being bullied at school.
I get it. You want your parents to see that you have friends and stop him, right?
I don't want to leave.
I finally made a friend other than you, Yuuji.
Then get them to meet your parents.
I'm not that close to her yet.
Well, that's not my problem.
I treated everyone the same
because I didn't care about anyone.
You meanie.
I am not.
Yes, you are.
Yuuji.
I have the biggest boobs in the whole class.
Daily duty
And yet, it was enough to make that one lonely little girl care about me.
I already told you I don't care about that!
Hey, Sakamoto!
Don't ignore us, you brat!
You can't get away.
Don't get cocky!
That's why I wanted to go home early!
What? I didn't hear ya!
What do you want?
I don't have time to waste with the likes of you.
Watch your mouth. That's not how you talk to your elders!
You're just a fifth-grade shrimp!
You guys have been waiting for me every day because I trounced you in the mock exam.
Don't you have anything better to do?
Or do you just not have any friends and want someone to talk to you?
You're the one with no friends, you little twerp!
Don't get so cocky just because you got a slightly higher grade than the rest of us!
We're sixth graders, got it? Show some respect!
Respect? You're a bunch of morons.
You want me to show you some respect?
I respect you for being moronic beyond words.
We're your seniors!
You've been studying a year longer, and you still lost to me.
Me, respect you? Don't make me laugh!
You brats oughta be polite to me!
What did you say, twerp?
Hey now, are you sure about this?
Touch me, and the teachers will know.
I'm special, remember?
Got it? So move along.
I don't want to see your ugly mugs ever again.
He really is annoying.
I'm so gonna kill him.
But what can we do?
Fuck, man! If we can't mess with him directly, we'll just have to make do with his books and shoes.
Great idea! They won't know it was us!
All right! We'll teach that brat how to behave.
Let's do that.
I'm home!
How was your day, Yuuji?
What were you doing out so late?
I had class rep stuff to do.
Oh, really? I thought you were playing with Shouko.
I'd never wanna play with her. Come on!
You're friends, aren't you?
No, we aren't.
Oh, don't say that.
She's gonna become a real beauty when she grows up.
By then, it'll be too late for you to realize she's as pretty as your mother!
I'm not gonna realize anything. You're not pretty in the first place.
How mean!
I'm gonna be late tomorrow too.
Do you have more work at school?
No, but I need to teach a lesson to some seniors.
Seniors?
It's a long story.
By the way, Mom, why are you wearing an apron?
I made your favorite! Meat stew.
I just started cutting the sweet potatoes—
Why are you putting sweet potatoes in stew?!
Well, I tried to thaw the potatoes, but they broke into pieces!
Rather than thaw them out, you need to look up what a stew is!
Well, never mind. At least it sounds edible this time.
And well, I forgot to buy the meat,
so I made meat stew without the meat.
Isn't that just steamed potatoes then?!
Library
They couldn't get to me, so they wanted to attack my belongings.
Still, I already foresaw such an event.
The Gordian Knot
This'll be fun.
I gathered everything I wanted to protect next to me.
I left a bait for the sixth graders to damage and waited to call a teacher on them.
The Gordian Knot
Well then! Where was that book I wanted to finish?
The Wright
Brothers
.................
Records of the
.........................
Three Kingdoms
Sun Tzu
The Art
of War
Sun Tzu
The Art
of War
Toyotomi
Back then, I used to think of my isolated self as some sort of hero.
Huh? Now that I think about it, Shouko didn't come to pester me today.
Wednesday | Daily Duty | Kirishima
Absentees
Nagare
Late
Kojima
Went
home early
Today's Activities
People to contact
Daily duty
Kirishima
Question 11:
Read the following passage
and answer the questions below.
Jihei asked, "Where is Sadakichi?"
Tasuke hugged him and answered,
"At Okiku's. He said he'd explain his
love of ten years in a beautiful song."
Upon hearing that, Jihei frowned and said,
"A love song, huh? We know how that will end up." "Definitely. His songs are terrible, but ____."
1. Insert the correct word in the blank to complete the sentence. Explain its meaning.
2. What does the underlined "end up" refer to? What do Jihei and Tasuke expect will happen?
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
1. "...terrible, but he likes writing them." It means that
Sadakichi enjoys writing songs, even though he's unskilled at it.
2. They expect that his terrible song to fail,
and his feelings to remain unanswered.
Teacher's comment:
Correct. The other idiom starting with "terrible" is
"a terrible copycat". Both indicate an utter lack of skill,
and from that, Jihei and Tasuke's negative expectations are obvious.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
1. "...terrible, but he never gives up."
It means that he sucks at writing songs, but he doesn't care.
2. Okiku will surely be moved by Sadakichi wailing with all his might.
Teacher's comment:
I can't say it's correct, but I really like this answer.
Back then, I used to follow Yuuji around everywhere.
Sure, he was cold to me,
but he was cold to everyone else too.
I wonder if Yuuji's still there.
That's why I loved being with him.
Dammit, he's not here either!
Stupid scaredy cat!
Maybe someone else already hid his shoes.
That's totally possible! He does get bullied a lot!
Never mind that, then. Let's do something else!
Sakamoto
Okay. What do we write?
How about "I cheat on all the tests"?
Awesome!
Excuse me!
Um... T-That's...
What do you want?
T-That's Yuuji's.
Don't ruin it!
What do you care? Get out.
But Yuuji is my friend!
"Yuuji would probably get angry if he heard that"
was what I thought, but I couldn't stop.
I do care!
He has friends after all!
A girl at that!
Hey, just ignore her and finish this!
Yeah, let's do a good number on this baby.
Don't!
What the hell? Go away!
Yuuji would probably yell at me that we weren't friends.
Don't!
Stop it already!
Why you!
Move aside!
No!
You're pissing me off!
But I still...
No!
Hey, man, you okay?
What'd you do to my shirt, dammit?
I'm really mad now!
Please don't!
It's too late for that.
I wonder if they're finished yet.
Oh, they're still at it.
What do you think you're doing?
What's going on? What's Shouko doing there?
Don't tell me she...
One glance was enough to tell me why Shouko was there.
I... I have to help her.
Indeed.
I'm a hero, after all.
I'm a smart and special kid compared to those bumbling morons.
There's such a big difference between us. What do I have to fear?
It's all right. Don't be scared.
Those losers are nothing before you.
There are three of them. I can already see the ending.
I know! I'll go call a teacher!
But what would happen to Shouko?
If the teachers told her parents that she was being bullied,
they'd make her transfer out.
I don't care about that!
What else can I do?!
What you can do? Don't you already know?
I just wanted them to think about what they did!
Then it's best you pretend you didn't see that.
I can't do that!
Whatever path you choose, you will suffer.
You'll be hurt, one way or another.
In that case, isn't there only one thing you can do?
But they're seniors.
There are three of them too! There's no way I can win!
And whose fault do you think that is?
But...
I guess you're afraid of getting beaten up.
Of course I am!
Aren't you a hero?
True heroes don't get scared.
Even if they know they'll lose, they still have to try to save—
Shut up! That shit only happens in cartoons and comics!
Haven't you been making fun of them all this time?
But that's only because they suck at school—
Man, you brainy chaps have it tough.
Look at you, making excuses...
looking for a way out.
Then would it be better if I was an idiot too?
That's true.
An idiot who'd confront them without a second thought
would look much cooler than you do now.
Why? Why did it come to this?!
Why do I have to worry about this?!
I haven't done anything wrong.
It's all their fault! It's Shouko's fault for being careless and picking a fight with them!
Yet...
why do I have to care?
I know. Shouko should call for help.
That's it! She just needs to shout for help.
Then, even if a teacher finds out, and she has to transfer,
it'll be her own fault,
not mine!
That's how it should be!
Shout, Shouko. Call for help!
Wouldn't you rather transfer out than get bullied like that?
Shout! Hurry up! Call for help!
Shout, Shouko! Shout for help!
Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!
No... I don't want to leave!
Why?
Why?!
Y-Y-You punks!
What do you think you're doing?!
Yuuji?
You've gone and done it now!
You lowlifes!
Sakamoto?
Damn, now he's here too.
Go home, Shouko.
Hey!
What was that, Sakamoto? You running away?
Yuuji!
You go home, Shouko.
But...
Go!
I'll go call a teacher—
You idiot! It's all right! You go home!
You're just getting in my way!
Okay. I'll go home.
On that day, I realized how immature I really was.
I was miserable and pathetic. It was embarrassing.
When I saw Yuuji shaking in fear, I could only curse myself for being so powerless.
It was my fault that Shouko got the wrong idea about what I was doing.
A mistake I had to pay for.
No. You're mistaken, Yuuji.
That's not the whole reason.
I...
Welcome back, Yuuji.
The school called. What happened?
Nothing really. It was nothing.
Well, something happened. You're a mess.
They were annoying me, so I beat them up.
Yuuji, was that the only reason?
Come on! I said they were annoying me!
That's enough of a reason!
They were annoying you, huh?
Auntie!
I'm sorry!
Yuuji lied to you to protect me.
It's okay. You told me the truth already, didn't you?
But, now Yuuji's gonna be punished!
He won't get a recommendation for Shimozuchi Middle School.
It's all right, Shouko.
Auntie's glad that her son's not only good with his books,
but that he can also protect something precious to him.
You know something, Auntie?
What is it, Shouko?
When I grow up,
I wanna be Yuuji's wife!
Oh, my! You already decided that?
I'm sure I can keep him happy!
You should tell that to Yuuji, dear.
Oops.
Then I'll cheer you on, so one day, you can tell him that yourself.
Really?
Yes, really! As long as you don't stop loving him.
Don't worry.
I'm sure...
I'll love him forever!
Hi! Ho! Let's go!
I can still tell when it was
I didn't forget. I still remember
I decided to be strong,
so don't look at me like that. I know
It's difficult
I really have to go today
I can't let you see me lose this fight
Just give me a thumbs up and tell me I did a good job
I won't lose
I'm always like
a strong wind
Hi! Ho! Let's go!
It's because you're with me
that I can go on
Hi! Ho! Let's go!
It's because you're with me
that I have the power
Every day, all day long,
you keep pounding on my back
Your feelings get stronger every year
This must be some kind of divine punishment
Even if history forgets it,
your heart will remember
I want to say something
It's really amazing. Let me say it
Question 12:
Answer the
following question:
What do you call a group
of people discourteously
acting as they want?
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
A mob.
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Well done, Himeji.
In olden times, this word was
used to describe a group of
monsters wreaking havoc.
It's also applied to people nowadays.
Sugawa Ryou's answer:
Those well-liked people
shall die!
Teacher's comment:
The question is about you students.
Question 12.
What do you call a group of people discourteously acting as they please?
Those well-liked people shall die!
The question is about you students.
Next time: Idiots, and clowns, and a song for the dead.
Next time:
Idiots, and Clowns, and A Song for the Dead.
Idiots,
A Song for the Dead.
This will be on the test.