Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono mune de
It now trembles within my chest
Mou kuru ki ga shita
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne to
So happy for them
This girl...
Medical Offices (After Hours), School Infirmary
She took in a whole lot of consciousness all at once, right?
Yeah.
Because of me.
No...
You fulfilled your most important duty as leader, Yuri.
You brought the SSS out of a major crisis.
Besides, nobody could have imagined this.
Clones were positioned all over the Guild, lying in wait.
And it was Kanade's...
That cold-hearted Kanade's plan.
When you consider that... it's Kanade after all.
You didn't have a choice.
I see.
You saying that helps, but...
Hey...
"There are no hospitals here".
"Nobody gets sick".
Didn't you say those things?
Then, why?
Why won't you wake up?
Damn it all!
Principal's Office
It's never happened before.
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
We've never seen Tenshi in that condition before.
Depending on the circumstances...
it's possible she may never wake again.
That possibility itself is what's irregular.
She'll wake up.
She'll eventually wake up and it'll be as if she just overslept.
And when that time comes?
What will she be like?
Whoa, Shiina talked!
This must be an incredibly important problem!
That's exactly right.
It's a problem.
So, which Tenshi will she be?
The first one.
The one we went fishing with.
But the ones that attacked us were all warlike and ruthless.
Yeah, and they had the power of almost 100 bodies.
The question of why she's lost her own will now...
Probably, all those consciousnesses have squeezed inside her little head and...
Like this... they're messing everything up and doing awful things in there.
So, if she wakes up, she might wake up with 100 warring consciousnesses inside her?
Statistically speaking, the chances of her waking up as she was before are probably about 1%.
What do we do?
We're already making our move.
I sent Takeyama-kun to Tenshi-area.
Along with some teammates who can help translate the manual.
What about TK and Matsushita?
They're at the infirmary.
They're keeping a lookout.
The way TK is, his English is completely useless.
Erase all the data, change the login password,
and then seal all of her abilities.  Am I right?
But that will only work as a temporary measure.
Do you understand that?
I know.
She'll eventually regain access and start creating data again.
In that case why not just destroy the machine itself?
Because there's a limitless number of replacements in the computer lab.
Software, too.
Aww, dammit.
Wow, everyone seems smarter than usual today.
Did you guys eat something strange?
All we can do now is wait for God's will.
I wonder, whose side is God on?
Oh, no.  I'm late.
The entrance exam...
Hang in there.
Hey!
Are you alright?
I feel a little faint.
You're bleeding from your forehead.
How's your awareness?
I think I'm alright.
How are you feeling?  Are you nauseous?
I'm okay...
Why, are you a doctor?
No way.  Just a student.
Can you stand?
Yeah...
Grab on.
You okay?
Yeah... thanks.
That's awful.
Yeah.
We need to call for help.
Shit!
No good?
I'm gonna help those still inside.
I'll help.
Are you gonna be alright?
I'm just a little giddy.
I'm Igarashi.
Otonashi.
Let's hurry.
Is help coming?
I'm gonna look for an exit!
If I get out, I'll call for help.
When that happens, I'll return for sure!
I'm gonna borrow the flashlight!
Okay!  We're counting on you!
Otonashi!
I know you'll find help!
You got it!
Damn it!
What is this?
Otonashi!
How did it go?
It was... a little difficult.
I see...
Everyone, listen up!
We're blocked in on both sides.
Cell phones won't work, either.
We can't contact the outside.
We're all in this together.
I don't want anyone to think they can just try to save themselves.
Gather up any food and water, and we'll all share it equally.
Hang on a minute!
Who put you in charge?
Then who's gonna be in charge?!
Who's gonna tend to the injured?!
This guy knows how to do that stuff.
Surely you're not recommending that we just ignore the wounded.
I... that's not what I meant...
Help is going to come for sure.
We just need to endure until then.
Let's work together!
If you're thirsty, please say so!
Food will be given at scheduled times!
If you're feeling unwell, call for Otonashi!
Just hold on for a little longer.
If anything happens, let me know.
Okay.
Otonashi.
What about food?
We've got handmade lunches and some snacks.
For drinks, we've got maybe 6 PET bottles of tea and water.
That'll last us 3 days at most.
Even so, you're pretty impressive.
How so?
You're very devoted.
Were you planning to go overseas in an NPO or something?
No... I wasn't planning to.
I was joking.
Don't take me so seriously.
Anyway, make sure you keep your own strength up.
We don't need you collapsing.
Yeah.
Hey!
You bastard!
He's taking the water!
Wait!
You shit!
The water!
Stop!
Wh-what do you want, Leader-sama?
You planning to tie me up?!
Do what you want!
Nobody's coming to help anyway!
Right?  Everyone knows that, right?!
That's not true.
Help is coming.
Nonsense!
That boy just wasted our precious water!
It's alright.
That was my portion.
I won't drink anymore from here on.
So, don't worry...
Somebody punch that guy!
I won't feel better until I see it!
Don't worry, I'll punish him plenty.
It's alright.  I'll split my portion with you.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it.
Alright, let's do something about this guy.
Hey, you help out too.
What...
Otonashi.  Otonashi!
Something's wrong, come here!
Damn it!
Come back to us.
Come back!
Damn it.
UTW Presents:
After that day... what was I working so hard for?
From her... from Hatsune, I learned my reason for living.
And then...
I saw someone's life end right in front of me again.
Nothing had changed at all.
I'm still so powerless.
Ever since then, nothing's changed at all.
Damn it.
Damn it!
Shouldn't you rest a bit?
I just wanna read a little more.
Fine...
Here you go.
It'd be bad if you caught a cold.
Still, I wonder why you haven't gotten better yet.
Maybe if I can find a donor...
Donor?
Igarashi...
Do you have a pen?
Sure.
TL Note: This is an Organ Donor Card used to specify which organs can be used for donation.
Sign: I, in accordance with my wishes offer my organs for transplant in the event of brain death.
Sign: Please circle the organs you wish to donate.
Circling: Heart, Lungs, Liver, Kidney, Pancreas, Small intestine, Eyeballs, Others
Circling: Kidney, Pancreas, Eyeballs, Others
Crossing out: I do not wish to offer my organs.
Writing: -nashi Yuzuru
Good grief.
What are you doing?
If I do this, even if I lose my own life...
Even then, my life can be used for the sake of another person.
We're giving our lives a meaning.
Man, you really are amazing.
Take a look, Otonashi.
Even in the midst of this despair, everyone is giving hope to somebody else.
You saved everyone's life.
Otonashi.
Hey, Otonashi.
Are you listening to me?
Otonashi.
Kanade!
I've been so worried about you!
Are you alright?  Is your body okay?
It was a grand battle.
Battle?
That the "me" who made that promise to you was the one to wake up... is a miracle.
Listen, I... remember everything.
When I died.
On my way to my examination...
I was in a train accident.
I... wanted to become a doctor.
I wanted to help somebody.
I wanted to live for people's gratitude.
That's what I thought...
... and I studied pretty frantically for it.
But, you know...
In the end, I left my body behind by donating my organs.
My body must have been able to save someone.
That's what I believe.
I'm sure that somebody...
despite not knowing you...
is even now still thinking "thank you".
Yuzuru?
Yes?
So, now you don't have any regrets?
That's right.
If I was able to save somebody...
My life wasn't such a bad thing after all.
That's what I think.
Wait...
Am I gonna disappear?
If you have no regrets...
I still have those guys.
That's right.
You want to stay with them all forever.
They're my comrades.
Of course I do.
But... now I have a different feeling, too.
Maybe they all can reach that stage too.
And we can all say goodbye to this world.
Another life might not be so bad.
That's right.
Yeah.
Wait a second.
Could it be that you wanted to bring this feeling to everyone?
You didn't know that?
I didn't know!
Besides, when we first met, you suddenly stabbed me!
That's cause you asked me to prove that you won't die.
They've just been spinning their wheels the whole time.
Those guys and this girl.
Talk about being awkward!
If we take classes seriously, would we be happy?
If we start doing normal club activities, would we be satisfied?
Well, everyone who comes here was unable to properly live out their youth.
Huh?  Really?
You didn't know?
I didn't know!
Besides, how do you know that kind of thing?
You didn't realize just from watching?
I see...
This place...
It was meant as relief for our souls.
Even Hinata, if he'd caught that fly ball to second...
... he'd have been fulfilled and disappeared.
What a lot of meddling we've done.
Yuri and I...
Iwasawa reached it with her own power.
She was fulfilled and disappeared.
Nobody is here because they want to be.
They're rebelling against the unfairness of life.
Kanade wanted to show us that that isn't right.
She wanted to show us a life that isn't unfair.
She wanted to give us a normal youth.
She wanted to persuade those of us who wanted to stop that.
That's...
... unbelievably ironic.
It was so simple all along, and yet...
Led by our beliefs, we opposed one another.
Eventually going so far as to create weapons.
Until eventually, every day was filled with conflict.
How bad with words are you?
I know.
At least you're aware of it.
Yeah.
But maybe...
If you're alongside me, I might be able to do it.
Are you... asking me to help?
To tell the truth, you probably should have disappeared by now.
But you're still here.
I... could become your very first ally.
Isn't that what's keeping you here?
You might be right.
But...
Until that day, I truly thought I was a responsible older Sister.
But everything I wanted to protect, was stolen from me in 30 minutes.
You don't find that unreasonable?
You don't find a life like that unforgivable?
There's no way.
But wait... that's just it.
Because it's her.  Trying to hang onto that memory forever.
I want to save her.
Can I do it?
Along with this clumsy Angel.
How unreliable I am.
Is it undoable after all?
No.  If I give up, the conflict will only continue.
What should I do?
I, a member of the SSS, but also Kanade's ally.
Shouldn't I be the one doing something?
Hey.
Will you help me?
Isn't that my line?
I see...
That's right...
What am I saying to Tenshi?
I understand, Kanade.
Let's have them graduate.
From here.
All of us.
And so, we now know that during the last testing period...
there was a group trying to sabotage Tachibana by switching her answer sheets.
Tachibana herself has proven that it was not her handwriting, and shown her innocence.
Itsumo hitori de aruiteta
I've always walked alone
Concordantly, she will be returning to her former position as Student Council President.
Furthermore, after assisting as replacement President, Naoi will be returning to his position as Vice President.
Furikaeru to minna wa tooku
When I turned around, everyone was far away
Ahhh, come on!
Why do I have to do this?
Soredemo atashi wa aruita
Even so, I walked on
They caught us all.
So, what was the point of all that tailspin flying?
You said it!
Oh my, we actually agree for once.
Sore ga tsuyosa datta
That's what it was to be strong
Only those who had to go through it can understand our feelings.
We're tailspin-flight friends!
Mou nani mo kowaku nai
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
Oho.  Are you trying to get me undressed?
Hell yeah, take it off!
Cut it out, you're being noisy.
Yeah, that's gross, cut it out!
Sou tsubuyaite miseru
That's what I try to tell myself
So, which is it?
Still, she seems to have completely forgotten about the past few days.
That's to be expected.  The 100 won, after all.
Itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
Eventually, everyone will be alone
The ones who attacked us.
I actually thought she might become our ally for a minute there.
Ahh, damn it!
Omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
They'll continue to live only through their memories
The first thing I need to do is learn about their pasts.
But, now that we don't have an enemy...
Kodoku sae aishi waratterareru yori
Rather than try to love and laugh at this loneliness
I doubt I can move without Yuri noticing.
So, Kanade...
I want you to go back to being the Student Council President.
Atashi wa tatakau n da
I will fight
I want you to fight them again.
I want you to move as I tell you.
Okay.
That plan is perfect for me.
Namida nante misenai n da
I will never show you my tears
I'll be leaving you all alone again.
I'm sorry.
But, when this is all over...
When it's all over...
When that happens...
When that happens, what happens to us?
UTW Staff
Translator: Ershin
Timer/Typesetter/Editor: Nikon
Timer: ar
QC/Stuff: Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c44] The band is dying because of your guitar.
[c164] Tenshi... you say?
[c47] As I thought, not one to be taken lightly.
[c47] I know that sound.
[c141] German Suplex!
[c75] It's just something I wanted to try.
[c192] Prepare yourself!
[c162] Has your idiocy been cured?
[c185] We men will win!
[c210] Hey, which side are you on!?
[c173] KISS YOU!
[c218] It's a miracle!
[c105] Alright! I'll grant it for you!
[c289] All of my happiness was taken away...