Two weeks had passed...
since Joe's failed attempt to escape.
The six were waiting patiently for him to return to their cell.
Joe!
Now, get in there!
Joe...
Joe!
Guys, I'm sorry.
Hey, did you see your sister?
Yeah.
We have no relatives.
Our only choice is to be used by others.
Don't... think about me anymore.
I can live on my own.
I...
really...
Why did I even go there?
Joe.
You got bruises all over your face.
Let's fix you up a bit.
Hey, Mario!
Go get me a wet towel!
Sure.
This is ridiculous.
In the end, we all got hurt for nothing.
Uncovered!
You...
I didn't lie.
Did I?
Hey!
How can you say it was for nothing?
The results don't matter.
For people like us, chances only come around once in a blue moon.
Joe went for the one chance he got.
You can't say it was for nothing.
"We're just the trash of society, and if we don't risk our lives for every chance we get,
we'll become nothing more than sore losers."
"Therefore, courage is our only hope."
Bro's words touched the boys deeply.
I...
I think I'll become a singer.
A singer?
Yeah.
Meg...
My sister is much more mature than me.
She's prepared for anything.
I can't just waste my life here.
I'll get out of this place as soon as I can, and I'll rise to the top.
I'll become the most famous singer in history,
and until Meg comes to find me...
I won't give up.
Hey!
You idiots!
Stop slacking and defend!
Sorry about that.
Is it our turn to bat now?
There's only two months left.
You guys seem to be rather fond of Sakuragi.
I'm not really that...
Well, I'm not saying it's bad, but...
Um, if you don't have anything to-
So...
do you even know why Sakuragi's in here?
You see...
He killed his own parents.
His own parents!
You want to be a singer?!
All right, let's hear you sing.
Wait, here?
No, he shouldn't sing in the dining hall.
Come on, a little won't hurt.
Well, if you like, I'll show you how it's done.
With your voice, you'll be sent straight to the isolation chamber.
Say that again?!
Bro, are you sure?
Yeah.
Thanks!
Cabbage!
Don't put that in your mouth.
Uncovered.
You can't fall any lower than eating something a murderer gave you.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
What do you mean, Uncovered?
Exactly what I said.
He's the worst piece of scum, a murderer!
Why don't you tell us all about it right here?
That you were sent here for killing your parents.
Who told you something like that?
Hit me if you want.
You're always like that.
Hey, Sakuragi, what are you doing?
Nomoto, what's going on?
Explain.
Nothing needs explaining here.
I see.
All right.
Come with me, Sakuragi.
Bro!
Uncovered!
What the hell's your problem?
He's our friend!
Friend?
Bro...
Don't get puffed up thinking you've tamed those kids!
Damn...
You're a fucking...
One Year Ago
How's that, Sakuragi?
Well?
I hope that taught you your place!
You done, Ishihara?
What was that?
If you want to hit me, you better do it while you can.
But... one day, I'll make you wish you were dead!
On his behalf, too.
Stop looking at me like that, Sakuragi!
Well yeah, we all respect Bro.
But... parricide isn't funny.
What are you saying?
He's one of us!
We need to believe in him!
Snap out of it, Mario.
People can't be trusted.
If you believe you've got friends, they'll just turn around and bite you someday.
Uncovered...
Bro!
Uncovered.
What's the problem?
It's Nomoto.
I'd like to go to the library to do some research.
Very well!
I'm sick of being in the same room as you.
Bro...
What he said isn't true, is it?
Please explain.
I can't just accept it as is.
Bro!
Shut up. You're just a kid!
Bro, you didn't need to do that!
That was low.
What now?
It's Sakuragi.
I'd also like to look something up in the library.
All right.
Bro!
I...
I'll believe anything you tell me.
Bro...
Why?
I thought... we were friends.
Tell me, Bro!
Bruises and fractures heal with time,
but the wounds in people's hearts do not heal as easily.
A sad cage of Hell where love and trust are fragile:
That was the world inside a cell.
I don't need any friends.
I won't trust anyone.
No way in hell I will.
After Japan lost the war,
everyone living in the cities became victims of starvation.
"I won't believe a single person."
His mother gave away her body to a disgusting old man for a mere handful of food.
Even as a child, Uncovered was pushed deep into a pit of misanthropy.
Yo, Nomoto.
Wh-What is it?
Come with me for a bit.
S-Sure...
Geez.
I'm impressed you hid these in a book.
Hey, Nomoto.
Sakuragi put these in here, right?
Didn't he?
Don't worry.
It's simple.
You just need to sign for your testimony.
Then I'll say I found it and give him a little beating.
Why are you going so far?
It's fine either way, Nomoto.
I can beat you instead.
If you care so much for the parricide, that is.
It's... Sakuragi's weed.
Good.
That's what I needed to hear.
Hey, Sakuragi.
The library's over here.
What's going on?
What's the alarm for?
A fire!
A fire?
It started in the library.
The library?!
No...
Mr. Ishihara, can I ask you to take the second compound?
Please evacuate everyone to the yard.
Damn kids, making me work.
Hey.
Sakuragi's in cell 2-6, right?
What did you do?
What to do...
I don't have the key to your cell.
Here, Nomoto.
You double check too.
Do I have the key for cell 2-6?
I don't, do I?
I can't unlock the cell, now can I?
Don't panic!
Evacuate to the yard calmly!
You just need to keep quiet.
If you do, I won't tell anyone about your weed.
Are we on the same page?
I'm saved.
What's going on?
What's all the commotion?!
Hey!
It's not safe!
Stay away!
We're making sure you're all here.
Line up according to your cells.
Nomoto.
There's no turning back now.
S-Sakuragi?
What?!
Sakuragi?!
Uncovered.
Sakuragi.
Why are you here?
Mr. Ishihara, I need your help.
Sure.
Mr. Ishihara!
Damn it!
That screwed up my plans,
but they're all trash anyway.
No one's gonna care about five less pieces of garbage!
Uncovered, where's the rest of the gang?
I... I... I...
I didn't do anything.
Uncovered?
I don't know!
I don't know anything!
Damn it, what's going on?
Why wasn't our cell unlocked?!
I don't wanna die here.
Turtle!
Keep down, or the smoke will get you.
Damn, it won't even budge.
Don't worry, guys.
Bro... will definitely come for us.
I believe in-
Wake the fuck up!
We gotta do something ourselves!
Mario...
No way in hell am I dying in here!
Where are they?
Are they still inside?
Uncovered!
It's not my fault!
It was...
It was all Ishihara.
I didn't do anything!
I... I...
Hey, you're not thinking of going to save them?
Are you nuts?!
Look at the fire!
No one's gonna pat you on the back for being a hero!
No one's waiting!
They don't think you'll come to save them either!
They don't see you as their friend anymore!
You're probably right.
Then why?!
Because...
I still see them...
as my friends.
It may not be too late.
What the hell?
Why are you going so far?
Nothing good comes from believing in people.
You have to look out for yourself.
Wasn't that... what it was all about?
"Perhaps it's already too late."
"Perhaps they're already dead."
"But if I don't act now, I don't get a second chance."
Bro runs.
He runs amid the scorching flames and the whirling smoke,
with hope nowhere to be found.
He runs to his friends.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
The flames only grow.
They are in a tight spot.
Don't give up!
We still have him.