This was the most
special of the special.
It was an emergency ration
for true emergencies.
that was saved for the
last of the last resorts.
All I'm asking is who ate this.
Grudges over food sure are scary.
Spike, by perchance, was it you?
If I was the culprit, I wouldn't leave
the empty box lying around like that.
Ed is hungry.
Maybe you ate it yourself,
but are pretending
to be upset because
we found the empty box?
What?!
We haven't had anything to
eat for two whole days!!
Don't you call a situation
like this an emergency?!
I wanna eat stuff like
fried beef noodles...
We're out of gas!
We can't do anything about it!
If you could hold out
like this a bit longer,
we'll reach Europa soon
thanks to inertia.
Tummy's caving in!
If only we could use that
energy to propel ourselves...
You keep mouthing off like that and
I'll toss you out into absolute zero.
And a stir-fry of liver and
chives would be good, too...
Sounds good.
At least it's better than aimlessly
floating around this place.
That was some collision...
Hey! Can you hear me?
Answer me! Hey!!
Isn't this...
a hit-and-run?!
This is bad! The shock from that
collision changed our trajectory!
What did what to who?
What's going on?!
Wow... Where is this place?
This is so uncivilized!
I don't think that's our problem...
We have to start by checking the ship.
Can you go get some food?
What?
I suddenly feel... a stabbing pain...
What are you trying to pull?
This expired a year ago...
I'm glad I didn't eat it.
Serves you right.
This is divine retribution!
Let's get to it...
Whatcha gonna do?
Ed will help, too!
We're fine here, so go outside
and find us some food.
Okay!
Gotta wear my socks
to go out, to go out...
Nothing here...
It's that hit-and-run ship!
Wait, wait!!
Wait, wait!!!
Smell...
Smell... food...
Food!
Give me!
1,000 woolongs each, including tax.
Cash only. No money cards
or cash cards allowed.
I don't have money.
Then hurry home, kid.
Can I have one?
1,000 woolongs each.
Cash only. Cards are...
Kid, no use staring.
If you want food,
go someplace like the town.
I don't need change.
In exchange...
If you see this man, give me a call.
Thanks!
Excuse us.
We would like to check your baggage.
Something wrong?
Apparently, a broker on
the wanted list
for illegal mushroom sales
made a getaway to this town.
What a coincidence.
I'm after that bounty as well.
A cowboy?
We're gonna check out your trunk.
Go ahead, feel free.
Hey!
All right! Freeze!
- Now, wait a minute...
- All right, stay still...
- I don't know anything about this!
- Turn around! Hands on the ground!
- What are you doing?!
- Now put your hands on the ground!
- Let go of me!!
- Hurry up!
Food, food, do you have any?
Oh, you don't? Oh, you do?
Boy, am I hungry...
Meanie!
What?
Give me!
Give me something!
Damn it, stop hanging all over me!
Hey!
I won't let you tell me you
forgot who I am, Domino!
Let's see...
Come on! Remember, damn it!
I'm the younger of the Shaft brothers
that bought mushrooms from you!
I really can't recall...
You do want to know why I drag an
empty coffin around like this, don't you?
It's because...
I'm going to go home after
putting your corpse inside--
Pieces... All in pieces!
What was what to who?
My big bro ate a mushroom
he bought from you,
and laughed and laughed,
and twisted his intestines to death!
A happy way to die.
Shut up!
Speaking of which,
it's all your fault!
That's what I call
an unjust resentment!
Ed is hungry, too!
Take this!
Wait, you bastard! Damn it!
Food!
Don't, Ein! We have to share!
Ein?
Bad mushroom?
This for real?
Delicious!
This really can't be happening.
Really...
This really has no way of happening.
Hey... You know, the world
really is a great place...
Did I just say something?
Hey, mister.
This is a stairway to heaven.
You know that, right?
An obnoxious little frog...
I don't care anymore.
I warned you!
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
I now know the secrets of the universe.
By the way...
who was I?
So, these mushrooms are
inedible after all...
So, as you can tell, it's time
for another episode of Big Shot!
We'll introduce you to more
and more bounties this week!
So, batting first for us today
is this man, Domino Walker.
He's currently wanted for
selling illegal mushrooms.
- That's the guy we just saw!
- The bounty is a conservative 1.2 mil.
That's cowgirl, Ein.
We earn money, and buy food!
Ein, you're a cow-woofwoof!
Here we go!
One!
Two!
Five!
Four!
Hello!
Hey, don't underestimate the police!
I really don't know anything!
Then why did you have a strange kid
and a dog in the trunk of your car?!
Hello... Yes?
Oh, it's you, Sally.
Really... You're so hopeless...
I told you so many times
not to call me at work...
And? Yeah, yeah, and that's it?
I mean, I didn't mean it that
way when I said "that's it?"...
Yeah, yeah, like that.
I love you, Sally.
Got it. Tonight at 7 it is. Bye-bye!
Hey!
What's wrong, young'un?
Lookin' like that...
Did your woman run off without you?
What to say...
None of your business, old geezers.
Oh, man... that's for
eating all at once.
They say when you're in
a hurry, go around.
Is that right?
He's not here...
That hit-and-run ship!
I'm sure they never even dreamed
that I was raising these in here.
This one's bad.
Well, making an emergency landing here
was the only miscalculation I had.
Were you surprised?
I was.
What the hell are you guys?
Why are you here?
That's my line!
How did you get in here
in the first place?
- The door was open.
- Is that so?!
Culprit of the hit-and-run,
prepare to get arrested!
Stink bug gas!
Wait, wait, wait!
Don't think that you
can get away from me!
Don't get in my way!
Ein! Growl!
C-- Come on! Let go of me!
Boo!
Gotcha!
W-- Wait...
T-- These mushrooms are
worth 100,000 each.
Let me go, and I'll give them to you.
Why?
Think about which one is worth more.
I don't know.
A-- Are you an idiot?!
Take the mushrooms!
Okay!
Thanks.
Oh, it's no problem.
Yahoo! Dinner! Mushroom!
100,000 each? Really?
That sure would make some money.
These are real?
Excuse me.
I'm with the police.
I want to ask a few questions about
Domino, an illegal mushroom dealer.
Unfortunately, we have no clue.
I'm so sorry we can't be of any help.
Ed knows who that--!
Don't mind her...
In exchange, I got--!
- Really...
- She's a troublesome kid...
Excuse me, sir.
They're okay.
He must really like shiitake mushrooms.
Well, sorry to bother you.
Here's dinner.
What's the menu?
Shiitake stir-fry, shiitake stew,
shiitake salad, and a shiitake dessert.
Again? How many days has it been?
No... I can't eat anymore.
Quit complaining, and be
thankful that we can even eat!
Thankful!
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
A videotape that was delivered to
the Bebop with no return address.
Because we wanted to view the tape,
things took a turn for the unexpected.
No, actually it doesn't go anywhere.
At first glance,
the story is pointless,
the actions are on a small scale,
and the ending is forced...
but what will you get out of it all?
Next episode: Speak like a Child.
At first glance, it's interesting.