In the year 845, two terrifying
new breeds of Titan appeared:
the Colossal and the Armored,
barreling through the outer walls as if
wholesale destruction was child's play.
The territory couched within the
circle of Wall Maria was abandoned.
Twenty percent of the human race perished.
As the Titan onslaught advanced,
our only choice was to withdrawal behind Wall Rose.
Five years later, the Colossal Titan reappeared in Trost.
Humanity had failed to stop the Titan onslaught.
Cadet Eren Jaeger, tragically
consumed early on in the battle,
later emerged, miraculously,
from the fallen body of an Abnormal.
One more time!
Are you a human being or a Titan?
I'm human!
So you say.
I'm left with no choice.
Those things, they just kept coming.
It's a nightmare!
Take it easy!
I watched those monsters eat my squad.
I saw my friends die, and I didn't even really
feel anger or sadness about the whole thing.
All I could think was, "better you than me!"
But soon my number'll be up, too. That'll be it.
The end. Kaput. Game over.
We're s'posed to fight those Titans
until they eat every last one of us!
I don't wanna be eaten. Screw that!
Hey! Come on. Keep it together, okay?
You're not alone, you know!
We're all fighting back our fear.
Look at Sasha! Even after what she's seen,
she remains a proper soldier!
Oh. My stomach aches. Please
cart me away with the wounded.
Lemme die! I just wanna die!
Hold on! Stop it!
Well the order to keep our
mouths shut makes perfect sense now.
As if the situation isn't bad enough already.
If they knew about Eren...
Cannon fire?
But why just one shot?
Look! Smoke!
It's inside the wall!
Did it bust down the water gate?
Impossible. It's the sturdiest part of the whole wall!
Maybe they set off a shell by accident?
But then why is there so much smoke?
Not now. Is that Titan steam?
Hey!
What the hell is that?
It's... It's alive!
Captain Woerman!
Let's see what it does. Maintain your distance!
All squads remain alert.
He could strike at any time!
Artillery Crew! Get that cannon reloaded!
What is that?
I know I heard them fire their cannon at us, and then...
Then there was a tremendous crash and a blast of heat.
And apparently we're now in
the innards of a giant skeleton.
Eren did this for us, Armin.
That's all we need to understand for now.
Those flowers weren't there before. How did they...
Armin! Mikasa!
Hey, are you guys alright?
Eren. How'd you...?
I don't know! But look.
It's already starting to vaporize,
just like the corpse of a Titan.
Let's get out of here!
Hard to tell if they're watching and waiting,
or just totally dazed.
I suppose it doesn't really matter much either way.
I'm sure once the smoke clears they'll resume the attack.
After seeing this, I think we've
blown any hope of reasoning with them.
The cellar. I'm starting to remember.
This key...
Our house in Shiganshina!
My father said I'd have to go
back there. Everything hinged on it!
I think it's why he gave me the power to transform.
If I can make it to our cellar,
I might learn the Titans' secrets.
Why did he keep this stuff secret?
How many thousands of Scouts have already died
because my father didn't share this information?
It could be the last chance humanity has!
And the answer's been hidden away
under our house this entire time?
Is he insane? Damn him!
Where have you been these last five years, Dad?
Eren.
We have other business to deal with.
Right.
Get ready, the smoke's clearing.
As soon as you see it, blast it!
Kill it before it gets us!
Hold your fire!
Listen. I'm getting out of here.
Where? And how?
Anywhere but here. Then I head over
the wall and straight to Shiganshina.
But I'll have to become a Titan again.
You can transform at will?
To be honest, I don't know how I'm doing it, Armin.
I just know that I can!
It's hard to put into words,
but it was like reflexive, see?
In that moment, my mind subconsciously
focused on stopping the cannonball.
That's why it's decaying.
It only had the endurance to meet that task.
Next time I'll be stronger.
I'll be a fifteen meter high
Titan-slayer just like I was before!
Eren!
Your nose is...
Your breathing is erratic. And you're pale!
Something's wrong, Eren. You're not well!
As things stand, my health is irrelevant.
But I have two ideas.
You two could make it outta here alive
if you stop trying to protect me.
I've brought you nothing but trouble as it is.
I'm doing this on my own, from this point forward.
You're kidding. But I...
Eren. I'm coming, too.
No way!
I plan to follow you whether
you give me permission to or not.
I swear. I'll never leave your side.
Mikasa, stop it. I'm being serious here!
I'm not your little brother and
I'm not some snot-nosed toddler!
Captain Woerman. The cannon is almost reloaded.
We're ready, sir. What are
your orders for the next attack?
All troops will await my signal!
Yes sir.
As it stands. The Garrison Regiment
isn't ready to assault our position yet.
If they were, Mikasa would have
reacted faster than a stray cat.
I'm not some snot-nosed toddler!
I would assume they have a
well-trained Artillery crew above us.
That cannon ought to be reloaded
in the next twenty seconds.
Eren will most likely spring into action
and be long gone before that happens.
Why am I thinking of that at a time like this?
Is it... Is it because this is the end for us?
When it's all said and done, at the moment of truth,
I was a coward. Same as right now.
I can't count the number of
times they've come to my rescue.
I was always so weak.
I could never reciprocate the favor.
I still haven't earned the right
to think of myself as their equal.
I-I can't afford to try and repay
their kindness by going with them.
I'd only end up slowing them down.
I'm afraid this might be the last time
the three of us will ever be together.
Listen, I won't...
Just wait a second, would ya?
If you recall, I said I had two ideas.
Armin, I trust you to make the right decision.
Eh? Huh?
Now hear me out.
And yes, I'm aware of how unrealistic this plan is.
The best-case scenario?
I try to use my Titan ability strategically.
Under Military direction.
This might sound crazy...
but if you think you can convince the
Garrison Regiment, right here and now,
that I present no threat to them,
I'll trust you and we'll go with that option.
That's my second idea.
If you don't think you can get it done,
then my last resort is the first idea.
You've got fifteen seconds to decide.
Think you can get it done?
Listen, I'll respect your opinion either way.
Eren. Why would you leave such a major decision up to me?
Because you keep a level head.
You always choose well, no matter how ugly things get.
I figure that's worth relying on.
W-When have I done that?
C'mon, you do it all the time. Take five years ago.
If you hadn't gone to Mr. Hannes for help,
Mikasa and I would've been eaten by the Titans.
That's how you see me?
You don't think I'm a poor excuse for a friend?
I had convinced myself that I
was just a burden to all of you.
But you never...
You never thought of me that way at all!
Armin!
Our time's up!
Artillery crew has reloaded, Captain!
It's your call, sir.
Eren and Mikasa have enough faith
in me to put their lives in my hands,
and I have complete trust in the two of them.
More than anyone else in this world.
And that fact alone is all the convincing I need!
I will persuade them, trust me.
You two just act as non-aggressively
as you possibly can, agreed?
Since Eren first appeared and fought as a Titan,
something has been gnawing at the back of my mind.
I haven't had a chance to collect my thoughts yet,
but I can do this!
I'll just have to think as I talk!
Halt! Halt!
Is this supposed to be your true form, Monster?
I don't buy it!
I'll give the signal to fire, I mean it!
Eren is not a foe of humanity!
We're willing to cooperate with Military Command
and share everything we've learned about his powers!
Your pleas fall on deaf ears!
He revealed his true form, and because
of that threat, he cannot leave here alive!
If you insist that he's not
an enemy of ours, show me proof!
Otherwise, we'll blast him back to
whatever nightmare he crawled out of!
You don't need any proof!
That's right! There's no need at all!
The fact of the matter is it doesn't
matter what we perceive him to be!
What?
The reports say hundreds of soldiers saw him.
And those who were there say
they saw him fighting other Titans!
And that means they saw him
get swarmed by the Titans as well.
To put it plainly, the Titans saw him the same way
they see each and every human being; as their prey!
And it doesn't matter how else you may look at it!
That is an irrefutable fact!
Kid's gotta point.
Prepare to attack!
Don't let yourself be swayed by his cunning lies!
The Titan's behavior has always
been beyond our comprehension.
I wouldn't put it past 'em to assume human form.
He's speaking our language
in an attempt to deceive us!
I refuse to let them continue this behavior unchecked!
It's hopeless.
He let logic give way to hysteria!
Too frightened to think it through.
Eren! Mikasa!
I am a soldier!
And I have dedicated my heart to
the restoration of humanity, sir!
Nothing could make me prouder
than dying for such a noble cause!
If we were to use his Titan ability and
combine it with the manpower we have left,
I believe we can do it!
We can retake this city!
For humanity's glory, in what
little time I have left to live,
I will advocate his strategic value!
Captain Woerman. His words are worth considering, sir.
Maybe we should...
Quiet!
Don't let their words sway you.
They're all traitors!
I swore an oath as an officer.
I will crush all insubordination!
That's enough.
You should really do something about
your nervous disposition, Captain Woerman.
C-Commander Pyxis?
Can you not see this soldier's heartfelt salute?
I've only just arrived,
but I'm quite aware of our situation.
Gather our reinforcements.
I think we could at least do these young
soldiers the favor of hearing them out.
According to reports from the Scout Regiment,
it was anticipated that the
Titans would appear from the south.
These reports were proven accurate when
the Titans attacked Shiganshina District,
located on the south side of Wall Maria.
Therefore,
it was surmised that their next most likely
target would be the fortified city of Trost,
on the southern side of Wall Rose.
Dot Pyxis. The commanding officer
responsible for the southern territory.
The man in charge of the defense of Trost district.
The man given full authority over preserving
humanity's most vital remaining territory.
Nope. Not any of you.
Eaten by a Titan wouldn't be so bad,
if it was a sexy lady one.
The man also notorious for being genuinely eccentric.
What the hell is going through the Commander's head?
Going up there with those freaks
and not bringing any bodyguards!
Well, sir. That's the Commander.
He's well known for taking a less traditional approach.
Captain Woerman.
We have finished assembling the troops, sir.
Ah. Well done.
That's that. So, visiting this
cellar should clear everything up?
Yes, sir. Well, at least I think so.
For the moment, there is no way to
validate all of the claims you've made.
For now, I'll just catalogue them in here.
With that said,
I can usually tell the difference
between the unctuous and the sincere,
which is why I personally guarantee your safety.
You're Cadet Armin Arlelt. Is that correct?
Yes sir!
You mentioned a plan to harness
this so-called "Titan Ability"
and then utilize your friend's power to retake the city.
Do you believe it could work?
Or were you grasping at straws to try and save your hides?
Uh, well... Both, Commander.
I was going to suggest that Eren,
using his strength as a Titan,
could lift that giant boulder.
We could use it to block off the wrecked gate.
That was the best idea I was
able to come up with on the spot.
I-I just wanted to make everyone see
how Eren's ability might provide a solution
to the problem we all face.
Hm.
Granted, I was pretty desperate to survive.
"Desperate to survive," huh?
That's as credible a reason as any, son.
Ahhhh.
What do you say, Cadet Jaeger?
Say, sir?
That hole. Do you think that you can plug it up, son?
Well, I... I don't know.
It's possible. But at the moment,
I don't understand my power any more than you do.
It's just, I sort of feel
irresponsible giving you an answer,
'cause I don't really know.
Ah, yes. Of course, my apologies.
I asked you the wrong question.
Are you willing to, Cadet Jaeger. Or not?
I'll do it.
I'll do it!
I don't know if I can seal that hole.
But... I'll do it!
Despite having fled in terror before,
the survivors choose to stand
on the field of battle once again.
Eren's mind is made up.
"I will be everyone's hope."