Grandma!
No!
It's useless. It's too late.
Grandma!
What's too late?
Takuto!
Grandma!
Don't worry.
She just fainted.
Izumi, you little...
I'm not going to forgive you this time!
Oh boy, now I'm the bad guy.
I was just trying to take
her soul for you Meroko.
Izumi...
More importantly, you remember
all of it now, right, Takuto?
Or should I call you
Takuto Kira of Route L?
Y-You!
How did you know that?!
I'd love to hear you sing
one of these days
before you become a ghost.
Takuto, do you remember
your past now?
Route L?
Dad and Dr. Wakaoji's band?
Takuto!
Did you really remember?!
Hey!
Takuto!
That's right.
I am Takuto Kira from Route L.
Mitsuki, I was the vocalist of the band
that your father and Keichi were in.
You were, Takuto?
Takuto!
You know what will happen
if you remember your days
as a human being, don't you?!
Yeah.
In that case, why?
Please, forget! Forget all of that!
It's all right, Meroko.
No, it's not all right!
I don't want you to become a ghost
under any circumstances, Takuto!
Takuto is gonna be a ghost?
It can't be helped, Mero.
Takuto wasn't cut out to be
a Death Spirit from the start,
so just forget it.
But poor guy,
becoming a Death Spirit
and then getting assigned to
the daughter of his former bandmate.
That's none of your business.
That might not be true.
What if I had arranged
for that to happen?
What?
You did, Izumi?
I'm just saying that
hypothetically.
I just saw Mitsuki's name on
a pediatrician's list by chance.
Izumi, do you understand
what you've done?
Do you really think something
like that is forgivable?
I'm only saying this
hypothetically.
Besides, it's just another dropout
Death Spirit becoming a ghost.
That happens all the time.
If that happened,
you, who loved me before,
could pair up with me again.
That wouldn't be such
a bad thing for you, would it?
Who would want to
pair up with you?
No, you couldn't turn down
such a good offer, Mero.
Whatever the circumstances,
you have never contradicted
any of my proposals.
Don't forget that you
betrayed Takuto too.
I taught you, didn't I?
That people's feelings are precarious.
Get out of here.
Get out of here!
Takuto!
Why are you getting
so heated up?
Shut up!
I don't want to see the face
of a scumbag like you!
What a thing to say.
I think a person who can't even do
their job right is more of a scumbag.
Shut up!
The person who
remembered was you.
You're just getting
what you deserve.
Takuto!
How petty that he can't
sever his ties with his past.
You're the petty one!
Does being a Death Spirit
make you so important?!
Does reaping people's lives
What is so wrong with
remembering my past?
It's... It's a testament
to my life!
Stop! Please stop!
It's not about
being important.
As a Death Spirit,
we must simply accept it.
It's an eternal punishment.
Takuto!
I'll bid my farewell to
Takuto the Death Spirit.
Next time we meet,
you'll probably be a ghost.
Bye bye, Takuto.
Damn it...
Takuto...
Mitsuki, I won't let you die
like this no matter what!
Are you really okay with everything
just coming to an end like this?
Are you really okay
with never singing again?!
But... But... Singing...
For what reason?
I no longer have
any reason to sing.
Do you need a reason to sing?
Don't you sing because
you love to sing?
You love to sing, right?
That's why you've been singing, right?
So what happened?
It's not like you started to hate singing.
And now you're giving it up?
Are you going to waste
the remainder of your life?
Yeah.
Mitsuki...
I love to sing,
but I don't want to anymore.
The reason I sang until now
was to get closer to Eichi.
But now Eichi is gone.
If Eichi in heaven heard you saying that,
he would be very disappointed.
He'd think that it was a waste to
fall in love with such a weak person.
You might be right.
But that's fine with me.
I was ill with a throat disease,
and if I hadn't met you, Takuto,
my life would've gone by
without me ever singing.
But we did meet, right?
And I gave you the body
that allowed you to sing.
Continue singing
to the very end!
You wouldn't be the real you
if you didn't sing.
You'll definitely regret it
if you let that happen.
Like me.
You have regrets, Takuto?
Yeah. When I was a human,
I got a tumor in my throat just like you.
Takuto! You can't remember, Takuto!
You'll become a ghost!
I don't care.
I don't care what happens to me.
Takuto!
If me remembering will make you
want to sing again, Mitsuki,
I will remember
everything for you.
For me?
I got a tumor in my throat
after Route L disbanded.
Even after I went solo,
I continued singing. But...
Eventually my symptoms worsened,
and I was no longer able to sing.
I was devastated.
If I had known that
this would happen,
I wish I had never known
what it was like to sing.
I wished I could run away to a world
where there was no music.
I went crazy and raced around blindly
trying to run away from everything.
Where is this?
Jeez! What the heck is this?
You are Takuto, right?
Wh-Who the heck are you?
W-What do you think you're doing?!
Stop that—
Stop...
Your memory of the past
has just been sealed off.
Let's go, Death Spirit Takuto...
to a labyrinth of eternal punishment.
I can't believe I died like that!
Why didn't I continue living to the end?!
I don't want you to have
regrets like I do, Mitsuki.
I don't care if I have regrets.
I made up my mind not to sing,
so I will never sing again.
Don't you get
what I'm saying yet?
You...
Takuto, what's the matter?
Takuto!
Don't tell me that his transformation
into a ghost has begun!
Please stop, Takuto! I beg you,
please don't remember anything more!
Meroko!
Don't worry about me, Meroko.
I must remember.
There's more I need
to tell you, Mitsuki.
Takuto...
To give Mitsuki
the will to live, eh?
Mitsuki?!
Takuto!
Don't remember any more!
If you continue like this,
you'll really turn into a ghost!
No! Not until Mitsuki
changes her mind!
Why?! Why are you
going to that extent?
Takuto!
Perhaps it's due to the pain, but I'm
starting to remember more and more.
You must continue to sing
that song, "Eternal Snow."
For Aoi and Hazuki.
For my Dad and Mom?
Yeah.
When I was a member of Route L,
I, the vocalist was still 12 years old.
The keyboard player
was Keichi Wakaoji.
The guitarist was
your father, Aoi Koga.
And Hazuki, your mother
was always with us.
What a beautiful melody.
It sounds like you, Aoi.
I'm so glad you like it.
Huh?
To Hazuki with love.
You wrote this song for me?
Yes.
Takuto!
What is it, Keichi?
It seems like a waste that
it's just for the music box.
We should give it some lyrics.
Sure. What kind of image
does it give you, Hazuki?
Let's see...
Eternal snow...
Snow that falls forever, huh?
That's how the song, "Eternal Snow,"
came to be written.
Since then, that song became
one of Route L's main songs.
That's probably because Aoi and
Hazuki's feelings communicated with us.
My dad and my mom's feelings...
Back then...
I wasn't able to
put it into words,
but some sort of hot feeling
welled up inside of me.
It was a very strange feeling.
You see?
You must continue to
communicate those feelings.
Songs aren't concrete things.
Unless you sing it,
that song won't exist anywhere.
But...still, it's...
For goodness sake!
Stop saying things that would
make Aoi and Hazuki sad!
Huh?
The last time I saw Hazuki
was when the two of them
told me they were getting married.
Really?!
Congratulations!
Thanks!
Look at this.
I thought we could use
the characters meaning "full moon"
and pronounce it "Mitsuki."
Mitsuki?
The name of our daughter.
Daughter?
I'm not sure it's a girl yet, but I want
to give her the name "Mitsuki."
Even after the moon wanes,
it begins to shine and wax again, right?
I want my child to shine
forever just like the moon.
To shine forever
just like the moon.
Those were their hopes for you
as you were born into this world.
Not only Aoi and Hazuki,
but Eichi as well!
And all the people around you today...
We want you to live too!
That's right, Mitsuki!
Please sing once again!
For everyone's sake!
No. For your own sake!
So you should just be
true to yourself, Mitsuki.
Because we'll all
make you shine.
I have given
a great deal of thought
to your request that
I produce Mitsuki's song.
I will agree on
certain conditions.
We'll do our best together forever!
Okay, Mitsuki?
No!
I-I don't want you to die!
Please, just come back!
Mitsuki!
For my own sake...
Be true to myself.
You have to return to how you
were when you were happy.
I have so much desire
to sing right now,
I feel like my chest is
going to burst open!
I want to warm people's
hearts with music!
You're really good at singing,
aren't you, Mitsuki?
Mitsuki, sing!
You know, they say live music,
don't they? L-I-V-E, live.
To those who have encountered music,
to live is to sing.
To sing is to live.
With that, I have told her everything
I needed to tell her.
No!
No! You can't
become a ghost!
What should I do?!
What do I need to do so that you
don't become a ghost, Takuto?
Stop, Meroko.
No! If you're going to become a ghost,
Takuto, I will go with you!
Idiot...
Takuto...
Mitsuki!
Mrs. Koyama!
Takuto!
How long has it been since
I fell in love with you?
My feelings keep
getting stronger.
- Mrs. Koyama! Have you come to?
- I wonder if
- Mitsuki... That song is...
- you can notice them?
- W-Wait a minute. Please let her sing.
- Even though I've
- Those are Mitsuki's true feelings.
- never mentioned it.
- I want to listen to her too.
- They're silent like the snow,
- This is the first time
- but they keep
- I've ever heard her sing.
- building up.
Please forgive me, Hazuki... Aoi...
I will take care
of your daughter.
Hold me tight.
Takuto...
I'm so glad.
- Yeah.
- If loving someone was
going to feel like this,
I wish I never
found out about love.
I love you.
My tears won't stop.
- If this is how it's going to be,
- Everyone is supporting me.
- I wish I had never met you.
- Everyone is making me shine.
So I'll continue to sing.
Just like the moon that waxes
and shines even after it wanes.
I'm sorry. I don't know what
came over me to ask Izumi.
It's fine.
You don't have to say anything.
Takuto, thank you!
Hey, it's no time to be down.
We have the important
task of protecting her!
Yeah!
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Hope to Live."
- Look forward to it!