To counteract a prayer for someone's happiness, someone else has to be cursed.
We magical girls are structured in that kind of way, aren't we?
I'm... really an idiot.
Sayaka!
What is this?
What the hell are you!?
What'd you do to Sayaka!?
Step back.
Hold on.
What the...?
It's fine!
This thing is...?
If you release my hand, time will stop for you as well.
Take care.
What's happening?
Just what is that witch!?
Formerly, it was the person Miki Sayaka.
You have seen and confirmed that, right?
We're running away?
If you find it disagreeable, discard that unnecessary baggage.
We'll kill that witch right now.
Are you up to it?
Don't screw around!
In your current state, you will only get in the way.
We are temporarily withdrawing.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 9
I Wouldn't Forgive That Sort of Thing
Sayaka-chan!?
Sayaka-chan, what's wrong!?
Hey, her Soul Gem...?
W–What's wrong with Sayaka-chan?
Her Soul Gem was annihilated after changing into a Grief Seed and giving birth to a witch.
That's... a lie, right?
It is truth.
That is a Soul Gem's final secret.
When these jewels are stained black with impurity, we become Grief Seeds...
and witches are born in our place.
That is the inescapable fate of those who become magical girls.
It's a lie...
It's a lie, right?
Right?
That's...
Why...?
Sayaka-chan...
She said she wanted to protect people from witches...
She said she wanted to be an ally of justice...
Those thoughts led her to become a magical girl, right?
And yet...
It means that prayer was counterbalanced with a curse, which was equal to the burden she carried.
In direct proportion to the people who that girl saved, from now on she will live while cursing people.
You... What're you intending?
Do you want to show off how knowledgeable you are about this?
Why are you talking with such pride?
This person is Sayaka's—
Sayaka's close friend, isn't she?
This time you're able to comprehend it, aren't you?
The kind of true character held by the thing you aspire to be.
Seeing that you purposely brought that dead body with you, take care in how you treat it.
Deserting it in a stupid location will cause trouble for you much later.
Despite that, you're still human!?
Of course not.
Neither are you.
Is it okay for me to come in?
I have something to say.
You're still alive, huh...
Were the things Homura-chan said true?
Nothing was wrong enough to require correction.
Then... in order to turn everyone into witches, you first make them magical girls?
I would like you not to misunderstand, as it doesn't mean we hold any malice toward humanity.
Everything is for the sake of extending the fate of this universe.
Madoka, do you know the word "entropy"?
To illustrate it simply, it means that the heat energy acquired from an open-air fire is not equal to the work necessary to grow a tree.
Every time energy is converted into a different form, it results in a loss.
The universe's total energy is continuously decreasing in worth.
That's why we searched for energy that was not bound by the laws of thermodynamics.
And what we discovered...
was the magic power of magical girls.
You... what exactly...?
We, my civilization, invented technology which converts the emotions of sentient life forms into energy.
Unfortunately, however, the "we" that I refer to do not happen to have anything similar to emotions.
For that, we examined many heterogeneous species belonging to this universe, and you guys, humanity, were our headline.
When you take into account the population size and reproductive rate of humanity, then the emotional energy created by a single human...
The energy required for that individual to be born and grow to adulthood is superior.
Your souls are a sufficient source of energy to overturn entropy.
Above all else, the most efficient...
are the hopes and despairs of young girls during the period of their phase transition when developing secondary sexual characteristics.
When your souls, which have become Soul Gems, burn out and convert into Grief Seeds...
it causes a huge amount of energy to spring forth at that instant.
Collection of that is a role assigned to us, the Incubators.
We're... disposable goods?
You're telling us to die for the sake of your race?
Do you understand just how many civilizations are crowded together in this universe, or how much energy is wasted in a moment?
Even you guys, humanity, will eventually separate from this star and join us as allies, right?
When that time comes, being delivered a universe that is withering to death would be troublesome, you know?
If you look at the long term, this is a deal that should be profitable for you guys, isn't it?
Don't say idiotic things...
For a senseless reason like that, Mami-san is dead, and Sayaka-chan went through such an experience...
It's too much...
It's too awful!
We insist that contracts are made with your consent as a prerequisite, don't we?
That alone should be sufficiently fair, I expect.
Aren't you just deceiving everyone!?
We can't even comprehend the very act that you call deception.
When times arise where a discrepancy in perception yields a regrettable judgment error,
for some reason, humans direct hatred toward others, you know.
I can't follow the things you're saying.
I can't grasp them at all.
We struggle to comprehend your, humanity's, standard of value.
Right now, there are currently 6.9 billion people, and moreover, you continue to increase at a rate of 10 people every 4 seconds...
Why do you all make such an uproar about the life and death of one mere body?
If you think like that... then in the end, you really are our enemy.
Even so, I came with the intent to justify, didn't I?
I wanted to get you to comprehend just how many wonderful things you guys' sacrifices bring about, but...
Somehow it looks to be impossible.
Isn't that obvious?
Madoka, I hope that someday you will become the greatest magical girl, and then change into the worst witch.
At that time, we will obtain a large amount of energy to a degree that has never previously existed.
If you ever feel like dying for the sake of this universe, call for me anytime.
Because I'll be waiting, okay?
Going this far to preserve the freshness of a dead body... Just what exactly is your intention?
What method do we use to recover this girl's Soul Gem?
As far as my knowledge extends, none exist.
So, that means there are also things you don't know?
Magical girls are existences that overturn logic.
No matter the absurdity of what you guys accomplish, it still isn't worth being surprised.
It can be done, can't it?
There's no precedent, you know.
That's why even I don't know of any methods.
It is unfortunate, but I can't give you advice.
I don't want it.
Who would... borrow a thing like help... from you?
Madoka-san, your complexion isn't excellent this morning.
Are you all right?
Yeah. It's just a little lack of sleep.
In any event, I wonder if Sayaka-san is absent again today.
Should we go visit her later, perhaps?
But would it be okay for me to go?
Right now, it's a little difficult for me to talk with Sayaka-san, but...
Hitomi-chan. Um, you know...
(After yesterday, today you're going to do something like casually go to school?)
Madoka-san?
(I have a bit to say.)
(Could I see your face?)
Hitomi-chan, sorry.
Today, I'm... going to be absent from school too!
Eh?
T–That's... Madoka-san, wait!
Um... you wanted to say...?
Miki Sayaka. Don't you feel like saving her?
We can save her...?
If we couldn't save her, would you just abandon her?
I asked that in an unusual way, didn't I?
I don't know if you think I'm an idiot, but...
As for me, y'know... Whether or not she can really be saved...
Until we ascertain that, I don't want to give up.
She has become a witch, but it's possible that she might still remember her friend's voice or something.
If you called out to her, then maybe she would regain her memories from when she was human.
The only one who could do that...
is probably you.
Will it go well?
I don't know that much.
We don't know, so let's do it.
Maybe, if I were to cut that witch right in half, then instead of finding a Grief Seed inside,
Sayaka's Soul Gem would pop out and fall to the ground, y'know?
There's stuff like that, right?
You know, stories where love and courage are victorious in the end.
Even for me, if I think about it, I aspired to be that kind of magical girl, y'know.
I had completely forgotten, but...
Sayaka reminded me of that.
If you don't want to come with me, I won't pressure you.
A fairly dangerous bridge is gonna have to be crossed, y'know.
By me too, so I can't make any promises like "I'll protect you no matter what happens."
No, I'll help.
I want to help you.
I'm Kaname Madoka.
Man, really now... you're cramping my style, seriously.
Eh?
It's Sakura Kyouko.
I look forward to working with ya.
Y–
Yeah.
Excuse me, I don't feel very well, so the school infirmary...
Who's the health officer for this class?
Kaname-san is absent today.
Hmm. Well then, the class representative should go—
I wonder, wouldn't Homura-chan help too?
She doesn't have that sort of personality.
Aren't you friends?
That's wrong, y'know.
Well, you could say our interests coincidentally match...
We're just allying together for the sake of battling things that we can't defeat alone.
After a few days, a Walpurgis Night will come to this city.
Walpurgis?
A super dreadnought-class big-shot witch.
Neither she nor I could likely defeat it alone.
That's why it seems like a united front or something...
Well, in short, that's the sort of relationship we have, y'know.
This is it.
I wonder if it's really Sayaka-chan.
I wonder if it could be another witch.
The magical power's pattern is the same as yesterday's.
There's no mistaking that it's her.
All right, I'm going to ask you once more.
You're sure you're mentally prepared for this, right?
Somehow, I'm... used to this already.
I've always just followed along from behind.
I haven't been helpful even once, though.
But please, take someone like me along.
You're really a weird one, aren't you?
Hey, Kyouko-chan?
Yeah?
For me, who's only watched other people fight while doing nothing at all myself...
In the end, I wonder if I'm really a coward...
Why would you become a magical girl?
Why, you ask...?
Don't take it lightly.
This job, y'know... it isn't something that just anyone is fit for.
But...
Eating delicious food every day and being surrounded by a happy family...
If a person like that, one who had no inconveniences in their life,
simply became a magical girl on a whim...
I wouldn't forgive that sort of thing.
First thing I'd do is smash them, y'know.
Exposing your life to danger, y'know...
That's something only people who have no options left and can't help it should do.
As for those who stick their neck in when that isn't the case, they're simply playing around.
It's a big joke.
I wonder if that's so...
Even for you, a time might come someday when you have to risk your life in battle, whether you like it or not.
When that time comes, you can think about it.
Yeah...
Kyouko-chan, why—
We were noticed...
It's coming!
All right, stick to the plan.
Y–Yeah!
Sayaka-chan, it's me.
It's Madoka!
Hey, can you hear me?
Do you know my voice?
Don't falter.
Continue calling to her.
Sayaka-chan, stop it...
Please, remember!
You wouldn't do something like this, Sayaka-chan!
Sayaka-chan, you're going to become an ally of justice, right?
Hey, please...!
Go back to the original Sayaka-chan!
Even if you can't understand her, there are limits, Sayaka!
Kyouko-chan!?
I'm all right.
This much is just a breeze...
You continue calling out... to Sayaka...
Stop it! Stop it already!
Sayaka-chan! Recognize us!
Hah, are you returning the favor from some time ago?
Come to think of it, we... started out trying to kill each other, didn't we...
I said you were lukewarm...
At that time, even if I had beaten you up more, you would have just stood up again, huh?
You're angry, right?
Anything and everything is unforgivable, right?
I understand.
Once those feelings are gone, wake up... okay?
Sayaka-chan...
I'm asking you, please...
Sayaka!
Didn't you say you believed!?
With this power, you could bring people happiness!
I beg you, God...
I've had a life such as this...
At least once, let me see a happy dream...
Kyouko!
Yo.
You...
I entrust that girl to you.
I made her go along with my idiocy.
It's a principle of yours not to fight alongside those who'll get in your way, right?
It's fine. That's the correct choice, y'know.
It's enough to simply protect the single thing that you want to protect until the very end.
Somehow, y'know... Even though I should have always been doing that up until now...
Go.
I'll take on the responsibility for this one.
Don't worry, Sayaka.
Being by yourself... is lonely, isn't it?
It's fine.
Let's go together...
Sayaka.
Kyouko...
Akemi        Homura
Did Sakura Kyouko truly have any hope of saving Miki Sayaka?
No way...
That much being impossible was already decided, wasn't it?
If that's so... why didn't you stop that girl?
Of course, if it was a futile sacrifice, then I would have stopped it.
But this time, losing that girl was hugely significant, you know.
With this, no magical girls exist anymore who can oppose Walpurgis Night, except for you alone.
Of course, there's no way you can be victorious alone.
That means for the sake of protecting this city, there are no options except for Madoka to become a magical girl.
I won't let that happen. Absolutely not.
Akemi        Homura
A heart encrusted in rust, a world without sound, what do you see?
錆びついた心、音もない世界、何を見てるの？
Searching for the face that will say "See you again," I just repeat it from the start
またねを言える顔を探すよ  それを繰り返すだけ
If you would notice, over there, it's the lone silhouette of a crying person's back
気付けばそこには  ひとりきりで泣く後ろ姿
It's a tough— and lonely place.
辛いような、寂しいような、場所。
and lonely place.
寂しいような、場所。
place.
場所。
I want to join my hand together with yours
手を繋いでいたいんだ
I'll call your name any number of times
even if the future is uncertain
何度でも名前を呼ぶよ  不確かな未来でも
Just thinking about the things that
I'll never let go pains my heart
離せないもの、思うだけ心が痛いよ
I'm right here, I'm right here
ここにいるよ  ここにいるよ
Your place to return to is right here, isn't it?
帰る場所はここだよ？
And that'll never change.
These are the feelings left behind.
いつだって変わらない  思いを残すの。
No one... will believe the future.
No one... will endure and stop the future.
Episode 10
I Won't Depend on Anyone Anymore
I won't depend on anyone anymore.