WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is the seiyuu for キュゥべぇ(Kyubey):
加藤英美里(Katou Emiri) - affectionately called えみりん(Emirin).
Okay! Well then, let's begin volume 5, umm Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika volume—
Ah, I already said that.
Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika volume 5, episode 9...
(lol)
Mahou Shoujo- Madoka☆Magika! volume 5, episode 9...
Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika! volume 5... episode 9...
Maho-Shoujo Madoka☆Magika! volume 5...episode 9...!
I Wouldn't Forgive That Sort of Thing.
(lol)
commentary shall begin now, with the role of Madoka I'm Yuuki Aoi!
Yes~
Yup! And with the role of Akemi Homura, it's Saitou Chiwa!
This time's guest—is:
Yup! With the role of Kyubey, I'm Katou Emiri!
KYAAAA!!!!
KYAAAAAAAAA!
I LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING WITH YOU!
I finally come!!
*clapclapclap*
Sheesh, everyone was waiting for this!
Waiting for it!
Reaaally?
Right!
Anticipation!!!
Ah, how tough~
I don't get the reason!
わけがわからないよ
(lol)
KYAAA!
SAY MORE!
SO EXCITINGGGGGGG!
SAY MORE!!!
SAY MORE, QB!!!
(lol)
We've completely become huge fans.
That's right!
Yaa, it has finally come. This conversation comes at just the right time.
Ne?
Ne!?
Aww!
QB-senpai.
QB-senpai!
QB-senpai will start by really moving you!
QB will move your heart!
Right, thank you very much, Beh-san.
Ah mou~
He will burden you with lots of darkness!
Right, that is true (lol)
(lol)
Ne~
Well, last time, we finished up episode 8,
where "For those of you who will become witches, you should be called mahou shoujo" is said.
Then finally this kind of world comes... You learn the true nature of things...
Right?
That's right.
Yaa... what to ask? With QB-senpai here the tension has really been raised!
Then, since we're here, how about a conversation about auditions?
That's right, ne.
A conversation about the time at auditions?
Right! Somehow, at the beginning... Somehow, when I did QB's character...
I totally... didn't know that he was this sort of "deceiving" character.
I didn't think he was a character who burdened you with his contract this much!
(lol)
Somehow, up until episode 3 he was relatively...
Really—
Yeah.
Right, normal—
He did things with them, somehow...
That's right, he was really cute.
Like eating fast food and such... It had that sort of feeling, so...
Mm.
Right, right, right.
At the auditions, too... I was told I could do a cute animal chara, with some human-like qualities, then...
"I'll take the cute animal chara, please." is what I said...
"Ah, understood."
So I gave it my all, and when it was decided... "Hurray!"
"I can do a cute chara!"
The mascot, right?
That's right! Then, um...
When it was decided, before initial broadcast, some lines were upped to the homepage, right?
Yes!
So then, I thought "All right, cute mascot chara GETTO DAZE!"
Then when it started... in ep3, when something very "surprising!" happened to Mami-san...
"Huh? Isn't something a little bit strange?"
(lol)
Like "That's in this work!?", you know.
I thought that. Then...
Somehow, gradually, QB got amazing, somehow...
He started talking pretty swiftly, huh?
When he started that swift talking...
(lol)
Ne?
"Huh?" (lol)
(lol)
At that point, I hadn't really understood that he doesn't have emotions...
Relatively close to the start, during episode 1 and 2, he'd say stuff like "It's dangerous, Madoka!"
Ne?
Mm.
He was relatively affectionate, so...
Right.
At that time he was normal, but...
Gradually, as conversations kept moving forward, the fact that QB had no emotions... I came to understand that!
Ne.
Ne?
"So it's like that!" is what I thought, and...
How he treated Homura and such as well, it seemed like he was doing it intentionally.
That was a bit...
ドS (do S) - Sadist.
The ド(do) comes from ドレッドノート戦艦級 (doreddonooto senkankyuu - dreadnought-class battleship).
The "S" comes from sadism/sadist.
It's like he's already ドS (lol)
He's like ドS.
ドS (lol)
(lol)
For his emotions to be that "held in"...
It feels as if though he holds no compassion at all!
Mm, mm, mm, mm.
That was that.
Amazing.
Really, the amount that Emiri-chan talks goes beyond everyone else in conversations... Somehow,
Right (lol)
what is it... It's just that unique style of talking.
Yeah,
He only talks in that unique style!
Right.
Somehow,
He says it all so smoothly, in such a kawaii-cute voice, somehow it gradually begins to just have such a feeling to it...
(lol)
That's right, huh?
QB is very scary, isn't he?
Ne—, seriously.
But you know, really, no one...
Maybe not "no one," but QB doesn't say anything wrong, so...
You really can't criticize either side...
That's so painful!
Right, right.
(lol)
Right, right, right.
QB believes that what he's saying is just an obvious fact, so...
Right.
Right, right.
Somehow, ne... he says "Why are you guys saying such a thing? I don't understand, I can't comprehend it!"
"What's wrong?"
Those lines have become popular, haven't they?
Like "I can't comprehend that!"
(lol)
"I really don't understand, ne."
"I really don't understand!"
Ne—
(lol)
Right, right, right.
Right.
But, QB has become too popular around me.
Ahh.
デコメ(dekome) - Decoration Mail.
This is a term which refers to text messages that have a lot of small animated emoticons, symbols, or other decorations included in them. The sprites used are generally very girly, with themes centered around fashion, make-up, princesses, chibi characters, or cute animals.
Somehow, I always add QB to the dekome that I send.
Amazing!
(lol) Amazing.
"Make a contract with me and let's go shopping together!"
(lol)
Right. Right.
And then, what is it, um, um...
For new members, in my circle, there's something like an entry board, right?
サークル(saakuru) - Circle
In this context, "circle" refers to something like a club at a university. I'd like to point out that on Japanese boards, a lot of people have responded to this comment of Yuuki Aoi's by saying "Ah, that's on ours too!"
We put QB on that, like "Make a contract with me and join this circle."
Ehh?
Amaziiing!
Ahah, amazing!
So he seems to be everywhere, even at university...
Mm!
He's already spread so far (lol)
Somehow ne, that seems really amazing, ne!
Amazing, ne?
Mmm!
I've heard that QB has spread across Akihabara, too...
秋葉原(Akihabara) - Electronic district in Tokyo.
Man, if you don't know Akihabara, you've probably never watched anime before.
Is that so?
Mm!
That's right (lol) QB (lol)
Right!?
(lol)
What's that, what's that?
I haven't seen it myself so I don't exactly know, but on internet news sites and such,
in Akihabara, somehow the store's mannequins...
(ﾟ∀ﾟ；) Heheh~
have become QB, and such.
Amazing, isn't it!
(lol) You know what? I went on a QB-tour there!
Eh!? How did that go!?
Eh!? That!
Why didn't you invite me? I want to go on the tour too!
Want to see!
(lol) Right.
やばい(yabai) - Dangerous (slang) (she uses past tense)
In this context, dangerous means "awesome".
It was dangerous! The real thing was dangerous!
Heee~
When I saw that, I was already like "HAHAHA!"
This "HAHAHA!" is excitement, not laughter.
I don't know what kind of general comment this is, but there's a nude QB with "Soul Gem" between his legs.
What Yuuki Aoi is referring to here is a shop mannequin that became somewhat infamous on JP boards for being pretty funny. We mirrored pictures of it (stolen from Akibablog) here:
http://tri4.net/madomagi/realqb/
Ehhhhh?
What is that!?
Like "Is this okay?"
What is that!? I want to see!
Why between his legs? (lol)
(lol)
There's a paper cloth with "Soul Gem" written on it there.
Amazing, ne.
Ehhhh?
This is going on the volume, you know...
That's right, mou.
Right,
Don't say things such as "in between the legs is Soul Gem."
(lol)
Right.
Yes, well, now... it's completely become this kind of sekaikan.
Ahh.
Really when QB comes, it raises the tension, ne?
It raises, ne.
Somehow,
Yeah.
"WAHH HE'S COME!"
Right, right, right.
Yeah~
I want him to come!
団結(danketsu) - Group Unity
The characters in "danketsu" translate individually to "group" and "bind/fasten/tie."
Yuuki Aoi is saying thanks to QB, that'll never happen.
They'll never danketsu!
Ne~!
Right.
It gives your heart a pretty weird feeling..
Right, right.
Mm!
(lol)
"This guy!" (lol)
Ne? He's covered in mystery, isn't he.
Like "What is he going to say this time?"
Mm, it's scary.
Riiight.
(lol)
Right.
The number one keyword was leaked to people, though.
Yeah.
Really, really.
Everyone knows the true meaning.
That's right, last time we learned that "Incubator" is his real name.
That's right.
This shadow has come again...
Ah~ There he is!
(lol)
See, he's come.
It's come~
He's treated like an apparition now. (lol)
(lol) Really
Come to think of it, around episode one, I thought he opened his mouth.
Yeah?
Right, that's right!
Right, right!
It was true for everyone, but...
Um, when there was no real art and it was just on the "board",
the name "QB" would come up, and he'd talk with his mouth.
So, um, during the course of our after recording, he'd breath and close his mouth, but...
At that time he properly breathed, ne.
That's right.
Mm.
When he said his name was QB [in ep1], his mouth actually opened up, he was talking from his mouth, so...
Mm!
Mm.
Talked from the mouth.
Somehow or another, I just kept at it!
Right, you tried hard to lip-sync.
Right.
I was trying to match lip-syncing up, so it was like... "Ah, this part is a bit too fast," or "Ah, this went a bit too long."
Mmm.
Right.
Understanding that is something I can do!
Even though I did that, on the broadcast "Ah, his mouth doesn't move!?"
That was a shock for everyone, you know!
Everyone was tricked when they saw it on air!
(lol)
Right!
He doesn't open his mouth!
Eh, but, in the end, what is it, umm...
When I saw the broadcast and understood that he doesn't move his mouth,
"But I properly synced it there!" is what I thought. (lol)
Right, right, right.
Well, this kind of shadow really has symbolism to it, doesn't it?
Ne~? Truly...
Ne?
Amazing.
This kind of presentation is truly amazing.
The explanation here is difficult, ne.
Mm, it's hard, ne.
Certainly.
Really, only difficult things are being said...
Even for myself, I was talking but I didn't understand what I was saying, it was too difficult.
And this kind of presentation is just so mysteriously wonderful...
Ne~?
Ahh.
Truly... Um,
mysteriously wonderful...
He blends in perfectly with those plush animals, doesn't he?
Ne?
That's right, isn't it?
He's got that cute appearance...
He's cute, but...
Yes, that's right...
Mmm.
Ne?
He's got that blank white face...
Somehow, for acting out QB, who has no emotions...
Unexpectedly, there's a little bit of acting where he seems to take interest... such as how he treats various people may differ,
that kind of thing is there, right? But he's never shaken up.
Ahh...!
Really, in the end... when it comes to Madoka, he might act a little bit different since he wants her to sign with him...
Mm.
Ahhh.
Since he wants her to become a mahou shoujo...
Amazing.
Somehow, what is it...
Just when it comes to Madoka, he might be trying to present something specific to her, so he acts a bit...
Like giving her a good feeling.
Ah!
Good feeling!
To give everything a good image, right, right.
(lol)
"Madoka☆"
"You really are..." and such.
Mm, mm, mm.
(lol)
In that way, he sort of talks to her with a kind voice...
Right.
Mm, mm, mm.
But then when it comes to Homura, QB acts a bit like he's on alert, so...
That's right, ne.
He sort of keeps his distance.
Yeah. It really is emphasized a little bit for that area.
Like "Akemi Homura...!"
Right (lol)
(lol)
Right, right, right.
Like "You really are...!"
(lol) Right, right.
(lol)
That's how it is...
Yeah. Then when it comes to Sayaka as well, and Kyouko too... personally, it's like...
Well, since they've become mahou shoujo, he has a feeling of keeping integrity...
Since they did it...
In the end, he does treat Madoka a little bit differently... for that part.
Mmm.
For you, Emiri-chan, other than QB, do you have any characters that you like?
Ahh, a character that I like?
Ehh, really it's... Kyouko... is amazing.
Like I thought!!!
That's right!!!
She's nice~ I think!
Yeah!
I get it, Kyouko is nice~
Somehow...
What is it, at the beginning she was very tsuntsun...
Mm.
Amazing, somehow her, what is it... advice... umm, sort of...
She has a bit of a different thinking style from everyone else.
It's different, isn't it?
Really, it's got a point of "you are yourself."
Really, no matter what she says, it has a bit of a strange reason to it...
Somehow, seeing that sort of kindness from time to time makes me think, "Amazing, Kyouko is nice~"
Right, right, right.
I think "This girl is nice!"
Ne~?
That's right, ne.
Yeah.
Ah!
I just realized it now, but us three might be the only ones who have seen everything...?
We're in all of it.
Ah! Right.
Ah, right!
The other characters aren't really there.
Right!
Isn't that so?
That's right, all of it!
We're the people in all of it.
Mm. That's right.
Is that right...
That's right, we know all the way until the end, so...
Yeah, know it!
Yeah.
The end, ne!
Ne~!
Ne!
Really~!
It's "fuuuu~n" (exhausting)
Right.
Well, it really piques your interest, you know~
Really, every time, we talked so much about "What will happen next", didn't we?
Ne~?
Ne?
I thought that~
For the scenes like right here, where I interact with QB, I talked a lot with Tsuruoka-san,
I was told not to make it seem like QB is an enemy, but instead like it was an internal conflict, so I thought "Ah I see!"
But QB's indifference to everything was angering me myself! (lol)
That's right, isn't it?
That's right, when I was doing work, my emotions were beginning to come out! (lol)
You have to be clear-headed, huh?
Right, um...
It's Yuuki Aoi who gets pretty irritated regarding QB (lol)
I become enraged (lol)
(lol)
Madoka doesn't know, but she's getting enraged.
Right.
Right, right, right.
Since Madoka might've been directing resentment toward someone without knowing it,
somehow, in relation to that, she still really didn't want to fight...
Amazing, it was causing a conflict within me myself. (lol)
(lol)
Like the scenes where she runs away from things.
Right, right, right.
That's right, isn't it~?
Right.
Somehow, the pain doesn't come from an attack, but from [her]self, I'd say.
Right, right.
She begins to carry more and more doesn't she? Madoka.
That's right, isn't it.
I think so. Today QB really talks a lot. (lol)
Right.
This is an episode where he talks a lot, isn't it?
Ne!?
It was amazing, when I was catching my breath and saw the script, there was so much written!
Ah, that's right.
Afterward you were completely exhausted, huh?
Yeah.
"Ahhh~"
"Ah finally, I said it!"
Right, right, right, right.
That sort of thing was exhausting too. (lol)
(lol)
"What does this mean?"
"I don't know." "I don't know, ne." "I don't know." Everyone said that!
Right, right, right.
But anyway, if there's something I don't get, isn't it "Entropy"?
(lol)
"Ahh, entropy. Yes, yes, yes."
It's a bit, you know...
(lol)
Really, for recording...
Since the details of conversation gradually got darker, the recording workplace got brighter, didn't it?
Yeah.
Brighter (lol)
That's right, ne.
Right.
You're in the company of everyone, so everyone is being bright and bright.
(lol)
Ne?
Right.
Your feelings actually switch over...
Really.
Mm, mm, mm.
Ne?
Right, right. For that, this kind of presentation has a "link" with you,
Madoka
since if everyone is feeling down, like Ao-chan earlier, your own emotions begin to feel that way...
That's right, isn't it...
Mm, mm.
Really, completely... "Okay! Recording over," at those times, everyone completely changes their moods.
Like that, I think that everyone in the workplace was very conscious of things...
That's right, ne.
Ne~
For that part, I thought that there was a lot of unity.
That's right, ne.
Mmm, it made it easier.
Mm.
Certainly.
That's right.
Also, I really respected everyone, so... there was this major reliance on other people, which made things easier.
I really held that within me too, and somehow,
since I was able to do this with a relieving staff, every part of the cast was relieving...
Like, this is the first time doing such a truly "blank thing."
original work
But somehow, I think I got along very well with everyone. It gave a huge sense of relief in my surroundings.
That's right, isn't it?
Right.
I think that's why I can say "QB frustrates me." (lol)
Right, right, right.
If you had to be careful, you couldn't say that, ne!
If you had to be careful, you couldn't say! that, ne
Saying that it's "FRUSTRATING!" (lol)
"But I love QB."
Actually (lol)
Oh~
Somehow for both people that I knew and didn't know, no matter whose face I saw, I had intense respect for all of them...
Ne~?
Right,
It's amazing, I love every character.
Mm!
Mmm.
There aren't any characters I hate or anything.
That's right. Right, right.
Right.
There aren't any!
Aren't any.
Mm!
That is an amazing part of this piece of work, isn't it?
Ne?
Even though it has such extensive development!
That's right!
Even though it agonizes you this much...
Ne!?
Somehow, it's true for the conversation now too...
I think that a lot while doing interviews and such as well.
Ahh.
Ne?
Everyone is really loved, aren't they.
Also, everyone, somehow... they go through so much, there's just no helping it.
Right, right, right, right.
Right, right.
Ne? Really.
Right, you properly hold an amazing opinion on every character.
Mm, mm.
Ahhh.
I really don't think any people, or any characters, were worthless at all, now.
Amazing.
Mmm.
Ahh...
Really.
It's really amazing, ne.
Ne!?
Ne?
Everyone does enough...
But in doing enough, everyone is aiming to do enough for someone more than themselves... Somehow,
that sort of balance is extremely rare...
Ahh...
Ne?
I feel like doing this work did a ton for me.
Yeah, really.
I get that feeling.
Ne?
1クール(1 kuuru) - 1 season (11-13eps) of a television program (from French: cours)
Really, even though Madoka is only 1cours...
Mm!
Mm.
Being able to craft such characters with only that... it's amazing...
It's truly amazing, I think.
Ne~?
Ne?
Amazing.
Mmm...
Since we've seen all of it, we're really living in luxury right now, aren't we?
Ne?
Really!
Right, seeing it all is truly amazing—UMAIBOU
Right? (lol) Umaibou (lol)
It's Umaibou.
Umaibou.
Right there is the beginning of Kyouko-chan and I getting along a little bit.
That's right, isn't it?
Right.
Niya niya.
ニヤニヤ(niya niya) - smiling
The person inside is niya niya. (lol)
中の人
(lol)
I get to talk with Kyouko-tan~♥
Ne? Since she her debut, quite a bit of time has passed, ne.
Quite a bit has, but her initial thoughts of me were as a bothersome, weak person. (lol)
But, finally...
Getting along—This, the problem written on the white board is hard, isn't it?
I totally don't get any of it.
Don't understand it, ne.
"Pokan"
ぽかん(Pokan) - slowly and lazily; gaping; absentmindedly; flabbergasted
(lol)
Yeah.
Oh—
Ah, it's come.
Kyo—Dango!
Kyouko always brings a different snack.
The whole time, she does!
Without fail.
Then she always eats it!
Right!
Then, when she puts the omochi in her mouth, and she goes hamu, that's cute.
Ohhh.
(lol)
And then, Ai-san is amazingly gifted at talking while eating!
Right, right, right.
Ne~?
I think it's amazing.
Like "Is that stuff even going to your throat?"
Right, right, right.
(lol)
She must be holding all of that in her mouth.
Right, right, right, right.
That's right...
ahhh...
uuu...
Kyouko-tan~♥
Ne~
Then, I think this everytime, but really, the landscapes and backgrounds, really...
Somehow, all of it... whoever had their hand in sewing this sekaikan is amazing.
Ne? Truly.
Like I can see its "stand out from the rest style," but it has really artistic light.
Amazing.
Amazing, those types of backgrounds have such a realistic feeling.
Ne?
Yeah.
Right, right.
Beautiful.
And that's why, when they enter the witch's worlds, it's like a view of a parallel universe.
Yeah.
That's right, ne.
Then, the characters have their own items which seem to define their character. It's amazing.
Ne?
I think it's truly amazing.
It really has a nice balance, doesn't it?
Ne?
Mmm.
Somehow,
mysteriously wonderful, isn't it?
Truly!
Ne? It's truly amazing.
Mm.
Every time... right before they enter the battle,
Wanna watch!
Wanna watch, wanna watch (lol)
"What kind of area will it be this time?" is really fun to think about!
Ne?
"I wonder what kind of world will come!?" is something I think.
Inu Curry-san's room, you know.
Sayaka—
Ah! This is... amazing,
It's sort of sad. It makes me think of Sayaka a little bit...
That thing just now is sad.
（；´Д⊂） Extremely sad...
Neー?
That's right, isn't it~
Mmm.
Right, but this, this um... you know...
Right before they come here, when Kyouko-chan is talking to QB, you know?
Relating that to the scene at the end, where he's talking with Homura about spoilers...
ヽ（＃｀Д´）ﾉ QB!!!!!
Ne? That's seriously...
That's right, isn't it?
For this work, really, every time you watch it then start from the beginning... you end up seeing things differently.
Mm!
Ne?
Truly.
Especially in relation to QB, who has a lot of hidden meaning—
That's right, you understand a lot.
The posters included here, it seems that when you decode them, they say "Look at me."
Ehhh?
(lol)
Is that right?
I learned what was written there.
Ehhh?
Knowing what it is, is another amazing part.
Inu Curry-san made a writing system to write words in, then it seems someone translated it into Japanese.
In the 2ch threads and nico video related to this commentary track, a lot of Japanese are correcting this part and giving credit to the English wiki for decoding everything (with lots of praise). Since we know you're watching, people who decoded the runes, just thought we'd give you a little shout-out too.
Amazing!
Right.
Right, right.
That was translated to Japanese, and the names of everything were revealed.
Right, right, right, right.
Amaziiing.
It's amazing, everyone has such passion.
Ne?
Ne!
The voice of the customers really flew far...
Right, right.
There was a staggering amount of people interested within the industry, too...
A staggering amount.
Each and every time, I was asked what would happen next.
That's right, when I went to different workplaces, I was told "Ahh, Madoka is amazing, I watch it, it's really amazing, huh?"
Mm, mm, mm.
Then every time, I'd be asked "Can you talk about it? Can you talk about it? Can you talk about it?"
Right, right, right!
"Eh? For me too, it really hurts, you know..."
"But, someone might regret something."
Right!
"Ah, she really said it! Stop, stop, stop!"
"Stop, stop, stop!"
Ne?
And now this time...
Waaa...
Ne...
Ne, up until now Sayaka has been watching, hasn't she...
Mm!
Ahh...
Really...
It has come.
It's come~
Ahhh~
Wah, it's completely... 'cause you know...
Somehow, this... this sort of violin song too, you know...
Ne?
It has a feeling "Ah, is that right..."
Mmm...
mmm...
Ahhh, it's sad, isn't it...
Sayakaaa...
Truly...
Girls who are really normal...
They become mahou shoujo... then witches... that's how it starts, right?
That's how to describe it.
Right.
So that's why, when you know that sequence of events, you think... "what sadness!"
Ne~?
Mm.
That's because all the witches up until now also went through that kind of sequence.
Right!
Mm...
"BECOME A MAHOU SHOUJO!" Is what they were all told.
Right!
But it's really something different!
They all become mahou shoujo!
Ne?
That's why it's true for all of the witches that they've fought up until now...
Since they all had some great hopes...
Yeah.
Ne?
That's another sad thing!
Ne? Really...
Mmm...
The one who ate Mami-san, Charlotte-chan too, it's, umm... what is it,
There was conversation about how her settei may be that of a sick girl, and such...
There's also the settei of her liking cheese,
Ah, that's right!
and such...
When I heard, I thought "I SEE!"
That's right, such sad things were written about everyone, then they became witches...
Mm!
Ne?
Right,
Thinking about it, all the witches up until now had love, which is amazing...
Ne~?
Ne? Truly...
That's right, isn't it?
Ne~ I see...
Ah, Kyouko... it's no good!!
It hurts...
Kyoukooo!
(lol)
Mou, fighting to this music is... truly sad...
Mmm.
Mmm...
That's right, ne.
mm...
Really, somehow...
It hurts...
When you watch this, it makes you think girls are strong but quite weak, doesn't it?
Ne?
Ne~?
They're giving it their all when they're suffering!
Right, right, right, right, right.
Up until then they've been through a lot, too.
That's why, looking at it from a girl's viewpoint, it really...
It really reaches my ears, you know...
Mmm.
Mm.
Ne?
You can really see a lot of different things, can't you?
Ahh...
Like the feeling of strength from a girl!
Right!
Sayaka really has a feeling of being representative of girls.
That's right, isn't it?
Ne?
That's why everyone shouts "Stop!"
Ahh.
Right, right.
Stop it...
"No, stop it Sayaka...!"
Right, right, right.
Ne...?
Right, she's too much of a good girl...
Ahh...
Ahh.
Ahhh...
（´；ω；｀） Ahh, 'cause Kyouko-chan really believed in justice, too...
Ne?
I'm really crying. *sniff*
(lol)
（´；ω；｀） I'm really crying... It hurts...
Ah but, really, this scene, you know...
（´；ω；｀） *sniff*
Mm.
When I watched it at home, I cried...
（´；ω；｀） I... cried...
Right.
The whole time, I've had my hand over my mouth...
Ahhh...
Even though I know what happens!
That's right, right, right...
Even though I know!
Right, right...
Even though I know, really...
Ahh, that silhouette just now, too...
Ne?
Right...
Help has come...!
Ahhh...
Kyouko-chan!!!
Help Kyouko-chan, too...!!!
（ ；∀；） Not just Madoka...
Madoka! Madoka is there! (???)
(lol)
That's right, ne.
But really, Kyouko is too much of a good girl...
Agh.
Ahhh...
Ahhhh!
That's right, Homura knows so much, but can't say it...
Ahhh.
Ne?
can't say...
Her internal affairs right now are also... ne.
Mmm.
Mm.
It hurts.
Right, right, right...
Ne?
*whimper*
Ahhh...
Ahhhhhhhh.......
Ah, mou. Amazing.
(lol)
;_;
Nooo~
I'm crying!
I'm really cr—
Stop!
Stop!!!
Ah, it's no good..........
Agh...
Fellowship among girls is amazing, isn't it?
Ne? Really!
No...
The one who's alone and sad is you, isn't it!?
｡・ﾟ・（ﾉД`）・ﾟ・｡ Ahh...
Ah, I'm really crying, what should I do...
It hurts, I'm really crying （´；ω；｀）
(lol)
Ahh...
Especially watching up until now...
Ne?
That's right...
｡・ﾟ・（ﾉД`）・ﾟ・｡
(lol)
｡・ﾟ・（ﾉД`）・ﾟ・｡ Stop already...
حَوّامتي مُمْتِلئة بِأَنْقَلَيْسو
Right...
حشي مينتيونيد أنك إ ذينك
I'm sorry I really can't understand Emirin when she's crying.
That's right...
Okay, actually I can't understand anyone.
For what it's worth, neither can people on nico.
I can't endure it anymore!
سايتو هو رائعتين تماما
Can you sing this work's praises?
Yes ;_;
Yes, um, somehow, it really fills my chest with a lot, somehow...
(lol)
I did QB, but somehow, um, when acting out QB...
I really wanted to be connected with QB's feelings,
so there weren't many times when I'd let my heart weaken, but really when rewatching afterward...
Somehow, it's amazing... for all that I've held up before, now it's all coming out...
I think it's a really amazing piece of work.
That's right, this is a work thoroughly made by everyone, isn't it?
Ne?
Yes.
Right.
Also this time, Ao-chan... it seems there's a special ending attached.
Ohh!
Ah!
It seems so! This time.
Somehow... ne!?
Yeah!
A special ending that didn't appear in the original, so please enjoy!
Yeah.
A ending thatdn't ffff appeYes!ar ifsn the original, so please enjoy!