High school finally starts tomorrow.
I wonder if I'll be able to make new friends.
All Contacts
Search
So
Sonoda Yuu
Maybe I should talk to Yuu-chan about it.
No, I can't just keep relying on her!
I'm going to be a high school student!
Bedtime!
Sonoda Yuu
Cell
Yuu-chan?
Hello?
Hello, Haruka? Did you remember to pack your pencils?
Yuu-chan? Yeah, I did.
Good.
She hung up.
It's Yuu-chan again.
Hello?
Haruka, after you go in the front gate tomorrow,
go straight to the boards to check what class you're in.
R-Right, I know that already.
Do you really?
I really do!
And what about you? Don't go to school with food on your face!
I won't. I'm not you, you know.
I wouldn't do something like that!
I'm hanging up now.
Don't come to school with food on your face.
I told you, you're the one who does th—
Haruka
She hung up on me.
What's with her?! Now I'm wide awake!
Stupid Yuu-chan!
She called because she was worried about me.
Yuu-chan's the nicest friend ever.
I wonder if she'll come with her usual hairstyle tomorrow.
Yuu-chan's really short, so I bet her uniform'll look baggy on her.
I hope we're in the same class.
And it'd be really nice if I got to sit behind her like I did in middle school.
The sakura petals will flutter by the dusk-stained classroom.
And then...
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
Entrance
Ceremony
Sorry, Yuu-chan!
Haruka, you're late.
That's because you called me so late at night!
Don't blame others. You need to carefully plan out your time before doing anything.
That's exactly right.
I'll learn from your example!
"Sakura-colored Beginnings"
My name is Takayama Haruka.
My family name begins with "Ta".
My best friend, Sonoda Yuu-chan's name starts with "So".
If we end up in the same class, then I'll be right behind her!
Class A
Sonoda Yuu
Takayama Haruka
Tsutsui Akari
Iizuka Yuzu
Ikeno Kaede
Oosaki Akiko
Look, Haruka!
We're in the same class!
Perfect!
So!
So
Ta!
Ta
If I sat behind her again, then I could help her out with classwork and stuff.
Haruka, I don't get this part.
Which part?
I don't get it!
Oh, for that formula...
Thanks!
Not at all.
Why is this happening?!
I have no idea what to talk about without Yuu-chan here.
What if the person next to me's an insensitive jerk?
Hey, I'm Iizuka Yuzu.
Looks like we're neighbors.
I'm Ikeno Kaede.
Ah, nice to meet you.
That's her!
Oh god, I made a weird sound! I'm so embarrassed!
No, she's not an insensitive jerk at all.
In fact, she's super sensitive!
No, I mustn't think that!
We'll be holding the entrance ceremony now,
Entrance
Ceremony
so I'd like everyone to follow me to the gymnasium.
Haruka!
Yuu-chan!
Let's go to the gym!
We're off!
Yeah!
Here we go!
Shall we do that too?
Link arms, I mean.
Nope.
You don't like linking arms?
It's just not something you do.
We're high schoolers now.
Yuzu-chan, you're too worried about you and Kaede-chan both being girls!
And you two are the exact opposite.
Yuu-chan, was it?
Yep. I'm Sonoda Yuu, Haruka's friend.
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
Yuzu, looks like we're in the same class.
Kotone.
This is Noda Kotone.
She, Kaede and I all went to the same middle school.
Nice to meet'chu all!
Nice to meet'chu!
You all play along too easily!
By the way...
The class roster?
What about it?
Check out this name.
Minami Shizuku
Minami Shizuku?
Doesn't it stand out?
With a name that sounds like it's straight out of a shoujo manga,
you know she's gotta be a beauty!
I wonder what kind of girl she is.
Peek.
She just raised their expectations.
Let's see...
Kitani Yuuka
Iizuka Yuzu
Ikeno Kaede
Oosaki Akiko
Kawatou Ai
Sonoda Yuu
Takayama Haruka
Tsutsui Akari
Niimura Akane
Noda Kotone
Minami Shizuku
Oh, isn't that her?
Are you Minami Shizuku-san?
Ah, yes.
So cute!
She lives up to her name.
Let's be friends.
Yeah, sure.
I'm glad there are so many interesting people in our class.
Yeah!
In three years' time, our school will shut down and merge with East High.
Therefore, you will be West High's last incoming class.
We're really high schoolers now.
I bet these three years will be over before we know it.
She fell asleep?
I want to be by your side for years to come.
Yuu-chan.
I still remember it clearly.
The day I first met Yuu-chan.
Until I met you, I didn't have a single friend.
Now, it's my turn to return the favor.
Club activities, the culture festival, and sports day—
our school trip too—
Let's enjoy them to their fullest.
They're sleeping in plain sight.
Yuu-chan, let's go home...
Sonoda-san!
Gotcha!
Geez.
That's my treasured spot!
Haruka, what's up?
M-My tr...
Tr—?
Tr...
Treasured spot!
J-Just forget it!
Trouble?
Trip?
Traipse?
Trapeze?
I ran away without even thinking.
Is this an unused classroom?
I wonder if Yuu-chan and I will change...
just like this classroom has.
It used to be just like us.
Haruka.
Yuu-chan.
Haruka!
I'm sorry I pretended not to know!
Know what?
That you're clingy and get jealous really easily!
Jealous
S-Still, you don't have to ignore everyone else and not make friends just because of me.
I just thought I was special to you.
Guess it was just me.
In that case...
Let's do something that we'd never ever do with anyone else.
That'll prove you're special to me.
Is it okay?
Sure is.
I want to try flower fortune telling!
She loves me, she loves me not, she loves me...
Go ahead.
Go. A. Head.
Geez, I'm trying to be serious over here.
Then, I don't know...
How about we make a memory that we'll never forget?
Then...
A-A kiss?
K-Kiss?! What are you saying?
School is a place of learning!
It's not a place for kissing!
My!
Did I just hear the word "learning" from someone who sleeps through her classes?
Not only is she bad at learning, but she can't even kiss.
My, my...
F-Fine then! Let's do it! Let's kiss!
Really?!
Rise!
Yes!
Yuu-chan just let out her voice.
She's so cute.
I'm starting to moan.
What should I do if Haruka hears?
Keep going, Yuu-chan. I want to hear you.
I need to hold it back!
One more time...
Can't breathe...
"Sakura-colored Beginnings"
The end
Pokitz came out with another new flavor.
No matter what they make, salad flavor will always be my number one.
It's that unused classroom.
I think it's locked.
The teachers did say not to go in.
Look's like that door's open!
Nice.
Yuu
Haruka
Your back is wide open!
Say something already.
She tried to say something funny,
but she's embarrassed because I didn't react at all. Yuu-chan's so cute!
"Yakisoba, Verandas, and Girls"
I wonder if they'll empty out this room.
Like the desks?
I hope they leave everything as it is.
Then it'll stay the way it is in our memories.
Te-he?
What's with that face that says you didn't understand anything so you decided to laugh it off?
Yuu-chan, did you already forget what we did here?
Please give me my math notebook back soon.
Why would I have it?
Come on, I lent you it this morning.
Yuu-chan's memory is so bad I can imagine it happening.
Let's do something that we'd never ever do with anyone else.
Did that kiss we shared really mean that little to Yuu-chan?
Then I'll just do it again!
Come on Haruka, let's hurry back.
Don't tell me you forgot that we're on a mission to retrieve yakisoba for Yuzu-chan.
How was your last lesson?
This is bad, Haruka! Teachers are coming!
Not bad.
We've gotta hide!
Then how about...
The locker might be nice.
What if they find us?
Don't you worry.
No, wait, the lectern would be good too.
S-Sorry.
Let's escape to the veranda!
Yuu-chan!
Yuzu, where's your lunch?
Haruka and Yuu were heading to the convenience store, so I asked them to get me something.
You don't see that every day. Those two usually bring their own lunches.
I just got this sudden craving for yakisoba.
They're bringing some for you too.
So I'm having yakisoba too, huh.
But while what you're imagining is probably this,
THIS
I can see them buying this one.
this
Can't you put some faith in your friends?
I have faith in them!
What I don't have faith in is your choice of words.
All you said was "yakisoba", right?
Just think for a second! There's no way a girl would ask for this.
There's a certain elegance to yakisoba bread!
Elegance...
freeze
Can't you even understand that?
Huh?
Shizuku-chan, not going to eat?
I don't have an appetite.
grooooowl
I've got boiling water.
Why would I want that?
Yuu-chan, are you oka—
Her face is so close! Now's the perfect chance to kiss her!
Who went and left this door open?
I wonder if someone's inside.
They came in! Good thing we decided to hide.
We even told them not to go in here.
Now make sure to keep absolutely quiet.
What are you doing out of the blue?!
This is not the time for that!
But... but Yuu-chan...
You forgot about our kiss...
And I thought you might remember if I kissed you again.
I'm sorry! I didn't realize how much you must've hated it!
That's not true, and you're too loud, Haruka.
Don't hate me!
You're the only one I have!
Haruka, listen to what I'm saying!
Yuu-chan, marry me!
Why do you sound so serious about that?
No, no, don't hate me, Yuu-chan!
No!
Haruka! Listen to me, Haruka!
Finally shut her up.
If you don't give me another one, I'll throw a fit again.
Why should I?
Don't want to?
Think about what would happen if the teachers found us.
Don't worry.
It'll be just one second.
Oh no! It feels so good, I can't stop.
Yuu-chan, forgive me.
warm
fuzzy
You said it'd be only a second!
Sorry, sorry!
Those two sure are late.
I'm getting pretty hungry over here.
I'm heading over to the school store; want anything?
Nah, I'll wait for them.
How about you, Shizuku-chan? Wanna go together?
I'm fine.
Maybe I should bring you that hot water?
I'll go to the store.
I wonder if the teachers are gone.
What did they even come here for?
Let's go back already.
clack
They came to lock the door!
We're trapped!
This is all because you started kissing me!
You were the one who wanted to come in here!
So it's my fault.
Wait, no!
Oh right, Yuzu-chan! This all happened because Yuzu-chan wanted to eat yakisoba!
It's entirely Yuzu-chan's responsibility.
What should we do now?
Stupid Yuzu-chan!
Yuzu-chan, I'm sorry.
Just hang on. We should be able to get out through the veranda.
The veranda?
You're so smart, Haruka!
impasse
What.
hyaa!
No choice but to jump.
I'll go first!
What do you mean first? Don't leave me behind.
Take me with you!
Yuu-chan, what're you doing?!
Lewd! You're so lewd!
I bet you did that on purpose!
Boob grabbing doesn't happen by accident!
I'm not lewd!
I'm so sorry! I was even the one who kissed you!
I'm the lewdest one here! Forgive me!
Need food
Come on, there's no time to waste.
Go for it, Haruka.
Hey, Haruka.
Yeah?
You're a C-cup, aren't you?
How nice.
Wow, you could tell.
I'm actually a D, though.
Haruka, look out!
I'll be the one...
...to protect you!
Are you alright?
W-Wake up!
Yuu-chan isn't breathing.
What now?
You're supposed to do CPR at times like this, I think.
But considering what we just did...
She'll probably get mad at me again!
No, this is an emergency.
You leave me no cho—
Ouchies... I hit my head.
What's going on?
Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan!
This is our classroom's veranda!
Did something happen?
W-W-Well...
I have to keep everything a secret!
Did you know Haruka's a C-cup?
Wait, what?
So did you bring my yakisoba?
Cup! Cup! Cup! Cup!
Knock the cup call off already.
You bet I did!
It was the last one they had left.
Here.
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
only
I think you're missing a dimension there.
"Yakisoba, Verandas, and Girls"
The end
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai deaeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!
Next Episode
I'm Minami Shizuku.
And I'm Noda Kotone!
Hey, why did you raise their expectations of me?
Shizuku-chan's such a cutie.
So why?
Expelled from school...
Shizuku-chan's such a cutie.
Shizuku-chan's such a cutie!
Next time, Trick 2:
"The Other Sakura-color"
"After School with Harry-chan"
"The Other Sakura-color",
and "After School with Harry-chan".
Look forward to it.