When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Hayate was about to welcome
a rare, peaceful morning.
However, he had no way
of knowing that this...
would turn out to be a life-altering day!
Nagi, why don't we go to the primary family
residence for once, where your grandfather resides?
That is... I would like
introduce Hayate as well.
You don't have to express
such undisguised loathing...
Who is this grandfather?
Grandfather Mikado, the head
of the Sanzenin family.
Head of the family?
In other words,
the person currently in possession
of the Sanzenin family estate.
I feel like I could end up getting
fired if I make the wrong impression...
No, he could easily wipe you
off the face of this planet.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
The human body holds untold powers.
The more you train, the more...
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
The Value of My Life: Priceless
So we hired a new butler.
I don't think there's any need to pay our
respects to that old geezer at this point.
Don't say such things.
Your grandfather is the only
immediate family you have.
Man, it's been a long time
since I've seen Grandpa Mikado.
Wait... Never mind all that.
Why are you here?
Oh, please! I'm related to the
Sanzenin family, too, remember?
But what kind of man is your grandfather?
If this were Dragon Quest, he'd be Zoma.
In the traditional storytelling
world, he'd be Danshi.
W-Will I do okay?
Meeting such a terrifying sounding person...
I doubt you'll be okay.
If ya offend him,
that man could easily crush
an indebted butler's life.
After all, he's da man who destroyed Compile,
just 'cause Puyo Pop was hard.
What?!
Incidentally, Nomura Toys'
downfall was also 'cause of him.
Are you serious?!
She's kidding.
Well, in any case, he's
kind of a fiendish guy,
so try not to be taken in if
he says anything odd to you.
I-I see...
What's that?
I'll have you know, it's not the castle...
of the poisonous-apple-eating
princess of the mouse kingdom.
Master Mikado Sanzenin.
This is her grandfather's primary residence.
Wait... So, what country are we in?
What line of work is your grandfather in?
Hmm... Oil baron, I guess?
That is not a line of work...
Hayate was belatedly
coming to the realization
that Nagi was not just your
run-of-the-mill rich girl...
Welcome home, Miss Nagi.
Right. I'm back.
But that she was an INCREDIBLY rich girl.
But talk about a stuffy bunch.
And Miss Sakuya and Maria, it
is good of you to come as well.
Not at all.
Come, this way, please.
By the way, I apologize for disturbing
you upon your return, but...
What shall we do with this
suspicious individual?
Help! Help!
He had snuck aboard the chopper.
He looks incredibly suspicious!
Help! Help!
I can appreciate your sentiment, but
he's not a suspicious individual.
He's Himegami's successor
and he serves as my butler.
This shabby-looking man, who
seems to have no luck with money?
Nobody asked your opinion.
But... um... that is...
Hayate put up with the comments.
Because he most certainly did
not have any luck with money
and there was no question
that he was shabby-looking.
You didn't have to emphasize it like that.
But man, that was hilarious!
Now, Saku, don't laugh at him so much.
It's fine.
I knew from the start that
I didn't fit in here anyway.
Well, don't let it bother you.
They just called it like they saw it.
There was no malice behind it.
That is right. You will only waste
your time letting it get to you.
It's true that I'm 150 million yen in debt,
but do I really look like I
have such poor luck with money?
In this world, there are more important
things than money, like compassion.
Each individual must be considerate
of the planet's future.
They won't look me in the eye...
Oh, that reminds me.
Nagi, being dressed like that for your
meeting with your grandfather is...
You're right.
Okay, I'm going to change, so go
get some fresh air or something.
Right...
I got kicked out.
Still, this is a belated realization,
but to let a man like me,
so deeply in debt, run loose
in this place packed full of
treasures seems far too imprudent.
Is this something of value?
It makes a good sound...
This piece alone just might be able
to pay off my 150 million yen debt!
At best, that vase will fetch
5 million on Yahoo Auctions,
so you won't be able to pay off your debt.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! It was
just an impulsive thought!
You needn't worry. I can
tell, just by looking at you,
that you're not the kind of person
who would do such a thing.
Hey, now. Don't look at me like,
"What's this senile old man saying?"
P-Pardon me.
Um, who might you be?
I'm a member of this household.
I'm taking care of the yard right now.
Oh, you're a gardener.
I swear... You don't have
faith in my insight, do you?
I'll have you know!
Whoops. Sorry about that.
All right, I'll show you just
how formidable my insight is,
so come along with me!
This old man's smile sparkles
like that of a boy...
Behold!
Say, Maria, this outfit is a bit big.
Oh, I knew it!
That's just peeping!
To train one's insight,
one must work daily...
And after working daily, what kind
of criminal do you intend to become?!
I just don't get it, though.
What is someone like you doing
with a debt of 150 million?
It was originally my parents' gambling debt.
My parents are incredible good-for-nothings
and they gifted me to some "very
generous people" as collateral.
And then, Miss Nagi took on that debt for me.
So now, I am in the process
of returning it over 40 years.
I see.
I am really grateful to Miss Nagi.
So grandpa, you mustn't peep at her, either.
Well, I'm going to go now.
In other words,
your life is utterly meaningless.
What?
You're awfully insipid for a man
that Nagi's placed her faith in.
Grandpa, who are you?
My insight is the real thing!
The bursting of the bubble,
the change in government,
and even Toshi losing his hair!
I anticipated it all with these eyes of mine!
Even the unprecedented little sister boom!
I foresaw its coming since before the war!
And these eyes are telling me now...
Your life is even more meaningless
than the lives of your scummy parents!
I, Mikado Sanzenin, assure you that it is.
My life is...
...meaningless?
Yes, it's meaningless.
A life spent merely for the
sake of repaying a debt...
...is utterly meaningless.
However, if you still wish to make
your life something of value...
I-Is this...
...a levitation stone?
No! That is your guide!
If you believe that your
life may yet have meaning,
do not lose it, do not
let it be taken from you.
Keep it with you until the day comes.
And if you are able to obtain the thing
at the end of the road that it leads you to,
never mind 150 million. A
billion! Even 10 billion!
All of that will surely be within your reach.
With the meaning of his life
denied in its entirety,
will Hayate be able to
begin walking down the road
shown to him by the pendant?
To be continued in the second half.
Wait...
Hey, Maria, are we okay with
not having a punch line?!
Oh, please.
We have not had much of a punch
line in the past, either.
Not good! If there isn't at
least one punch line a minute,
a Kansai person's blood starts to tingle!
Don't run! It won't make for a punch line!
That punch line is already an empty shell!
I say this to you, it is garbage!
Shaddup! Punch it already!
All right, I guess it didn't happen.
Lambada.
The baby boomer generation.
O Granddaughter, do you want to
inherit the Sanzenin family fortune?
Huh?
I don't particularly want it,
but if it means that you'll
be dying soon, I'd welcome it.
Maria! O Maria! My granddaughter
is being mean to me!
Oh, my, now that is a problem.
It's not like I'm being mean.
Grandpa, never mind the fortune,
can I get some pocket change?
Besides, even without all that,
as long as I have the World Business
Satellite show and the stock market,
I will never have money problems.
Damn it! Uselessly gaining more
and more knowledge every year...
You're the one who had me educated
so that would happen, remember?
However...
I don't recall teaching you
to draw such worthless manga!
Seen From Below
Can't show you!
Where the hell did you
get a hold of my manga?!
My granddaughter really is mean to me!
Yes, yes.
Oh, but Grandfather, why did
you suddenly bring this up?
Oh, the truth is, at this rate...
...Nagi will end up dead.
Loser Park
-inner
Th-There it is again...
All right! I got it this time!
Winner
Yes!
That's ominous...
All I ever thought about was money,
because of the way my parents were...
I'd never even thought about my own life...
But am I okay with my life being like that?
A life spent solely for the
purpose of repaying debt...
Hayate!
Oh, Miss.
I've been looking for you.
Come on, let's hurry up and leave.
What? We're leaving already?
Yes, I can't put up with that
stinking old geezer anymore!
Did something happen?
Something did happen...
Or rather, will happen...
What?
What is about to happen?
Wh-Wh-Wha... Who is this person?!
Damn! So he's really come.
You are quite skilled to
dodge Gilbert's sword!
Wh-Who is this fake-sounding foreigner?
Um... It's a long story, but...
He's the man who may inherit all
of the Sanzenin family fortune.
I-Inherit it all?
Um, in other words...
The story will grind to a halt if
we leave the explanation to Nagi,
What?!
so we will have you watch the
rest of the earlier scene here.
Oh, but Grandfather, why did
you suddenly bring this up?
Oh, the truth is, at this rate...
...Nagi will end up dead.
Huh?! Why would I end up dead?!
Have you finally gone senile,
you stinking old geezer?!
I have not gone senile, nor do I stink.
Just think about it, Granddaughter.
I do not have long to live.
And once I die, the family fortune
will go to you in its entirety.
However, many of our relatives
do not favor this arrangement.
It's true.
There are people out there who would
sell their son for 150 million,
so it seems plausible that some
may try to take Nagi's life.
Indeed.
So I came up with an idea.
If someone can fulfill a certain condition,
I would leave the Sanzenin
family fortune, not to Nagi,
but to that person instead.
Oh-ho. And what is this condition?
Yes, this condition is...
I'm sorry.
I've lost.
I'll leave the family fortune to you,
so please have mercy on me.
...and make you apologize in tears.
The Tail Wagging the Dog
I'd rather die than spout
such embarrassing lines!
I don't know...
I just don't understand the things
that rich people come up with.
Not to worry, I don't understand it, either.
So, that being the case...
Please apologize in tears to me!
Like hell I'm apologizing to you! Moron!
Don't you have any pride or anything?!
Doing such things is
useless! Get out of here!
Is that so? Then you leave me no choice.
What are you doing to Hayate?!
According to Old Man Mikado...
If I just beat that weak-looking
butler to a pulp,
there's a chance that the Miss
might apologize in tears.
So I'm gonna beat the crap outta him
and make the family fortune mine!
If the Miss can no longer inherit
the Sanzenin family fortune,
that means she won't be enormously
rich like she is now, right?
If that were to happen,
would this girl be alone...?
Rendered homeless, like me?
The rice porridge is ready.
I'm sorry, Maria, for all the
trouble I'm putting you through...
We promised not to talk about that, remember?
If only Hayate would pay you back...
I shouldn't have lent him
that 150 million yen.
That could be possible!
Hayate, watch out!
Prepare to meet your fate!
Money! Money!
Damn it! Why you!
Money!
A life spent merely for the
sake of repaying a debt...
...is utterly meaningless.
Meaningless!
The Miss came to my rescue, wearing
that silly-looking mask...
The Miss put her heart and soul
into nursing me back to health...
To think the Miss might face
adversity because of me...
At any rate, I'll think of a
way to repay my debt quickly.
But right now, there's the Miss!
I don't yet know what the
meaning of my life is,
but right now, I just have to...
Why you!
Universe!
H-Hayate...
I'll protect you.
What?
Anyone... who tries to make you cry...
I'll protect you from them.
Would that... be all right?
Um...
That is, uh...
I-I'll be counting on you.
What's this? Is this gonna become
a battle anime startin' next week?
No, it will not.
The boy shook free of uncertainty
and found meaning in his life,
protecting his mistress.
In which direction does butler
Hayate's tomorrow lie?!
Next time, he will be fighting
with all kinds of circumstances.
Don't you lose that pendant, boy.
Still...
Oh, Maria has gone...
That hurt!
Wh-What's this? You're still here?
I still haven't gotten my
pocket change, after all.
Never mind that, how do you plan to get home?
Nagi and the others are over there already.
What?!
Y'all left me here all by my lonesome?
Wooooooo...
What a cold era this is!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Butler Report
Unfortunately, our week of being
reinforced by Maria ends today.
What? It does?
Starting next time, that hugely
popular character will be appearing!
Could that possibly be the #1 in
popularity polls? That Hina...
No!
Hayate, it will be Nagi's turn
on duty starting next time.
Or rather, this is the end of my week.
Aren't I being treated
awfully poorly for all that?
Look forward to next time with keen interest!
Bye-bye!
Preview
Um, is that you, Hayate?
M-Miss Nishizawa...
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
We haven't seen each other since Christmas.
What in the world have you
been doing since then?
Well, a lot of things happened...
I'm working as a butler
at a certain mansion, now.
What? Is that a joke?
Oh, but I'm glad. I'm really
happy that I got to see you.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Long Ago, We Learned from a Space Sheriff
"that Being Young is About Not Looking Back".
Wait, Hayate!
My... My feelings for you are...!
Long Ago, We Learned from a Space Sheriff
that Being Young is About Not Looking Back
You'll get to see Newtypes in combat!