Good luck, Tanaka Tarou-kun!
As a member of the Dollars,
I'm taking this.
So you're still walking around all big,
even though Harima Mika is gone.
What would it take for her to die?
You heard the Slasher struck
again in Ikebukuro, right?
Then, I'll have to cause a war
that only I can cause.
Screw it all!
Welcome! Welcome!
It's Russian sushi!
It's good.
It's cheap!
Eat sushi!
The Slasher?
Again?
How many has it been?
The Slasher!
The Hidden Darkness of Modern Times
This is where the Slasher's attack took place last night.
That massive meeting that suddenly occurred,
in downtown Ikebukuro, six months ago...
The Slasher started appearing
right around then, didn't he?
The Ikebukuro youth say that a "Headless Rider"...
America has already made contact with the
Headless Rider and gained access to its technology.
Slasher...
Headless Rider...
I'm scared.
In this town, things are born every
day, and things vanish.
No way!
Have some sushi!
Still, nothing happens.
Really?
Nothing changes.
The Dollars...
That was her everyday life.
Takes a
Sudden Turn
Everything about our love is fake.
But it's stronger than the real thing.
I love the scars on your neck.
Through them, I can attain true love.
I love you.
I love everything about you, with everything I have.
Man, I get so jealous every time I see them...
Then don't look at them.
If there's a pretty girl, you look at them.
Then you talk to them!
That is our Team Men destiny,
encoded into our DNA!
I don't want to be on the same team as you.
But don't worry.
My body belongs to everyone,
but my heart is yours alone, Anri.
I always think to myself,
"Why is Anri so erotic, so cute?"
There's no "erotic" there, man! No "erotic"!
So you'll at least admit she's cute?
Well... Um...
So she's not cute?
She is!
She is, but-
I see! So you admit she's cute.
But I admit her eroticism, as well.
Thus, I understand and love her
more deeply than you.
And so, I win this battle!
What kind of standard is that?
You lose!
Dollars
Slasher
Six months ago,
there was a bit of an incident.
The whole town and school talked about it for a while.
But it had nothing to do with her.
She wasn't interested.
You OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That was her everyday life.
Hurry up!
I'm so glad I had those points saved up!
Yes, sir.
What are you going to do about that poster, Yumacchi?
She's got the pedal to the metal.
Don't you think she's a bit more open
about it than she used to be?
Yeah.
I'd prefer things like that to be a bit less open.
It should be like "the lady's secret,"
where only we know it.
The Secret of Nogizaka Haruka, right?
You guys...
Hey, don't worry about it.
I'm sure she's got her own stuff going on...
Look!
It's the Headless Rider!
This is the everyday life of Celty Sturluson.
It was something she was used to.
Those who were dragged into extraordinary panic...
And then she'd flee.
That was how Celty Sturluson did things.
But...
You know, I've always thought
that whenever there's a manga or a movie
with something like you, we're the foil.
By the time the hero with superpowers appears,
we're always lying on the ground, in a pool of blood,
just to show how strong you are.
That's fine.
That just means we're considered
powerful enough ourselves.
For a movie, it's a good way to do things.
But I always wanted to add something in.
If there really was a monster, or an evil psychic,
or an artificial human, or a ninja...
Just one thing... Just one thing I'd want to say.
Don't screw with the cops, monster.
I'll say it one more time.
Don't screw with the cops, you stupid monster!
Celty!
Welcome-
What?
What's wrong?
I'm as honored as Buddha to be held by you...
I may not be using that phrase right.
Hey, you're shaking.
Really, what happened?
Celty?
I was scared!
I was so scared, Shinra!
The cops are monsters lately!
The cops?
There were like ten motorcycles and patrol cars there,
and they all followed me,
like they were all one huge monster.
Come to think of it,
I heard they brought in an external
motorcycle cop to deal with you.
I think his name is Kuzuhara Kinnosuke.
He's a bit of a problem cop who often chases
people too hard and causes accidents.
I was scared... Really scared.
I was arrogant.
I'll be quiet from now on, so forgive me.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Who are you apologizing to?
It's not like you to get this frightened.
The only time I want you to be weak with me is in bed-
Don't say stuff like that right now!
Yes. Yes, you're right...
And um, this may not be the best time,
but can you pick someone up for me?
It's not a job.
He's back.
My dad.
Jeez... He should just take a taxi or something.
He's always been after me.
What's this?
Get a load of this guy!
White.
Too white!
No way...
What's with this guy?
That's quite an outfit, don't you think, Horada-san?
The air in Tokyo is dirty.
Don't you agree?
But I suppose your filthy faces
protect you from the filthy air.
I think he's cracked.
Well, whatever.
I guess it's time to show you the power of adults.
You seem to think that you're protected
by the youth laws and can kill anyone you want.
But remember this!
When you attempt to kill someone,
you must be prepared for them to kill yo-
He's nuts...
I'm over twenty!
W-Wait a moment!
That really hurts, and you're stepping
on my foot so I can't run.
You're sticking me with your finger!
What are you doing, Celty-kun?
Hurry up and save me!
I really don't want to...
Didn't you realize that the reason I said
all that was because I saw you?
Horada-san, it's the girl on the black bike.
What?
Really?
I saw her on TV.
I heard you were at the Dollars
meeting six months ago.
Everyone thinks they can act all
high and mighty on our turf...
Come on! Say something!
What the hell?
That was the right response.
Oh, good. It's not broken...
Shinra gave me this. It's very important to me.
Did you see this?
This is the power of adults!
I really don't like him!
Is there really any meaning to this?
What are the rules for this?
Russian Sushi!
President!
Oh, Izaya!
Yo. You're working as hard as ever.
You've been coming to Ikebukuro often lately.
Stop by the restaurant.
We just opened a new can today.
Fresh fish!
Sorry.
I'm actually busy.
I'll drop by soon!
"You cannot hide an eel in a sack."
"Don't talk about rope in a hanged
man's house," was it?
OK! Let's share things we like about Anri,
to see who understands her better.
Me first:
She's erotic!
That's what you start with?
Let's get off the erotic stuff.
Those who laugh at the erotic,
die by the erotic.
I don't even know what that means...
This was the first time she'd been friends with guys.
No, more precisely... She may not have
ever been friends with anyone.
That's not what I'm saying!
Then say it.
Say it now!
Once, her role had only been
making Harima Mika look better.
But that had been fine with her.
It had been a place for her.
But...
With that now gone,
she couldn't find anywhere to be.
OK!
Let's go hit on some girls, all three of us,
to prove how erotic and cute she is!
What the hell?
H-Hit on girls?
Don't worry.
You're just a trap to make the girls
think since there's a girl,
it's safe to go with us!
You don't have to do a thing.
Wait, Masaomi-
OK, let's go!
Follow me!
Let's ride on!
Here we go!
K-Kida-kun?
Masaomi!
Was this really OK?
It's fine.
He'll go hit on girls by himself.
Jeez...
Man, what a pain...
He's so introverted, he needs a serious handicap.
I'm such a lady-killer.
Um...
She knew that the two boys were interested in her.
But...
This twilight is pretty!
But there's a weird cloud over there.
It may rain later.
Let's be careful.
I will.
Um...
What?
I'll be going.
See you tomorrow!
OK... See you tomorrow...
Shouldn't have mentioned the twilight...
If either of them were to ask her
to date them, she had no answer.
She still loved Harima Mika.
And the two of them just as much...
She still doesn't know the difference
between friendship and love.
To her, Harima Mika, Ryuugamine
Mikado, Kida Masaomi...
You're sure?
We need you.
I told you,
it's got nothing to do with me.
This isn't my place anymore.
I'm not coming back.
Not to this side.
Seriously?
Who Is the Slasher?
Eight This Month!
Slasher attacks continue in
Tokyo's Toshima district.
No connections among victims.
Are the attacks random?
The Slasher attacked a guy I know!
Was he killed?
Moron. The Slasher doesn't kill.
He slices them with a katana.
He doesn't kill? Boring.
The Slasher is the Dollars!
They think they run Ikebukuro!
It's the Headless Rider.
It's got a big scythe, right?
I saw the Headless Rider attack someone!
There are lots more yellow people in town lately.
Yellow?
You're right.
You can see their colors, so they
stand out more than the Dollars.
Oh, the Yellow Scarves?
You know them, Setton-san?
Yeah, I suppose so.
They've been around a long time.
The Yellow Scarves...
They were a gang that used to be in Ikebukuro.
They got in a fight with another gang
and then vanished.
Ah, I've heard that story.
They're back, then?
Ikeburo's gotten dangerous recently.
Really.
The police are scary, too.
No, really...
Don't underestimate the police.
The police?
She fell!
Fail.
We just kind of lightly kicked her.
She's so clumsy.
She's a pinworm!
What's that look?
I don't think they're going to solve
the Slasher case for a while.
By the way, did you hear it?
The rumor that the Dollars are the Slasher.
Some people say they're the Headless Rider, too.
Who said that?
I think that's untrue.
Jokes aside...
You really should watch out for the Yellow Scarves.
Some of them don't like how the Dollars have
grown in power while they were gone.
Really?
OK. I'll be careful.
Jeez! After Harima, you're slutting it up
with Ryuugamine and Kida?
And Nasujima, too?
How many guys are you going to
sell yourself to, you whore?
You can't live without being a parasite,
feeding off someone.
Pinworm.
The girl thought to herself that
what they said was true.
She'd been dependent on Harima Mika.
And now...
Why so quiet?
Why not say something?
Do pinworms not have mouths?
She was dependent on the two young boys, too.
She was trying to find a place for herself there.
You stink, pinworm...
Don't even come to school.
I lost two boyfriends to you!
What's wrong with you? Huh?
This is how she protected herself, her heart...
Nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That was her everyday life.
Your room's nearby, right?
We'll drop by!
We'll see what you've got hiding.
Take us there.
SinSong joined
She's here!
Huh?
Cut.
Cutted.
I'm the one who wants to cut you!
Was wrong.
You're the one who's been trolling boards,
the last six months, aren't you?
Weak. Wrong.
Can't. Control.
We didn't block her yet?
Want is desire.
I did!
But it just doesn't work!
Love not enough love
Oh, I see.
Love want person
I'm blocking her remote host,
but she always comes in from a different host.
More Strong Love want
A proxy?
Wish I Mom Mom
I don't think it's a proxy.
It's kinda scary.
Mom. Mom. Mom. Mom. Mom.
Nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That was her...
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Turmoil
Reigns
Somewhere in this town, there's a Slasher.
Every time there's an attack, terror
spreads a thousand rumors across the stagnant night.
But...
Next time:
Turmoil Reigns.