Rider?
Idiot!
What's wrong with you, breaking the shutter open like that?
Why didn't you take spirit form, like when you went in?!
I can't carry these in spirit form.
Stop panicking.
You make me sound like a thief.
If you're not a thief, then what are you?!
There's a big difference.
A cowardly thief would sneak away in the night.
The King of Conquerors sings triumphantly as he leaves with his loot!
I'll carry these!
Now disappear. Disappear right now!
Very well! I shall leave you to carry the spoils.
Be careful not to drop them.
Geez! Why is this happening to me?!
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
The summoning went fine, so why is this happening?
See the
World Now!
World Map
And what's the deal with these books, anyway?
World Now!
World Map
I told you. They're preparations for the war.
War cannot be waged without maps.
Hey, boy.
Where are Macedonia and Persia?
Wh-What's with that attitude?!
I'm your Ma...
I'm well aware that you are my Master.
Did we not forge a contract?
Yeah.
I'm more interested in learning where the territories I ruled over are.
Around here, I guess.
Tiny! I spent my life conquering
that land, and behold how tiny it is!
Very well! I cannot wait!
Where are we now on the map, boy?
Here.
Right on the other side of the world, then.
Pleasing news yet again!
This will guide us in the coming battles.
Guide us?
First, we head to the other side of the world.
We go west, and only west.
And we shall conquer every land we pass through!
I shall return to Macedonia triumphantly,
and my people will hold a festival to honor my revival.
Exciting, is it not?
Do you even know what you're here for?!
You're here for the Grail War! The Grail!
That's right.
Speaking of the Grail, I forgot to ask...
What will you do with the Grail, boy?
Wh-Why would you want to know?
Why would you care?
World Map
If you are also intent on conquering the world,
that would make you my enemy.
World Map
The world cannot serve two lords.
World conquest?
I-I'll tell you what I want.
I just want people to treat me fairly.
The people at the Clock Tower don't acknowledge my talents, and I want to change that!
Small!
Small! And so narrow-minded!
How foolish.
You're in this battle just for your reputation?
And you dare call yourself my Master?!
How disappointing!
If you wish so desperately for others to revere you...
perhaps you should use the Grail's power to grow another thirty centimeters.
How dare he talk to me like that?! He's just my Servant!
I'll show him!
I address my Command Spell.
Abiding by the Grail's laws, I order Iskandar, King of Conquerors...
Calm down, Waver.
A Master can use his Command Spells to compel his Servant's obedience only three times.
I won't be able to control him if I use up all my Command Spells.
I have no complaints as long as I get the Grail.
Do whatever you want afterwards-
Yes, okay! I'll acquire the Grail for you.
You seem confident.
What makes you think you can win?
Are you saying you wish to see my power?
O-Of course!
You need to prove that I can rely on you!
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
With the swing of my sword, I declare my supremacy!
King Gordias made this very offering to Zeus.
Its renown must be the source of my designation as Rider.
If you want the Grail, then go find me another Heroic Spirit or two!
Until then, I shall entertain myself with these maps.
No problems with that?
Okay! I won't lose today!
Found one.
No way! Where?!
I'm pretty sure I didn't miss any!
That's today's first walnut bud.
One point for me.
I... I won't lose!
Found one!
I found one, too!
But I already found two.
That's not a walnut branch.
No, Ilya. That's called a wingnut.
It's similar to a walnut.
That makes it a walnut bud, too.
No fair!
No fair! No fair!
You've been cheating this whole time, Kiritsugu!
But Daddy has no chance of winning otherwise.
I won't play with you if you keep cheating!
Oh, no! I'm sorry! I apologize.
Do you promise not to cheat anymore?
I promise.
Very well.
I accept your challenge.
A champion takes on all challengers!
Indeed. I am honored...
...my princess!
I'm so high up!
What are you looking at, Saber?
Your daughter and Kiritsugu are playing in the woods outside.
Surprised?
I was under the impression that my Master was colder than that.
Well, I can see why you might think so.
If that is Kiritsugu's true self...
I must have gravely offended him.
Irisviel! This isn't funny!
I'm sorry.
I was wondering if what happened during your summoning still bothered you.
It does, a little.
It's true that I passed myself as a man,
but there was no need for both of you to be so taken aback.
Well, we just couldn't help it.
Your legend... King Arthur's legend... is simply too famous.
Do you suppose Kiritsugu thinks light of my ability because I'm a woman?
Not at all.
But...
Indeed, there's another reason why he's upset.
Another?
He's probably upset at the people who were around you.
People cruel enough to force the role of a king on a young girl.
It was inevitable.
I had resolved myself to that fate
when I drew the sword from the stone.
The fact that you accepted your fate upsets him all the more.
He forgets his place, then.
He does not have the right to question decisions made by those of my time, including myself.
That's why he isn't saying anything.
Emiya Kiritsugu and the Hero Arturia will never see eye to eye.
Indeed, he's given up on trying.
He wants to use the Grail's power to save the world.
Is that not Kiritsugu's and your common wish?
Yes, but I'm merely repeating what he said.
My own desire for the Grail is the same.
I wish to save Britain, since I was unable to do so before.
I think what you and Kiritsugu seek is right.
It is something to be proud of.
Our next match won't be until you come home from Japan, right?
That's right.
How long will your work keep you and Mommy away?
When will you be back?
I'll be back in about two weeks.
Mommy won't be back for quite a while, though.
Yeah, Mommy told me already.
She said she'll be away for a long time.
She said that even if we can't see each other for a long time, she'd always be by my side.
So she told me I shouldn't feel lonely,
last night before I went to bed.
I'm gonna be together with Mommy forever and ever!
I see.
Listen, Ilya.
Kiritsugu?
Can you wait for me?
Even if you're lonely, can you hold on until I come home?
Yeah!
I promise you, then.
I'll come home straight away.
Fill, fill, fill 'er up, fill...
Repeat four times...
Wait, was it five times?
Um, destroy each when filled...
...or something?
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill.
All right, that makes five times!
Okay.
At all three murder scenes, a mysterious pentagram drawn with the victims' blood was found.
At all the locations
of the
bizarre serial killin
gs in Fuyuki City,
mysterious pen
tagram
s have been dra
wn in blood.
Maybe I went a little too far.
The purpose of the pentagrams remains unclear.
At all the locations of
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
mysterious pentagrams
have
been drawn in blood.
At all the locations of
mysterious pentagrams
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
have
been drawn in blood.
At all the locations of
mysterious pentagrams
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
have
been drawn in blood.
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
mysterious pentagrams
have
been drawn in blood.
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
Today, we've invited a specialist in criminal psychology-
Do you think demons exist, kiddo?
All the papers and magazines call me a demon.
But wouldn't that be kinda rude if demons really did exist?
You've gotta be clear about these things.
Sup! I'm Uryuu Ryuunosuke, and I'm a demon!
I dunno if that's how I should be introducing myself.
So like, I found this.
It's some old book I found in the storehouse.
It looks like my ancestors were researching how to summon demons.
So like, I've gotta find out if demons really do exist!
But y'know...
If a demon really did come out, it'd be pretty dumb to just chat with it and have nothing to offer him.
So, kiddo...
If a demon really does show up...
Mind if we let it kill you?
I wonder what it's like, being killed by a demon!
Not many people get to experience that- Ow!
What's this?
I ask you.
You, who calls me and seeks me...
Summoner who manifests me under the class of Caster...
I ask your name.
Yes...
Who are you?
Uh...
I'm Uryuu Ryuunosuke.
I'm currently unemployed, and I like killing people, pretty much.
Especially kids and young women.
Very well. The contract is made.
I desire the Grail, as do you.
The vessel of paradise shall belong to us.
The Gra... What?
Anyway, how about a sacrifice?
Wanna eat that kid?
Whoa! That's human skin, right?
Cthulhu fhtagn.
Don't be scared, boy.
Can you stand?
Now, boy, you can leave the room through that door.
You can go by yourself, right?
Yeah.
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
Some forms of terror are fresher than others.
The more intense the fear, the more the emotions die.
Terror, in its truest sense, is not a static state, but a dynamic one.
It is the moment when hope turns to despair.
Did you enjoy that?
The taste of fresh terror and death?
Cool! You're awesome!
You're so cool, man!
Okay!
I don't know about this Grail crap,
but I'm following you from now on!
Kill more!
Show me even cooler ways to kill people!
Ryuunosuke, wasn't it?
How fortunate of me to be blessed with an understanding Master like yourself.
It feels like my dream is almost within my grasp.
Oh, yeah. I didn't get your name.
My name?
Let me see. In this era, I would probably be known as...
I think I'll take the name of Bluebeard for now.
The Church has just informed me that the seventh Servant, Caster, has appeared.
The final Servant has been summoned? Then it is time.
Indeed.
You are to head immediately for the Tohsaka household.
And when I arrive?
The house's powerful magic fields should be child's play to you.
Are you sure?
I believe you're supposed to be allied with Tohsaka Tokiomi.
Don't worry about that.
Even if you end up having to fight Archer, there is no need to fear.
No need to fear Archer, one of the three great knight classes?
I'm counting on you.
You are to promptly kill Tohsaka Tokiomi.
This is too easy.
Little worm crawling on the ground.
Who gave you permission to look up?
He said...
I didn't need...
...to fear him?!
You are not worthy to gaze upon me.
A worm should just continue staring at the ground...
...as it dies.
Episode 2
False Opening
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
At last, it is time for the 4th Holy Grail War to start.
It's unspeakably ugly.
Where is the thing I left with you?
This will be fun!
Welcome.
Bring me victory!
Yes, without fail.
Next Episode
Land of Winter Trees