Space has a beginning, but it has no end.
Infinite.
Stars too have a beginning,
but are by their own power destroyed.
Finite.
History dictates that he who holds wisdom is the greatest fool.
This could be called God's final warning
to those that still rebel.
Okarin!
Let's go.
Prologue
of
the
Beginning
and
End
Initiating building infiltration.
El Psy Congroo.
There aren't many people here.
As I suspected. This reeks of Organization interference...
What's going to happen here?
You came along without even knowing?
Doctor Nakabachi's Time Machine Invention Press Conference
A time machine...
Amazing!
Doctor Nakabachi's Time Machine Invention Press Conference
Doctor Nakabachi has done what the rest of us could not,
and he's here today to announce the invention of the century.
I'll be paying careful attention to what he has to say.
An earthquake?
No, from above?
What's this?
You called me here for this?
There aren't many left of this series,
and Mayushii's out of 100 yen coins!
Don't act so spoiled, Mayuri.
Even though you're my childhood friend, I won't loan you any money.
I'll teach you how harsh life can be...
What's this?
It's not painted?
M-Metal...
It's a metal...
A metal Upa!
Is it rare?
Extremely!
Then you can have it.
Are you sure, Okarin?
It's Hououin Kyouma.
Thanks, Okarin.
I said it's Hououin Kyouma.
Doctor Nakabachi's press conference
will now begin in the 8th floor's hall.
In the handouts, I have outlined
the time machine's basic design.
I will use this conference as an opportunity
to discuss the fundamental theory behind it.
Scientists all over the world...
Received Mail
Time:
Sender: Mayuri
Subject: My Upa...
"I think I dropped my metal Upa,
so I'm going to look for it."
Currently, there are more than ten major theories in regards to possible methods of time travel,
Basic design of the time machine...
and they've been examined from nearly every possible angle.
Doctor!
What is it?
You know exactly what it is!
What is this "time machine theory" of yours?
Kerr black holes?
World lines?
This is all taken directly from John Titor!
Titor called himself a time traveler,
and posted this theory on the Internet back in 2000.
Don't attempt to feign ignorance!
How rude!
Of course I know about him!
Don't compare my theory to that fraud's!
Then why don't you explain
the differences between your theories?
Hey, you...
Titor, huh?
Come to think of it, there was
some similar stuff in the John Titor books...
Who are you?
That's what I'd like to know.
What?
Back there, you were going to tell me something,
weren't you?
Back there?
About fifteen minutes ago.
I don't have the slightest idea...
Makise... Kurisu?
You had a paper in "Science Magazine" a while ago.
I'm surprised you know of it.
Are you a university scientist?
You!
Are you an agent of The Organization?
Organization?
What?
I just wanted to ask you...
There's no need for me to answer you!
It's me.
I've been caught by an Organization agent.
Yes.
Makise Kurisu.
Who are you talking to?
Yeah, it should be no trouble.
I'll get out of this somehow...
Huh? It's turned off.
I'll tell you a secret.
That's a special cell phone for secret missions.
If anyone but me touches it, it deactivates.
I see.
You were talking to yourself.
I'll make this brief.
What were you going to tell me?
About fifteen minutes ago.
You were trying to tell me something, weren't you?
It seemed like it was really important...
I've seen through your tricks.
Genius Girl, when next we meet, we will be enemies.
Farewell.
Wait!
What was she talking about?
She met me?
Date: 2010/07/28 12:26
Sender: sg-epk@jtk92.x29.jp
Subject: (No Subject)
Attachment: IMV001
Received Mail
Okarin!
Mayuri!
What were you doing?
I messaged you, didn't I?
I can't find my metal Upa.
I even put my name on it...
You dropped it?
I think so.
Give up.
On auction sites, a metal Upa goes for 10,000 yen!
10,000 yen...
Find it!
My lab is almost entirely out of funding!
Even if I find it, I won't sell it.
With 10,000 yen, we could acquire the parts
for a new future gadget...
I said I'm not selling it.
What was that?
Run away!
Hey...
Is someone there?
Makise Kurisu...
What?
Someone's been stabbed...
Okarin!
What's wrong?
You're pale.
I saw a corpse...
On the 8th floor!
Looks like someone stabbed Makise Kurisu.
To: Daru
Subject: Trouble
Send?
Wh-What?
What's going on?
Tuturuu~
Here you go, Okarin!
What is this?
What's what?
The people... Why did all the people disappear?
They disappeared?
They all disappeared!
All the people here! They were right in front of us!
I don't know...
You have to know!
You saw it, didn't you?
Right?
I didn't.
What are you talking about...
Hey, you there!
Can you see us?
Why don't you answer?
You, on the other side of the monitor, with the vacant expression!
Whatever.
This is the Future Gadget Lab.
I'll introduce our staff.
First up is Lab Member 001.
He's the lab's founder and an insane mad scientist...
It is none other than I, Hououin Kyouma!
Okarin sounds much cuter though.
Silence!
Okabe Rintarou is the name I use to deceive the public eye.
Next up Lab Member 002.
She's the lab's lone female member, and her hobby is making cosplay outfits.
It's Shiina Mayuri!
It's me, Mayushii.
And finally, Lab Member 003, Supah Hakah Hashida Itaru!
It's "Hacker," not "Hakah," duh.
It's only us.
Isn't it about time to give up?
You can't expect too much from software you got out of a 500 yen bargain bin.
Listen well.
Future Gadget Lab
CRT
TV
Work-
shop
To get to our lab go down Chuo Street,
turn left on Kuramae Street.
at the Suehirochou intersection
We're in a multi-use building, in the first alley
before the traffic light.
The goal of the Future Gadget Lab
is to reform the ruling structure of the world...
To create inventions which will bring about chaos.
Do you understand?
If you understand, then tell me your secrets!
Hey, do you think we look
like a video game to Alpacaman?
Don't you think the concept of what's real and fantasy
is a little beyond him?
Then are your 2D girls like that too?
That's different.
Those are mai waifu.
Nobody cares about your wives.
But isn't that an interesting idea?
If we did exist solely inside a monitor,
do you think there would be any way we could tell?
Nope.
That was fast.
Thus, this discussion is pointless.
We'd do much better to spend our time
thinking of ways to battle The Organization
and destroy the world's ruling structure.
That delusional crap again? Fail.
Silence, Supah Hakah!
I am the Insane Mad Scientist, Hououin...
Kyouma!
That's your backstory, isn't it?
My, my, Daru.
You shouldn't go hiding in your shell.
You should listen to what others have to say.
So, this is today's "you're the last one I want to hear that from" thread?
Anyway, it looks like the news helicopter has arrived.
Special Report
Where did it come from?
A mysterious satellite appears!!
The object, thought to be some sort of satellite, crashed in Akihabara, Tokyo,
around 12 o'clock today.
What was that?
This morning, Mayuri and I left the lab for Radio Kaikan,
to attend Doctor Nakabachi's press conference.
But the next thing I knew, a satellite had crashed into the building.
And not just that...
Me?
Yeah... You saw the satellite crash on TV and said,
"The Organization has finally made its move!"
So the two of us went over to see it.
Canceled?
Don't you remember how angry
you were this morning? You said something like, "He got cold feet and ran away!"
Doctor Nakabachi's press conference!
It was at 12 o'clock, at Radio Kaikan!
It really wasn't, bro.
And a good thing too...
If it had been, that satellite would have smashed you.
This discrepancy in memories...
Is it The Organization's memory control?
Right...
This is the choice of Steins;Gate!
That again?
That Stein-whatever doesn't make any sense at all, y'know.
Daru, get me Future Gadget #1!
Alpacaman got mad because you changed the channel.
Curse you, Mr. Braun!
Making us use this piece of crap...
He gave it to us for free, didn't he?
Daru, get the TV!
Yeah, no thanks.
It's pretty hot today.
And like,
don't think I'm strong just 'cause I'm fat.
That's not something to brag about!
Mr. Braun!
I told you to call me Tennouji.
I'd like to ask you to fix this immediately...
You broke it already?
You don't have enough love for the Braun tubes.
1,000 yen to fix it.
If anyone's at fault here, wouldn't it be you, for giving us something defective?
Is that how you address your landlord?
I'll pay the repair bill.
Mayuri, you should give up on this guy.
But Mayushii is Okarin's hostage!
Hostage, huh?
Is this broken as well?
Repair bill's 2,000 yen now.
If you don't like it, take it back.
What will you do?
It's me.
The Organization has finally gained control of the bald man.
I'm encountering sabotage.
Here you go.
You really do like Dr Pepper, Okarin!
It's an intellectual drink for the chosen ones.
The cicadas are really loud, aren't they?
Daru!
Now that the Organization
has begun using Mr. Braun to sabotage us, we're putting the plan into action.
We've been backed into a corner!
The plan? The what now?
The plan is the plan!
What else could it be but the introduction of
Future Gadget #8 to an actual combat situation?
Oh, the Phone Microwave (name subject to change).
How do you use a microwave in combat, anyway?
It's been nearly three and a half years since we met.
Second year of high school...
We were in different classes and barely spoke,
so it's more like two years?
The details don't matter.
Anyway, it's been that long.
Please reach the point
where you can keep up with my conversations already.
That is-n't...hap-pen-ing.
Actually, want to try again?
It's all set.
Mayuri, bring the bananas!
You're making gel-banas again?
It's such a waste!
If we're stingy, we can never succeed against The Organization!
We don't need to win...
You know, Mayushii's the one bringing bananas, right?
I know.
This is R-E-N-G, the Phone Microwave (name subject to change).
You can manipulate the timer from here.
Please press the pound key,
and then enter the number of seconds you want to cook for.
One, two, zero, pound.
Pretty turntable, isn't it?
It goes in the opposite direction.
Opposite?
Might be important!
When you think of what's happening at the quantum level,
and you apply Hund's rules...
I'm sure it... isn't.
It isn't?
Nope.
Hasn't changed.
It doesn't get warm, and it doesn't get cold.
Mayushii's Juicy Karaage Number 1 froze...
Well, something involving Steins;Gate is at work here, that much is clear!
That again?
Daru, don't you want to try eating this?
I don't.
Then we'll give the honor to Mayuri.
The gel-bana was soft and squishy.
And it had no taste.
You ate it?
Mayushii?
Say, "Your banana is soft and squishy."
"Your banana is soft—"
Don't make her say that, you pervert!
I-I'm melting...
It hasn't been ten minutes since we left the lab.
When it gets hot like this, I don't want to go any farther than Faris'.
I wish they'd just host it at May Queen Nyan-Nyan.
They're not going to host a university lecture at a maid café.
If they didn't take attendance, I'd never go.
It's so cold.
I'm alive.
A satellite fell, didn't it?
That again?
You're not going to Radio Kaikan to see it?
There's probably too many onlookers to see anything anyway.
I'm reading the reports on @channel
from the people who went.
"Work Temporarily Canceled."
Another giant thread?
Oh, right. Back then...
Give me your cell phone.
Why?
Just do it!
That's a violation of privacy! Denied!
I sent you a message!
A message about Makise Kurisu being stabbed.
Oh, the one from last week?
Last week?
It was split into three messages.
I thought it was spam!
See?
Okabe Rintarou
(No Subject)
Sent on July 23rd, 12:56...
"Looks like
someone stabbed
Makise Kurisu."
See?
Last week... Let me check my sent folder.
Mayuri
Re: Upa...
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Faris
Re:
Revival Prophecy
Song
It's not here!
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Faris
Re:
Revival Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Faris
Re:
Revival Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Daru
Re:
(No subject)
What is today?
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Faris
Re:
Revival Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Faris
Re:
Revival Prophecy
Song
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Mayuri
Re: Upa...
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
The... The 28th.
What's wrong?
That message was sent to the past...