My part-time job is going well.
The plans for the
new book are pristine!
And then of course my second
dojin exhibition and sale event!
But something feels like it's missing.
Something's missing?
Like, how do I say it...
Like passion or tension...
What about rivals for that?
That's true! In any manga,
the main character gets all fired up...
...due to the appearance of a rival!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
What's wrong?
With what?
You've looked like a
burned-out boxer since earlier.
Burned out, huh?
In a way, I think that's right.
Did something happen?
No, nothing...
It's not good to keep it
all bottled up inside.
I'm not bottling it up.
I'm just a little tired.
I'm okay. I'm sorry to worry you.
Is that so?
Would you listen to me?
You do want to say it.
It was when I went to go
buy some dojinshi like usual.
Sorry to make you wait.
Those guys...
Please take care of me today.
Okay!
Najimi and Hoshi-kun were...
Why...
Where they eventually ended up was...
The love hotel district?
No way!
Najimi wouldn't do such a loose thing!
5th Edition
Let's do it together.
Why don't you ask her yourself?
No, it's not something for
me to go ahead and ask.
Plus, Najimi is an adult that
can make her own decisions.
That's true.
She is an adult female.
But the main problem is
if I should ask or not.
You're an adult that
can't make a decision.
Wouldn't she despise me and
say I'm intruding on her privacy?
In conclusion, you don't
have the courage to ask her.
No, wait a second.
It hasn't been decided as that yet.
Becoming incoherent is foolish.
That's true.
There are many options
for things to do in a love hotel.
This. That.
This kind of thing. That kind of thing.
Man, this really helps!
To tell you the honest truth,
doing it alone still isn't doing much.
You don't have to thank us.
It's more fun doing it all together.
That's true. If you're going to do it,
it's better to do it with two than one.
Hey!
If it's the three of us,
then it's on a plane of abnormality.
Could you stay quiet for a little?
What are you talking about?
It's too early for a little child.
Ask!
Ask.
What is it?
Um, well, how do I say it...
It's about that frame, but I think it's
better if you show it as a whole more.
Oh, thank you!
Oh, in your book,
they go to a love hotel in this scene.
Yeah.
Najimi, you're such a perv!
It's too early for a little child.
Right, Justice?
Najimi, you perv!
What was up with that?
No clue.
That guy named Hoshi...
To think he did
improper things to Najimi...
I want to make him
regret it in some way!
I know! Manga!
I'll make him realize it with manga!
The theme would be the
sinfulness of infidelity and...
...the magnificence of pure love.
It will compose the fall of a young man
who has committed many sins.
Okay, even if it becomes
hundreds of pages...
...I will complete it
just to show that guy!
Perverted Najimi
So, truthfully, how is it?
In this scene, a love
hotel comes up, but...
I've never been to a love hotel,
so I don't know how it really is.
And so my drawings end up
looking like a hospital room.
So you two went to
research a love hotel.
Hotel?
Did you go traveling somewhere?
I mean, they wouldn't let me in alone.
Why! Why!
You tried going in alone too, huh...
Plus, asking Justice
would be kind of weird.
And he would have totally
gotten the wrong idea.
He ended up totally having
the wrong idea anyway.
But Hoshi-kun is pretty fishy too.
He's fine!
There is nothing like that between us.
I can swear on that.
I know. It'd be more fake if you
were saying that something happened.
What is that "something"?
Well, show the result of
your hard work researching.
It's almost the next
exhibition and sale event.
What is that "something"?
This place is...
Oh, Najimi!
Ah, Justice!
How's your draft?
Are you going to make it in time?
I should be able to.
Najimi!
Najimi-san is mine!
I'm going to take good care of her.
Why you!
Justice, save me!
Najimi...
Najimi!
A dream? Oh no, I fell asleep...
Of course I did.
The last time I slept
was five days ago.
We came to help... you...
Oh, Najimi, you were okay?
Um, more like are you okay?
Is there something today?
You called me last night...
...saying that you haven't slept and you
won't be finished, so we came to help.
Oh, that's true. I'm sorry.
Hey, are you really okay?
Also, Sora's with us too.
I wanted to see you, Justice!
Sora...
Hey, you should rest a little.
But I need to write this epic piece
to reconfigure a certain individual!
Why are you saying
such a stupid thing?
This is amazing.
How many pages are you going for?
500 pages.
He's stupid.
Us three will try to work on it as much
as we can, so why don't you sleep?
It's okay!
Even I got a little better at it!
I will help too!
I understand.
Then I'm going to take this offer
and just for a little...
Okay! I'll do my best!
Hey Najimi, isn't that beta
too far outside of the line?
Is it?
Oh no, this wasn't
supposed to be beta!
At times like this, use the white ink.
Najimi, you are supposed to use
the white when the ink dries...
...too late...
It blended together!
It's okay, it's okay!
I can just wipe this with a tissue.
Oh man, it really spread!
You can't save this anymore.
Hey, that's enough. Thank you.
And complete.
It's here. I finally found it.
Thank you in advance for today...
No, thank you in advance...
It's the girl that's worse than me.
If you would like,
please have my new book.
Ah, mine too.
Did this girl laugh just now?
No, no, it's just me.
She just flatteringly smiled.
There's no way she can
laugh at me with this quality.
Good luck!
What's with that relaxed attitude?
Why is she cheering me on?
No way...
Does she...
...think I'm worse than her?
Comic Festival has now begun!
Okay, so Najimi-san's booth is...
Is this all dojinshi?
Wow...
Tsk, tsk, it's forbidden to run
within the exhibition center.
Hey, Sora.
Yeah, sorry. There were a lot of boxes.
I'm glad.
I heard about Najimi from Tsuyurin.
Tsuyurin?
The two of them were
taking pictures at the love hotel.
What a bothersome guy. Seriously...
It hung up.
Man, Justice is like Najimi's dad.
He's always worried.
Sora, you didn't use enough words.
You have to say that they were
just taking pictures of the love hotel.
Well, whatever. It's getting interesting.
Why did I run?
I don't have any reason to run.
I believed that you were
definitely going to come.
Hoshi-kun...
H-He's going to get me...
We have sold out!
Well, I guess the morning is like this.
Yeah, the usual pace.
Can't sell even one copy...
With that kind of quality,
of course it won't sell.
If I sell more than her,
that means I'm better than her.
This battle...
...the one that sells one copy...
...is the winner!
A couple is born!
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
Something that gets busier
than a summer festival...
...and somewhere you can
see more skin than at a beach.
When you think about it that way,
an exhibition event is pretty good, right?
6th Edition
I'm going to take one first.