Say, how do you like my face?
Pretty disgusting, isn't it?
It's pitiful, isn't it?
It's amazing, right?
You know, I was trying to ruin Iona,
so it was my face that ended up being ruined...
I was trying to end her career as a model, you know,
but it's my career that's over now...
It's funny, isn't it?
It makes you laugh, doesn't it?
So...
laugh!
Ruuko!
This is how super-cute Aki-lucky's face looks now!
Come on, take a look! Ain't I just pathetic?
Quit it, Akira!
It's your fault.
I lost to you...
And that's why I'm stuck with this face now.
So, now...
Yours, and yours, and Iona's...
I'm gonna make all of your faces look like mine!
What are you girls doing there?!
Stop!
You girls wait here!
Let's get away from here, Ruuko.
O-Okay.
She's not chasing us...
Y-Yeah...
I'm glad...
There's nothing to be glad about...
Akira-san is right.
It's my fault that Akira-san is...
Ruuko...
If you really don't have a wish,
you should quit while you still can, Ruuko.
Quit. Your grandma will be sad if something happens to you.
I'm not the only one who
should quit! You should, too!
If you lose, then your family...
Kazuki-kun would be heartbroken, too!
I'm not going to quit.
Yuzuki...
You saw what happened to Akira-san!
I won't end up like her.
But... why...
Ruuko, I'm sorry to make you worry.
Yuzuki?
But I can't quit now.
I almost gave up on my impossible wish...
But now it's right before my eyes.
Let's not be friends anymore.
I'm going to become an Eternal Girl.
And if you're with me when that happens,
you'll always be burdened
by the sad memories you'll make.
W-Wait...
I'm sorry.
Wait, Yuzuki!
Ruuko!
I really had fun with you!
I'll treasure my matching scrunchie forever!
Yuzuki...
Next time we meet, I'll be a new Yuzuki!
I'll be Kazuki's girlfriend!
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
Ruu? Ruu?
Ruu...?
Ruuko!
Where in the world have you been?
At least give us a call
if you're going to be this late!
That's none of your business.
It may be none of my business.
But...
you still shouldn't do anything to make Grandma worry.
Ruuko?
Is Grandma home?
Yeah. Hurry up and go see her.
I'm back...
Welcome home, Ruu-chan.
Icy, icy!
I just made some warm amazake.
I figured Ruu-chan would come home all cold.
Now, come on in.
Why...
Why aren't you asking me anything, Grandma?
We'll talk when you want to talk.
Is that all right with you?
Ruuko
Ruu?
Did the amazake taste good?
Are you asleep?
You know, Tama likes when Ruu is having fun battling.
But...
I don't like to...
see you sad.
Morning, Kazuki!
You made this, Yuzuki?
Well, yeah. Turns out I can make stuff like that.
Here's some soup, too.
I'm glad...
About what?
You went straight to sleep
when you came home last night.
I was worried about you.
Girls have days like that. Don't you forget it!
Sounds inconvenient.
Come on now, time to eat.
Right. Thanks.
Tastes great!
The last time you made French toast, the eggs were still raw.
Well... I tend to rush things.
I kind of lose my cool a lot.
Calm down, and wait for the right timing.
Set your eyes on your goal.
As long as I don't get lost on my way, things will be fine.
Right.
Meeting up with your friends?
Ah, yeah.
I'll be back soon, though.
Got it.
I'll make dinner tonight.
Really?
What would be good? We had French toast this morning...
Curry udon!
I know everything about you, Kazuki.
All right, I'm going.
Have fun!
Hitoe... I'm sorry.
I...
I won't end up like you.
Card Shop
ACE A
I will make my wish come true.
Welcome.
Guest
To Selectors
Would you like to have a battle on Sunday?
I'll be wearing a red scrunchie in my hair.
That...
Did you write that?
Isn't it a bit dangerous to look for opponents with that method?
It probably is.
I don't have an issue with that,
but other Selectors may get upset.
Even my LRIG is questioning what you did.
No Entry
Okay.
I don't really want to battle more than I need to.
Guess I'll finish it with this one.
Huh?
With this battle,
I'll make my wish come true.
You're pretty confident, aren't you?
Okay. Let's start.
Open!
I'm probably going first.
I wonder why.
Things feel different today.
Yuzuki...
Let's go, Hanayo-san!
I see where her confidence is coming from.
I was wrong all along.
That's what people made me think.
A love that isn't allowed.
I mean, I feel so sorry for Kazuki-kun when I see him being stalked by you.
A feeling that isn't allowed.
How lewd! That's just too pervy!
Spell! Severing Steamroll!
Direct damage!
I'm not wrong.
I'll turn everything on its head.
I'll turn this world where my feelings aren't allowed on its head.
I'll be by Kazuki's side!
Yuzuki.
Dang, I lost...
You're so good, Kazuki-kun!
Guess there's no beating you...
All right, it's my turn now.
I'm not gonna lose to you at least!
Hey, can you take a look at my deck?
Sure.
You're running a red deck?
Yup. The SIGNI with the gem theme is really cute.
Yuzuki uses a red deck, too.
I feel like drinking something.
Excuse me, is it okay if I bring a drink in?
Sure, go ahead.
Kazuki-kun, can you come with me?
Hey, the vending machine...
Can you follow me?
Huh?
I'm sorry to spring this on you.
But I really need to tell you how I feel.
I...
want to be with you.
Um... I'm not really looking for anything like that right now.
Sorry.
Is there someone else you like?
That's not it.
Would Yuzuki-san happen to be the reason?
You're always with her!
What else can we do but get suspicious about you two!
Wh-What are you saying?
What do you mean by "suspicious"?
Like, doing it even though you're brother and sister!
That's what everyone is saying!
Who's this "everyone"?
Who's spewing stuff like that? Tell me!
That's so rude...
Don't you feel sorry for Yuzuki?!
Tell me! Who is it? Matsumoto-san? Senda-san?!
I'll go tell them all they're wrong! Now tell me!
You're usually so kind...
But when it's about Yuzuki-san, you lose your temper.
Stop it!
Prove it to me if you think I'm wrong!
Prove it to you...?
Kiss me.
Why should I...
You don't even have to go out with me!
But you can kiss me at least, right?
If you can't kiss me, it means you must love Yuzuki-san!
Isn't that right?!
This is crazy.
Wait, Kazuki-kun!
It really does feel different.
I summon Cannon! I use its effect to banish Hass!
I feel a burning sensation inside of me,
but the very core of my body is surprisingly cold.
Maybe that means...
This battle really will be...
Yuzuki, I'll ask you once again—no, one last time.
Hanayo-san?
If you win this battle,
the wish you hold dear will come true.
Are you sure about this?
When I saw what happened to Hitoe, I blamed you.
But I...
Even if I had been told the truth from the very beginning,
I still would have wanted my wish granted.
I still would've gone down this road, all to become an Eternal Girl!
Go! Eagle!
I would have been scared, but I'd still have done it.
I feel really sorry for Hitoe, but...
Her wish could have come true
without her becoming a Selector.
My wish...
is a wish that could never come true, even if the world was destroyed.
A wish I couldn't make come true
without entering Selector battles.
Yuzuki.
Your final attack, and your final oath.
We'll say it together.
Now, let's say it together.
I accept...
I... accept!
the Laws of the Selector.
The Laws of the Selector.
And now!
A new Eternal Girl will be born!
Adamasphere!
It's happening?!
It's the birth of an Eternal Girl.
Hanayo-san...
It's your long-awaited day off.
Are you sure you don't want
to see your friends?
Y-Yeah.
Being with Grandma really relaxes me.
Battling is a whole lot of fun,
but I shouldn't get involved anymore.
That...
Let's not be friends anymore.
Ruu-chan?
Ah, sorry. It's nothing.
Really?
I can't get involved anymore.
Yes...
What the hell are you doing, leaving like that?!
Honoka-chan's fuming! She's saying you did something horrible to her!
I'll apologize with you, so you better come ba—
Girls are terrible.
Yuzuki is nothing like them.
Yuzuki always has a smile on her face.
She doesn't put on a facade.
She keeps it to herself when things trouble her.
Like, doing it even though
you're brother and sister!
What am I thinking?!
I'm back...
Yuzuki? What's the matter?
I just got dizzy there for a moment.
Sorry, dinner...
You should lie down!
Can you walk?
Yeah.
Thanks, Kazuki.
It's fine.
Did you put something on?
Like, a perfume...
Something smells pleasant.
They say that if you think someone smells good,
you're attracted to that person on a genetic level.
The one you're fated to be with... smells good.
Wh-What are you talking about?
I mean, I've heard that too, but it can't be.
That's only for people with
different genes to begin with.
Maybe we are that different.
But we're twins.
Maybe we were born with differences that were split between us.
With this, we're one.
Something's not right.
What's not right?
You, and everyone else.
Did something happen with the others?
I want you to talk about anything with me.
I'm always on your side, Kazuki.
I'm eternally yours.
Can I come in?
Hitoe, did you eat?
You haven't eaten lunch either, have you?
You need to eat a bit at least...
Ah, right, Hitoe!
I have something good for you.
Here.
You liked this, right?
I saw an ad about a new WIXOSS deck coming out, so I went and bought it.
Go ahead and take a look.
Oh, I also bought a cake.
Maybe you'd rather eat something sweet.
Let me go get it.
Nice to meet you,
That
Oath
is
Falsehood
Selector.
Once you give yourself to the shadow of the clockwork
tokeijikake no kage ni unadzuitara
darkness begins to encroach from the door of the end
owari no doa ga hiraki hajimaru yami
Menacing answers lie hiding in wait
ayaui kotae soko ni miekakureru
Today's wish will become tomorrow's taboo
kyou no inori wa ashita tabuu ni naru
Lost in a labyrinth where the world is turned upside-down
ten to chi wo utsusu sakasama no meiro
the gears slowly start to turn
mawaridashita haguruma
Quietly from within the waves of people
hitogomi no naka de mimi wo sumashitara
a bell rings out, beckoning my very being
tamashii wo maneku ano suzu no ne hibiku sora e
I have no choice but to walk the endless path
mugen no hate made wo susumu shika nai
for this is the future I willingly chose
jibun de eranda mirai dakara
In the wake of the unreachable summer clouds
todokanai natsugumo yureru kagerou
lies the place of smiles I'll one day reclaim
itsuka torimodosu egao no basho
A card game?
The card did what?
Wish...?
Did you spread it to everyone?
Thank you, Hanayo-san.
Do you remember me?
That
Truth
is
Cruel
That truth is cruel.