So Ra No Wo To
It happened one afternoon,
almost a year after I arrived at the fort.
Wow!
You've gotten really good, Kanata!
Really?
I'm so happy to hear that.
Lately, Rio-sempai's started
praising me, every once in a while!
You said you joined the military to
learn to play the trumpet, right?
Yes.
So,
then what's your dream?
The Sound of the Sky - The Horizon of Dreams
Dream?
Yours is simple.
To be good at the trumpet, right?
Yeah.
But when I told her that...
She said, "That's a short-term
goal, not a dream."
Mishio's such a little brat.
But like, are goals and
dreams different?
I'm asking because I don't know!
I see.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
If you're sure you know
how to achieve it,
and it's close at-hand, it's a goal.
If it's far away and hazy,
then I think it's a dream.
Hazy...
OK, all done.
What? Don't you have a dream?
Do you have one, Kureha-chan?
Yeah, I guess so.
What kind of dream?
Y-You shouldn't share your dreams
with people so lightly!
Do you have one, Noël-chan?
I do.
But it's a secret.
You've been rummaging around
with Rio-sempai lately.
Does it have anything
to do with that?
That's for my hobby.
Not for my dream.
Then why won't you tell us?
If I do, I may lose a part of it...
I see. Dreams, huh?
When I think about it,
I don't really have any kind
of far-off dream...
It makes me kind of sad.
Do you have one, Rio-sempai?
I guess so.
That's so nice...
Hey, just getting better at
the trumpet is a big goal.
There's no need to be so down.
That's true, but...
Don't rush into adulthood like that.
Nothing.
OK, then. Dreamless girl,
let's focus on your immediate goal.
I'm heading out for a while.
When I get back, I want you to
have mastered that song we went over,
up to the third movement.
But that's really hard-
You'll play it for me when I return.
I'm looking forward to it.
Aw...
But she's right.
I need to take it one step at
a time! Do what I can!
That sound...
Claus-san!
You seem different than usual.
I got my hair cut. Maybe
that's why.
Anyway, I came to
give this to Rio...
A special message from
the Roman Emperor.
I've never seen one before, either.
He wants proof of receipt.
I can't leave without a
signature... Is Rio in?
Are you in a hurry?
Yeah. I'd like to get
it as soon as I can.
Then I'll go find her.
Oh, right. Claus-san.
Do you have a dream?
Yeah. When I've worked long
enough to get a pension,
I'm going back to the country
and owning a big farm!
A farm?
Yeah.
A big one!
And then I'm going to make some
good rice and eat it all.
That's wonderful!
When your job, for so long, is just
running things from one place to another,
you want to create something yourself.
That helps a lot.
Thank you!
Kureha-chan is making
lunch in the cafeteria.
If you'd like, you can
have my portion.
I'm sure she'd be happy to see you.
Roger.
They're getting ready
for the festival!
Are you OK, Kanata-san?
Yumina-san...
You scared me.
You were headed straight
for that pillar...
I just learned to drive.
It's still hard.
You need to stay focused
on the road.
Right.
Mishio-san asked you?
Yeah.
She asked what my dream is,
but I couldn't answer her.
I think I know why she
asked you that-
Look ahead!
Ahead!
Kanata-san!
Yumina-san!
Kanata-san, are we gonna be OK?! Are we?!
Yumina-san! I don't think we are!
We're not OK!
Someone help!
All Gods, we offer thanks to you
for the fact that we're alive.
These are called "ema."
The priest told us about them.
In this land, they're an old tradition.
You write a wish, and
the Gods will hear it.
And we all decided to do it, along with
the water-throwing festival this year.
There it is!
This is Seiya-san's.
To marry Kanata-neechan...
Um...
What do you think?
I'm honored...
Seiya-san will be disappointed that he
doesn't live up to your standards.
No!
I've never even thought about marriage
or anything like that!
Then Mishio-san will be relieved.
Can't you tell?
She really likes Seiya-san.
I think that's why she asked
you about your dream.
Cute, huh?
I see.
Everyone has dreams.
It's kind of nice.
Would you like to write one, too?
Do you have a dream?
Well, I serve the Gods...
But if I were ever to
leave their service,
I'd like to be a tailor!
For clothes?
Yes!
I want to make pretty
clothes, in all colors!
Soft, fluffy dresses...
Ones that make you feel wonderful
just by wearing them!
I think you're in the right
profession now...
Nothing!
It's wonderful to have
a dream, isn't it?
Yes!
Wonderful dreams, huh?
Oh, my. Kanata-chan!
Maria-san.
Rio left for the glass factory.
You're looking for her, too?
The boss said her request is ready,
and to deliver it to her.
Maria-san... Why do you work
at the glass factory?
My dream is to make something as good
as the boss makes, and sell it here!
Not happening.
I'm not putting out the works of the
daughter who left me behind.
That's awful, Mom.
You decided to go with
that dork, right?
Call me Naomi-san or "Miss."
Umm... Mom... Go with?
You didn't know?
The boss and Naomi-san
used to be married.
The errors of youth...
And I'm the fruit of their love!
Maria
See?
Here's the proof.
Why did you split up?
That's a hard question
to answer, you know.
I'm sorry!
Well, I guess we just had
different dreams.
Maria
This shop was everything to me,
and he had his glasswork.
Neither of us could give those up.
We were young... Both of us.
So I was the result.
OK, be careful.
Don't get distracted by the scenery
and take your eyes off the road.
Right.
OK, take care of this
for me, would you?
What is it?
A necklace.
For the Flame Maidens.
But that's odd...
I should have passed
her at some point.
Kanata, Rio might have stopped midway
to think about something.
Watch the sides of the road, too.
Maybe I didn't need to say that.
So, someone from the Fortress will
be a Flame Maiden this year again?
Seems so.
I see...
You heard from Kanata and them, right?
About the Roman version of
the Flame Maiden legend
that that Aisha girl
was talking about.
It was bothering me,
so I looked it up.
And it looks like the version
in Rome is closer
to the original version
of the legend.
The mourning festival
held by the people
who had driven them
to their deaths
eventually became a lovely
story of self-sacrifice.
And that's...
The truth behind the water-throwing
festival?
Kanata...
Rio-sempai, I found you!
I see.
I'm sorry...
I was thinking.
About the Flame Maidens?
Did Naomi tell you?
Yes.
What did you think?
I've been hearing about people's
dreams all day.
They all had wonderful dreams.
And so I think...
I don't know what really happened,
all that time ago.
But if it's thanks to the Flame Maidens
that the town's here,
and that everyone
has their dreams,
then that's a wonderful thing.
And even if the people of the
town don't know the truth,
on some level, they realize it.
So they observe the festival
out of thanks and as an apology.
Dreams, huh?
That's right.
The past shapes the present.
And because we have the present,
we can dream, believing
in the future.
Tomorrow, huh?
Oh, right!
I've got something else for you.
Here.
This is...
Claus-san needs you to sign for it,
or he can't go home.
I see.
Sorry for the trouble.
You really are a princess,
aren't you?
A letter from the Emperor, huh?
It's wonderful.
Hey, Kanata.
The world is ending.
Have you heard about it?
A little...
But the wars don't stop.
Rome and Helvetia may
be at peace for now.
But Galia and Frank, who share
a border with Rome...
and Gen, the superpower
to the west...
Even as we speak, most
countries are fighting.
Fighting over the small bit
of land left to humanity,
shaving away at what's
left of the population!
Small bit of land?
What's this?
You've never seen one
before, have you?
It's a world map.
It was made in Rome.
There are a lot of unexplored areas,
or areas where people can't go.
So it's very speculative, but...
This is Helvetia.
It's so small!
But most of this big continent,
which used to be called Eurasia,
is now a dead zone, No Man's Land.
And...
the No Man's Land
keeps expanding.
Out here on the borderlands
of Seize, it's still OK.
But the northern part of Rome
is being devoured by desert.
They say it won't be long before
it engulfs all of Rome.
I went to Rome, prepared
to marry,
and I saw for myself...
The world is truly ending.
We need to stop the fighting,
as soon as we can...
Before the world ends.
Is that your dream, then?
To make a peaceful world?
No.
This is...
Yeah, the way Mishio
put it, it's a goal.
Then what's your dream?
Do you want to know?
All set!
Roger!
Noël-chan.
Roger.
It's really floating...
Looks like it worked.
Good work, Noël-chan.
Wow...
It's so amazing!
Look, sempai!
The Takemikazuchi
is so small now!
The town!
This is the first step to my dream.
When I was young, my
mom told me this:
At the ends of the Earth,
there's a reborn sea that's
birthing new life.
I want to search for it.
This balloon's the first step.
Next, I'm going to bring
back airplanes.
Machines that let people fly,
like birds, through the sky.
And then, I'm going to the ends
of the Earth and beyond!
Beyond the ends of the Earth...
It's still a dream.
It's still far-off.
But someday, I'll make it
more than just a dream.
I'll make it reality.
OK. Let's decide this year's
Flame Maiden.
No drawing lots this year!
Why?
'Cause last year...
What's wrong?
Then let's do it by rock-paper-scissors.
One round.
Let me introduce you to...
It looks great, Kana-chan!
Really?
OK, let's finish you up.
It's been exactly one year
since you came here.
It's gone by fast.
Rio-sempai. I've decided
on my dream.
Can I follow you, always?
I want to share your dream.
Yeah, that's fine.
Thank you!
She'll follow my dream, huh?
Oh, right.
I wrote one of these.
Can I see it?
Whatever.
I want to be a military doctor
and save lots of lives.
Once, my dream
was my sister.
But now...
That's wonderful!
My mom was a medic,
but when Aisha was shot...
I'm her daughter, but I
couldn't do anything.
I hated it.
I'm sure you'll be able to do it!
Me, too.
A pretty bride...
It's OK!
I'm sure you'll be a
wonderful bride!
I'm sure there's a really strange guy
out there, and you're just his type!
I see...
I'm glad.
I'm going to follow
my own dream.
What did you write?
I wrote that I wanted to be
with everyone forever.
How normal...
That's awful!
So someday, you'll find your
dream and start to follow it.
Your dream...
And yours alone.
Until then, I'll take your
hand and lead you...
Until you find your own dream,
your own sound,
and begin to play it.
I can hear the footsteps of dreams
and the voices of the future.
Goodbye.
I'll always be here. So
wherever you are,
you have a place to return to.
Filicia...
Rio-sempai! Rio-sempai!
Let's go where
our dreams lead.
Even if the world
ends someday...
Our future will go on,
right until that fateful moment.