Juju Tsukuyomi
Oh? Lady Juju.
What are you staring at?
I got postcards from Sasami.
They look like photos from a trip.
Wow, it looks like she's been having-
...fun, you think?
I wouldn't know.
So this is the hotel Sasami has been staying in.
Papa-lin is here!
At the fingertip of God
My seasons are made
It's much longer than the starry sky
The song shakes up the sleep
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
It felt like my existence got wiped out
When I stood in the crowd covering my ears
To play what's in my heart
I'm not that mature to be able to select the noise
The flower that I found in the wilderness
It's scary yet gentle
The moment I touch it
Even the diorama could turn into reality
God drew the map for my future as a joke
Because the thousands of melodies echo
I destroy the tomorrow that's chasing me
The bond that cuddles under the starry sky
I saw the warmth
The bond that's born from the pain
That's the kind of bond I want to protect
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 11                                             Ganbaranai
"LOVE IS NOTHING BUT AN URBAN MYTH"
I'm hungry.
I felt like I ate because I shared senses with Tama,
but Tama is the only one who actually ate
and I haven't eaten anything.
Thank you for the food!
Oh yeah.
I need to go take a bath myself, too.
Now that the Dragon Vein that flows through
this island and my body have fused;
my body is now attuned as the divine spirit
that represents the nine-headed dragon.
All that's left for me to do is to save the energy
needed to resurrect the nine-headed dragon...
You're taking a morning bath, too, Edogawa?
Don't tell me you've already sniffed out my plot, Sasami!
But you're too late!
The ceremony is already under way!
All you can do is to wait!
What? You shut up! What else could it be?
She's my enemy!
She must be trying to make me lower my guard
so that she can interfere with my plot!
Edogawa...
So you don't have that thing on you right now.
Who cares about stuff like that?
Oh, so you don't care...
What's up?
WHAT'S UP?
"Tsurugi-chan" has entered the chat room.
TSURUGI-CHAN HAS
ENTERED THE CHAT ROOM.
Good morning, Tsurugi.
GOOD MORNING, TSURUGI.
AH~~~!
What are you doing naked?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING NAKED?
YOU'D BETTER NOT HAVE DONE
You'd better not have done
a sex scene while I was sleeping!
A SEX SCENE WHILE I WAS SLEEPING!
I won't be able to complete the CG!
I WON'T BE ABLE TO
COMPLETE THE CG!
But this is not a game...
Anyway, what happened to you?
ANYWAY, WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
Where's Tama?
WHERE'S TAMA?
Huh? Oh, I get it.
HUH?
OH, I GET IT.
DID YOU CALL ME?
Did you call me?
"tama" HAS ENTERED THE CHAT ROOM.
"tama" has entered the chat room.
Never mind.
NEVER MIND.
I figured that one out.
I FIGURED THAT ONE OUT.
So you go back to sleep.
SO YOU GO BACK TO SLEEP.
Okay.
OKAY.
Wake me up when it's time to eat.
WAKE ME UP WHEN
IT'S TIME TO EAT.
"tama" has left the chat room.
"tama" HAS LEFT THE CHAT ROOM.
Umm, Edogawa...
Since we're here together,
why don't we wash each other's backs?
What?
j@s*r/d&' IS THAT SOME KIND OF TRAP!!!?
What am I supposed to?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
Sasami is Tama Yagami.
SASAMI IS TAMA YAGAMI.
If I touch her carelessly I'm going to be consumed!
IF I TOUCH HER CARELESSLY
I'M GOING TO BE CONSUMED!
But nothing happened
BUT NOTHING HAPPENED
when you touched her yesterday.
WHEN YOU TOUCHED HER YESTERDAY.
You worry too much,
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH,
Milady.
MILADY.
Then why do we have to wash each other's backs?
THEN
WHY DO WE HAVE TO
WASH EACH OTHER'S BACKS?
Her motive is unclear!
HER MOTIVE IS UNCLEAR!
Hey, guys, you know you're hogging the room, right?
Who are you guys?
Th-this is not good!
TH-
THIS IS NOT GOOD!!
I posted the message in the wrong chat room!
I POSTED THE MESSAGE
IN THE WRONG CHAT ROOM!!
Delete the message and log out!
DELETE THE MESSAGE AND LOG OUT!!!
Jou has left the chat room.
"JOU" HAS LEFT THE CHAT ROOM.
"KITSUNE-CHAN" HAS LEFT THE CHAT ROOM.
Kitsune-chan has left the chat room.
Komori has left the chat room.
"KOMORI" HAS LEFT THE CHAT ROOM.
I don't really know what's going on.
I'm going back to sleep.
Umm...
Th-this is not good!
Y-you were talking about
washing each other's backs, right?
Fine! I'll challenge you head-on!
I'm able to consume my opponent if I need to.
So the odds are even for us!
It's a eat-or-be-eaten backwashing showdown!
No, you don't have to be that prepared to do this...
I guess Sasami is slowly getting better
at interacting with others. That's good.
Yawn... What's going on so early in the morning?
"Kagamin" has entered the chat room.
"KAGAMIN" HAS ENTERED THE CHAT ROOM.
Let's do this!
Okay, I'll start first.
She went first...
Wow, you're so beautiful, Edogawa.
Those pop idols have nothing on you!
Who cares about my appearance?
Strength is the real issue.
How strong you are is all that matters.
But I'm not strong.
BUT...
...I'M NOT STRONG.
My hair is unruly
MY HAIR IS UNRULY...
and my chest is flat...
AND MY CHEST IS FLAT...
Edogawa...
EDOGAWA, YOU MAKE ME...
...you make me envious.
...ENVIOUS.
You're modest, aren't you? But you're annoying.
It's like you're complaining about what you have
and wanting what you don't have.
I don't quite get it, but I guess you're right.
I should complain after trying my best at least, huh?
I'm sure you put a lot of effort into it, too.
That's right! In order to outdo you guys,
I went through bloody hell.
That's incredible, Edogawa. I'm impressed.
Having fun already this early in the morning?
Good morning, Kagami!
GOOD MORNING, KAGAMI.
You know,
YOU KNOW,
I think I'm going to have a new friend!
I THINK I'M GOING TO
HAVE A NEW FRIEND!
That's great.
THAT'S GREAT.
This is the first time I've talked to
a classmate for this long. I'm excited!
That's great.
THAT'S GREAT.
Maybe my communication skills have improved!
That's great.
THAT'S GREAT.
Thank you, Kagami.
So she's your first friend.
SO SHE'S YOUR FIRST FRIEND.
No way.
NO WAY.
You're my first friend, Kagami.
YOU'RE MY FIRST FRIEND, KAGAMI.
But I was just a stepping stone.
BUT I WAS JUST A STEPPING STONE.
I was a demo.
I WAS A DEMO.
What?
I guess I'd better stop ruining the happy moment for you.
I don't want to be a fifth wheel.
FIFTH WHEEL
Let me get out of here.
GET OUT OF HERE
Kagami?
KAGAMI?
What's the matter?
What? Oh, it's nothing.
You can be so subservient, but I think you
should behave more confidently.
You should be more positive
even if you're not feeling that way.
What?
It's irritating to watch you.
You're my enemy, so I don't want to
see that puny look on your face!
Thanks. You're so sweet, Edogawa.
Wh-who are you calling sweet?!
I-I'm the greatest villain of the century and...!
If you don't mind, can we exchange
cell phone numbers later?
What? Why?!
You don't have to if you don't want to.
Am I being annoying?
Fine. That's no big deal.
Thanks, Edogawa.
I...
I just want to be friends with you, Edogawa.
FESTIVAL
She looks like she's having fun in this photo.
Right. She should enjoy her youth
while I'm holding the power of God.
Oh?
It's too bad that there are no girls in swimsuits,
but this is very nice and relaxing,
unlike those crowded public beaches.
I wish Tsukuyomi was here with us, too...
Sasami-san
I see what you're doing, Sasami!
You're plotting to attack me when I'm in my swimsuit,
when I'm at my most vulnerable!
I expect nothing less from my archenemy!
"Attack you"? This is a beach volleyball game.
You must be trying to lower my guard
so you can launch an attack on me!
But I, Jou Edogawa, have no blind spot!
Oh, that's Big Sister Kagami, I mean, my Onee-sama!
Is it okay to ask her to join us?
So you're calling for backup? What a coward you are!
Fine. I'll knock both of you down!
Hey, Kagami, why don't we play beach volley ball?
No thank you. I don't want to ruin the fun.
You won't. I'm sure it's going to be fun.
It's okay. I'd rather focus on building a castle.
Okay.
See you later then.
I'm still weak on the defense.
What kind of trip is this?
How would I know that?
HIGH QUALITY
ROOM-DRIED
SEAWEED
Oh, Sasami. I've missed you so much.
HIGH QUALITY
ROOM-DRIED
SEAWEED
Everything's going to be okay now that I'm here.
RESTAURANT
Don't worry about eating, bathing and all
the things that you can't tell others about.
BATH
WOMEN
STAFF ONLY
KEEP OUT
I'm on Papa-lin's lap! I'm on Papa-lin's lap!
HEY, TAMA!
Hey, Tama!
It's not "Papa-lin",
IT'S NOT PAPA-LIN,
it's "Big Brother"!
IT'S 'BIG BROTHER'!
Besides, I don't cuddle with him
BESIDES, I DON'T CUDDLE WITH HIM
or let him hold me.
OR LET HIM HOLD ME.
You need to do a better job
at pretending to be me!
YOU NEED TO DO A BETTER JOB
AT PRETENDING TO BE ME!
What?
WHAT?
But you always act like this, Mama-lin!
BUT YOU ALWAYS ACT LIKE THIS,
MAMA-LIN!
I love you, Big Brother!
Oh well...
OH WELL...
SHE'S JUST A KID.
...she's just a kid.
Hey, you're finally up, Tsukuyomi! Let's go to the festival.
Buy me some takoyaki, cotton candy
and all kinds of other stuff, Big Brother!
Is a festival going on?
It's the annual shrine festival.
It's believed that gods are enshrined
in everything in this country.
Even actions such as "eating" or "playing"
should be worshiped.
Let's go check it out, since we have to eat anyway!
Hey, you're going to be my wallet!
Oh yeah, the festival...
I want to go check it out with Edogawa.
What's going on?
What are you plotting?
Calm down a little.
CALM DOWN A LITTLE.
Edogawa!
You called me all the way out here. What do you want?
The ceremony is already in its final phase.
I see. If she creates a rift within what I've
cultivated so far, everything's going to fall apart.
She must've been waiting
for a perfect opportunity all along!
That's why she's never initiated any attack!
Most impressive, Sasami Tsukuyomi, my archenemy!
Umm, I don't really know what this means,
but do you have "Chuunibyo"?
Note: "Chuunibyo" = "Middle School Syndrome"; a syndrome afflicting middle
school students in about year two, causing them to act out delusions or fantasies.
Chuuni...?
She says, "Did she just say 'archenemy'?"
That's embarrassing coming from a high schooler!
"I bet she'll start talking about stuff like past lives,
abilities and organizations before you know it."
Are you talking about our organization?!
Have you already found out about it?!
Do you really have an organization?
How much insight do you have into our plot?
More importantly, Edogawa...
"Do you want to go to the festival with me?"
Hey, Awashima!
Tell me what's going on? Explain it to me!
You're overreacting.
YOU'RE OVERREACTING
I don't feel any ill intent coming from Sasami.
I DON'T FEEL ANY ILL INTENT
COMING FROM SASAMI.
I think she's genuinely trying
I THINK SHE'S GENUINELY TRYING
to be close to you.
TO BE CLOSE TO YOU.
I'm ready over here.
Okay, I get it.
So you want to become close to me?
What? Yes!
I finally realized it. I'm sorry...
As your superior, I needed to be cautious.
Okay. So you're my friend now, Edogawa!
You must want to be my servant, right?
WHAAAAAAAAT
What?!
That was totally unexpected!
Well, umm...
The fact that you're my archenemy
must've complicated things.
You've been sucking up to me simply because
you wanted to be my servant.
Well, umm...
To Milady, there are only two categories of
people: either her enemies or servants.
What? Isn't that a logical interpretation?
I think Sasami wants to be equal with you and
have a closer and deeper relationship with you.
I see... I didn't know that.
But now I can see everything crystal clear.
You began approaching me
after my body turned male.
So basically you fell in love with me.
What?!
That was a drastic turn of events!
What? What?
Everything makes sense!
That's a little problem, but it's not bad
being liked by someone.
Calm down, Milady! You're way off now!
Shut up!
So you like me, don't you?
Y-yes. I like you, Edogawa. We're friends now-
Don't you call me "Edogawa"!
If you like me, you will address me in a different way,
such as Queen or Master or whatever.
What? Well then...
Can I call you "Jou-chan"?
This is so stupid.
THIS IS SO STUPID.
Where are you going, Kagami?
Let's go check out the festival together.
But you tend to depend on me when I'm around you.
BUT YOU TEND TO DEPEND ON ME
WHEN I'M AROUND YOU.
What?
WHAT?
SHE'S A FRIEND YOU DISCOVERED
ON YOUR OWN.
She's a friend you discovered on your own.
I want to see you be closer to her on your own, too.
Kagami...
I wish you happiness, Sasami.
Kagami!
Big Sister Kagami!
Hey, what's going on?
Big Sister Kagami... Big Sister Kagami!
Just explain what's going on!
You're going to be my servant, aren't you?
I'm really sorry, Edogawa.
I've got to go. I'll call you later.
Hey, you wait a minute, Sasami!
I don't care! You don't have to come!
Tama, hurry!
TAMA, HURRY!
Okay!
OKAY!
There she is!
Kagami?
Please don't look.
What's the matter?
Tell me what happened?
Kagami.
Kagami...?
I'm being strange.
I should be happy and supportive,
but when I see you trying to
be close to Edogawa...
I don't even know what it is myself...
Someone who means a lot to me
is about to make a friend.
She's trying to make her
wish come true and be happy...
But I can't support her... I must be broken somewhere.
I'm a robot. When I'm out of order,
I shouldn't be around humans.
Kagami...
You're no robot, Kagami.
You don't have to support me,
but I want you to be by my side.
You're human. You're so much
more of a human girl than anyone.
That's why you were hurt, and I'm the one who hurt you.
So I need to apologize to you.
Don't cry, Kagami. I'm sorry.
Right now, Edogawa means more to you than I do.
You're silly. You're foolish.
Trust me.
TRUST ME.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH
No matter how much I change
I CHANGE
or who I come to associate with
OR WHO I COME TO
ASSOCIATE WITH
or what happens in the world
OR WHAT HAPPENS
IN THE WORLD
I...
I WILL ALWAYS
ADORE YOU, KAGAMI.
I... will always adore you, Kagami.
Not having you around
NOT HAVING YOU AROUND
is more painful than dying!
IS MORE PAINFUL THAN DYING!
You were making new friends, because I am lacking
in many ways, compared to humans.
But the thought of it made me feel so miserable
I just wanted to disappear.
There's something wrong with me. I'm broken.
I'm glad that you feel that way.
I'm glad to know that you were hurt
because of my actions.
You're so... cruel...
Everyone looks happy. I hope this lasts forever.
Right, Lady Juju?
What's that?
"Tsukuyomi Shrine Daily Duty Log, kept by Mitchan.
"Today was my birthday."
"Master gave me a collar. I guess
that was supposed to be my birthday gift.
"At first I thought, 'What is this old man thinking?'
because I thought it was meant for me to wear,
"but I realized that Master's name
was engraved on the collar.
"Then I saw Master, completely naked, acting like a dog.
"This indescribable feeling emerged
inside me and I blacked out...
"When I came to, Master was..."
I'm sorry!
WHERE IS HE?!
It's taking her way too long!
What is Sasami doing?
She said she was going to call me later!
But you told her that she didn't have to come.
BUT YOU TOLD HER THAT
SHE DIDN'T HAVE TO COME.
Are you feeling lonely, Milady?
I-I'm not lonely!
I just made a plan to meet up for a battle. That's all!
Sure, sure.
Wow, it's delicious!
What's going on, Tama?
What happened to pretending to be Sasami?
Mama-lin told me that she had exhausted
her spiritual powers so she wanted to take a break.
Big Sister Kagami, buy me that!
I was buying for you, pretending that you were Sasami.
Can you buy it for me please, Onee-sama?
Don't get carried away!
Why didn't it work?
Hey, fireworks...
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah...
It's beautiful.
Big Brother.
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Good night.
Now it's show time, everyone!
It's brought to you by our super idol Sasami!
Now enjoy her beautiful and lovely voice!
Sasami! Sasami! Sasami!
Sing it, girl!
You can do it, Mama-lin!
Hey, what's going on?
I already told you that I'm not going to sing!
Yawn! You wish that were the case!
The people higher up are seriously upset
so we really need you to sing it.
It wouldn't hurt to give it all you've got
just this once, would it?
All right, I'll do it! But I want you to sing with me, too!
Akiregao kimi ga warau
You look fed up, but still smiling
Nee issho ni kaerou
Hey, let's go home together!
Kikoeru yo
I can hear it
Kimi no koe ga
Your voice
Dokomade mo hibiku symphony
That's a symphony that echoes far away
Hikari sasu koi iro
Light shines on the love color
Zutto te wo tsunagou
I want to feel the press of your hand over mine
Kasanari au shintoatsu
Kanjitainda
For a long time
I can't do this anymore...
I'm not going to do my best anymore starting tomorrow.
You really did your best!
Next Episode
Preview
Ganbaranai
It's time for Ganbaranai@Drama.
@Drama
Recap from the previous episode.
Recap from the previous episode
All kinds of things happened.
What's going to happen to the two now?
Recap from the previous episode
All kinds of things happened.
What's going to happen to the two now?
We've been through a lot together, haven't we?
WE'VE BEEN
THROUGH
A LOT TOGETHER,
HAVEN'T WE?
Yeah, things do happen.
YEAH,
THINGS DO
HAPPEN.
To be continued...
To be
continued
Next Episode
Preview
Next episode preview.
Things will happen.
Things will
happen.
Things will happen all at once.
Things will
happen
all at once.
What's going to happen to the two now?
What's going to happen
to the two now?
Don't miss it.
Next time, final episode"
Next time,
Final Episode
"I won't do my best tomorrow, either"
I Won't Do My Best Tomorrow, Either