Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
That's where school uniforms come in!
Leave the curry to me!
Let's go visit Hanako!
It's funny how they get pulled in.
Oh, yes. I am going to be a zombie.
I will give her educational guidance!
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
How about a café?
And we can cosplay.
We could do a haunted house.
Or do fortune telling.
Oh, I like that.
All boring ideas.
Then, what do you think?
Huh?
You have some really amazing ideas, don't you?
Hm, a cat café...
...or something?
A cat café?
Well, a dog café is fine, too!
No, but I want it to be related to cats.
"Cultural Festival" "Panel Presentation"
Okay.
Present your ideas with decorations,
"Cultural Festival" "Panel Presentation"
material acquisition and production,
an ordering system if serving food, costume preparation,
"Cultural Festival" "Panel Presentation"
work shifts, and tear-down process.
All right, who has an idea to share?
"Curry Tastes Better on the Second Day"
"Cultural Festival" "Panel Presentation"
So, we have a panel presentation composed of cell phone pictures.
Any others?
We have to think of the whole layout, though...
Right?
Yeah...
That's too hard.
Here! Over here!
Odagiri?
A curry shop!
What?! That sounds like a lot of work...
This only happens once a year.
I want to do something cool!
Curry's easy to make.
"Curry shop"
Curry shop.
Will we have costumes?
It'd be a lot of work to make them.
That's where school uniforms come in!
Ordinary curry made by high school girls in
uniforms with aprons? That's worth something.
Recently, there are many cheap-looking,
mediocre costumes. They are common.
Ordinary uniforms! That's the
easiest and best way!
Oh, she's from the cake shop.
What?! No way. I'm just mistaken!
Oh, yeah!
Right? It's hard to make costumes.
If we're just wearing our uniforms...
I have an apron already.
Wait, is she in our class?
Huh?
Where did she go?
She's small and doesn't have curves,
so she didn't look out of place.
This is a nightmare. A daymare!
So, our class decided to do a curry shop.
Sonobe...
It's a good idea. A lot of people like curry,
and we can entice them with the smell.
Can't resist the smell!
It must be stressful since
you are class representative.
Not really.
Nishiyama was eager to help out with
decorations after I told her she's good at it.
Wow!
She's so easy to flatter, I feel sorry for her.
She likes to be in the limelight.
What is your class doing, Miss Yoko?
We are going to do a haunted house.
A haunted house?!
This is my first time. I wonder what it is like?
I-I'm not very good with those.
Futaba?
Oh, are you scared of ghosts and such?
It's not fair if you can't see or touch them.
And you can't punch them if you need to!
Oh, yes. I am going to be a zombie.
A zombie?!
Oh good. You can punch those.
I don't want to!
If we use our desks as tables, we should use
paper placemats so they don't get dirty.
Tablecloths are hard to clean,
so disposable placemats are easier.
I see! You're so smart.
I'm thankful there's somebody who will
step up to take the lead during these events.
I didn't expect people to be
so reluctant to work.
I'll call you Leader Nishikawa from now on.
No, stop!
In exchange, leave the curry to me!
"Stuffed Hut"
"Challenge Menu" "Pot of Curry"
The extra large challenge just happens to be curry.
Here you go.
Curry is just a drink! I won't lose!
Ready, go!
Okay, time's up!
I-I couldn't finish.
It's spicy! Way too spicy! It's impossible.
Hm, really? Somebody already finished
it yesterday, so I thought it was too easy.
What?!
"Thanks, Mr. Stuffed."
Her nerves are probably dead.
You can't eat the curry,
because it's too spicy? What a kid!
What?
I can handle spicy foods. And that's because
I'm an adult. I'm older than you!
Shoot!
You're the same.
What is this? It's way too spicy!
What? That's weird.
I'll have to rethink this one.
You couldn't finish, but since you're
both regulars, I'll give you half off.
Really?! This would be a waste,
so I'll take it to go!
Me, too!
"Cultur--"
So, I did lots of research yesterday.
You even took the pot?
If I add a few things, I might be
able to tone down the spiciness.
But, that curry's from yesterday.
Curry tastes better on the second day!
The cultural festival is still days away.
Well, I'll use Mr. Stuffed's flavor as reference
and make it from spices like real curry.
Oh, you don't have to do that.
We don't have a budget for it, and spices are
expensive. Let's go with store-bought roux.
Well, it's a cultural festival, so I guess
we'll go with the ordinary stuff.
People might think it's weird if
we serve something authentic.
"Curry"
Everybody will bring the cut
ingredients they're in charge of,
and we'll use disposable utensils. Then...
I can make curry, but I'm a little nervous,
since I haven't made large amounts at once.
Oh, go ask Odagiri for tips.
Hayama!
Do these decorations look okay?
Ask Nishiyama about decorations.
Nishiyama...
Preparing for the cultural
festival usually seems tough,
but those two have been unexpectedly
helpful, so things are okay.
Um...
You don't know how to prepare to be a monster?
Yes. My classmates seem to know,
but I am the only one...
I know. Why don't you ask Tsuji?
Tsuji is...
...very popular among my classmates.
She does remind me of a small animal.
What's wrong, Miss Yoko?
Did something happen?
Actually...
Then, let's go to the bathroom.
What? Why?!
Let's go visit Hanako!
Why are you referring to her like a friend?!
I'm not going. She's not there.
She's probably very busy.
But, if you're doing something after school,
you've got to see one of the seven wonders.
Where did you get that rule?!
No! I don't like scary things!
Because you can't eat them?
Even if I do like eating, that's not why!
Who is this Hanako?
What? You don't know?
You see, she haunts the bathroo--
Not listening! I'm not listening!
Are... they done?
She looks super interested!
Let us go! Let us try to see
if we can meet this Hanako.
I can't! No way, it's dangerous!
What if she drags you into the toilet?
I will give her educational guidance!
All right, let's go.
Yes, let us!
No!
--Okay, I'm going back to the classroom.
--Hey, w-wait.
E-Everybody's gone.
Wh-What should I do?
"Haunted House"
Maybe I should go back to the classroom, too.
Odagiri.
It's a high school girl ghost who's been
in second place for a thousand years
and has unfinished business in this world!
Wh-What? How rude!
You're in charge of the curry, right?
Come on and do your job!
Kondo is gone, too.
Where in the world did she go?
Kondo went with Miss Yoko
to visit Hanako in the bathroom.
What?! The Hanako from the bathroom?
What's the point of looking at that?
To give educational guidance?
They're up to something!
We have returned.
H-How was it?
Hmph, it's impossible to look
in every toilet in the school.
Yeah, it's too much work.
O-Oh yeah? I'm glad.
Miss Yoko, you'll be a zombie?
I am supposed to wear makeup and scare
the visitors, but I still do not know what to do.
Then, I realized that there is
a professional monster here.
How can I move stealthily like you?
I'm a human and move as I think a human would.
No! You are not a zombie, Miss Yoko!
And you'll be scaring people?
You're not that kind of character!
Your classmates don't understand you at all!
Does your homeroom teacher know about this?!
This must be what it means to be "monster parents,"
huh? We're not your parents, though.
But, I am looking forward to the
cultural festival. I will be going, too.
As am I!
Thank you both! Wait, you both come anyway!
Indeed.
Oh my, how scary.
By the way, Sonobe, I heard you snuck
into Class 3! Get on your knees!
"Cultural Festival"
We will now commence Central Girls'
High School's 32nd cultural festival!
"Beautiful Metamorphosis"
The theme is "Beautiful Metamorphosis."
Let's all do our best and make this
a wonderful day full of memories.
All right. The curry is ready.
Okay, let's do our best, everybody!
Okay!
Well, eating curry probably isn't
the first thing people do--
Two bowls, please!
What?!
Hm... Actually, make that three!
Already?!
I won't have energy unless I eat.
And it'll be good advertisement.
Welcome.
Would you like to have your fortune told?
What should we do?
Hm...
"Curry" "First year, Class 3"
Mm-mm! This is yummy! Plain delicious!
What a simple and gentle flavor! It tastes like
high school girls made it. So ordinary!
"Curry"
Welcome! We have curry made by high school girls!
This curry is made by high school girls?
"Curry"
I see. It's plain delicious!
Thank you very much!
Hey, so many people are here!
We can do better than this.
I'll go out to advertise.
Maybe Futaba can do that.
Leave it to me!
Yeah, I wouldn't want her to eat all the food.
A lot of people come to our
cultural festival, huh?
Yup.
"Curry"
All right! Let's attract some customers!
Hm?
Curry!
I think there's a place that's selling it!
Let's go see!
First year, Class 3's
homemade curry is that way.
It's plain delicious!
"Curry"
It's funny how they get pulled in.
They just keep getting pulled--
What?!
Wh-What's going on?
H-Huh?
Wh-What? What is it?
It already has a mosaic?!
I see. Miss Yoko, you were trying
to draw in customers, too.
It's a zombie. It's rotting.
You put way too much into
this for just a cultural festival.
Sonobe helped me with the makeup.
I tried out pastry shop techniques.
You tried out pastry shop techniques?
How long have you been there?
I do not know why, but whenever I go out
to advertise, people outright avoid me.
Commoners must shrink back in fear when
someone of Miss Yoko's rank speaks to them.
Oh, Yamaji!
I'm used to him popping up unexpectedly.
Therefore, do not fret about their reactions.
You think so?
No, I think it's because of the zombie makeup.
I see! They tremble with fear
because of your realistic acting!
Yup, I get it. You should get your ears checked.
So, how is the haunted house going?
It is surprisingly lively. I have not
been that involved, though.
I refuse to go through the haunted house.
It's made by high schoolers,
so it's probably fine.
Oh, yeah. Maybe even I can do this.
Let's go in!
Mua ha, ha. You've entered, Futaba Odagiri.
I'll scare you and avenge my brother.
Hey, it's darker than I expected.
I can't see.
Hey...
She's here!
Boo! Feel my vengeance!
I said, I can't see.
Oh, here's a flashlight.
--Right here...
--Where?
Hey, did you hear that scream?
It's here. It looks fun.
Okay, no pushing. Please line up
so you don't get hurt.
I ended up attracting customers here, too.
You're a huge help.
"Fried Octopus Balls"
"Rockin' Popcorn"
High school cultural festivals are great.
This cute cultural feel is the best!
Ms. Sonobe. Welcome!
So forceful.
Ah, er, I'm full.
It's fine. It's just juice!
Well, I guess if it's juice...
"Apple" "Orange" "Grape" "Fruit" "Oolong Tea" "Cider"
Let's see, I'll have...
I recommend the vegetable juice for you!
"Vegetable Juice"
You just look like someone who'd like it.
I give off that image?
Here you go! Free extra large for you.
Ah, it's about to spill.
Oh, are you going to see Teru?
Oh.
Take this to her, will you?
Is this some sort of trial? But, even if I've
gone bad, I must do this as former maid...
And this is for Yoko and Futaba.
I will not fail!
"Curry"
Hey, are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Haunted houses and stuff are just
not good. Not good at all.
The quality of Miss Yoko's
costume was just way too high.
I apologize, Futaba.
No! Don't come near me with that face!
Take that, Futaba Odagiri! I can't believe
you're scared of a haunted house!
H-Hey!
Boo! I'm a ghost. Feel my vengeance!
Ah, yes. You're trying very hard.
No! You're supposed to be scared!
Watch out!
Right there... are the...
...the remnants of what used to be a student!
Please, run away!
Oh, wait-- This is just vegetable juice...
Hey...
"Karaoke Battle"
♪ Sakura! That's the name of an angel! ♪
Please make sure to separate trash
and dispose of it in the marked areas.
"--Festival"
Students who are done cleaning,
please make your way home promptly.
Phew. The cultural festival is over.
Both the curry shop and haunted
house were a success. I'm glad.
Quite right. They will make great memories.
I was very anxious. I thought I would be
the only one who could not be of help.
However, everybody did have fun.
I had a lot of fun, too!
Miss Yoko.
That's great.
Yes!
By the way, Miss Yoko?
Yes?
When will you take that makeup off?
I have it on already, so I
will wait until I get home.
Wait, no! You should take it off. You'll get
arrested. They'll be after your head!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is
so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
"Personal opinion." "Not available on this site"
Yes, I have it everyday. I used to be worried about my dry hair.
Everything changed after I drank it! The world became brighter.
"Personal opinion." "Not available on this site"
It cleansed my ugly heart.
These are some of the great things people are saying about it.
"That Juice" "Made by Kou" "Indescribable flavor"