It's summer!
It's almost over.
It's the beach!
Sticky sea breeze.
Bright sunshine!
Skin-destroying ultraviolet rays.
Sexy yukatas at night.
Donating blood to the mosquitos.
N-new people to meet, heightened expectations!
Same old faces, different place.
Yummy food!
Cold noodles after heatstroke, or food poisoning from something else.
Do you hate summer, or just us?
I love them both.
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
oshitari? hiitari?
Pushing? Pulling?
sakusen!! doushiyou?!
Which strategy should I use?
oh! what a night! tomaranai
Oh, what a night! Don't let it end,
risou to mousou bousou BATORU
This out of control battle of dream and delusion
mekuru meku sekai jinsei kore deai
This amazing world!  For life to encounter this..
ikenai? demo mitai nee motto motto
I shouldn't, but I want to see!  It'll make me more and
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
More and more and more and more and
shichaundeshou?
More excited, won’t it?
iijan iijan iijan iijan isshoumon no yuujou
It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! Lifelong friendship!
HIIROO mitai ja nai kedo guttokichaimasu
He doesn't look like a hero, but he'll come running to
kimi boku dare? sore are kare dare de mo OK! donna basho de mo
You, Me, Who? This, that, him, whoever, OK! Wherever we are!
minna to ireba saikou no hoshi nan desu
If we’re together it’s the best planet ever!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
This sort of thing is nice once in a while.
We haven't done anything summer-esque.
The comic market is pretty summer-esque.
Not like that, but more under the sun, you know?
You can't do that.
Look, Sora-chan.
It's the ocean!  Wow!
Alright Kaneru-chan, but take your shoes off.
Wow, it's so nice!
It's rude to sit like that.
Look, there's a sea gull flying!
She's twenty four years old right?
Yes... it's not like we're here to play.
Seriously.
Huh, what'd you mean?
Huh?  Drawing camp?
Yup.
We came all the way to the beach to draw doujin?
There's a bright clear sky, just like you wanted.
Yes, but there's better things you can do under a blue sky!
Najimi, you're so perverted!
This isn't what you would call relaxation.
If you have any problems, talk to the mastermind.
Mastermind?
Justice!
Yaay, it's Justice!
Justice, are you crazy?
No worries, this suit is water-repellent and has excellent air flow.
That's not what I meant.
Your clothes are crazy too, but why do we have to draw doujin at the beach?
Najimi-san, think of it this way...
After basking in the sun, we let the stored solar power add an explosive dynamic to our art!
You sound like a Power Ranger, but I still don't get it.
Also, they say that seawater has the same salt concentration as amniotic fluid.
Is that so?
By placing yourself in a situation similar to your mother's womb,
you can add nostalgia to your work.
Why would an ero-manga need nostalgia?
Anyway, I'm not drawing.
I see.  That's a problem.
What?
Doujinshi spot sale opening?
Beauty Love-sensei and Nidou Kaneru-sensei's...
Limited edition original art sale...
That's amazing, Najimi-san, our mangas are being advertised!
The sales event starts two days from now!
There's no way we can do it!
Why did you advertise it already?
Hey!  How many of these did you give out?
Najimi-san, I've been waiting.
I've handed out flyers all the way to the next town. Five thousand of them.
I hope people show up.
We're going after her, Hoshi-kun!
Huh?  Right!
Now, you two. Just let out the overflowing freedom onto the paper at will.
Right.
I'm feeling entrapment more than freedom.
Don't worry, you'll be able to draw something amazing now that you're cornered.
With your back to the ocean, there's no place to run or hide.
I almost want to just throw myself in.
Najimi-san.
A-are you okay?
Yeah, they're fine.
I meant Hoshi-kun.
I'm alright... Beside the point,
Najimi-san, that outfit...
I thought it'd be a shame if I couldn't wear it after buying it, so...
Is it weird?
Absolutely not! You look excellent!
Thanks.
But Hoshi-kun, you don't have to work, you should go play.
Um, well... Yes, but...
Hoshi-kun is bound to Justice in servitude.
Well, umm... Yes.
Even when we went to the hotel for research...
I was hoping to make a move if the mood was right...
But in the end, the mood never was right!
Never was right! Never was right! Never was right!
I had to open my big mouth...
N-no!
Servitude...
Wow!
Justice!
Let's go swimming.
Sorry, Sora.
There's alot of customers at noon.
It'll slow down in the evening.
There's no reason to work at the seaside shop.
Then let's play, Najimi.
I'm way too pressured by the deadline to play right now.
Boo.
Want to play with me?
You can't!
Sora-chan, come play with me.
Nidou-san, you don't have time to play either.
Tsuyuri, will you play with Sora-
Not happening from the look of things...
I'm going to thoroughly examine the male figure at the beach.
You say that way too boldly...
That might actually be beneficial.
I'll leave her to you, then.
Okay. Come along, Sora-chan.
Ok!
Um, how about you go to the beach for a sketch too?
If you want, I'll model for you.
Do you think this is sharp enough?
I'll just go make some yakisoba...
Nidou-san, aren't you going to swim?
I can't swim.
B-but I'm vigilantly watching Sora-chan!
If something were to happen, you can't swim, right?
I'll shout for help.
Do your best.
Hey, Aiorusu...
Am I doing a good job as a guardian?
No! Aiorusu!
Ahh, so relaxing.
Tatami is best for japanese people.
They say ideas come when you change your surroundings.
What a lie.  I can't think of any stories.
How are you doing, Nidou-san?
The bath is ready.
Kaneru-chan!
The bath feels great.
Really?
So, you guys aren't fighting because you're in the same room, are you?
Of course not.
Hey, where's Justice and Hoshi-kun?
At the beach.
At the beach at night...
How bold...
I never thought I'd be sleeping here with you.
I thought I'd finally get to sleep in the same room as Najimi-san.
Ah, nothing.
I borrowed this car from my brother.
I see.
I'll have to send him my thanks.
Justice-san, you may meet my brother eventually.
What do you mean?
Him as the brother of the groom and you as a close friend of the bride.
Oh? What makes you so confident about that?
Y-youth, maybe?
Oh?
What's the problem?  Won't you accept it, already?
I've been suppressing things I shouldn't have to as a healthy man.
What is youth!?
Oh no, I stayed in there too long.
Terrifying is the lure of the hot spring.
Ah, Najimi-san, wear this instead of that yukata.
Well, I think I'll go with the yukata since we're here and all...
M-matching outfits?
Yup, I got it to show camaraderie for our combined effort.
N-no thanks.
But, I went to the trouble of buying them...
Doesn't it make you want to work?
I-I wonder...
Najimi.
Are you here to bother us?
Let's make a run to the store.
I need every minute I can get.
Go away, go away!
We won't have dinner tonight.
Justice cancelled dinner, saying it's a drawing camp.
That hasty guy...
Fine! I'm not going to die just because I didn't eat tonight.
No!  If I don't eat dinner... I... I...
Want some of my snack?
That's not enough.
Alright, alright.
We're coming right back after we get food, ok?
Yaay, food run!
Food run! Food run!
I'll borrow Hoshi-kun's car. We'll go by the train station.
Tsuyuri, you can drive?
Probably.
Hey!
Huh, they're both gone.
There they are.
Justice!
Hoshi-san.
What happened?
He was stung by a jellyfish, then partially drowned.
He isn't breathing.
What?  Leave it to me!
Thank goodness!
We were so worried.
N-Nidou-san...
Your nose is bleeding...
I-it's not what you think!
What's wrong, Nidou-san?
It's not what you think!
Hey, wait!
I'm sorry to trouble you all.
I can't believe you were the one who saved me.
What are you saying?
You're an important friend.
Then, about Najimi-san...
That's a seperate matter altogether.
You should rest in our room for a bit.
Oh, and can we borrow your car to go to the store?
Ah, Sure.
Go ahead.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you Junichirou's friend?
Yes. And you are?
Next time's a beach story, too!
Slip...
fushigi itsu no ma ni ka
It's strange
hajime no ippo fumidaseba
Before I noticed
maru de yosou gai de
After taking the first step, despite my predictions
iya mo iya mo suki ni naru
It might be icky, but I'm starting to like it,
hontou no watashi ga mezamechatta!?
Has the real me woken up?
mufufu miryoku kamo ne
Hah ha ha! It might be charming,
jinsei kake masshigura
To live life fast and free.
sora wa PINKU iro de
The sky has turned pink,
BURUMA mo BYUtto tonde iku
Even bloomers fly through the air,
mitaiken na ERIA saa susumou!!
An area I haven't experienced! Now, forward!
yume miru otome wa SUI SUI CHAO!
Girls who dream can do anything smoothly,
kewashii michi mo hiraoyogi
Swim through even the hardest path,
mizutamamoyou no ashita ni naare
Get used to a polka dot future,
dakara ganbaccha Oh!
So then, let's give it our all!
Next time: We've come so far, and now a mysterious new character.
We've come so far, and now a rather normal preview.