Bye bye!
It seems so sudden.
It seems like you only enrolled the other day.
You're becoming a second year already...
You're right.
And then, Run-chan will be in her third year.
Later.
Yeah.
Bye bye!
Tooru, are you up?
Yeah.
The new term starts today.
Don't be late.
I know.
I'm off.
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Alien
Good morning, Nagi.
Hey.
What's wrong, Nagi?
You seem down.
Last night, the sequel to a novel piqued my interest,
and I read it all night.
So, you didn't get enough sleep?
Don't stay up late, then.
No...
Actually, during that time, I ate two boxes of chocolate.
I currently hate myself.
You lost to the temptation of sweets!
I read until dawn recently, too.
That book called "In That Night".
Oh, that, so you read it!
Yeah.
It makes you cry, doesn't it?
Like, when one of the lovers died of an illness.
Didn't that make you cry?
Just thinking about it makes me want to cry.
I...
In That Night
I just started reading it...
I'm sorry...
Huh?
You're doing your homework now?
Oh, I couldn't finish it yesterday.
That's not like you.
I read a book all night.
The answer is "C".
No, "A", right?
This one is "B".
You're wrong; that's "D".
"B".
"D".
What's going on?
Are you done?
A little bit more, just a little bit more...
Oh, you...
This is a "3", right?
No, it's an "E".
Then, this is a "mu", right?
It's a "7".
You're reading it upside down.
TL Note: When you turn a 7 around, it looks like a katakana "mu".
Oh!
Did you finish your homework, Run-chan?
Don't worry.
I finished it during the break.
Run's talking to a boy.
Is Tooru going to get mad again?
Isn't it about time she appeared?
Should I go visit her and keep her pinned down?
Or should I just stop these two?
What is it, Yuuko?
English is hard!
Right now, Run is...!
Hey, Tooru.
What?
Right now, you know, it's a little...
Let me in.
I can't!
W-What are you doing?
No, I can't!
Tooru, you were here?
The coast is clear.
Never mind, Tooru.
Huh?
Hey, Tooru?
Dear third years,
please pay great attention to maintaining good health.
First and second years, be prepared to move up a grade level.
Listen to me!
If you don't pay attention,
the third term will be over before you know it.
Let's keep our minds focused during this time.
Hey, you there!
Are you talking to me?
Right.
Can I ask you to do something for me?
Please hand these out to everyone.
Sure.
But I have a question before I do that.
Hm, what?
What's my name?
Sensei... You can't possibly...
Right?
I'm in your homeroom class...
I'm sorry.
When you become an adult, you just become unable to remember certain things, sadly.
Kamade-sensei, that means you're a failure as a teacher!
Kitou-sensei!
Oh, how come?
Forgetting a student's name simply won't do!
I have all the students' faces and names,
and which class and year they attended, perfectly memorised.
Wow, that's quite a feat!
It's a given as a teacher.
You never know when one of your cute
students will come to you with a problem.
And when that happens, you can't ask, "Who are you?"
Kitou, Kitou, Kitou!
She got away because of you,
so you take these and hand them out.
Also, treat me to food on the way home.
I finally finished my homework thanks to you, Too-run.
Wasn't that supposed to be an answer check?
I'm guessing that you didn't do any of it yourself?
You're exactly right!
How did you know?
Oh, you...
You're going to be a second year soon! Pull yourself together.
The weather is fine again today!
Don't change the subject.
There's a cat up there.
I wonder if it's stuck.
I can't just leave it there.
I'll save it!
Yutaka.
Hey, don't do that.
It's dangerous!
I'm fine.
I may not look like it,
but tree-climbing is actually one of my strong points.
Just wait a little! I'm coming for you.
Just sit still...
Gotcha!
Uh...
They're mad!
I'm sorry.
I'll clean them up...
That's not the point!
What if you'd fallen?
Right!
You could've hurt yourself.
Too-run, Mipo-rin...
Why are you laughing?
But yeah, good job.
Yutaka did a great job, right?
I'm glad you're okay, too.
No, don't do that.
Don't lick me like that.
*Grind*
Stop playing around! Help us clean!
Tooru!
There you are!
Run-chan.
Will you be much longer?
You're done for today?
Yeah, I am.
Huh?
Look, there's a bunch of torn leaves in your hair.
I'll get them for you.
You don't have to.
I'll do it myself.
You don't have to be so reserved.
*Stare*
There you go.
You're all clean now.
Thanks...
What's up with you, Tooru?
Nothing, nothing at all.
A-Adorable...
New Year Burger
Limited-time offer!
Is something wrong, Tooru?
If you don't hurry, it'll get cold.
This Durian Burger is delicious.
Surprisingly, it is.
Tooru, you've got ketchup on you.
On the side of your mouth.
Hm, you're right.
Thanks.
You got some too.
Here.
I bit my tongue...
Is it blood or just ketchup?
Hey guys, sorry to have kept you waiting.
Sorry for taking so long.
A foreigner just asked us for directions.
We somehow managed to tell him, but...
What language is that?
Is she testing me?
She bit her tongue a minute ago.
Look, I'm currently collecting points.
I want some of the merchandise you can get here.
Oh, that.
And I thought, if you didn't need yours,
I'd like you to help me out.
Take mine.
Thank you, Tooru.
Thank you too, Run.
I'm not collecting them either, so I'll help you, too.
For real?
I'm glad!
So, what are you trying to get?
A key ring with a plush bear on it.
It's cute.
Sure...
I need to use the bathroom.
Yeah.
Speaking of which, how many more points does she need?
Ow...
White is trying too hard.
One point.
The lace is cute.
Two points.
That person threw his points away!
It's such a waste, but it's in the trash can.
I can't just pull it out.
I've got it!
If I stay here,
maybe I can get them from people who throw them away!
Yuuko is taking her time.
What's she up to?
I don't need the points, so if you'd like...
Thank you.
There seem to be a lot of people who don't collect them.
That way she'll have enough in no time.
She'll be surprised when she returns.
Excuse me, are you collecting these point cards?
Yes.
Why?
Why isn't anyone throwing their point cards away?
Limited time...
It's a Durian Burger!
It's a limited-time offer!
Let's get some!
Not today.
Why?
You have to do your homework, right?
Limited time...
This is the one you wanted.
Thank you.
Please come again.
How did it go?
I got it.
Good for you, Yuuko-chan.
Yeah, thank you.
I got them together in no time at all. Incredible!
Ta-da.
Cute, no?
You're a sucker for cute stuff, Yuuko.
It's fine.
Cute stuff is cute.
It's done!
What?
It's an origami crane.
Tiny, isn't it?
It's so small, I can hardly make it out.
That's unfair, Nagi-chan.
Lend me your magnifying glass.
I don't have such a thing.
What about the thing on your face?
Do you even understand the purpose of glasses?
Here you go.
Thank you.
So, you gave them to her after all.
It's fine. I don't mind.
Run, is your head all right?
That's a Nagi impression.
If you don't need them, give them back.
Weren't you going to use them as a magnifying glass?
I have no choice then.
Hey, Nagi, you're shrinking!
Wow, you're small!
Yeah, so are your eyes.
Also, your impression earlier wasn't like me at all.
You think so?
Can you do any better, Nagi?
I want to see that.
Try an impression.
I usually don't show this to people...
Nagi-chan, magnifying glasses suit you well!
Look!
You said you don't want to show it to people.
That's not what I meant!
Then do it again!
I want to see it again, too.
I can't do it again!
This time, I'll watch, too.
I don't care!
Nagi-chan is upset!
Sorry, but your impression was really close.
Yeah, really close!
You didn't even see it.
How about this place?
They're selling a limited-time Durian Burger.
See?
No, no way.
These kinds of places are no good,
because the students frequent them.
You're right, because it's a limited-time offer.
That won't do!
Buying food on the way home from
school is the first step to delinquency!
I have to go stop them!
It's all right.
But!
So we're looking for another place.
Yeah, yeah, you sure work people hard.
Wait a minute, this isn't over-
Speaking of which, isn't there a more high-class place for adults?
Really?
I like it.
Your treat?
Kitou's.
Wait a second!
We're splitting the bill!
So you see, that diet is pretty bad.
Really?
I believed it, too.
Right?
I was surprised, too.
So I changed to another diet.
Should you be eating fries?
These are fine! It's all calculated.
Really?
Tooru?
Are you sleepy?
Nah, I'm fine.
It's already this late.
We talked too much.
Should we head out?
Yeah.
Yeah, let's go home...
...to space!
You're spouting nonsense again.
Actually... I'm an alien!
Nagi is going to retort...
I knew it!
I always wondered if you actually were one.
It makes sense.
You eat and don't get fat.
Sometimes you fly through the sky, too.
moshika moshika shitara kiita koto nai?
Maybe, just maybe, you might have heard of it?
Run-chan.
omoudake soradake suujichaundasu
Just by thinking, your thoughts are understood.
sore wa nani nanikato kikare tara sou
What's that, what is it, you ask, and...
kotaewatada hitotsu oshieteageru
There's only one answer, and I'll tell you what.
See you, Run.
uinku hitotsu
With a wink,
Take care of yourself.
handemo fuwafuwa
everything's fluffy.
Yeah.
See you later, guys!
fushigi na koto bakari yo
It's a heap of mysteries.
Run-chan, wait!
Yeah.
Bye bye.
uchuu no shinpi terepashiine
A mystery of space, it's telepathy.
The food on Earth is really good.
donna koto datte o mitoushi
You know everything,
What do you eat in space?
demodemo  kiwotsukete
but please watch out.
Space food!
I see.
ima wa himitsu no mama de ahan
Because, it needs to stay a secret for now.
That's an Earth product!
Run-chan!
Ah, you woke up.
You were fast asleep.
A dream?
Indeed.
Next stop, your place.
Sorry.
And thank you.
Never mind.
I'll get going, then.
But not into space, right?
It's rare for you to tell a joke.
Later.
Yeah.
Bye bye.
Are they going to graduate like that?
Are you going somewhere?
To the convenience store.
It's dark outside.
Be careful.
Yeah.
I can't help this gloomy feeling,
so I'm going to get something sweet to cheer me up.
Run-chan?
Tooru!
Run-chan.
What is it, Tooru?
Run-chan...
You'll never change, will you?!
Never!
yume to harukaze no kagaku
夢と春風の化学
The chemistry of dreams and a spring breeze...
tomaranai yokan
止まらない予感
An irrepressible premonition.
Lucky Happy kono yubi ni tomare
Lucky Happy この指に止まれ
Lucky, Happy, stop at this finger.
itsumo kashimashiku hashiru sono saki wa
いつもかしましく走る　その先は
Were we always running so wildly?
wakaranai
わからない
I don't know,
kedo sore ga ii ne
けどそれがいいね
but that's fine,
hajimaru yo
始まるよ
it's the beginning.
honpou my pace
奔放　マイペース
Wild, at my own pace,
jugyou chuu wa gahaku
授業中は画伯
and artistic during class,
kirehashi ni wa keikaku
切れ端には計画
scribbling plans on scraps of paper.
doko ni ikou
どこに行こう
Where are we going?
kitto ima ga paradise
きっと今がパラダイス
This right now is paradise.
neji maki sugi no munasawagi
ネジ巻きすぎの　胸騒ぎ
An overly wound-up uneasiness.
yakusoku wa chikoku
約束は遅刻
I get there later than promised,
da kedo douchaku
だけど同着
but we still arrive at the same time.
skirt no stage wa
スカートのステージは
Upon the stage that our skirts dance,
donna hibi ni naru no?
どんな日々になるの?
what kinds of days will unfold?
yume to harukaze no kagaku
夢と春風の化学
The chemistry of dreams and a spring breeze...
tomaranai yokan
止まらない予感
An irrepressible premonition.
Lucky Happy kono yubi ni tomare
Lucky Happy この指に止まれ
Lucky, Happy, stop at this finger.
itsumo kashimashiku hashiru sono saki wa
いつもかしましく走る　その先は
Were we always running so wildly?
wakaranai
わからない
I don't know,
kedo sore ga ii ne
けどそれがいいね
but that's fine,
hajimaru yo
始まるよ
it's the beginning.
Tooru!
You took so long.
I got tired of waiting.
Now, let's get home quickly.
Here we go!
Nagi
Yuuko
Run
Tooru
Bye Bye!