The treacherous sunset wipes away those annoying sweat drops.
As if it wanted to tear it apart,
the machine roars as if it's singing a song.
Selty
Sturluson
The quiet fairy is over here.
Yagiri
Seiji
Atonement is a piece of a broken love.
Yagiri
Namie
The morning sun rises, yeah!
Heiwajima Shizuo
Over the valley of buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't be meaningless.
Erika
Karisawa
The morning sun rises, yeah!
Yumasaki
Walker
Kyohei
Kadota
Coming out of the darkness!
As long as you feel it now,
Togusa
Saburo
you'll see that dream isn't meaningless.
There's surely something only we can see.
Mikado
Ryuugamine
Something that no one will snatch away from us.
Masaomi
Kida
The fact that this aim isn't meaningless!
Anri
Sonohara
The sun rises, yeah!
Brezhnev
Simon
Over the horizon, oh!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
that light won't be meaningless.
When I think about it, it seemed like a miracle.
But, when I look back on it some more it doesn't seem all that miraculous.
Regardless, I knew my life would never be the same.
Though in reality, nothing changed at all.
It was a very, very weird event.
Then again, weird things like that could've happened to anyone.
Here in Ikebukuro...
First
Words
I-I'm sorry...
I want to go home.
I don't want you to laugh at me, but...
In both elementary and middle school, I stayed home from field trips.
Later!
Yet, here I am, a fifteen year old boy who's on his first trip to Tokyo, who has never left his hometown before.
That's me, Ryuugamine Mikado.
I bet you'd like to know why I'm standing here like a deer in the headlights in front of the Toubu-Toujo line.
Well you see the reason is that in April, I'll be starting class at Raira Academy, in East Ikebukuro.
Academically it's slightly higher than normal schools, the campus is pretty, and it has all the facilities you'll need.
The main reason I'm going is because a friend of mine from elementary school invited me.
My parents wanted me to attend school that was close to home, but...
I've always wanted to see Tokyo.
Mikado!
Huh?
Kida-kun?
Was that a guess?
I'll give you three choices!
One! Kida Masaomi!
Two! Kida Masaomi!
Three! Kida Masaomi!
Kida-kun! Is it really you?
Are you just going to ignore the joke I spent three years coming up with?
Long time no see!
You look completely different! I was shocked!
I never thought you'd dye your hair.
And your joke sucked.
It's been four years, after all.
Come to think of it, you haven't changed a bit since elementary school.
Also, don't hate on my jokes.
Yes. This is my best friend, Kida Masaomi.
I haven't seen him since he moved away while we were in elementary school,
aside from his looks, nothing's changed.
OK, let's go!
Let's get out of this station.
Today, I feel like going west!
You might think we're going to take the west exit, but we're actually taking the Seibu exit...
His jokes suck, but he's a good guy.
We chatted online every day,
so I never ever realized how far apart we were or how long it's been since we've seen one another.
Hey, do you know what the difference between the west exit and the Seibu exit is?
But after meeting him for the first time in four years, it really feels like we've been living apart.
In Ikebukuro, the Tobu Department Store is on the west side,
and the Seibu Department Store is on the east side.
Dammit... Why am I explaining a missed joke?
But inside, he hasn't changed at all, especially his terrible jokes.
Ah, whatever.
Is there any place you want to check out?
Hmm... Sunshine 60, maybe?
Right now? That's the place to take your girlfriend, not another man.
Th-Then, what about Ikebukuro West Gate Park?
Just call it Nishiguchi Park like everyone else.
But I thought Ikebukuroans called it that...
What the hell is an Ikebukuroan?
What? You really want to go?
No, but...
H-Hold on!
Stop it!
It's already nighttime!
The Color Gangs will kill us!
I don't even think I can take you seriously when you say it like that.
Besides, it's only 6 o'clock.
I see you're still the same chicken you always were.
--  Tanaka Taro has joined the chat.
Good evening
'Evening.
--  Tanaka Taro has joined the chat.
Hey, Setton-san.
I'll actually be living in Ikebukuro, starting tomorrow.
Oh, really?
You might end up living near me, then.
Maybe so.
I'm still at home right now,
but starting tomorrow, I'll be living in an apartment near Sunshine.
Welcome to Ikebukuro.
Amazing...
This is a world that I've only seen in manga and on the internet.
It's more amazing than Kamisakuramachi-Ginza.
Then I'll take you to Shibuya some time.
Or, if you like crowds, maybe you'd prefer a horse track.
Lately, the Color Gangs haven't been very active.
There were a lot of really flashy ones around last year,
but they picked a fight with Saitama, and a big group of them got arrested.
Ever since then, if you get a bunch of people wearing the same color clothes in one place,
the police are on them like white on rice.
Then, Ikebukuro's safe now?
I don't really know too many details myself, so don't take everything I say on the matter seriously,
but there are lots of other dangerous people around. Be careful.
Is that so...?
By the way, this is 60th Street. There's another road called Sunshine Street.
They most likely made Sunshine Street first.
S-Sorry!
Oh, it's Kida-kun.
Hey, Karisawa-san and Yumasaki-san. Yo!
Long time no see.
Yo.
How's it goin', Kida?
I haven't heard from you in a while!
Who's this kid? A friend of yours?
Yeah, this is an old friend of mine. He just moved to Ikebukuro today.
Ah, is that so...?
This is Karisawa-san.
And this is Yumasaki-san.
Over there are Kadota-san and Togusa-san.
U-Um, my name is Ryuugamine Mikado.
Did I say something bad?
A pen name?
Why would a high schooler have a pen name?
Oh, maybe he's on the radio or writes for some magazine?
U-Um, it's actually my real name.
No way! It's your real name?
Wow, what a cool name!
Like the main character of a manga series!
Aw, you're embarrassing me!
What should I do? I'm completely lost in this conversation.
Were you guys out shopping?
Yup.
Dengeki Bunko just released their latest publishing run. I picked up thirty copies or so.
Dengeki Bunko puts out thirty books a month?
No, of course not!
One each for him and me, and then, oh... Ten more for other stuff.
"Other" stuff.
What do they mean by "other" stuff?
Like a copy to keep, or a copy for work, or a copy just to look at or something?
Well, we've gotta get ready to go.
See you guys next time!
Yeah, later.
Oh, hold that by her head.
Later.
Hey! Don't let it bang into the car!
Well, they're a bit weird,
but if you get to know them, they'll seem pretty normal after a while.
I didn't know you had friends like that, Kida-kun.
I get involved in all sorts of things.
I know where all the shops are, where to get good used clothes, even how to get street vendors to cut their prices.
I wonder what he's been doing over the last four years, while I was alone sitting at home.
Well, if you know everything that's going on, it makes it that much easier to talk to all the girls.
He's a perv.
She's here.
Are you sure?
She matches the description. There's no doubt about it.
Roger.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Make sure you don't make a mistake.
If she doesn't wake up, we get a pay-cut.
Does it really matter? She's a teen. That's an extra fifty percent, right?
Twenty percent, twenty percent.
This is our first big target in a while. A teenage girl!
Yeah. Thank god for that informant.
Good evening.
Kanra-san!
I didn't know you were here.
I was on the phone.
Oh.
I just finished reading the logs. You're moving to Tokyo?
Congratulations.
Want to get together IRL?
That sounds good.
Doesn't it?
Oh, speaking of meeting offline,
ever heard about mass suicide meets?
Yeah, those were big for a while, weren't they?
People find each other on the internet, then commit suicide together.
That doesn't sound good, does it?
But you don't hear much about them anymore, do you?
Maybe they chickened out at the last minute...
Or maybe there are a bunch of them,
but people haven't found out yet?
Like they haven't found the bodies or something.
That's not cool.
Come to think of it, a lot of people have gone missing lately.
Huh?
Really?
Hmm...
Usually illegal immigrants,
or kids who've run away from home and made it to Tokyo.
I heard it mostly happens between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Magenta-san?
Yes.
Oh, are you Nakura-san?
Good! I figured it was you.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Shall we get going?
OK.
It's just a little further.
Two others are there already.
OK.
That's it.
Hey.
Hello.
Are we all set?
There's no one around.
Well then... Sorry for tricking you!
There is someone here.
Kida-kun just kept on blabbing.
I was getting tired.
I don't know whether it was from walking, or from listening to his bad jokes.
Even though we chatted online all the time, there's just so much to talk about when you meet in person, huh?
Probably both.
Y-Yeah.
I figure I've only gone over about 5/400ths of what I had to cover.
Oh, and 4/400 of that includes Karisawa-san and the others.
I was debating whether to humor him or not, and that's when I saw him.
Hey, miss. Long time no see.
He was dressed like a chef and trying to bring in customers...
No, a black guy dressed like a chef, who was really big...
No, someone dressed like a chef was trying to bring in customers, but for some reason, they were black...
Mister, long time no see.
Hey, Simon!
Long time no see!
Oh, Kida!
Want some sushi?
It's good.
I'll give you a discount.
Sushi is good!
Nah. I'm broke, so you'll have to bear with me.
I'll eat here once I get a job and some money, so how about you treat me to some next time?
I can't do that!
I'd disappear into the seaweed of the Russian tundra!
Seaweed in the tundra?
Later.
Mister, long time no see.
You know him?
Yeah. His name's Simon. He's a black Russian.
He brings in customers for that Russian sushi shop over there.
Sorry. I don't buy that.
I'm serious.
His real name is Saimia, but everyone reads it like it's English and calls him Simon.
Mister, long time no see.
I don't know the details, but his parents took refuge here from America or something.
Anyway, a Russian friend of his started a sushi place, so he started working there.
You don't want to make an eneny out of him, you got that?
I once saw him stop a fight by picking up a guy as big as him with one hand.
Speaking of which, another guy you shouldn't make an enemy out of is...
Wh-What's that?
What's going on?
Speak of the devil.
Well, just stay away from a guy named Heiwajima Shizuo.
If you live a normal life, you'll never have to talk to him.
Wh-What kind of person is he?
Huh, they still haven't come yet?
That's weird.
They're so unprofessional.
They need to be more aware of the time.
Well, it's not like it matters.
We've got plenty of spare time .
Yea, that's true.
A man's body needs times like these.
A time to kick back and relax from the toils of this society.
By the way, I saw that black bike today.
Black bike?
Um...
You don't know?
Everyone in Shinjuku and Ikebukuro's talking about it.
It's been sort of an urban legend for a while, but, a lot of people have been catching him on camera lately.
Yeah. I know, I know.
But isn't it just a normal biker?
It's not like anyone's ever seen him in a group or anything however.
If he's riding with no lights he has to be an idiot.
Well, if he's human that is...
What do you mean by that?
Um, well, you see...
He's kind of like a monster.
Hey.
Um... You one of the higher-ups?
This guy can't possibly be one of them.
Then who is that?
Are you makin' fun of us?
We're kinda busy here.
If you're gonna get in the way, then you'll just have to die!
A-Are you fucking serious...?
Shit!
Ho-H-H-H-Hold...!
Stop! Stop it! Stop it!
Didn't I tell you to stop?
Shit, shit, shit!
Wh-What the fuck is that?
What the fuck is that?!
A monster? What do you mean by that?
Dotachin calls them the Grim Reaper.
Dotachin?
Who's Dotachin?
You see, the man on the black bike...
You're gonna ignore my question on Dotachin?
Damn it!
You see what happens!
You son of a bitch...
...doesn't have a head.
He's headless, yet he still moves around.
This ain't right... Wh-What the fuck are you?
Wh-What the fuck are you?!
Hey, are there any other people I should watch out for?
Well, aside from the yakuza and the gangs...
there's a guy called Orihara Izaya.
Orihara Izaya?
That's a peculiar name.
You should be the last one to say that.
That one's extremely dangerous, so stay away from him.
Well, he usually hangs out in Shinjuku, so you'll probably never even see him.
Oh, and stay away from the Dollars, you got that?
Dollars?
Yeah, as in "One" dollars.
"One dollars"? What's that?
I don't know many of the details, but apparently they're a big group who'll beat you to death on a moments notice.
It seems like they're a color gang, but no one knows what color they represent.
Well with the way things are now, they can't really get together, so they could have disbanded already .
Is that so...?
Hey! Are you OK?
You OK?
Um, I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Um...
No... No! No! No!
Hey!
What the hell was that?
Couldn't she be a little more grateful?
I wonder what happened to her.
Who knows? In this town anything can happen.
Your luck is pretty good.
Just today, got to meet Kadota-san and the others, you met Simon,
you saw Shizuo throw people and vending machines around, and you bumped into a real babe.
Is that what you consider good luck?
I'm happy.
Huh?
In this city, I get to go to school and hang out with you again.
So am I.
You really do have good luck!
You get to witness an urban legend with your own eyes, too!
Kida-kun!
You saw the black bike, Tanaka Tarou-san?
The one you mentioned the other day!
I saw that black bike today!
Oh, good evening,
Setton-san.
The one you mentioned the other day!
I saw that black bike today!
Was it around 9 PM?
The one you mentioned the other day!
Ah, did you hear about it already, Setton-san?
Well yeah, I was there too.
Huh?
What do you mean, "urban legend"?
The black bike!
The Headless Rider!
At that time, my body began to shake.
I wasn't scared.
It was probably more like I was deeply moved.
I saw something amazing.
Right here, in this town, I experienced something that I'd never get to experience anywhere else.
Right now, the seemingly impossible reality, that I thought I'd never see, was right before my very eyes.
It may contradict what I said when I first arrived here,
but at the least, at that very moment, that's what I believed.
For the first time, I shook with excitement thinking of the new reality that was beginning for me.
Really?!
Then we might have passed each other without knowing!
Maybe.
By the way...
Who is Dotachin?
I'm here
I'm right here.
Call me
I'm right by your side.
Trust me
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My dear
This invisible thread,
Trust me
exists because of our warm bond,
I feel so much warmth coming from it.
I hear the voice of your wonderful heart perfectly.
We're no longer kids, but love is still right here.
It's okay to try to cry. It's okay to try to depend on me.
It was then that I decided to take away your pain.
I'm here
Wherever you may be.
Call me
We'll become one.
Trust me
These feelings for you won't change.
My dear
Just put down
Trust me
those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
I'm here
I'm right here.
Call me
I'm right by your side.
Trust me
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My dear
This invisible thread,
Trust me
exists because of our bond,
I feel so much warmth coming from it.
This is a work of fiction.
Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Durarara!!
Next Time
Highly
Unpredictable
A girl who's past is enshrouded by shadows
catches a glimpse of a reality unknown to her.
A reality that everyone can reach, but never quite reaches there.
What seen through the eyes of a girl who should've died was...
Next time: Highly Unpredictable.