Dewa
Tendou Shougi
Town
I lose.
Then as promised, you will fight the 7th generation Kyotouryuu head Yasuri Shichika, with Outou Nokogiri on the line.
Yes.
Kiguchi Zanki
There are limits to how much you can look down on someone!
A swordsman can't fight without a sword!
Or are you telling me to wield my sword against an opponent who bears neither armor nor weapons?
This is an affront to the Shinou Issou school!
Togame...
Shichika! Shichika!
Huh?
What...
meguriatta ga un no tsuki
巡り逢ったが運の尽き
Our encounter becomes thy fortune's end
Katana-
gatari
Mazui
presents
harari koboreochiru
ハラリ 零れ落ちる
Though words doth joined
kotoba tsuranetatote
言葉 連ねたとて
From my lips run over
dare mo watashi ni aru makoto fure mo dekin jaro
誰もわたしに在る真 触れも出来んじゃろ
Can yet any convey the truth I hold?
sakura mau ga gotoku
サクラ 舞うが如く
As cherry blossoms doth dance
konjou to wa osaraba
今生とはおさらば
To this life I bid farewell
saredo oya ni moratta
されど親に貰った
Indeed this body, parent-hatched,
kono mi ga kawaii
この身が可愛い
I cherish duly
命より重い
But graver than life,
inochi yori omoi
bebe matoi warau
ベベ纏い微笑う
Here, smile-clad
kizu wa taenu kenka joutou
傷は絶えぬ喧嘩上等
Put forth battle, such my scars not fade
kakugoshiiya
覚悟しいや
Ready I stand
nuite wa modosu katana to saya tachikiru ha shura
抜いては戻す 刀と鞘 断ち斬るは修羅
To draw is to return, the sword and sheath, to cut what is the battle
sono sakeme ni ochita yume no fu wa muzan zo
その裂け目に堕ちた夢の腑は無惨ぞ
The heart of the dream abyss-fallen lies bestial
ai mamiete tagiraseru chi wo wakeaeru nara
相まみえて滾らせる血を分け合えるなら
If we share such seething blood as we face,
itoshii sonata todome wo
愛し其方 止めを
Then, my love,
sashitekunnamashi
刺してくんなまし
Deliver the finishing blow
hana no sakari ga oshii kae
花の盛りが惜しいかえ
Dost thou lament the flowers' bloom?
Outou
Nokogiri
Saw,
the King
Note: Dewa Tendou Shougi Town
It's October, and Autumn is well under way.
This is the so-called Shougi sanctuary, Dewa Tendou Shougi town.
In order to obtain Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blade Outou Nokogiri for their sword collection journey,
the strategian Togame and the 7th generation Kyotouryuu head Yasuri Shichika have arrived at this town.
They quickly entered negotiations with the 12th generation head of the Shinou Issou school, Kiguchi Zanki.
However, it ended in failed.
Sorry.
You beat her at Shougi, but I went and blundered...
You really can't use swords, can you?
Yeah...
What's the reasoning behind it?
I agree with Kiguchi in finding it hard to believe that you become weaker when you wield a weapon.
It's true that it sounds like nothing but an excuse.
I can't explain it.
What now then?
Now we're at a stalemate.
Though, I kind of got this feeling...
Kiguchi seems too pure to be under the effects of the poison of Shikizaki's Deviant Blades.
She might not be.
In fact, that might be the focus of Outou Nokogiri.
What do you mean?
I mean, it's the one Shikizaki Kiki sword that doesn't carry Shikizaki Kiki's poison.
To put it simply, its lack of poison is proof of kingship.
For example, were you to face Kiguchi fair and square without having to use armor or weapons, do you think you could win?
I don't know...
I can only say that she felt very cautious to me.
Kind of like a taut rope.
I guess her "aura" felt very sharp.
I think that's the first time I've seen someone with such a strict zeal for the sword arts.
She's probably one of the better opponents I've fought so far.
Cheerio!!
Geez...
Ow!
Why are you admiring the opponent you lost to so much?
Right...
Hey, Togame...
Don't you have some plan, like with Sabi or Nee-chan or Biyorigou?
Well as far as the actual fighting aspect of plans go, I know very little.
Like how my plan to pierce Kanara's armor failed in Satsuma when we went to get Zokutou Yoroi.
Oh right, I remember that.
In the first place, the schemes I used against Sabi, Nanami, and Biyorigou all relied on your strength and skills.
If you were to become weaker, even I wouldn't be able to think of a solution.
A solution, huh...
How were Kiguchi's shougi skills?
She was pretty good, I guess.
If she had devoted herself to shougi instead of the path of the sword, she'd be truly formidable.
I wouldn't even be a match for her.
Wow, she must be pretty good for you to praise her.
I'm not praising her!
When Houou said the next one's in Tendou, I figured it'd be this dojo.
But I didn't know the head had changed.
The granddaughter succeeded the position...
I see...
She only recently became the head?
She's around the same age as you too.
So around 24, 25?
I would've thought she was younger, but I can't really tell women's ages.
Well, I guess that's natural for you.
I do know you're younger than me though.
Cheerio!
Who are you saying looks like a child?!
I didn't say anything like that...
I'll admit it's true that I look quite a bit younger after your sister cut my hair though.
You didn't have to go out of your way to say that...
And didn't you say you liked my hair this way?
Well? Well?
Uh...
Excuse me.
W-What's the matter, Kiguchi-dono?
Togame-dono, about the match earlier...
Y-Yeah?
I've come to believe it was unfair.
After you left, I also gave it some thought.
Given that Shichika-dono was that weak...
It couldn't really be called a proper fight.
I think it was unfair.
I wish to correct that injustice.
And so I propose that Shichika-dono studies at the Shinou Issou school under my direct tutelage,
and after training there, face me again in a fair fight.
What do you think?
It's around here?
Y-Yes...
It's o-over there.
Dokutou Mekki
So this is Dokutou Mekki...
No doubt about it.
Kawauso's left hand also agrees.
It's so pristine even in this harsh environment...
It has survived without any rust or corrosion...
I think this is actually the perfect environment.
It's not that it was preserved so much as sealed.
Because of this environment, its ominous aura was kept from leaking outside.
Well, I suppose that's typical of a Shikizaki Kiki blade.
Just as a warning Oshidori, don't try to draw this sword.
Understood.
A-As a swordsman, if Umigame had been able to see this...
Indeed, what would he have thought?
Indeed.
Sword training...
Kyotouryuu wielding a sword?
Imagine if Dad or Nee-chan got wind of this.
But what's involved in sword training?
I've never been trained by anyone other than Dad.
You sound like you're complaining about it, but why do you have that huge smile on your face?
Eh? I'm not smiling...
You always get like this whenever you spot a woman!
Huh?
She can teach you all you want about how to use your body!
Huh? What?
What's wrong Togame?
Togame-san?
This could be bad though...
Bad? This is the worst!
She's the kind of person who refuses to accept a handicap on her opponent, even if she has one.
But fighting without armor is an advantage to me, not a hindrance.
You couldn't explain that to her though!
Yeah...
I guess there are people like that around.
She's an enigma to someone like me who knows nothing but devising genius strategies.
That's why my plans won't work.
The name Zanki is written as "Slay your heart's demon with your heart".
I can't use my ordinary methods.
Kiguchi is far too honest and upright.
Upright, huh...
Going to the extent she has makes her almost inhuman.
I kind of understand now why the Shinou Issou dojo no longer has any students.
Time to go then.
Huh? You're not coming?
What would be the point of me going?
I was thinking you'd watch me practice...
I'd just be a distraction if I were there.
Not in the slightest.
Besides, I need time to work on my own plans!
I guess that's true.
I'm off then!
You didn't even put up a fight!
Try harder!!
Huh? Was I too early?
No, training has already started.
Please use that cloth over there.
Shichika-dono, we begin by cleansing the dojo in order to prepare a refreshing space for us to train in the martial arts.
O-Okay...
Answer with "yes!"
You may be uncomfortable with formalities, but starting today, you are training in the school of Shinou Issou as my student.
You must act as such.
Yes!
Alright!
Shichika's probably feeling lonely since this is his first training session.
I should show up and surprise him.
That'll be enough for the cleaning.
That was a good morning sweat.
Shichika-dono, don't move.
Shichik—
Togame-dono?
Togame?
Why's she running away like that?
This was on your hair.
Oh...
Do not kill it.
This school is not one of slaying.
I-It's not my business!
It's nothing!
No, no!
No!!
Let us begin then.
Alright!
First is the swing.
One!
Two!
Wha—
Three!
Four!
He's late!
I'm back!
Huh? You're already sleeping?
Man, I'm tired...
I've got to say, swordsmanship is a lot harder than I thought...
And Kiguchi sure is strict.
I kind of like it though.
Oh? And how do you like it?
You were awake?
Well, well...
That's quite the turnaround from when you told me you hated swords.
I'm shocked!
No, it still feels wrong to me to wield a sword as a Kyotouryuu.
It's just that Kiguchi is giving me such strict training despite being her opponent...
Oh really?
Strict training? I wonder what kind.
Well, today was upper swings...
Oh really?
Is that so?
Huh?
Oh right, didn't you come to the dojo today?
I thought—
I didn't!!
But...
You mistook someone else!
But that figure was definitely—
I'm tired! I'm sleeping now!
What's she mad about?
One!
Two!
Three!
Bath?
Practice in the bath?
No, training?
Discipline? Waterfall?
Towel rubdown?
Nooo!!
Shichika-dono, here.
Ah, thanks.
Now then...
I'm back.
Man, that was rough.
That Shinou Issou stuff is pretty amazing, Togame.
It's a "sword of life".
It's a school that exists only for the pursuit of the way of the sword, abstaining from conflict.
It's so different from the killing schools that it even disapproves of squashing bugs.
I guess it's kind of like the complete opposite of Kyotouryuu.
Togame?
Food.
Huh? You haven't eaten yet?
Don't tell me you were waiting for me?
You're so late.
Sorry, I already ate with Kiguchi—
So you can't eat anymore after having dinner with her??
I was waiting for you!
Wait, that's not it—
What's not it?!
When did get so close to that woman that you can eat dinner by her side?!
No, that's not it!
The training was so rigorous that I got so hungry I couldn't move anymore!
Kiguchi couldn't stand the sight, so...
I'll eat this too, of course!
I would never turn down dinner with you!
And the food Kiguchi served was kind of frugal, so I didn't really get full on it.
Still, you could have gone ahead and eaten without me.
It doesn't taste good eating alone.
Nothing!
So, how was today's training?
It was pretty rough.
The learning curve is pretty steep...
But Kiguchi is really—
That's enough!
Food first!
Huh? Didn't you bring the topic up?
Let's eat!
Thanks for the food...
Good morning.
Good morning!
Is this good enough?
Yep!
Woah.
Keep your focus ahead of you.
Yes!
Drop your hips more.
Shichika-dono.
Stop for a moment.
Drop your hips just this far.
Okay.
Now walk forward like that.
Sorry.
It's okay, you've gotten better at footwork.
Remember these essentials.
Yes.
Now, how about we have lunch?
Shichika and Kiguchi were...
No way...
Huh?
What's this?
Why am I... crying?
What's happening?
How did it come to this?
To think time could pass this slowly when you're alone...
No good, no good!
Togame! Cheerio!!
I'm off to train!
Oh? You seem quite happy.
Is training that fun?
Actually, it's been almost ten days and I haven't really made any progress.
So it would seem.
How do you know?
I can tell just by looking at you!
I don't even need to see you doing it!
But it has become fun going to the dojo, like you said.
And in spite of how badly I'm doing, moving my body feels good.
Cheerio!!
Good work, Shichika-dono.
Thanks.
It's already been ten days since we began, huh.
There must be something wrong with how I'm teaching you.
The truth is you're actually my first student.
I'm sure I'm lacking in various ways as a teacher,
but I can't do anything about it except ask you to bear through it.
That's not true...
I've got to say,
you're different from any of the other Deviant Blade masters I've met.
I'm sure that's not true.
If I consider what's best for the nation,
I'm aware that handing over Outou to Togame-dono would be the best thing to do.
But even knowing that, I still can't part with it out of my own amateur selfishness.
For the sake of the nation, huh...
But I'd like you to understand.
This both represents the dojo and proves my identity.
It's been passed down from generation to generation,
but what happened during General Kyuu's sword hunt?
How did the Shinou Issou school keep it from him?
During that period, Outou Nokogiri had not yet come under the ownership of Shinou Issou.
If I recall correctly, it was the 8th generation Shinou Issou head who first took possession of Outou Nokogiri.
Your grandfather's grandfather's grandfather's grandfather?
No.
While it's true that I'm the granddaughter of the previous head, the Shinou Issou school is not one of blood inheritance.
Is that right?
That's different from Kyotouryuu.
So does that mean you don't know any details about how the 8th generation head obtained Outou?
I do not.
In fact, I don't have the slightest clue.
It wasn't as long ago as the sword hunt, but it's still a very old story.
I am an amateur.
You said that earlier...
I'm an amateur now, but in the past you couldn't even call me that.
I rejected the way of the sword and spent all night and day in the town playing shougi.
My behavior caused many fights between the previous head and myself.
Oh, Togame said you're very strong at it.
Not at all.
Do you play shougi?
I don't have a clue about it.
When my grandfather died, I had to leave behind my life of shougi.
Succeeding a dojo with no students had no appeal to me,
but the instant I took up the inheritance of Outou, my body became tense.
That's the best I can describe it.
If it's true that I've become a more upright person since that time, then I can say it is all due to this sword, Outou Nokogiri.
Come to think of it, my grandfather also mentioned that he felt like he was reborn when he first took up Outou himself.
He called the feeling "Outou Rakudo".
TL note: King's Paradise
Outou Rakudo...
If Tsuruga Meisai had known about this sword, she'd have done anything to get a hold of it.
Who is Tsuruga Meisai?
Ah, never mind.
Well, if you really were reformed because of that sword, there's not much more you could have hoped for.
I wonder.
In the end I am a worldly person.
No, there's no way you're worldly.
You live your life honestly and earnestly.
Not a single day passes when I don't think about the other life I might have had.
Other life?
You must know of a life of love, right?
When I see you and Togame-dono, I cannot stop that feeling which I threw away from welling up inside me.
But there's nothing wrong with following the way of the sword.
But what can swords accomplish in this age?
I am certain that Shinou Issou will die along with me.
That is why I hold true to my determination to become a swordsman worthy of my ancestors.
That said, I'm always clinging onto this idea that I will be the last generation,
but it's crossed my mind that it might just be a lingering affection.
Sometimes I also thi—
What's the matter, Shichika-dono?
Well, maybe it's a good thing.
Killing schools aside, Shinou Issou is a way of life, right?
It must have a place somewhere in this age of world peace.
Shichika-dono.
Even though this is a practice sword, it will kill if it strikes a person's head.
If it strikes a hand it will break bones.
If it hits the torso it will rupture organs.
If it strikes the throat it will smash the windpipe.
That's why in matches, armor must be used.
Only, it cannot cut.
I wield a way of life only in name.
In reality it deals death as much as any other.
Come, let us continue your training.
Sign: Owari
That unpleasant woman...
It seems her strength as a strategian is the strength to affirm.
That strength to affirm everything from her own weaknesses to the ugliness of the world is definitely a threat to me.
Which is why I denied her.
Judging from the results though, I look like I'm always on the losing end.
You suffer the same losses each time, so this isn't an unfamiliar problem to you, right?
Well, no matter how many times I'm defeated,
I raise myself to the same position anyway.
Conversely, you could say that's a weakness of hers.
Though I suppose you could say that's an expression of her strength.
No.
It might be something more fundamental than that.
If a strategian is one who makes schemes, then maybe that's all they can do.
While she excels at thinking, maybe she also excels at not thinking about things...
Hey Emonzaemon,
at some point in the future, you're going to have to settle things with that woman once and for all.
Though the chances of her reaching the last sword are still maybe 50-50.
Hey, have you been listening to me?
Oh, right...
He's gone off to kill Maniwa Houou...
This is a different beast from the Zettou Kanna that Koumori had.
I was shocked when I touched the sword's scabbard with Kawauso's hand back in the Fuji wind caves.
Zettou's focus was how it wouldn't bend or break, and cut easily.
But Dokutou Mekki's focus is a poison stronger than any other sword.
W-W-What's wrong, Houou-sama?
Nothing, I just found it funny.
That Strategian has collected eight of Shikizaki Kiki's Perfected Deviant Blades,
and the Maniwa Corps has been whittled down to this sad state...
And yet, we have managed to obtain the most deviant of the Deviant Blades before she could.
Ironic, isn't it?
I wouldn't quite call us equal, but with this we have a bargaining chip against the Strategian.
B-But, with Umigame-sama's death in Shinano...
Assuming it wasn't Kyotouryuu, there must be another opponent out there...
What do you mean?
Another sword...
Um... maybe...
He might have been close to Entou Jyuu or Seitou Hakari.
U-Um... Houou-sama...
Did you glean any new information about the other swords when you touched Dokutou Mekki with Kawauso's left hand?
I haven't yet.
To do that I'll have to dive in deeper.
Ninpou: Kiroku Tadori isn't my own ninpou, so I can't say I have a strong command of it yet.
I need to master it first.
I think we should head to where Umigame fell in Shinano for now.
Yes...
We should give Umigame a proper burial...
A-And for the o-others as well...
I-I'm sorry!
Chouchou-san is...
It's fine.
We'll definitely bury them properly.
Y-Yes...
Let's depart then.
Unallowable.
You're—
I cannot allow you to do that, Maniwa Corps soldiers.
I'm back!
Togame, I learned something good today!
Cheerio!!
You've been hitting me for no reason way too much lately...
Did I do something?
No reason?!
What are you talking about?
You think there's no meaning to that punishment?
Shichika! Sit here!
Aren't you ashamed?
You're putting way too much into this Shinou Issou training!
Don't you have any pride as the Kyotouryuu head?
I really don't want to hear that from the person who told me to do this...
As a side note, you can jump pretty well with such heavy clothes.
I've become more nimble after my hair was cut.
I could probably reach the sky now.
Eh?
Never mind that!
You're getting along rather well with that Kiguchi, aren't you.
Yeah, I am.
You admit it??
Kiguchi's your opponent, you know!
Well, see...
Shinou Issou and Kyotouryuu are both forgotten schools, and we both became heads recently so—
Kiiii!
"Kiiii"?
Nyaaa!
I'm afraid that your fun training times are over!
I'm ending it!
Huh?
Well, it took me way longer than I'd have thought possible, but I've come up with one!
Come up with... what?
A scheme, of course!
I thought about it for a while, and I came to the conclusion that there is only one real way for you to beat Kiguchi Zanki in a fight!
There's only one way I can beat Kiguchi?
And with a training sword, armor, and match regulations too!
If you were allowed to fight her barehanded without any shirt, I'm confident you could beat her,
but there's no way Kiguchi would allow that.
There's no way?
So what's the scheme you have for me to beat her?
We're going to use that very weakness of yours.
Weakness?
You haven't forgotten your fight with Itezura Konayuki on Mt. Odori, right?
It was your first defeat throughout our whole journey.
Yeah... I couldn't forget that...
We're going to do likewise.
Likewise?
Maybe I should put it in a different way.
We're aiming to win by fluke!
Unfathomable.
I didn't think those two would just escape and leave you behind.
A smokescreen...
Quite an antiquated ninpou you used.
You're noisy.
All it means is that I'm more than enough to take you on by myself.
Quite the confidence.
However, I am not content to have you as an opponent.
My objective is to assassinate Maniwa Houou.
Who are you?
Unanswerable.
Might you be the one who killed Umigame-san?
Is that Dokutou Mekki?
Oh, so you heard us talking?
You've got good hearing at such a distance.
No, I already knew.
What?
You need not understand, for you will die here anyway.
Is that so?
Whips?
Maniwa Ninpou: Eigouben!
TL note: Infinite whips
Maniwa Ninpou: Eigouben
Here I come!
"Mandarin Duck the Rewind" Oshidori, huh...
What now?
Interesting.
I'm flattered by your praise.
In return, let me teach you something.
This doesn't actually have that much striking power.
If you watch out for the blades on the ends, you can avoid any fatal injury.
However,
even so, Eigouben will slowly torture you to death.
It's the perfect weapon for me!
In that case...
Aioi Kenpo: Hairouken
Note: Rear Trickery Fist
I'm sorry, but...
Unbelievable.
I am truly shocked.
For Hairouken not to have worked...
I thought Maniwa Houou was the only one in that class.
Oh? Do you and Houou-sama know each other?
He's more than just an acquaintance, but not quite a sworn enemy.
That's no answer!
What's wrong?
Is that all?
It is, right?
This is my whip's barrier.
As a defense, it serves as the best offense.
Allow me to finish this then.
I will offer your life as a sacrifice to Umigame-san.
I'm afraid that will be ineffective.
What... is that...
Discontent.
In the end, I failed to assassinate Maniwa Houou.
Though, this woman did well in carrying out her duty.
A true ninja.
You are far more honorable than someone like me who left the ninja ways.
You have my respect.
Unlistening.
Chou...chou...san...
Hey, if possible I'd like to avoid a dirty fight with Kiguchi.
S-So you really have f-fallen for her!!
Have you changed your heart yet again?!
"Again"? When have I—
I know what the two of you were doing together in the dojo!
Right, training, as you know...
Yeah, what kind of training I wonder!
What?
I even trusted in you and got you to go there!
Dammit, I can't bear your erratic nature any more!
I'm the one who can't bear you!
You're always the one who brings up this subject.
These past ten days, I've done just as you said—
Togame, this might be bad.
"Bad"?
Well, it's true that my order for you to study at that school as a student might have been unfair,
and maybe that drove you away from me, but I had my reasons!
You could have just asked me about it!
You could have!
I get it, I get it.
That discussion is already over.
What's over?!
There's still more to talk about!
How can you end the relationship we've built up together in such a one-sided manner?!
How do you think I've felt these past ten days...
No, I mean what's bad is your scheme.
Really?
That's fine then.
No, it really isn't...
So what's wrong with my scheme?
Basically, you're relying on the premise that I'm a complete amateur at using swords, right?
I don't know about before ten days ago, but in the time you came up with that scheme,
I've been receiving direct training the whole time from Kiguchi, a master.
At this point you can't really call me an amateur anymore, right?
I see...
I didn't take that into consideration.
That was a mistake on my part.
Okay, fine.
Kiss.
Do you still remember anything?
I've forgotten it all.
Shichika-dono is still not at a level to be competing against me!
Don't you think it's rather conceited to claim that your opponent is not skilled enough to be a worthy fight?
That's not at all like the way of the sword.
No matter what the difference in skill is, once you take up your sword and face each other, you are equals.
Understood.
Okay.
That went exactly as Togame planned...
However, I have a request before that.
If I win this fight,
I'd like you to give up entirely on Outou Nokogiri.
Agreed.
We'll begin with best of 9 shougi then.
Checkmate.
However the score is 4 to 5.
You win the best of 9.
Then next is the one round, one game swordsmanship match.
Are you ready, Shichika-dono?
Yes.
I just want to say before we start that you've taught me a lot these past ten days.
I was a terrible student who couldn't even take baby steps, but I feel it was a good experience.
No,
I learned far more from the experience.
I most likely still don't have the qualifications to teach anything.
I am truly sorry that I could not provide better results for you in the end.
Don't apologize yet.
If I'm able to beat you here, it'll actually be proof of your worth, right?
I suppose.
Shichika-dono...
Um...
You're holding your sword incorrectly.
Oh, right.
Shichika-dono.
Slay your heart's demon with your heart.
From this comes the name Zanki.
I am the 12th generation Shinou Issou head, Kiguchi Zanki.
Demonstrate your skills before me.
I would without being told.
However, by that point you might be torn into pieces.
Then let us begin.
Then let the match begin!
Pawn to 6,7.
I reply with pawn 3,4.
Pawn 2,6.
Pawn 4,4.
Pawn 2,5.
Bishop 3,3.
It's almost as if she's reading what moves I'm making...
Gold 4,8.
I can't move...
Not good, she's throwing off my concentration...
Gold 3,2.
Pawn 5,6.
I see.
That's why she lost the 9th game...
Gold 4,3.
It was so she would have the first move...
Gold 5,8.
I've only ever played 10 games with her,
and yet in only 2000 moves, she learned how to read my play...
Pawn 5,5.
King 6,8.
I just have to stop thinking about it.
I see...
Silver 6,7.
Shichika-dono doesn't know how to play shougi...
Gold 7,8.
I should just stop thinking, but I can't help myself!
Gold 5,8.
Silver 7,7.
Rook 2,2.
King 7,8.
Men!
TL note: Head strike in Kendo
Woah!
The first match between the Shinou Issou school and the blade-wielding Kyotouryuu was incredibly quiet and anticlimactic.
Even so, the match was decided.
I see, psychological warfare...
That's definitely an area I'm terrible at.
I kind of wish you'd have shown that genius against Tsuruga Meisai too.
Fool.
I keep telling you, battles are by nature your domain of experience.
This time was just an exception.
Well, I guess...
But isn't what you did technically foul play?
Talking to the contestants from the sidelines seems unfair to me...
What are you talking about?
Of course it was foul play.
Wouldn't Kiguchi have objected then?
You'd think so, given how strict she normally is...
But think, Shichika.
Who was it who broke the rules?
The referee—me!
I guess...
And in that town of all places, there's no way anyone would call foul on talking about shougi.
That's the holy land for shougi, after all.
Your shougi was really amazing, though.
Please don't hold back.
In the blink of an eye...
In 42 moves.
I lose.
It was an overwhelming victory for you.
You also won overwhelmingly despite being restricted to fighting at 60% strength at one point.
No no, I just barely won after using Hyakka Ryouran.
I lose.
I underestimated you, Shichika-dono.
Please forgive my rudeness in treating someone with your skill as a student to such a novice as I.
I said you don't need to apologize.
There was nothing wrong with your swordsmanship.
Becoming weaker when wielding a sword is almost like a curse.
Curse...
Here.
As promised, I hand Outou Nokogiri to you.
Are you sure?
Isn't that the proof that you're the school's head?
It seems I am no longer qualified to hold this sword.
No, on the contrary...
I've obtained more than enough strength from this sword.
Whether you'll use it for the greater good of the country or just throw it away, I leave it in your hands.
Please visit again sometime.
When you do, I would be honored to face you again.
Until then, I will look forward to your coming, and continue to watch over the Shinou Issou school's legacy.
Legacy?
Isn't Outou the legacy?
Slay your heart's demon with your heart.
From this comes the name Zanki.
Henceforth, I myself will be the proof.
I'll be the showgirl!
TL Note: Terrible pun on legacy = kanban → kanban musume = showgirl
It was fun.
Cheerio!
What are you looking all happy for?
How?
Oh, now you're conscious of it?
What do you mean?
Well, whatever.
Anyway, there are only three swords left.
I wonder if the Maniwani have been collecting them while we were out and about.
I wonder.
I'm not incredibly impressed by their skills, but it wouldn't surprise me if they'd gotten a hold of one at this point.
Shichika...
What we learned this time implies a possibility about what lies ahead that I don't really want to think about.
Oh, you mean I might get weaker by trying to use a sword?
I doubt I'll ever get a chance to do that again though.
Well, while that is worrisome, I was referring to General Kyuu.
General Kyuu?
The sword hunt.
Why wasn't he able to get a hold of Outou Nokogiri?
Why?
Setting aside that it didn't give off poison, or that maybe it removes poison,
Besides those "King's paradise" effects, it was just a training sword.
How was its owner able to repulse General Kyuu's armies back then?
The sword hunt...
Its official purpose was to build the Sword Buddha.
Its hidden purpose was to eliminate all the swordsmen.
Its true purpose was to collect all of Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blades.
But I wonder if perhaps there was another hidden purpose.
It's possible that General Kyuu failed for reasons other than what I originally thought.
So what would that mean?
Then... that would mean...
No, it's still just a possibility.
You needn't worry about it.
Forget it.
Forget it?
You can't just tell me something that interesting then say that...
Or what, do you...
Do you want me to make you forget again?
Oh?
After this, the two made a brief stop at Owari and quickly moved onto their next objective.
What's wrong, Shichika?
Their 10th target is Seitou Hakari.
And the land they're headed to is Oushi.
The story is reaching its climax.
We shall see Togame's hidden birthplace, the land where the next Perfected Deviant Blade, Seitou Hakari resides.
It will have been about 20 years since she visited her parents.
And on that note,
the story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening ends here.
kumori naki sono hamon yadori shi kedakasa wo mitomu
曇り無きその刃文宿り士気高さを認む
Thou who wields this unclouded blade, I behold witness to thine honor
uchi naru mi ni mamiete moyu
内なる身に見えて燃ゆ
The sacred flame of thy dharma body
taezu nagareru tomadoi mayoi wo furiharaishi toki
絶えず流れる戸惑い迷いを振り払いし時
Whence thou shrug the endless running confusion and hesitation,
tsumi ete nasu iyashiki oi
罪得て成す卑しき老い
Build sins, end in vulgar ancience,
tagaeru ishi wo miokuri
違える遺志を見送り
Bid farewell to a lying, dying wish
ayumi ga koto koto naredo
歩みがことこと鳴れど
The steps echo
tooku
遠く
Far away,
mukau tabiji sono hate wa
向かう旅路　その果ては
My journey, what lies beyond
fukaku
深く
Deep,
waga kokoro kono shizukesa
我が心　この静けさ
My spirit, this silence
tsuyoku
強く
Strong,
togisumasareta inochi ga
研ぎ澄まされた　命が
Sharpened, life
waga akashi
我が証
I was