Okay, this "AD."  Who knows what this means?
The day... it's finally come.
What?  Is something starting?
Oh yeah.
Tenshi will be starting her assault.
Uh huh.
Tenshi assaulting?
A-An assault?  But why?
Because exams are coming up.
Yeah!
Um, why?
Think about it a little.
It's important to make us attend class, but it's also important she force us to take tests and do well on them.
To Tenshi, that is.
However, this exam period could turn out to be a good chance for us to retaliate against her.
Looks like you got an idea, Yurippe.  Let's hear it.
We'll be a nuisance to Tenshi day after day and work to make her fail as many exams as possible.
And with that she'll drop to the bottom of the school rankings.
What happens then?
Loss of honor.
Will she be able to maintain her dignity as the Student Council President?
You're saying something like that would weaken her?
At the very least, the teachers and the students will start seeing her differently.
As a result, a change we have yet to see will come about.
What kind?
I wonder.  I can't predict that far.
Then are you sure there's a point to doing this?
But, if she is not an angel created by God, and doesn't have a tin man's heart...
If she has a human soul like us...
Then the loss of honor will inflict some emotional conflict.
First, we'll decide upon the members taking part in this operation.
I've already arranged for us to be in the same classroom as Tenshi while taking the exam.
Then shouldn't we all distract her as one?
Keep your poor ideas to yourself!  We can't fail this mission.
If the operation leaks, we'll be moved to a different classroom and won't have the chance to make Tenshi fail.
I see.
Then I'll pass.  This kinda work is for sissies.
In that case, the team will be:
Takamatsu-kun.
Hinata-kun.
Ooyama-kun.  Takeyama-kun.
Otonashi-kun.
I-I'm involved again?
Call me Christ.
I simply chose the most normal-looking bunch.
So...
Operation, start!
The seating will be decided on the day of, based on lottery.
If we can't get a seat near Tenshi, our conspiracy against her will be difficult.
Listen up.  Be sure you get the seat in front of her.
Don't ask for the impossible.
Let's see.
20.
Bummer.
11.
I'm far away from Tenshi.
33.
I'm completely far away.
So, my turn.
25.
Man.  I'm far, too.
Look, I drew number one!
Like that's useful!
Isn't anyone close to her?!  Front, side, or wherever!
I'm in front of her.
Way to go!
So, what am I supposed to do?
When the answer sheets get passed out, hold on to two.
When collecting them, swap it with Tenshi's answer sheet.
On a blank sheet—
Actually, turning it completely blank will be too suspicious.
Fill it in with ridiculous answers.
Easier said than done.
Write down things like what you want to be in the future.
It's a Physics test, you know...
Who cares?  Write something like "airplane pilot" or "dolphin trainer."
Sounds like answers from a real idiot.
How do you propose we accomplish this during the pickup?
Hinata-kun!  Do stunts at the right time to grab everyone's attention.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Why do you think I put you in this operation?
What?!  You added me in to be a clown?
At that moment, Takeyama will take Tenshi's answer sheet out of the collected pile and swap it with a fake copy.
In any case, even if something unplanned happens, we'll watch each other's backs.  Got it?
Ah.  Hang on a moment, please.
What should I write in the name block?
"Tenshi."
You retarded?  Wouldn't "Student Council President" be better?
Yeah, since she's supposed to be stupid enough to answer "dolphin trainer."
No, it'd be too stupid to not even have the name written correctly!
Rather, I'm surprised that none of you know her real name!
There's been no opportunity to learn it.
How is that possible?!
Then why don't you go find out?
Go to the Faculty Lounge and find it in the student roster.
For God's sake.  Can't they be more—
Where are you going?  Don't you know the test is starting?
Oh, no, I...  I'm getting a little nervous.
Damn.  What should I do?
I feel bad that her test will be turned in as "Student Council President."
Or rather, when asked,
"When a voltage of 3.0V is applied across a resistor of 20Ω, what is the amount of current flowing?"
that "'I want to be a train conductor' amps" will be the kind of answer turned in!
Are you that nervous?
N-No, it's not that bad.
Relax.  It'll be fine.
You're...
A-Ah, Otonashi.
Otonashi-kun.
I don't know your name, either.
Me?  I'm Tachibana.
And your given name?
Given name?  Kanade.
Tachibana Kanade.
It has a beautiful ring to it.
[ Note: Kanade's name means to play a melody or song. ]
As the name's meaning implies, a very nice, lyrical name.
Thank you.  You've helped me calm down.
Okay, good luck.
It's Tachibana Kanade.
Oh yeah, I remember now.
So you knew!
No, I had forgotten.
Okay, we're starting.  Take your seats.
Huh?  Why can I solve these so easily when I don't have any memories?
Don't solve the problems too diligently.
It could become a prompt for being obliterated.
Shoot.
I'm not supposed to be taking this seriously.
Okay.  Pass forward the tests from the back.
What the hell is that?!
A huge bamboo stalk is growing out of the field!
You're a dumbass, Hinata.
Damn.  So useless.
I placed a propulsion system under your seat just in case you messed up.
What did it feel like to be an astronaut?
I crashed through the ceiling and instantly came back down!
Besides, how did you even make a propulsion system?
I covered your screw up, so be thankful.
Looks like it went well, Takeyama-kun.
It went perfectly.
And call me Chr—
You're up next, Takamatsu-kun.
What will I do?
It's your turn to attract attention.
I-I thought that was Hinata-san's role.
Ever heard of the boy who cried wolf?
Repeated lies lose their effectiveness.
Exactly.
I-Is that why you brought along this many people?
I wonder.
I resign!
You're doing it.
Give up and fly gracefully.  And right through the ceiling.
I must think of something that will gather everyone's attention.
What should I do with the next answers?
Man, but you have it easy.  You only have to swap papers.  You don't have to fly on top of it.
What are you talking about?  I'm responsible for a more critical part of the mission.
Then please change with me.
I don't want to!
See, so you do prefer your seat!
Must be nice to have such a good luck of the draw!
This is delicate work that only I can accomplish!
All you have to do is fly.  It's not like you have to use your head.
What?  Are you calling us idiots?!
Hey!  Stop fighting!
Crap!
Sorry!  We were arguing over one of the answers.
We just came to a conclusion.
We concluded that Hinata got a zero.
Everything's all right.  No problem!
Sorry for being so noisy.  Everything's good!
I see.
You idiot!
Who is?
So, how should I answer the next test?
What's the next subject?
It's World History.
Then fill in the blanks assuming the Earth has been taken over by aliens.
All right.  Pass forward the answer sheets.
I suppose I have no choice.
What's the matter?
Teacher, I must confess.
I look thinner when I dress.
What do you think?
Sure, now take your seat.
Yes, ma'am.
Damn, I can't believe you were able to pull off something that stupid so proudly.
I was confident it would work.
Since you wouldn't expect it out of me.
Since it goes against my character.
Since I secretly train.
Put your shirt on already.
It went well this time too, right, Takeyama-kun?
Of course.  Now would you start calling me Chr—
Okay!  Next up is Ooyama-kun.
I knew it'd come to me!
I don't have anything I can pull off.
Your seat is close to Tenshi, diagonally behind her.
A-Ah, right!  Then maybe I won't have to pull off a stunt, right?
Sure, all you have to do is confess your love to Tenshi.
Right!  Wait, what was that again?
I said confess your love to Tenshi.
"I'm sorry to say it at a time like this, without even considering the place.
I've always been in love with you.  Please go on a date with me."
Do exactly that, and you won't have to be launched.
Damn!  All he has to do is ask her out?
That's not fair.
Come on!  Put yourself in my shoes!
You've only suffered physical injury, but I'll have tremendous emotional scars!
This will be my first time asking a girl out!
And I even know ahead of time she's going to turn me down!
What a baby.  This will be perfect practice for him.
Unlike you, I don't need practice!
I only need true love!
What?  Are you saying I cheat on people?!
Hey!  You guys stop fighting!
Sorry!  Yuri's a little emotionally unstable.
Because last night, Hinata showed up in her dream and—
Don't think that the me from today and tomorrow will be the same.
Watch out.
That's what he said, and Yuri just proved it.
Are there two Hinata-kuns?
Y-Yeah... that's right.
Is there a chance that there's more than three of him?
Huh?  Oh, uh... it's possible.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Everything's calmed down, so don't worry.  It's good now.
All okay.
Sorry to worry you.
How many of me are there, did you say?
Who's emotionally unstable?
Hey now, I covered for you guys, so don't give me that.
You all brought it upon yourselves.
So, what should the next set of answers be?
What's the subject?
[ Note: Katakana is a Japanese character set generally used to represent foreign languages.  In English class, they would be expected to write in the roman alphabet. ]
It's English.
Then answer all the questions in katakana.
Okay.  Pass forward the answer sheets.
Tachibana-san!
I'm sorry for saying this now, without even considering the place!
I've always loved you!  Please go on a date with me!
Then please consider when and where you ask me.
You.  Take your seat.
Yes, sir.
Ah, he's done it.  Now he's—
Hey, hey!  Wait a damn minute!
What?  Don't come near me!
Why was it that I took flight?!
Well, Ooyama-kun suffered a deep enough wound to his heart.
Well why did you choose me?!  I don't get this at all!
That aside, everyone, let's have lunch.
Are you prepared, Takeyama-kun?
Always am.  And it's Christ.
I've been taking flight and crashing into the ceiling, here. How many more times do I have to go through this?
Throughout the exam period.
Let's change the team members tomorrow!
Matsushita-kun and T.K. look heavy.
Don't choose us by weight!
Besides, taking flight with the chair sure has an impact, but everyone will get bored quick.
"Oh look, there he goes again."
They'll even stop turning around soon enough!
That's why I'm adding some spice.
What's waiting for us from here on?  You're scaring your allies!
Then participate!
I said you're scaring us!
Is she going to make me confess love again tomorrow?
Maybe I should take my pants off, too, next time.
The operation is nearly perfect.
But, will something really change by doing this?
We're just making a commotion like always, and the calm returns like always.
I thought that's all there would be to this.
And so, the exam period ended.
Tachibana?
What's wrong?  Did something happen?
Nothing.
It's starting to mill around.
What has?
The rumor about Tenshi getting a zero on all subjects.
Seriously?
And that the answers were all making the teachers look like fools.
They're even saying that?
What did you guys do?
We flew, added some spice, and eventually we even flew out the window.
What the heck?
But don't the teachers know that it's not Tenshi herself, but someone's prank?
How many times do I need to tell you?  The teachers can't figure that out.
Just like the in real world, if the Student Council President were to turn in an exam with ridiculous answers,
then of course they're going to summon Tenshi to yell at her, just the same.
So that's what she was doing.
Do you think Tachibana tried to explain?
I don't know.  Besides, it's in every subject.
How would she explain it to all the teachers?
From the teachers' eyes, well, it must seem like a single person performing a rebellion.
A rebellion performed by a single person...
And so, several days later...
It happened during the school assembly.
Therefore, Tachibana Kanade-san will be resigning from her seat on the Student Council as of today.
Instead, Naoi-kun, the Vice President, will be taking over the seat as a deputy.
What?
She's not resigning.  She's being removed.
Yurippe.
Now that she's one of the ordinary students without any authority, will she be able to stop us?
Tonight, we'll do Operation Tornado again.
It's the final piece Iwasawa left behind.
Was it all right for me to put lyrics to a piece like that?!
Well, I guess it all depends on how people will react to the song and the second generation of GDM.
Hey.
What do... we fight against...?
Against whatever comes against us, obviously.
Who's going to come in our way?
Who other than Tenshi?
Or, maybe that deputy president.
He's an NPC, isn't he?
We can't shoot him.
Ah, right.
Will Tenshi come?
She's here!
Let's take her down before she deploys her Guard Skills.
Wait, don't shoot!
Why not?
Something's not right.
What's not right?
I don't know.
But, she looks like she's not here to fight.  I don't sense any hostility from her.
She looks more like she's stopping by here for another reason.
What do you mean?
Tenshi?!  What's going on outside?
What should we do?
Hold on a minute.
What is this?  Something's not right with her.
What is she doing?
That's the infamous mapo doufu that no one in the school orders because it's so spicy!
Why?  Why is she buying that?
Is she trying to make us eat it and get her revenge?
Yurippe-san, the heat is at its max now.
Your orders, please.
Sure...
Turn them on!
Spin it, please.
Hey!  That's the infamous mapo doufu that no one orders because it's so spicy!
The best way I've seen to eat it is to pour it over rice to buffer the pain.
Well, I grabbed this, so I don't have a choice.
One bite and I'm on fire!
Hey, but it's good.
Give it a try, Hinata.
What?!  You're joking.
Okay, then just one bite.
It hurts!  It's hot!  It's spicy!
But, this flavor that follows the pain...
I see.  This stuff really is good.
See?  You've never had mapo doufu that tasted so good, right?
Maybe it's some sort of secret winner.
That's the ticket Tenshi bought.
T-This?
Yeah.
So, she just wanted to eat this.
This must be her favorite flavor.
I even took away such a small piece of happiness from her...
Tenshi must be a human.
What kind of angel comes to eat her favorite mapo doufu to comfort herself?
As the Student Council President, she couldn't let us run loose and promote disobedience.
Because we started to build weapons at the Guild, she began developing Guard Skills to fight against us.
Is that how all this started?  How ridiculous...
I haven't even found a hint to God, yet.
You know...
Maybe Tenshi, how she is now, could join our side.
Don't be stupid!
Do you know how many of us died because of her?!
Well, none really died, but...
Do you know how much pain we've gone through?
Yeah!  She was docile today, but who knows when she'll become aggressive again!
She could get us right when we drop our guard!
That was a silly question, wasn't it, Otonashi-kun?
Seems so.
Why did I make such a foolish proposal?
It's because I imagined how she would be eating mapo doufu alone at a table in the corner of the room.
Having lost all trust and her position, she looked painfully lonely.
What are you guys?!
They're NPCs.
That's enough.
I have various charges against you all,
but for the time being, I'll have you sent to the Introspection Room
for violating school rules regarding activity hours.
Now that I'm the Student Council President, you will not be left with an easy way out.
Take them away.
What's wrong with that guy...
That's the deputy Student Council President...
Naoi Fumihito-sama.
Dora dora.  Dealer Mangan!
Don't be freaking ridiculous!
We need Tenshi.
You dare to rebel?  Against God?
Hand Sonic: Version 2.
Reflect on what?!
Are you going to accept that?
It's them...
Please, God!
Your life should have been the real deal, too!