I will be one!
Nuh-uh!
You couldn't be a princess in a million years!
Maybe I can't be...
The Princess of Flowers
a pretty, pink princess...
You can.
Is it your dream to become a princess?
Huh?
Yeah...
Then you can.
Really?
Dreams are powerful things.
I'm certain your dream will come true if you hold it dear.
Okay!
I'll do it!
In that case,
I shall give you this.
What's this?
A charm to guide you to your dream.
It's so cute!
Thank you!
I'm Haruka! And you?
I am Kanata.
Huh? Kanata?
Haruka...
Huh?
Never... give up on your dreams.
Kanata...
Okay!
I'll become a princess!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
I can't believe I have to say
goodbye to my little Haruka...
Your poor daddy's heart can't take it!
Oh, don't cry.
Come now, all academies require students to live on campus.
I know, but still.
Make sure you call us every day!
I see it!
They don't allow cell phones...
That's Noble Academy!
My life's beginning to blossom!
I'm a Princess?
The Birth of Cure Flora!
Noble Academy Women's Dormitory
Haruka!
We're leaving, so take care of yourself.
You made the choice to enter this school,
so show them what you're made of!
Gotcha!
Bye!
Have a great time!
Thank you!
Let's go!
That's the school building!
It's way bigger than a normal school!
This place is huge!
And next up...
There it is!
It's the women's dorm!
Haruno Haruka
Nanase Yui
Splendid!
Oh, how splendid!
It's simply splendid!
Getting to live in such a splendid room makes my happiness blossom!
All right...
Umm...
Miss... Haruno?
Uh, yeah.
A pleasure to meet you.
My name is Nanase Yui.
Your roommate, it seems.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Haruno Haruka.
Well met.
I was hoping nobody would see that...
Would you like to take a tour of the dorm with me?
Sure!
We do the cleaning and laundry ourselves at this dorm, right?
We do.
Bonjour.
B-Bonjour?
It how we greet each other at this school.
B-Bonjooour!
This is the lesson studio.
Lessons?
Dancing is a required class.
Wonderful!
This is the cafeteria.
It's huge!
This is huge too!
This is the party hall.
Party?
They hold events like that here.
Party...
Haruka?
S-Sorry!
Next is...
It's Minami!
Bonjour.
She's so pretty...
That's Kaidou Minami, the student council president.
She's a flawless student, athlete, and ballerina, as well as the daughter of a CEO.
Everyone calls her the academy's princess!
Princess?!
Oh, this is simply splendid!
Bonjour.
Heya, bonjour.
Now, where was my room?
You know, they say academy is a place where students live together and make their dreams come true.
Yeah! There are lots of famous people who've graduated from here!
I like to create stories.
That's why I want to be a picture book writer!
I want to write a lot of picture books that get read around the world!
Splendid!
That's a splendid dream!
Thank you!
What about you?
Huh?
You always seem so happy, Haruka.
I'm sure...
you have your own dream you're chasing, right?
I...
Well, uh, ya see...
Hey, a raccoon!
Lemme take a look!
Haruka?
It's too embarrassing to say!
I can't tell her I want to be a fairytale princess!
And then I blurted out "raccoon"...
This is just hopeless...
This way, bro!
Perf!
Thank you!
This raccoon talked!
I'm not a raccoon, I'm Perf!
This poodle talked!
I'm not a poodle either!
You leave Perf alone!
This parrot talked!
Wait, those do talk...
I'm no parrot, birdbrain!
Bro!
That hurt!
Are you okay?
Why are a poodle and a parrot...
'Cause we're not!
We are Hope Kingdom's Royal Fairies!
Fairies...
Found ya...
ya little fairies.
That'll do it!
Thank you!
Now don't trip anymore!
Perf and Aroma, right?
Perf.
Roma.
I'm Haruka.
Nice to meet you!
But you look just lik—
We're not!
Really now, a crisis looms over us and you want to chitchat...
Crisis?
If we don't hurry, the world will fall into despair!
What are you talking about?
What?
There you are.
Who are you?
He's from Dysdark!
The name's Close.
I ain't lettin' you revive the legendary Princess Precure.
Princess?
Haruka!
I finally found you!
Yui!
Sweet timing.
Lemme see that dream of yours!
I'm done!
This is my picture book!
Ain't you the dreamer.
I'll toss that dream into the cage of despair!
Close your dream!
Come, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Wh-What's that?!
A devil born from trapping a dream in despair!
A Dyspairvil!
Now hand over the fairies.
I won't!
Then you can get destroyed along with 'em!
Dyspairvil!
Wait, you can fly?
Yui...
Let Yui go!
Why should I?
But... oh, what should I do?
You can't fight that!
But—
Only a Princess Precure could save that girl!
And what kind of princess is that?
That's it, Dyspairvil!
A keyhole?
The Princess Perfume fell!
End of the road.
Yui...
How could this happen to you?
'Cause she had one of those dumb ol' "dreams."
C'mon, wanting to be a picture book writer?
What a moron!
What good's it do ya to put your hopes in some dream?
There ain't one of 'em worth squat,
so I'll get rid of 'em myself!
You can't do that!
Huh?
Yui's dream is nothing short of splendid!
You can't take that away from her!
Lemme guess, you got a dream, too?
Well, spill it.
I could use the laugh!
My...
My dream...
My dream is...
to become... a princess...
Couldn't hear ya!
I want...
to become a princess!
What's that?
It turned into a key?
Th-That's a—
A Dress Up Key!
How did you get that?
Hand it over.
Now!
Put that into the Perfume!
With that,
you can fight against them!
Hand it over!
We won't give it!
Beat it!
Perf!
How dare you!
Hurry!
What perfume?
This?
Here's a key, and here's a keyhole...
but fighting? Me?
Against them?
Good luck.
You really think you've got a chance?
I mean... there's no way...
But...
if I do...
then Yui...
and Yui's dream...
might still be saved!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
Princess Precure?!
I've finally...
found you!
Huh?
What happened?
Did I transform?
Gimme a break...
I got no choice!
Dyspairvil!
Dys!
I'm high!
Oww...
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
You've got to have a clear idea of how you want to move!
This is a bit sudden for ideas...
No!
Close call!
I've got this! I think.
What power...
You did it!
Time to turn the tables!
Now say it loud!
Say what loud?
Say whatever!
Just make it princess-y!
Uh, gotcha!
Uh...
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dyspair... vil!
Dyspairvil!
Now's your chance!
Insert the key one more time and unleash Cure Flora's power!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
My dress...
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Dreaming...
Adieu!
I'll remember this, Princess Precure!
I... really did become the Princess of Flowers...
You did it!
Now use the key to save that girl!
Right!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Now this girl has regained her dream once more!
Oh...
Thank goodness.
So, what is all this?
Who are you two?
We left the land nestled between hopes and dreams, Hope Kingdom, in search of the Princess Precure.
We came Sir Kanata's stead.
Hope Kingdom?
Kanata?
This man!
K-Kanata!
It's him! It's Kanata!
That's Sir Kanata to you.
Huh?
This man is the venerable prince of Hope Kingdom!
You will address him as Sir Prince Hope Grand Kanata!
Huh?
H-He's a prince?!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
I found a real princess!
She's beautiful, smart, athletic, and a brilliant ballerina!
Huh? She'll teach me ballet?
Don't expect my lessons to be easy.
This sounds hard, but I'm grateful for the help!
Go! Princess Precure!:
The Academy's Princess!
Cure Mermaid Arrives!
Go say bonjour to your dream!