So tired...
School sure is a lot of work...
I can't do this anymore...
Big Brother?
Let's see what kind of adult DVDs
my big brother watches.
Being interested in other women
means he's cheating! This is cheating!
I understand he's at that age,
but I won't forgive him if it's anything
other than sister-love category!
So I'm Tsurugi Yagami
and am in charge of the project.
I'd like to start carrying out "Sasami Watch Project" now.
What?
Kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
Watashi no kisetsu tachi
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
Nemuri wo yusaburu uta
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
Kokoro wo enjiru niwa
Zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otonaja nai
Deatta kouya no hana
Kowakute yasashikute
Fureta shunkan ni diorama datte hontou ni naru
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta watashino miraichizu
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
Oikakete kuru ashita wo kowasu
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 4                                              Ganbaranai
"PARASITIZING AT HOME"
Mic test, mic test. Do I look pretty, Tsukuyomi?
Yes, you look normal.
What is this?
The Sasami Watch Project
is to support Sasami Tsukuyomi,
who's successfully returned to society
after overcoming many hardships.
Support me?
If living as an ordinary girl despite possessing
the Power of God is her way of life,
I'd love to help her do just that
with everything in my power.
That's also the purpose of our existence.
Tsurugi...
That being said, I'd like to help her grow through trials.
Sasami Watch Project is a project in which
we film and record her progress
and laugh at her as she blunders along her way.
I was stupid for falling for that...
We've already given Sasami duties and
my elite sisters have been filming that.
Hey, Camera 2, tell me what's going on over there.
Too close, too close! Get away from it!
Yawn... This is Kagami Yagami at Camera 2.
I'm currently following 30 meters behind Sasami.
Is that me?
It doesn't look like Sasami has noticed me.
When did you film this? I don't remember
going to a place like this.
I can't recall it... What is that?
Good work, Kagami.
Next, let's go to Camera 3. What's going on over there?
Yup, that's right. Tama became a member
of the Broadcast Club at school.
But because I talked way too loud during the broadcast,
the school principal, with his heart condition...
Oops. Telephone.
Hello! It's Tama!
Where are you right now?
You know what? The sky flashed really bright
and the next thing I know I was here.
And these short silver people with big eyes,
who are filming me right now, came to talk to me,
saying, "We have something that we
want to ask intelligent life on Earth"!
Don't you go with strangers so carelessly!
They'd vivisect you and implant some
mysterious metal things in your body!
What?!
Just get back to work!
Excuse me, Miss Tsurugi, that was...
Don't say anything! Just pretend you didn't see that.
Camera 2, what's going on with you?
Yawn...
What are you doing?!
Would that be a problem if I kept this?
We'll talk about that later! Where's Sasami?
Let's see...
It looks like I've lost her.
You idiot!
I'm going to detect Sasami's location
using something like psychic waves from orbit.
Got it. It looks like she's on the
other side of the shopping mall.
Wh-whoa, hey!
Hey, you! Don't run on the roofs!
Are you a ninja or what?
Teh heh!
Don't "teh heh" me!
Aren't you adorable! Marry me!
It looks like Sasami is entering the drug store.
Good, good. She must be going in there
to buy what I asked her to get.
Oh? It looks like she's unable to find
the item she's looking for.
Big Sis, what did you ask her to get?
Can I help you find something?
Well, this...
One dozen of Happy Family Planning?
Do you know exactly what you asked
a minor to buy for you?
A cute little high school girl asks for Happy Family
Planning as she blushes. Is that awesome or what?
I'm sorry, but we don't carry that item.
I see. My teacher told me
that I could find it at a drug store...
Note: Kamiomi is riffing (almost perfectly) the mascot of a Japanese Anti-Piracy ad
campaign shown in movie theaters
By the way, what is Happy Family Planning anyway?
What? You don't know?
It's a sad reality, but young kids
these days don't call it that.
I know you wanted that to be a form of
sexual harassment, but it misfired.
No way! Back in the day you could make people
crack up just by saying Happy Family Planning!
It looks like Sasami is heading to
the next shopping destination.
EVERYTHING
100 YEN!
Oh, she entered the 100-yen store.
Why is she going there?
You didn't instruct her to go?
No.
Oh, she just came out.
It looks like she bought something. Let's see through it.
You can see through things?
I see sunglasses, a knit cap and
something that looks like a sweatsuit.
I don't care about stuff like that.
Just see through Sasami. What color are they?
What is she trying to see?
No one cares about the color of Sasami's panties.
Forget the panties! Get the color of her nipples!
Stop it!
Oh?
What's up? Don't tell me she has nothing on!
PUBLIC BATH
BATH                                                                                                          BATH
BATH
It looks like Sasami is going to the public bath.
I wonder why. She could take a bath at home.
She may feel uncomfortable taking a bath
at home because Tsukuyomi peeks.
I don't peek! I always go right in there fair and square.
What? What did you just say?
She's inside. Let's follow her.
TICKET                                 CHANGE
One high school student please.
I'm surprised that they let her in with the camera.
WOMEN
I've Altered the human's notions, so no one cares.
Great job! I expect nothing less from my sister!
I spotted Sasami.
Stop filming!
Don't take it off!
Stop it!
No!
Now it's a commercial break.
COMMERCIAL
BREAK
That was one quiet winter night with brilliant moonlight.
Hey, when did they...!
No! This isn't what you think!
Jeez.
What the heck are we watching?
My secret collection of Sasami's sleeping face.
You know you're supposed to ambush her,
wearing a red helmet and carrying a big sign.
Note: She's referring to a specific segment starring Masashi Tashiro
from a variety show in the past.
That's enough. Give me Camera 2!
Kagami! What is Kagami doing?
You are being too loud!
Why are you relaxing? What happened
to the Sasami bath scene?
Yawn... It looks like Sasami changed clothes and left.
I'm sleepy now. I'm sorry but that's it for today for me.
Yawn.
Hurry up and go after her!
Have you forgotten what I've done for you?!
Your Big Sis loves you so much that she'd change
your diapers, give you pacifiers and play with you!
I have no idea what you're talking about,
you super pervert.
You need to tell me more of that stuff!
We have no choice, Tsukuyomi! We've gotta go!
What's this DVD anyway?
I don't recall running errands like this.
What is this? I've got a bad feeling about this.
This is bad...
All right, we're here! I'm positive that Sasami will be here!
What is this place?
This place is called "Uzume no Ana",
a department store specializing in sub-culture
goods such as anime, comics, games and so on.
In other words, it's an otaku shop, right?
You put it too bluntly, didn't you?
So where's Sasami?
On the 3rd floor! Let's go!
Online Purchase
In-Store Pick-up
Creative Dojinshi
Adult Goods
3F Adult Dojinshi
Dojin Goods
Commercial Publications
But it says you need to be 18 to enter the 3rd floor.
Where's Sasami?
I see her.
She's in disguise, but she can never fool me.
Well... This is it, right?
Yamato Taisen                                                        Yamato Taisen
Taketake*Run                                                         Taketake*Run
Ibuki                                                                      Kumaso
Yamato Taisen
Taketake*Run Ibuki
Let me see.
Buy the limited edition
with the detachable
armor. You can't
detach the armor
with the regular
edition ones!
"Ibuki from 'Yamato Taisen Taketake * Run'?
"Buy the limited edition with detachable armor.
"You can't detach the armor with the
regular edition ones"... Who cares!
Yamato Taisen                                                        Yamato Taisen
Taketake*Run                                                         Taketake*Run
Ibuki                                                                      Kumaso
Ltd Castoff ver.
LIMITED CAST-OFF
LIMITED QUANTITY
Whoa, stuff like this costs 30000 yen?!
Anyway I need to find a store clerk...
She's walking away.
Good job, Sasami! Welcome to my world!
Now I give you the half of the world!
Stop it! Don't go!
"Imouto moe"? In love with little sister?
Wh-what is up with this shameful development?
What?
No way... This is the little sister, right?
Oh, I guess it could happen. Yeah, that's right.
What? What's going on here? Isn't this man's...?!
BIG
BROTHER
Kill me! Just kill me!
Imouto
Moe
Um, excuse me.
It looks like you're still in high school or something.
Well, I'm just...
Maybe you're here for the seiyuu show on the 4th floor?
What? Oh, yes!
Sorry, it's complicated to find the way there.
The stairs are over there.
Let's go after her, Miss Tsurugi!
Shut up, you moron!
I told you that I'm not in elementary school!
What?
Just hurry up and sell it to me!
Like I said, little girl, only adults can buy manga like this.
I told you that I'm an adult! Grrr!
I'll go ahead!
AKIHABARA A                                  AKIHABARA B
Event Hall                                            Event Hall
Adult Dojinshi                            Dojinshi for Women
(anime/manga/novel)                            Dojinshi Software
Say! You! Say! You!
Note: Seiyuu (pronounced 'say you') means 'voice actor'
SEIYUU MINI LIVE SHOW!!
Thank you, everyone!
What are you doing? You need to synchronize!
What? Okay.
That's not it. It's the red one for this song!
Okay.
Excuse me! Please let me through!
I'm sorry, but no camera is allowed.
Note: completing the Anti-Piracy ad parody
What? No, I'm filming Sasami, not the seiyuu.
Ka-Kamiomi! What are you doing here?
You're the priestess from Tsukuyomi Shrine!
N-no, I'm not! I've never heard of
Tsukuyomi Shrine before!
Please leave, Kamiomi!
People from the Tsukuyomi Shrine are here...
So that must mean that this suspicious event is...
Now!
Now let it go!
Father!
My daughter! Pass your burdens
of the past to your father!
Sasami!
Now the Sun hands over the beautiful stars to the Moon.
The Human World gracefully receives a new leader.
What are you doing, Father?
This thing plotted it all!
As the seal grew weaker,
it regained consciousness and then contacted us
and suggested this plot to us.
Don't tell me...
That's right. The power of God is
right here right now. It's inside my hand!
Hey!
How dare you interrupt us? So annoying!
Oh? What are you doing, Tsukuyomi?
Do whatever you want.
I knew I felt a suspicious vibe.
Yawn...
The sin you committed by interrupting
my blissful sleep time is very serious.
Move out of the way!
I'm sorry! I'm on the run because
the government is after me!
Don't worry. Tama will protect you.
I'll let no one touch the mystery of the
universe, Sotosumodento!
You woman right there!
Hand that alien to the Earth Federation!
He's going back to his mother planet!
We have no choice.
Commence attack!
What the hell? What kind of story development is this?
This seems to be the kind of drug used to erase memory.
Everyone! Eliminate all intruders!
All men! Charge!
Let's get out of here, Kyupi!
I... will be free...
So there you have it.
What?
I beat up those guys from the Tsukuyomi Shrine.
Tsukuyomi called the ambulance
and took Sasami to the hospital.
Your memories became disarrayed
after you inhaled the green smoke.
So I created the DVD through the alteration
and just showed you exactly what happened.
Now do you remember about yourself...
...Sarcoma?
You used to be a part of the same body.
You must've come home,
believing that you're Sasami herself.
What are you going to do with me?
You're a part of Sasami.
You have no idea what's going to happen to you
if you remain detached from her.
I'm going to Alter you back to the sarcoma
and then merge you into Sasami.
Everything will be back to the way it was.
Don't give me that!
I'm going to be free!
She and I are two different characters!
Do you understand the pain of being trapped
inside someone's body, unable to do anything?!
I'm finally detached from her!
Now I'm going to have a free life!
That's right. I have the Power.
This body has the Power of God!
I can do anything I want to do with you, too!
In the name of the Supreme God, I order you! You shall...
Give it back.
That's a toy you don't know what to do with.
What?
I would've been nice to you
if you looked sorry and stayed quiet.
But don't worry.
I felt sorry for you at least a little.
I'm not a hard-working god, but
I make a miracle happen every now and then.
So you came to, did you?
What happened to me?
Now it's back to the way it was.
Although that sarcoma is gone.
Okay...
You and she share the same body.
You two wished for the same thing
and have the same free lifestyle.
You two also give others trouble.
But she has committed a sin.
She tried to benefit only herself
at the sacrifice of others.
On the other hand, you recognize the trouble you may
cause others and do your best to minimize that.
You don't misuse the Power of God.
You almost seem to despise and reject it.
Since I'm a perverse person, I entrust you
with this along with some expectations.
Keep on doing your best until the day you can't.
Here, Meat! Big Sister Kagami is here!
"Meat"?
It's her name.
I can't call her Sasami just because
she used to be a part of her.
But "meat" is the name of food.
Note: "Meat" (Niku or 肉) is used here as a diminutive form of
"Sarcoma" (Nikushu or 肉腫)
She's so cute that she makes me want to eat her
although I don't need to eat because I'm not a human.
Okay...
By the way where's Tama?
Goodbye!
Science has a place Humanity shouldn't enter just yet.
Yahoo! I'm Sasami Tsukuyomi, the main character
of this story that everyone loves!
Today I'm going to sing just for you guys,
so please listen!
It's "Shintoatsu Symphony" by Sasami Tsukuyomi!
Mata ashita ne
See you tomorrow!
Bai bai shitemo nanka suguni aitaku naru
I already miss you right after I say goodbye
Densha ni norumade zutto koe wo kiitetai no
Until I get on the train I want to keep hearing your voice
What's going on with you?
Do you have a fever or something, Sasami?
I mean, are you really Sasami? Who are you?
Stop it! I'm always like this.
I love you, Big Brother! Kiss kiss!
What? What is this awkwardness that I'm feeling?
Kikoeruyo
I can hear it
Kimi no koe ga
Your voice
Doko made mo hibiku symphony
It's a symphony that echoes far away
So this sounds okay, right? Did I sing okay?
Well, yes. The song itself was perfect.
Then I'll sing it next time, too!
Things got really crazy in this episode,
but there's a place for me here.
I'm going to be happy!
Let's do our best in the next episode, too!
You're NOT Sasami, are you? Just who are you?
It's time for Ganbaranai Hotline.
Dear SHAFT
Tokyo Suginamiku Kamiigusa
Yuji
This is a letter from Mr. A, who lives in Tokyo.
I have no energy to do anything lately.
So my life has been quite dull for a while.
I'm a person who can
I'm a person who can accomplish anything,
but I think it's society that makes me this way.
I'm a person who can
accomplish anything,
but I think it's society
I'm a person who can
accomplish anything,
but I think it's society
that makes me this way.
You do understand where I'm
coming from, don't you, Sasami?
Don't ask for my sympathy. Get a job.
Episode 5
Next time, episode 5:
"I Haven't Given It All Just Yet"