In truth, the act of Völundr
merges human with Valkyrie.
They become as one,
united in both body and soul.
A Valkyrie doesn't merely transform
into a weapon through Völundr.
Her fate is bonded to her wielder's.
We fight together and...
we live or die together.
[sobbing]
Please don't cry, Göll.
Leif was prepared for this.
She knew how dangerous
her battle would be.
Every Valkyrie does.
A time may come when you too
must prepare to follow in our footsteps,
and put your life on the line.
I'll get my revenge on those
piece of shit gods.
Once I'm through with them, there won't
be enough left to scream for mercy.
[Hrist and Göll] Poseidon?
Then they intend to break
our spirit as soon as possible.
It would be my honor.
When did he...?
What the heck's going on here?
I thought when a soul
was summoned to Ragnarok,
no matter how old
that person was when they died,
they would be summoned in their physical
prime, not as some crusty old geezer.
Isn't that how it works?
That is how it works.
And yet, this man claims to--
[whooshing]
Ugh.
Oh.
[Brünnhilde] He's certainly not
what I expected.
But still, right before our eyes,
he moved with the grace of a master.
The man before us is the real thing.
Hm.
It's been 400 years since I was
called up to heaven,
Since then I have tirelessly worked
to hone my swordsmanship.
The nature of my Ganryu
has never stopped evolving.
[shimmering]
In other words, this old Kojiro
is a swordsman in his prime!
All right, sister.
You ready to offer yourself?
Of course.
[heavy metal music playing]
TYRANT OF THE OCEAN
[seagulls calling]
[waves crashing]
[crowd murmuring]
[male god 1] This new arrangement
is quite impressive.
[male god 2] The arena,
they did do quite a bit of remodeling.
A massive ocean.
Ocean... Then the next fighter has to be...
Really? Do you think it's possible?
[Heimdall] Well... [clearing throat]
Welcome to round three of Ragnarok,
the ultimate battle between man and maker.
With mankind struggling
under two losses in a row...
Oh! What a shame!
The blessed creators have forsaken their
children to suffer this harrowing ordeal.
But, hey, that's the gods for you.
They do as they please,
that's what defines them.
So let's bring out our next challenger.
Here comes god warrior three.
It's time to get wet!
If they say Zeus
is the father of the cosmos,
that makes this champion
the sultan of the seas,
the frosty tyrant of the ocean,
ruling the waves with an iron fist.
[gods cheering]
[male gods 1 and 2] I told you!
[Heimdall] Even other deities quake
at the thought of provoking his wrath.
Everyone fears him!
[gulping]
One of the three most powerful
Olympian immortals,
also known as Zeus Enalios,
he's the king of the aquatic,
the wonder of the waters...
Poseidon!
Hm.
Circus of filth.
[ravens shuddering]
Huh. What an awful personality.
He's worse than you and the old man
when it comes to a lack of humor.
[gulping]
Even his fellow gods are terrified.
That makes sense.
He is Zeus's brother after all.
Pop quiz! Brought to you by the fool
who's challenging our maritime master.
Representing the humans
is this man, right here.
Who's the greatest swordsman of all time?
Is it Minamoto no Yoshitsune, who cut
down the Taira clan with his katana?
Nay!
Is it Nobutsuna Kamiizumi,
the Sengoku era hero
who founded the Shinkage-ryu,
and scared off Takeda Shingen?
Nay!
Perhaps it's Takayanagi Matashiro,
the silent samurai
of the Bakumatsu period,
whose skill was utterly unmatched?
Nay!
Let it be known.
The greatest one
is none other than this underdog.
But what makes this once defeated duelist
the undisputed king?
Is it his deadly finisher,
the Tsubame Gaeshi?
Or could it be that burning vendetta
against his longtime rival Musashi?
Nay!
Nay, I say!
Some think it's prose, some think
it's song, but everyone is wrong!
Even in the face of defeat, he advances!
Even after the throes of death,
he continues to evolve as a swordsman.
Even now, he lives in pursuit
of the perfect strike!
Behold, history's greatest loser...
THE STRONGEST LOSER IN HISTORY
SASA
KI
KO
JIRO
KOJIRO SASAKI
[crowd murmuring]
What? The fate of our existence
is in the hands of this fossil?
What? There's no way he'll win!
Is this supposed to be a sad joke?
[boy] I don't care.
Whatever they say, it's a load of bull.
[growling]
How come he gets to fight for the people
when my papa beat him fair and square?
He's the famous swordsman
Musashi Miyamoto.
He's the hero who should be
named the greatest of all time!
And you know, he also wrote
The Book of Five Rings,
which is practically the bible
of tactical warfare.
Don't you all agree?
I'm totally right, aren't I?
Hmm. Yes, I would say that checks out.
Your father's the only one
who ever managed to take me down.
- [man] Indeed.
- Hm?
I would be fascinated
to hear Mr. Musashi's thoughts.
MUSASHI MIYAMOTO
FOUNDER OF NITEN ICHI-RYU STYLE
[all murmuring]
[Göll] That's not good.
Humans are starting to get restless,
Brünnhilde! What should we do now?
We must believe in him.
And trust in his devotion
to mastering the blade.
Have faith.
[ringing]
[echoing]
What in the...?
What did that mortal just attempt to do?
This is quite the surprise.
Eh! This should
be thoroughly entertaining.
Humanity still has
a few tricks up its sleeves.
The ripples in the water have stopped.
Was it something the old-timer did?
Hmph! What's so cool about that?
It's just another one of Sasaki's
cheap gimmicks he's always pulling.
Isn't that right, Papa?
Uh...
Why did you do that?
Weren't those all your sacred teachings?
We won't be needing them anymore, son.
Huh?
[choking back tears]
[whimpering]
There it is.
He's found that state of enlightenment
every swordsman yearns to reach...
where no man can beat him.
NUMBER ONE UNDER THE SUN
Kojiro Sasaki is
the Number One Under the Sun!
[Heimdall] In this corner,
the ocean god Poseidon,
versus history's underdog, Kojiro Sasaki!
Hm.
THE THIRD BOUT IN THE FINAL BATTLE
BETWEEN GOD AND MAN
Fight!
[gulping]
The tension in the ring is too unbearable.
[humans murmuring impatiently]
Wait, how come neither of them
have budged yet?
Huh.
A false start can leave you
wide open to attack.
I believe that both fighters are
waiting for the other one to strike first.
- [laughing]
- Huh?
Excuse me.
You're sadly mistaken.
Poseidon wouldn't
concern himself with that.
Hm?
If it's withing range, he'll decimate
any object without a speck of hesitation.
That's all there is to it.
Hmm.
He's sweating buckets
from standing in one place.
Can't expect to win with that strategy.
Ha! He's already all tired out
and with nothing to show for it.
Man, what a joke. At the end
of the day, he really is a loser.
That human is meticulous.
He has attempted to engage
in combat for several movements now.
Huh?
From inside his head. Mentally.
Sorry, I thought you were following along.
Uh, I was.
I... Yeah, right!
You meant he was
brainstorming simulations.
Clearly. He wasn't really attacking.
So... The point is I knew that.
[chuckling]
Hmm.
Well, that won't work.
[narrator] The standoff had just begun.
But nobody knew that he had
already been slaughtered 18 times.
What a pain.
No matter how you slice it.
I'm bound to get gored like a fish.
That blondie, he's not one to mess with.
Yes. I wonder if we stand a chance.
Ah, I guess Kojiro's officially
backed into a corner.
I think I'm beginning to see
why they call Poseidon
the most fearsome of the 12 Olympian gods.
That number's wrong. There's one more.
Hm?
Göll, listen carefully, there's
something important you should know.
Uh, what's the matter?
A long time ago,
when the gods were much younger,
just as there were 13 Valkyries,
there were once 13 Olympians.
[Göll] Uh, what do you mean?
I don't remember hearing about that.
One of the deities amongst
their ranks was murdered...
by one of their own.
The killer was Poseidon himself.
[gasping] Betrayed by a god.
That's horrible.
Wait, I have so many questions.
Tell me who the victim was.
The unfortunate Olympian...
was Adamas.
[gasping] I've heard that name.
I thought that was supposed to be
the name of Zeus's final form.
It is.
But it is also the name of an heir,
who inherited the bloodline
of the almighty Cronus.
A birthright he shared
with his brothers Zeus and Poseidon.
Adamas, dark lord of conquest.
Once upon a faraway time...
What's this talk about that little shit
being next in line?
Were those idiots even thinking?
He's a child. If they think
I'll accept it, they're wrong.
[Brünnhilde] Previously,
Zeus and the Olympians worked together
to overthrow the Titans
during the Gigantomachy.
As the second eldest, Adamas disagreed
when they appointed Zeus to the throne.
Incensed and spiteful,
he then staged a rebellion.
At his command, the Titans and the giants
were freed from imprisonment
in the underworld of Tartarus.
He subjugated Typhon, successfully
bending a frightening beast to his will,
and marched onward to Mount Olympus.
POSEIDON'S PALACE
[Adamas] The time has come!
I have secured
the support of Zeus's council.
All members have pledged to follow me.
And there's more.
Thanks to Hermes,
several of the Olympians have promised to
provide me their unconditional allegiance.
You're the only one left.
We will execute Zeus. You and I.
Doesn't that sound enticing?
No sibling should be allowed
to rule over his elders.
That's a reasonable ask, right?
Now then, swear your loyalty.
I'm practically a mentor to you,
right, my brother?
Yes, a terribly pathetic one at that.
[gasping]
[growling]
My apologies. I believe I misheard you.
You're a bit far.
Tell me, what did you say?
You'll need to speak louder.
I want to be sure that I understand you.
Say it once more.
Go ahead. I'm listening.
I expected this from Zeus.
But not you!
You should defer to me, yet you two
act like a pair of worthless brats!
I'm talking to you!
I outrank both of you imbeciles.
Show some respect!
A god needs no army.
Nor to resort to betrayal.
They need only themselves.
A god is complete.
We've always been
the embodiment of perfection.
But you, you've managed to defile
everything we represent.
Bastard!
How dare you try to make a fool out of me.
[whistling tunefully]
Don't mess with me!
[Adamas] Since the day you were born,
you've always been
an arrogant little prick.
To this day...
not once...
Not one single time
did you acknowledge me.
[whistling continues]
Look at me!
[Brünnhilde] In the moment their eyes met,
Poseidon took his brother's life...
with one swift gesture.
Why...
brother?
[Poseidon] Out of the 13 Olympian gods,
it seems one of us
was unsuited to the title.
Wouldn't you agree, Hermes?
[Hermes] Someone has a sharp eye.
[chuckles]
Yes, sir.
[Brünnhilde] On that day forward, his name
was erased from the annals of history.
As if the number of Olympian gods
had always been 12 from the dawn of time.
You know, that does ring a bell.
The shock of Adamas's
attempted insurrection.
I remember.
There was a rumor back then
about how we had a dirty traitor
hiding among the 12 of us, wasn't there?
Oh, the rotten scoundrel was me.
Huh? Mmm.
So, it was you! You betrayed us?
The fallout from the ensuing war
would have torn the heavens apart.
Which is exactly why I found
the prospect too exciting to resist.
Huh? Sounds amazing!
A great idea!
A great big, bloody war!
Can't wait to get my muscles dirty.
Master Zeus was positively
beside himself with elation.
Gimme a break.
All these years and I never knew.
Adamas was a fighter, and to think
he was killed in one fell swoop.
You'd have to be a warlord yourself.
Actually, his precision for bloodshed
is hardly his most horrifying quality.
Hmm?
You see, as soon as Poseidon decreed
that Adamas never existed,
it became canonized
as an undeniable reality.
Whatever he says becomes the truth.
None are granted any room to object.
In my humble opinion,
that's what's scary.
Hmm. Sounds right.
That's what makes him
the force of nature he is.
A paragon. A king of a divine being.
Hm.
I get the feeling
I'm not enough of a threat for you.
So how do you suggest we speed this along?
Ah!
[both gasping]
[shrieking]
This is a tough situation.
[sighing]
But I'm not dying today.
[Japanese pop ballad playing]