From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
That's why we wanted to become true friends.
We crossed that barrier...
I inquire of you, bearfendant Yurigasaki Lulu:
Will you back down on love?
Or will you give up your kiss?
I won't back down on love.
I'll give up my kiss!
Please turn me into a human girl!
I have to go to the other side of the barrier together with Ginko!
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Storm!
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shite
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so give me your approval
kaze ni notte ehon no page ga
As pages from a picture book flutter in the wind
kagirinaku kioku wo yurasu no
so sway my countless memories along with them
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
kurai kono sekai no naka
in this dark world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
Welcome to the Severance Court.
The gate has now been opened.
Severance Court
LOCATION
Let all living beings bear witness to this face-off between man and bear.
I am Life Sexy.
Judge
Life Sexy
JUDGEMENS
I am Life Cool.
Prosecutor
Life Cool
JUDGEMENS
I'm Life Beauty.
Defense
Attorney
Life Beauty
JUDGEMENS
Shiny shine!
As it is, the court is not in session today.
Thus we entertained the thought of telling you all
a story that might elucidate some goings-on.
Your Honor!
Please don't tell me that we're going to do it in these forms.
I know, aren't I way too cute?
Shiny shine!
This isn't cool at all.
You're so adorable, Cool.
Though not as much as me.
Order in the court.
The Princess Who Gave Up Her Kiss
"The Princess Who Gave Up"...
..."Her Kiss"?
The Princess Who Gave Up Her Kiss
Let us begin.
That is sexy.
Shabadadu.
The Princess Who Gave Up Her Kiss
Once upon a time, long before the Severance Barrier had yet to separate man and bear,
there was a certain kingdom of bears inside a forest.
In the kingdom lived a very beautiful princess.
Her name was Princess Lulu.
Princess Lulu was next in line to the throne.
She was to be the next queen.
Princess Lulu was blessed from the moment she first drew breath.
There passed not a day when her charm and grace was not praised by her subjects.
12 Years Ago
Lulu, Age 4
HISTORY
How lovely she is!
Princess Lulu is more precious than any treasure in our kingdom.
Gems and jewel dull in comparison to her brilliance.
We are truly blessed to serve such a beautiful princess.
How happy we are!
It is as you can see. Princess Lulu garnered everyone's attention in her kingdom.
Desire.
But then one day, it happened.
Stars came raining down from the heavens in greater numbers than ever before witnessed.
Day of Severance
HISTORY
They were fragments of the asteroid Kumaria from beyond the earth's horizon.
Princess, it is time to rejoice!
The Queen has given birth to a healthy young boy.
You have a younger brother now, Princess.
Handmaiden
BEAR
The King and Queen are overjoyed.
Handmaiden
BEAR
He is our long-awaited Prince!
Now our kingdom has nothing to fear.
Handmaiden
BEAR
Then... who will succeed?
The Prince.
Shabada! Shabadaba-daba.
At that instant, Princess Lulu lost her position at the top.
Several Years Later
HISTORY
You're adorable, Prince Milun.
He is so precious.
Nothing could make us happier than serving a prince like you.
From the moment of Prince Milun's birth, those of the court—no,
everyone in the country was infatuated with him.
Princess Lulu, however, had become an unwanted child.
Oh my.
Onee-tama!
That kid's a pest pest pest!
Hey, Onee-tama.
Does true love really turn into stars?
It said so in the picture books Mama read me.
Hey, does it really turn into stars?
Well, does it? Does it?
It does. True love rises to the heavens and becomes a star.
A shooting star!
"And the shooting star fell down to the earth and became the promised kiss."
As if love can become a kiss like in those stupid stories. Yeah, right...
Then does the promised kiss shine as bright as the stars?
Maybe so.
You know what? I'll go get a promised kiss for you!
Because I love you so much,
that shooting star must've been my love!
I bet it's fallen somewhere close!
At that very moment, Princess Lulu realized exactly how to get rid of her pest of a little brother.
Desire.
Bear Shock!
Say, Milun.
Do you love your big sister?
Yeah, I love you!
Onee-tama, give me a kiss!
Gladly, if you bring me a promised kiss.
Sure!
Could you sit in that box for me?
Okay!
Love
Die!
Desire.
Now I'll stand atop the throne again.
The world will realize my greatness once more.
However...
I'm back, Onee-tama!
Prince Milun, whom she had taken for dead, returned.
Moreover...
Here!
A promised kiss!
It's bright and sparkly, just like a star!
Th-This is just run-of-the-mill honey.
Onee-tama, you promised! Give me a kiss!
Come on, you promised! Kiss me! Kiss me!
Come on, Onee-tama!
Kiss me, Onee-tama!
I don't don't don't don't don't want it!
Princess Lulu threw the promised kiss
Prince Milun brought her right out the window.
She had no use for something she did not desire.
But once again...
Say, Milun.
Do you love your big sister?
Yeah, I love you!
Onee-tama, give me a kiss!
Gladly, if you bring me a promised kiss.
Sure!
Could you sit in that box for me?
Okay!
Love
Die!
This time for certain I will get my desire.
Onee-tama!
You promised! Give me a kiss!
Come on, a kiss—
I don't don't don't want it!
Say, Milun.
Rest Omitted
HISTORY
Yeah, I love you! Onee-tama, give me a kiss!
Love
Die!
This time I'll get my desire max!
Onee-tama, you promised! Give me a kiss!
Come on, kiss me!
In a surprising twist, no matter how many times Princess Lulu pushed him to the brink of death,
Prince Milun came back to her time and time again.
And in his hands, the promised kiss.
He begged for her kiss with a smile on his lips and a jar of honey in his hands.
I don't don't don't want it!
It happened on just such a day.
Th-The unthinkable has occurred!
Prince Milun
has passed away.
I saw it with my own two eyes.
It was a complete and total accident.
An accidental death!
Either way, my plans have resolved themselves.
Princess Lulu had finally
become the apple of everyone's eye.
I had that same dream...
Porridge, start to boil up.
Bubble, bubble, boil up.
Growl, growl!
All that's left is my special ingredient.
That was no dream.
I did that to Yurizono-san...
But, a human bear?
Why? And how?
Oh, are you awake?
Yurigasaki-san?
I told you to call me Lulu, Kurechin.
Kurechin?
Growl! Kurechin because you're Kureha.
Isn't it cute?
Lulu's a genius!
Who cares? How did you get in here?
The window was open? Well, more like it was broken.
What are you scheming? You snuck into my house and even used my kitchen.
I can only stand so much of your intrusion!
We came to check up on you.
Kurechin, you haven't come to school since then.
I've already informed Yuriika-sensei.
Still... we were worried.
Worried? Spare me.
I'm sure you two have long since become invisible.
You're wrong.
Ginko and I... are your friends.
Friends?
Yeah! So open wide. This is my special honey porridge.
It's so yummy your cheeks will melt right off!
Sumika...
Flashback
Here.
Let's eat together, Miss Gourmand.
It really does taste better when I'm with you.
My only friend is Sumika!
The Princess Who Gave Up Her Kiss
Just about one year ago
HISTORY
Prince Milun passed away, and Princess Lulu
was again the center of attention.
Since then, several years have passed.
Princess Lulu had matured into an elegant lady,
and princes from neighboring kingdoms came to court her.
My Princess.
Bestow upon me your promised kiss.
Let us share a love hotter than the sun itself.
That is sexy.
Shabadadu.
Oh my.
My Princess, you mustn't be fooled by such a bearvert.
Were you to confer upon me the promised kiss,
I would double—no, decuple this country's economy!
I'm so cool.
Oh my.
You two are such fools!
The most important thing for a man is cuteness!
Shiny shine!
I'll follow you wherever you may go, Princess!
The promised kiss...
Oh my.
Well, there you have it.
She received appreciation,
authority, and affection from all.
Princess Lulu received all she could wish for.
If not for Prince Milun's death, she would have nothing.
And yet, Princess Lulu felt not an iota of joy.
Rather, she felt as if—
As if she had lost something precious.
She fell into the depths of apathy.
And on just such a day.
What? I don't need any more dresses or princes.
Milun!
I'm back, Onee-tama.
Here, a promised kiss.
Just how far did you go looking, Milun?
Everyone thinks you're dead.
Real far away!
It was really hard, but I finally made it back home!
But if you give that to me,
I'll surely just toss it aside again.
That's okay! I'll just find it again.
Onee-tama, remember?
You promised. Give me a kiss!
Milun?
Wh-Who are you?
Here.
Wasn't this your brother's?
S-So what?
I found it deep in a valley, so I came to bring it back.
Did you throw it away?
I did.
But it belongs to you.
If you forget what you have lost,
then you'll never get it back.
Take it.
Flashback
I saw it with my own two eyes.
It was a complete and total accident.
An accidental death!
He said that he was getting honey for his beloved sister as usual,
but when he approached the beehive, he was stung and lost his life.
It all happened so fast.
Onee-tama, you promised! Give me a kiss!
From the very beginning, I loathed you,
and from the very beginning, I loved you very much.
What a waste.
Your honey porridge is really good.
I'm the one who made her mad.
I told her that we were her friends.
And then, Kurechin...
Lulu.
Ginko.
My love is to fulfill your love.
If I do that, I get the feeling I'll meet him again.
I'll see him once more.
That's why I...
Flashback
Bye. There's somewhere I must go.
Wait! Where are you going?
Beyond the Severance Barrier.
To the world of humans?
You'll just be killed if you do that.
I'll be fine. I have the love she gave me.
She gave you love?
Yeah. I'm going to do the same.
I want to deliver my love to her.
I promised to meet her again and give her a kiss.
A kiss?
Yes, a promised kiss.
Onee-tama, you promised! Give me a kiss!
Is that girl beyond the barrier?
Yes, I'm sure she's waiting for me there.
Doesn't that mean she's human?
She might kill you when you meet.
So she might.
Are you fine with that?
I am. I'm a crimibear, after all.
I won't back down on love.
Take me with you.
Huh?
I said take me with you to the other side of that wall!
I'll help you fulfill your promise.
I want you to give your promised kiss!
But why?
Because I'm a crimibear too.
That's right. You're like me before my loss.
No, that's not quite right.
You've probably lost once already.
But even so, you can still meet that person once again,
even if they live beyond the barrier!
I inquire of you, bearfendant Yurigasaki Lulu:
Will you back down on love?
Or will you give up your kiss?
I won't back down on love.
I'll give up my kiss!
Please turn me into a human girl!
I have to go to the other side of the barrier together with Ginko!
If you do, then you will forever lose your kiss.
My kiss has already been lost.
I'll never see him again.
But Ginko still can!
I'm sure she can realize her
promised kiss in place of mine!
In short, you want to entrust the wish
you couldn't fulfill to Yurishiro Ginko?
Your desire to self-actualize through her will end in naught but stroking your ego.
That's pride.
It's a sin.
I don't care. I know I'm a crimibear!
I understand. I shall hand down my sentence.
Lily, Approved!
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
This is how Princess Lulu,
or should I say Yurigasaki Lulu, set off for the Severance Barrier alongside Yurishiro Ginko.
Now then.
Will the promised kiss be fulfilled? Or perhaps...
That is sexy.
Shabadadu.
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger