Here, nobody, here.
Always alone.
38th District is sunny.
Slight rock showers.
Chance of rock showers today
is 20 percent.
39th District is cloudy.
Chance of rock showers
this afternoon is 10 percent.
Bebop, here, here! Welcome!
Chance of rock showers today
is 90 percent.
Now it's time for today's news topics.
Today we'll discuss
the mysterious land paintings
that suddenly appeared
in what was South America.
As usual, we have commentaries by
a researcher of supernatural phenomena...
Me, Yuuri Kellerman.
Yuuri, about these land paintings...
Yes, yes. Well, I believe that
it was some sort of a message.
Who would it be from? Can it be...?
Aliens. It has to be from aliens.
However, the land paintings were drawn
by lasers coming from satellites...
The police think it was a prank pulled
by a hacker who got into the satellite.
They already have a bounty
of 8 million woolongs on the culprit...
Listen carefully. The bounty of 8 million
is a conspiracy of the government.
Even if it was drawn by a laser,
there is the possibility
that aliens put a message
into the brain of that hacker.
Once again, the government is
hiding something from us.
I see. A secret cult.
Yes. And that is the mystery that
I have been searching for all this time.
I'll pass on this one after all.
You're leaving me alone with her?
Nothing wrong with it.
She's gung-ho about it.
I'm not the type
to be led around by women.
Then lead her around.
I'm even less the type to do that.
It's easier to...
divide 8 million between two than three.
Here we go.
I'm appalled. You're afraid of hackers?
I just hate tedious work like that.
Guys cheap enough to hack into things
are depressed pale fatsos with glasses.
And I'm sure he's
a demented nerd with smelly feet.
Piece of cake.
Do you have something
against someone like that?
I mean, they might've all been
like that when you were young...
You're saying I look older than you?
You can't tell a woman's age
just by looking at her.
Exactly.
You can't tell just by looking
that I can do things like this...
That's all I know of you.
You guys make a good team.
Hurry up.
I'll be waiting for a souvenir from Earth.
There's nothing made on Earth that's good.
Well... about this incident...
Apparently, an old artificial intelligence
satellite has been hacked into.
The investigation is taking
longer than expected because
the access code
to that satellite has been long lost.
Now a commentary from Mr. Amjad.
Yes, yes.
About the relationship between
Earth and the hacker...
Yes. Since the Gate accident 50 years ago,
the people of Earth have
migrated underground as a result
of the change in climate, namely,
moon rocks falling onto the planet.
To them, the "space network"
created by computers is
necessary for them to stay in contact
with those living in space.
I see.
That's becoming a foundation
to create outstanding hackers.
Radical Edward!
It's the police! Come out!
Yeah!
What? What's wrong?
I saw it.
Why?!
There's nobody in there!
Mistake, mistake.
Okay.
This is where the satellite was
when it was hacked.
This is where it could be accessed from.
I'll look at all the antennae that
can transmit light signals one by one.
I'll ask around for info
on any prominent hackers in the area.
Bebop's looking
for land picture criminal...
All right!
Satellite of long, long ago...
Where in the world is your access code?
Okay. Let's start with all the antennae
that are currently communicating...
That's probably Ed, man.
I hear he's a huge guy, two meters tall.
Supposedly he used
to be a basketball player.
Yeah, I know Ed.
Radical Edward.
I hear she's a very beautiful,
yet whimsical hacker.
No, no, that hacker is a child.
A brat that loves horrible pranks, I hear.
Oh, what I heard from the lady next door
is that that hacker is gay.
Hacker? You mean Ed?
He's an alien.
That's what everyone says.
Hey, man.
Can you buy some of this
as the price for the info?
What is that?
You don't know?
It's "Piyoko,"
a well-known specialty of Earth.
The stolen satellites...
Where are you?
What? What's this?
The information isn't connected to Earth.
It's connected only between satellites.
And nobody hacked into it.
Here, nobody, here.
Always alone.
A voice... inside... head...
Who are you?
What? What did you just say?
Who, you? Here, always.
Edward. A 'net diver from Earth.
Earth?
Yup. Hey, what's your name?
I am the satellite control program
on the D-135 artificial satellite.
What's that? Don't you have a nickname?
Then Ed will give you one.
I know!
Because you're a computer,
you can be MPU.
MPU! Cool name!
Ed is Edward Wong Hau
Pepelu Tivrusky the Fourth.
Ed for short.
Nice to meet you.
Here. A souvenir from Earth.
Is this food?
It makes me doubt
that they have any sense.
Unlike you, I learned some information.
They said that an unknown hacker named
Radical Edward is the suspicious one.
It doesn't mean anything if he's unknown.
I know, more or less.
- It seems okay.
- What kind of thing is it?
Two meters tall. Ex-basketball player.
Beautiful kid.
And on top of it, a gay alien.
Why did you doodle on Earth?
Long, long ago,
long before the Gate accident...
Earth was a beautiful planet
where many people lived.
And back then on Earth,
there were many pictures like this,
and I always looked at them.
I remembered those times,
and I tried
to recreate at least the pictures.
I see, doodles like this were
on Earth long ago, too.
Yes. I recreated them
with a 2-percent margin of error.
MPU is good at drawing.
Can Ed draw something, too?
What? What's wrong?
This is...
The police are putting out
a jamming signal.
Hey! MPU! Hey!
Looks like the cops touched base
with Radical Edward, as well.
Listen! I found your bounty.
What the...?
Bebop!
The real culprit
in the satellite-jacking wasn't a hacker.
Since when do we have
an interactive channel?
No, that's not it.
This is a real-time hack job.
Who is this kid?
I'll send you MPU's data now.
Wait a minute, what is MPU?
A friend of Ed's.
Hey, do you know Ed?
Yeah, because Ed is Ed.
I don't care about that. Who did it?
I could tell you.
But I have a favor to ask in return.
A favor?
Yeah, yeah.
Your big sister will listen to you later.
Come on, hurry it up.
I see. The AI from the abandoned satellite
is doodling of its own will.
What? What's up?
And on top of that,
it was supposedly listed as
a weather satellite,
so nobody suspected anything.
Then this satellite is our bounty?
Since the access code
to MPU can't be used anymore,
you need to go directly to the satellite.
And what do we do?
Break the antennae that it uses
to communicate with the other satellites.
Then make a direct connection
to the satellite and download MPU.
And when you do, don't use
computer support for firing or flying.
What? All manual?
Yup. If it notices you,
all the attack satellites connected to MPU
will automatically fire back.
Is this hard?
It's not just hard,
it's downright impossible.
It's like playing baseball with no bat.
Hey, Spike.
That's the kind of stuff I like.
Hey. Wait, you.
How do you know about us?
I know everything.
Last week, you let Ajiz, a bounty on Mars
worth 1.5 million, get away.
And in Pyortle before that,
the police got to them first.
Are you really that hacker,
Radical Edward?!
Yeah. You've heard?
Connect D-7 to 2. That way,
the main cannon will fire
without a computer.
I'm trusting you, man.
Now listen. Avoid using the missile
if you can help it. It's expensive.
Roger.
1200 to target.
It's almost time
to cut off computer controls.
Now, the only chance...
Once is enough.
Anyway, you can prove
that the satellite itself,
and not a hacker, is the bounty, right?
Ed can do that.
Anyway, please, listen to my favor.
Then I'll give you all the bounty, too.
Oh, you're a surprisingly good kid.
That's it?
Someone...
How was it?
Did you get it?
No, I missed. The satellite
in front of it shielded the blast.
Then you have
to shoot down all the satellites.
All of them?
If you don't, they'll shoot us down.
ECM, eh?
Cheap ones are no good after all.
This is getting pointless.
Approach to within 20 meters of MPU.
That way,
the other satellites can't attack.
However...
Until then, Faye will act as a decoy.
Me?
Yeah, thanks.
Come on, hurry up.
All right, it's all yours.
MPU!
MPU? MPU?!
Oh, Ed.
Ed, we meet again.
They have a bounty on you, MPU.
Bounty?
Yup, but if we copy you
and let them catch that,
you'll be all right.
All right?
And you must be lonely there alone, MPU.
If you come over here,
there are lots of friends.
Friends?
Here. It's not scary.
And so, the strange end to this case.
The captured criminal...
was the AI program for a spy satellite
launched before the Earth was ruined.
According to government sources
from back then, it supposedly would
continue activity on its own
even without commands from Earth.
Well, it was the perfect excuse
for the cops to go on a hacker hunt.
But anyway, why did it start doodling
on the Earth with a laser all of a sudden?
I'm sure...
that was because it got lonely.
Yoo-hoo, Bebop!
Hey, over here! Hurry!
Promise, promise.
Well, let's get going now.
But the kid is saying
something about a promise.
Promises are made to be broken.
Anyway, let's get going. Liftoff!
Not coming, not coming.
What is this?! What's going on?!
What did you promise?
It's a promise...
to be a member of the Bebop.
Amigos, all you bounty hunters.
It's finally time for Big Shot!
Now today's hot news.
You heard about the doodling satellite
that got caught?
Of course. It had a big bounty on it.
Just a few moments ago,
the Earth police made an official report.
What was it?
"This bounty is only for when humans
or other life forms are the targets.
It is difficult to determine whether
or not a computer program is a life form.
To begin with, from the viewpoint
of biological logistics..."
What's that? I don't understand well.
In other words,
they can't pay up on non-living things.
Oh, my!
To those who caught it,
I feel sorry for you.
Hey, Jet, did you know
that there are three things that I hate?
Whatever.
Rugrats...
beasts...
and tomboys.
Don't give me that.
Why do we have all three
neatly gathered here?
Ed loves Piyokos.
And once again we didn't get any bounty.
Hey, wait, you're a girl?
Really, nothing good comes out of Earth.
No regrets about the woman who ran away,
but a small thorn still pricks the heart.
Letting one flow along with time itself,
living all alone from that day to this.
But to the sounds of waves
that come and go,
the migrating birds
find their hearts drawn.
Next episode: "Ganymede Elegy."
Jet Black will sing it up full of soul.