Can you see the shining eyes of the children?
The Hatsuya Department Store has everything children love.
Bugs. Yes, insects.
Back in the day, you'd have to hike in the mountains to catch them,
but nowadays you can just buy them in stores.
What's your favorite insect?
What's that bug called?
I wonder. Maybe it's a big rhinoceros beetle?
That's our treasure for the day.
It flew into a fisherman's boat just last night.
Scientists have been saying
it might be a brand new species!
That sounds interesting.
I'm not giving it away
for under a hundred grand.
That's four of my monthly paychecks...
A hundred?
My one hundred grand!
What could be happening?
A fog... A black fog has appeared.
There have been reports the past few days
of a black mist disrupting flights and trains.
This must be it.
What's this fog?
Don't worry.
Thanks for helping me.
Who are they?
Bugmen from Tartaros.
Report on that!
This is your job, isn't it?
We couldn't show it on air anyway, could we?
A shapeshifter!
August
Concrete Revolutio
Superhuman Illusion
I could hear the voice cursing fate
I could see the way to use my power
It's not words you're looking for, right?
You want to see the love beyond them
Justice isn't on my side
because I follow my own guidelines
Come on! Wake up! Let's go!
Someone wished for these illusions,
and protecting them to the end
will clear the tainted skies
Our clashing cries won't solve anything,
and yet that's what we make our reason to live
This world is so far gone
but only those who continue to search
for ways they can change it
can bring about the revolutio for the future
In the
"Black Mist"
Shinka 45
Summer Festival
Nothing's changed at all.
Winner
I won!
Would you look at that!
Another one then!
This one won too!
Winner
There's nobody here.
They must all be in university
or looking for jobs by now.
August
Meteoterre.
Little Hoshino, witch powers...
...should only be used to help people, right?
But nobody's looking now.
We'll never get to return
to our homeland like this.
Oh, the news should be on.
You can turn it on too, Ullr.
As we reported earlier,
the black fog that appeared around 9 AM this morning
flowed from Ginza towards Kasumigaseki,
What could that be?
and currently, at 11 AM,
it has engulfed the Diet building.
No idea.
There are just too many superhumans
and rivaling evil on this planet.
There hasn't been an official announcement,
Science. Magic. Aliens or time travelers.
but there are reports of the Prime Minister,
some of his cabinet, and other staff being trapped inside.
It could be any of those.
Time to go. We've got work.
Hitoyoshi! Don't just barge in!
It was locked too!
This is a shelter for superhumans
prepared by the Department.
Of course I have keys.
But more importantly,
we've got work to do. Get dressed.
Is it the black fog?
No.
The Department specializes
in dealing with superhumans, right?
The government hasn't officially recognized
the existence of superhumans.
But we exist.
I mean, I'm here.
And there are aliens like Große Augen too.
We fight evil aliens and monsters.
They still don't acknowledge it officially.
At newspapers or TV stations,
you could get fired just for publishing a photo.
Then sometimes the disputes of superhumans
cause trouble for normal people.
Don't call them "disputes."
They're clashes between
the forces of good and evil.
Our job is to deal with incidents secretly,
and to oversee and protect superhumans.
But is that black fog
unrelated to superhumans?
We have no records of any superhuman
that could be associated with it.
Then what's our job today?
Security Unit 1 head to the Diet building,
take control and provide reinforcements.
Guard Units 1 and 2, check for survivors.
Guard department, report in regularly.
Uh, Hitoyoshi!
Patrols, arm yourselves and secure the perimeter.
Jirou, where are we going?
Three, four!
Here I go!
Wait!
No one could get inside the black fog?
They should just let that robot
detective handle stuff like this.
I'm a shapeshifter!
I can pass through stuff!
Hold it!
Stop pulling pranks!
Surround him with people!
He can't pass through living things.
Geez!
A shapeshifter?
Get your stuff done, Kikko.
You're so rude again.
Meteoterre.
Wh-What are you doing?!
What a convenient size.
You would fit in the overhead container.
I'm not carry-on baggage!
Sorry. We're from the Health
and Welfare Ministry's division... uh...
Supervision of Human Resources.
So cute!
Whoa, that's so cool!
Superhuman Department, huh?
Now that you mention it,
I think I've heard of that before.
That there are people
who protect the superhumans.
Wait. Institute of Supervision
of Human Resources?
Super... Human...
Where's the "Department"?
What's with this kid?
He's a shapeshifter.
Ah, similar to Ogre Emi?
Monsters and shapeshifters are different.
Monsters are an old line of intelligent
life forms different from humans.
Shapeshifters, however...
...are?
I don't really know.
They love to play with children
and never physically mature.
That's about all we know.
This is the first time I've seen a real one.
I see.
So you're all superhumans too.
I'm the only regular human here.
You're regular?
Whatever.
It sounds like fun, so count me in,
Superhuman Department!
Slow down.
We're not recruiting now.
Kikko only just joined
our ranks a few days ago.
I'll be blunt.
We've taken you in so that you
can't cause any more trouble.
We'll register you and check
on you regularly at your home.
I've got no home.
There was this kid I got along with well,
but then they kicked me out for
playing too many pranks on him.
I'm a homeless shapeshifter now!
You're surprised, aren't you?
Let's go and catch those
Tartaros bugmen already!
Tartaros? What are you talking about?
Oh, you don't know?
The monsters who control the black fog!
What?!
Boss, nobody's been able to get in touch with the
Prime Minister and his staff in the black fog, right?
It appears so.
But the Public Security Forces
have already mobilized.
Here you go.
Come on, I'm not actually a dog, you know.
You might look like a kid,
but you're different inside, aren't you?
Stay put.
I'm forever a kid, so I can play forever.
That's what being a shapeshifter is all about.
You grow at a different
rate than humans, don't you?
People all die in a few decades.
Even then, I'll still be a kid.
We're perfect for each other, don't you think?
H-Hey!
I just don't get girls.
Concrete Revolutio
Superhuman Illusion
There hasn't been an official announcement,
but there are reports of the Prime Minister,
some of his cabinet, and...
I've heard of Tartaros bugmen before.
But that was ages ago. Literally.
I thought they lived in a different universe.
If they're an evil organization,
then there should be a superhuman to counter them.
Right. That's the rule.
But they're nowhere to be seen now, are they?
We should just go home.
Retreat!
The PSF superhumans...
This might turn out to be
a job for us after all.
Ouch!
It was the bug from this morning.
I'm so glad I could see you again!
Again? Have we met before?
I want to ask you something. I—
Sorry, I've already got someone I fancy!
I just met her today, but—
That's not it!
I want to be friends with you.
Friends?
That's it?
Yes.
Getting along with kids
is the job of shapeshifters!
My name's Campe.
I'm Fuurouta!
Sorry, I was on my way somewhere!
See you around!
Oh!
Campe?
Was she a shapeshifter too?
Shapeshifters shouldn't
play tricks on each other!
I'm sure that was written in the
shapeshifter rulebook or something!
Is this it?
Hitoyoshi
There hasn't been an official announcement,
but there are reports of the Prime Minister,
some of his cabinet, and other...
Sorry for the wait, Akita.
Not at all.
Your help is much appreciated, Professor.
How's Jirou doing?
He works his part.
Is that it?
Before the war, when I was in South America,
I was shown a grave of giant insects now extinct.
The world's reign shifted from giant insects
to amphibians, then to reptiles.
But why would the insects
step down in the first place?
Maybe the Tartaros bugmen are what those
giant insects evolved into after moving elsewhere?
I cultivated the virus I found at the grave.
This is what brought them down
300 million years ago?
Yes.
Are they superhumans?
No. They are invaders.
Even if they used to reign supreme on Earth,
we have no reason to accept them now.
Welcome back, young master, Lady Emi.
Sorry, I just got this urge to eat out today.
It's fine.
You've got work tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
I know.
Those two are living under one roof.
Wait, you knew?
Emi was Professor Hitoyoshi's assistant
while studying at the university.
That's how she met Jirou.
Then they both got a job at the Department
where the professor is an advisor.
But living together?
They're dating, so who cares?!
I just thought I'd tell you...
I've known about it forever!
I can't just quit the Department now!
You're wrong!
I just want to work to protect the planet!
Wait, Kikko!
I'd recommend running, young man.
August
I'm from the Division!
Don't take me lightly!
I've been looking for you so long.
I've finally grown enough to take you on.
What?
Die, Fuurouta!
Hitoyoshi?
Long time no see, Fuurouta.
You haven't changed at all.
What are you doing here?
I've told you, Campe.
Campe?
August
All superhuman members of the
Public Security Forces have been confirmed dead.
This means that we cannot disregard
the Tartaros bugmen any further.
Just yesterday they told us
we weren't needed, didn't they?
We can't let them be
after they invaded the Diet.
I'll go.
Nice, Jirou.
But they might turn out to be superhumans
who strayed onto the path of evil.
So let me try negotiating first.
We've just gotta beat the bad bugs, right?
I'll do it!
It's cold!
Moron!
The virus is hibernated in liquid nitrogen.
You're here to meet your lawyers today.
I know about the bugmen.
I can enter the black fog too.
Plus, I want to do something good.
Something good?
And if I succeed,
let me join the Department!
Fuurouta!
Thus you came after us.
After "us"? What do you mean?
Why are you here?
Oh, you again? I'll save you!
Take this!
Did that work?
That was close.
Hey!
Don't let humans or Tartaros catch you again!
Did you let them go?
Nah, that was just a big bug.
I can talk with bugs and other animals, you know.
I was the queen of Tartaros.
The queen?
While still immature,
I was caught by some humans.
They put me on sale.
Then you saved me.
The black fog came for me.
Then you're really—
Since ancient times, the Tartaros bugmen
have lived in the Japanese forests.
That was their deal with humans.
But modern politicians knew nothing
about that and sold off state-owned forests.
Loans with state-owned forests as collateral
Government report submitted
Having lost their home,
they came to punish the politicians.
With the black fog.
Then I...
What happened to your people, Campe?
You know well what it was that you threw.
A virus...
Campe is the last remaining Tartaros bugman.
So that's why you came.
I thought that you at least were my friend.
I had no idea you're of
the same kind as those bugs!
Still, I was happy.
There were still people out there
who'd try to get along with us.
However...
Stop.
I told you.
I intended to attack you as well.
Even if your goal was right,
your means was unfit for
a superhuman of justice.
It's fine.
I did something that can never be fixed.
You think your sole life could pay
for the millions of Campe's kind you killed?
You could never compensate for it.
What would taking Fuurouta's life change?
I still can't forgive him!
You can't forgive him
because you were friends.
Can't you forgive him,
because you are friends?
Look at me, Fuurouta.
I've grown up.
You're still the same as back then.
We can't be friends now.
Things were so much simpler back then.
Yeah.
There were bad guys,
and good superhumans beat them.
I was a hero of justice too, right?
When did things get so damn complicated?!
I can't tell good and bad apart anymore!
You and I are enemies too! I don't get it!
Is it because I'm forever
a kid that I can't understand?
I wanna grow up too then!
No, it's fine.
You just stay the way you are.
It's fine.
Let us now decide whether
or not to let Fuurouta join.
Please raise your hands if you agree.
I think he can be useful.
I find his shapeshifting interesting.
What about you, Hoshino?
I don't think this is a place suited for children.
And...
I've been against the idea
from the start. That means—
Huh?
Why?
He thinks we fight evil
and protect good superhumans.
Huh?
With him around,
I'll always be able to remember that too.
That's why we need him.
It's fine.
Just stay the way you are.
There is one single detective at the Metropolitan
Police who specializes in dealing with superhumans.
I've got a soul of justice and a body of steel.
I work in secret for the peace
and safety of the people.
Don't call me superhuman!
I'm just a detective.
The Iron Man
Detective Shiba Raito!