O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
This is a victory for us!
Jetzt, hier ist ein Sieg
Our fame starts here!
Dies ist der erste Gloria
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
"I died for naught" — I won't let it end like that for you
muimi na shi de atta to iwasenai
until I am the last one standing
saigo no hitori ni naru made
The enemy is cruel... We will kill—
Der Feind ist grausam... Wir bringen...
The enemy is colossal... We will jump—
Der Feind ist riesig... Wir springen...
In our hands we hold blades of glory
ryoute ni wa Gloria
and sing in the name of victory
utau no wa Sieg
We bear the wings of freedom on our backs
senaka ni wa Flügel der Freiheit
Swearing iron determination upon our hearts,
nigirishimeta ketsui wo hidarimune ni
we slash apart the circle of idiocy
kirisaku no wa Ringe der Torheit
and soar through the sky
soukyuu wo mau
with our wings of freedom
Flügel der Freiheit