You forgot something.
As you can see,
I'm just some old man.
Unfortunately, I don't have any children.
I never said it was yours.
Oh, was it a customer's?
I will hold it, then.
How about it?
Wanna go somewhere?
It's a little too early to go to bed.
I'm an early riser. I go to sleep early.
If you want a prim and proper life,
I have just the place for you.
A hotel where you get three meals
and a bodyguard, all for free.
I'm sure that's impossible
without a reservation.
I'm talking about Hotel Prison,
Teddy Bommer.
I'd rather not, Spike Spiegel.
Oh, you know me?
It's a popular story among criminals
that we never want to be caught
by you, or by Andy.
Andy?
I will fulfill my objective!
It won't blow up.
I took out the ignition pin.
Three million woolongs,
graciously accepted.
That's not the only bear.
You'll die, too.
I love them to death.
Why do you want
to blow stuff up so much?
You wanna know? I'm giving a warning.
I am ringing a bell of warning!
All right, be mindful of what I say!
Andy.
Andy?
Call me Wyatt Earp.
You! Teddy Bommer, serial bomber!
Me?!
The fact that you'd plant
a bomb here today
was easy for me to figure out
after calculating your criminal cycles.
You don't think it's him?
He's a security guard!
Just look at his face!
In this day and age, a face means nothing.
Then what is the basis of your theory?
That is--
My gut instinct. Yes, inspiration!
Hey, wait!
Wait!
Oh, shit.
That's why I said
Teddy Bommer was that guy, you idiot!
Dangerous!
That was a close one.
- A horse?
- Yeah, a horse.
A horse, huh?
I thought it was fishy when you said
you'd nab that guy as part of your trip.
What do you mean by that?
You used the food money for all of us,
didn't you?
- Come on.
- What did you use it on?
If you think I'm lying,
explain this on my back!
All right, I hear you.
- The horse I can believe.
- You can?
But you have to be more creative
than a cowboy in a cowboy outfit.
Is that the problem?
- Now, if he was dressed like a samurai...
- That would be more plausible.
Here he is, little Andy!
"Little Andy is a guy in the YMCA."
A Christian?
Nope. Young Men's Cowboy Association!
Such a thing exists?
But he got kicked out soon after joining.
The reason?
Because he caused others trouble!
Of course!
"Andy von de Oniyate,
the noble son of Oniyate Ranch."
Hey, he's pretty cute.
"A hundred and twenty-three cases
of property damage.
Eighty-nine cases
of destruction of public property."
Many, many people injured.
A good match for someone we know.
- I told you he existed!
- All right, I hear you.
- Any reactions?
- None yet.
However...
we can't let it explode
with all these people around.
His only target is the building.
He's not one for murder.
You think we can trust him?
Guys like him are often concerned
with their sense of style.
Well, this is the perfect party
to hide yourself.
Did you know that a serial bomber
is gonna come here?
To tell the truth, I didn't know.
Well, he's coming.
Hey!
The world is about love and peace!
- Yo.
- How did you know it was me?
This lead the way to its papa.
I think I would've known in either case.
You guys just don't quit, do you?
Speak for yourself.
Why do you want
to blow things up so much?
You wanna know?
I am giving out a warning.
Listen, in this world,
the root of all evil--
A horse.
A cowboy.
- Hey, you! Teddy Bommer!
- Me?!
- See, I told you.
- Or is it you over there?
Do you have no memory?!
We met just yesterday!
I have no recollection.
You!
Sir, your horse is an inconvenience.
It proves rather troublesome
for our other customers.
Oh, my beloved steed, Onyx,
is no ordinary horse!
At times,
she sets my troubled mind at ease,
- at others she is my chess partner.
- Like horses play chess!
It doesn't matter either way.
I detest being ignored!
What happened to his sense of style?!
Calm down! I'm telling you to calm down!
Love and peace, man!
Such a lovely horse.
Do you like her?
Would you like to be my escort?
Now, get behind me.
You little--
In my life, I've never seen such a...
tasteless room.
Now, I present you with my
special son-of-a-gun stew.
I'm sure you'll find it
extremely delicious.
So, why are you a bounty hunter?
If you're so rich-- I mean,
if you have so much comfort in your life.
Why? Let's see.
Because it suits me.
That feeling a cowboy gets
when he corners a bull.
But you don't have to go after
such a dangerous bounty, do you?
I know why nobody wants
to go after Teddy Bommer.
Nobody wants
to get a piece of the explosion.
You think we can worry about that?
Yes! I don't worry about things like that!
Once I set my mind on something,
I can see nothing else!
I think I've seen this personality
somewhere before.
Oh, nothing.
Now!
Here's looking at...
my reflection, kid.
Cheers.
Hi, I got a souvenir.
A souvenir! A souvenir!
I ain't gonna eat that!
Guess this is for dinner.
I will not eat that.
Your stomach will suffer.
But what about him makes you so hotheaded?
They're too similar.
You know how
similar people hate each other.
What part of me is similar
to that shit-headed idiot?!
The part that makes you damn troublesome.
Oh, big shot has already started.
Well, the last thing we have to tell you
is info about T.B., Teddy Bommer.
Can you believe it?
We got a message from him,
just for this show!
What? Is that for real?
Let's see.
"Warning: This is for those
that have made fun of me.
My next job is your last chance.
This time, I'll blow you up as well,
like fireworks."
My, my, he doesn't sound calm.
"That is,
if you know where I will set up next.
And lastly,
I will tell you my true intent--"
Whoops, looks like time is up for us.
That's all for today.
I'm sorry I couldn't read all of it, T.B.
Well, until next time.
Good luck!
The next one's in city hall.
You figured it out already?
T.B. is blowing up tall buildings
starting with the tallest one.
The reason was that simple?
What are you gonna do?
I'm getting out of this one.
I'm gonna pass, too.
Spike, what are you going to do?
Like you have to ask?!
Late!
Damn it! If they think they can get away
with this, they are sorely mistaken!
- You alone?
- How dare you take so long to get here?
Wait!
Wrong guy.
I never intended for humans to be targets!
But you guys are different!
Guys like you deserve--
He's here.
You! It was you!
So, you finally remember me.
- You always--
- You always butt in and get in my way!
You're the one that's in the way!
Now that I have both of you here,
I will tell you.
The reason why I continue
to blow buildings up is because--
Today we settle the score
once and for all.
What?! That's my line!
Listen to what I have to say!
- Shut up!
And you are? Who are you?!
Can't you guys put some effort
into your work?!
- We have to catch him first!
- Wait!
You guys take me too lightly.
That elevator door will never open again.
And once it starts moving, that's the end.
It will never stop.
At the top floor,
my cute little bears will greet you.
So, the moment that the elevator
reaches the top floor...
boom!
Well, live what little you have
of your life left without regret!
Farewell, and good luck.
Rest assured. I understand.
I know how he does things.
Don't worry. I know how he does--
This afternoon,
I reverted the secret emergency code
that had been changed. Yeah.
I reverted it this afternoon!
Change after change...
means it's back to where it started!
Stop, you idiot!
What do we do?! What do we do?! Oh, no!
Stop. Shit. It's too tight!
- You are in the way!
- What? Get out of the way, damn it!
Farewell.
Come to think of it,
they were brave young men.
They're climbing, those two monkeys.
They like high places.
So, they are similar.
Let's just go back.
Then I'll go turn him in.
You don't even deserve
to be called a cowboy.
I will never forgive you.
I lose.
That was some punch.
You are a true cowboy.
As of today, I will no longer be a cowboy.
This really is a hats-off!
So... what are you gonna do now?
I will no doubt find a new way of life.
See you, Space Cowboy.
Well, it was only a rich boy's hobby.
His level, no, rank,
was really no match for me.
Hey, are you listening?
Yeah, yeah.
So, he just wasn't any enemy of mine.
Of course,
I never had him in my line of sight.
- Hey, are you listening?
- Yeah, yeah.
But, anyway, why did you want
to blow stuff up so much?
I wanted to give a warning...
about all the unnecessary waste
created by capitalism lacking philosophy.
Planets that needlessly gets colonized.
Media that needlessly gets circulated.
And buildings that are needlessly tall
to symbolize it all!
And by destroying them, I wanted to raise
the question
of how a true pioneer should be.
Wait, wait, wait!
Andy!
Call me Musashi!
Go, Jiroumaru!
But...
it was all a waste, wasn't it?
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
Did you pay close attention to me
and my wonderful role?
Hey, wait a minute.
- Now, the next episode, the next story--
- Why are you doing the preview?
Once again, it's time for me, Andy,
to have an active role in the story!
Your turn on the stage is already over!
Now that I'm a space samurai,
watch me completely crush cowboys
left and right!
You're not in the show anymore!
Next episode of Cowboy Bebop,
"Andy Strikes Back!"
- The title is nothing like that!
- Please look forward to it.