Rin.
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
Hey!
You bullies shouldn't gang up on someone like that!
You suck!
You really suck!
What's your problem, Tohsaka? This is none of your business.
In that case,
why don't you do take it out on me, as well?
Then it will be my business.
Hey.
This is boring!
Here!
You used too much prana at once.
Maintain a calm mind.
In order to control magic,
you must first control your mind.
Lose control,
and the prana will rebound back to your body.
Too much power, or its wrong form,
won't only endanger you,
but those around you, as well.
Strive to consistently maintain the proper flow.
That is the Tohsaka family motto.
It means always remaining reserved and elegant.
You shouldn't keep quiet when they do that stuff, Kotone.
If they're the offenders, you have to get mad.
You're amazing, Rin. You always speak your mind.
It's not amazing.
I think it's normal.
That's right... It's normal.
Put out your hand.
Father, teach me more!
How do I make something like this?
Hmm...
It might be a bit too difficult for you right now.
But if you work hard every day,
you'll be able to make it eventually.
After all, you're a daughter of the Tohsaka family.
Hey, Rin...
Can you show me how to do this part?
Of course. Where?
Me, too!
Me, too.
And me...
This was on page twenty-three, in the textbook.
Here you just did the math wrong.
For this problem...
It's just like in this example.
Kotone?
Have a seat. I'll help everyone in turn.
Okay!
Do I have to go live with the Zenjo?
Once the Holy Grail War begins,
Fuyuki City will no longer be safe.
I want to help you win the Holy Grail War...
Rin...
You mustn't cause trouble for your father.
Are we in the way?
Not at all.
This time, I'll need to make extra battle preparations.
That includes making sure you are safe.
And in order to do that,
you cannot stay in Fuyuki City.
I'm certain there's something I can do to help!
That's right...
I just haven't learned how to yet.
So all I need to do is study on my own.
I-I don't understand at all...
What is this? Jeez!
Du, wer die Tür geöffnet hat,
wird Freunde sein.
I have to close it.
Für die Aussage nimm meine Hand
wir werden in meinem Zimmer treffen.
I can't move.
Klein? Groß? Schlank? Steif?
Rin!
Are you all right?
It's still too soon for you to read this book.
Some things in this world
contain their own prana.
This is called a prana compass.
Normally, it doesn't indicate anything.
But if there are prana traces in the area...
Rin, try generating prana in this.
Okay.
See? Like this.
And with that book...
Anything that provokes a reaction like that
is beyond your ability, so take care.
I'll give this to you.
As an early birthday present.
Thank you, Father!
Once the Holy Grail War ends,
we'll try some real Jewel Magic.
Then strange things started to occur.
They said we have study hall again...
The morning news was talking about the kidnappings again.
In Fuyuki City, the sudden disappearances of children...
The teachers are still having their meeting.
They said we won't have fifth period today.
All right!
But they said we should stay home.
Why?
Another kidnapping...
They said only children have been kidnapped.
Hey, did you hear?
They said the body isn't inside the coffin.
Supposedly, it was in really bad shape.
It definitely happened in Fuyuki, right?
U-Uh, my name is Tohsaka,
The person you have called is not home.
and I'm in Kotone's class...
Please leave your message after the beep.
Please be safe...
Kotone...
This is Fuyuki at night...
It's completely different from daytime.
It feels really terrible.
What is this?
I've never seen it act this way.
There are traces of magic everywhere?
I have to find Kotone!
Someone out with a kid this late?
What was that?
Oh, no!
Whew...
If they find me, they'll take me home.
You've gotta walk, kid.
Two of them?
There are more kids.
Why?
Wait... Why am I hiding?
I can't accomplish anything this way!
No one's here?
H-Hey!
Kotone!
Kotone! Kotone!
Did they do something to her?
What do I do? Something...
Huh? Are you lost?
No... Um...
It's fine.
We're just about to start a party.
But we still don't have enough people...
You wanna help?
The more, the merrier. Right?
No!
What was that?
Don't run...
He's using that bracelet on them?
Ow!
I have to destroy it!
What? So you are gonna help me?
Huh? What?
You used too much prana at once.
I can destroy this!
Kotone!
Rin...
What's going on?
There's no time to cry! Run!
Hey! Wait!
Oh!
Man...
I hope he won't be too pissed.
Huh?
Where's Rin?
What a relief...
I should start back.
I did it, Father.
What?
Anything that provokes a reaction like that
is beyond your ability, so take care.
Rin...
I can't believe she went to Fuyuki...
Rin!
Rin...
Rin is fine. She's just asleep.
Kariya...
What? What's happening here?
What are you doing here?
Your face...
Behold the Matou family magic.
You offer your flesh, and your life is slowly devoured.
That is the magic's price.
But Sakura is fine.
I'll save her before this happens to her.
Zouken only desires the Holy Grail.
He promised if I win it for him, he'll release Sakura.
The Holy Grail?
Yeah, so don't worry.
My Servant is the strongest.
It won't lose to anyone.
Right now, Sakura dares not even hold a speck of hope.
So since she cannot, pray for her sake.
For my victory...
For Sakura's future.
Kariya, you...
Some day, I'm sure
we'll all play in this park, like we used to.
and Rin and Sakura will be sisters once more.
So, Aoi,
you don't need to cry anymore.
Kariya...
After you kill Tokiomi...
Do you intend to die?
Mother?
Rin!
I was so worried...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
My lord Kirei,
are you certain you wish to leave
Tohsaka Tokiomi's wife and daughter like this?
It's fine.
Continue monitoring Berserker's Master.
Understood.
It wasn't much, but I did manage to do something.
But I guess I'm still not an adult.
I passed out halfway through.
That means I need to work harder.
But that's fine for now.
I'll have plenty of time for that later.
Someday, I'll fight as a Tohsaka magus.
I'll have to practice really hard,
and obey my father, so that I can be ready when the time comes.
And when that happens,
I'll do the best I can, as elegantly as I'm able.
Episode 10
Rin's Adventure
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
A weak king is even worse than a figurehead!
Of what worth is a king who fails to protect the powerless?
We stand to lose nothing.
A Reality Marble?
I shall have to kill you myself.
Your goal was supposed to be world conquest!
Next Time:
The Grail Dialogue