Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Yo!
Sis!
How'd the test go?
Same as always...
Another disaster.
We have more free time during testing...
...but you end up following your usual schedule...
...so you have to cram the night before, right?
You should act more like someone applying for college...
Under
the
Sun
Thousands of manga and games were confiscated from the suspect's room.
Based on his methods, it is believed that other crimes can be attributed to him.
Another story about this...
Incredible...
There was another person like you on the news.
Every time this happens, it makes me think how it isn't fair.
They always use these kinds of manga as examples.
There are good manga out there.
They just never get mentioned.
R-Right...
I feel kinda bad.
You're a good person!
Usually, people just make fun of me for being a helpless otaku.
Looking at the people I know...
...sisters tend to absorb characteristics from one another.
Like you and Cousin Yui...
Or Kagami and Tsukasa...
I was talking about that with Big Sister this morning.
You're really close to Miyuki-chan.
You're as close as sisters.
I see.
It was absorption?
Kona-chan!
Happy birthday!
I would have forgotten if Tsukasa hadn't mentioned it.
Congratulations.
Thanks, everyone!
It makes me happy when people celebrate my birthday...
...but at this age, I really can't be happy about getting older.
Nah.
It makes me super happy.
Why?
Do you want to get a driver's license?
Because I can play adult games now.
Haven't you been openly playing them the whole time?
Of course not...
You've grown older...
...without aging mentally or physically.
Let me go!
Miyuki probably gets mistaken for someone older.
'Cause Yuki-chan looks like an adult.
When I go out in my normal clothes...
...I occassionally get mistaken for an office lady.
So they skip straight past college.
In your case...
...if you walk around in normal clothes...
...they'll think you're in grade school.
Say what you want.
Starting today, I'm an adult!
What are you talking about?
Besides...
...if you're an adult now...
...shouldn't you be less passionate about anime and manga?
Y-You still need to have a child-like
heart filled with passion and dreams!
Make up your mind...
This?
While Big Sister's at work...
...we're going to secretly prepare a birthday party for her.
Sorry I'm late!
Okay!
Let's get everything ready.
Yes!
Happy Birthday
Big Sister
And here's a call from Konata.
Wonder if she'll be coming home soon.
Konata?
Sorry!
Forgot to tell you...
...but my coworkers are throwing a party for me...
...so I won't be eating dinner at home.
And I'll be coming home late.
Yutaka.
Doesn't this taste great?
We worked hard.
Yui-chan.
You can take that off now.
Future aspirations, huh...
I have dreams and stuff...
...but it's kind of hard when you stop and think about it.
That's right.
The major you decide on...
...will have an effect on your career.
First is nutritional science.
Second is fashion design.
Third is marketing.
Since I like cooking and sewing.
So you wrote down your dreams.
And what about you, Miyuki-san?
I want to be a doctor...
...so while I didn't write down colleges...
...I put medical schools for all three choices.
That's our Miyuki-san.
You have a clear goal.
What about you, Kagami?
Me?
My first choice is law.
My second choice is economics.
My third choice is literature.
Sheesh.
Too boring.
Is that a bad thing?
What about you?
First Choice
Brigade Chief
Second Choice
Nanto Shinken Master
Third Choice
Storyboarder
Here we go.
Some people try to turn it into a joke.
Actually...
...do you have any talents besides making faces?
Talents...
I can name every Poke**n!
Th-That's definitely amazing.
But it has nothing to do with your future.
Here it is!
I'll go pay for this.
When you buy magazines and manga...
...you always take one from the bottom.
Everybody's already touched the ones on top.
I'd rather buy a clean one.
I know what you mean.
Like when I go to a sushi-go-round...
...I order straight from the chef...
...instead of taking them off the belt.
You know...
Most of the ones on the belt are already dry.
You do that?
What a bad customer.
No way!
You don't?
What a scrooge.
I've been wondering...
How can you stand reading books that are all text?
Don't you get sleepy?
But this is a light novel.
It basically feels like reading manga.
Sure about that...
There are plenty of insert pictures...
...and the writing is simple.
Why don't you give it a try?
W-Well, you know...
They already made an anime of it.
So I'll just watch that.
If it were a manga...
...you'd be talking about how the original has its own merits...
...and check both out.
Just read it already.
I must respectfully pass.
But you know...
You read lots of stuff besides light novels.
How should I put it...
When I become more culturally refined...
...my soul becomes richer.
Well, it's like food for the soul.
I see.
What is it?
By that reasoning...
...the snacks are for making your body richer.
Shut up!
Aren't there also light novels...
...serialized in the magazines you read?
Not just comics.
I look at the pictures...
So despite everything you say...
...your love is pretty weak.
You skim, huh?
Fine!
Be that way.
I'll read it!
Hey, it's okay.
No need to push yourself.
I only skim 'cause I have lots of other stuff to read!
Fine by me.
I didn't say a thing.
Oops!
I forgot my world history textbook.
I left it on my desk after studying.
Konata.
Lend me your world history textbook.
You didn't take it home, right?
Okay.
Did you forget yours?
That's unusual.
Here.
Hiiragi.
This is one fun textbook.
No, this is...
Not getting anywhere...
Guess I'll find something to drink.
Sheesh.
Huh?
Thought there was some leftover from last time...
Gives me a chance to get some fresh air.
They're closed!
This is some kind of challenge, isn't it?
Your total comes to 320 yen.
Huh?
What's wrong, Sis?
Yeah...
When you're in a bad mood...
...you make a bunch of little mistakes...
...which just makes your mood worse, right?
I know what you mean!
You can't seem to do anything right.
Like a negative spiral?
That's right!
I baked a cake.
Want some?
Yay!
Studying is rough...
...so you have to take breaks now and then.
That's it!
I'll bake cookies tomorrow!
That'll relieve stress.
I'm counting on you!
Afterwards...
Now I've got a new source of stress.
Right?
Don't you agree, Iwasaki-san?
That's right.
Those two are so busy that they keep missing each other.
I know what you mean.
That's right.
Big Sister is applying for college...
...so I shouldn't disturb her studying!
Sorry...
I'm going to talk softer.
Yu-chan.
Let's play a game after you're off the phone.
Get your game on!
Say what?!
Guess this is the last year I'll be wearing this uniform.
That gets me thinking...
There's something inside.
My favorite handkerchief that I thought I had lost...
It was in my summer uniform's pocket, huh?
Didn't we have some wasabi octopus?
What is this?
What was this?!
It's changed so much I can't tell...
It sure rains a lot in the rainy season.
Sure does.
It starts getting really hot...
...and then we switch to our summer uniform just in time...
...but the temperature can suddenly drop, which sucks.
You guys are still here?
You're lucky since you can change your clothes whenever you want.
What are you talking about?
It's so much easier when you don't have
to think about what to wear every morning.
You're really wack, Teacher.
Ya-ho!
It's the rainy season!
So humid!
Sis.
Cousin Yui.
It sucks how it's always raining.
Do you want some tea?
Please.
On a happier note...
...it's almost been a year since you got married, right?
That's right.
Time sure flies.
The image of a raining sky...
Is like the image of Cousin Yui's heart when her husband
is away on business with their first anniversary coming up...
Her heart is...
Sorry...
That was my fault.
It's okay.
I'm used to this kind of pain.
Here.
Have something warm to drink.
But I'm still depressed...
It's delicious.
That's a relief.
Sheesh.
At this rate, my love's going to rust eventually!
If you took it to an auto repair place...
...it'd probably be good as new after 45 minutes.
You could at least comfort me...
Sorry.
Force of habit.
Hello?
So you can come home!
Didn't even take 45 minutes.
It was like an instant.
That's right.
You haven't gotten your clothes back from Matsuri?
That's bad.
If you don't ask for them back soon...
...she'll say they're hers.
That would be bad!
I really like those!
I envy Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san...
...for having two sisters.
Pretty much.
Really?
In my opinion...
...I'd rather be an only child like you two.
Right?
I get that feeling sometimes...
But you know...
...you can do so much more with a bigger cast.
Like the story set in olden America...
...of a mother and her four daughters...
...waiting for the father to return.
Or an enigmatic band of female thieves who target art.
One, two.
Huh?
One too many.
Seriously...
She turns every conversation into
something about anime or games.
Hey, Kagami.
Did you buy the stuff for dinner?
Did you forget to tell her, Tsukasa?
Sorry...
What? What?
What's going on?
Geez. Did you forget?
Mom and Dad are out tonight.
Their trip was today?
So then...
...we were supposed to buy groceries for dinner.
I completely forgot.
I called Kagami's cell...
...and left a message.
You have 1 message
Matsuri.
Just use what's in the fridge.
I finally get a chance to cook...
Just let it go this time.
Sheesh.
This is all your fault!
Sorry...
Fine.
I'll go now.
Geez...
You just had to go and say that.
But...
And does she even know what to buy?
Geez, man...
She doesn't even like to cook that much.
Why's she so worked up?
Sis!
Tsukasa.
Sis...
You don't have the shopping list, right?
They're late...
If you're gonna worry...
...you should have gone yourself.
You're late.
What's wrong?
Matsuri was really worried.
The usual store was out of saffron.
I said that curry powder would work...
...but Sis insisted that we find some, so
we went to the supermarket farther away.
Geez.
You didn't have to do that.
So sorry.
Come on.
Let's make dinner.
Whew, I'm starving.
Here.
Sorry for the wait.
That just leaves Matsuri's masterpiece.
I'm done!
It looks great!
Looks like it was cooked just right.
Hey, Matsuri.
When did you learn how to cook this?
I went to this one restaurant with
some college friends a while back..
...and this was on the menu.
It was so good...
...that I wanted to let you all try it...
...so I asked for the recipe.
I'm surprised they gave it to you.
Anyway, chow down.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Listen to this.
Your father got the date wrong.
What do you mean?
The reservation was apparently for next week.
Straight out of a comedy...
Dinner now?
You haven't eaten?
Paella, is it?
Matsuri made it!
Oh.
That's amazing!
But Kagami bought the ingredients for it.
She went all the way to the farther supermarket.
Then I'll help myself.
Good idea.
This is pretty good.
Who took the mussel?
Mussel?
Was I not supposed to?
Unbelievable!
I was saving that for last!
Then write your name on it.
Geez. Stop fighting.
Yo.
I'll hang out with you after school today.
Do you need to buy something?
Shin** Yamada's new book.
Though, we have a bunch of homework lately...
...so I don't really have time to read.
I also have a pile of unread manga by my pillow.
But I end up going for a new one.
I kinda know what you mean!
Finish your old stuff before you buy new ones.
Well...
It's reassuring if I buy it first.
Or I end up feeling unsatisfied otherwise.
Right?
Don't look at me.
Good lucky!
Okay!
Let's have a blast today!
We're already on the seventeenth episode of Lucky Channel.
Okay!
Your navigator...
Red roses have thorns!
The platypus of the idol world!
Akira Kogami!
And...
Hello!
...we've invited a really big guest today!
How long are you going to make me wait?!
Crap.
He really did come back.
Sorry, sorry.
Here he is...
Um...
Today's guest...
Special Guest
Meito Anizawa-san
...is the Anime Manager:
Meito Anizawa-san.
Okay!
This program is too weak!
But...
Um...
Lucky Star is a slow and relaxed anime...
...about completely ordinary high school students.
Which is why...
...Lucky Channel should be considered...
...slow rather than...
That won't work!
Where'd he go?!
Fast!
Listen.
Do you know what the three factors
for determining an anime's success are?
The three factors?
Um...
Voice actors, animation, and script?
Wrong!
My back is burning red!
The answer is...
The answer is?
The staff and cast's love for the show!
And time!
And production cost!
Well, those factors are all out of our control...
Understand?
It doesn't matter how good the original work was!
There's no point if the script is bad!
It doesn't matter how hard the voice actors work!
It won't work out if the characters aren't in color!
Just look at Shiraishi.
N-Now I'm white(shiroi)!
Each respective part requires its resources!
You have to put your all into the work!
Love and passion are what...
...truly create a beautiful piece of work!
Is that how it works?
You.
You're currently Akira Kogami-san, correct?
Currently?
I've always been Akira.
When you were Rou**n!
Gao**nger!
**tato!
Mai**i!
Didn't you have love?!
What are you talking about?
If you still have regrets...
Nope. None.
...you should burn yourself out as Akira Kogami!
Like I was saying...
Okay!
I will burn myself out as Minoru Shiraishi!
Well said, Shiraishi!
Okay, first of all.
How to work a live event!
Over?
You were MC at an event recently, right?
Bye-bee...
You were watching?
Of course! It's my job!
Good work, everyone!
It was a huge job.
I'm leaving now...
My nerves were a wreck the whole time.
You still have a lot to learn!
Shiraishi can handle the rest.
First, your ad libs are weak!
Yes!
You shouldn't be losing to Sugita—
Minoru
Shiraishi
Theater
Ma'am!
Are you unsatisfied with your husband?
Hello. Minoru Shiraishi here.
Now, please listen to me!
Sweet sunshine!
Looks peachy, doesn't it?
Hey!
Wrapping for a uniform...
Turn-off, ain't it?
Hey!
Just work it!
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
I sweat! I sweat!
DARLIN' DARLIN' F R E E Z E!!
FeeLING crummy!
SomethING's coming!
I LOVE you so!
Oops!
I screwed one upsie-up!
A nail biter!
A steel beater!
Cut that out already!
Is that new blushing flower...
...considered a normal girl or what?
Wowzers!
Take it!
Firm noodles!
Fill 'er up again!
DA-DA-DA!
BON-BON
Cheerleaders!
How about it?
Yeah!
Leavin' an impression.
Take it!
I'll still be laughing in the end!
'Cause it's a sailor uniform.
← Q.E.D.!
It's only Sunday and I'm already blue.
※Fast forwarded for your convenience.
What to do?
I'd rather wear my summer clothes.
← So cute!
3 pics incoming!
That's a toughie to pick!
Ooh ☆
Just work it!
To the limit!
MY DARLIN' DARLIN! P L E A S E!!
Next Episode
Well, next time...
Too boring, Shiraishi!
Stop following protocol!
Heil Braiking!
Manager!
Okay!
Now listen to me!
Lessons on how to become a big-time voice actor!
Number one!
Lesson number one!
If you can't beat them, join them.
That's sad!
Next time:
「To Each Her Own」
To Each Her Own!
That's it for Anizawa. Goodbye.
Finger!