Space travel log 0968.
It sounds good to call the bounty-hunting
job a "freelance" job...
but all that means
is that we're self-employed.
When we have no jobs,
we have none at all.
Well, that's all a part of our destiny...
but it's troublesome
that we're out of money,
And so, we get urges
to make quick cash.
Any problem with using these?
Evens!
Evens, is it?
No, odds after all!
Odds, is it?
Yeah odds.
Double ace Even.
I can't eat any more
Well, it would be easiest for me
if you paid up in cash.
So, what'll it be?
A man does not take back his word!
That's why I told you not to do it
Humans were meant to work
and sweat for their money after all.
Those that try to get rich quick...
or live at the expense of others...
all get divine retribution
somewhere along the way.
That is the lesson.
But one thing about humans
is that they quickly forget
the lessons they just learned.
Damn it.
There was a fridge way back here?
"Survival of the fittest"
is the law of the land.
To fool and to be fooled
is the reason we live.
I've never had anything good
happen to me when I trust others.
That's the lesson.
How much did you swindle?
Would you stop saying things
that would hurt my reputation?
He lost on his own!
Because he couldn't see
through this cheat?
It's part of one's skill
to see through it.
At least give his clothes back to him.
I'll lend them to him.
Greedy, aren't we?
It's rough out there in the real world.
Hey, what's up?
Something bit me.
What do you mean, "something"?
It wasn't a rat!
Look at this! This wound on my neck!
Hey!
This is silly. It was a waste
of time running over here.
Spike! I was bitten around that fridge!
Fridge?
You have a clue?
I'm sure there was something.
Nope, can't remember.
You sure this is gonna work?
The only thing it doesn't work on
are myopia and cavities.
- Then it works on athlete's foot?
- Of course.
Don't you have something more
legit that would get rid of sores?
That would be this.
- That gets rid of sores?
- Yeah.
Crush this, and you boil it
in three cups of water until
the liquid simmers down
to 1 cup, and you drink it.
Spike, isn't there something
more different?
Oh, I got just the thing.
Yeah, give me that.
Give me what you had before.
Hey I'm feeling a lot sicker now.
Do I look pale?
You're pretty pale to begin with.
What is this awful smell?
- Herbal medicine.
- Herbal medicine? This?
It smells like you just left a rag
that cleaned up spilt milk out to dry!
I think it's more like rotten soybeans.
Knock it off!
I have to drink this, you know!
Oh, brother.
Hey, now, this goes too far for a joke.
It was a rat, right?
There's nothing to make a fuss about.
Am I wrong?
I have no clue.
He seems to have gotten some poison
that's not in this database.
Looking at similar poisons.
Cryptosporidium.
That's not it.
Cholera?
Nope
Ebola virus?
Nope.
Bifidobacterium?
Not even close.
What is it?
Ein, you're being noisy.
I can say for sure
that it wasn't an ordinary rat.
Hey, keep it quiet.
So, what is it?
Well, it's...
A mysterious space creature!
Spooky! The attack
of a horrible space creature!
Oh, yeah, there's that possibility.
Yeah, right.
Then what is it?
It's not in the database.
- Yeah.
- These base-pairs are weird, too.
You think so?
We've never seen symptoms
like this before either.
Other than a space creature,
what is it? What is it?
Well, perhaps something like
a rat went through a mutation...
and evolved into
some mysterious creature
and carried a mysterious poison.
What's that about?
That isn't too different from the
"mysterious space creature" theory!
This is too silly.
Aiya, what are we gonna do, Ein?
It's a space creature!
It's spooky!
All right. This is made
to sense heat sources.
It's usually used
to find bounties that are hiding.
Can you see me?
All right, I'm gonna test it,
so move just like I tell you.
Ein! Where are you going?
Hey, wait!
Hey!
That's weird. Is it broken?
Was that response from you?
That story you were telling, about some
mysterious creature or something.
- Oh, yeah.
- What happens if you're bitten?
I can't say for sure until we catch
the creature, but I'm going to guess...
death?
No, why did it have to be this way?
I still have a lot to live for.
I haven't committed any crimes.
I'm still young and lively.
Lively?
Oh, poor little me!
Hey, now, why are you getting into this?
August 6th. Skyday.
Today, we will go look for the spooky,
mysterious space creature.
Lesson, lesson if you see
a stranger, follow him!
Are you here?
Are you here, Mr. Spooky Creature?
Ed! Ein!
Hey! This isn't hide-and-seek!
Exploration, experimentation, exclamation.
Lights shine bright in the many towns.
I will come back alive.
I trust you, Ed.
Ein!
Are you in here?
You're not in here?
Answer me!
Really...
Ein, Ed What happened?
Ein!
Hey, hang in there!
Where's Ed?
I can't believe it got you this easily.
You're a dog! Where are your instincts?!
No choice. Guess I'm going in!
Cruising down Route 66.
Approximate cruising time left: 82 hours.
From here, we will enter full autopilot.
After passing the gate, this ship
will automatically land on Mars.
The route cannot be changed
after confirmation.
Ed! You aren't here, are you? Hey!
Did that thing get her, too?
Don't surprise me!
I've been waiting for you!
Excellent!
Come on, you slime!
Got him!
This thing seems familiar.
I guess I should have eaten that.
Oh, yeah, it should be in the fridge.
That was when I remembered everything.
It was, oh, one year ago.
When I'd gotten a hold of a real lobster,
I hid it in the fridge in this stockroom.
Just so nobody else would eat it.
But I had forgotten about it,
and left it in there for a whole year.
I wonder what it looks like in there now.
Shit!
Damn it!
You shouldn't leave things in the fridge.
That is the lesson.
Sweet bean roll!
Can't eat anymore.
And so they all passed away.
Everyone, it was brief,
but thanks for your support.
This was the last episode.
I hope they rest in peace.
Amen.
And starting next episode,
we bring you "Cowgirl Ed"!
I'm the main character!
Hey, wait a minute!
What kind of selfish crap is that?!
Next episode: Jupiter Jazz, part 1.
There really is another episode!