</lyrics>
Mazui presents
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemuri asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I open my eyes again, to a sleepy morning
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to
教室のドア潜ると
When I pass through the door of the classroom
honno sukoshi mune wo hatte arukidaseru
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I puff my chest out with a little bit of pride
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind that blows past everyday life
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す　今この胸で
It started to shake within my chest
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would come now
iku oku no hoshi ga kie satteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched countless stars as they vanished
miokutta te wo futta yokatta ne to
見送った　手を振った　良かったねと
I waved goodbye, "I'm glad"
Teaching Staff Building
Principal's Office
Why is the new song a ballad?
Is that bad?
For a diversion, yes.
Um...
What do you mean by "diversion"?
Didn't I tell you during Operation Tornado?
She leads a school rock band which is very popular amongst the normal students.
We don't directly cause any harm to them,
but sometimes we use them, and if they're in the way we have to remove them from the scene.
At times like that, we use GirlDeMo to divert their attention.
They're pretty trendy for NPCs.
It just goes to show that their band has real skill and appeal.
So, no good?
A ballad is kind of...
We won't be able to carry out a flashy operation if it's that kind of a calming song, right?
I see, rejected then.
Well then, let's get back to the briefing.
Here's everyone's orders.
Otonashi-kun.
Close the curtains.
Our next operation will be the revenge of the Angel Area Invasion Plan.
We commence in three days.
You want to use that plan?
But last time—
This time, this person will be accompanying us.
Pleased to meet you.
From behind the chair?
Four-eyes.
What kind of joke is this, Yurippe?
Will a coward like him really be useful?
Now now, don't say that.
Then...
I'll test him!
You don't have any friends, do you...
3.1415926535897932384626433832795028841971693993751058209
Stop!
Please stop!
No way, Pi?!
Four-eyes.
Stop, stop!
That guy's an idiot!
That's right. Our weakness is that we're stupid.
That's not something the leader should say...
In our last invasion plan, we displayed a clear lack of intelligence.
However!
This time, by using the man who made a name for himself as a genius hacker —
handle name "Takeyama-kun" — the planning team can do a detailed investigation of the area.
That's not his real name?
If you could, please...
Call me Christ.
Look, you went and ruined his cool handle name.
That's Yurippe for you.
So, what is this "Angel Area"?
It's where Angel lives.
Where she lives?
I wonder what kind of place she lives in...
Wait, why would we need a hacker for that sort of place?
The core is computer-controlled.
It's mechanical?
There must be a way to get through to God in there somewhere.
This plan is crazy!
Considering this is our second attempt, Angel will have tighter security than before.
We'll need GirlDeMo to put on an especially flashy show.
Understood.
Get chance and luck!
Beneath Connection Bridge 2
Good, I'm doing well.
Wait, aren't I getting a little too used to this?
But those guys aren't as bad as my first impressions of them.
Classroom block B  Message Board
Is this the "flashy diversion"?
Ah sorry, did I startle you?
Oh, it's you.
You know me?
Yes!
My senpai who always walks around with a huge axe told me to be wary around you because you bring calamity or something.
That bastard...
But is it okay to advertise that it's in the sports hall like this?
No, it's quite dangerous. Unheard of.
It's not even a guerrilla live this time, it's an announced event.
The teachers won't ignore this, and there's no knowing what other obstacles we'll face.
But I heard that the plan this time requires that we go this far to gather an audience.
Girls Dead Monster, huh...
By the way, you must be...
I'm Yui!
I'm still an underling in the diversion unit.
But I'm happy with even just that!
I get to be a GirlDeMo roadie!
Do you know? Girls Dead Monster are amazing!
"GirlDeMo" for short!
They perform amazingly for an all-girl band,
and above all they have Iwasawa-san on vocals and guitar!
She even does the composition and lyrics!
My favorite is Crow Song!
The climax feels like it has such amazing resolution!
The lyrics are about Iwasawa-san, and...
And, and, you know what pumps me up?
Alchemy! Alchemy is...
I'm not finished yet! Alchemy is...
Do you have time to waste here like this?!
Work a bit more seriously for your beloved GirlDeMo!
Oh yeah!
Well then, excuse me.
Classroom block A   Empty classroom
Whoop!
Sorry, I need to restring my guitar.
Okay, break time.
You guys were on fire.
I can understand why the students go crazy for you.
Before I realized it, I stopped to listen.
Thanks.
So, you don't have any memories?
Yeah.
Must be nice.
Are your memories also...
Someone else told you about their memories?
Yeah, Yuri.
Oh, Yuri...
Hers are the worst.
Mine aren't that bad.
Not as bad?
It's nothing much.
I couldn't sing the songs I wanted to, that's all.
My parents were always fighting.
I didn't have my own room,
so I just crouched in a corner with my hands over my ears.
My only escape was to hide in my own little world.
There was nowhere I could rest.
That's when I discovered a band called Sad Machine.
The vocalist was in the same kind of unhappy situation as me.
I heard that when things were painful for her, she'd cover her ears with headphones and escape to the world of music.
I tried it too.
It was like everything was blown away.
The vocals screamed for me.
They grieved for me.
The ones who put on the act of common sense were wrong.
Those who cried were right.
We, the lonely, were more human.
They screamed at the absurd, beat it down, and destroyed it.
They saved me.
I first met it one day abandoned in the rain.
That's when I began singing.
Even in such an empty life as mine, I had songs.
Are you serious?
With your grades, you could go anywhere—
I don't want to rely on my parents anymore.
I did part time jobs for a living,
and kept auditioning at recording studios.
I told myself I'd leave that house when I graduated.
I'd go to the city, and then...
live by my music.
That's what I thought.
Huh?
Maybe I'm tired...
I can't play the guitar like this...
Maybe I should cancel the performance tonight and rest...
When I woke up, I was unable to speak.
Cerebral contusion.
It was aphasia due to a stroke.
The cause was an accident during a fight my parents were having.
I cursed my fate.
I had nowhere to escape.
And like that, my life ended.
Iwasawa!
Oh, Hisako? Okay.
We're tired of waiting already.
No-memory boy!
You can have that.
Just now...
Those were eyes that curse the unfairness of life.
She also had a harsh life.
No one's afraid of becoming a water flea.
The people here...
They're all trying to rebel against God,
against accepting an unfair life.
They're trying to fight it.
Just overlook it this one time, president!
Yeah, GirlDeMo's live concerts are the only fun we get to look forward to!
Don't take that from us!
Yeah, yeah!
Right?
Huh?
Where'd she go?
It's almost like I'm the bad guy.
Sports Hall
Got it? The operation this time will be carried out with the bare minimum number of members.
It will take place today, 1900 hours.
Operation start!
Too few...
You get a special seat.
It's time.
Alright...
Let's put on a show!
Clear!
Alright, infiltration successful.
What?
Angel Area infiltration.
Close the door!
Takeyama-kun, we'll leave the computer to you.
Call me Christ.
Um... this is...
This is just a normal girl's room!
We're trespassing!
What the hell are you doing?
Girl's Dormitory
This is the girl's dorm!
Turn off the light!
And "computer-controlled"?
There's just a computer in the room!
A password...
Nobody could figure it out before.
I see.
Then this is where I demonstrate my skills.
Beginning analysis.
Oh? Looks like you're not so useless.
Hey come on, respect people's privac—
Hey, stop!
You're too noisy.
Keep it quiet, or I'll be taking your throat out.
What the hell!
I was just starting to think you weren't so bad, too!
Why...
We need more people to come...
Alchemy? This soon in?
That's good!
I want to live forever
mugen ni ikitai
無限に生きたい
And if I could live forever
mugen ni ikiraretara
無限に生きられたら
Everything would be granted
subete kanau
全て叶う
All sorts of things
iroirona mono ga
いろいろなものが
Keep having their way with me
atashi wo oikondeku
あたしを追い込んでく
All the time I have to live
ikiru nokori jikan wo
生きる残り時間を
Warping where my dreams will go
yume no zahyou wo kurue
夢の座標を狂え
Even though they're so important to me
zenbu daiji na mono na no ni
全部大事なものなのに
If it's all I can, right now
iza kokora de chotto
いざここらでちょっと
I'll go eat something sweet
amai mono tabete yukou
甘いもの食べてゆこう
Stop thinking like that
sou iu shikou teishi
そういう思考停止
It's meaningless to talk
katari to muimi datta
語りと無意味だった
I look back at the path I walked and
aruitekita michi furikaeru
歩いてきた道振り返る
What the hell is going on?
What are you doing?
Go back to your dorms!
No way! We have to watch this!
That's right! Why don't you just go away!
Yeah!
She's here!
Give me more energy, everyone!
No, no one can do that for us...
We'll do it with our own strength!
Angel has appeared.
Understood.
Takeyama-kun.
I'm currently running a high speed password-cracking program.
It will be done soon.
Also, please call me Christ.
We're in.
Good job, Takeyama-kun!
Copy all the data!
That would take too much time.
An hour, at least.
And please, call me Chri—
Why don't we just take the whole hard disk?
She'll notice that!
So what do we do?
Just show us any suspicious data, Takeyama-kun!
It's Christ!
A list of students?
NPCs...
No, we're included too.
It's just a name register!
There's not going to be anything suspicious there!
This really is just trespassing!
Shut up!
The diversionary squad has been suppressed.
Angel is returning.
We're out of time...
We didn't manage to get anything this time either...
We're retreating.
Dammit, stop screwing with us!
Stop it!
This is for us!
Let them go!
Their music supports us!
Please!
We were just being lenient till now.
Don't get cocky!
We're confiscating all these instruments.
It's not the cultural festival or anything.
We won't let you get away with this again.
I can throw this away, right?
Don't touch that...
Don't...
Don't touch that!!
Stop that!
Stop!
Hand it over.
joushiki butteru yatsuga waratteru
The ones who ignore common sense laugh
常識ぶってる奴が笑ってる
tsugi wa donna uso wo tsuku
What will they lie about next?
次はどんな嘘をつく
sorede erareta mono
What will be gained
それで得られたもの
daijini kazatteokeru no?
Can we hang it proud?
大事に飾っておけるの？
The new song...
hito wa sore demo susumanakya naranai
Man must go on regardless
人はそれでも進まなきゃならない
sonna no wo utau yo
That is my song
そんなのを歌うよ
Takeyama-kun!
Got it. And call me Christ!
naiteru kimi koso
It's because you're crying
泣いてる君こそ
kodokuna kimi koso
It's because you're lonely
孤独な君こそ
tadashii yo
You're right
正しいよ
ningen rashii yo
That's being human
人間らしいよ
otoshita namida ga
Those tears I cried
落とした涙が
kouin wo
In time...
光陰を…
konna ni mo utsukushii
It's so beautiful
こんなにも美しい
uso ja nai
It's not a lie
嘘じゃない
hontou no bokura wo
For the real us
本当の僕らを
arigatou
Thank you
ありがとう
This is my life...
To go on singing like this...
This is why I was born.
Just as I was saved...
I'll save someone else like this.
Finally...
I finally found it.
Iwasawa...
Can you summarize what we learned, Yurippe?
Angel is developing her own powers herself.
And strangely enough, it looks like she's doing it the same way we make weapons.
What does that mean?
I'm not certain yet,
so I won't say anything now.
Come on, don't be so secretive, Yurippe.
The fact that she needs to use the same methods as us...
The only conclusion we can draw from that is...
the worst case scenario.
There are no gods anywhere.
Why doesn't Angel get her powers from God?
Why does she have to develop them herself?
I'll bring up the next issue then.
Where did Iwasawa-san disappear to?
Didn't Angel erase her?
But it was in the middle of a concert!
What are you saying happened, then?
Who could have done that to Iwasawa-san...
No one.
She accepted it herself.
That's all there is to it.
To disappear, you have to obey what Angel says and lead a normal student life.
But that isn't the only way.
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつも一人で歩いてた
I've always walked alone
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返ると　皆は遠く
When I turn around, everyone's far behind
sore demo atashi wa aruita
それでも あたしは歩いた
Even so, I kept walking
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That was what strength was
mou nani mo kowakunai
もう何も怖くない
"I'm not afraid of anything anymore",
sou tsubuyaitemiseru
そう呟いてみせる
I try to whisper to myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Everyone becomes alone someday
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They live on only in memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ　愛し笑ってられるように
So I can laugh with my heart, even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will show no tears
Play ball!
I'll be useful!
It's baseball.
Don't stop the dancing!
It's a challenge, kid.
This is Iwasawa's replacement?
I don't know what the hell I did before I died!
Yui, nyan <3
Let's make the best team ever!
Just who are we fighting?
You're fired.
It's a punishment game more terrifying than death.
Your team is not registered.
That might feel better than anything yet...