This is the Flower
of Forgetfulness.
I believe a Death Spirit
who recovers his memory
becomes a ghost because of
the attachment to his life on earth.
That's why, if his memory is erased
with this Flower of Forgetfulness...
But...
- Staying a Death Spirit by losing
- Whose fault do you think
- by losing his memories
- it is that I look like this?!
- or becoming a ghost
- You said it was the cat
- by holding on
- on the second block, right?
- to the memories.
- Y-Yeah, it's because of the cat.
- Which one would
- The cat, the cat, the cat!
- make Takuto happy?
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I couldn't say it last night
or the night before.
I'm going to say it tonight.
Yeah.
Hey, are you all made up,
graduate?
Takuto, you're coming too?
Stupid, do you think I would
miss your graduation?
Oh, right.
Hey, hey,
if you're like that already,
you might even cry
before the graduation!
Huh?
Make sure to smile
as you graduate.
Yeah!
Wakana Kimura.
Yes!
Mitsuki Koyama.
Ma'am...
Congratulations.
Kumi Sagimiya.
Yes!
Congratulations, Mitsuki.
We finally graduated.
It's farewell to
this school today.
But next month, we're just moving
to the junior high next door.
Yeah.
I'm just so glad that I got to
graduate with all of you.
Of course you'd
graduate with us!
Mitsuki.
- We should be going soon.
- Oh...yes.
Mitsuki!
Dr. Wakaoji...
This is the first time
I've come here with you.
Yes.
I am sorry.
Grandma...
Dad, mom... I graduated from
elementary school today.
Aoi, Hazuki, she will be thirteen
next month and go into junior high.
I will take responsibility in
raising your daughter well.
Grandma...
That's right. Mitsuki, there is still
a very long road ahead in life.
Doctor Herberd,
who will be present at the surgery,
is set to arrive in
Japan next week.
Thank you, Dr. Wakaoji.
Sure.
All right.
Well, we do wanna end
with something great,
so maybe we could
do "Myself."
And then...
Do you want me to say it?
No, I'll say it.
Say, Mitsuki.
Continuing our conversation
from before...
Huh?
The conversation about how
we should do the concert.
Oh, yeah.
I thought about the order of the songs,
but how about this?
Y-Yeah.
Looks good.
Doesn't it? Now we have to
think about stage direction.
Mitsuki...
Actually, I won't do it today.
We grew wings when
we did "Myself" before.
Is he okay?
Yeah.
But...
Don't worry about it.
Leave your concert up to me.
Of course I believe in you,
Takuto.
But... But what if...
What if there is a way for you
to not have to become a ghost?
If there were a way,
I would have done it already.
In that case...
Is there a way?
You become a ghost because
you recover your memory.
Isn't that true? Then...
You're saying I should
erase my memory again?
Y-Yes.
No thanks.
Just like how you graduated
from elementary school with
all sorts of memories,
I want to graduate from being
a Death Spirit with all my memories.
It's totally better
to do it that way
than to throw away all your memories
to be a Death Spirit forever.
Takuto...
I was able to make lots of
good memories this year.
Most of all,
I was able to meet you.
By being around you, I was able to
feel like I was making music too.
It was fun.
It's thanks to you that
I was able to sing.
I'm also really glad I...
Even I know that nothing is
going to happen by saying this.
You are a human being
and I am a Death Spirit.
It's something no one
can do anything about, but...
I like you, Mitsuki.
Well...I just wanted to say that.
But you can just forget about it.
I guess it's one-sided.
Oh man.
Happy birthday, Mitsuki!
- Happy birthday!
Thank you, everybody.
You turned thirteen
before the rest of us!
You're so grown up!
Hey, hey, if a 13-year-old
is a grown-up, then what am I?
Oh, Ms. Oshige!
Hey, you seem too be
doing well.
- Huh?
- Wow! Madoka Wakamatsu!
Hello!
Why?
To tell you the truth, I told her
that today was your birthday.
And I came here
for my precious fan.
Huh? Weren't you
a fan of Full Moon?
Huh? Well, I like Full Moon,
but I also like Madoka.
Well, that's fine.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I have a birthday present
for you in this backpack.
Wow, thank you very much.
Open it and take a look.
Okay.
This is...
It's a ticket for my concert
the day after tomorrow.
By the way, Full Moon will
also be performing.
It's the other way around!
You're performing in
Full Moon's concert.
She never changes.
I have ones for your friends too,
so all of you please come.
Actually,
since we're fans of Full Moon...
- We already have tickets!
What?!
Yeah, we all decided to go.
Then I'll give the tickets to
your Grandma and Ms. Tanaka.
I apologize, we also already...
It's my first show since
Fuyuko Komaki's dinner show.
Oh, what should I wear?
Now then, please give me your signature
on the surgery agreement.
Mitsuki, are you
all right with this?
Doctor, I will entrust
myself to you.
Mitsuki, let's do our best.
Yes.
I like you, Mitsuki.
Eichi... What am I
supposed to do?
Please forget about me.
You don't need to worry anymore.
You can just forget about it.
Why did both of them
say the same thing?
But this feeling...
Why do I feel the same way
as when Eichi said it?
I don't wanna. I can't forget
about either Eichi or Takuto.
Because Takuto is...
One more day left.
At least tomorrow, I'll...
I see.
I don't understand
these kinds of feelings.
How can I feel this way?
You can.
It's okay to feel that way.
I was the same too.
When I was teamed up with Izumi,
I really liked him.
At first, my feelings
didn't reach Izumi,
but after confessing my love to him
over and over again, finally...
But Izumi never really
opened his heart.
Division Chief, why?!
Why do I have to pair up
with this newcomer? I'm...
Izumi Lio...has requested
to disband from you.
Izumi! Why did you...
A person's feelings are
unstable and unreliable.
That's why,
what you're saying...
I thought that if I had to experience that,
I never wanted to be in love again.
However, when Takuto came around,
I started to like him.
Although in the end, my heart
was broken by Takuto as well.
No way.
It's okay.
I don't regret it at all.
I'm fine if Takuto is happy.
I bet Eichi feels the same way
about you too.
Meroko...
Don't you like him? Why don't you be
more honest with your feelings?
But...
It doesn't mean
you'll forget Eichi at all.
You're alive. Of course
a new romance will begin.
That's what it means to live.
What you have to do right now
is convey your true feeling.
Takuto will surely understand
if you tell him the truth.
KOYAMA
Welcome home.
Izumi and Jonathan.
What do you want?
I was wondering
what happened.
Did you already have
Takuto drink it?
No, but I'm going to talk
to him about it now.
Is that so?
Take care.
Izumi, you're not acting like yourself,
being so concerned about Mikki.
You think so?
Since some people
abandoned their work,
I wonder what's going to
happen to Mitsuki's fate.
Her fate probably
won't change though.
You think so?
Do you really think
that fate can't be changed?
What is that?
The Flower of Forgetfulness.
It's the only way for you
to not become a ghost.
The Flower of Forgetfulness?
If you drink this,
you'll forget all your memories.
What do you mean all?!
Memories from when
you were a human,
as well as after you
became a Death Spirit.
Y-You've got to be kidding.
But Takuto, if you don't drink it,
you'll become a ghost!
Stupid, I already told you!
I'm gonna be around until
your concert is over!
But I don't want you to become
a ghost even after the concert is over!
Mitsuki...
Takuto, please.
No, I'm definitely not
going to drink it.
Why would you go that far to
try to make me drink this?
Right now, I can touch
your hand like this.
But if you became a ghost...
I told you to forget
what I told you!
Wasn't that how you really feel?
I also want you to
always be by my side.
I don't want to lose you.
I...
If I can listen to your singing,
to Full Moon's singing, tomorrow,
then that's fine.
Even if I become
a ghost after that.
I don't want that.
That's not fine at all!
Then it won't be Full Moon's
LIVE concert.
Doesn't live also mean "to live"?
That's what you taught me!
But then how can you be fine
with becoming a ghost?
This is your live concert. As long as
you have the passion to live...
You're wrong, Takuto.
Full Moon doesn't
just belong to me.
I was wondering for a long time
what Full Moon is.
And I finally figured it out.
Full Moon is a dream that
Takuto and I created.
Meroko, Ms. Oshige, and Dr. Wakaoji...
Everybody helped to
build this dream.
You said it yourself. That you felt like
you were making music with me.
Full Moon is a dream that can't be
seen without you and me together.
Full Moon's live concert
won't be a live concert
unless we feel that
we need to live.
Mitsuki...
Takuto...
Let's live together.
Let's make tomorrow the first day
for the new you and me.
Yeah, you're right.
Takuto... I like you.
Mitsuki, I...
Hey, Takuto, what are you doing here?
This is no time to be daydreaming.
Meroko...
There's no stopping now that
we've made it here.
We have to do
what we can do.
Thanks, Meroko.
You're right.
We have to prevent her from dying,
no matter what!
Yeah!
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Fated Day."
- Look forward to it!