Why are we forced to work?!
Why must we pay money in order to eat?!
Can't we all just share?
The rich get fat while the poor die!
Where is the true freedom in this world?!
We are all slaves to our work!
And is work fun?
No! How could it be?!
We do not want to work, period!
That's why I, Hammerhead,
will change our society
into one where only those who want to work
will work, while the rest are supported!
We will create a utopia!
The Paradisers led by me, Hammerhead,
will make all this a reality!
Boss, no one's listening.
What?!
Bah! These civilians are idiots!
Let's go!
Zeniru's the richest man in town.
We'll wreck his posh penthouse and show them we're serious!
High-rise apartments are symbols of inequality!
Yes, sir!
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
This whole building is Zeniru's home.
There's no way he made so much money legally.
Unforgivable! Bring it down!
Yes, sir!
Target destroyed!
Hm, these experimental
battle suits sure pack a wallop.
It was definitely worth
risking our lives to steal them.
Wait, that was the wrong building.
My bad, Boss.
Zeniru's house is a little further up.
Everyone makes mistakes!
The important thing is
to learn from them. Am I right?
Yes, you're right!
All right, then onward to Zeniru's!
Thanks, bicycle guy!
Don't come asking to play rock, paper,
scissors with a booger on your finger!
A dream?
The terrorist group responsible for
the riots call themselves the Paradisers.
They have destroyed
a high-rise building in City F.
The situation seems to be
spiraling out of control.
We have just learned
the identity of their leader.
B-CLASS CRIMINAL – HAMMERHEAD
Hammerhead is a B-class criminal who has been
involved in several violent incidents in the past.
He is a man of large stature,
standing 2.15 meters tall
and weighing 210 kilograms.
According to one report, he once fought twenty men
in a street brawl and sent them all to the hospital.
The Paradisers sent the following
message to this TV station.
"We will continue to riot until food, clothing, and shelter
are provided free of charge to those who do not work,"
amongst other unintelligible demands.
Sounds pretty boring.
Like Hammerhead, the group is made up of
unemployed young men with no motivation to work.
No need for me to get involved.
Also, the group members all have shaven heads,
making them quite intimidating.
Those who encounter any shaven-headed men
on the street are advised to leave the area immediately.
What?
But that's—
They stole
my look!
I spend all this time trying to be a hero,
but if they keep acting up
I'll be treated like a villain!
I'm gonna smash them!
Run!
It's them!
The Paradisers are coming!
They aren't backing down!
This is too dangerous!
Stop right there, you pack of thugs!
The cyclist for justice, Mumen Rider, is here!
Mumen Rider has come to save us!
There's nothing to fear if he's here!
A hero? What a joke!
Here I go!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Mr. Zeniru, you must flee!
But running away from terrorists
would hurt my reputation.
There's no need to leave.
You're a lucky man,
having this occur while
I'm still under contract.
But you're a bodyguard—
Oh, Sonic!
Can I leave this to you?
The men coming are—
Of course.
It's their lives you should worry about.
But please do think of a way
to dispose of the pile of corpses.
The Paradisers...
A bunch of upstarts equipped
with some new type of battle suit.
That and the B-class criminal Hammerhead.
He might have some backbone.
THE MODERN NINJA
Boss, you can see Zeniru's building
on the other side of the woods.
People call it the Golden Turd.
All right, let's go!
There's something there.
I've been waiting for you, Hammerhead.
Zeniru sent me.
Let me start out by saying...
no opponent of mine has ever escaped alive.
I plan on keeping it that way.
When it comes to my work, I'm a perfectionist.
But if you surrender right now, I'll let you live.
So, what will it be?
What is this?
What's going on?
Why is every—
Shit!
Bastard!
What's this now?
Trying to intimidate me?
You can't see me, can you?
There you are!
It's a terrorist!
No, I'm not!
So he decided to fight instead of run.
Oops, there goes my bad habit again.
You're just a little dog
bought with Zeniru's money.
You think someone like me,
who fights for a noble cause,
can lose to a dog?!
Yes, I see what he's up to.
I see. He really is just a complete fool.
Couldn't he have at least tried to arrange
the rocks in a less obvious way?
There are plenty more rocks
where those came from!
If you don't stop me, they'll keep coming.
So you think you'll be able to deal with my speed
if you know which direction I'm coming from?
How pathetic. But I'll play along.
In fact, I'll take you…
straight on!
He's too fast. I can't see him.
But it doesn't matter if I can't.
Because of this!
Gotcha!
Think about how stupid you were to face off
against me on your way down to Hell!
It's over.
Unfortunately, I couldn't go easy on them.
Yes, Hammerhead's body is here too.
I'll head back now—
The body disappeared?
That was close!
Good thing he hit my head.
My skull has always been
several times thicker than normal.
Dammit. I don't know who that bastard was,
but one day I'm gonna kill—
Huh?
Now what?
Hm?
Oh, there you are.
As with the mosquito monster,
I once again underestimated my opponent's power.
I let my guard down,
and Kabuto took advantage of that.
If Master Saitama had not been there,
I would certainly have been destroyed.
I see.
Well, I'm glad you're okay—
Doctor…
Master Saitama saved my life twice.
You, Doctor Kuseno, restored my life to me.
Later Master Saitama saved that same life,
and now he's saved it again.
Yes, I get the picture, Genos.
What you're trying to tell me is
how amazing this Saitama fellow is, right?
Yes.
Genos, they're not ready just yet,
but I am developing
a new series of augmentations.
When I replace your existing
parts with these new ones,
you may be able to surpass this Saitama.
I imagine he must possess an enormous amount
of strength for you to go on about him so.
Yes.
What's your deal?
You here to sign up with the Paradisers?
No, no.
I'm just a guy who's a hero for fun.
For personal reasons,
I'm here to smash your heads in.
So, where are your followers?
Then, die!
I better get out of here quick.
Huh?!
I thought I punched him?
What a letdown.
These battle suits got me all excited.
But the design is lame,
and all they do is give you
superhuman strength.
You have no idea how hard it was
to get hold of these things!
How could you know their value?!
I've been looking for someone
to test the full power of this suit on!
Spin attack!
I used to use that move
all the time when I was a kid...
Huh?
No way...
Hammerhead, huh?
He's a lot like me.
What the hell are you?!
W-Wait. I just wanted to get out of working...
Don't be bad anymore, okay?
Huh? So you're not going to kill me?
Get outta here.
Okay!
Guess I'll go home.
Where did Hammerhead go?
There's no one left but you.
Hammerhead went that way. Buck naked.
What's this?
Hey, you got it wrong.
I got what wrong?
I'm not one of the Paradisers.
You're lying.
No, no, no.
Don't be dumb! Look at me!
I don't need to.
With that bald head, there's no denying it.
No.
Look! It's me. Me!
You know, the guy who's a hero for fun—
Never heard of you.
Oh, I see...
Either way, it doesn't matter.
You read my attacks. Twice.
That's the real problem.
Born in a ninja village,
I've been perfecting
my techniques since childhood.
Yet you saw right through them.
This I cannot allow.
What's he talking about?
My pride won't have it.
I don't care who you are.
I can't just let you walk away.
Oh, come on.
You just want to try out your moves on me.
I can tell by that innocent smile of yours.
What do you think of this supersonic speed?
Of these shock waves?
Can you even see me?
How can you possibly keep up with me?
Um...
Can I go home?
Bastard!
Wind Blade Kick!
Checkmate.
Sorry!
That wasn't on purpose.
I meant to stop before hitting you,
but your momentum carried my fist into your...
We are experiencing technical difficulties. Please stand by.
I've worked every job
from assassin to bodyguard.
No ninja is more deadly.
I am Speed-o'-Sound Sonic!
But I'm putting my work on hold.
Now that I've found
such a formidable opponent,
I'm dedicating myself
to training until we settle this.
Let me know your name.
It's Saitama.
Saitama!
Next time we meet, it'll be your demise!
Okay.
I, Speed-o'-Sound Sonic, the ultimate ninja,
will bring you down without fail!
Train hard!
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic?
Who is that?
And who would possess
such a redundant name?
Dunno.
He suddenly appeared,
declared we were rivals, and took off.
If he is a nuisance, I will get rid of him.
Well, you're hardly different.
Actually, why are you here again?
Go home. It's not like we're related.
Master, I must become stronger—
Shut up!
I'm now aware of a serious problem
and am reeling from shock.
So I beg you, go home for today.
A serious problem?
What could cause a problem
for someone as great as you?
Please share with me.
No one knows who I am.
It's been three years
since I first became a hero.
I've defeated many monsters
and evil organizations during that time.
I've never heard of any other
heroes doing as much as me.
Everyone in the world
should know me by now!
Isn't it weird that I don't
have any fans or anything?!
You know what he said to me today?
"Never heard of you."
Plus, everyone in town took me for a terrorist.
They've all forgotten how
I beat those monsters for them!
He is right.
The news report did not mention
Master Saitama or Speed-o'-Sound Sonic.
Instead, the credit for defeating the Paradisers
went to a hero called Mumen Rider.
Wait...
Master!
Are you listed with the Hero Registry?
HERO ASSOCIATION OFFICIAL HOMEPAGE
"Take a test at any local branch
of the Hero Association.
If you score better than the cut-off,
you will be registered in the Hero Registry and
will be allowed to officially
call yourself a 'hero.'
Once you are recognized by the Association,
you are deemed a professional
and will get paid from donations
collected by the Association.
All heroes in the public eye
are registered, professional heroes.
You may be doing plenty of hero work,
but self-proclaimed heroes are really just weir… does…"
"…weirdoes spouting nonsense
viewed with suspicion."
I had no idea.
Genos, are you registered?
No. I feel no need to.
Let's register! Register with me
and I'll make you my disciple.
Let's go.
P-Please… F-Forgive me...
Pleading for his life after stealing
battle suits from the organization?
He truly understood nothing.
Of course, we did let the theft take place
in order to collect data from the suits in the field.
And the body?
Leave it.
Thanks for giving me my thick skull, Mommy.
I promise I'll get a job!
APPLICATION FOR
HERO TEST
Our guest today is Mr. Majimeda, an expert on
the labor issues confronting young people today.
Thank you for having me.
As we saw with the Paradiser incident recently,
there's an increase in young people
who lack all motivation to work.
Can you comment on this phenomenon?
Even in the case of the Paradisers,
I think they've been influenced by irresponsible lyrics
I'm not so different...
in popular songs like "Don't Give Up on Your Dreams"
and "Make Your Dreams Come True."
from those unemployed guys.
People who believe such hogwash end up
making excuses for themselves and become discouraged.
One wrong step and I could've been one of them.
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Ready to go, Master?
Y-Yeah.
HERO
TEST
SITE
Next
Time
The
Ultimate
Mentor
Err… I'm the recently reformed Hammerhead.
Before I introduce next week's episode,
I'd like to do a little PR for myself.
Oh? You won't allow that?
Next time on episode five
of One-Punch Man,
"The Ultimate Mentor."
Yeah, if I'd had a mentor like him,
maybe my life would've been different.