Today is the last day of the holidays.
How will you be spending it?
I'm gonna die of boredom...
Seriously, it's all that disgusting dog's fault.
It's not my fault that you can't see Kitamura.
Didn't I already tell you that clubs and the student council would be busy during the holidays?
It's a dog's job to think of a plan, isn't it?
Even if you got to see him, you wouldn't be able to talk to him.
Go to hell!
It spilled on me!
What are you doing?!
Hurry, find a washcloth or something!
Seriously...
This is what happens when you mess around!
So noisy...
Oh, we woke her up...
Here, use this to clean yourself up.
You were going to eat rice omelets while I was sleeping...
I put yours into the refrigerator.
Did you write my name on it using ketchup?
I did, so don't cry.
I got it, I'll sleep some more, then.
What should I do?
It's stained already...
You can get it out if you do it properly.
I'll help you, but in return...
Going to Jonny's again?
It's not that bad, right? Please!
I can't go by myself.
Note: Summer Colors, simple and charming, wearing it will make you feel better
June issue, sold tomorrow!
You should also support me and Kushieda!
Shut up! I'm gonna puke!
W-What?
pure pureparaato
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
Pre! Preparation!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed there's nothing
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
Kawashima Ami
Kushieda is taking a day off...
A hard-working girl has to take a break sometime, too.
Isn't this your punishment for only caring about your own happiness?
Unlike you, who has confessed and been confessed to, I still haven't-
My eyes! My eyes!
Don't say such embarrassing things, you horny dog.
Seriously, what are you doing?!
This is so cute!
What is?
It's too big for you.
What I want is the bag!
Welcome!
I'm tiny, after all.
But I haven't caused any problems because of that...
What's-
Ryuuji, this!
Another bag?
Not that, the model!
Model?
Look at that person!
Isn't this her?
You're right!
Her name is Kawashima Ami, she's the daughter of the actress Kawashima Anna.
What is she doing at a place like this?
I'm sorry for making you wait, Ami.
What-
K-K-Kitamura...
Oh, if it isn't Takasu and Aisaka!
What a coincidence!
Why?!
Hey, they're coming this way!
Even if you say that...
What are you pulling on him for?
You two are getting along well as usual.
N-No!
What's wrong, Yuusaku?
Let me introduce you guys.
Yuusaku?
Her name Kawashima Ami, she used to live in my neighborhood.
I guess you could call us childhood friends.
This is Takasu Ryuuji and Aisaka Taiga.
-Childhood friends?
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
That's...
Oh right, we were just looking at this, and...
Oh dear...
You saw an embarrassing side of me.
I should have worn some better clothes and makeup.
I kind of let my guard down when I'm not working...
Well, umm... That's not true.
Since we're all here, how about the four of us have a chat?
That's okay with you, right, Ami?
Of course!
This place makes me feel nostalgic.
We used to come here pretty often, didn't we?
That's right, with our families!
Here, have some too, Takasu-kun.
Do you prefer the non-fat one?
No...
Oh, so are you one of those people who drink it black?
Hey, what's up with the questions?
I'm sorry!
Yuusaku put some in his, so I kind of...
It's okay...
I screwed up again.
People always say I'm clumsy and air-headed.
I'm sorry.
No, not at all!
I like sweet stuff anyway.
Thank you, you're so kind!
Gosh, silly me...
Oh, sorry...
Gosh, why are you apologizing?
Well, I'm going to use the toilet.
I'm going to use the toilet too.
I really can't stand it.
Just as I thought, you left too.
Weren't you gonna use the toilet?!
What is it?
I want you to answer me honestly.
What do you think about Ami?
What do you mean what do I think?
You suddenly brought such a cute girl, and I got so nervous that I didn't know what was going on!
I admit that she's cute.
She's also a really nice girl!
She's a bit air-headed, or should I say innocent...
Well, take a look first.
Boring.
Hey, I finished my iced tear. Get me another one.
Are you deaf?
Speaking of which, wasn't there something wrong with your attitude just then?
Oh right, I'll get your boyfriend to get me another one.
It seems like he'll listen to whatever I say.
Can I take him from you?
Even though I don't need him!
He's not my boyfriend.
Oh, really?
I don't really care, though.
That's how she really is.
Spoiled, selfish and rude. A typical princess.
I think she's more of a demon...
Well, in this desolate city, those are the only kinds of guys that exist.
Hey, how tall are you?
I just noticed, but isn't your height a bit strange?
Speaking of which, do they even sell clothes in that size?
But when you buy jeans...
But really, I can't believe Taiga is taking it so well-
There was a fly.
Oh, it was a mosquito.
Why you...
Hey Ami, it's time to go.
Yuusaku...
I get it, I get it!
I'm sorry, Aisaka.
We'll be leaving first.
Seconds!
There's none left.
I already cooked two and a half cups of rice...
It's all her fault.
Just thinking of that bitch makes me hungry.
You mean "angry", right?
But Kitamura is probably having a hard time.
What should I do...
Will Kitamura-kun hate me for doing such a thing?
Well, I don't think that'll happen.
In the end, Kitamura is...
I hate that bitch.
Don't cry.
You too! You were all lovestruck over her!
I wasn't really...
Besides, who the hell acknowledges themselves as "air-headed"?!
Whatever, it's not like I'm ever going to see her again.
I'll be the adult this time and swallow my hatred.
Hey, that's mine!
Shut up!
I've transferred to this school today. My name is Kawashima Ami.
Please call me Ami!
Is she...
...the model who works for CanVi?
Oh my god, she's too cute!
An angel has descended!
Thank you, God.
Everyone, please get along with our new friend.
Well, let's find you a seat first...
Next to me!
Winner!
I'm so glad I'm in this class!
Somehow I think this is too flashy, I'm a bit embarrassed.
What are you saying?
It looks good on you, it's fine!
Yeah, the style is pretty good too.
I really want to wear the same jersey as everyone else!
Ami-chan is pretty cute, and her style is great, but...
But the Minori Radar, which is used to find cute girls, has no reaction.
Minorin...
Are you all right, Ami-chan?
Jeez, why did I trip here?
I must've looked pretty lame...
Are you really clumsy?
I think you're a bit air-headed.
That's not true!
But people sometimes do say that I'm a bit air-headed...
So it's true.
But it's not!
All right, we get it.
Jeez, I'm serious.
She's pretty amazing.
Yeah, she knows how to control people's hearts.
Why didn't you tell me that she was transferring here?
If I told you, you wouldn't be able to see her true nature.
I can't let that happen.
What's up with that?
To be honest, I don't dislike Ami's true form.
That's why I want people to know her true self and like her true self.
No, that's-
If people hated her even if they knew that, then Ami would accept it, too.
I don't want her to continue faking herself.
Thanks...
Me first!
So they have vending machines here!
Why are you-
Because you left the classroom when fourth period was about to begin.
I was worried, so I followed you.
I can't, I can't, her true nature is...
It's against the school rules to buy drinks when it isn't lunchtime.
Then...
...we're accomplices.
I'll pay you back.
It's all right.
This is for apologizing for yesterday.
Apologizing?
I was really surprised to find out that we were in the same school.
Aisaka-san, too...
Yuusaku didn't tell me anything.
Hey, did Aisaka-san say anything about what happened yesterday?
Yesterday?
About yesterday, it's all my fault.
I was a bit too air-headed, so I guessed that made Aisaka-san mad.
We were chatting normally...
Then Aisaka-san said I had too big of an ego...
Then...
But Aisaka-san isn't at fault!
If only I had more self control, something like that wouldn't have happened...
It happens to me sometimes...
...you know, being hated by other girls...
So I don't mind it.
I'll do my best.
I see.
That's why I hope that you won't tell anyone about what happened yesterday...
I...
I understand what you're trying to say.
So let's go back for now...
Thank you!
Let's go!
The sun is rising high, I went out without doing anything special...
Note: Why did you run to class together with Kawashima!? -Taiga
Why...
Seriously...
To: Takasu-kun
From Minori
Takasu-kun, I'm really mad!
There seems to be something suspicious going on between the transfer student and you!
Are you being unfaithful? Are you!?
If you dump Taiga, I will...
...punish you!
Damn it, why is this happening to me?
To Kushieda, from Takasu.
Although this is a completely different matter,
what do you think of a person who acknowledges themselves as air-headed?
Okay, is there anything you kids don't understand at this point?
What's wrong with you kids?
Hey, Takasu.
Haruka said that he would introduce me to three freshmen girls on the track team.
You're coming, right?
I'll only scare them away if I go.
That's not going to happen!
He's just making it up-
Besides...
The Palmtop Tiger!
...that's how it is.
How did you let it become like this?
I didn't do it on purpose!
I can't help it since it was an accident!
I'll get a wash cloth, you can go back first.
No, I'll wait for you in the classroom.
Ryu-
Jeez, why are you here?
You're a real eyesore, you know?
Don't come near me, you bitch.
I'm so scared!
As expected from Aisaka-san, who even scares the teachers away!
I just went to the faculty room and all they were talking about was how cute I am.
They were worried that I might get bullied by you.
It seems like you're really hated.
Then let me have some fun with you.
I wonder how long that dual persona of yours will last.
It's pretty simple to make you reveal your true nature.
But that would be too boring, wouldn't it?
I'll always be watching you.
Even if you change classes or graduate,
just like a stalker.
You're a really annoying runt!
That's why you have no friends.
Oh, there's one, Takasu Ryuuji.
It seems like that delinquent is interested in me.
How disgusting!
But you'll really become all alone this way.
I pity you.
Even a humanitarian like Yuusaku hates you.
What did you say?
What you did to me in that family restaurant made him feel really sad.
I guess he probably hates you.
You're done for!
Kawashima?
Hey, move it.
Wow! Ryuuji's fried pork cutlet!
Seriously...
It's best to eat it when it's just cooked.
If you're worried...
Bring it over to her.
Ah, you're so absent-minded.
Taiga, I'm coming in!
Hey, you're in here after all.
You didn't even turn on the lights.
Hey Tai-
What did you come here for?
What do you mean?
To tell you that dinner's ready!
T-Taiga, are you all right?
Kitamura-kun... hates me...
That bitch told me everything...
I... I...
It's all right.
What's all right?
Kitamura knows everything.
Even Kawashima's true nature, what really happened in the restaurant and the fact that she's lying.
He knows it all.
Really?
Really.
Besides, Kitamura isn't a person who would hate someone over something like that.
You should know that the best.
Then... why am I so tiny?
Huh?
Why do I have such a strange name?
No, that's...
Why?!
Just because she's 165 cm tall!
Just because she has the same name as someone in Sailor Moon!
And because she's also Kitamura's childhood friend?
Sorry, are you okay?
But, even if you worry about such uncontrollable things-
I'm different from you, I'm delicate!
You...
Ryuu-chan!
We're going to eat fried pork cutlets, but there's no sauce... That's too...
Fried pork cutlets?
It's from a black pig.
Hey, what about pudding?
We're only here to buy sauce.
Huh?
Let's go back.
Yasuko will be upset.
Ryuuji, look at that.
Note: Kawashima Ami-chan is going to take a break due of studies.
This is...
That's what they mean by suspension, right?
What's so good about our school that she would take a break from work?
That's...
That bitch.
It's Kawashima Ami, right?
What's with those clothes?
And she's holding nothing but snacks.
Is she having a party?
No, that's not it.
That's...
I just saw something very interesting.
banira saruto de banira...
A salty vanilla... Vanilla...
amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience.
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla
Next Episode Preview
My True Self
God, it's so annoying!
If you keep bothering me,
Ami-chan will kill you.
Named: Stupid Chihuahua.