When the sun set on the town,
When the sun set on the town, I saw my mother.
I saw my mother.
She wore her usual priestess clothing,
and walked as though drifting through the twilight.
When I saw her,
the joy of seeing long-lost family somehow overtook my fears,
and I unconsciously called out to her.
But my mother...
mother
continued walking, step by step, as though she didn't even notice.
Confused, I followed her,
and turned a corner right where my mother did.
mother
When I did,
I found nobody there.
Had I made a mistake?
Yes, I must have.
My mother shouldn't be here, after all.
mother
Because my mother...
Just then, as I noticed the dim street lights flickering on,
I saw, standing nonchalantly in the pale fluorescent light,
my mother staring in the distance.
mother
The rings of her staff echoed,
and the faint scent of medicinal herbs drifted with it.
The scent was that of the mother I knew.
mother
As the street lights flickered on and off,
the sight of my mother flickered with them.
mother
I called out to my mother and ran to her,
but each time the lights flickered,
my mother grew further and further away.
mother
I couldn't reach her no matter how fast I ran.
My mother, carried only by her gentle gait,
mother
appeared just beyond my grasp with every flicker.
Driven by the fear of never seeing her again,
I shouted for my mother at the top of my lungs.
mother
When I did,
my mother turned to face me.
mother
At that moment,
the street was bathed in a blinding light,
and with their filaments burned out, the lamps shut off.
My mother's figure disappeared into the darkness.
mother
I couldn't comprehend what had happened,
and stood frozen in place.
I missed her,
I loved her,
and I wanted to be with her.
And though I knew I could never see my mother again,
mother
she stood there before my very eyes.
But...
I knew how unbelievable a sight it was.
Because...
my mother is already...
Because my mother is already...
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens
Hey, Kagami!
Kagami!
What is it?
My morning naptime is quite important.
Please do not perturb me.
Kagami, listen!
You could certainly learn to listen as well.
I saw my mother yesterday.
Please do not spout such absurdities.
Yesterday,
my mother...
Are you a retard, and have you considered suicide?
I would much prefer it if you said nothing while I slept.
And I have not the time to partake in such idle gossip.
Do not disturb my slumber.
So Kagami, come shopping with me after school!
What is it now?
So, I want a bicycle,
and I don't know what to pick.
And how is this relevant?
Even scatterbrains have some logic.
My brother always drives me on his,
but that makes people mad...
Relevance!
So Kagami, help me pick one out!
Unfortunately,
I must take Meatie to her physical examination.
Meatie?
Yes!
She is a white, fluffy, cuddly, and adorable little critter!
She would have died of loneliness had I let her be,
so I had no choice but to befriend her.
Hey, I'm pretty lonely, too!
Do not ask the impossible.
Besides, adventuring alone can be a positive experience.
Kagami's so insensitive...
So now I'm on the same level as a rabbit?
That's a laugh.
Mother...
On my way home, I saw my mother.
What is it, Sasami?
Are you shopping?
Huh?
Um, yes...
What will you buy?
Um, well... a bicycle.
I see.
If it's for transport,
one imbued with divine protection should suffice.
Huh? No, that one's ugly!
A Tsukuyomi priestess needs no beauty.
Seeking comfort in appearance is a weakness that brings only doom.
Likes and dislikes
are but bottlenecks that cloud the judgment of one leading the world.
I don't have many memories of my mother,
but I remember what I do have clearly.
Learning techniques, training together...
I don't have many memories of my mother, but I remember what I do have clearly.
As a child, my mother and I were as close as could be.
What is it, Sasami?
Oh, nothing.
What is this loud, beeping contraption?
Oh, well you see,
when you press this button, the crane moves.
And you're supposed to get one of the plushies inside.
Want to try?
Idolatry is wicked.
It is trivial to hide a soul within a fake creature,
so the danger of finding one imbued with a violent curse is great.
Good!
Listen to your elders!
Shoot, it's hard!
Allow me to intervene.
You can't do that!
A Tsukuyomi priestess values haste.
But there are rules!
The employees are totally looking!
Then I shall cast a spell,
and have the stuffed animal move itself.
Oh, it's in.
Can we do this?
I shall permit it.
To receive the permission of a Tsukuyomi priestess is as a god—
Shoot, they're coming here!
Let's go, Mom!
Don't run so suddenly!
I'm poor at exercise!
My mother
My mother had a weak body from birth,
and was often bedridden due to illness.
I often nursed her, as well.
If we were slower, they'd have caught us!
For a Tsukuyomi priestess to yield to authority...
I would like a respite.
Mom, there's a problem if you're more out of shape than I am.
I have found no need for physical ability.
Wait here.
Here.
I sense a disturbing chill.
What is this?
Ice cream. It's a frozen treat.
The consumption of luxury foods is wicked.
The pleasure could affect others' preferenc—
Just eat it!
Cold!
Mom, that sounded pretty cute!
I am always cute.
That was not bad...
Mom, do you have a computer?
They're pretty handy.
A Tsukuyomi priestess does not value convenience.
Mom, buy this for me!
I refuse.
Worldly possessions are wicked.
But Brother would've bought me a ton...
Out of the question.
Reliance on objects rots the heart.
I'll pick some clothes out for you, Mom!
Don't you get tired of that priestess outfit?
I am a priestess, so it is only natural to wear priestess garb.
I have no need for worldly garments.
Man, that was fun!
Mom, do you still have time?
If you want, we can have dinner!
For a helpless, incompetent nestling,
you have grown quite full of yourself.
What do you want to eat?
I want nothing.
More importantly, Sasami, I have something to tell—
Oh, how about Italian?
You've never had that, right?
Wait, Sasami!
I said wait!
The final memory I have of my mother
still lingers in my mind.
Lookie lookie!
There's a bunch of petties!
There is so much fluffiness and cuddliness!
Could I be in heaven?
Now, widdle Meatie, you will see the vet!
Have no fear, and be a good widdle girl!
Ooh, you got an infantilism fetish?
We really are sisters!
Never speak again. Please commit suicide.
They are fluffy and cuddly and wearing widdle clothes!
Bunny Clothing
Could it be?
This is a divine message telling me to be lovey dovey with Meatie!
I'm not so sure.
Now Meatie, which do you wike?
We're gonna be here a while.
Sasami.
What?
Who is it that takes you here?
Brother, usually.
Don't worry, it's easy!
Watch.
Just twirl...
More importantly, Sasami,
I have something to tell you.
What?
When the sun set on the town, I saw my mother.
This day has been fun.
Sasami, I have truly enjoyed it.
From what I remember,
we have never once shopped, conversed, or spent time together like a normal family might.
I was not a good mother.
My apologies, Sasami.
But...
Don't apologize, Mom.
I'm happy.
Spending some time together as a family
has always been a dream of mine.
When the sun set on the town, I saw my mother.
She wore her usual priestess clothing, and walked as though drifting through the twilight.
I've left you with painful memories.
Don't worry.
You were busy with work.
And I know you tried to raise me to be a good successor.
Sasami...
The street was bathed in a blinding light, and with their filaments burned out,
the lamps shut off.
My mother's figure disappeared into the darkness.
I couldn't comprehend what had happened, and stood frozen in place.
I missed her, I loved her, and I wanted to be with her. And though I knew I could never see my mother again, she stood there before my very eyes. But...
Thank you.
I really am grateful.
I love you, Mom!
The street was bathed in a blinding light, and with their filaments burned out,
the lamps shut off.
My mother's figure disappeared into the darkness.
I couldn't comprehend what had happened, and stood frozen in place.
I missed her, I loved her, and I wanted to be with her. And though I knew I could never see my mother again, she stood there before my very eyes. But...
I knew how unbelievable a sight it was.
But...
that's exactly why I have to say something, too.
Oh?
Because my mother is already...
Because...
my mother is already...
Because my mother is already
dead...
I am... dead,
you say?
Sasami.
Did you believe that I had not noticed?
Huh?
Of course I am deceased.
Then, Mom...
My appearance is due to a Transformation,
but this body is but a corpse.
It decays ever slowly.
But those around me do not recognize it.
This is my true form.
Humans inevitably die.
Their souls cross the border of death into the underworld.
There is no cycle.
The dead cannot return.
Those are the rules.
But there is one way out.
Before I tasted the fruit of Hell,
that is, before I took residence in the land of the dead,
I negotiated with the ruler of the underworld.
We decided it would be to our mutual benefit,
and agreed that until my body rotted away,
I would be given another, fleeting life.
But why?!
To return from the dead
is so abominable that even the God of Creation couldn't stand it!
You ask why, Sasami?
By all rights, I should have passed on with no regrets.
However,
I saw something.
I saw you flee the shrine,
abandon your duties as a Tsukuyomi priestess,
and idly fool around!
I could not allow myself to die.
I should have left more guidance.
When I left the world to you,
you nodded, and then you said,
"I'll do it, Mother."
But you broke that promise.
You do not bear full blame, nor is it your sin alone.
Before your training and efforts could bear fruit...
Before you could mature, I passed away.
It was my sin as well.
Return to the Tsukuyomi Shrine, Sasami.
You will continue your training.
The shrine was destroyed.
I am aware.
But the building matters not.
All you need is a quiet place to train, away from this meaningless society.
We are leaving.
No!
I'm not going!
What's the point in leading a world that only lets people cry and cough up blood?
I'm not a Tsukuyomi priestess anymore!
Do not be mistaken, Sasami.
Nobody asked for your opinion.
This is for mankind.
Do you place your pleasure,
your freedom,
and your comfort
over the future of all humanity?
Your fate is not all that rests on your shoulders.
It is not your life.
It is something far more grand and noble!
Do not spew such selfish complaints!
But...
I shall not coddle you, fool!
How long will you act like a child?
If you will not be a Tsukuyomi priestess,
then your life is worthless.
Your wasteful living, neglecting of your duty,
and indulgence in indolence are all but sins!
What do you not understand?
I was too soft in raising you.
You idiot daughter!
Hey!
Shouldn't get too worked up,
Mommy.
Wanna have some family counseling,
Mommy?
Tsurugi.
I'd heard it happened, but I've never seen one myself.
People returning from the dead, that is.
Wicked gods have no right to speak in human tongue.
You may grin,
but you led Sasami astray with your sugar-laden words.
Hey, I ain't evil.
The real monster here's the one who's back from the dead.
Death ain't somethin' a god, much less a human, comes back from.
That's a rule straight from the old man.
Having a limited life is what lets us live with no regrets.
I may be a slacker who abandoned her own duty to watch over the world,
but there are some rules I can't let people get away with breaking.
So lemme fix that.
Nobody led Sasami anywhere.
She chose her path herself!
And I ain't lettin' a rotten corpse
show up outta nowhere to look down on her!
You're takin' a bullet train to Hell!
You underestimate me.
The Tsukuyomi Shrine is tasked with exorcising all manner of demons, and I am their head priestess.
Exterminating evil gods is my specialty.
And I ain't evil!
You're as poor at combat as the legends say, Sun Goddess.
Tsurugi!
Sister!
Stay back!
She's tough!
You can't take her!
Please escape by yourself.
You cast off your original power.
Cram it!
What kinda teacher lets a parent hit a kid without sayin' a word?
You three take this too lightly.
The gods of this country seek too much idle pleasure.
I cannot leave the fate of this country in your hands.
This world only achieves progress and prosperity because humans manage it.
All is for the world and its people.
Training Sasami to fulfill the duties of a Tsukuyomi priestess
will be my final duty.
I bear you no resentment for intruding,
but you will die.
Well I ain't goin' to Hell.
I've got a lot of enemies there!
What?
Such is the Heavenly Gathering of Clouds.
It does have considerable strength.
But it is a blade of defense,
and a grass cutting tool made to defend lacks the malice to destroy an enemy.
That can't be...
The sword that killed the Eight-Forked Serpent, yet once broke due to a curse.
The blade of misfortune sharpened in the land of the dead, Heavenly Slasher of Wings.
This god-killing weapon was entrusted to me by the lord of the underworld himself.
The lord of the underworld had the Heavenly Slasher of Wings?
So that's it!
I thought you were too strong for a human, and now I know why!
Nobody asked that mother-fucker to make a copy!
Sister!
How dare you!
How?
The protection of the lord of the underworld.
With this divine blade in my hands,
gods of your level cannot touch me.
Kagami!
You bitch!
You are all too weak.
For someone returned from the dead,
it is trivial to open a portal to the underworld.
If you cross the border of death even once,
return is nigh impossible, even for a god.
Your reign ended long ago, Sun Goddess.
Drown, and relinquish the world to the moon.
Now.
Move, weakling.
It may have been fun for you all to play the hero and protect my selfish daughter.
But it has no meaning.
No merit.
For the sake of the world and its people,
Sasami will become a Tsukuyomi priestess.
This country must be led on the proper path.
I don't know...
I'm a dummy.
But still,
why are you so mean?!
We were all finally happy!
Tsurugi was having fun,
and Kagami, she was smiling!
All because of Mamarin!
And I still don't know what you're talking about!
I don't get it!
Then I shall make it clear.
You are a nuisance.
Stop it!
Stop it, I'll go!
I'll go back to the shrine!
I'll be a Tsukuyomi priestess,
so stop it already!
Please!
Welcome back
to the world of humans.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Now, we're doing it today, too!
Time for the ending theme!
This time, Sasami's lovely singing voice will surely reach living rooms across the country!
Or so I'd hoped, but you see,
this isn't quite the best time for it.
Oh, why did this happen?
There's nothing left but to try on my own...
What is this?
Oh, Mother, excellent timing!
Quick, come here for a bit!
What is this about?
Take this mic. Are you ready?
Now, please sing!
Wait, wait!
I cannot comprehend what is happening!
And I do not sing!
A Tsukuyomi priestess needs no song!
I'm tellin' ya, it's all right!
This chapter was serious in the novels,
so it'll leave an impression if we cut to the ending theme!
Though we probably won't use it even if we record it,
so please, sing just in case.
Now, in a big voice!
A resounding... si... sy... symphony?
Um, sh-shines a deeeeep...
Foolishness! Do not trick me!
Why must I do this?
Kamiomi, stand right there!
I will knock your jaw off!
Ouch!
Mother, please don't hit me with the mic!
We still need to use that.
U-U-U-Um, see you next time!
Apathetic Aerobics
Now, it's time for Apathetic Aerobics!
First, take a deep breath!
Fill your lungs with Sasami's scent, and
one two,
hoo haa,
two two,
hoo haa!
Next, puff out your chest,
and as though you're hugging Sasami,
one two,
Sasami!
Two two,
I love you!
Now, let's give it our all today!
Next time, on Episode 7,
"I Forgot How To Speak."