Good morning, Yuuji.
The weather is nice today.
Do you want to have some breakfast?
Yuuji, are you still sleepy?
Shouko, hand me my cell phone.
Hello, is this the police?
I have a trespasser here.
TRESPASSER
Yuuji, what is this?
Sign: sweat
W-What is that? I had no idea that I have that kind of thing!
It was in the lower section of the third drawer of your desk,
hidden under a study book cover.
Hello? Did something happen? Hello?
Sorry, I was mistaken.
I'll forgive you if you burn it.
Wait a sec. Punishing and forgiving aren't the same thing!
Okay then, I won't forgive you even if you burn it.
I have to burn it no matter what!
So what are you doing here this morning?
Here.
Sign: Shouko's View
Isn't that the Kisaragi Grand Park's premium entrance ticket?
Sign: Yuuji's View
Why do you have this?!
A nice person gave it to me.
The only person I know who had this is Akihisa!
Special Wedding Experience Event.
Hello, who is this?
I'm going to kill you.
Eh? What? Who are you—
Let's go then, Yuuji.
No way.
You're a liar.
I never agreed to going.
You promised me that if you lost to me in the Summoned Being Exam War, you'd go out with me.
I've long forgotten that.
Then you can choose.
You promised that if you break the promise we'd immediately get married.
The details of the promise just completely changed, didn't they?
Damn it! Akihisa, that bastard!
You're definitely going to regret th—
All couples hold hands with each other.
But you're the only one who locks the joints to prevent escape.
Welcome to Kisaragi Grand Park.
Hey, Akihisa, it looks like you're enjoying yourself, eh?
Run!
You've got the wrong person.
Why the hell are you here?
You're here too, Hideyoshi. What's with that?
What are you talking about?
I'm an employee at the Kisaragi Grand Park;
I have nothing to do with whoever it is you know.
If you want to keep faking it...
Ah! My hand slipped!
Was that necessary?
Do you have the tickets?
Here.
This is the Special Premium ticket!
Alpha to Bravo. Target?
Kouta, shift to Wedding mode.
We must bring him down without fail.
Hey, what's with that suspicious phone call?
Please don't mind me.
It's nothing you need to concern yourself with.
It's pretty clear that it's about us!
Let's move on to the special commemorative photographs service.
Sorry for the wait.
Shouko, I'm sorry!
Long term habits are hard to break, aren't they? Ninja Pervert.
Yuuji, you pervert.
I won't do it again. Forgive me.
We'll continue in bed.
I just said I won't do it again!
I don't have any interest in your panties!
This... I can't forgive.
It hurts... My temples...
Cheese.
Sign: We're getting married
What kind of picture is this?
This is the special border that our service provides.
This photograph will be placed in the park's photo gallery as a commemoration.
Are you guys crazy?
Yuuji, are you embarrassed?
I really can't tell what's embarrassing about this picture.
Look, look, Ryuta.
Let's have them take a picture of us too!
Good thinking, Riko.
Hey onii-chan, take a picture of us too.
I'm very sorry,
but this service is only for those who hold premium tickets.
Huh?
Come on, it's just one picture;
we're customers here!
Compared to that boring brat, I'm much more suitable for advertisements.
That's right. Ryuta is a hundred times more handsome than that loser.
Wait, where are you going?
Those people said bad things about you.
Just ignore that kind of thing.
If you say so...
Spare me your crap and just take a picture of us!
I understand. If you insist, then please come this way.
Okay! Please put your hand here.
Very good. Now squeeze as hard as you can.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Cheese.
Bastards, what the hell was that?
You said that you wanted a similar picture.
You wanna die?
Crap! Hamburger Head is mad!
Don't look down on me, you brats!
Why do I get the feeling that things will become even more of a drag?
How the hell did those three get in here anyway?
Yuuji, are you embarrassed?
What kind of man gets embarrassed just because his joints are locked?
But all couples hold hands.
In what way does this position make us look like we're a couple?
Hey! The sweet, adorable couple over there!
Look. It thinks so.
It's pretty obvious that this guy isn't normal!
Hi, Phi the Fox here to introduce you guys to a very interesting attraction!
Akihisa was asked out by a college girl a little while ago.
Eh? Yoshii-kun? Where did you see him?!
Are you here working part-time, Himeji?
Hi, Phi the Fox here to introduce you guys to a very interesting attraction!
Go ahead, if you want to play dumb.
Tell me where you recommend.
Okay! Phi recommends the Haunted House you see over there!
Is that so? Shouko, let's go anywhere but the Haunted House.
Please wait! Why?!
You guys probably placed traps there to get me.
I beg you, please go to the haunted house!
I refuse.
That's as far as you'll go, Yuuji.
If you dare upset Phi, I, Noin, will definitely make you pay!
What's wrong, Akihisa? What's with your retarded head?
How rude! There's nothing wrong with my head!
Yuuji, it's because Noin-chan is a klutz.
There's no klutzy fox that would put his head backwards.
Yoshii-kun, you put it on backwards!
Oh crap! No wonder I couldn't see!
If you don't fix it right now, Sakamoto-kun will see through us!
Do these idiots still think I haven't realized yet?
Anyway, Akihisa, what happened to the date with the college girl?
Eh?
Yoshii-kun, I heard you were fooling around with other girls
during such an important battle phase...
Mizuki
Minami
SENDING
W-What are you talking about, Himeji-san?
Mizuki
Minami
RECEIVING
Minami-chan says she's coming too.
Please explain to us what the heck is going on, okay?
You can't spill blood in a happy amusement park...
What the hell is going on, Aki?!
Let us hear your thorough explanation, okay?
You have to be completely honest.
This is a misunderstanding.
Hurry, Shouko.
Let's go somewhere other than the Haunted House.
Eh? Shouko?
We're going to the Haunted House.
Hideyoshi, what the hell did you whisper to her?
We can hug all we want in the Haunted House.
Sign: Hell's Hospital of Fear!! Haunted House
Please sign this before you go in.
Sign what?
A contract.
A contract needs to be signed in order to enter any dangerous attractions.
Is it really that dangerous in there?
But I guess it'll be interesting like this.
Let's see... Contract:
I, Sakamoto Yuuji, take Kirishima Shouko as my lawful wife, to have and to hold, from this day forward, for better
or for worse, until death do us part.
Here's a pen.
And here's your official stamp.
Stamp ink is here!
Is it only me? Am I the only one who finds this situation strange?!
This is carbon paper. Underneath it is the wedding request form.
Thank you for your efforts.
Efforts my ass!
Please come this way.
I'll leave my purse with you.
It'll spill, so don't tilt it.
I got it.
Now please enjoy this super exhilarating and horrifying experience.
They used an abandoned hospital to build a haunted house, huh?
It does have the correct atmosphere.
Rather than Himeji...
This voice... Yuuji?
What is this, a computer-generated voice? Or is it Hideyoshi imitating me...?
Whatever it is, it's not scary at all.
Himeji suits me better than Shouko; her boobs are huge!
Yuuji, is this true?
Is this what he meant by exhilarating and horrifying?
Yuuji,
prepare yourself.
God damn it. Even though the theme changed, it's still freaking scary!
You can't escape.
Wait! Don't be so rash! This is a trap!
Nice work.
So how was it? Want to get married now?
How does this have anything to do with marriage?
It's well-known that when a man and a woman go through a life-and-death situation,
their relationship becomes stronger.
That's only when the woman is not the one threatening the man's life in the first place!
Yuuji, it's about time we have lunch.
Yeah, we've been running around the whole time. I'm hungry as well.
Excuse me guests, I'd like to announce that there's a special lunch at our restaurant today.
It's a special menu prepared for those with premium tickets, so please try it.
Special menu, eh?
Please head towards the restaurant.
I'll lead.
What's wrong, Shouko?
I'm looking forward to the special menu.
Oh?
That was pretty good.
Anything is good if I eat it with Yuuji.
Everyone, thank you for attending our special lunch show!
We actually have a high school couple who are going out to get married!
What?!
Therefore, we shall be hosting a special event for them!
It's called the Kisaragi Grand Park's Wedding Experience Present Quiz!
Crap, they cut off the escape route!
There are a total of five questions. If all of them are answered correctly,
you will receive an extremely extravagant wedding plan!
If you so desire, you can immediately register too! No problem!
There's a problem!
Then Sakamoto Yuuji-san and Shouko-san, please head up on stage.
Who the hell's going?
Wedding Experience... I must work hard.
A dream-like wedding experience!
Calm down, Shouko!
Shit, I have to think of some way to get out of this.
Let's begin!
Oh right! I'll just have to answer them wrong.
I was once known as the "Prodigy."
Answering the questions wrong should be a piece of cake!
First question.
Bastard, go ahead!
There is no question that I don't know the answer to!
When is Sakamoto Yuuji-san and Shouko-san's marriage anniversary?
What is this? I don't even know what the question means...
I know it.
Every day is our marriage anniversary.
Correct! Every day is their marriage anniversary!
Stop! I can't handle the embarrassment!
Second question.
Damn it, I have to answer wrong no matter what!
Where was their wedding held?
Miso Mackerel!
Correct!
What did you say?
Their wedding will be held at the Kisaragi Grand Park's Phoenix Room,
also known as the Miso Mackerel Room!
Wait! You definitely gave it that name just now!
Okay, to the third question!
I know what you guys are up to.
I'll definitely answer the next question wrong, just watch!
Where did the two meet?
This one is mine!
Sign: eyes
At elementary school.
Correct!
I'll answer half-way through the question!
Fourth Question.
You guys—
I know the—
Correct!
Crap... There's no way I can answer the questions wrong if this continues.
Sign: End
Is it over for me?
Hey, wait a minute.
We were planning on getting married too.
Why do only those two get special treatment?
Let us go up there too!
Excuse me, the round is still—
Shut up, octopus.
I'm also a customer, you know?
I want to go through a wedding experience too, just saying.
Just saying?
Stop blabbing, idiot!
It means we want to participate too!
Then how about this: we'll ask the questions.
If they answer correctly, it's their win. If not, it's ours!
You can't just—
Hell yeah!
With these idiots,
I can definitely escape from this horrifying wedding experience ordeal!
Here's the question, listen up!
Where is the capital of Europe?!
Congratulations! Sakamoto Yuuji-san and Shouko-san won
the Kisaragi Grand Park Wedding Experience Present!
Sign: Wedding Experience
We'll finally be moving onto today's main event: the wedding experience!
Everyone, please give a warm welcome to the groom!
I'm definitely killing you guys later.
Let us introduce the groom to everyone!
Actually, never mind. It's just an experience, and it's also a pain to do this. Let's skip it.
Hey!
Okay, here comes the bride!
She's beautiful.
Yuuji.
Do I look like a bride?
It's all right. At least you don't look like a groom!
Yuuji.
W-What is it?
I'm really happy.
Hey, what's wrong?
It's always been my dream.
Dream?
Since I was a kid, it's been my dream
to have a wedding with Yuuji.
Becoming your bride...
It's a dream that I thought would never come true.
So I'm very happy right now.
With no one else. Just here, with Yuuji...
Shouko, I...
How boring.
It's putting me to sleep.
Screw the boring love story; hurry up and get to the next part!
We're really busy, but we still came, you know?
We don't need the soap opera crap; just show us the good part.
And really, your dream is to be a bride? How old are you?
Seriously, it's disgusting.
This is just a big joke, isn't it?
What did you say, you bastards?!
How dare you say that to Kirishima-san!
Let's take this outside!
Stop it, Yoshii-kun!
You'll ruin the whole thing!
But...
Calm down, Yoshii-kun.
If they keep doing this, Kirishima-san will...
Please!
Shouko...
Yoshii-kun, you find her?
She's not over here.
Yuuji!
Where did Kirishima go?
I don't know.
What?
Do you have any idea where she could be?
If we don't hurry and find her...
Sorry, but I'll pass.
It's troublesome. Besides, I want to go to the bathroom.
How could you?
I'm about to burst, so see ya.
That wedding sure sucked beyond belief.
It's my dream to be a bride.
How was that? Close, eh?
You sounded just like her! Hilarious.
Hey, you guys.
You bastard, you want something?
Nothing important.
But lend me your face for a bit!
Yo!
You're late, Shouko.
Why are you...
I figured you'd come here.
Yuuji.
What is it?
Is my dream weird?
Shouko, I'll just say this now.
The feelings you have for me are misplaced.
Seven years ago, I was an idiot, and I dragged you in with me.
I just wanted to take responsibility at the time.
You've wasted so much time on a good-for-nothing like me.
I'm sorry, really sorry.
Yuuji...
I won't laugh at your dream!
Although you've got the wrong person,
I do think that it's admirable to stay faithful to one person for so long.
So have pride in your dream. It won't lose to anyone else's.
But only if you don't have the wrong person!
This is from a rare occasion, so take it home as a souvenir!
Yuuji...
Oh, and also!
The bento was pretty good.
Go home now, we don't want people to get the wrong idea.
Yuuji!
What is it?
I didn't misplace my feelings at all!
The eighth question. What is the Japanese name for "computer?"
Choudenjizunou!
TL Note: Literally means Super Electrical Brain
Sounds strong.
Next week: Rampage, Labyrinth, and Summoned Being Custody Plan
These will be on the test.