In the
era
of the
Warring
States
A time of corruption
There was
the
strongest
Style of
the Sword
that used
no swords
Oushuu Province
Hida Castle
The traitor...
Takahito Hida.
User of the Swordless Style...
Hmm, I see.
So this is where I'll lose.
There's no point anymore.
Miss?
You can see it now.
May I inquire as to why you're headed to a deserted island?
It's not uninhabited.
That's the island where the hero of the rebellion was exiled.
Sword
Story
Zettou
Kanna
Shogun Yanari, who came to power after the rebellion, fearing the hero Yasuri Mutsue's power,
exiled him, along with his family, to this lonely island.
For the next 20 years, nobody dared to set foot on the island.
What a pain...
What are you doing, Shichika?
Sis...
It looks like we're out of water, so...
Please don't come out wearing that, it's cold out.
I'm okay.
It doesn't feel bad if it's just for a little while.
Also, I do believe it was my turn to do the chores today.
It was?
Didn't I tell you to stop treating me like a delicate little thing?
I didn't mean to...
It's fine.
It's just another part of my training.
I don't remember teaching you to treat me this way.
See, I'm telling you, go back inside!
There's no reason for you to train anymore.
Sis...
What use is there in prolonging the life of a martial arts style that ends with you?
I don't think it's meaningless.
Hey, Shichika.
It's been over a year since Father passed away.
Haven't you done enough?
You don't really mean that, do you?
Like... I thought up a new special move only yesterday.
It's really... fabulous...
Well, the only one who was banished was Father.
It's impossible for me, but you could build a boat and...
Don't be ridiculous!
It seems this wasn't the best way to start off the morning, was it?
I'll prepare breakfast, so hurry back.
Sure.
A new special move, huh...
Let me see it later.
Leaving the island...
I was expecting her to mention it eventually.
But this is the only thing that Father left me, so...
I want to preserve it as best I can.
After all, this is all I have.
How bothersome.
If Father was around, he'd slice through them all in one hit.
Hey!
Someone from the mainland?
First time meeting one of you.
Is that a katana?
First time seeing one of those as well.
I don't particularly mind if strangers come here to visit, but...
But, umm...
Bringing weapons here is strictly prohibited.
Is that so...?
Indeed.
Pardon me, then.
I was not aware.
Please forgive me.
Well, I wasn't the one that made the rule.
How did you get here?
By a boat, of course.
It isn't like I really want to know,
but I'm supposed to ask in a situation like this.
Next up is...
"Why are you here?" Right?
Exactly.
Why did you come here?
I heard that Mutsue Yasuri, the sixth head of the Swordless Style, resides here.
Do you know of him?
If you're talking about my father, he died.
A year ago.
I see...
Right now, I'm the head of the family.
The seventh head of the Swordless Style, Shichika Yasuri.
I see.
Excuse my impoliteness.
My information is from 20 years ago, so I should have considered the fact that he may have passed away.
I see...
He looks strong.
His looks aren't half-bad either.
I'd say that he passes.
Did you say something?
Ah, no. Just talking to myself.
It seems that you had some business with my father... sorry about that.
You're partially correct.
My business is with the head of the Swordless Style.
Which means the business I had with your father has become business with you.
Shichika, I haven't told you my name yet.
I'm Togame.
Togame?
What a strange name.
I serve as a super-strategist for the army of the Shogunate.
First off, I'll be putting the Swordless Style to the test.
This is an early work of Kasamaro Mibu, a swordsmith of the 36 Fugakus.
Test?
That would be what I said.
Here I go!
Shichika Yasuri and Togame the super-strategist.
The somewhat unfortunate meeting that began their destiny together...
took place in the middle of January, during the Kunakatta period.
I'm back.
You said you're the super-strategist, Togame, correct?
As the first guest to this island of ours,
I'm not entirely sure how to welcome you...
No...
It's my fault for coming here so suddenly.
I am Mutsue Yasuri's daughter, Nanami.
I heard you came to visit my father; how did you know him?
I haven't really met him at all.
You haven't?
Nope.
You can think of me as someone who got dragged into this, Nanami.
I'll keep your katana in my care.
It's forbidden to bring such things to this island.
Is it the way of the Swordless Style?
It's written as "path of the empty sword".
A hidden style that uses no weaponry.
The only people to have openly demonstrated the style...
were the first generation's head Kazuni Yasuri...
and the sixth generation's head Mutsue Yasuri.
When the entire country is submerged in chaos,
the head of the deadliest style is called to the battlefield.
That man is the seventh head.
Togame.
You tried to attack my brother?
I just really wanted to see the Swordless Style in action.
I'm not used to fighting though.
I'm a super-strategist, not a swordsman.
Your technique was still pretty impressive.
I've practiced it.
Then why not keep practicing until you've mastered it?
That was a rather violent method, no?
It's understandable that you see it that way, but I need to pass my own expectations.
I've only heard Mutsue Yasuri's name. I don't know what he looks like.
It would've been a mess if I had approached the wrong person.
I thought if he could demonstrate the Swordless Style, it would prove more than a name ever could.
Even if Mutsue was Shichika, wouldn't it still be the same?
In that case, why not test him again?
Consider yourself lucky to have tripped over that rock as you did.
If your blade had reached Shichika's body, there's no way you'd have escaped with only a lump on your forehead.
No.
I'll accept your words as proof of the Swordless Style.
Is that so?
Let us discuss what business you have then.
Alright.
So, wouldn't you like to rule the world?
No.
Exactly.
It's a natural thing for anyone that lives in this world.
There's nothing wrong with ambition.
Who can deny the feelings that traitors possess?
If you research it, you'll find the members of the current Shogunate were traitors who usurped the previous rulers.
Which means... wait, you said "no"?!
Yeah.
What do you mean?
You don't get it?
Togame.
We were born and raised on this island.
We have no desire to take over an unknown world.
It's best if you assume we don't understand your feelings.
Is that so?
In that case, could I ask you to leave this island?
That's a pointless question.
There are two reasons why.
The first is that the Swordless Style is inherited by blood.
If my father was still here, I'm sure he'd have us stay as well.
And the other reason is because I don't like to think.
Really? So does that mean you're bad at thinking?
Then I'll continue my story under the promise of confidentiality.
Do you know a swordsmith by the name of Kiki Shikizaki?
No.
Exactly.
Even on this tiny island, any respectable martial artist would have heard of the man.
For the weaponless Swordless Style, Shikizaki is a natural enemy.
Wait, you said "no"?!
Yeah.
I get that he's a big deal and all...
Kiki Shikizaki...
If I remember correctly, he was a famous swordsmith from the Sengoku period?
You didn't know that?
I heard that he had a close relationship with the founder of the Swordless Style.
Shikizaki didn't have a style.
He was a heretic that isolated himself from others.
However, it's said his work dominated the Sengoku period.
Dominated the Sengoku period?
I'm not sure if I get what you mean...
Belonging to no particular country or style, he randomly passed out the katanas that he made throughout the land.
Within 25 different countries,
he gave out a thousand katanas.
A thousand?
That's quite a lot!
No, not really.
Not very many, then.
The countries that received his katanas were given an edge on the battlefield.
With this advantage, they dominated during the Sengoku period.
Couldn't it be the other way around?
Maybe large countries that held an advantage in combat were able to amass more of his katanas.
That's probably how it looks from a practical standpoint.
On the other hand, there is a basis for these myths.
It's said that 150 years ago, Shogun Kyuu obsessed over these mythical weapons and nearly unified the world...
by holding a majority of the katanas, 507 of them.
How childish...
After that, Shogun Kyuu, who put all his trust in Shikizaki's katanas, made the corrupt decree to collect every katana.
The one he said was for making a Buddha statue or something?
That's was only for appearance.
I heard the real purpose was to bring together all the swordsmen.
No, the true goal was—
To collect all of Shikizaki's katanas.
Exactly.
That's quite surprising to hear.
That being said, Shogun Kyuu collected over 100,000 katanas.
100,000 katanas?
That's not very many!
Quite a lot.
Quite a lot, then...
So, did he collect all of Shikizaki's katanas?
No.
He gave up at the very end.
He managed to track down the locations of all 1,000 katanas...
but only their locations.
Shouldn't he have been able to collect them all, then?
After all, he had the authority of the Shogunate.
It didn't work out that way.
Among the 1,000 katanas, the final 12 were incredibly unique.
It's now believed that the first 988 were merely practice for the creation of those 12 katanas.
1,000 for the sake of 12?
Pretty crazy story, right?
Kanna.
Namakura.
Tsurugi.
Hari.
Yoroi.
Kanazuchi.
Bita.
Kanzashi.
Nokogiri.
Hakari.
Mekki.
Jyuu.
And the evil of those katanas is incomparable to any other katana you've heard of.
Records say that the armies sent by Shogun Kyuu to collect them were wiped out by the power of a single katana.
This is the first time I've heard that.
And that's why I've come to this island.
Shichika Yasuri, head of the Swordless Style.
I've come to convey this command to you: gather the last 12 katanas that the legendary swordsmith Kiki Shikizaki made.
So that's what you meant when you asked if I wanted to rule the world.
Indeed.
I didn't actually mean you would rule the world.
The current Shogunate has been stable for a long time, right?
They were able to suppress the rebellion by using all their strength.
Indeed, all their strength.
No, I mean that rebellion was a problem.
The Owari Shogunate has been in power for 150 years now.
No one in this generation really understands what the Sengoku period was like anymore.
These days, no one really thinks of Kiki Shikizaki's katanas as anything more than trinkets; just looking at them is enough.
But if those who were behind the last rebellion were to get a hold of those 12 katanas,
what would happen to the current Shogunate?
They fear a revolt...
You can never be too careful, huh?
So where are these katanas currently?
The ones we know of are in Inaba, Izumo, Satsuma, Ezo, and Tosa.
The rest are still being searched for.
You only know where half of them are...
Say "you've already found half of them" instead!
What is it?
If they're afraid of a revolt, wouldn't it be smarter to not provoke the current owners?
The Shogunate's order was to "do it skillfully."
How would you do it skillfully?
We have a super-strategist for that very purpose!
Someone who can move about in the shadows.
Umm...
What exactly is a super-strategist?
Specifically, I'm the general director of Tatematsu Akuzari's army, under Shogun Yanari of the Owari Shogunate.
I'm Togame the super-strategist.
Umm...
Is that a new post created in the last 20 years or something?
No, I just made up the title.
Self-named?!
If tactics are created by a tactician,
strategies are created by a super-strategist!
I'm special, so special orders are given to me.
That being the case, will you lend me your strength?
If you're really from the Shogunate, there's no need for you to go out of your way to find the Swordless Style...
I know what you're trying to say,
but I can't use people who will work for money.
The ninjas entrusted with the task of collecting the katanas...
betrayed us.
Even though they're ninjas?
Your surprise is understandable.
By doing that, they destroyed the trust they had built up over all those years.
Even so, once they found the katanas, they disappeared.
The entire ninja army, along with their whole village.
Unbelievable...
The final katanas are considered such a treasure that you could buy an entire country with just one of them.
That's why those who would work for money are unacceptable.
I see.
Then how about honor?
My father taught me that swordsmen should do what's right.
Honor, huh...
Swordsmen are no good either.
The Shogunate picked one of their strongest, most loyal and honorable swordsmen.
His name was Hakuhei Sabi.
They tasked him with retrieving the most difficult katana: Hakutou Hari.
However, he obtained it amazingly quickly.
Wow!
He obtained it, then disappeared.
No way!
Its poison is too strong.
This was precisely because of his swordsman's honor.
He couldn't resist the honor of owning one of Shikizaki's katanas.
Ninjas and swordsmen...
So the katanas are now possessed by very powerful people...
Your followers must all be running away.
That's right!
What else could happen?
Like I'd know!
So that's why you sought out the Swordless Style.
Swordsmen who don't work for money and don't wield katanas.
Exactly.
Head of the Swordless Style, Shichika Yasuri!
Will you lend me your skills to ensure the prosperity of the Owari Shogunate?
I understand why you came here,
and it sounds important to you, but I don't have any interest in katanas.
Are you scared?
Of course I am!
But more importantly, it's a hassle to leave the island and cross the sea.
Do you think I didn't anticipate that answer?
Do you believe that this super-strategist, who has been betrayed so many times in the past,
came to this island without preparing an adequate reason for you?
You've been betrayed, have you?
Well, do you have one? A reason?
Yeah.
People who work for money are no good.
People who work for honor are no good, too.
That only leaves one reason.
Love!
L-Love?
People who work for love can be trusted.
Shichika Yasuri...
fall for me!
Shuriken?
What the hell?!
This is the home Dad built!
Shichika...
Honestly, what an illogical...
No, that was the right thing to do.
With aerial weaponry, you have to make split-second decisions.
Well, he's just moving on instinct...
A ninja... from the Maniwa squad, it seems.
Maniwa?
The ones who betrayed us the instant they learned the value of Shikizaki's katanas.
How many are there?
Probably just one.
Maniwa ninjas hate working in groups.
What I don't know is why they're here...
I wasn't tailed, and I didn't tell anyone my destination.
If the enemy is really here alone,
then they're likely trying to lead Shichika to the beach to confront him there.
You seem pretty confident in him.
The enemy is from the Maniwa squad, you know?
A user of the Swordless Style won't lose to a mere ninja.
That's reassuring, but the question of why a Maniwa ninja is here is a far more important matter!
That's true...
Togame, are you sure there was no way you were followed?
Don't insult me.
It was precisely because the opponent is a ninja that I was more cautious than usual.
That's also why I didn't tell anyone my destination.
I really wonder how...
Did you come to this island alone?
You're seriously asking that?
Well, how did you get here?
I came by boat, of course!
Did you row the boat yourself?
What a weird question.
My specialty is brain work.
Does it look like I'd have the strength to—
So there was a ferryman?
Uh... yes, but...
Oh no!
That guy has one of Shikizaki's katanas!
I hope you're not thinking that
you've driven me into a corner.
It's really the opposite!
I'm the one who led you here!
Wait, wait...
My head is spinning from all the visitors here today.
Could you not all come on the same day like this?
I don't give a damn about your problems.
I'm one of the 12 heads of the Maniwa squad, the great Koumori Maniwa!
Maniwa squad?
Oh yeah, I heard you're a ninja or something.
The fact that you learned that is bad luck for you.
Otherwise, I'd have just ignored you.
My objective is to get the woman who has all that information.
You were eavesdropping?
That's a distasteful hobby.
You should say it's a good hobby!
You tailed Togame here?
Nope.
I wouldn't do something so sneaky.
We came here together.
I rowed the boat all the way here.
It was hard work you know.
That woman just sat on her ass the whole time without lifting a finger to help.
Does everyone from the mainland talk this much?
She's got quite the nerve, geez...
Don't you think so?
Right...
You're a pretty dull guy.
Well, you are from the boonies I guess...
Can't help that.
It's nothing personal, but I'll have to kill you here.
Come to think of it, this is my first real battle, isn't it?
Are you scared?
No...
From what I can tell, you aren't carrying a katana...
Oh right, you're a swordsman who doesn't use a sword, right?
When it comes to "swordsmanship" you usually assume that you're going to be fighting with swords.
That's some pretty absurd swordsmanship!
Not really, but I don't know much about how ninjas fight.
Don't worry.
Though I'm not a swordsman, it's not like I can't use a sword.
So, how about I bring out the katana I'm carrying?
What the...?
Humans can do that?
Listen, look, and be shocked!
This is one of the 12 deviant katanas that Kiki Shikizaki perfected, Zettou Kanna!
Your body has shocked me more than that katana.
They call me Hellish Koumori!
Which means I'm pretty generous when it comes to serving up presents from Hell.
Koumori the maid?
Note: The word "Hell" sounds just like "Maid".
It has a pretty cute feeling though.
Stop talking crap already!
Putting that aside, aren't you feeling anything right now?
Just to let you know, this is one of the Shikizaki katanas that the woman was talking about earlier.
Nothing at all?
I don't really want to take it when it's all sticky like that.
It's really valuable, right?
Should you really be walking around with it like that?
It's totally the opposite of it.
If I didn't keep it stored inside my body, I'd be worried about the safety of such a valuable treasure.
On top of that, it has an interesting power.
That woman called it poison, but this thing is the ultimate medicine!
When you hold it, you feel its desire to cut off people's heads!
Perfect Retribution strike!
Swordless Style, first dance: Lily of the Valley
Then how about this one?
Perfect Retribution strike!
Swordless Style: Misgiving!
Huh?
You bastard...
You saw through—
You're so noisy!
You have my gratitude.
It's been a long time since someone has managed to surprise me.
You use your arms and legs as swords...
You're pretty good. I guess you really are a swordsman.
I'm not as surprising as you though.
Also...
Not as surprising as that "Kanna" either.
Did you notice anything from that attack?
The technique I used wasn't supposed to catch katanas.
"Swordless Style: Misgiving" is a technique that breaks your opponent's sword in two.
That katana is definitely weird.
No matter what you think, this is weird!
It would be strange if it didn't seem weird.
This Zettou Kanna was created with toughness as its main point.
Katanas are expendable, so when you use them they'll break or bend and lose their ability to cut.
However, this Kanna is different.
It can neither be broken nor bent.
That's why it cuts so well.
It's so straight that no matter what you do, it won't chip.
It's a katana that wouldn't break even if an elephant stepped on it.
It'll sell for a really high price too!
I did some research as well...
Even though that geezer Shikizaki was a swordsmith, he also dabbled in the occult and alchemy.
Doesn't that seem suspicious?
A guy who pulls katanas out of his mouth like you is 12 times more suspicious.
Anyway, there's a reason behind this story.
You must now understand that Swordless Style cannot match up to Shikizaki's katanas.
Your sword-breaking technique couldn't break it after all!
Swordless Style aims to destroy the opponent's weapons.
Wow! I'm fabulous!
But I would have loved to see you succeed!
Swordless Style, second dance: Daffodil.
This time, I will break that damn Zettou Kanna for sure.
Idiot!
What do you mean break it?!
If I bring it back like that, they'll make me kill myself!
Didn't you hear a word I said?!
I never said I'd accept your request in the first place...
That's not the problem here!
Do you actually understand the value of things?
That's right!
Since I understand the value of things, smashing something valuable is beyond my imagination.
How about I start off with this?
It's been awhile, kitty.
Koumori... Maniwa.
Don't be so mad.
Ninjas might be traitors, but it's exactly what people pay us to do.
You bastard!
We'll have plenty of time to talk about this issue later, super-strategist.
Nice and slowly, after I destroy this Swordless Style guy!
Shichika, defeat him!
Okay, but that Kanna has got me puzzled.
Like I said, just don't break the katana!
Alright, alright.
If you have any other requests, say them now.
I'm going to end this in an instant.
Well, then let's see...
If you can, do it with some flashy move.
I'll have to report to them about how we obtained the katana.
If you have some cool flashy move that'll capture the reader's eyes, it'll be awesome!
Once again, don't destroy that katana, no matter what.
If you do, this story will end in the very first chapter.
First chapter? Are you writing a book?
I'd also like to do that sometime in the future.
It'd sell!
Then I guess I'll show you something flashy.
The wait is over, Koumori.
Wai- hey!
No, no, it was me who kept you waiting.
What are you doing?
It won't be much of a fight like this!
I'm not a swordsman, you see.
I'm particular about this katana, so I wouldn't be much of a shinobi if you beat me here.
Note: The word "Shinobi" also means "Stealing"
Oops, was that a pun?
I don't care.
Either way, I will beat you.
If I fight using ninjutsu, you will be no match for me.
My battlefield experience is on a far higher level than yours.
I've been warming up until now.
This is one of my bad habits.
I'm going to get serious from now on.
Stop screwing around!
Don't drool all over it like it's some decoration of yours.
Take it out! Take it out right now!
Geez, that kitty is pretty noisy.
Alright then...
Oh? You're unexpectedly cooperati—
Ouch...
Huh?
Damn it, that was really close.
That kid is pretty good.
Well, I figured that he wouldn't be a weakling, right kitty?
What is this?
Oh, you're awake already?
Don't worry, I'm getting serious from now on.
Koumori!
You thought you'd be okay if you stayed beside him, didn't you?
You're naive!
He may be used to battling, but he hasn't been on an actual battlefield.
You're just a running coward.
Hey, hey, hey. What crap are you talking about?
Aren't smart people supposed to fight brawn with brains, super-strategist?
All you do is bully weak people!
I come up with ways for the weak to overcome the strong
by slowly whittling away at the opponent's energy and spirit.
Don't even compare me to yourself, you trash!
Seems like strategists are also good at running their mouths.
Anyway, you didn't mean that, did you?
What?
"Fall for me."
Come on, that's madness!
I was so surprised that I accidentally spat out some of those shuriken.
That wasn't intentional?
I was too embarrassed to bear with it.
Don't be so uptight, I've always wanted to say that.
Well I'm glad I overheard the information I needed.
Hurry up and kill me already!
Stop trying to act so dignified, kitty.
Even when you say that, you're still trying to think of a way to fool me, aren't you?
Your brain is probably all over the place right now.
Don't worry, I'm not going to kill you.
I missed that shuriken attack earlier on purpose.
You don't understand the concept of moderation, do you?
If even one had hit me, I would have died.
You don't know how fragile I am!
That isn't something you should be bragging about!
When I return, I'll torture you some more. So bear with it a little longer.
I'm sure you're not completely clueless about the location of the remaining katanas.
Since this is the end for you, I'll ask you.
How about turning your back on the Shogunate and following us?
I'll give you some action.
I refuse.
People who work for money can never be trusted.
Are you afraid of being betrayed?
I'd say it's even more strange to trust a ninja.
Well then...
I'm pretty sure you've been thinking about it,
but the truth is, you're not actually a hostage.
How about this?
What if I made myself look like you?
This way, even that Swordless Style guy will let his guard down for sure.
You must be aware of my ability, right? I found and stole Kanna under your orders after all.
After I kill that Swordless Style guy,
maybe I'll transform into him to kill you.
Sorry, but you'll have to wait here until then.
Wait!
I originally betrayed you for money...
But had I known what kind of person you were from the start, I never would have worked with you.
Even that invitation just now was so I could work with you...
And then betray you once again.
No one in this world would stay by your side.
That's strange...
Where on Earth did they go?
Leave the island, huh...
This late...
What a hassle.
It's true that the Swordless Style is a particularly troublesome opponent against Shikizaki's deviant katanas.
I'll have to use this chance to kill him.
I'll make sure he's dead. It's too bad...
Well, once that woman set her eyes on him, his luck had already run out.
Should I go now?
The premise will be that I barely escaped from him with my life.
Before he can say anything, I'll hug him...
and then kill him.
Shichika!
Swordless Style: Peony!
Why?!
Something went wrong.
The disguise?
No, this isn't even a disguise, my transformation was perfect!
Now that I look at it, isn't it Togame?
This guy...
He used the technique without even knowing who I was?!
Huh?
Wait, then I guess you're Koumori?
Guess?
Y-You...
Can't you even recognize who's in front of you?!
Well, this is the first time I've ever seen another human besides Sis.
I can't recognize faces that quickly.
What the hell?!
The disguise wasn't the problem then!
This guy couldn't even recognize people from the beginning?
That was close...
If it was her, she'd have died.
This is beyond boonies...
This guy is like an animal!
She asked for a flashy move, but it's getting kind of boring.
You...
Do you really want to help that woman so badly?
I'm asking if you want her to use you!
Used?
Didn't you think there was something strange about her story?
Why the Shogunate suddenly wants to collect Shikizaki's katanas?
Isn't it because they're afraid of rebellions?
That is one of the reasons, indeed.
It's true, however...
Don't you think it's a bit too perfect?
The Shogunate today doesn't hold the same reverence for Shikizaki's katanas as Shogun Kyuu did.
They're far more pragmatic.
Also, collecting the katanas will help that woman gain more recognition.
Togame the super-strategist...
It's just a move for her to gain fame within the army as general director.
I don't really understand that recognition stuff,
but isn't general director of the army already pretty high up?
That woman isn't happy with that level.
She's aiming for the top.
Don't you ever doubt anyone?
That woman will use any dirty tactics she needs to rise to the top.
Mental power isn't everything in this world.
When I first met her, she terrified me.
There is only ambition in her eyes.
You can feel her willingness to sacrifice anyone and anything for her goals.
She was even planning to use the Maniwa squad.
A fearsome ninja brigade made up of professional assassins, you know? This is madness!
And now she is using you, Swordless Style user!
Is it going to end here?
In a place like this?
So before you were betrayed, you betrayed her?
That's right.
There's no way I'd follow a woman like that.
What do you think her ultimate goal is?
The right hand of the Shogun!
The current Shogun is already too old.
It won't be long before he retires.
When that happens, I'm sure you can imagine what the natural step will be for the young lieutenant after him, can't you?
Ruling the world...
I threw away my name and my family, all for it to end on this island?
That's not really something to accuse her of...
Well, for someone like you who was used, I'm sure it won't feel right.
I don't really care about being used.
Getting used and using others is the way of the world.
However, my problem is the reason I was used!
Just to let you know, I'm not the brightest. I have trouble understanding when you talk like that.
This woman is the daughter of the leader of the last rebellion, Takahito Hida!
Who can deny the intentions of traitors?
In better times, she'd have been the princess of her own country.
I can already see it.
It's within my grasp!
That woman is just aiming for promotion without caring about anything.
She aims to be the right hand man to the current Shogun.
I'm sure you understand what that means.
Father's dreams...
Father's heart...
She was willing to ask for help from her father's enemies to collect those katanas?
It must be clear to you already what she's planning...
Revenge!
Even after I have gone against Father's feelings!
It's revenge for having her whole family exterminated!
After all, that girl was watching as her family was murdered.
Even if it was my last resort, to ask the person responsible for my father's death...
Even if it wasn't the man himself, but to depend on his son...
Even though I'm the son of her enemy...
Maybe I was wrong to rely on the Swordless Style after all...
She's an insect born from the leader of the rebellion.
I don't want to hear about treachery or cowardice from her!
This is a good body.
Allow me to use it as a reference from now on.
Your strength, musculature, and balance are all perfectly fit.
But,
I have a little advantage here since you've got the pain in your arms and legs where my shuriken hit earlier.
Just to let you know, an attack like that doesn't hurt, or even make me itch, anymore.
That's what it seems like, so I guess we're as equal as two rocks.
But my rock is quite strong.
Hey.
Is there anyone else who knows Togame's secret?
There's no way I'd just give away such intriguing information.
So it'll be fine if I just finish you off here, right?
You're suddenly in a fighting mood now that you're facing me?
I am the 7th generation Swordless Style head, Shichika Yasuri.
Here I go!
Don't try to act cool!
Come!
I'll finish you with an amazingly fabulous move!
Ultimate Attack!
Perfect Retribution strike!
Wh-Why?!
Swordless Style men don't have any skill whatsoever with a katana!
We're not swordsmen who don't use swords,
we're swordsmen who can't use them!
I'm going to be...
I may have called it "Ultimate Attack,"
but it only sounds cheesy because it's an ultimate move I just created yesterday!
The opponent is hit seven times in the blink of an eye, and gets split into eight pieces.
So for now, I'll call it:
Swordless Style: Shichika Eightpiece!
What a pathetic state I'm in now...
And I'm from a samurai bloodline too!
Before this gets any more embarrassing, I've got to...
This rope won't loosen without being unraveled.
How am I supposed to twist free without using anything?
This is going to be quite a challenge!
So you were here.
So that's the "eye" he was talking about.
To me, at least, it sparkles in quite a pretty way.
Well for now, I've got one of the katanas.
Why does he sound like he'll be continuing?
Shichika, what about Koumori?!
I finished him off with a fabulous move.
You missed it.
That's too bad.
Don't get me wrong, I did it for you.
It's not like I want money, or that I've been lured in by Shikizaki's katanas.
And I don't feel a shred of obligation to help the Shogunate either.
I've just decided that I want to help you.
I've fallen for you.
Togame.
I wanted to let you know, I approve of this decision.
Is that right?
I thought for sure you'd object.
I suppose...
Well to be honest, I don't really care at all about the actual basis of your journey.
If that child has found a reason to leave this island, I approve of it.
He's been on this island for 20 years, training and studying hard,
and it'd simply be too much of a waste if he didn't put it to use.
Just so you know, it's not going to be a simple journey in any sense.
There's the Maniwa squad and Hakuhei Sabi, of course, and any other monsters that may lie where we're headed.
Demons and serpents...
I'm bringing along your brother to fight those kinds of battles.
You're quite kind, aren't you?
You truly care about him, don't you?
I have no worries entrusting him to your care.
I'm...
I'm not such a kind woman.
Shichika Yasuri, I have four directives for you.
Four?
Let's hear them.
First I'll repeat what I said earlier - don't break the katanas.
Understood.
I will protect the katanas.
The second?
Protect me.
Even though our objective is to collect Shikizaki's katanas, if I die it will all be in vain.
Understood.
I will protect you.
The third?
Protect yourself.
This isn't me being considerate of you or anything.
Until we collect all 12 of Shikizaki's katanas, dying is unacceptable.
Understood.
I will protect myself.
The fourth?
Protect yourself.
This is me being considerate of you.
Don't die.
The road will be harsh, but you mustn't die.
You can do that right?
I won't let you say you can't.
Hurry up and say you get it!
I completely understand.
So what do we do now?
No need to rush ahead.
When we get to the city, I'll buy you some clothes.
Got it.
I love you.
Yep.
Love me as much as you want.
A man unknown to everyone, a woman who closed her heart.
Those two began their journey.
A journey to collect katanas, without destination or destiny.
Demons and serpents await them.
The story of Katanagatari on this evening...
...ends here.
Though...
That child is so weak... will they be okay?
Drifting on the waves are flowers nestled together
which are broken up and cut
until all that remains is their transient story
Most people never break the habit
In your dream, eyes turn to moonlight
The life of my immortal soul
To half-closed eyes turns around
the proof of an oath
The flower raised to the eye
and the area we protect wither
By the raven's judgment, we are poor
Among all the flowers,
a single flower's fragrance dissolves
My secret life calls attention to itself
It's cruel we dream of the fleeting time we met
This is the general director for the army of Tatematsu Akuzari,
who answers to Shogun Yanari of the Owari Shogunate,
Togame the super-strategist here.
Everything is going according to plan.
You doubt me?
I also calculated that you'd think that.
Now then, it's time for my peerless, uplifting,
solemn story of justice to begin, but...
About that Swordless Style man,
Shichika Yasuri...
How far will he serve as my blade?
Zantou
Namakura
Next episode: Katanagatari - Zantou Namakura.
Cheerio!