This is hard!
I give up! Help me, Yui!
Haruka.
Haruka!
Kanata!
On second thought, I'll go ask Minami!
Haruka...
You found a Dress Up Key?
It's because you've all become
ever more radiant as princesses.
My staff was finally able to catch their signal.
I'll display them on your Lesson Pad.
Isn't this...
Noble Academy?!
They were right under our noses!
That means we can pick them up right away!
But this school is pretty big.
The Dress Up Keys appear where dreams are brimming
just as the ones that were drawn to you once did.
Where dreams are brimming?
Dreams?
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Where Is It?
The New Dress Up Key!
Gotta find the Dress Up Key!
Gotta find the Dress Up K—oomph!
A place brimming with dreams?
A place brimming with dreams...
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Guess it's not here.
I figured the clubs would be filled with dreams...
But where else would the Dress Up Keys be drawn to?
We should ask someone who knows everything about the school.
Shirogane, dorm mother.
It's getting late, so please return to your rooms.
Okay, will do.
She's like the academy's sage.
Of course! Let's ask Mrs. Shirogane!
Mrs. Shirogane!
Huh?
Mrs. Shirogane always shows up out of nowhere and disappears before you know it.
She's like a ninja.
There are rumors that Mrs. Shirogane is the descendant of an ancient ninja clan.
Really?
Oh yeah, Mom said that once.
Come to think of it, I don't know a thing about her private life either.
Rumor has it that she can actually teleport!
Or that she's actually three people!
Quite the enigma.
I've seen Mrs. Shirogane do something suspicious before.
Really? What?
Last Sunday,
I happened to wake up early.
And there I saw Mrs. Shirogane heading somewhere.
She had an odd looking key hanging around her neck...
but I lost sight of her pretty quickly.
An odd looking key?
That could only be...
Hey, Haruka, want to follow Mrs. Shirogane together next time?
Yeah!
Shoot! Finding the Dress Up Keys is a Precure thing!
Yui isn't supposed to know!
O-On second thought, I'll pass!
I'm not a morning person, after all!
G-Good night!
Oh...
Good night.
Yui...
I'm sorry.
Is that the Dress Up Key?
I can't tell from here!
For now, let's follow her trail!
Shades!
Shades.
I've never been here before.
Mrs. Shirogane's in suspiciously full bloom!
Cure Flora!
If you hadn't butted in,
I would've defeated Cure Mermaid!
The consequences for failure go without saying.
Think, blast it, think!
I gotta get back on her good side!
It's a dead end.
Yes, a dead end.
Where's Mrs. Shirogane?
How could we lose sight of her here?!
Come on...
Haruka!
Ouch!
Where am I?
Are you okay?
Isn't this an underground tunnel?
It looks ancient!
This calls for some exploration!
Yeah!
A rose garden!
It's splendid!
It reminds me of Hope Kingdom!
Are these roses too?
Yeah! Those are White Magics!
Those are Hana-gasumis, these are Destinies, and over there are Ingrid Bergmans!
This is amazing!
You know your flowers!
I'm trying to be the Princess of Flowers, after all!
I never knew such a splendid place was atop this cliff.
Hm?
Could that be...
Splendid!
Haruka!
Guess nobody's home.
It's open.
Let's take a breather.
Perf!
Water?
What is this place?
Hey, look!
The water's great!
But this place is strange.
Indeed, it's very well kept.
"My dream is to be a singer-songwriter."
"I'll be a world famous fashion designer."
What are these?
"I'll be a top model who shines around the world."
"Amanogawa Stella."
This is my mom!
"I'll be a fitting successor to the Kaidou business."
"Kaidou Wataru."
My brother...
These are all dreams written by Noble Academy students!
And what might you all be doing here?
Ribbon Pigtails!
Noble Academy students have come to this cottage as part of their graduation ceremony for generations.
They write their dreams alongside the
friends they made here and plant a rose.
It's a tradition that has always been
kept secret from those still enrolled.
Normally, students can only enter here once they've completed the ceremony.
I deeply apologize.
We're sorry.
Under the rose...
Huh?
So as to not speak a word of this place to others...
It's an old European saying that
means to keep something secret.
That's why this place is surrounded by roses, right?
Then, that key is...
You mean this?
I've been tasked with this garden's upkeep since my own graduation.
Since your graduation?!
I was the first graduate to write one of these tiles.
Wow, really?
A senior in more ways than one...
So you've maintained this place ever since?
What a nice breeze...
Hey, look!
The tiles of dreams are sparkling!
Wow!
Your seniors all stood here once.
They vowed to soar toward their dreams with the sea and sky before them as the wind beneath their wings.
I ask that you all support each
other in following your dreams.
Our seniors were just like us!
Yeah.
What?
Haruka, what are you doing here?
I feel it...
This place is stinkin' with dreams!
Isn't he...
Dress Up Keys!
Haruka!
With all the dreams stuffed in here,
I'm gettin' a crackin' strong Dyspairvil!
The Dress Up Keys!
Get outside!
Close your dream!
Come, Dyspairvil!
Mrs. Shirogane's still—
Dyspaaaaair...
Viiiiil!
That cottage was filled with our seniors' dreams...
That's a bloody lot of dreams in there!
Get 'em, Dyspairvil!
Dyspair...
Vivivivivi...
Get back!
Vil!
Yui!
Are you okay?
Haruka!
Yui!
I think I sprained my ankle...
Dyspaaair...
Kaidou? Amanogawa?
What...
What's going on?
Yui...
I'm sorry I never told you.
Let's go, girls!
Right!
We've got no choice!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go! Princess Precure!
Princess Precure?
Haruka?
Our seniors' dreams shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dyspairvil!
Ouch!
Here it comes!
Dyspair!
This one's gonna be a pain.
Huh?
Watch your step!
I'll get it in one shot!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Dreaming...
Vil!
No way...
Why didn't that beat it?
All the dreams trapped inside it
make it that much more powerful!
Gotcha, Precures. There's nowhere to run!
Not like ya ain't gonna try!
Dyspairvil!
You're finished, Precures!
Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
I won't let you ruin them...
Huh?
The cottage filled with dreams...
The memories of friends who supported and swore upon each other...
weren't meant to be twisted into that!
I won't give in here!
We'll protect everyone's hopes!
And dreams!
From the likes of you!
Dysp—
Dyspairvil!
What?!
The light of the Dress Up Keys!
Now's our chance!
Vil!
Let's go!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Rage, O seas!
Precure!
Mermaid Ripple!
Shine, O stars!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
She's fine. She's only lost consciousness.
Thank goodness.
New Dress Up Keys...
These are the Elegant Dress Up Keys!
Twinkle has the Luna Key!
Mermaid's Key is the Ice Key!
Flora's Key is the Rose Key!
Nice to meet you...
Haruka...
I... I can still...
How pitiful, Close.
What?!
Thaaat's...
Lady Dyspear!
Dyspear?
That's her?
I've finally found it.
It must be around here.
I must deliver these to the Precures!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Dyspear used her powers to make Close transform?
You intend to throw away who you are to fight us?
We'll need a new approach for this battle!
It doesn't how much you've powered up, Close! We still won't lose!
As long as I have a dream within my heart...
We won't give in to despair!
Go! Princess Precure:
A Colossal Crisis!
Precure vs. Close!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Saitama Prefecture - Kirara (Age 11)
Shimane Prefecture - Nao (Age 7)