"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Morning, both of you!
S'up?
Good morning!
You remembered to wear the winter uniform.
Hey, I'm no Tsukasa.
What?!
But it's still hot out,
so I think we could've stayed in
our summer uniforms a bit longer.
And when we swap to the summer
ones, it's still cold.
I really wish that they'd let us
choose on our own when to change.
Right!
I think it's mostly trying to get
us to change gears, mentally.
Otherwise, we'd end up with people
who are less clear-cut, like you two.
"Pandora's Box"
Our family isn't like this,
but I hear that some parents
out there check out the e-mail
on their daughters' cell
phones and computers.
Oh, I hear about that every once in a while.
That doesn't happen with you?
I don't think that happens here, either.
Your dad loves you to death,
so he wouldn't do anything that
his daughter would dislike, right?
Well, there's that...
But my dad uses computers, too.
So, he probably knows it's humiliating
when someone peeks at your D drive.
D? What?
Summer was so full of classes and stuff
that the only play time I had was
when we went to see the fireworks,
and that time in Ariake.
So you went to Comiket after all.
Comiket...
Of course.
Thanks to that, my wallet
is feeling a bit lonely.
Just how much did you spend there?
You really cut loose there.
Each volume cost an average
of 1,000 yen each...
So I think somewhere around
40,000 to 50,000 yen?
Hold on!
There are limits as to how much your
financial outlook can be warped...
You say that, Kagamin, but "fair
market value" exists in this world.
Self-published items are
relatively expensive.
I'm not talking about that!
I'm talking about your mental state,
spending so much money on them!
Whew.
It's still hot out, though
it's already September.
You're right.
It seems that it's especially
hot out this year.
They're talking about
global warming and such.
Yu-chan can get heat
exhaustion really easily,
so she often rests in the living
room and other rooms with A/C.
Tsukasa always spends her time in
rooms with air conditioning, too.
Though she's just slacking off.
Well, Dad and I join her,
and we always roll around,
in the shape of the kanji "shou (small)."
"Shou?" By that, don't
you mean "kawa (river)?"
No, Dad always lies down in the middle.
Your house is always like that.
I guess Yutaka-chan has gotten used to it.
Yoo-hoo! Yutaka, are you doing well?
I'm here to visit!
Oh, Sis!
Oh? Who might this be?
This is my friend, Minami Iwasaki-chan!
Oh, this is the Minami-chan that
you always talk about, Yutaka?
Sis!
I'm a little bit jealous,
with so much hope coming from
someone that is closest to you...
Well, I've heard many a rumor,
but you really are pretty.
I'm totally surprised!
Want something to drink?
Okay, beer!
Oh? Didn't you drive here?
Just kidding! Barley tea. Barley tea!
Oh, I see... one sibling absorbed
that of the other... absorbed...
Oh, it was just the yassai-mossai festival.
I always get so sleepy at night.
Is there a good way to avoid it?
Isn't it better to just go to sleep
early and wake up early in the morning,
instead of forcing yourself to
go on? You'd feel better too.
I see! You're right!
I'll wake up a bit early, and do my best!
Oh? Why is it the same
time as usual right now?
That's right, I remember stopping
something somewhere in the middle.
Because of my old habits,
even if I get up early,
I feel reassured and fall asleep again.
So weak-willed!
Maybe it's better for me to do my best
and keep going late into the night?
You won't get better results if you're
rubbing sleepy eyes the whole time.
In that case, why don't you
have someone wake you up?
Mom and the others wake up early.
Right, Mom?
Yes, yes. I'll make sure to get you up.
Yeah, this will definitely work.
Nothing less from you, Sis.
Mom! I told you to wake me up!
I did wake you up, and you answered me, too!
Eh? I don't know anything about that!
You don't remember?
Sis forgot her lunch.
Thank you!
The hallway of a different
graduating class seems so strange.
I feel like I'm under some pressure.
Oh, I know what you mean.
I'm sure Yu-chan really got some attention.
I mean, she looks like this...
It's usually just you overreacting,
but upper or underclassmen aside,
going to a different place
creates a strange atmosphere
that makes you feel like you're
the center of attention.
I'm small to begin with, so I stand out.
But when I think upperclassmen are
looking at me, I really feel pressure.
I rather like getting that kind of attention.
Oh, I see.
But even if I go into the 10th graders' area,
I don't get much attention,
since they don't think I'm an upperclassman.
"Doesn't give off the feeling
of an upperclassman"
Oh, Patty-chan.
Hi! Nice to see you!
Are you going to work now?
That's right. I put in too
many shifts this week.
You're still going on with that, right?
Yeah. We're pretty popular.
The A-Boys are all moe-moe for us!
A-Boy?
That's what you call the boys that
look like they are that type,
the ones that often are found in Akiba.
But Narimiya-kun was a bit different.
You've gotten quite accustomed to Japan now.
Though only in one particular point!
Oh, I came up with a good idea.
When I get out of the
bath, I'll sketch it out.
Wait... I can't remember what it was!
This always happens when I don't
jot down a note right away!
It was so amusing! I know
it was really amusing!
I'm tired today too...
Oh, this idea may be a bit amusing...
I'll sketch it out when I
get up tomorrow morning.
Huh? That's strange... What was it?
I'm sure it was a wonderful idea.
I wish I wrote a memo to myself,
instead of feeling too lazy to do it.
Oh, geez! I even woke up right away!
Why do I forget dreams so easily?!
I'm so positive that it was an amusing idea!
Lucky Star!
And so, all of you, talk it
out and make up your minds!
Since we're going all the
way out to Kyoto and Nara,
look up those tourist spots
that you feel will be the bomb!
Aren't we going to hit all the
tourist spots together by bus?
The places we're all going
together are so standard-fare
that it won't be any fun!
When you say that, you take
all the fun out of it.
So Iris went inside here...
Now, I'd like to give you a tour
of the ancient capital of Nara.
It has been about 1300 years since
the relocation of the capital
to Kyoto, back in the year
710 of the Heian era.
Please enjoy the historical dramas from Nara,
drama that you can nar-row down
as events specific to Nara.
Nar-row down to Nara! -
Is this where you're supposed to laugh?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
So this is the main body, and all
the little ones around it are...
...options!
You know, you'll get divine
punishment for that.
I'm all sticky.
Smelly! I'm all smelly now!
Here, here.
It's rather smelly.
What's up with this?
Please, please.
I'm sure he means, "Please
push the shutter for us."
Um, let's see...
Click, click.
Okay?
At times like this, how much
you usually study really shows.
Like you can talk?
Let's see...
Sis, how do you say "Cheese!" in India?
You mean, in Hindi? Let's see, um...
Oh, even the genius Kagami is at a loss!
Um, don't they understand
English in India as well?
That's right. I think "Say
cheese!" should be good enough.
I see.
Say cheese!
You know, on these study tours, a lot
of couples suddenly start dating.
The events during the study tour are a must.
In the end, I believe that the environment
outside the school grounds
makes you feel more open.
I guess it's the time that
you feel is the right time.
It's rather embarrassing, but
I can't settle down and sleep
when I have to use a different pillow.
It's rather embarrassing, but
I can't settle down and sleep
when I don't have this next to me.
It's rather embarrassing,
but if I don't turn this on
at least once a day, I can't
settle down and sleep...
Everyone, the bus will soon
arrive at Kiyomizu Temple.
The hill leading up to Kiyomizu Temple
is called the Three-Year Hill.
Legend has it that if you trip here,
you will die in three years' time.
Then Three-Year Hill (sannen-zaka)
Turns into Sorry Hill (zannen-zaka).
Does that include laughing to death?
Listen up! We're starting
the group activities now.
Walk around, but be careful
of cars around you!
We're going to meet back up in
front of Chioin Temple at 12:30.
Don't be late!
Anyone who's late has a 20-page
report in their future!
Like this?
Let's try it.
Maybe this is about how heavy
that Dragon Slayer was?
This is so high up!
They say, "Feeling as if you were
jumping off the Kiyomizu stage,"
but if you really were to jump
off from here, wouldn't you die?
So do they mean it doesn't
matter what happens afterwards?
Kagamin, you have no dreams!
Hey, hey, it's a god of romance.
Apparently, this is a very famous
god for bringing couples together.
So easy to understand!
Oh, see, they have love fortunes over there!
Let's all pick fortunes!
Yeah, let's do it, let's do it.
As expected, I can't figure
out which is which.
Of course you can't!
This one!
"♪78 Great blessings"
Whoa! Great blessings!
Wow, I'm jealous, Kona-chan!
Oh, I was just fortunate.
That's really good enough. Now, as for me...
"♪7 Half-blessing"
Half-blessing? What's this?
Maybe it means you're half-blessed.
In other words, you're half cursed.
I could care less about love fortunes.
So cute!
Oh, that's nice.
No, Kagami, I think this one's for you.
What do you mean by that?
I'm going to buy this one.
Kagami, Kagami, you forgot. You forgot this.
I'm not buying it!
Then, what about this one?
I won't buy it!
Hey, be more careful!
"Devotional tablets to fulfill romance"
Hey, that says, "Konata is my wife."
All right, is everyone here?
We're going to the hotel now
to have lunch. Let's get going!
Okay, when you're ready.
It was written that Koizumi's
character song was sung IZAM-style.
Ma'am!
We have someone following us from behind!
What?!
At this rate, it will be
Hokkaido all over again!
You have to say, "___tel!"
That idiot! 50-page report for him!
Driver, excuse me! Please stop the bus.
"Hotel Honnouji"
Later!
"To Hiiragi"
"I want to talk to you, so please meet me at 9 PM in
front of the hotel we're staying at. --From a certain boy"
Kinkaku Temple is golden, but
Ginkaku Temple isn't silver.
Since it's brought up as a pair with Kinkaku,
they named it "Gin (silver)"
to complement "Kin (gold)."
So, it wasn't meant to
be silver to begin with.
I wonder if they don't have Sapphire
or Ruby, like they do in Pok_mon.
Then, I'd capture...
Our shrine was in the news the other day...
Only one day left now.
We've got our free activity plans down pat!
Tomorrow is our true study tour!
Onward, to the sanctuary!
Yeah...
You said in front of the hotel...
Was this the right place?
Yeah... Were you waiting long?
So, what did you want to talk about?
Yeah... I can't say this to
anyone but you, Hiiragi...
I want you to give me that doll!
Huh? Doll?
You know, the one you bought at the
souvenir shop at Kiyomizu Temple.
The little Yatsuhashi doll.
You mean Yatsuhashi-kun?
Right, that's the one.
I really took a liking to
it, and I really want one,
but I don't know what everyone would say
if anyone saw someone like me buying it.
Please!
Okay...
Thanks! I owe you one!
And don't tell anyone about this, okay?
That's right. That story about
brothers that turn into dragons...
What was it called?
You mean Sohryuden?
Yes! That! I'd like to see the
anime for that, if they ever...
I can't get it off!
The steam inside has cooled down,
and created a small vacuum.
They released an OVA for
it quite a while ago.
If you slightly slide one end,
Oh, is that so? I didn't know that.
Air will enter and make it easier
for you to take the lid off.
I see... Then...
Though it only goes to
volume 4 or so of the...
But, those books...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
You sure put on a show, even to the end.
I totally did the background
research for the location.
Can we really go there?
It's fine, we're only going to look
at the building from the outside.
You don't have to go this far just
because you're in Kyoto, you know.
You don't understand the marron
of being an otaku at all!
Nor do I ever want to understand.
There's nothing here.
This is just about right, so that
they can concentrate on their work.
The building is a lot more normal
than I thought it would be.
They keep the number of titles
small, so this is just about right.
Did you have to come all the
way to Kyoto to buy that?
No! That's so embarrassing!
It's all right. Think of
it as a memory of this day.
Let's take a picture together, Sis!
It will be for memory's sake.
After all, we came all the way out to Kyoto.
What part of this is like Kyoto?
Yeah, Tsukasa and I are both back, just fine.
Tsukasa is already asleep, though.
I thought that you'd be asleep
already from frustration, Kagami.
Why would I be asleep from frustration?
Did you stick that Print
Club sticker somewhere?
There's no way I'd be able to stick
that embarrassing thing anywhere!
That embarrassing thing...
We had our study tour this
week, so I really worked hard!
Now, this weekend, since it's been a while,
I'll play my heart out on 'net games!
"Announcement of emergency maintenance"
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Today, I have another booming
installment of Lucky Channel!
I'm Akira Kogami, your navigator!
And I'm Daisuke Ono, the assistant.
Time passes by so quickly, and
we're already on episode 21!
You're right. We're finally
getting to the final stages.
Now, let's hurry on towards this segment...
"This Week's Maggare"
This Week's Maggare...
Ugh... Who is that? What is it?
I've scooped some up.
Sniff sniff...
What is this? It's lukewarm!
I can't possibly drink something like this!
At this rate, I'd rather drink
something from a vending machine!
Don't mess with me!
You! You!
Just how much of your antics
do you think I've put up with?!
You always, always have
nothing but selfish requests!
Minoru?!
Today, of all days, will be
the day I break it to you!
Do you know how I've felt each week
when I was doing this segment?!
I spent day after day working
part-time at Ko_____hi!
I make more part-time than
I do as a voice actor!
And thanks to that, I'm one
of the veteran employees!
Before I lift your spirits every week,
I'm frying up ground meat cutlets!
So you are better suited for that occupation.
What?! What?!
Why are you sitting there
in the first place, Ono?!
That seat's reserved for me!
You have been cut out of the loop
by the producer and director.
What?!
They're too quick to come to judgment!
I'm the type that matures late in the game!
I can instantly turn into
a Starga__r from here!
Can someone like you really do that?
You're mocking me?!
I can't keep going with someone like
Hi__mosu, or with Lo__-and-__rry!
I'm going to quit!
I'm going to quit this show, goddammit!
What about Lucky Channel, dammit?!
What the hell are you filming me for?!
What about Misoji Misaki (Cape Thirties)?
If something like that can be
a comic idea, I'll admit it!
I'm almost 30!
Like I'm ever going to forgive you!
Welcome to Idaho!
"His belt isn't long enough, so he has
someone holding it behind his back."
Hey there, I'm Minoru Shiraishi.
Now, I'll have you listen up!
- Song of Shikaidar, boom!
What's up with this?
Dammit, don't move!
Don't move!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
Have you had enough of this?
Shikaidar is... Shikaidar is...
Don't stutter!
He is a cyborg!
Until the day evil is obliterated,
he will continue to fight!
You've had enough, right?
You can't fight like that!
How was it?
Obviously no good. You'll have to do it over.
Yes.
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's up with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
Akira Kogami here.
Daisuke Ono here. Caw.
Pekko? Pekko. Pekko pekko pekko.
Caw, caw.
Pekko?
Caw caw.
Pekko!
Caw.
Okay, that's enough of the animal talk.
Oh, so those were animals?
Next episode: The Yonder Here.
I can cross the finish line, right?
Pekko!
A ramen set!