Forgetting what someone just gave you is an act worthy of death, Araragi-kun.
Oh, sorry.
Even if you apologize, I won't forgive you.  So I came to give you a good ass kicking...
But it looks like you got hit by a car.
Something that looks like your
beloved bike is wrecked over there.
It's stuck in a telephone pole.
You'd have to be hit by a tractor-trailer or something for that to happen.
No, I just stumbled.  Alone.
I was trying to talk on the phone and pedal at the same time,
and I slammed right into the telephone post.
I see.
But you slammed into it hard enough to smash that block wall
and got away with so few injuries...
I'm impressed.
Hm, you don't need an ambulance, do you?
Naw.  If I rest for a little bit, I should be able to move.
I see.  Then I'll do something for you.
Lie there and be happy until you can move.
It's better to back off now while there's still time
Before we misunderstand each other even more
Before I knew it,
The staple you used to bind your words pierced my heart
It's your fault
Don't come to me the way I am now
Don't look at me wherever I go
Don't let go of me with that smile
No matter who you are
I prayed for an endless eternity
In the sky that stretches on forever
Like the sea with its harsh love,
You dove into my heart to take it
I want to deliver these feelings to you
That can't be weighed
GHO      ST   ORY
S U R U G A   M O N K E Y
bakemono
gatari
As a ghost story, or a horror, it was well done.
A textbook
tale of terror.
A truly historic, seemingly antique legend--
I guess
it's a classic.
If I asked Kanbaru for her opinion, she'd say
that it's not on the level of a vampire, and that
a monkey's paw is something pretty major that's
been remixed in various ways by various media.
The biggest thing
that makes the
monkey's paw the
monkey's paw is--
It is said that the monkey's paw fulfills its owner's wishes.
However, it is said to do so in a way that does not suit the owner.
It seems to have those two points.
It's that kind of item with an interesting history.
It seems
that
the monkey's paw was produced in India by a miracle-working sage in order to teach men
that they must live within the constricts of fate, and that to contradict it invites disaster.
When I think about things that grant three wishes,
my first thought is the magic lamp from Arabian Nights, but
that had many different conclusions in many different stories.
Beyond that,
around the world,
stories like those are well-known.
Tumult
Perhaps the type of story where something that can grant any wish appears before
someone is an archetypal story for those who possess unfulfillable huge desires.
Red
Episode 7
Suruga Monkey
Part 2
Font used in video:
HGP Mincho B
Black
Here you go, Araragi-senpai.
Sorry about the clutter.
Make yourself at home.
Honestly, you have an impressive level of sensitivity if you're hesitant to enter the room of a girl you don't know.
But that's not the case right now, is it?
Yeah.
Kanbaru.
What?
Can I have an hour-no, just thirty minutes-to clean this room?
Cleaning
Red
So, where shall we begin, Araragi-senpai?
Actually, let's start with last night.
I thought I'd apologize.
So it was  you?
Beast
Saying "it was  you" makes you sound irritated, Araragi-senpai.
You saw through it?
If you didn't, you wouldn't have visited me.
Not really.
It was just guesswork.
I judged by your build, outline, and silhouette.
Reminiscence
And by people who knew I'd gone to Senjougahara's place to study.
By breaking it down to those points, and thinking about it that way...
Reminiscence
Body
I see.  That was a great idea.
Does this have anything to do with the rumor
that some guys can identify girls by their hips?
Sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
Uh, apologies aside, what I'd really like to know is the reason.
Anyway, about the reason, I'd like to ask about that power.  That supernatural power.
Just what are you-
Black
Red
I guess that's the best place to begin.
That's right.
But...
First I want to ask if you're the kind of person who can believe in extraordinary things.
Extraordinary things?
You don't get it, huh.
What I meant was, can you believe what you see with your own eyes?
I don't believe anything I don't see.
Black
So I believe everything I see.
Senjougahara
Of course, it was the same with Senjougahara.
Crab
You even knew about that?
You on the basketball team and Senjougahara on track made the Valhalla Combo, right?
That's right!  You really do know a lot!
Sorry I overlooked that.
I heard the reason too.  It's a well thought out nickname.
Isn't it?  I'm the one who came up with it.
Red
She came up with it herself?
Black
It's been a while since I've felt so hopelessly sad for someone.
Well, that's about it.  The Valhalla Combo was us in middle school-
No.
Before we talk about that, there's something I want to show you.
To be honest, it's not really something I want people to see.
Girl
I know I may not act like it, but I'm still a girl.
Black
Well, it's like this.
Oddity
Reminiscence
It's like a monkey's paw...
Araragi-senpai, you have such unfathomably quick insight.
I'm impressed! I didn't think you'd be able to identify it with just a glance!
Don't come to that conclusion ahead of time!
I'm just saying what I see.  I didn't detect anything.
Really?  "The Monkey's Paw" was the title of a short story by William Wymark Jacobs.
It's an item said to fulfill its owner's wishes in twisted ways.
I didn't know about it at all.
You stated the truth without knowing anything!
Araragi-senpai, you must have been selected by someone up above.
Black
C-Can I touch it?
Sure, it should be fine now.
I-I see.
Living oddity
It's living...  I knew it, this is a living-type oddity...
Don't make weird sounds!
It's because you touched me in a weird way!
I didn't touch you in a weird way or anything!
I'm ticklish.
So there's no reason to make a noise that breaks down how your character's been established up until now!
Oh well.
Black
Just like this, I can move it at will.
But there's times when I can't.
No, times when it moves against my will.
Against your will?
No, by will I mean-
It's hard to explain, but...  I'm the one who assaulted you last night.
But I don't really have any memory of it.
It was as if I was hallucinating, or dreaming.
It's not like I don't remember at all, but...
A trance.  That's a trance.
The kind of oddity that possesses humans violates both the body and mind.
You know a lot.
I see.  These kinds of things are called oddities.
Well, I don't particularly know that much.
I've just had a lot of experience with them recently for some reason.
And there's someone I know who does know.
I see.  I'm glad you're such a great person.
If you had run away when I showed you this arm, we wouldn't have been able to talk.
And I think I would've been pretty hurt.
Putting it that way, I was a little bit surprised.
But since you showed me that first, I'm confident I won't be shocked no matter what follows.
I see!  Yeah, that's why I showed you this arm first.
Have to get the tough things out of the way first.
Now let's get to the point.
I'm a lesbian.
You're a guy, so that may have been a bit blunt.
Um, lemme rephrase that.
I'm into yuri.
That's the same damn thing!
What? Why?
You and Senjougahara were called the "Valhalla Combo" in middle school, right?  Just as fellow students?
Or were you "that  girl" for her?
When she said yesterday that she'd never broken up with a guy,
could she possibly have meant that?
Wrong.
Senjougahara-senpai was my unrequited love.
To me, Senjougahara-senpai was my pure and perfect ideal upperclassman.
Reminiscence
I was happy just being by her side.
Memory
She was popular with everyone,
but you can draw a line between that and my feelings for her.
I have pride in that.
I would have been willing to die for her back then.
But she changed.
She changed completely.
I'd heard she contracted a severe illness when she entered high school.
And due to its length, she quit track.
But I didn't think she had changed that much.
I thought it was just a bad rumor.
But I was wrong.
It wasn't just a rumor.
Something even worse happened
inside Senjougahara-senpai's body.
When I realized that, I thought I had to do something.
I thought I had to save her.
Didn't I?
In middle school, even though we were in different grades and on different teams,
she was so kind to me.
Black
So this time, I thought I'd save her.
I thought I could do something about what Senjougahara-senpai had.
Even if I couldn't do that, I thought I could heal her heart just by being with her.
Heavy
I really thought so.
Memory
But I was rejected with no consideration.
"I don't think of you as a friend or even as an underclassman.  Not now, not then."
Red
She said that straight-up.
[Soliloquy]
So since then, I haven't gotten close to her.
After all, that's the only thing she wanted from me.
Of course, there was no way that I could forget about her.
But...
That's...
If forgetting her could help her even a little bit,
I'd accept it.
You...
But then a year passed.
Reminiscence
I learned about you.
I saw you two billing and cooing in a classroom one morning.
She had a happy smile she'd never
shown me even once in middle school.
Reminiscence
Don't you understand?
You did what I wanted to for so long,
but never could and gave up on,
as if it were the most natural thing in the world.
Kanbaru... No, that's-!
Love
[Complete change, silence]
At first, I was jealous.
I tried to reconsider.  But in the end, I was still jealous.
Why not me?
I figured that if I was a man, it'd have worked.  That it only didn't because I'm a woman.
Even if I couldn't be a friend or an
underclassman, that didn't rule out being a lover.
So...  So wouldn't it be okay if it was me?
Red
I have already become completely inhuman.
I became jealous of you and disappointed in her.
And I was dumbfounded.
So what about healing Senjougahara-senpai?
So what about backing off?
Do you really think she'll praise you if you do that?
You're such an idiot.  A hypocrite!
But...
Even still...
I just wanted her to be kind to me like the old days.
It doesn't matter if it's ego or
whatever, I just want to be by her side...
So...
So that's why I wished on this paw.
Girl
Left Hand
To be by Senjougahara-senpai's side...
Beast
Monkey
Gho  st  ory
Commercial Next
Is this a transformation?  Are you an alien?
That's a secret.
CENCOROLL
Director - Script - Key Animation
Uki Atsuya
Music
Opens 8.22
Ikeda Theatre Diamond (Tokyo)
Theatre Umeda (Osaka)
So he's named Oshino Meme?
Meme in katakana?
Yeah, but he's not as cute as his name implies.
Episode 7 Password: Yuri
If we don't hurry up, the sun's gonna set.
Your left arm gets bad at night, right?
Look at it the other way.  As long as the sun's up there's no problem.
We'll definitely be fine for at least a few more hours.
Red
Araragi-senpai, there's something I want to ask you.
What?
What about Senjougahara-senpai caught your eye?
You spent two years as just
classmates, not even really speaking.
Why are you asking that?
Well.  If you just want her for her body, maybe I can take her place.
I think I'm pretty cute.
She said so herself
I can grow my hair longer and look a bit more girlish, and improve my complexion.
And I've played sports since way back, so I've got a nice slim waist.
I'm seriously up for it.
If you want it, I'll be the uke to your seme anywhere, anytime.
Seme?  Uke?
Why do I have to want that?!
It swelled
Oh, I see.
Araragi-senpai, you're not into BL?  That's surprising.
I don't wanna talk BL with a girl from a younger class!
BL is an abbreviation for "boys' love".
I know!  That wasn't the misunderstanding!
I just realized that when I cleaned Kanbaru's room-
Reminiscence
You really didn't misunderstand?
Then just what are you so angry about?
Don't tell me you're an uke?
Shut up!  This conversation is over!
I'm afraid I'm going to say something intrusive, Araragi-senpai.
If you can't even enjoy talking dirty with a younger girl,
how are you going to survive once you get out into society?
That's exactly the kind of thing I don't want a younger girl trying to convince me of.
Say what you want.
If you cling onto that cheap fantasy of womanhood,
you'll be so insistent on purity that you can't even say hello.
There's no way around it.  Even girls like to talk dirty.
Gossip Topic
So let's get back to talking about
whether you prefer boxers or briefs.
We never talked about that to begin with.
Oh?  Then were we talking about whether I wear panties under my bike shorts?
[Far more magnificent]
You're not wearing any panties, Kanbaru-san?!
S-So underneath those bike shorts you've got peeking out from under your skirt is-
A maiden's
secret honey
Even if I wasn't, would it really be that surprising?
Bike shorts have always been a type of underwear.
[Meaning]
Underpants which fit the body sheerly
That makes it even worse!
Showing off your panties all the time is no way to go through life!
When you put it that way, you're right,
but for now, it's just a stylish gift from a sporty girl.
Wrong!  It's perverted exhibitionism!
Oh, that's right, now I remember.
We weren't talking about that.
We were talking about whether I could be a replacement for Senjougahara.
Red
Hold it, don't change the topic back to avoid getting to the truth of matters!
Give a definite answer as to whether you're wearing any or not!
Why don't we leave out that little vulgar bit of information?
It's trivial.
Koyomi
Dumbass!
It's not trivial!  It's the divide between my
underclassman being a sporty girl and an exhibitionist!
My
[Sporty Girl]
Koyomi
[It's the divide!]
I suppose so...
Then why don't you think of it like this?
Kanbaru Suruga
Araragi Koyomi
[Sporty Girl]
I'm a sporty girl, and  an exhibitionist.
Koyomi
Black
Exhibitionist
[And also a]
A sporty girl to those who think of me as one,
[Sporty Girl]
Hurrr
Koyomi
[Sporty Girl]
Black
and an exhibitionist to those who think of me as one.
Exhibitionist
For those who think
Cogito, ergo sum
Stop with the wordplay!
[With words]
Koyomi
Saying "I'm xx to those who think of me as xx, and ** to those who think of me as **"
[I am **]
I am also xx
Black
Suruga
are **
Black
are xx
Kanbaru Suruga
Araragi Koyomi
[Only impressive]
is only impressive through middle school!
[through middle school!]
Koyomi
What are you, my little sister?!
Good grief
Koyomi
Araragi
Black
But seriously, Kanbaru.
No matter how hard you try, you can't take Senjougahara's place.
After all, you're not Senjougahara.
No one can become anyone else's replacement.
No one can become anyone else.
No matter how much you like her or look up to her.
That's right.  It's just as you say.
Black
Yeah.  Anyway, let's stop wasting time chatting and get going.
Oshino Shinobu
Black
H-Hey, Araragi-senpai.  Wasn't that kid so damn cute?
Red
Why are you saying that with the biggest grin you've had today on your face?
I want to embrace her.  No, I want to be embraced by her!
But it's best not to get drawn in by her.
Black
Emergency Exit
You're late, Araragi-kun.  I was about to fall asleep waiting for you.
What's up?  You brought a different girl today too.
Every time we meet, it's a different one.
I offer my sincere congratulations.
Shut up.  Don't just keep using that line.
Oh, that's right, I saw Shinobu on the stairs.
What's she doing there?
She's been sulking ever since I brought a box back from Mister Donut and ate one more donut than her.
She's been like that since yesterday.
What the hell kind of vampire is she?
Oshino, this is Kanbaru Suruga, from one grade below me.
Kanbaru's written with the "kami" from "god" and the "hara" from "fields".
God
Field
Even though it's normally "hara", it's "baru" here.
Suruga, umm...
It's the "suruga" from "bondage torture".
Bondage
Torture
Oh, bondage torture.  I get it.
Aaah
I'm Araragi-senpai's underclassman.  Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you, young lady.  I'm Oshino Meme.
If you're his underclassman, you're also Tsundere-chan's, right?
Anyway, Oshino.  First off, take this.
It's from "Tsundere-chan"-Senjougahara.
Akasegawa
Oh, money, money!
That's great! I was about to have to cut down my standard of living.
And what's up with the young lady?
That bandage, huh?
Oshino-san, I'm-
Wait your turn.  It doesn't seem that interesting.
Stories about how one's arm got bandaged are never interesting.
Especially to me.
Even worse, it's your left arm.
Red
Take off the bandage and let me take a look, young lady.
Gaze
Black
Is this enough?
Yeah, that's enough.
I see.  I figured.
Araragi-kun.  Young lady.
Let me set your initial mistaken impression straight.
The young lady's left arm isn't a monkey's paw.
I've never heard of a monkey's paw binding onto its owner.
Young lady, that hand once belonged to a mummy.
It binded onto you, sucked your life force, and now it's a rainy devil.
Rainy?
Yeah, a lesser devil.
Among them, the amount of devils with a
monkey's paw and a raincoat are certainly limited.
If it binds with its owner, it has to be a rainy devil.
It's not a monkey's paw, it's a devil's arm.
It can make anything come true.
But it takes your soul in exchange.
Her soul?
In exchange for your soul, it grants three wishes
In exchange for your soul, it grants three wishes.
Isn't that obvious?  Since it's a devil.
Ghostory
Monkey
Suruga Monkey Part 2
Continued
Next Episode
Deneb, Altair, and Vega
That's the Summer Triangle you pointed at
I remember that when I look up at the sky
I finally found Vega
But where are you, Altair?
You'll be alone like this
I looked up from the pitch dark world
It's like the night sky is filled with raining stars
I wonder when I started to chase after you
Please, no matter what
Don't be surprised
Listen to
These feelings
Of mine
Preview
I'm Karen!
I'm Tsukihi!
Preview quiz!
We're the Fire Sisters!
Power
Brains
Quiz!
Preview Izu!
A bit unsatisfied
Stupid?
Weakling?
Izu?
Izu is mysterious!
Trying it the other way around
yay
oomph
Izu is mysterious?
Next time!  Suruga Monkey Part 3!
Next Time
Suruga Monkey Part 3
It didn't turn out very good
Izu is quiz!
It's puzzling!