[GLUTTONY SCREAMING]
Will you stop killing me?!
I don't want to die anymore!
[GLUTTONY SCREAMS]
That hurt!
[LING GRUNTS]
[GLUTTONY SCREAMING]
[LAN FAN]
My Lord!
We can catch up later...!
Let's finish him off!
[LAN FAN]
Right!
Why won't you just
let me eat you already?!
[GLUTTONY SCREAMING]
[GREED LAUGHING]
[GREED]
You're really kicking ass!
And that's some
woman you've got.
I didn't know you
were such a stud...
Where've you been
hiding her all this time?
Well, y'know...
I'm full of surprises.
[GLUTTONY SCREAMS]
[GLUTTONY]
I don't get it!
It's so dark here!
So how...?! How do
you know where I am...?!
You can't see me!
[GLUTTONY SCREAMS]
[GLUTTONY WHEEZING]
[GLUTTONY GRUNTING WORRIEDLY]
[GLUTTONY SCREAMS]
[FU]
The ruler of Shing
controls the chi
known as the Dragon's Pulse...
This knowledge allows him to
govern the flow of our kingdom.
As the personal
servants of our ruler...
We too are trained to
read the flow of chi.
Not only that...
We're also trained to
act in the darkness.
I recognize
that voice.
Long time no see...
Huh, kid...
I still can't see you,
Fu... But wait...
How were you
able to find us?
[FU]
We've been hiding
out in Central
trying to keep an eye on
things for a while now...
We detected several large
chi converging out here...
So we
followed them...
[LOUD BANG SOUND]
There are two enormous forms
of chi battling nearby.
That must be Greed and
Gluttony you're sensing.
Greed, huh...
The one who
swallowed the Young Lord.
[FU GRUNTS]
And then... There's another
large chi within the forest.
[DARIUS]
Our companion
is fighting
a Homunculus called
Pride out there.
There's one more in
the settlement nearby...
And there's something
disquieting about that one...
It seems to dwarf the
others in comparison.
That's probably
Ed's father.
[ED]
You think so?
Are you saying that
your father isn't human?
Trust me, he's the least of
our concerns right now...
We've gotta figure out how to
deal with these Homunculi.
You don't have to
worry about Gluttony.
Lan Fan's
dealing with him.
Lan Fan is
fighting Gluttony?
Hold on...! It hasn't even
been a full seven months
since her automail
was attached!
[ED SIGHS FRUSTRATEDLY]
That's crazy, old man...!
She's not gonna
last without help!
[GLUTTONY SCREAMS]
[LARGE EXPLOSION]
[ED YELLS]
[FU]
I said not to worry...
We have resources besides
hand to hand combat.
Give us some
warning next time!
[ED YELLS]
[MAN 2]
What's going on?
[MAN 1]
Something exploded!
[MAN 3]
Was that in the forest?
[MAN 4]
Why aren't the lights back on?!
[MAN 5]
Hey...! Get a lamp!
[ED COUGHING]
Damn.
Alright...
That eases my mind a little.
Tell me something...
What all do you have
besides explosives?
[FU]
Hm...? All
sorts of things...
Tear gas bombs...
Flash bombs, flares.
Hmm...
The lights are
starting to come back on.
Which means Pride can
use the shadows again.
We need to get over
there and help Heinkel!
Yeah.
Can you help me...?
I need you to detect Pride's
chi and lead me to him.
Hmm...?
I could really use
your help, old man.
I'll do what I can.
[DARIUS]
Ed.
[ED GASPS]
Watch yourself, kid.
Don't forget what
Pride is... Alright?
[HEINKEL BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HEINKEL YELLS]
The hell do I have to do
to make you stay dead?
[DOG BARKING]
[MADAM CHRISTMAS]
I'm afraid your hunch
was right on the money.
He may look like
a cute little brat,
but Selim Bradley's not human.
[ROY]
How old are these photos?
Twenty years... This one
is over fifty years old...
And he's with a government
official in every one of these.
[MADAM CHRISTMAS
DEEPLY EXHALES]
[MADAM CHRISTMAS]
I decided to check into
the Fuhrer's supposed
hometown as well.
They've got
plenty of records
showing that he was
born and raised there...
But I couldn't find
a single resident
who's even seen
the Bradley family.
Their mansion is
just a hollow faade...
And of course there
aren't any relatives.
I appreciate this,
Madam Christmas...
It couldn't've been
easy to get this intel.
Yeah... Although...
As soon as I found out Selim
Bradley wasn't human...
well my exhaustion didn't
seem to matter anymore...
I've gotta wonder...
How hasn't any of this
gotten out before?
Because he has
a father named "King"...
who happens to be the most
powerful man in the country.
They can hide anything
they want... Fabricate anything.
[HEINKEL BREATHING HEAVILY]
You little bastard!
[MAN 6]
Hey!
Who is that...?
Is someone out there?
[HEINKEL GROWLS]
A monster!
[MAN 6]
Oh, no...!
It's got a kid!
[HEINKEL GROWLS]
[HEINKEL GASPS]
[HEINKEL SCREAMS]
[LANTERN CLANGS]
There's two monsters!
Damn it...
[HEINKEL GASPS]
[PRIDE]
I'm glad they shed
some light for us...
Now let's shed
some of your blood.
Goodbye... Chimera.
[HEINKEL GRUNTS]
[ED]
Just in the nick
of time, pops.
[HEINKEL GASPS]
Who would've thought...
A little kid like this
could be a Homunculus...?
I admit you fooled me...
...Selim Bradley.
Appearances rarely
show the whole truth...
Isn't that right
little alchemist?
[ED GRUNTS ANGRILY]
Now where were we?
[DOG BARKING]
[UNDERCOVER SOLDIER 2]
Hmm...?
[UNDERCOVER SOLDIER 3
BREATHING HEAVILY]
[UNDERCOVER SOLDIER 3]
Where is he...?
Where's Mustang?
[UNDERCOVER SOLDIER 1]
He's still in the bar.
He doesn't usually spend
this much time in there.
The woman who owns
the bar, Madam Christmas...
Her real name
is Chris Mustang...
She's his foster mother.
[UNDERCOVER SOLDIERS GASP]
Damn...
[LARGE EXPLOSION]
[RUMBLING]
[MADAM CHRISTMAS]
There it goes...
My poor little chateau.
I'm sorry it had
to be this way...
But I'll buy
you a new one.
[SPLASHING]
Well, you've got
some time to do it...
It's probably best if
I lay low for a while.
And what about all of
the girls that work for you?
Of course you're
worried about them.
Well don't concern
yourself too much...
They're off sunbathing
in an exotic locale...
...and I doubt
they're thinking of you.
[ROY LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
Now get focused.
There's too much at stake...
You need to be thinking
about saving this country.
[MADAM CHRISTMAS
LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
And the next
time I see you...?
You better not be
inside a body bag
and marked as a dissident...
I won't be happy with you.
Thanks for
everything, Madam...
I promise that
I'll repay you.
[MADAM CHRISTMAS]
Oh, so you'll remember me
when you've made it big...?
Well... I guess I'll have
something to look
forward to then, won't I?
[ROY LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
I really wish she'd
stop treating me like a
kid one of these days.
Alright then...
Guess I better get moving.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[RAT SCREECHES]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
About time, Colonel...
Didn't think you
were gonna show.
Keep up with the
smartass comments...
I'll take them as a
sign of confidence.
You made sure that
you weren't followed?
Yes... And if
we had been...
This little guy
would've alerted us.
[DOG BARKS]
Good boy.
You keep your
nose peeled, okay?
What're the
Bradleys' status?
I've got the entire
family's itinerary
for the next three days.
The Fuhrer went to observe
the training in the east...
Selim joined him
for the trip as well.
Then you haven't
heard the news...
The Fuhrer's train
was destroyed...
...with the Fuhrer
riding in it.
[BREDA AND HAWKEYE GASP]
Well I'll
be damned...
Old Man Grumman doesn't like
to take any chances, does he?
That means that security is
gonna be elevated now...
This could be
even more difficult
than we thought
that it would be.
How much is this
going to affect our mission?
Is the Eastern battalion
still going to invade
Central as planned?
[ROY SIGHS FRUSTRATEDLY]
All we know is that
the Fuhrer is missing...
This is either a
once-in-a-lifetime chance...
...or we're
walking into a trap.
It doesn't really
make a difference.
We've gotta see
this thing through.
Your orders, sir?
Whatever action
we may take,
we're heading straight
for the battlefield.
And no matter the outcome...
There's no turning back.
Even if we win,
this mission still won't
be close to completion.
Not until we
rebuild this nation...
With me as the Fuhrer...
We'll still have the task
of setting things right.
In other words...
I'm only giving you a
single order to obey...
Don't die...
Understood?
Sir!
[ED GRUNTING]
[PRIDE THINKING]
What is this...?
Why can't I cut him?
[ED YELLS]
[ED BREATHING HEAVILY]
Looks like I made
the right decision
by keeping my northern
automail after all...
This carbon fiber base has
turned out to be pretty handy!
[PRIDE THINKING]
A carbon base?!
So, he's taking
a cue from Greed?
Back to plan A then.
[ED]
What's the matter?
You're not
giving up, are you?
[ED LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
[PRIDE LAUGHS]
You brought
this on yourself.
[ED]
Al!
I figured this might
give me the advantage...
Unless you want to
destroy your brother.
[ED LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
Now, old man!
[PRIDE GASPS]
[EXPLOSION]
A flash bomb!
No!
No more... No more...!
What's that?
[LAN FAN WINCES IN PAIN]
[LING]
Lan Fan...?
What's wrong?
Lan Fan!
Mr. Gorilla!
I'm on it!
Al!
He's not conscious...
You've gotta get him
out of here. Now!
[DARIUS]
And you're positive
he's not still possessed?
Yeah...
I've noticed that if you
sever a part of their body...
It disintegrates
into dust.
[ED]
The flash bomb severed the
shadows holding Al's body...
So he's free
from Pride's grasp.
[PRIDE]
You're not getting away!
[ED]
Have another!
Did'ya see that
bright light, Pride...? Huh?
[EXPLOSION]
[PRIDE WINCING IN PAIN]
[GLUTTONY]
My eyes...!
You're pushing your luck.
[GLUTTONY WHIMPERING]
[PRIDE]
They've really
roughed you up.
Yeah, but only 'cuz Greed and
that girl weren't fighting fair.
They were both
doing something
so that they could
see me in the dark.
Is that so?
[PRIDE THINKING]
She must be the
warrior from Xing...
The one Wrath had
an encounter with...
She can sense our presence.
And Greed must've
turned his body over
to the Xingese prince
in order to do the same.
How pathetic.
[PRIDE GASPS]
[PRIDE]
Gluttony...
How many times have
they killed you now?
I lost count... but
I know it was a lot, though.
They've beaten me up
pretty badly as well.
The way things
are going...
There's a very real chance
they might annihilate us.
Yeah... But that's okay
'cuz Father'll fix us.
No... Please don't
do it, Pride!
[GLUTTONY YELLS]
[PRIDE LAUGHS]
[ED GASPS]
[LING GASPS]
No, Pride...!
Don't eat me!
It hurts...!
Please help me...!
Luuusst!
He devoured him...
One of his own kind!
[PRIDE]
Ahhhh.
This should make
things much easier...
I can practically smell
every movement you make.
I could do without
the ravenous hunger,
but I suppose that I'll
just have to sate it.
Oh wait...
[PRIDE SNIFFS]
I recognize that scent.
You're somewhere
close by, aren't you?
Hohenheim...
[GARDNER]
From what we've uncovered...
Mustang's gathered
his subordinates
and is sneaking around.
Mustang's got to have something
to do with the Fuhrer's train.
Hell, he's probably the one
behind the Ishvalans
pouring into the city...
I doubt that
it's a coincidence.
It does seem like
it's all perfectly timed.
[FATHER]
Then where do we find him?
You're all more experienced
with the way this Mustang
character operates than I am...
What would you predict to
be his next plan of action?
[HARRIS]
Hmm...
[OLIVIER]
If I were in his place...
Well... I would most likely take
the Fuhrer's wife as a hostage.
Why bother
doing such a thing?
He must know that's futile.
So he's going to take
a pointless hostage
and make sure that he's
branded as a traitor...?
Even further
proof that humans
are relentlessly
ridiculous creatures.
[CAR ACCELERATING]
Huh...? Ahh...!
[BODYGUARD 1]
Hey!
Move your vehicle!
What? Roy Mustang?
[BODYGUARD 2 YELLS]
[BODYGUARD 2 GASPS]
[BRADLEY'S WIFE GASPS]
Sorry to harass you at such
a late hour... My apologies.
What's going on,
Lieutenant...?!
Why would you do
something like this?
[BRADLEY'S WIFE GASPS]
Please forgive us for
startling you like this...
I need you to come
with me, Madam Fuhrer...
We have no intention
of harming you.
[BRADLEY'S WIFE GASPS]
Please... It's important.
[NARRATOR]
Memories separate
the unwanted and lost times
within the human mind...
But when an inhuman being
is seized with
recollections of the past,
they're confronted with the
terror of what they're becoming.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood,
Episode 49,
"Filial Affection".
With their reasons known
only to themselves...
...they now face the daybreak.