Irisviel...
Utw
Presents
Will one last miracle come to pass?
あと一度だけ奇跡は起こるだろう
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
優しい声で描く歪んだ未来
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
もう誰も泣かない世界の為に
Mou dare mo nakanai sekai no tame ni
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
紅く汚された空の何処にも
Akaku kegasareta sora no doko ni mo
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
届かず消える叫びと祈り
Todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
慰めは捨てて行ける
Nagusame wa sutete yukeru
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
綺麗な月の光が始まりへと沈み行く
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga hajimari e to shizumiyuku
Into the distance
その彼方へ
Sono kanata e
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
閉ざされてく瞳でまだ遠くへ手を伸ばす
Tozasareteku hitomi de mada tooku e te wo nobasu
I believe in your sorrow
君の嘆きを 信じて
Kimi no nageki wo shinjite
I've lost sight of them.
If I can't see them, I'll sense them.
A chariot?
I've got you, Rider!
Rider, look.
She's following us, isn't she?
Well, if it isn't Saber.
Saves us the trouble of looking for her.
Wait.
Hey, boy, are motorcycles usually that fast?
That's a motorcycle?
No, that's impossible.
But with Saber's Riding skill...
I suppose it's possible.
Interesting.
In that case, I'll have to play along with her.
We're going down?!
Change of plans.
I shall use a race to settle things with the girl.
Fine, but take it seriously, okay?
Don't worry.
Nothing in Heaven or on Earth can stop me!
This is bad...
I'm reaching the machine's limits.
At this rate...
I'm so close, too.
Invisible Air!
No way...
She's closing the gap!
She's going to catch up to us!
How impressive for a mechanical contraption to go that fast.
However, this is a chariot!
I'm not going to simply play by the rules.
This is what it means to eat my dust, Saber!
Excellent!
You really are the renowned King of Knights!
Truly the flower of the battlefield!
Don't underestimate me, King of Conquerors!
Rider!
Prepare yourself!
Irisviel isn't here?
No...
That was definitely Rider.
Then where could Irisviel be?
You thought you could fool me with your Servant masquerade?
Rider's Master isn't capable of gathering the necessary intel to find that place.
Tohsaka is in no position to attack.
By process of elimination, only the Matous could have kidnapped Irisviel.
Answer me.
Where is Irisviel?
N-No idea!
I have no idea!
Where is Matou Kariya, then?
Kariya?
Who knows where that fool is...
I don't know!
I really don't know anything!
He left this morning with some guy
who said he was a judge from the Church!
A judge?
Kotomine Kirei...
I did not expect the real Rider to appear.
How very convenient for us.
Luck certainly favors you on the battlefield, doesn't it?
Matou Kariya.
Priest, was this little deception really
worth the use of two Command Spells?
Do not worry, Kariya.
Hold out your hand.
As long as you work with me, you may use
your Command Spells to your heart's desire.
Still...
That transformation ability...
It's a shame he's of the Berserker class
with such an excellent Noble Phantasm.
He's a Heroic Spirit with many stories telling of the
deeds he accomplished under someone else's name.
So this is the best result even with the Command Spell's control?
Your Servant's obsession with Saber is incredible.
That's enough.
Disappear, Berserker.
This woman...
Is she really the Grail vessel?
Her contents are, to be precise.
Don't worry, Kariya.
I'll let you have the Grail.
But before that, there's the other promise you made to me, priest.
Oh, that?
Everything is arranged.
Come to the church tonight, at midnight.
You will find Tohsaka Tokiomi there.
Don't forget, Kariya.
Tonight, at midnight.
Your wish will be fulfilled then.
Now...
We're alone.
I don't know who you are, but show yourself.
So, you sensed me.
You are indeed a veteran Executor.
Matou Zouken?
Correct.
Hey, Rider...
Are we really going to attack from here?
From this range?
Straight ahead?
There's a delay before she can activate the sword of light we saw at the river.
We'll strike then.
Why resort to something so crazy?
Because it's crazy.
If she loses even after all this, her defeat will be absolute, without a doubt.
She might even decide to join my troops.
You'd go that far?
On the battlefield, she is certainly a star.
But it is only after she has joined
my army that she can truly shine.
He was never interested in his opponent's power or wealth.
Without destroying or degrading them, he sought to conquer their souls.
That's why he is the King of Conquerors.
Very well, Rider.
Win it your way.
Boy, it seems you're finally beginning to understand conquest.
Glory lies beyond the horizon!
Let us go...
Via Expugnatio!
Wind!
Excalibur!
What do you want, Matou Zouken?
Well...
I was awfully interested in seeing what clever trick you'd use to break Kariya.
You'd let the Matous' chance of victory disappear?
Watching Kariya suffer in anguish...
...is something I'll never tire of.
Victory for the Matous, or a miserable end for him?
I can't choose.
You enjoy watching your own kin suffer like that?
And I was thinking you'd understand.
What?
You have the same smell as I do.
That of a crawling maggot, attracted by the aroma of Kariya's rotting meat.
Oh, scary, scary.
Green or not, you are a dog of the Church.
Simply teasing you endangers me.
We'll meet again, young one.
By then, see that your true nature
has ripened enough to rival my own.
Rider...
Sorry, boy.
I have failed.
Rider!
Use Ionian Hetairoi!
The chariot is all I'm willing to expend on Saber.
But still...
She's gone.
A motorcycle, huh?
A magnificent vehicle.
Hey!
Those are your first words after losing?
Hey, Rider.
How do we get back to town?
Well...
We'll have to walk.
I guess you're right.
How many more days do I have?
How many more times can I fight?
But I'm not done yet.
I'm not...
Tohsaka Tokiomi!
So you think you've killed me, Tokiomi?!
In your dreams.
Until I've made you pay,
I'll keep coming back...
Tohsaka...
What?
Kariya-kun?
Aoi-san?
No! It wasn't me!
This was...
Are you satisfied, Kariya-kun?
Now the Matous are sure to win the Holy Grail.
I...
Why?
Was taking Sakura from me not enough?
Of all the things you could've done, you killed him in front of me?
Why?
He...!
It's his fault!
If it weren't for him, no one would need to suffer!
You... and Sakura-chan...
All of you could've been happy!
Shut the hell up!
You don't understand a thing about any of this!
You've never even...
...loved anyone!
There was someone I loved.
She was warm and kind...
I wanted her to be happier than anyone else.
I would throw away my life for you.
That's why I've endured this pain until now.
Endured...
Endured, endured, endured, endured, endured, endured, endured...
Endured it all!
I'll never forgive you if you deny all that!
A lie, a lie, a lie!
I do have someone I love...
I definitely have someone I love!
What did I do this for?
Whose fault is it?!
If I'm going to die, then I might as well...!
That was a terrible piece of cheap drama,
but not so bad for your first playwriting attempt.
Well, Kirei?
What are your thoughts?
The taste of this wine...
It's different from what I remember.
I see you've begun to understand what
it means to expand your horizons, then.
If it means the wine will taste this wonderful...
...I would dearly love to sample it again.
Episode 21
Knight on Two Wheels
Doushite sora wa konnani aokute
どうして空はこんなに青くて
Why is the sky so blue?
Nanimo kanashimi wo shiranu you ni
何も悲しみを知らぬように
As if oblivious to sadness
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita e to kuzureochiru
いつも躊躇わず明日へと崩れ落ちる
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuru no ne
命は足りないまま生まれてくるのね
I suppose we are born with our lives short
Kakeochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
かけおちた心にあなたが触れて
You have touched my torn heart
Futari de yuku mirai wa kegare no nai tsuyosa de
二人で行く未来は穢れのない強さで
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
空は高く 風は歌う
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Yume wo miteta yorokobi e to
夢を見てた喜びへと
Men will one day come to realize
Hito wa itsuka tadoritsukeru
人はいつか辿り着ける
The joy of chasing after a dream
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
子供の瞳であなたは信じた
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
Soba ni iru yo
そばにいるよ
I'll be right beside you
Kooritsuita mori wo nukete
凍りついた森を抜けて
As we pass through the frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni mayowanu you ni
その瞳が世界の嘆きに迷わぬように
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
By my Command Spell, I order you.
Open your eyes and watch to the end!
I won't be holding back tonight.
I'll just quickly eliminate him.
How do he and I differ?
If he isn't lost, then what is he?!
If I'm in here, who am I?
Next Episode
All the World's Evil