3rd Street
“The Cat Boy”
Eyes.
To be stunned.
To don a serious visage.
To be partial to someone.
To keep an eye on something.
Our eyes are organs capable of
passively receiving visual information.
At times, they are also organs that actively convey unspoken intent, emotions, and inner thoughts.
Eyes can say just as much as one's mouth.
This is a fitting and accurate way to describe them.
That man... he's been here before, no?
Yeah. He's our homeroom teacher.
I wonder why he stopped by.
Hotori probably caused trouble again.
Mr. Moriaki, can I ask you something?
What is it, Arashiyama?
You came all this way to see me after school...
Did you fall for me?
Come again?
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
(From Vol.1, Chapter 4)
“Eyes”
Huh? What!?
It's not adding up!?
No pulse! Heartbeat, breathing, blood pressure... all zero!
Oh, you're a bachelor, Mr. Moriaki?
And you're so handsome! What a shame!
He has to make his own lunch. He must be lonely...
It ends up in my stomach either way.
Take off! Quit flirting with him!
You don't own the customer, ya know.
Arashiyama.
I saw him first!
You didn't even have a pulse!
So, whaddaya want with me anyway?
If it's extracurricular classes, count me out.
I came across something strange
when dividing my grandfather's estate.
He just ignored my flirting?
This is it.
A portrait?
It's a portrait, right?
Looks like an ordinary portrait to me.
What's so strange about it?
Hmm, this is a pretty odd painting.
What?
We all just said it was normal, so why would you say it's odd?
You're just trying to steer the
conversation back to you! You uppity little—
That's not it! Okay fine, maybe a little, but still...
I knew it!
Look at it. The canvas is a perfect square!
Portraits are usually taller or wider, right?
She's got a point.
Now that you mention it...
I see. This portrait does have a 1:1 ratio. In other words, a perfect square.
Well done, Arashiyama.
I brought this here because I knew you had an eye for the extraordinary.
You're a very special person to me.
O-Oh gosh... but I'm still in high school!
Again with the selective hearing...
These were done by my grandfather.
The last of 3 children, he was an unsuccessful painter.
He was also a gambler. He didn't leave much behind, but he did amass quite a few paintings during his lifetime.
After his death, they were split between myself and his two siblings.
But the real issue lies with the other portrait!
What the heck is that?
He's got four eyes!
It's creeping me out!
According to the labels on the back, I believe these are self portraits.
And the titles for both portraits are the same:
“Eyes”.
“Eyes”?
Why would my grandfather paint something so bizarre?
Ever since I laid eyes upon it, it's bugged me to no end.
My heart is tormented with confusion!
As you know, I am a math teacher.
My job is to view things in a linear and logical fashion.
What went through his head as he drew this?
Ha! Nonsense!
I'm not him, so how could I possibly figure it out!?
Ahahahahaha!
Ahh, he's snapped!
But with the right perspective, it should be possible to produce a hypothesis.
Arashiyama, you like detective novels, right?
Yup! Love 'em!
That's why I want you to solve the mystery of this painting.
Who, me?
You're to present me with an acceptable answer.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Moo.
Sheesh. What a troubled man.
On the other hand, it may be because of his
difficult personality that ladies don't flock to him.
Better bag him while you've got the chance, Hotori!
Enough about him. You guys are disturbing my thinking!
You still haven't got it?
I've already figured it out.
What!?
I solved the riddle too.
You too, Granny!?
Care to hear my reasoning?
Do you know who painted this portrait?
Yeah, that's—
Post-impressionist painter Vincent van Gogh.
It's said that he painted using such unique colors and
styles because that's how the world appeared to him.
Likewise, it follows that this man also painted reality as he saw it.
Huh?
Ergo, Mr. Moriaki's grandfather had astigmatism!
Ohh, that's some nice detective work there.
But how come he only drew one nose and mouth on each portrait?
Head Maid, I'm gonna beat her!
The other one's perfectly normal anyway.
It doesn't make sense that there are a different amount of eyes each time!
You're too naïve, Hotori.
In that case, think of it this way.
Mr. Moriaki's grandfather left behind many paintings.
And the fact that Mr. Moriaki found it odd
means that there were others that he didn't find weird.
Like landscapes, still-lifes, and so on.
Out of all those ordinary paintings, only that one was strange.
Yeah, I guess so.
He was a man who only drew ordinary pictures.
If you think of it like that...
Instead of thinking this portrait is unique,
realize that it was also drawn just as he saw it, and it all comes together!
What?
Ergo, Mr. Moriaki's grandfather was a four-eyed alien!
When he drew this, the eyes on top were closed!
Wow, discovery of the century!
You nasty little brat!
Head Maid, can I hit her?
Wait! If you think of it as more than just a painting...
That's it!
What is?
Are you okay?
Did your brain overheat or something?
A detective always laughs like that when they solve the mystery, duh!
Huh?
Now then, let's hear your answer.
Pay attention, sir.
I've got six playing cards here.
How would I divide these between three people?
Are you mocking me?
You give two to each person, obviously!
Exactly.
Okay then, how would you split this castella between three people?
Cut it into thirds, naturally.
Bingo!
Oh crap, there's none for me!
What are you getting at!?
Those were hints.
I hate how detective novels beat around the bush!
Quit giving me hints and just get to the point!
That was the last of them.
If you connect the dots, you can solve the mystery.
Just think about it, sir.
Don't tell me you don't get it?
Well?
Why don't you understand!? It's
simple if you just use the formula!
How does this not make sense!?
So this is what it feels like!
This feels so good!
This must be how Mr. Moriaki sees me!
Arashiyama.
Arashiyama!
You better hurry up and tell him, or he's gonna lose it.
How can Arashiyama understand something I can't?
Too much... this is too much...
Here, this is how I solved it!
W-What the?
This is the original form of the paintings!
It's a die.
I drew the missing parts.
The title “Eyes” refers to how he
thought of the dice as his own eyes.
Each painting made up one face on the die.
A fitting self-portrait for a gambler like your grandfather.
But when the complete cube was divided between three people,
the work lost its meaning.
What you ended up with was an odd pair of portraits!
And that's the truth behind them.
What say you, my client?
Oh my god, she actually looks smart for once!
It's a miracle!
Your body won't go soft no matter how much vinegar you drink.
Eyes can say just as much as one's mouth.
One's eyes will always speak the truth,
but this rests on whether or not people's eyes can perceive the true meaning of these words.
To Arashiyama
Upon discussing it with my relatives,
just like you said, we found the remaining 4 portraits.
The work now assembled like my grandfather had intended,
I give to you as a token of my thanks.
Hell no!
Don't taint this store more than you already have!
If we hang this here, it'll scare off the customers!
Hey, cut it out! This is a gift Mr. Moriaki gave to me!
Then hang it in your own room!
Nah, that'd be kinda weird.
Poco means “a little bit” in Italian.
“The Cat Boy”
(From Vol.1, Chapter 11)
Onions contain an allyl compound that causes hemoglobin in the blood to oxidize.
When consumed by animals other than humans, it induces hemolytic anemia, which can be deadly.
However, in humans it is said to improve health, though there is insufficient medical data to corroborate this.
When an onion is cut, allyl sulfide is released, evaporating into the air and stimulating the production of tears.
But if chilled beforehand, the release of allyl sulfide can be prevented, and therefore will not induce tears.
Such wisdom is part of the housewife's repertoire.
Aren't you gonna ask me why I'm crying?
It's onions.
Car-rots, on-ions. Now you try.
Car-rots, on-ions.
Car-rots, on-ions, ready, go!
I'm not a little kid! I can manage to go shopping by myself, you know.
You mean like last time?
You've got a history of forgetting. That's why we're doing this.
Oniorrot
See? Oniorrot.
If you forget on the way there, just remember that.
You're really making me mad!
There's a limit to how much you can mock someone!
Onions and carrots. Who could screw that up?
Huh?
It was “oniorrot”, so...
Yeah, round with a pointy part. That's right.
Hmm? Wait, was the round part supposed to mean potatoes?
Huh? Which one was it...
Pounding it into my head like that just makes me question myself more.
Pearl!
Pearl! Pearl!
Darn it.
Whoa. A pretty boy.
Eyes.
Crossed eyes.
Crying.
Optimism.
“When it rains, it pours.”
Eyes are the mirror that reflects our hearts.
Thus, through people's eyes can we convey
our emotions, and understand one another.
What're you lookin' at?
Your butt, stupid.
What?
Hmm, seeing as how his voice is cracking, he must be around 12 or 13.
Dying his hair blond at this age will end up turning it gray.
Hey, you. You're Hotori, right?
Huh?
I saw you plow into that cop on your scooter the other day.
“Hey you?” Shouldn't you be calling me “Miss Hotori” or “big sis”?
This here shopping district's pretty rough on kids who don't pay their dues.
Oh yeah?
What are you doing, anyway?
You're acting awfully suspicious. You praying or something?
See for yourself.
It's a cat!
“Cat's eyes.”
A phrase used to describe someone of fickle character.
It refers to a cat's pupils widening and narrowing at a moment's notice.
Most people would argue that this phrase was actually inspired by a cat's ever-fickle dispositions.
Also, because many cat owners are charmed by their cats' personalities,
“cat's eyes” can also refer to someone who is devilishly charming.
My cat won't come out from there.
Oh, that was her name?
Yup.
Why would you name your cat Pearl?
Oh! Like “casting pearls before swine”, right?
You're pretty clever!
Thanks.
I know. Here, use this oniorrot.
You mean onion?
You want some?
Why would I want an onion?
Not for you, for the cat!
I'm saying we could use this to lure her out.
And I'm saying cats don't like onions.
Besides, it's bad for them.
Oh, yeah. Doesn't it spook them or something?
You're thinking of squids.
Squid pro quo...
Squid pro quo.
Go home already! It's freezing out here!
It's even snowing, dammit!
I'm sorry! I don't know what
possessed me to say something so stupid!
Pearl! I won't let her tell any more dumb jokes, so come out already!
This is my  fault!?
Cat's don't like the cold.
Pearl!
Relax. She'll come out eventually.
Cats are just fickle like that, right?
My Pearl's a good girl, though.
Yeah, that's what every owner says.
It'd be a bad if I left her here and she got sick.
Hey, you're a nicer person than you look.
W-What is it?
What the hell are you doing, dumbass!?
Y-You hit me!
'Cause you were trying to strangle me!
What the hell!?
Well, I was thinking if her owner's in trouble, she'd come save you.
What is she, Lassie?
I have a dog too, you know.
And I'm sure it'd come save me from danger.
Pretty sure, anyway.
I told  you — listen. Does that look like a dog to you?
Sheesh. Guess we have to get serious and think of a plan.
Whatever, just take off, all right?
She came out!
See? I told you onions were the way to go!
Grab her, Hotori!
Right! Leave it all to big sis!
Gotcha!
I call it “The Maid's Cage”!
That sounds like the name of a porno!
Nasty little brat.
Meow!
Jeez, you had me worried sick!
Yay, good for you, Pearl!
Good for y—
No way! Did I step on her?
Do you see a tail-looking thing lying around?
Are you by chance looking for her tail?
Uh, it wasn't my fault!
Okay, maybe it was, but it was an accident!
It wasn't on purpose!
This little angel never had one to begin with.
Huh?
Cymric are a breed of cats that don't have tails.
Long ago, when her ancestors boarded Noah's ark,
the door closed on its tail and tore it off, or so the story goes.
Thank god, I thought PETA was gonna have my head!
Kinda cute don't you think?
But doesn't that story seem weird?
Pearl and her ancestors are different cats.
The dad's injury wouldn't be passed onto his kids, would it?
Who cares? It's just a legend.
'Kay then. Thanks anyhow!
Don't mention it!
Thanks anyhow, huh?
What a snotty little brat.
Oh yeah, what's your name, anyway?
Huh?
Meh, cat boy works, I guess.
We should have taught her the “don't stop and smell the roses” song too.
That, or at least drawn her a map.
Hotori!
Oh, you're the cat bo—
...girl?
Sorry! I thought you were a younger boy.
I did think your voice was kinda odd.
So you go here too, huh?
I knew the whole time, though.
What class are you in?
Class A.
You don't say...
Hang on, I'm in class A too!
Was she always in my class? No, she wasn't!
I at least remember all of my classmates' names!
Crap! I figured I'd run into a ghost one day, but this is...
Speaking of which, she did suddenly disappear yesterday.
I bet if I look up now, poof ! She'll be gone, or something!
She followed me all the way to school, which means I'm already doomed!
Mornin', Miss Kou!
Miss?
Hey, Haribara. We're holding a
tournament today during club time.
This new rubber paddle will be the
reaper's scythe that claims your head!
You can talk trash after  you beat me.
Oh my, I wasn't aware you were my senior, madam.
You just look so young, that's all...
I'm terribly sorry if I offended you.
There, there. Don't sweat it, “big sis”!
Could we just drop that already?
Hip-hop isn't just rap.
“Maid.”
In modern Japan, the word refers to girls who labor dressed in the cloth of the English housekeeper.
Maid cafés, maid bars, maid massages, maid mahjong parlors,
all the way back to the original duty of cleaning.
Their momentum has carried them
through to today, with no signs of stopping.
And now, here we have two girls battling it out with their maid spirit on the line!
Why are you doing this?
You wanna know? It's because of the maid's—
Underworld (meido)
Write the term used to describe
traditional British hired houskeepers.
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living for rock!
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
Living lonely, blasting my music.
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Kyou mo Kare ni wa Nasake Kokurezu
and I still have yet to tell him how I feel.
Toppuu ni Inochi wo Sasage Ashikoshi wo
Putting our lives in the hands of a tornado,
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
we train our legs by playing drums.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We're the Maids, yeah!
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Chiisai no wa Zessan Eigyou Chuu
The little one's working inside, making a profit!
Thank you very maid for coming!
And the Town Still Turns
Next Episode
There's a curse that's been haunting people, one after the other.
Woah, that's scary!
The curse moves to a different person every minute.
That's an awfully lenient curse.
Once the first victim is cursed, the
whole school follows in 10 minutes.
Now, what if you started with two victims?
How fast would the whole school fall under the curse?
Twice as many people, so... five minutes?
Wrong!
Next Time, 4th Street: “The cursed equation”
Café Seaside
4th Street“The Cursed Equation”
The world turned yesterday, too.