All done.
Do I look cute?
Yeah, totally.
Does looking at my nape excite you?
Wh-What should I do?!
That aside, what should we do next?
More love research, obviously.
Research?
What does she mean by "love research"?
What is the president talking about?
Yeah, totally.
You're spinning too fast for me to see, though.
This can't be!
This can't be the president I know!
This can't be the president everyone admires!
I feel sick.
Are you stupid?!
If your admirers could see you now, they'd cry.
If that happened...
I'd cry first.
I-I'm so sorry!
H-Hey!
Was that the first-year secretary?
That was a fairy.
A fairy, yeah...
Oh no! What have I done?
What should I do?!
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
The Cool, the Shy, and the Voyeur?
Hey, come on.
It's already been two days. I think you'll be all right.
No!
I'm done for!
I am so done for!
Come on,
let's get some hugging practice done with your beloved Huggy!
B-But you're always...
Oh, hell!
You'll be fine, I tell ya!
She didn't even laugh at you.
I'd much prefer being laughed at.
Seeing her run away like that was
much worse than being laughed at!
She scorned me!
That nice girl completely scorned me!
The next day
Hey, Suzu.
Have you become friends with the president already?
I'm so jealous of you!
Kurahashi joined the student council too, right?
Suzu?
You've been acting weird lately.
Are you having trouble with Kurahashi or something?
A-Absolutely not!
Kurahashi's the Wild One I look up to!
My Wine, in short!
Wine?
Do you really look up to her?
Did something else happen, then?
Well...
I saw their secret and ran away
even though they tried to stop me.
I'm the worst.
They must be so angry at me.
Is Tanahashi Suzune here?
Wi—
What's with this bizarre chant?
W-W-W-Wine!
Suzu!
Wine?
Stupid me!
I ran away again!
My heart wanted to stay but my body wouldn't listen!
Tanahashi?
You're in there, right?
I-I'm so sorry!
I felt a big one coming all of a sudden!
R-Right...
Say...
Yes?
Why were you hiding in the student council's office?
H-Hiding?
That's not what I meant to do.
I didn't have the courage to stand face-to-face with you two.
That's why, the other day, I...
I tried to leave my paperwork there
while the two of you weren't around.
And that's when...
I wonder what we should research today!
That's how it went.
I see now.
So that's how you came to see everything.
I'm so sorry! I won't tell anyone! Please forgive me!
I don't think there's any need for apologies or forgiveness here,
but could you just try talking to Maki about this?
What?
She's really worried.
Worried that you've come to hate her.
N-No way! I wouldn't dream of it!
I'm the one who's worried...
So yeah, why don't you tell her that?
Later.
Do your best and let that big one drop.
After school
I hadn't considered how the president feels.
I should apologize to her.
E-Excuse me!
Oh, they're not here yet.
What now?
Maybe I could get some cleaning done while I wait.
Huggy!
Oh shit!
I didn't pay attention to where I put that away!
Huggy's cheating on me!
That's what you react to?
I-I'm so sorry!
Where are my glasses?
My glasses...
Glasses...
Ow!
They must've gotten fed up with me for sure!
I came here to apologize,
but there's no way I can do it now!
They must hate me!
President?
Tanahashi...
Please become my Master of Klutz!
What?
What the heck's a "Master of Klutz"?
Maki Natsuo, student council president.
Extremely popular among teachers and students alike.
Precise and quick worker.
Thanks for everything, ma'am
Extremely thoughtful.
The perfect girl!
But every six months,
she messes something up completely.
How does that sound?
In one ear and out the other.
Come on, Riko.
I'm talking about contrast here!
People who have it together sometimes make mistakes.
Did you forget?
You said I wouldn't get a guy if I
didn't screw up from time to time.
You still haven't given up on playing the klutz?
Like when you open your bag and a dove flies out, for example.
Are you a magician?!
Or when you try to gracefully make some tea,
only to end up with a bunch of flags in your hand!
Those are magic tricks!
Normally, you'd accidentally make green tea instead of black tea,
or put in salt instead of sugar.
That's just nonsensical.
I'd really like to know what you
consider "common sense" to be.
Doing it naturally is the right way of the screw up.
I don't think I can screw up naturally.
That thought process of yours is screwed up in its own right.
S-Sorry. You two were so funny, I couldn't help myself.
I apologize for my actions the other day.
Did I let you down?
I was really shocked at the time,
but now I think the contrast with how you usually act makes you cute.
Good for you.
See, Riko?
Contrast is the only true answer!
We should study the "attract by contrast" method!
Don't get too full of yourself.
Um, by research, do you mean love research?
Exactly!
Riko, a love expert, is instructing me on how to go about things.
H-Hey!
Expert?
Yeah!
She's apparently had loads of guys wrapped around her fingers!
Wow!
I can't even talk to boys due to how bad I am at dealing with them!
Yeah, lying is bad.
I should tell them the truth!
Um...
Is psychologically incapable
of letting people down
I always thought you two operated
on levels beyond our understanding.
But now I see that just like us,
you're interested in romance too!
This makes me kinda happy!
I'm also very happy to have friends who accept me even after I show them my true colors.
Friendship can only begin when you learn the truth about one another, right?
I must maintain my position,
so let's keep this a secret outside this room.
In return, let's never lie to each other in here.
Yeah!
My mom used to tell me that lying was the first step toward thievery.
You don't look well, Riko.
Nah, don't worry about it.
The next day
Kurahashi!
Oh, Tanahashi.
What do you think the president's going to research today?
Who knows?
I'm sure it'll be something stupid again.
Playing her straight man really wears me out, you know?
Well, actually...
You looked like you needed some help, so I made something for you.
Huh? What'd you make?
Here you go!
You're pretty merciless, huh?
Maki!
Oh no! President!
Hey, Maki!
Pull yourself together!
W-We should call an ambulance.
Carry me in your arms like I'm a princess, please.
Well? Care to explain yourself?
I wanted to practice being carried like a princess.
Every maiden longs to be in that situation!
We'll run across the plains, the mountains, and the 53 stations of the Toukaidou!
Is this Maki's Delivery Service?
Jeez, you always come up with the most ridiculous ideas.
It's so novel!
What?
Have you never dreamed of being carried like a princess?
They  have
When you're talking about the
most standard situation for that,
it's gotta be "when a girl's fainted," right?
That's what you were practicing, huh?
But I've never once fainted in my life.
How does it feel?
I don't think I have either.
Apparently, when you actually faint,
sometimes your eyes roll back and
you have a faint smile on your face.
Er... I wonder how you get carried.
Like this, maybe?
I hear you feel like dead-weight when you've actually fainted, which means you have to be carried like this.
And you start hearing shouts of "heave-ho!"
Let's stop talking about fainting!
Yeah! Fainting's gotta suck, right? It's rude to make light of it!
Then how about "she's sprained her ankle and can't move"?
Owwie!
I sprained my ankle!
That was quite abrupt.
Could someone be so kind as to carry me?
Quit being on standby!
I figured I'd be easier to carry that way!
You don't need to be that considerate!
Instead of being totally up for it,
you gotta act all embarrassed and turn them down once!
And when you're acting all stubborn, he'll pick you up by force,
and then say, "Wow, you're so light."
You're being awfully specific.
Crap!
I used to frequently daydream about that, so I blurted it out!
Oh, I see.
You're speaking from experience, aren't you?
Truly an expert.
I want to be told I'm light too!
Please teach me what I should do to have him find me cute while he's carrying me!
Whatever am I going to do with you guys?
I'm such an idiot!
How can I make myself seem lighter?
Like I know!
Put all your strength into your belly, and all of your spirit too!
That way, your body'll seem lighter!
Maybe.
Okay!
And how should I make myself seem cute?
I'd like to know that myself!
Uh...
F-First, you put your head down!
Okay!
A-And then...
Y-You look up from time to time,
and let your eyes do the talking!
"Eyes do the talking"?
Yeah, let your eyes do the talking!
He'll find you cute if you communicate with your eyes!
Maybe.
Okay!
Let's take it from the top.
Belly!
Eyes do the talking!
What's wrong?
Well, I kinda feel like I'm being watched lately.
Is it just my imagination?
Ohmigawsh, it's Kurahashi!
So wild!
It's the Wild One!
That's neither your imagination,
nor is it a recent development.
Look out!
Wow! Wi—
The heck is this?
Harassment?
Maybe. I'm not really sure.
You slim
girl!
I'm not really sure what this is.
I know, right?
I also found this mixed in with the
documents the teacher handed me.
Maki Natsuo's
way too damn slim!
Oh my! Another act of harassment?
There's a smile on your face, y'know.
Enomoto Yuiko, third-year.
She's decently cute,
sorta smart, and kinda capable.
Somewhat trusted by the people around her,
she's an adequate sorta person.
Hey! Could you lay off the half-assed praise?
Also, those guys don't look hurt at all!
You sure you saw it with your own eyes, Sayo?
I knew there was something wrong with this.
There's no way they'd want to be all macho.
But I heard what they were saying.
Belly!
Eyes do the talking!
Wh-What the?!
Those were the words I heard.
They were yelling them like they were working out.
And why would that lead to them trying to be macho?
Anyway, it's clear that they're up to no good.
We're going to gather evidence and expose them to the whole school.
That'll settle things once and for all.
That it's not Maki Natsuo who's fit to be president, but me, Enomoto Yuiko!
You sound like a villain when you laugh.
Huh? There's something written on the back.
Vice President
Low-ranking Official
Mine's got...
What the heck?
I'm not low-ranking if I'm a
member of the student council.
Did they mess this one up or something?
It just says "vice president."
What a malicious prank!
What?
Oh, yeah. You were actually just an acting president.
Yeah, she did say something to that effect.
I get it now.
That explains the "vice president."
The next day
No way! For real?!
For reals! She was laughing—
You there!
Keep your voices down in the hallway!
W-We're sorry.
Jeez.
Who was that?
Enomoto, a third-year.
You know, the one who surrendered
the seat of president to Fuji's Princess.
I didn't surrender a thing!
Eno, keep your voice down in the hallway.
This sucks!
They're treating me like I'm a relic of the past!
I'm officially still the president!
Why don't you just announce that you're making a comeback, then?
That way you won't have to spy on them using binoculars like a voyeur anymore.
Hey! Yesterday was only the second time I did it!
I'm no voyeur!
She sounds like a criminal making excuses.
I tried to settle things amicably, you know.
But when I talked to the student council advisor about it...
Huh? B-But Maki's gotten pretty established in the role.
I-I'm not saying you're not good enough.
But, well, you know?
Then I got all pissed off and spied on them, and I saw them doing something weird!
Peeping falls under voyeurism, doesn't it?
You've got it all wrong!
I just want to find something I can blackmail them with!
You want to go back to being the treasurer too, don't you?
The biggest event, distribution of club budgets, is already over, so I guess I don't really care.
Huh? Don't you like making monetary calculations?
What I love is the money, not the calculations!
Making me do intangible calculations would be torture!
Sayo sometimes sounds like a very dangerous person.
But I must get her to be more serious about cooperating with me.
You're right. The distribution of
club budgets did already happen.
But you know, clubs are going to get special budgets for the summer tournaments.
So if you make a comeback now, you'll be able to touch and feel the real thing all you want!
Now you've made me want to go back by hook or by crook!
Yes!
Up until now, I was only helping you out on a whim, or rather, because I found your voyeurism amusing...
Stop calling me a voyeur already!
But I'll be taking this seriously now!
I'm not a voyeur!
Would you listen to me?!
Why does she keep yelling out "voyeur" over and over?
Hello? Can you hear me?
And the other was yelling about how she loved money.
Why are you just laughing?
Was that the reason she got kicked off the council?
Just who do you think I am, anyway?
They're hurting their
reputation more than
they are their enemy's.
Hey!
You sure you're not overthinking this whole harassment thing?
But just in case there really is someone like that out there,
I'll work harder than ever and have them give up.
There you go taking everything on by yourself again.
I'll be fine. I'm more than capable of handling this.
Also, once this goes away,
I can get back to love practice feeling all refreshed!
Refreshed?
Oh, right!
You said you banned the treasurer from this place.
Just have them come back and help you with wor—
I figured out the mastermind behind all this.
What?
It's Mizushima, the treasurer.
She's capable of doings things like these.
She tends to randomly show up out of nowhere,
and she's abnormally good at concealing her presence,
which allows her to close in and
rummage through things silently.
Hey.
What is this?
Wh-When'd you get in here?!
Mizushima!
What? She's the treasurer?
I'm back.
Mizushima!
Hey, Tanahashi.
What's this thing?
Tell me, what is it?
Well, that's president's bo—
Tanahashi!
Bo?
Bo what?
Trick her!
Deceive her!
Bo... Bo...
Boom the Baron's self-portrait!
Who the fuck?! Baron?!
Why's that baron's self-portrait here?
Hey! Don't you have something to say about the "baron" part?!
The baron is the guardian angel
of the student council activities!
Just stop, Tanahashi!
Oh, so that's why he's wearing a uniform.
She interpreted it in a way that's convenient for us!
Perfect addition to the story, Tanahashi!
Am I the weird one here for finding issues all over the place?!
But I have to say, he looks like quite the loser.
Loser?!
Huggy's an illustration I—
Fool!
You? You what?
I... I...
My parents and I were on a journey, when a mysterious merchant encouraged us to buy an expensive...
You're going too far! Also, why the broken English?!
Expensive?!
So it was pricey?
I can't believe she responded to that!
In that case, let me go sell—
Er, show it to everyone else.
Wait!
Don't do that. Please.
Why not? Will something bad happen?
Is she pretending to be an idiot to get information?
Aw, come on. Lend it to me for a bit.
We'll lose the guardian angel's protection, so we can't.
Oh well.
Guess I'll have to give up on that!
Huggy!
Look out!
Are you okay, President?
That was way too desperate.
Oh no. I went and threw the
student council's guardian angel.
But I'm sure he'll grant me forgiveness.
He is forgiving a scrub who does nothing and a vice president who does everything, after all.
I knew it. She's...
See you later.
Don't ever come back here!
Huggy!
She said she'd go snoop around a bit,
but Sayo's taking too long here.
Maybe she got caug—
I refuse to peep on them anymore.
I'm not a voyeur. Why would I?
Eno...
Sayo.
How'd it go?
I went and declared war.
Huh?
Hey...
What?
What?!
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
Born as the third son of noble family that'd fallen into ruin,
he left his hometown behind in search of his dreams and adventure.
And after encountering all kinds of things on his travels, he reached an island country far to the east.
Fuji Girls' Kingdom.
There he met a princess who was mixed up in a dispute over ascension to the throne,
and he crushed the ambitions of an evil
witch who wanted to take over the land!
What on earth are you talking about?
The story of how Boom the Baron became the student council's guardian angel.
You're one of those people who get way too invested in an absolutely pointless backstory, aren't you?
Sayo and Eno the Aggressors