His plane has come in sight now.
I wonder how he feels, seeing Mt. Fuji
for the first time in 28 years?
He had no idea that the war
was over and kept on fighting alone.
Alone for 28 years! Back home in Japan from Guam!
Now he's back home.
February
Concrete Revolutio
Superhuman Illusion
I could hear the voice cursing fate
I could see the way to use my power
It's not words you're looking for, right?
You want to see the love beyond them
Justice isn't on my side
because I follow my own guidelines
Come on! Wake up! Let's go!
Someone wished for these illusions,
and protecting them to the end
will clear the tainted skies
Our clashing cries won't solve anything,
and yet that's what we make our reason to live
This world is so far gone
but only those who continue to search
for ways they can change it
can bring about the revolutio for the future
February
The Iron Man
A bomb was detonated in
a restroom here at Haneda airport.
Even this late, the airport is still in uproar.
The police suspects that the bombing
gang that has been underground
They found a bomb on a
Tokyo-bound bullet train too.
for the past three years has now resurfaced.
We'll have to search every nook and crann—
This again?
There have been no demands made,
so the criminals' goals and incentives are unclear.
None? It was a huge explosion!
There should've been some debris!
And we did recover a large amount of machine parts.
Machine? Not bomb-related?
Yes. But they were all
taken away on higher orders.
These are all the remains
from the Haneda case.
Who'd expect security bots to go nuts?
And this is the fourth case like this.
They keep targeting Yatsuka
Heavy Industries people.
Why the Superhuman Department again?!
If it's a criminal case,
we should be handling the investigation!
Am I wrong?!
If the explosions had a target,
it must've been someone
in the departures lobby.
There's no one by that name here.
That's impossible.
A person injured by the bomb told the hospital he worked
for the Kamada Laboratory at Yatsuka Heavy Industries.
He then disappeared.
Hey, stop! Hey!
We had the laboratory relocate, just in case.
That's wise. Yatsuka Heavy Industries
is at the forefront of Japan's tech industry.
Who is this villain,
targeting only people connected to them?
There are rumors that Yatsuka
is developing robotic weapons for use abroad.
It's legal if it's just research.
Suppose such a weapon has been completed,
and someone is trying to prevent
its deployment in a war.
That's what a superhuman
of justice would do!
But what they do is serial bombings.
Not without casualties either.
нет! нет! Я не знаю, русский!
I was surprised the news
said it was a bomb!
It was a terror attack!
Someone attacked the scientists of
Yatsuka Heavy Industries. Is that right?
The suitcase of the Japanese
man changed its shape...
If I still had that camera...
I have retrieved the camera of the witness in question.
I gave him the newest German model in exchange.
Hey, shapeshifter!
Okies!
And the last!
The person that shadow belongs to attacked
the Yatsuka people headed for the US.
They panicked and activated the security bot
they had with them, but it was taken out in one hit.
This is so dangerous.
I want to try talking with him.
He must have a reason.
Capture superhumans
and oversee them in safety.
That's our job, after all.
I'm looking for evidence regarding the attacks
on the Yatsuka Heavy Industries employees.
I suspect you are hid—
I heard it was getting closed soon.
Nothing unexpected there.
Who are you?
Oh, Detective Shiba!
He's a detective?
I didn't do nothing!
You've gotten even more weirdos
in the time I haven't seen you.
The shapeshifter Fuurouta.
And some young girl, here of all places...
You should join us too.
Police officer duties must be tough.
There are all those public protests too.
Your department is too fishy for me.
He called us fishy.
I-I don't want to know!
Nothing fishy here!
Attacks? Wasn't the Haneda explosion
done by some serial bomber?
You pressured the media to announce so.
The same as always.
The attacker is a superhuman.
That's why you're covering it up.
What if Yatsuka Heavy Industries was an
evil organization, and he was a superhuman of justice?
That's just what you imagine...
Or rather, wish for.
How many times have we been over this?
There's no such thing as a
"superhuman of justice"!
There's just monsters already causing
or bound to cause trouble for honest citizens!
We will find the attacker.
I'll take them down first.
I've got the authority.
He used to be a gifted young detective.
However, an evil organization
robbed him of his life.
Then a genius scientist, on a whim,
planted his mind and memories into his current body.
He's a robot?
He wanted to stay a detective.
The one single officer who specializes
in dealing with superhumans.
Superhumans...
With their illegal powers,
they wreak havoc as they please.
There is no "justice" in that.
Farewell, my love...
The old songs...
Sorry. I didn't realize I wasn't alone.
It's okay. I like that song too.
What would she think if I told her
I was cooling my electric brain
by transforming the heat into sound waves?
Are you with Yatsuka Heavy Industries?
From that new factory just over there?
Oh, no.
It's dangerous here. Hurry!
You're...
What happened just now?
Run, now!
He's... He's there.
Who are you? No way!
Jaguar! Is that girl—
Pay attention!
You're targeting the wrong guy!
Who's she?
What are you doing?
Should I stop time?
There are too many uncertain factors.
Here they come!
Get the cargo out!
Let go of me!
Answer me!
Were Haneda and the others also your doing?
I'm sorry.
It's not him.
But it smells like him.
You can't use this for war!
No!
Stop!
Kikko!
Yes, sir!
Meteoterre!
Jirou, get the car! After them!
Hey!
Are you all right?
He's just a robot! Leave him be!
He's a superhuman too!
It's our job to protect him!
Hey! Who are you?!
Identify yourselves!
Stop... I'm...
not a superhuman... I'm normal...
Concrete Revolutio
Superhuman Illusion
I captured him and
returned him to his homeland.
He was the only one found in Guam.
Your existence will be kept hidden.
Why would you come back
after all this time?!
Who the hell are you?!
I've been waiting for you.
For me? Who are you?
Shiba Raito, former detective of the
Metropolitan Police First Investigation Section.
Now I am a wanted criminal.
A former Japanese army sergeant has returned alone.
There are no records of anyone accompanying him.
February
I saw the 8mm.
I'm impressed that still exists.
February
It's that B model developed
at Ikuta Labs during the war.
Top Secret
Imperial Army Research
..Final Report
Confidential
B model? Ah, the artificial humans
made in a male-female pair?
Confidential
Male-female pair?
They both disappeared
during the chaos after the war.
It seems one half
of the pair has reactivated.
Ikuta Labs
Female "B model"
Male "D model"
Merged ??
I heard there was a passenger plane
accident near Matsushiro.
It might be related.
Either way, she's a precious superhuman.
We will secure her.
The Kidnapper Self-destructed
Right Before Arrest
Kidnapper Called Himself "Heaven's Bow"
I'm coming in.
I didn't make you join
the department to do this.
I'm sorry, Father.
Is it true that she was
built during the war?
You were listening?
Ah, with your ears,
you don't even have to try.
Professor Hitoyoshi, there are rumors
that you worked at Ikuta Labs during the war.
I'm surprised you know.
But that facility is long gone now.
Imperial Ikuta
Laboratories
They say Ikuta Labs was developing
secret weapons during the war,
but I was researching the
tactical deployment of superhumans.
Why would they make
a male-female pair of robots?
Robots can be made to look like any
other nationality, and they can learn languages.
Very convenient for infiltrating enemy countries.
Female B Model Sketch 1
Female B Model Sketch 2
They made one a male and the other a female,
so they could be disguised as a couple.
She said she was looking for "him."
That must be the male artificial human
she was separated from twenty years ago.
Machine love.
That's incredibly unscientific.
But—
They are machines.
If she's looking for her male counterpart,
that's because she was made that way.
You are simulating a late human's memories
and mind in your electric brain.
Because of that,
you are an autonomous creature.
However, B model Kourouni Mieko and D model
Handa Kaoru are completely artificial humans.
Their thought processes and morals
are as installed by the scientists.
They were developed to look for their
counter-pair and try to merge.
Merge?
Why?
They were advertised to become
the strongest weapon that way.
I wasn't in charge of the project,
so that's all I know.
Weapons...
They'd infiltrate enemy
territories as normal humans,
then they merge and become a bomb.
The strongest weapon.
I wouldn't know.
You're not fully repaired.
Don't push yourself.
Did you tweak my body?
The Ikuta research has been used
in many ways after the war
and has become the
foundation of modern robotics.
The tech seems to have
been used for you as well.
That's why father could fix you.
Imperial Ikuta
Laboratories
We're rolling!
She was born here?
The male D model was flown
south near the end of the war.
She's just a criminal looking for her man,
but since she failed to find him,
she's targeting similar people.
If you intend to protect her,
you have no right to claim justice.
You say that destroying her
is the only possible justice?
Just leave it to me.
The night is almost over, it's time to depart...
Hey, where are you going?
Wait, could you be—
Farewell, my home, beloved mountains and rivers...
Now, I cross the hills of sunrise...
So weird. I thought we'd never see each other again.
And the boy, the boy heads for the wasteland...
It's not weird at all. You sought me.
That's right. But I'm not looking for you.
I know.
Let's go together, and share the burdens...
But your man is no more.
The robot had a mind of its own
and turned against its creators.
That's how I imagined it.
Like a deserting soldier
who realized what justice is.
A runaway?
But Mieko's not like that.
She's just looking for the man she loved.
It's not love.
They're programmed to seek each other.
But... Humans are the same, aren't we?
We're programmed to
fall in love with someone else.
That's why we have to love.
Am I wrong?
I think that fits with justice.
Shiba says destroying her is justice.
Are there so many justices?
No.
I'm just looking for that one person,
but these weird people always get in my way.
That's because you're programmed that way.
It's an implanted, false love.
That's why you get attracted to
Yatsuka robots that use the same tech.
But for me, you too—
Mieko!
I froze time within a hundred meter radius.
It only lasts about thirty seconds.
Do you understand?
Here I go.
Raise your head, Equus!
Jaguar!
Are you all right? Jaguar?
Was that enough time for you to find her?
What?!
Sorry. We tailed Detective Shiba.
We knew you'd show up for him.
You knew?
My design is basically the same as
the male D model you're looking for.
That's why I had a special reaction to you.
Your design is the same? That's all?
This should be enough.
I'll use the shutdown override,
then in a secure place—
There's no need for that.
I'll destroy her right here.
Detective Shiba!
I'm not letting your department
or anyone else take her!
Tell me!
I still want to find him!
Why?!
You're programmed to
merge with him, the D model.
You'd probably become
a powerful bomb then.
A bomb?
You wouldn't become a bomb with me!
Is this where the waterworks used to be?
February
Yeah.
Back then, there was still water here,
since the construction was delayed.
More of those are going to
spring up here soon.
Unbelievable, isn't it?
Five years ago,
I thought Mieko self-destructed.
But actually she dug herself
under the bottom of the plant
and slept there.
An acquaintance of mine worked
here and notified me right away.
It must be fate that you
returned at the same time.
I had no idea.
I was hiding in the south
following my orders.
This country has gone rotten
to the core during those years.
The justice I believed in was thrown away,
and many youth have died.
So please, merge with her!
You are given a false love, a false justice!
This is a chance for me
to show you true justice,
to force this Japan to open their eyes!
What are you doing here?
Stop!
What are you doing?
Not yet!
What's the point in detonating them here?
This is a distant sports development!
We must show the world how our government—
Cross-megassing.
Stop!
What... happened?
My father told you that they'd merge
into a powerful superweapon.
No one said it was a bomb.
They're the artificial human, Megassing.
No one knows of this superhuman yet.
They could infiltrate the conference,
merge and wreak havoc.
Detective Shiba.
I cannot do as you say.
Why?
Mieko, I reunited you two!
I appreciate that.
But your goal is evil!
What do you know, you machine?!
Not a machine. Justice.
How could they know what justice is?
The scientists taught them what justice is.
Protect the country. Save people.
What is right?
Humans interpret that as they please,
and sometimes reach a wrong conclusion.
But a machine obeys precisely.
So you're saying they're justice, and I'm evil?!
It's not me.
They're saying so.
Detective Shiba!
I'm Raito!
The Iron Inspector, Raito!
Whoever wins, we're no longer justice.
We still have to do it!
An underground world where
no man stepped foot before.
Tropical islands not even on maps.
A mystical world ruled
by creatures, not humans.
Behold!
An explorer of unknown lands
and one of Japan's brightest minds!
He is Magotake! Hitoyoshi Magotake!
Japanese
"Monster"
History
Japanese
"Monster"
History
Part 1