Ya think ya can win?
Hilarious.
She's quick.
She moves as fast as Ushio.
No,
maybe even faster.
Pulling out all the stops fer the final battle,
Hizuru?
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps god's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
That was a close one.
C'mon, Shide.
This ain't time fer a nap.
Up and at 'em.
Yer pretty good at handling my
sacred treasure, Amenonuboko.
Ryuunosuke is a shadow, after all.
He can't copy, but he's good at imitating.
The wrath in each strike is shocking!
I've known ya since ya were a baby.
Ya hate me that much?
Why go so far?
Why risk yer life to fight?
What I hate are your words.
My words?
Humans have language.
Human nature determines how to use words.
You'll never understand, no matter how long you live.
I have one question fer ya.
Why did ya come back, Hizuru?
Only a fool would come only to die.
It ain't like ya.
You should know the answer.
The last time you asked that, you scanned my mind.
Oh perhaps it's just beyond your comprehension?
Why don't you scan me again?
Ask my shadow to answer.
Not falling fer that.
Hizuru, ya must be immune.
Mio could've done that.
Ya just want to destroy this body the moment I flash.
Is it that obvious?
Ya think ya can defeat Shide if it weren't fer my eye.
Then it'd be easy to destroy my real body that's underground.
Haine.
Just wait.
So answer me! Why come back?!
Was it because of the message?!
That's typical of Ajiro Shinpei.
While stepping back logically,
when he encounter something he doesn't understand, he persists on getting answers.
What's with all this talking?
It's a perfect way to buy time.
Just let me handle it.
At first, it was curiosity.
Now I think I'd been waiting for this.
It's my chance to make it up to him.
Make it up to him?
Shide is right.
Ryuunosuke died because of me.
His death was treated as an accident.
No one blamed me.
My friends and parents consoled me.
I became this pitiful child who lost her twin in an accident.
But the truth is, it's as if I killed him.
It was a miracle that I met his shadow, and it let me apologize to him.
But that doesn't mean he's alive again.
There's one thing I can do now.
I can at least save the lives that would otherwise be lost.
So I'll save them.
I must.
Ya want to make it up to him? So that's the reason.
How pathetic.
Ya risk yer life fer strangers?
I hate people who believe that they're doing the right thing.
The right thing?
The right thing, you say?
Me?
You clearly aren't seeing the big picture, Haine.
Do you actually think he's acting for your benefit?
What?
Your goal of going home and his words at the end of the third loop contradict.
You said that it was your ending.
What did you mean by that, Shide?
Ending?
The man only thinks of himself.
He can't see beyond his own perspective.
Ending, huh?
I'm lost.
It's nonsense, Haine.
She's trying to trick us with words.
Yes.
That means she has nothing left.
Enough of this pleasant conversation.
I didn't want Haine to see this,
but I guess I can only ask for so much.
The rest is up to you, Tokiko.
Shide's armor is no one.
It's empty inside.
So...
you can get inside it.
Ryuunosuke, you know well how to possess people.
Get into his armor and destroy it from the inside!
What?!
Y-You...
So this was up yer sleeve, Hizuru.
Copying Ryuunosuke's data to Shide's armor and use that to...
A shadow was born?!
W-We really did it.
Sis!
Stand back, Shin.
It's dangerous.
I was waiting fer ya.
Where are Mio and Sou?!
So ya did come see Mio first, Shinpei.
I told ya to stand back.
I'll handle him.
Shouldn't ya kill Shinpei rather than me, Mio?
I sent Mio and Sou to Hiruko's grotto.
Mother is probably eating them now.
Ya were just a bit too late, Shinpei!
Ya got some guts, Shide.
Ya didn't run away.
I can't leave this to other shadows.
I don't want to lose any more allies.
A human like me can't be hacked.
What?
He's afraid of hacking.
He must think Ushio is alive.
What's this?
Wait.
If he thinks she's alive, I should let him.
Oh, ya got us.
Mio, kill Shinpei and make him loop.
If ya don't, it'll be too—
Okay.
Well, I'll be reborn in the next loop anyway.
So chatty.
Shin, what he said was true.
Mio just died.
Ya can tell?
I can feel if my original dies.
Wanna go back?
No, not yet.
We need to grasp the situation.
Search his memories.
Okay.
Strange.
He has no memories.
What do ya mean?
There's no memory at all,
not even of the conversation we just had.
What's going on?
How was he moving?
Shide has two bodies then.
Not shadows, but cloned humans.
True, he didn't have that burn on his hand.
There must be another.
He must be with Ms. Nagumo.
She must be in danger.
Haine called from her phone.
Shin, this way.
Toki!
Thank goodness you're alive, Shinpei.
I came this far searching for Mio's presence.
Tokiko, what happened?
Nezu and Totsumura helped me escape.
Go to Torajima.
Please. You have to.
Ryuunosuke is fighting Shide.
Save Ryuunosuke, please...
She's dead.
These are Tokiko's memories.
Hurry. Let's go to Torajima.
It's Dr. Hishigata's Derringer.
Toki had it.
There's one bullet left.
Shin.
Okay.
I'm not going.
Ryuunosuke and Ms. Nagumo might be dead.
I couldn't tell fer sure from Tokiko's memories.
I don't have time to go and confirm it.
We know that Mio is dead.
The event horizon is getting closer.
If we don't hurry, Mio's death will be set.
There's still time to save everyone.
If I loop now, it'll be around 10:10 a.m.
I was leaving Mt. Takanosu with the kids.
Ya can see that?
Yeah, vaguely.
But I can't stop Haine's call at 10:10 a.m.
First, I'll hurry back to Bistro Kofune.
I have to save ya there.
Then I'll go after Mio and Sou to stop them.
Once we loop, we have to move quickly.
Don't ask questions. Just come.
We'll save both Mio and Ms. Nagumo.
It's a battle against time.
I'm going now.
Summer Time Rendering
28 minutes since the start of the ninth loop
10:39 a.m.
Whoa!
I-It's y'all.
Why are ya here?
Shin?
W-We made it in time.
Mio ran through the sewers from Bistro Kofune to get us here.
Ya saved her?
She's all right.
More importantly, why are yer phones turned off?
What?
I mean, ya told us to turn them off in case a shadow might call.
Fool. That was a shadow telling ya that.
Sorry, Shinpei.
I should've known.
It's okay.
We don't have much time.
I'll head to Torajima with Mio's shadow.
I'm sorry I shot ya.
It hurt, but it's okay.
I just copied ya and healed my wounds.
It did hurt a lot, though.
I'm sorry!
Don't worry.
I would've done the same.
Sou and Mio, go back to Bistro Kofune and protect the kids.
Leave 'em to us!
Shin.
Save Tokiko and the others!
Yeah, I got this.
Let's go, Mio.
To Torajima!
#1: 9th loop starts
Alain's field
According to Tokiko's memories,
Ms. Nagumo sends the signal at 10:45.
#1: 9th loop starts
Alain's field
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
#3: Stop Mio and Sou
Bistro Kofune
#2: Save Shadow Mio
Torajima
Please!
Let me get there in time!
We don't have time to fight, Mio.
I'll jump.
Don't bite yer tongue.
We made it!
That's the attack Shide did that I saw in Toki's memories!
What did it do?!
Rose was gone in a second!
So this is how things can change.
Rose!
He's here.
Quicker than I expected.
Shinpei!
Stand back, Tokiko.
You'll die.
Ya looped, so ya know how this battle ends.
Tokiko must've told ya after she escaped.
Oh, why so surprised, Shinpei?
Because ya looped, we got to fight again.
No...
Thanks to ya, it was an easy win.
Ms. Nagumo!
Yer too far. Don't waste bullets, Totsumura!
What?!
Is that Haine?
Second time fighting this battle?
After the loop, it knew my attack position. Dammit!
We've only got my hatchet,
Totsumura's Derringer,
Gil, and Mio.
This ain't gonna be pretty if we fight now, Shinpei.
We're all gonna die.
What?!
Shinpei. Mio. Let's pull back!
Get on Gil!
Are ya deaf, Shinpei?!
I don't wanna leave Ms. Nagumo!
Ya shit-fer-brains! We gotta pull back!
Don't waste her sacrifice!
This is...
Let's go, Shide.
We're outnumbered.
This is enough fer now.
I understand.
W-We're safe.
Ms. Nagumo!
Stay with me!
I-Is that you, Shinpei?
Ms. Nagumo!
I-I'm sorry.
I-I said I'd save you.
It was a promise...
But I don't think I can keep it.
That's not true!
Not at all!
Totsumura! Give me the gun!
Huh? Here!
I'm going back.
No.
I'll save you next time.
Stop.
It's too late.
Ya know more than anyone.
Yer looping ability is reaching the limit.
Ya can't save both of 'em.
W-We need to take her to the hospital.
I'm sure Mio can...
Listen closely.
Haine is just a child.
She may be a monster,
but her original personality is shy and wants to be loved.
She's just a kid.
Shide's aim is not the same as Haine's.
Haine is probably just being used by Shide.
Shide is the one in charge.
Shinpei, please free Haine.
I will.
I promise.
Enough.
Don't talk anymore, Hizuru.
It's not such a bad way to end.
Stop being so gloomy.
It doesn't matter how long I've lived,
but how I used my life to the fullest.
I'm putting my brother in your care.
What a comeback story this'll be.
Hey, Hizuru?
Hizuru!
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time
Ajiro Shinpei's Longest Day