Don't know...
I don't know...!
Lose three times, and not only
do you lose your wish...
...that very wish is reversed.
Hitoe's wish was "to make friends"...
With that wish reversed...
She loses... her friends?
That's not all.
She will never make friends, ever.
And with the third loss,
the battle for her wish ends...
The words written here...
"Having friends is great."
Hitoe told me that she can't see them.
She also said she doesn't know you girls.
All her memories of being
a Selector disappear.
I...
...don't know... what to do...!
I don't know, but...
Hello, Kurebayashi... Ruko-san?
I heard you were sick, but are you okay?
I-Is Yuzuki...
She isn't home yet.
Hello? Did something happen?
No, nothing! Sorry for the bother!
Ruko-san...?
The truth rests solely on
the front/back of a card
It has not yet been solved
Upon the dazzling, dizzying stage,
destroy those entangled emotions
as many times as it takes to satisfy you
What should the tomorrows
wandering after fate's beckoning
choose and discard so that
they can become one?
I can't afford to disclose my reproachable hand
The days spent draining
the already-dry sea of regret
desire within limited words forgiveness
for the unplanned smile
I don't mind forgetting reality
I don't want to know anything now
Okay?
One two...
One two!
No more...
...battles.
I need to stop them...
I need to stop them...!
Any here?
No, I sense nothing here.
"Kazuki"
"Dueling Tables Available"
Yuzuki-chan?
I haven't seen her today,
but is something wrong?
--No...
--I summon, Amber! Attack, Amber!
If I only pulled Guard...
Is there a problem?
"WIXOSS Card Encyclopedia"
Ru?
Ru, look depressed...
Sad?
No...
Then let's battle!
Battle will make Ru happy again!
Beating me until I groveled...
You were enjoying it!
No! I...!
Ru?
I need to stop this...
I can't go through there...
By the way, I can't get
in touch with Akira at all...
Akira?
Do you need her or something?
Well, she took some outfits home with her...
Why'd you let that happen?
I'm sorry. I've been asking
her to return them, but...
Come on...
They can't get in touch with Akira-san?
What are you doing there?
I-I was...
Are you here for the shoot?
What magazine are you here for?
Magazine? Well...
Well, I...
Oh, excuse me.
She's my guest.
She's your friend, Iona-san?
Well, sorry about that there.
Iona-san?
Um, I...
So you wanted to do it, too.
You had the urge... didn't you?
N-No! I just wanted to see
Akira-san and talk with her...
Well, that's disappointing.
What do you want with Akira?
Well...
She's not here anymore.
Well, more like she'll probably
never come back here again.
Huh?
She lost a battle against us.
She lost to you, too, right?
You came here to see what happened
to the person you beat?
You're so sweet. Or, is this just
your composure as a winner?
That's not it!
Akira... lost to another
Selector besides us before.
Wait... That means...
You and Iona smashed her good. She lost
thrice already. Game over for her.
No...
So... Akira-san is...
I don't know. She may be
crying herself scared someplace.
Just like your friend.
Friend?
Hitoe-chan. Isn't she your friend?
Hitoe? What did you do to Hitoe?
Hitoe... we beat her too.
A... battle?
I'm sorry, but... Hitoe... her wish came true.
So she doesn't need to battle...
You're so lucky to get your wish to
come true before losing three times.
So lucky...
She also has a very earnest wish
she wants to fulfill. So... how about it?
That's right... I already have
Ruko and Yuzuki as friends.
Even if I lose...
Hitoe...
Okay. Let's battle.
She didn't know what
it meant to lose three times.
It can't be...
You knew that Hitoe already had two losses?
You knew, and...
That's terrible! Why did you...?!
So, do you want to battle us now?
You can't forgive what we did, right?
You want to battle, right?
Battle!
Even if I... battled you...
Hitoe will never...
Wish.
What?
A wish... Did you find one?
Wish?
You found one.
I don't have any wishes.
Liar.
You were the one who told me that battling
as a Selector without a wish is blasphemy!
But, I'm glad I don't have any wishes.
I can always quit battling...
No! Don't quit battle! Tama wants
to battle together with Ru!
More battle!
I'm sorry, Tama... I'm already...
Wanting friends and wanting to be
together with someone you love...
Worthless wishes, right?
They're not worthless!
Your wish is different from the others.
I told you, I don't have any wishes!
But you do... We know.
No you don't! Why?
Why are you saying this?
My wish...
...is the same as yours.
That feeling... It was the first for me...
I didn't have a bad life...
It wasn't especially good either.
Wh-What are you talking about?
All I did every day was live.
And I didn't even question that.
I assumed it is what it is. But...
I felt it...
I understood it...
I savored it...
That feeling...
It was the first time I felt
that I was actually alive.
I felt my life, and my soul.
Battle is my blood, my flesh, my bones...
No...
It is me.
But... if you lose three times,
you'll have to suffer...
Even if you win,
someone will suffer instead. That's...
It can't be helped.
That's what these battles are about.
That's what we are about. Me...
...and you.
Is she wrong?
I...
You felt it, too. Once you feel that
excitement, there's no way you can quit.
You can't hold your urge to do it...
You want to do it...
You want to do it, right?
I want to do it with you.
How about you, Ruko?
...I want to do it.
Ruko!
I want to battle...
I want to... I really do...
But...!
Open...
What's the matter?
You said you want to battle.
I-I did say that, but...
that's not what I wanted to say!
What were you trying to say, then?
Just give up, and have some fun.
Now, let's start this.
Battle!
Aw, Ru!
Oh, my. Hitoe-chan was a lot
more fun to play with, you know?
"Get Bible"
A spell to search for your low level cards?
Why would she use that now?
This is strange... Something isn't right...
Why is she only using low level attacks?
Tama, Grow.
"Sacrificial Smile" "Cure El"
Ru! Battle! Need to be serious!
Very good, Iona...
You looked into your deck using a search spell
to see what was used for the Life Cloth.
If Ruko attacks now...
Tama doesn't attack! End turn!
Oh? Well then...
Next is...
Spell, Blessed Reminiscence!
I knew it!
Here it comes!
Arts! Anti-Spell!
Very good... Tama-chan.
Say, don't you want to keep battling?
More!
Forever...?
Forever? What is "forever"? I don't know.
It means for a very long time.
Long time? Yes!
Long time! Battle, forever!
Forever!
Yuzuki...
Over there... A Selector.
She's...
Where's Iona?
She's already in the dressing room.
Shouldn't you be bringing her here already?
Ah, yes! I'm sorry!
She is the one...
Iona-chan... Huh?
I found her...
...finally.
Tama! Wish Crisis!
"Archangel Herald" "Arc Gain"
I finally found her...!
Iona-chan?
The shoot is going to start.
Can you please stand by?
Yes. I'll be there right away.
That was wonderful.
Wasn't it?
Well... I...
Want to do it again!
Tama likes battling Iona and Urith! Forever!
Long time, forever battle! I like forever!
Do it forever! Do it forever!
I found you...
We won.
I wonder how many losses she has now...
"Kazuki"
It's okay.
You can stay home, Grandma.
But...
The cafe that Ruko went to with her friend's
mom is the one down the street, right?
Yes.
She said that Ruko ran out all of
a sudden while they were talking.
What the heck...
Grandma, you stay put. I'll go look for her.
What happened?
I...
I forgot about Hitoe, and Yuzuki, and Akira...
I forgot about the others...
That was wonderful.
Wasn't it?
Scared... I'm scared...
What's happening to me?
How far am I going to get into this...?
Ru.
Tama...
I'm sorry, Tama. I shouldn't battle after all...
Ruko.
Yuzuki!
Oh, um, Yuzuki? I was...
So, did you do it?
Did you... battle?
You did battle.
I did too, and won.
"I want to, I want to meet you"
"I want Ru-ru with you too"
Akira said for us to come.
Akira-san?
Hanayo-san... do you sense anything?
No... Nothing...
Ruko?
What kind of person was your opponent?
What do you mean...?
Mine was about the same age as me.
I wonder what she was wishing for...?
Yuzuki.
Aw, poo...
So you both are enjoying
your lives being Selectors.
Well of course.
Yuzu-pon is trying to cross the forbidden lines
of love with your cute brother...
and, Ru-ru is mad in love for battles...
...just like her.
Wh-What do you mean by that?
Akira-san?
I'm so lucky to have met you two...
Lucky... lucky...
Aki-lucky...
Nodding to the clockwork shadow
opens the door to the end,
bringing in the darkness
There we catch glimpses of the perilous answer
Today's prayer becomes taboo tomorrow
The upside-down maze reflects
the heavens and the earth
The gear begins to turn
Listen carefully among the masses
and that bell resounding in
the skies beckons the soul...
I must move forward even beyond eternity
Because it is the future I chose
The unreachable summer clouds
and flickering heat haze
One day I'll get back my place of smiles
I wonder why...?
Things feel different today.
Yuzuki! What's the matter?!
If you lose...
I won't become like her.
There's nothing good about this.
"That False Vow."