Hm? Morning already...?
Good morning...
That scared me...
Why was I sleeping up here again?
Oh! That's right, it's morning!
I couldn't wait for morning to come!
I was waiting for Mister Sun to come up!
Today's the day I finally go to Meirocho!
I'll be back, Setsu!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see a light! Which way? (That way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
Which way should I go? I can't decide!
The path to our dreams is always a big labyrinth
To the left? To the right?
Which way is right? (Which way?)
No matter which way I go
It'll be fun because my friends are there!
That's the right answer!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see the future! Let's walk together!
See, you can see a smile! Which way? (This way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
This is Meirocho.
In this town live diviners, called Urara,
who possess a strange magical power.
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
A place where the lost and worried
come to seek guidance.
Girls who have passed their fifteenth birthday
come to this town with dreams of becoming an Urara.
THE
URARA
IS IN
Fortunes
Now, another girl has come...
...with many more?
Those look so yummy!
DANGO
There are so many things
that I never saw in the mountains!
My, young lady, you must be a visiting traveler.
On the hunt for a bargain, are you?
Huh?
HUNT
I get to hunt?!
Note: Pun on "buy" and "hunting/gathering."
What kind of bandit are you?!
Huh?
You sure are an interesting girl.
Are those animals your pets?
No, I don't know them.
They just gathered around me before I knew it.
Maybe they think I'm their friend!
Huh? You're giving these to me?
There they are! The animals that stole our stuff!
Are you the boss of this thieving gang?
Huh?
Wait, everyone!
Ow, ow, ow...
You told the animals to go to our stands
and eat through all our goods!
You'd better take responsibility for what they've done!
Huh? Uh...
Oh no, everyone's angry at me!
What am I supposed to do at a time like this?
Um, uh, when they're angry...
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
What am I supposed to do?!
What?! You want to fight, then?!
I'm sorry!
What?
What's going on?
Ah, Captain!
A strange girl robbed our stalls!
Robbed your stalls?
Goodness, all this fuss over a little girl-
She's a harlot!
Wh-wh-wh-what's going on here?!
This girl used her animals to steal food from us!
What?!
I am Saku, the captain of the 10th Bloque
Patrol Unit in Meirocho.
It's my job to uphold the peace in this town!
Using animals to get a free meal
only erodes the moral fiber of our town.
Th-this person is really angry!
Using animals to get a free meal
only erodes the moral fiber of our town.
What a... what a shameless act!
You may still be young, but that will not get you out of...
I'm really sorry!
Why are you doing that, after all that?!
Why is she getting mad at me for apologizing?!
Stop!
APPLAUSE
She's light on her feet...
Dammit!
Yay!
I should be fine no-
Look out!
I'm... I'm sorry! Are you alright?
I'm sorry, too!
Huh?
A-are you alright? Does your stomach hurt?
No, that's not it!
When you apologize, you have to show your belly!
Belly?
I'm Chiya!
I turned fifteen today! Who are you?
I'm Kon. I'm also fifteen.
Kon?! My friend's named Kon, too!
And you smell just like Kon, too!
Huh?
Kon's super cute and warm and soft,
and really popular, too!
My...! I can't believe you think
I'm like such a wonderful person!
I'm really happy!
I've never talked with a girl my age before!
Excusez-moi.
Huh?!
Enchanté, mademoiselles!
Could I ask you for directions?
There's another girl!
Shh! She's probably trying to sell us something!
We shouldn't bother with her.
Huh? Hold it just a moment!
I'm just asking for directions!
What's with you? And that strange outfit!
Huh? It's strange?
Yes!
I feel like the two of them
are a good match for one another.
Really, what kind of theme are you trying for with that outfit?
I don't understand what you mean,
Huh?
but it's always best to wear as little fabric as possible!
Is that letter an invitation to Natsumeya?
NATSUMEYA
Invitation
Huh? Yes, it is.
What a coincidence, I need to go to that shop.
Oh, I have the same letter!
Really?! Then that means...
Uh-huh!
All of us...
...are apprentices to Urara!
What's an Urara?
What are you talking about?!
Everyone knows who they are!
Every girl in the country wants to be one!
Really?
Yes, really!
They can see your fate,
and guide those who are lost on the path of life...
And only a girl can be one.
They're diviners with strange magical powers!
That's what an Urara is!
Your face says you don't understand
what's going on at all.
Why did you come all this way, then?
Huh?
You came to Meirocho because you turned fifteen
and wanted to become an Urara, right?
That's right, yes!
If that wasn't the case, the guards at the gate
wouldn't have let you in!
U-um...
NATSUMEYA
Invitation
Setsu just told me to take this and go to Meirocho.
Setsu said a nice person would tell me everything.
Wai-
I'm sorry!
Why is she showing me her stomach?
I don't know why, but she does this a lot.
Alright, alright!
I don't know what's going on,
but stop looking at me like an orphaned puppy!
Sorry, I was a little harsh on you.
I know... I'll tell you what I know.
I'm sorry, too.
Wh-what's that face for?
That's no good!
When you apologize...
you have to show your belly!
I found you, you little runaway!
What are you doing in the middle
of the street, you harlot?!
That's what I want to know!
I'll never be a bride now!
Meirocho
Gate To 10th Bloque
I see. You're here to be the Urara's apprentices.
But I can't simply allow someone
to degrade the moral fiber of this town.
As Captain of the 10th Bloque Patrol Unit,
I hereby expel you from Meirocho!
N-no!
We haven't done anything!
Saku...
Thank you for all your hard work.
But could you please wait for a moment?
Hello, cute apprentices.
I am Nina, the owner of Natsumeya.
They're your students, Nina?
You know, Saku...
I'm sure these girls aren't bad girls.
Y-you're getting too close, Nina!
Just turn a blind eye this once.
Hey, Nina, wait...
If something else happens,
I'll take responsibility for them...
...and slit my belly!
W-wait, Nina! Get a hold of yourself!
If I bring shame onto Natsumeya,
my successor will have to bear it.
W-wait, Nina! Get a hold of yourself!
If I bring shame onto Natsumeya,
my successor will have to bear it.
Okay, okay! I won't expel them!
Please be my second and behead me.
Sorry things got a bit out of hand there.
Natsumeya
I've learned a little about you from your invitation letters.
TEA
Let's start with Tatsumiya's only daughter, Kon-chan.
KON
My name is Kon. Pleased to meet you.
Next,
the daughter of the Yukimi conglomerate, Koume-chan.
KOUME
I hate that old, boring name.
Could you please call me Miss Plum?
Then I'll call you Pu-chan.
Pu!
I hate that more!
Lastly, we have...
Chiya-chan, from the Goten Mountains?
Chiya
That's me!
The Goten Mountains? You mean that secluded area
far from any human settlement?
Yeah!
How did you get from there to here?
I ran!
Are you some kind of feral child?!
Oh, my!
You came all this way from the mountains,
without knowing what the Urara or Meirocho was?
Why on Earth did you come here?
I came to see my mom!
Huh?
I heard my mom lives somewhere in this town.
So I really wanted to see her.
Ever since I was little,
I've looked forward to coming to this town!
What kind of town is it?
What kind of people are there?
What future is waiting for me there?
That's all up to you to decide.
The four of you should stick together,
work as a team, and do your best together!
Huh? Four?
Nono!
Huh?
N-nice to meet you.
NONO
I'm Nono.
How long have you been there?!
S-since we both met you.
That was a while ago!
She's a little shy.
She's a lot more than just a "little" shy!
I'm... I'm sorry!
When you apologize...
Run-!
...you have to show your belly!
Chiya, stop that!
That's no good, you have to show a lot more!
Looks like you'll all get along just fine!
Alright, let's all do it! You should be showing yours!
NO!
They saw my belly, they saw my belly,
they saw my belly...
Ch... Chiya, how are you not out of breath after all that?
It was good exercise!
Seriously, she's crazy feral...
Here you all are!
Ooh, sweets!
Let's all have tea together.
Yay!
It's sparkling!
I've never seen such a pretty piece of food!
Can I eat it?
Of course!
Looks like it really had an emotional impact on her.
Would you like to have mine, too?
This is kind of fun. Have mine, too.
M-mine, too.
Hey!
My, my... everyone's getting along so well!
Hey, Chiya, you're too close, too close!
I'll never be a bride now!
What a beautiful tea set.
Really? Thank you.
My sister does tea leaf fortune-telling.
With tea leaves?
Since we have it out,
why don't I give you a demonstration?
A demonstration?
Chiya-chan, will you help me?
Yeah!
I...
Concentrate. Show me who you really are.
Entrust everything to me.
For all people, east to west, west to east,
tell a fortune and blow off steam.
Now, let us see all the good and bad fortunes
awaiting this warm hand.
Bring these fortunes forth to see.
Tell us, O leaves!
Here you are.
Please enjoy.
That kinda sent a chill through me!
When you're done drinking,
hold the teacup in your hand,
then turn it around clockwise three times,
put the lid on it, and turn that around.
Then we'll read your fortune
from the leaves left in the cup.
That was good!
Let's take a look. Um...
Chiya-chan, there aren't any tea leaves left in your cup.
Huh? I can't drink them all?!
Let's try it again.
MORE!
My stomach's so full.
That's because you drank
all the tea leaves so many times!
But it was so yummy!
Chiya-chan's fortune says today will be a day
when new green shoots sprout up.
You may have surprising encounters or discoveries.
Wow! That's so cool!
Tea leaf fortune-telling, huh...
My favorite is tea, but there are many other kinds of
fortune-telling out there in the world.
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
It doesn't matter what, just pick something
that's easy for you to read as your intermediary,
and use the gods of Meirocho to read it.
The gods?
That's right.
Urara like me borrow the power
of invisible gods to tell fortunes,
then offer the words they gift us with to the lost soul.
One day, you'll all find the style of fortune-telling
that's right for you.
Oh, that's right. Before that, let me give you these.
So this is a Rank 10 card!
Yes, I've always wanted a Rank 10 card!
So what's a Rank 10 card?
What?! Um, well...
Hey, Kon?
This card is important to an Urara.
It's basically your license to tell fortunes.
What's this number ten for?
That's a good question!
Uraras have ten ranks, from ten to one!
NATSUMEYA
To obtain a card with a higher rank,
you need to pass an exam.
Ranks 10 through 8 are apprentices,
who learn their trade at teahouses.
NATSUMEYA
After you obtain rank seven, you can take on jobs.
Kon, you're amazing!
Like a teacher!
R-really?
I'm an apprentice Urara, so I should know all of this...
So once I get seven, huh...
But to do that, we have to find
the right kind of fortune-telling for us.
Huh. I wonder what would be good for me?
I just have to do something flashy!
Something cute and girly and colorful!
"Calafull"?
It means it has lots of colors.
Lots of colors...
Like mushroom fortune-telling!
I guess she's right, in a way.
Yes.
What do you think would be good, Kon?
I like...
Kokkuri.
Kokkuri?
Note: Kokkuri is almost exactly the same as a Ouija board.
It's a spiritual style of fortune-telling
that uses the power of a fox god.
The fortune teller uses hypnosis to put themselves
into an altered state of consciousness.
I see, that's why it's called kokkuri...
'cause you pass out like 'kokkuri!'
Note: Phonetically, "Kokkuri" is also the onomatopoeia for 'to doze off.'
That's wrong.
What about you, Nono?
You don't have to get so scared!
We're all gonna be together from here on out!
I'm... I'm sorry!
It's alright. We can gradually become friends.
Still...
Looks like she's already close with Chiya.
Huh?!
Ch..Chiya-chan's hair is so fluffy and soft,
it calms me down somehow.
Let's see.
Hmm, hmm...
Um...
Don't calm down on me there!
So, what are you going to use, Nono?
I, uh, I'm not very good at it, but...
Doll fortune-telling.
What's that?!
Ventriloquism?!
Wow!
I've been shy since I was really little,
so I only played with this doll.
But one day, she started saying what I was thinking,
and I started being able to understand
what she was thinking, too.
HEART
WARMING
Ever since, she's helped me
decide everything important!
No, no, no, that's so scary, that's so scary!
Okay, my turn!
Tarot cards!
That's a Western fortune-telling technique, right?
I've only seen those in books!
Yes, well...
How do you use them?
How?
W-well, I guess...
...it's kind of like this? Maybe?
Everyone's so cool!
I guess I'm the only one who hasn't decided.
I know, Kon!
Use that paper to tell me
what kind of fortune-telling I should do!
Huh? Why me?
Because you look like you'd be the best at it!
Huh?
C'mon, please?
B-but I...
I'll give you my fried tofu tomorrow at breakfast!
Note: in Japanese mythology, foxes enjoy eating fried tofu
I don't want it!
Huh? Why? You're a fox!
I'm not a fox!
Huh?
Don't "huh" me!
I mean, you've got ears on your head.
It's a ribbon!
You're right.
They're so soft.
Alright, I'll tell your fortune.
But just so you know, it might not be right!
Yay!
Let's begin.
I ask you, O strange and mysterious spirit...
Kokkuri, Kokkuri, come out.
If you are there, please answer me.
We ask you for the fortune of Chiya,
sitting here with us...
A calm afternoon.
Blue sky above, with a gentle breeze.
But somehow, I feel as if the doors of fortune will open.
Like we're about to peek into a forbidden world.
It's dark and deep, as if we've touched upon a secret...
"Hard"?
"Hard"? What is that supposed to mean?
I don't know. Do you, Nono?
Maybe it means you have to work hard to find it?
What're you doing, Chiya?!
I thought you had to have a tail, Kon!
We're done with that conversation!
I really will never be a bride now...
You just don't learn your lesson, do you?
What are we going to do
if we run into that guard again?!
What's wrong, Nono?
Maybe I'll do a different kind of fortune-telling.
N-no, Matsuko-san!
I'm not going to cheat on you! Just...
DANGO
FORTUNE
RED BEAN                   DANGO
JAM                      FORTUNE
FORTUNE
RED BEAN                   DANGO                    RED BEAN
JAM                      FORTUNE                     SOUP
FORTUNE                                                  FORTUNE
Sweets Cafe
ARINSU
That looks yummy.
This makes you think.
Yeah...
I... I wanna eat it!
At any rate, this is the town of Meirocho.
The girls set out on their dream to become Urara.
Their stories have only now just begun.
Sweets Cafe
ARINSU
Captain Saku, you're so gallant!
Captain Saku, you're so cool today!
What's wrong, Captain Saku?!
Alright! I was able to say her name!
Now that I think of it, you've been sneezing a lot lately!
Alright! My attempt to appeal to her
with my constant observation worked!
No, I just got really cold all of a sudden.
Maybe someone's talking about me behind my back?
Or could it be a cold?!
Is this my chance to nurse her?!
This is serious!
But she looks kinda good
in her slightly weakened state!
Excuse me!
A hot red bean soup for Captain Saku!
A dumpling and some red bean jam, too!
Why?!
Sweets are best for when you have a cold!
Also, my love!
Huh, really?
Oh, no, sorry. I don't like sweets.
You two should take care of yourselves, too.
It'd be terrible if my precious subordinates
caught my cold.
I... I... I... I want to catch the Captain's cold!
Precious?! You flatter us, Captain!
Please give me your cold, Captain!
Even if we fall sick, we'll put our lives
on the line to do our work!
I want the Captain's cold inside me!
We'll work for you in our next life, too!
I'd work for you in the life after that!
Then I'll work for you in the life after the life after this life!
What is that?
Don't know.
Then I'll work for you in the life after the life after this life!
That's right, Captain!
If I turn the corner, I wonder if I'll reach my dream
Getting lost and wandering in circles
It'd be great if I could just run into you!
There are some days when I don't have it altogether 1 to 10
Which way should I go to get a happy ending?
From right to left, from like to love
Uh-oh, I'm in love with love! I'm in such a hurry!
I want it badly, I can't get out of it!
I'm looking
I'm looking for you!
I haven't seen what you look like, but my heart's beating fast
Kiss me in my imagination!
The moment we meet is a crash
It gets a little complicated, that's fate
Maybe, maybe you're lost too?
We can't see the end
The maze that starts with romance
Will you find me in there?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"The Things We Search For and
Our Dreams are Sometimes Sweet"!
We'll use flower fortune-telling
to tell what kind of episode it'll be!
Oh, that flower looks yummy!
You can't eat those, Chiya!
"The Things We Search For and
Our Dreams are Sometimes Sweet"
You're right...