Attack with Cannon.
That's game.
Kazuki, you're just too damn strong!
C'mon, one more battle!
I'm not gonna quit before I win at least one battle!
Guess I won't be going home tonight.
Say what?
So you're not with your sister for once, huh.
Huh?
Come on, don't put it like that.
Hey guys, mind if we play too?
We picked up WIXOSS recently too,
but it's kinda hard to understand...
Kazuki-kun, aren't you good at this?
Hey, can you teach me?
Uh, sure.
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
Official WIXOSS Tournament!
Solo Battle Tournament
Adults' Division
Kids' Division
Tag Battle Tournament
Adults' Division
Kids' Division
Grand prize awarded to the winners of the tournament!
Entry Cards
Feel free to take one!
WIXOSS Party?
Entry Cards
Feel free to take one!
It's more of a get-together of sorts.
Only the guys used to come before, but a lot more girls are participating these days.
Oh, right! Why don't you three enter together?
You should totally go in matching clothes!
That'd be so cute! I'll help you pick them!
Momoka!
Hey, there you are!
Anyway, you can enter the day of,
so why not go and take a look?
Y-Yeah...
Hey.
I'm almost done here. Just a sec, alright?
Yuzuki?
Yeah...
So, what should we do about this event?
For someone without a wish to
participate as a WIXOSS Selector is...
blasphemy.
I'll go.
There may be Selectors there, you know?
Ah, but I...
Right, your wish already came true.
Yes...
And I'd feel bad for my opponent if I were to win.
Shouldn't it be fine as long as
that opponent isn't a Selector?
Besides, you can battle guys all you want.
Oh, right!
As long as they're not Selectors, I can battle anyone!
Yeah!
All right!
I-I guess... I'll enter, too...
I wanted to test my new deck anyway...
Right, Midoriko?
Midoriko?
Huh? Oh, right.
All right, it's settled!
So, what now?
Wanna pick out matching clothes now that we're going?
The kind idols wear, like this!
But these clothes are...
Tunic
Wide-neck Pullover
Pretty expensive, huh... Scratch that idea.
Hey, look!
Whoa, cheap! Only 100 yen!
limited time only
And there's all sorts of them!
How about we use these?
Scrunchies?
Yeah! Clothes might be a bit too expensive...
Hey, how's this?
This one's green, so it suits you!
Ah... thanks!
I'm getting a red one!
Ruuko, you take a white one... nevermind, none here.
Well, you can have that weird-colored one.
I don't want the weird-colored one!
How about this one, then?
That one's just as weird! Come on, Yuzuki...
Sorry, just kidding!
And then we bought matching ones, and then—
Hitoe, I know you're happy,
but you just stepped out of the bath.
You'll get kinks in your hair.
I'm fine!
And then Ruuko really was about to get a weird one,
but then she picked a light blue one—
Slow down! We'll talk about that later,
but I need you to put on something warm and dry your hair first so you don't catch a cold.
Okay!
Oh, it did get kinked...
The scrunchie's a bit wet, too!
I should have seen that one coming...
I'm such a dolt.
Hitoe.
What is it?
It's best you throw me away.
Throw... you away?
Your wish has already come true.
You don't need to battle anymore.
T-True, but that's no reason to throw you away, Midoriko.
If you keep me,
something terrible may happen.
No!
Ruuko and Yuzuki aren't the only ones.
Midoriko, you're my dear friend, too!
Hitoe...
Now stop saying weird things like that.
Right, the hair dryer...
It's no use...
What's the matter?
Um, well...
I figured I'd tie up my hair for a change.
You're a bit too clumsy for that.
Here, let me do it for you.
D-Don't worry, I can do it!
But Yuzuki—
I'm fine! I can do it myself!
So cold...
Look!
There's a giraffe on top of that pillar now.
Giraffe! It's going to battle that other giraffe!
Tama, all you ever think about is battling...
Do you want to...
do it with me?
That Iona person... she was pretty,
but also kind of scary...
I'll beat all scary people!
Looks like I'm here a bit early.
I just got here... I'll be waiting...
Yuzuki
It's Hitoe.
I just got here,
I'll be waiting.
Sending
Waiting here with so many people around...
It kinda makes me feel like a normal girl.
You are a normal girl, Hitoe.
Heh, I guess...
The weather is so nice.
You know, when I moved to Tokyo,
I thought there wasn't much of a sky to look at with all these buildings.
But there it is. A blue sky like any other.
Why haven't I noticed it before?
Was I...
looking down all this time?
Hitoe...
Hitoe!
Please, throw me away! Hurry!
Ruuko, hurry!
I'm sorry! The restroom was chock-full,
and that kid behind me said she was about to wet herself, so—
We're making Hitoe wait!
Ah, hold on!
Huh? Where did she go?
This place is full of people, too!
Did you find her?
No...
She's not replying to my texts either.
I wonder if she got angry
because we made her wait...
Hitoe's not the type to get mad over something like that.
Don't you think so too, Hanayo-san?
Hanayo-san?
Oh, ah, well...
Field!
What's the matter, Tama?
A battlefield is open somewhere!
Don't tell me...
Hitoe?
This opponent... she's strong!
Are you all right, Midoriko?
I'm fine...
Forgive me, Midoriko...
I won't make you suffer any more than this.
I'll try to lose as fast as I can!
No! You can't give up, Hitoe!
It's okay. My wish already came true.
So there's no need to draw this painful battle out.
Hitoe... I'm sorry.
There's something I haven't told you yet.
Midoriko?
I told you that you can become an
Eternal Girl if you win three times.
Hitoe?!
S-Sorry...
Where are you?!
But if you lose three times...
Is it around here, Tama?
The battlefield is gone.
Hey, Hanayo-san? Do you know anything?
Look there.
Hitoe!
What's the matter? We were looking all over for—
Hey, Hitoe?
Wh-What is it?
Why do you know my name?
What are you talking about, Hitoe?
Wait!
What's wrong, Hitoe?
Hitoe, are you hurt somewhere?
No! Don't touch her!
Wh-Who are you?
Wait!
Hitoe lost.
Tama?
Hitoe doesn't smell like a Selector. She lost the battle.
She's not a Selector anymore?
What's this about?! Why is she like that?!
Is it because she lost three times?!
Hanayo-san!
It's not just that your wish doesn't
come true when you lose three times;
your wish is reversed.
The wish... is reversed?
Yes.
Let's say that you wish to acquire great wealth.
Losing your battles means that you'll be stripped of everything and fall into poverty.
If we say that your wish is to master the piano,
you would lose your instrument or
become incapacitated in some way.
In any case, you wouldn't ever be able to play it again.
That's horrible...
I... I just don't understand.
What happened to Hitoe, then?!
Hitoe's wish was to make friends.
And when you reverse her wish...
She loses... her friends?
That's not all.
She will never make friends again.
You saw what happened to Hitoe.
When someone with the potential to become her friend approaches her,
her body reacts with immense pain.
That can't be true!
And now, with her third loss,
the battle for her wish has ended.
All the memories she made during
her time as a Selector have disappeared.
I'm scared... I'm scared... I'm scared!
What's wrong, Hitoe?
Who... were those girls?
It didn't hurt.
Why?
It hurts, it hurts... it hurts!
I'm scared! I don't want to think anymore! I don't...!
I've decided.
I'll wish for Hitoe to go back to normal again!
That will be my wish!
Right, that would—
That's illicit.
No wish granted through Selector battles—
whether fulfilled or reversed—can be undone.
Hanayo-san...
Why did you keep something that important a secret?!
Why aren't you answering me?! Hanayo-san!
Man...
The sky is overcast with clouds now.
Looks like it's going to rain.
I don't have the right to cry.
I've ripped your most precious wish from your heart.
I loved you, Hitoe.
I wish I hadn't been your LRIG, Hitoe...
Farewell.
You scare me, Hanayo-san...
I trusted you all this time.
You can throw me away.
It's fine, Yuzuki. You can throw me away.
Shut up!
Yuzuki?
What's the matter?
Uh... it's nothing...
Were you fighting with Hanayo-san?
Yuzuki, you've been acting strange lately.
You used to tell me about everything.
Not everything.
I want you to talk with me again and to rely on me again.
I can't tell you what I truly feel.
We've been together all this time.
If I say it now...
Yuzuki?
It's nothing. Really, there's nothing wrong!
So you won't tell me no matter what...
It's about time I stopped hanging off my sister, too.
Kazu—
Hello? Ah, yeah, I'm fine.
Tomorrow? Everyone's going to come?
No, I'm not really busy...
Alright, I'll be there.
Right. See you.
No... Please, no...
This is Tama's first time at this kind of place!
I've only been to family restaurants with Grandma before.
You're not going home?
Grandma's really sharp...
She sees right through me when I hide failed tests and stuff.
Ruu...
Tama, did you know?
Tama doesn't know a lot.
There's a part in my head that goes white when I try to think.
Tama loves battles! I want to battle more! Much more!
But I don't want to see Ruu sad.
Tama...
There you are!
Piruluk told me there's been a battle around here.
I thought Ruu-Ruu and the others could be involved, so I mailed Yuzu-pon and Hittoe,
but only Hittoe replied!
Funny thing is, she doesn't remember a thing!
From: Hittoe
Subject: How was your battle?
What do you mean by battle?
Who is this?
If this is a prank, please stop.
I guess she's not a Selector anymore.
You knew this is what happens when you lose?!
What was that?
What's going on?
Come with me.
Let's tinkle together!
A-Akira-san...
The first battlefield I encountered wasn't for my own battle.
Huh?
When I was on my way back from a shoot,
Iona was just about to battle another Selector,
and I got pulled into that field.
The opposing Selector had already lost
two battles and was at the end of her line.
She looked pretty sick, you know, and she was huffing and puffing trying to win the battle.
Well, Iona still beat that tragic heroine real bad.
After that she had this huge seizure, and there
were like, ambulances and stuff all over the place!
Iona's LRIG is quite a sadistic character, y'know? Poor girl...
S-So, what happened to that girl...?
No idea. They took her to the hospital.
But from the looks of it...
That's... terrible...
Like, seriously, right? Compared to that...
not being able to make friends ever again is just... you know?
H-How did you...?!
Did you forget?
I saw her wish in our last battle.
Well, Hittoe was a hyper-loner anyway.
You should be happy, though. Now you don't have to bother with her royal slowness.
They'd just have started bullying you, too.
And hey, now she knows what she can and can't do.
Like, it's totally impossible for her. She's so gross!
Even if she doesn't ever make friends again, it's not like that's a problem.
Not a problem?
Right, so—
Take that back!
Nopey-nopey!
I'll never forgive you if you don't take that back!
Huh? You won't forgive me?
It doesn't matter if Ruu-Ruu forgives me or not.
That doesn't faze good old Aki-lucky!
Say, how about we battle if you really can't forgive me.
If you give me a good beating, I just totally might feel like apologizing.
Fine...
Ruu?
I'll battle... and I'll make you apologize to Hitoe...
I'll make you apologize to my friend!
That
Vow
is
Illicit
Once you give yourself to the shadow of the clockwork
tokeijikake no kage ni unadzuitara
darkness begins to encroach from the door of the end
owari no doa ga hiraki hajimaru yami
Menacing answers lie hiding in wait
ayaui kotae soko ni miekakureru
Today's wish will become tomorrow's taboo
kyou no inori wa ashita tabuu ni naru
Lost in a labyrinth where the world is turned upside-down
ten to chi wo utsusu sakasama no meiro
the gears slowly start to turn
mawaridashita haguruma
Quietly from within the waves of people
hitogomi no naka de mimi wo sumashitara
a bell rings out, beckoning my very being
tamashii wo maneku ano suzu no ne hibiku sora e
I have no choice but to walk the endless path
mugen no hate made wo susumu shika nai
for this is the future I willingly chose
jibun de eranda mirai dakara
In the wake of the unreachable summer clouds
todokanai natsugumo yureru kagerou
lies the place of smiles I'll one day reclaim
itsuka torimodosu egao no basho
Hitoe lost three times...
You're the worst!
What's that to you?
No... no, no!
Why would you care?
I'm not scared of anything!
This
Heart
is
Pure White
This heart is pure white.