[NARRATOR]
As the fateful "Promised Day"
loomed over the new year,
those who refused to become
victims of an unknown destiny
began preparations
to alter the outcome.
Their plans advanced
with the passage of time
until spring was upon them.
Ready or not, the "Promised
Day" would soon arrive.
[SHEEP BLEATING]
That's a lot of sheep.
[STATION ATTENDANT]
Oh, yes sir...
It's our Resembool
Spring Sheep Festival.
Well, we're sorry
to interrupt...
We just need to
replenish our water.
Of course...
Please help yourselves.
Alright...
Unload the tanks.
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
[CRATES THUD ONTO THE GROUND]
[MICK GRUNTS]
Doesn't look
like anyone's home.
We're here now,
Miss Winry.
[WINRY EXHALES HEAVILY]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[DOOR CREAKS CLOSED]
Hmm... Still
smells like home.
[MICK]
Whoa.
It's like an
automail bomb went off.
Try not to touch
the stuff in progress.
[WINRY]
It's gotten so
dusty in here.
Hmm...?
[ED STAMMERS]
[WINRY SCREAMS]
[MICK AND LIAM GASP]
Hey! What's
the matter here?!
[ED STAMMERS]
When did
Edward Elric get here?!
[GUNS COCK]
[DOG BARKS]
Drop your guns.
[DARIUS SCREAMS]
What the hell is
going on up here?
[WINRY]
Ling?
Wait... You guys are
Kimblee's men, aren't you?
[DARIUS GRUNTS]
Hey, I know you guys.
You're from Briggs.
You two have been
following us this whole time?
[DOG BARKS]
[HEINKEL]
Everyone calm down!
Lower your guns.
[WINRY]
Okay, Ed.
You wanna tell me
what's going on here?
Looks like a
cautionary tale about guns.
Don't be a smartass,
tell me why you're in my room.
I just wanted someplace
private to eat my sandwich!
[DARIUS]
Whatever, just
put your guns down!
[LIAM]
Quit shouting at us!
[DOG BARKS]
[MICK]
Will someone
shut that dog up?!
[DOG BARKS]
[WINRY]
Get out of my rooooom!
[MICK, DARIUS, LIAM,
AND HEINKEL YELL]
[WINRY BREATHES HEAVILY]
[WINRY GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[ED STAMMERS]
[WINRY SLOWLY EXHALES]
[WINRY]
I was worried about you.
[ED]
Uh...! Yeah... I was
worried about you too...
I thought Al
was with you.
[WINRY GASPS]
He's at the train
station right now...
He's with Miles.
The train's
gonna leave soon.
You might be able to
make it if you hurry.
[ED BREATHES HEAVILY]
Hey, what's wrong?
Don't you wanna see him?
[METALLIC CLINKING]
Well, technically
I'm a fugitive right now...
I can't risk
anyone seeing me.
But, still...
[SHEEP BLEATING]
The spring sheep festival...
That takes me back.
We'll be leaving
in just a minute.
Okay.
The next time you
see your home town,
I hope that it's with
the eyes of your original body.
Yeah.
[METAL DOOR SLIDES CLOSED]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[PINAKO]
Winry?
Welcome home.
Hey, Granny...
I hope you weren't worried.
I missed you.
[PINAKO]
So who are these hooligans
you've brought with you?
I'm really sorry about
all the chaos earlier...
Liam and I are both
soldiers from Fort Briggs.
[LIAM]
We've been acting as
Miss Winry's bodyguards.
Huh?
Hey, Ling...
You remember me?
What...? Oh, right...
I guess you know this guy.
[WINRY EXHALES]
Heh... The name's Greed...
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Uh... Huh?
[EATING NOISES]
[GREED]
And after all
that went down,
these guys signed
up to work for me.
[WINRY]
Why did you
come to our house?
We're trying
to get prepared...
His automail's in
serious need of maintenance.
And I need him
in peak condition.
[PINAKO]
Give him
a look-see after dinner.
It is your fine
craftsmanship after all...
I'm not really
comfortable tinkering with it.
Uh...
[WINRY GRUNTS IN AGREEMENT]
Yeah, of course.
Ya don't say...
Liore's getting up
and running again, huh...
Good to hear... I was
nervous they might not.
So... Why is Al traveling
with Major Miles anyway?
[WINRY]
I'm not sure
on the details...
but the Northern troops
are hatching some plan
in the east...
Al figured he could help out,
so he volunteered to tag along.
I see.
We ran into your
father in Liore.
He should be on his
way to Central now.
I think he's headed for
some slum named Kanama.
You ought'a go there and
get the full story from him.
You know... It's almost
The "Promised Day."
Ling and Greed told
me all about it...
It could give us the chance
to get our bodies back...
but it's most
likely gonna result
in catastrophe for Amestris.
Listen...
What is it?
I want you to take
Granny and Den...
...and leave
the countryfor a while.
[WINRY GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[WRENCH POUNDS
AGAINST ED'S FACE]
I'm not running away!
You can't just send
us off like that!
I know you
wanna protect us,
but you need to try
to save everyone!
I'm gonna do everything
I can to stop it
but there's a chance
it might not work!
I don't wanna hear
any doubts from you!
Please, Ed... You can't let
them go through with this.
Just tell me you're gonna stop
them and save the country!
I wanna hear you say that
you're gonna protect the country
and then get
your bodies back...
Do whatever it takes
to make that happen!
[ED STAMMERS AND SIGHS]
Winry... You make it
sound like it's easy.
This isn't the time to
start doubting yourself, Ed!
Listen to me!
[ED GROWLS]
Winry, you just don't know
when to shut up, do ya...?
Edward!
[GREED LAUGHS]
Oh, man...
She's a peach.
Sounds like she wants
everything... My kinda girl.
That kind of wanting
is dangerous...
It's not how reality
works... Take a look...
This is what I got for wanting
something unrealistic.
I disagree.
You wanna bring back
someone that you've lost...
You might want money...
Maybe you want women...
Or... You might want
to protect the world...
These are all common
things people want...
Things that
their hearts desire.
Greed may not be good...
but it's not so bad either.
You humans think greed is
just for money and power,
but everyone wants
something they don't have.
[WINRY]
You're leaving in
the middle of the night?
[ED]
We were actually planning
on leaving earlier today,
but then we ran into you.
It was good to see you...
And thanks for
the tuneup, Winry.
[ED LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
[PINAKO]
If you happen to
run into Hohenheim,
you make sure to
give him that message
from your mother, all right?
I will, I will.
[WINRY]
Wait, Ed... I need to--
Just lay low until
the Promised Day passes.
We're gonna
stop them, Winry.
And Al and I'll be home
before you know it...
Have an apple pie
waiting for us, okay?
[WINRY GRUNTS IN AGREEMENT]
Man... That was
a serious day of labor.
I can't help but feel like we're
wasting our time right now...
We should be getting ready
for the Promised Day.
By doing what...? We're still
waiting on Marcoh and Scar.
[ZAMPANO]
Where the hell are they?
And what's taking them so long?
[ZAMPANO SHOUTS]
Doctor!
Oh, it's you guys.
Yeah, the guys who
you've kept here waiting!
You wanna tell us
what took you so long?
There's no time...
We need to
get to Central.
[GERSO]
You know... It's kind of
funny when you think about it.
We're former
Amestrian soldiers...
...and here we are, working
with an Ishvalan dissident.
[ZAMPANO]
Yeah, I know...
We were born in Amestris
so it makes sense that
we're trying to save it.
I mean our families are here.
[GERSO]
And while Scar has got every
reason to hate this country...
Who'da guessed an
Ishvalan like him'd be here
fighting to save it
right along with us.
You've got it all wrong...
I'm not trying to save your
country... I'm changing it.
I want Amestris to acknowledge
what it did to my people...
And I wanna make sure
that it's incapable of
ever doing so again.
[MASTER]
If you truly dream of
changing the world...
you must first be able
to change yourself.
The ebb and flow...
It's a simple rule of life.
They're Ishvalan!
But how?
What took us so long...?
As you can see, we've been
busy these past few months.
These men have chosen
to join us as our allies.
I look forward to
this every year... General.
[GRUMMAN]
Well, I'm just happy we're
holding the drills on my turf
for a change...
It's too cold up north for my
men to have a fair fight.
Everything is
set and ready to go.
Everything's set
on our end as well.
They've placed one
small stumbling stone
in our path though.
Hmm... What do
you mean, General?
[GRUMMAN]
Well, it seems
Bradley himself
has come to
observe the exercise.
[MILES EXHALES FRUSTRATEDLY]
[MILES]
The Promised Day is right
around the corner...
I figured they would send
someone to keep an eye on us,
but I wasn't expecting this.
[GRUMMAN]
Oh well... we'll just have
to do something about it.
[AL HEAVILY EXHALES]
Not again.
It's starting to happen
more frequently...
and it's lasting
longer each time.
We have to hurry...
This bond isn't gonna
hold much longer.
[LOUD THUD]
[AL GASPS]
[AL HEAVILY EXHALES]
[SPLATTERING SOUNDS]
[GLUTTONY]
I smell him!
That's him alright...!
I smell the Fullmetal
Alchemist's brother,
the little armored boy!
[AL GASPS]
You want me to chase you?
[GLUTTONY YELLS]
[AL]
Not good!
I can't fight him right now!
Not in this condition...!
[AL BREATHES HEAVILY]
[AL YELLS]
[AL GASPS]
[AL YELLING]
What is this?!
What's happening?!
[LOUD CLANG]
No... not now... Not now!
[AL WHIMPERS]
[LOUD THUD]
You rest up, Alphonse...
Just take it nice
and easy for a while.
We'll wake you on
the Promised Day.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
Good evening...
Mind if I intrude?
Hm... Just don't expect me
to offer tea or anything.
[ROY]
Just to warn you...
I'm gonna have time to take
you out to dinner soon.
[OLIVIER]
So you're going
to follow through
on your threat
after all, huh?
[ROY LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
I've gotta say...
Your mansion is enormous.
Very fitting for
the Armstrong family...
If you wanted to,
you could hide an entire
battalion in there.
You seem to be rather
enamored with it, Colonel.
I'll leave it to you...
...if something
happens to me that is.
It's not like it'll
fit inside my casket.
You mean you don't plan
on leaving it to your brother?
If I had to decide
between the two of you,
I'd rather you have it.
Try not to take
that as a compliment.
[ROY LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
Nonetheless, I'm honored.
[ROY]
I know it's a little late...
...but congratulations on
heading the Armstrong family.
They're hyacinths?
" Selim Bradley is
a Homunculus"...?
Y'know what
they represent...?
Those hyacinths...
Know what they mean?
I don't.
They represent
ladylike charm.
[OLIVIER GROWLS ANGRILY]
[OLIVIER]
Get off my property!
[ROY LAUGHS]
[ROY]
Oh... I thought you'd
like them... So long.
Tch... That little punk.
[FIRE SMOLDERING
AND CANONS FIRING]
[CANONS FIRING]
[GUNFIRE]
[GRUMMAN]
This is beyond frustrating...
I feel so helpless...
Why don't we just, accidentally
blow up the tower Bradley's in?
Please don't
do that, sir.
Major Miles, sir?
[MILES]
So you haven't had any luck
locating Alphonse Elric?
[SOLDIER 6]
No sir, no one has...
We're continuing to
search the area... but...
Do you think they
might have caught him?
The Promised Day is
tomorrow, so let's hope not.
Uh, sir?
Hmm...?
General Hakuro is here.
[HAKURO]
Your Excellency... I've come
here to give you a warning...
General Grumman plans to--
To use the Eastern
forces to stage a coup...?
I've anticipated the
General's next move.
Actually... the threat
of a joint coup d'etat
is just a decoy,
sir... A distraction.
Their plan was
to draw the bulk
of the military's divisions and
attention away from Central.
Ishvalan terrorists are
gathering to attack the city.
Afterwards... General
Grumman will invade
Central under the pretense
of stopping the terrorists.
The General then plans to
ally with Colonel Mustang
amidst the chaos in order to
take control of Central Command.
[CANON FIRING]
[AIDE]
According to
the latest report,
A large number of Ishvalans
have been seen gathering in
the slums outside of Central,
so we have evidence to support
General Hakuro's intelligence.
[BRADLEY GRUNTS]
Prepare the train
to depart for Central.
I'm leaving you in command.
[AIDE]
Yes, sir.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
We should've known...
Mustang's treacherous.
It wasn't enough to
strip him of his pawns...
We should've put him
down in the first place.
[TRAIN SCREECHING TO A HAULT]
We've stopped.
What's going on here?
[AIDE 2]
It's a herd of sheep.
[AIDE 3]
We don't have time for this.
[LOUD METAL CLANG]
Hey... The engine just
started moving without us!
It did what?!
[AIDE 3]
What the hell...?!
Hey...! Stop them!
[LARGE EXPLOSION]
[CONDUCTOR]
Heh...
We've safely cleared the
sheep off the tracks...
We're now heading for
the rendezvous in
Central, as planned.
Let's move out...!
The Colonel's waiting for us.
[6 SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[AIDE]
Damn it!
[AIDE GROWLS IN FRUSTRATION
You've been played
for a fool, General.
They set us up.
They attacked
the Fuhrer's train.
They blew it
up over a ravine!
[HAKURO GASPS]
[GRUMMAN LAUGHS]
[GUN COCKS]
[HAWKEYE]
This is it... Everything
goes down tomorrow...
It's do or die now.
I'm glad the two of
you've got my back.
Hey, anything
for you, Riza...
Even if it does
mean deserting.
Aw, man...
There go our careers.
[HAWKEYE LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
Once the dust has settled...
We'll make sure
the Colonel answers for us.
The Fuhrer's dead?!
He can't be dead!
This has got to be a mistake!
We're still waiting on
confirmation that it's true.
So have they even
started searching yet?
[CREMIN]
Last I heard, they haven't...
[OLIVIER THINKING]
They start panicking the moment
they lose their leader...
...like chickens
with their heads cut off.
[FRANK]
Gentlemen, this
is no time to fight!
Our commander in chief
might very well be dead!
[HARRIS]
We're aware of that!
[OLIVIER THINKING]
This could be my chance.
[OLIVIER GASPS]
[EDDISON LAUGHS]
[FRANK]
It's a genuine honor
to have you amongst us.
Calm down...
Stop panicking.
I'm still here with you...
And I'm watching over Central.
[NARRATOR]
Is it a demon
lurking in the darkness,
or is it something
far more sinister
hiding within the guiding
light you've always followed?
The young man's only hope
is for a blast of black wind
to separate him from
this unspeakable crisis.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
...Episode 47:
Emissary of Darkness.
Strike a light deep
within the heart of man
in order to ward
away the darkness.