“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Even now, when I think about it, it's weird,
but somehow I also feel like it isn't.
Anyway, I experienced something that would change my life...
Something that was actually completely normal,
but still very, very strange...
and yet could happen anywhere...
...in this place called Ikebukuro.
THE FIRST WORDS
Ah! S-Sor... ry.
I want to go home.
Don't laugh when you hear this.
I've never gone on any field trips in elementary or middle school,
See ya!
so I've never been outside my hometown.
That fifteen-year-old boy having trouble on his first trip to Tokyo...
That boy never leaves home, does he?
Yeah.
That's me... Mikado Ryugamine.
Why am I just looking around while standing in front of the Tobu Tojo Line's fare control area?
Because starting this April, I will be going to Raira Private Academy in the east part of Ikebukuro.
It's a fairly prestigious institute; it looks nice.
The facilities are in pretty good order too.
More importantly though, a friend from elementary school told me I should go there.
My parents were against it, saying I should go to a public school,
but I've always wanted to go to Tokyo.
Mikado!
Ah! Huh?
Kida-kun?
What, you have to ask?
Well then, I'll give you an answer.
Which of the following am I?
1. Kida Masaomi.
2. Kida Masaomi.
3. Kida Masaomi.
Whoa! Kida-kun! Is it really you?
Did you not just hear the joke I've poured my heart and soul into for the past three years?
Hey! Long time no see!
You look totally different! I'm surprised!
I didn't think you were the type to dye your hair.
Oh, and that joke was pretty lame.
Well you know, after a whole four years...
Anyway, you haven't changed at all since elementary school, Mikado!
Or should I say, don't blow my jokes off as being lame like that!
That's right. This is my best friend, Kida Masaomi.
We haven't seen each other since he moved away during elementary school.
But despite our appearances, we haven't changed a bit.
Well then, let's go! I say we go this way.
Feels like I should say, “Go West!”
What a tricky guide I am, saying we're going to the “Nishiguchi” when we're really going to Seibuguchi!
His jokes are lame, but he's really a good guy.
Kida-kun and I had been chatting every day,
so we never felt the time or distance between us change,
...like, aren't the 'Nishiguchi' and 'Seibuguchi' the same place?
but meeting him like this four years later,
When really, Ikebukuro has a mall at its west entrance,
I truly realized that he'd been living somewhere far away.
and a separate one to the east with West in its name...
Ah, crap. Why am I explaining my joke after I messed it up...?
However, even with all of his lame jokes, he still really was the same inside.
Oh well. Anyway, is there somewhere you wanna go?
Uh... Maybe Sunshine Sixty.
Right now? If you're gonna go there, you should at least bring a girlfriend with you.
W-Well then, maybe Ikebukuro West Gate Park.
Just call it Nichigushi Park like everyone else does.
Huh? But I don't think all the Ikebukuroans call it that...
What do you mean, Ikebukuroans?
Wait, what? You want to go there?
Ah... but... W-Wait!
L-Let's call it quits. It's already night time!
We'll get killed by the “Color Gang”!
Come on, don't talk like that.
Or should I say, it's only six o'clock! Seriously.
You're as cowardly as always, I see.
Good evening!
Evening.
Ah, Setton-san.
Actually, starting tomorrow I'll be living in Ikebukuro, so...
Oh, really?
Maybe you'll be close to where I live.
Maybe.
Right now I'm online at my parents' house, but tomorrow I'll be living in an apartment near Sunshine Sixty.
It's amazing!
A whole world I've never seen, except for on the Internet and in manga, is spread out here before my eyes.
It's more amazing than Ginza, Kamisakura-Machi.
Well then, next time I'll take you to Shibuya.
Or, if you're not used to crowds then should I take you to a racing track instead?
We've also been seeing a lot less of the Color Gang lately.
Last year they did a lot of things that drew attention.
But during a gang war with Saitama a lot of 'em got nabbed,
and since then the cops have been showing up in a flash whenever a bunch of guys get together wearing the same colored clothes.
So, Ikebukuro is safe now?
Well, I don't know the whole story. So I don't know for sure.
There are still tons of dangerous folks around, so keep an eye out.
Is that so?
By the way, this is Sixty-Floor Street. There's another street called Sunshine Street.
I wonder if they built Sunshine Street first?
S-Sorry!
Oh, it's Kida-kun!
Hey, Karisawa-san and Yumasaki-san! Hi.
Long time no see!
Yo!
How are ya, Kida?
Hey, we haven't talked in a while!
Who's that kid? A friend?
Yeah. This guy's a childhood friend of mine who moved to Ikebukuro today.
Oh, is that so?
This person is Karisawa-san.
This is Yumasaki-san.
Over there are Kadota-san and Togusa-san.
U-Uh... My name's Ryugamine Mikado.
Is it something I said?
A pen name?
Why would a high schooler use a pen name?
Oh, maybe for the radio and writing to magazines?
N-No, uh, that's actually my real name.
No way! Your real name?
Wow! That's so cool! Man, he's just like the main character in a manga!
Aw, guys, you're making me blush!
What do I do? I have no clue what they're talking about.
Going home from shopping?
Yup!
The latest issue of Dengeki Bunko just came out, so I bought thirty of them.
Does Dengeki Bunko really come out that many times a month?
No, it doesn't! We got one for each of us,
and then we picked out about ten volumes of... well, other stuff.
Yeah, other stuff.
What do they mean, other stuff?
Books on conservation, or management, or fashion, or something like that?
Well, we'll be moving along now.
See you soon! Bye!
'Kay, see ya.
Okay, let's take this from the head...
Later.
Hey you! Don't frickin' hit the car!
Well, those guys are a bit strange, but as long as you get along with them, they're good folks.
Wow, I didn't know you knew people like that, Kida-kun.
Well, what can I say, I've been around.
I've got the scoop on stores and old clothing...
These past four years,
what kinds of things and how much has he been up to...
while I've been withering away in our hometown?
Well, if you stay informed about all kinds of stuff,
you can usually strike up a conversation with a girl.
He's changed.
There she is.
Are you sure?
From the top of her head to the bottom of her feet, it's just like you said. No mistaking it.
Roger.
Let's go.
Sir.
Get the amount right this time.
If you're not watching properly, it won't come out right at all.
Does it matter? You increase it by half for a teenage girl anyway, right?
Twenty percent, twenty percent!
We haven't had something so tasty in a while, have we? A teenage girl.
Yeah. According to various sources.
Good evening!
Kanra-san! You're here!?
I was on the phone earlier.
Oh.
I just read the log. You're coming to Tokyo?
Congratulations!
Do you want to meet in person?
In person? Sounds good!
Yeah!
Speaking of meeting in person,
Have you heard of offline suicide meetings?
Yeah, they've gotten popular.
Meeting on the Internet, then both committing suicide...
Not a pleasant subject, is it?
But they haven't mentioned anything about it in the news lately, have they?
I wonder if people stopped doing it...
Or, maybe they're doing it a lot,
but nobody notices.
Like, they haven't found the body...
That's not very discreet.
Speaking of which, there've been a lot of disappearance cases lately...
On the news?
Um...
It's mostly illegal immigrants,
or local kids running away from home,
and apparently they've happened a lot in between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
Excuse me...
Yes?
Magenta-san?
Yes. Oh, are you Nakura-san?
Good! It is you.
How do you do? Nice to meet you.
The pleasure is mine. Shall we go, then?
Yes...
It's right around the corner. There are two others coming as well.
Okay...
There it is.
Hello!
Hello.
Is anyone around?
Not a soul.
Well then.
Sorry... to fool you!
There is one person here.
Kida-kun kept on talking without pause. I was a little tired.
Was I tired from walking, or from retorting to Kida-kun's lame jokes?
I tried having a conversation with her, but I found out right away,
that I didn't know anything she wanted to talk about!
Probably both.
Y-Yeah.
On the inside it feels like I've only said about five four-hundredths of what I have to say.
And about four four-hundredths of that were about Karisawa-san.
Just then, when I wasn't sure whether I should make another retort, it appeared before my eyes.
Oneesan, it's been a while.
A guy dressed as a chef, handing out...
No, a giant black guy dressed as a chef...
No, a guy hawking his shop dressed as a chef, who for some reason was black...
Oniisan, it's been a while!
Yo, Simon, long time no see!
Mm, Kida. Eat some sushi?
Okay. I will make it cheap. Sushi is good.
Eh, I don't have any money, so not today.
I'll make some money working part time and then I'll eat here, so gimme some free food until then.
Oh, no! If I did that, I would die in seaweed, in the land of Russia.
In the seaweed, even though it's land?
Well, see ya.
Oniisan, it's been a while!
Do you know that guy, too?
Yeah. His name's Simon. He's a black Russian,
and he has a job touting for that Russian sushi restaurant over there.
Sorry... what do I say to that one?
No, I'm serious.
His real name is Sermya, but everyone reads English, so they call him Simon.
Oniisan, it's been a while!
I don't know the details, but his parents were exiled from America or something.
Then, another Russian he knows started a sushi restaurant, so he's the one who pulls in the customers.
Don't make him your enemy though.
He's been in a fight before, and by the end of it, he was holding up a guy his own size with one hand.
Oh, and finally, there's one more person to not make enemies with...
What? What's that?
Speak of the devil.
Anyway, don't go near that guy; his name is Hewajima Shizuo.
If you're alive and well, there's nothing to talk to him about anyway.
J-Just what kind of person is he?
Huh? He's not here yet. How strange.
The guy upstairs sure is lazy. We'll have to get him straightened out.
Well, who cares? We have free time.
That's right.
This really is precious time.
In a wild and crazy life, a fleeting moment of leisure.
Speaking of which, I saw those black motorcycles today.
Black motorcycles?
Yeah.
Haven't you heard? They're talking all about them in Shinjuku and Ikebukuro.
It seemed like an urban legend to me, but a lot of people have taken pictures of them here...
Oh, I've heard of it. I've heard of it.
But, it's just a regular biker gang.
Ah, and it's not like they're getting together and causing trouble.
If they're riding around on two wheels with their headlights off, they must be idiots.
That is, if they're human...
What do you mean?
Well... to put it bluntly,
They're like monsters.
Hey.
Um, are you the boss?
There's no way he is.
Then who is he?
Or should I say, aren't you cocky?
We're kinda busy right now, so if you're going to bother us...
would you mind dying?!
Are you kidding me?
Crap!
W-Wait, wait, wait, wait!
S-Stop, stop!
That's why I told you to stop.
Crap. Crap. Crap!
What the hell was that?
What the hell is that thing?!
What do you mean, monsters?
Dotachin says they're death gods.
Dotachin?
Who's Dotachin?
But, you know about men who ride black motorcycles...
Are you just ignoring the Dotachin thing?
Dammit!
I sure showed you! You piece of trash!
There's nothing above their necks...
And despite being completely headless, they can still move.
What the hell are you?
W-What the hell are you?!
STOP
Hey... is there anyone else I should stay away from?
Let's see... There's the obvious like the yakuzas and a few other gangs...
And there's a guy named Orihara Izaya.
Orihara Izaya? That's a weird name.
Don't say that.
That guy is bad news, so don't go anywhere near him.
Well, he's usually in Shinjuku, so I don't think you'll even meet him.
Oh! And, it's also best not to get involved with a group called the Dollars.
Dollars?
Yeah. Dollars, as in One Dollars.
What's “One Dollars”?
I don't know the finer details,
but anyway, there are a lot of them, and it sounds like they're pretty crazy.
They're like the Color Gang, only we don't know what colors they wear.
They can't just meet up without being careful, though,
so they'll eventually break up.
I see.
Hey! Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Ah! Uh... I'm sorry! Are you okay?
Um...
No! No! Ah!
Hey!
What's with her? Not even a “thank you”?
I wonder what happened to her?
Who knows? This is a town where anything can happen, after all.
You're lucky.
Huh?
Just today, you got to meet Kadota-san and the others, and Simon,
plus you got to see Shizuo throwing vending machines and people,
and you ran into that hot girl.
Does that mean I'm lucky?
I'm glad.
Huh?
That I get to go to school with you here, and hang out with you again.
Me too.
You really are lucky!
Huh?
On top of it all, you get to see an urban legend up close!
Kida-kun!
What? You witnessed the black motorcycle, Taro Tanaka-san?
Did it happen to be just past 9 p.m.?
Oh, you know then, Setton-san?
Well, I was there too...
What is this “urban legend”?
The black motorcycle! It's the headless rider!
At that moment, I noticed that I was shaking.
It's not that I was scared. Rather, I think I was moved somehow.
I saw something amazing.
Here, in this town, I experienced something that would be impossible to see anywhere else.
It felt like an impossible reality, which, up until now, I thought was out of reach,
had just revealed itself in front of me.
It may contradict what I said at first, but that's what I was thinking at that moment.
I was shaking with the premonition that my own new reality was beginning.
Really?!
Then we might have passed right by each other without even knowing it!
Yeah, maybe.
By the way,
Who's “Dotachin”?
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time on
Durarara!!
There One Moment, Gone the Next
Somewhere, a girl in the shadows catches a glimpse of a reality she has never seen.
A reality that everyone comes close to, but never finds.
What this girl, who in all reality should have died, saw was...
Next time: There One Moment, Gone the Next.