So, under the Roman Republic,
the tribes occupied the important government offices.
In Rome there was a clear difference between the two castes:
the nobles, called the "patricians",
I'm bored.
and the common folk and farmers, called the "plebs".
The two consuls, the dictator and the three hundred senators
were all chosen from the ranks of the nobles.
The Senate was the highest institute of legislation,
and the popularity of the Sena—
What?
Is that Mr. Omichi from Class A?
I'd say so.
It really is Class A. I wonder what happened?
Who knows? I guess Omichi is just going nuts again.
Is that... Chitanda?
Right.
Let's continue with the class.
Where was I again?
Ah, the Senate.
The Senate was the highest institute of legislation...
Bored, sitting on the windowsill,
I frown at the wind to hide my awkwardness
Hyouka
I nod uncertainly as I shape
the future in my hands feeling mighty
I feel that the wind is bringing change
I guess that's your fault for calling out to my heart
The cloudy sky tells a tale of what's to come
Spread our wings with more courage than ever before
Light and dark are still vague in the distance
but still we want to know the reason behind kindness
No one so far has ever reached
the shining distance far beyond
Let's get there before the past takes it all
To Commit a Grave Sin
Earth Sci. Prep. room
This was all your idea to start with, Fuku!
Mayaka, please calm down.
You shut up, Chi.
I don't care if you had a reason! This is going too far!
Oh right, Mayaka, would you like some cookies?
At least pick up the damn phone!
You can back out if you have to, just give me a call or something!
Uh... Umm...
You do have a phone, don't you?
Should I go get some milk, then?
If it were just me then I wouldn't really care!
Don't make that face! Just listen to me, dammit!
Don't you get the big picture here?!
A reckless person... Chitanda Eru.
Just apologizing to me isn't gonna make this right!
It's ridiculous that someone so smart lacks the most basic consideration!
You can't do a thing about it.
You knew what was going to happen, and still you said nothing!
It was raining, and windy, and it even started to hail!
I bet you wouldn't have noticed even if you showed up,
but I actually bothered to pick some clothes out,
and then I got soaked! Soaked! Do you get that?!
And this is all whose fault? Guess who! It's yours!
Aren't you tired yet?
I kinda am.
At least stop to breathe in between.
Will do.
I didn't do that for your sake.
Wow, you sure know how to get mad.
Is this how you relieve your stress?
If you showed a little consideration I wouldn't get stressed to begin with.
Ah, well...
Still, you should take lessons from Chitanda.
I've never even seen her get angry.
Now that you mention it, I've never seen you or Oreki get angry either.
Fuku does get angry.
Satoshi can get really angry.
Really?
I guess.
I don't do it as enthusiastically as Mayaka,
but sometimes I blow my top.
I can't really imagine you actually getting angry...
I'm only human, you know?
Sometimes I get mad.
He just acts all uppity and tries to hide his emotions.
Really?
Even when he gets mad, he's not scary at all.
Not at all?
Taking me lightly, huh?
I might be... interested in that.
I can totally imagine Chitanda coming up with some scheme to make Satoshi angry.
I expect great things.
Do you get angry too, Oreki?
Oreki? Angry? No way in hell.
Because he's a nice guy, right?
Because he's so pitifully dull that he can't even summon the energy to get angry.
Hey, isn't that a bit too harsh?
Oh, I got angry at that!
Well, Houtarou's lack of emotions aside,
Chitanda's on a totally different level when it comes to not getting angry.
I don't know if it's just a matter of tolerance, but you should try to be
more calm, just like Chitanda.
That's a lot easier said than done.
I could never be as calm as Chi.
Um... You're not praising me, right?
Well, I'd say we kind of are.
They're just making observations. It's not a matter of "good" or "bad".
Actually, as long as it's not because you can't get angry,
being able to stay calm is a good thing.
Anger is a grave sin.
You should treat me better than that, Mayaka.
A sin?
It's one of the seven deadly sins.
That's it! Nice one, Chitanda!
They're pretty famous, so I bet you've heard about them too, right, Mayaka?
Yeah, I know that much at least.
Weren't there 108 sins?
You're thinking of worldly desires.
Whatever.
Um...
Anger, pride, gluttony, greed...
Envy, lust and sloth, right?
That's it!
Sloth, huh?
What're you looking at me for?
But then you're perfect, Chi!
You're hard-working, you don't eat much...
Oh, c'mon...
I can't imagine you being greedy, and you're very diligent.
But...
And you're not... lewd, either.
And you show no signs of envy.
They're not praising her anymore.
It's more like they're making fun of how perfect she is.
Please, stop that!
Besides, sometimes when I get hungry I eat a whole lot!
Yeah, envy doesn't fit her at all.
That's no surprise.
It's time we welcomed Saint Eru!
Her name even sounds like an angel's, right?
Uriel, Gabriel, Chitanda Eriel...
Please, stop it!
She got angry.
She told us off.
Sorry, sorry, Chi!
Whatever.
See, now you've gone and made her mad!
You were totally into it as well!
I don't think that people should never get angry.
That applies to the other deadly sins as well.
For example, I think that pride and greed are also important.
What do you mean?
If someone didn't have any pride,
wouldn't they also be lacking in self-confidence?
If someone was free of greed,
wouldn't they have trouble supporting their family?
And if people didn't envy one another,
wouldn't they stop inventing new things?
Um... You don't have to pay such close attention...
I see. That's pretty interesting.
Moderation in all things, right?
I don't think the concept of "deadly sins" can be applied to our lives that simply.
So you think that getting angry isn't a bad thing?
Yes.
Wouldn't you say that if you can't get angry about anything,
you can't really love anything either?
I can get angry.
But if that's the case, how come you don't get angry?
It's too tiring.
I'd rather save my energy.
Chi-Chitanda's been infected by Houtarou!
An evil spirit is haunting Kamiyama High!
It's known only as... "the low-energy lifestyle"!
Chi, please come to your senses!
Feel free to shut up any time.
I'm just kidding.
Kidding, huh?
And here I thought I'd found my soulmate.
Sorry. It was a spur-of-the-moment thing.
It's not like I never get angry.
I can get angry.
Let's see, for example...
I get angry if I see people wasting food!
Each grain of rice is a drop of sweat!
She's from a family of farmers all right.
That reminds me...
Speaking of getting angry,
weren't you the one who got angry in Omichi's class during fifth period?
That's right!
How could I even forget?
I meant to ask you about it!
Damn.
Can't stop thinking... Can't stop thinking...
Well, I'm gonna head home.
I meant to ask you about it!
Did something happen?
Yes!
During my fifth period math class,
I got angry!
You did?
But I don't understand what made me get angry.
That almost never happens to me at all,
so something must have set me off.
But I don't know what it was!
What?
I don't understand what—
Anyway, I can't stop thinking about it!
A prelude to the scorching days of summer.
Gentle Heat
Hyouka
I had math class during fifth period today.
Mr. Omichi is the teacher.
Oreki and Fukube know what kind of a person he is, I think,
but I'll explain from the beginning anyway.
Um...
He arrived to class right when the bell rung.
Omichi
Before he entered the classroom, he paused for a moment
to check the sign outside.
That's not the first time he's done that, though.
Firstly, he wrote a quadratic equation on the blackboard.
Oh, right.
The equation was quite simple,
Range
but the range of x was restricted.
Omichi
Then, he called on Kawasaki to draw the range of y on the plane.
Kawasaki clearly had trouble with it.
Which made sense,
because we hadn't even covered range in class yet.
Kawasaki said he didn't know.
The teacher got angry when he heard that and started railing at us.
The next person he called was Tamura, who's really good at math,
but he didn't know either.
That was when I realized that he'd forgotten where our class was up to.
The others realized it too, and the classroom got a bit noisy.
The teacher got even angrier and launched into a harsh tirade.
That's right,
he kept hitting the blackboard as if to punctuate his rant.
I think there were people in my class who could've solved the problem,
but everyone kept quiet.
Then he called Tamura again, told him to stand up and started yelling at him.
That's when I stood up.
I asked him to double-check where we were up to in the curriculum.
Right,
that's when I got angry.
Then what happened?
Well, he looked at his book,
mumbled "Oh, I see," and a few words of apology,
told Tamura to sit down, and the rest of the class went on as normal.
He's that kind of teacher, huh?
You can't even imagine how much trouble he caused me after the midterms!
We had teachers like him in elementary and junior high too.
He's not a bad teacher.
And your poor grades aren't his fault.
Try to shape up before finals.
So that's my story. What do you think?
What's strange about it?
Right, I wanted to ask you why he'd make a mistake like that!
He's usually a lot more careful.
That's true.
Omichi is hard on his students, but he's hard on himself as well.
So why would he make such a mistake?
I don't get it.
Neither do I.
Oreki!
I don't know.
If you want to know, go ask him if you can take a look inside his head.
I would've done that already if I could!
I see. Too bad.
Better give up.
But I can't stop thinking about it!
You should think about it as well!
Why me?
I just know you'll be able to figure it out!
Get rid of that can-do attitude.
There's no point expecting so much from him, Chi.
He was a grasshopper in his previous life.
Mayaka, you know about people's past lives?
That got her attention! Good one, Ibara!
But right now, I'm still wondering about today's class.
Dammit. There's no shaking her.
I can't stop thinking about it!
I often see him writing in his notebook after class.
Why do you think he does that?
I think he must be noting down where the class is up to.
I agree.
That's why he double-checks which class is written on the sign beforehand.
It sounds like a foolproof system, so how could he have made that mistake?
If he's taking notes,
I suppose he'd write something like "Page 15, 1st July, Class A".
Otherwise, he'd forget where they were up to.
What if he just read the wrong day's entry?
Then he'd revisit old material, not something new.
Use your brain.
That's right.
Do you mind if I ask you something?
Sure, go on.
I understand why you'd get angry,
but even then you wouldn't normally speak out against a teacher like him.
So why'd you do it?
I got angry,
but I don't think it was because of how mean he was.
Then, was it because the students who could've solved it stayed quiet too?
No,
I don't think anyone would have volunteered at a time like that.
Then, was it because no one else told him that he was wrong?
No...
Could it be because you felt sorry for Tamura?
I did feel sorry for him,
but that wouldn't have made me angry.
After all, it'd be understandable for a teacher to tell off a student
who didn't seem to have learned anything from the previous class.
But I don't know why I got angry.
It's hard to analyze myself like that.
I guess.
What makes Chitanda angry, and what makes her happy?
I don't know her well enough to judge that.
What do you think, Oreki?
Omichi probably does take notes of the class's progress in his book.
And yet, he still made a mistake.
He was ahead of the class,
which means there must have been a note saying the class
was up to a page further on in the textbook.
Your class hasn't studied range yet, right?
That's right.
What if you actually had?
What do you mean?
Omichi teaches math every year.
Last year's 1-A must've learned it by this point.
Sadly, simply getting the year wrong won't cut it as an explanation here.
What do you mean?
The teachers are issued new textbooks every year.
They need to keep up with any minor changes made to the students' editions, after all.
Omichi is using the fourth edition, which was published this year.
I see.
You're a real cornucopia of useless facts, aren't you?
Please, call me a database.
What if Omichi took so many notes that he simply got them mixed up?
No, Chitanda wouldn't believe that.
I don't understand this "range" thing either, though.
I have a hard enough time just writing x and y on a plane.
I'd have a pretty hard time if Omichi called me out.
Wait a moment.
Class D's already learning about range?
Yeah.
So Satoshi's class is already up to range,
but not Chitanda's class or mine.
I see.
Your face says you figured something out.
I guess.
Chitanda.
Yes?
We can say for sure that there was a note specifying a later page in the book.
Yeah, I agree.
And we know that the note related to the progress of a class from this year.
Yes.
Then, what if the note wasn't about your class at all?
What if it was meant to record the progress of Satoshi's class?
My class?
Omichi is teaching classes A, B, C, and D.
Just because it wasn't A or B,
doesn't mean it had to be D.
And what's so special about D?
I wouldn't be surprised if he mistook D for A.
There's no way you could mistake the letter C for an A, though.
Huh? You're just talking nonsense again.
You couldn't mistake the letter D for an A either.
Omichi is a math teacher.
So what?
A math teacher would be more likely to mistake the letter D for A.
Huh?
Oreki Houtarou's drawing
Let's say Omichi wrote "Page 10, 1st July, A" and "Page 15, 1st July, D"...
What if he did?
There's still no room for mistake there.
If he got the A and D confused, that would explain it.
It would, but how could he?
Because a math teacher would write them like this.
Ah, he'd write A and D in lowercase!
I see!
That's possible.
I lost marks on my English exam because the teacher couldn't tell them apart.
Oh? You too, Mayaka?
Though, it was N and H for me.
Yeah. That's definitely possible!
I guess that's it.
A and D...
I can't blame him for getting them confused.
I was too harsh on him, I guess.
I was in the wrong.
Eh, why do you say that?
He was in the wrong! You were right to tell him off!
To begin with, you're—
Come on.
It's already rather late.
Should we get going?
But, Fuku!
Come on, Mayaka.
The mystery's been solved, after all.
That's not it!
Fuku!
Chitanda got angry despite herself,
and wanted to know the reason why.
Despite what she said before about anger not being a bad thing,
in truth, she doesn't want to get angry herself.
Houtarou, Chiatanda, let's get going!
She wanted to know why
because she believed there must have been a reason for Omichi's anger,
Right, I'll tidy up!
and wanted to consider her own anger to be her fault alone.
That's the kind of thing Chitanda Eru would do, right?
Nah,
what do I even know about Chitanda in the first place?
Even if I can predict what she'll do,
I can't actually figure out what's going on in her head.
I know what this is all about.
One of the seven deadly sins...
Pride.
I gotta remember to be more careful.
How many times has she surprised me
just in this one day?
Oreki!
Aren't you going home?
Oh, right. I am.
Oreki,
thank you.
You're always helping me out with my troubles.
Now if only someone could help me with mine...
What are you two doing?
Aren't you coming as well?
Yeah, we're leaving now!
Shall we?
I'll just deal with the rest tomorrow.
Oreki!
That's true for you, Mayaka, but think about it for a moment.
And thus, another day of my high school life was wasted.
As for my deadly sins,
sloth is more than enough for me.
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
This sprouting warmth confuses us
Don't you understand this feeling yet?
Normally such random glances hold no meaning
Isn't it the same when making friends?
The little shooting stars we wish upon, vanishing into the dawn
are a magic that only unfolds in the night
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
Next time: True Colors.
True Colors