Vanilla salt
When I try to show some weakness
my other side rears up and all I do is act pointlessly strong
In truth, I'm a little crybaby
I'm not saying that out loud, though
My, lobster is such beautiful thing.!
I beg of you!
Hot!
That day,
I learned the sacred art of making a boxed lunch.
Pre! Preparation!
I'm not strong but
Pre! Pre-parade!
but I'm gonna catch you one of these days
When you let your guard down,
I'm gonna tickle you silly! Prepare yourself!
I may be small,
but I can still pluck you like a flea
I'm longing for a plastic heart
Plus, plus, somehow a minus
But the one who realizes how boring that'd be will win
Love is so bittersweet
Plain and simple while complicated and mysterious
You get worried about the most pointless things
How does it feel?
That's how it feels
You're gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
I act tough as we cross swords
I get dizzy whenever I try to be honest with myself
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation!
In my mind,
I'm always alone on an
innocent pre-parade
Sacred Art of Making a Boxed Lunch
It’s good once in a while, don’t you think?
I love how we four gays can get together like this for lunch.
It’s guys, you know.
And there's not four of us either.
Besides, where is Lord Kitamura?
He's the one who brought this up.
Thanks for waiting!
I'm sorry. I had to go get this from the Student Council room
because I couldn't fit it in my locker.
What... What is this?
Could it be...
I-Is this your boxed lunch?
That's right.
So then I...
Really now? You gotta be joking!
Nobody would bring a boxed lunch like that!
H-Hey, Haruta. It's not polite to make fun of someone's lunch—
It looks like something out of a comic book!
Wait till you see what's inside!
What's going on here?
Let Uncle have a look—
Minorin?
What's this? Maruo is having a feast!
Huh? What are we celebrating?
Wow, that lobster's antennae are so long!
Does this 39 mean...
It's all for Yusaku?!
Exactly!
Your grandma made this, didn't she, Yusaku?
Really? Your grandma made all of this?
Yeah. My parents are on a business trip in Guam.
So, while they're gone, my grandma's staying with me.
This awesome looking lunch is... handmade?
She got a little too enthusiastic, and made these.
She loves her grandson, doesn't she?
I appreciate the thought, but this is really too much.
So, I wanted you guys to help me.
Huh?
Are you sure we can have some?
Seriously?
Of course!
Cool!
She'd rather have it all finished, so why not?
What should I try first?
Oh, I suppose you girls will be okay with this.
Let's dig in!
Is this for real? It's so good!
Amazing!
I wouldn't expect any less from Yusaku's grandma.
So tasty! I guess there's always room for dessert!
What's up? Have some, Takasu!
S-Sure. I'll have this fried chicken, then.
T-Taiga?
What's the matter, Aisaka?
You can have some too.
T-Then I'll...
I'll have some lobster.
You're amazing! How can you be so bold?!
I thought you were holding back, but you were really aiming for the main dish?
This has nothing to do with you!
Yeah, but still...
That's the spirit! Please eat up!
Amazing! Each bite tastes better than the last!
I am so, so happy!
Hey, did you eat your own lunch yet?
Of course I did! But lobster goes to a different stomach!
The taste is out of this world!
It doesn't just look good!
The flavor is perfect too!
Takasu.
Yeah?
Can I take a picture of your boxed lunch with my phone?
What?
Well, I want to let my grandma know what a normal boxed lunch should look like.
Oh, but I was in a rush this morning so I didn't make it really well...
It's fine, really.
Great! Thanks, Takasu.
I don't... I don't want her to think...
Hey, everyone, please eat more!
All right!
Lobsters are so dumb.
that this is the best I can do.
If they weren't so delicious, they wouldn't get eaten so much.
Crabs too, right?
Damn you, Yusaku. I ate too much.
K-Kawashima!
H-Hey!
Huh? What is it?
Kitamura's grandma...
Is she a cooking teacher or a chef or something?
She must be a professional?
Right?
Huh?
I think she's just an ordinary housewife.
Ordinary... housewife?
I think so, yeah.
Anyways, what's her name?
What? Why do you think I would know—
What's that face for?!
Huh?
Your evil mug startled me!
Oh, I remember her name now.
It's Miyo.
"Mi" is written like in "the year of the snake".
Miyo, eh?
Let me see what's the best boxed lunch you can make!
I accept your challenge!
Come at me, Miyo!
Hey, are you sure you're all right?
Kitamura!
Let's eat lunch together!
Your grandma made your lunch again, didn't she?
Yeah, but...
See? It's a normal one today.
Precisely. It should be cheap and easy to make,
but enough to make a high school student's stomach full.
Now that we're both abiding by the same rules, this will be a fair fight!
Let's see now...
Something wrong?
Okay. Bring it on, Miyo!
Oh, I'm jealous, Takasu.
You brought cutlets today!
Yeah, these are just leftover cutlets from yesterday's dinner.
I just wrapped them in egg really quickly this morning.
Oh, I see. Well, what do I have today?
So, what do you have?
Did you use expensive ingredients out of your love for your grandson, even though they're against the rules?
Is it a caviar bowl? Or a shark fin bowl?
Huh?
It's pretty basic.
I did ask her to make something simple like rice balls. I guess she took it too far.
That's...
That's too small! It can't possibly be enough for a high school student!
I've won— Wait!
That shining sparkle on the seaweed paper! Sesame oil!
That means...
Wait, that's...!
This is delicious!
There's grilled beef inside! What a surprise!
This is Korean seaweed.
Yeah, I like this kind of boxed lunch!
Oh, this one has dried plum in it!
What about this one?
Yay! Tuna and mayonnaise! My favorite!
She got him to exclaim in joy.
The grilled beef to surprise him,
followed by the classic dried plum,
and finishing with his favorite, tuna and mayonnaise.
It was a perfect combination to stimulate every tastebud.
Mine is just sweet broth.
It's just the same...
monotonous...
flavor.
Ryuji!
Thanks a lot.
That cutlet with egg was delicious.
Oh, thanks.
Wow! Those rice balls look really good!
Maybe we should have rice balls for dinner tonight.
Last night's cutlets were really delicious, but having them two days in a row was a bit too much.
Y-Yeah, I know.
But we had cutlets left over from dinner, so I had to...
No, this isn't good.
I have to make an exquisite lunch if I want to compete with Miyo.
But I needed to follow the rules.
That's why I needed an excuse like using last night's leftovers.
That's why I made cutlets last night!
Just to have some leftovers for today's lunch!
A true housewife thinks of cooking in terms of continuity!
I might have overdone it yesterday, but today I'm back on track!
Ah! Miyo!
What the hell?! By her first name?!
Boxed lunch...
What to do...?
What should I put in...?
Boxed lunch...
Hey, what should we put in the rice balls?
I'm thinking salmon,
but I prefer the regular kind over the salted ones...
Rice balls, for real?
How do you expect me win if I copy Kitamura?!
Huh?
I'm not talking about today's dinner here, not your boxed lunch.
I couldn't care less about dinner right now!
I... I was so proud of my housekeeping skills!
So proud...
But I'm stuck at the varsity level.
The competition is just too steep in the professional scene.
I'm akin to the frog in the well that knew nothing of the ocean.
Thrown into the vast ocean of the pro scene,
a shark called Miyo suddenly—
Hmm, dried tuna sounds good, too.
Hey, what are you doing?!
What are you talking about?
I'm taking care of shopping since you're being a lazy-ass..
Shopping?
But all you put in the cart are snacks and pudding.
Hey! I put in dried tuna too!
That's our dessert.
Did you know? I heard that if you put soy sauce on pudding, it tastes like melon!
That myth is old, and besides you got it wrong.
Really? Is that so?
Hmm, was it watermelon instead of melon?
I can't waste any more time...
That's it!
What do frogs have that sharks don't?
Or was it miso... on tofu, maybe?
It's of course...
Youth!
Yo, Taiga!
Hey, do you know where Kitamura—
You know you're supposed to fill it up to 5mm beneath the line.
No more, no less!
It's getting there soon! Almost there!
Oh, shut up.
You usually always give me crap for eating these things.
What's that? Cup noodle?
Oh, Minorin.
I see you've brought a electrical water boiler as well!
I see.
Far out!
Ain't that cool, you two are ballers!
What? Are you guys having cup noodles for lunch?
I'm so jealous. I'm so bored of cold lunch.
That smells really nice!
It looks so good!
I bet it's really tasty!
It may be ordinary if you eat it at home...
But on the schoolgrounds it becomes something else entirely.
Bringing a ray of joy to the lunchtable...
There's no way Kitamura's grandma would have this kind of youthful and innovative idea!
Today's match...
is in the bag!
Minorin, why can't we have lunch together today?
Oh sorry, I have a lunch meeting scheduled with the club today.
Hey, hey!
Kitamura, man!
Let's head out soon, man!
Sorry, sorry!
Yo, Kitamura.
I accidentally overslept today, so we're having cup noodles for lunch.
What. So you have hot water?
Oh, yeah.
Do you mind if I use some?
Thanks dude!
Grandma handed me a cup of instant onion soup today.
She said that there must be someone at school eating cup noodle,
so I could just mooch some hot water from them.
I thought it was kind of a stretch, but you timed it perfectly!
Today's lunch will be soup and some sandwiches.
It'll be easy to eat during the meeting, don't you think?
Hey, Kitamura!
Thanks for waiting, Kushieda!
Let's go!
See you later, Taiga.
All right.
Sandwiches sound good right now.
Then don't eat your noodles.
What?
In fact, we shouldn't eat it!
Gimme that!
What are you doing!
What?
Don't eat it! Just don't eat it!
What are they doing?
You're making no sense at all!
You shouldn't eat it! I'm saying just don't!
They are probably not getting enough Calcium from just cup noodles.
Hot!
Coming!
Thanks for waiting!
It's so puny...
Oh, so puny...
Or so it seems...
But!
I piled 'em up high on a separate plate!
Thanks, Minorin!
Don't thank me! If it isn't enough, just ask!
I would stack them even higher, and higher...
till it reaches the sky!
Yep!
Are you sure about eating so many carbs so soon after school?
Cup noodles aren't enough to fill me up!
Besides, I didn't even get to eat it...
You know...
The lunch Ryuji usually makes is fine in my book,
but he's trying too hard these days.
Oh, Taiga, you poor thing!
You can no longer live without the food Ryuji Takasu feeds you!
What?!
Calm down!
Food is the basis of life itself, so no wonder you came to love his cooking.
In any case, you're welcome to stay as long as you wish!
Boxed lunches, huh...
No. This is wrong.
This just isn't right.
This isn't how it should be done...
Whoa, it's like having a party!
They all look so delicious!
But I can't eat this much, you know.
Where is Taiga?
No idea.
Oh, can I take some to work with me?
Mr. Yaegashi is divorcing his wife, you see.
I'm sure he would love your cooking!
Your dishes are all so delicious!
I'm off!
I guess I should get some food, too.
Delicious!
Oh, looks like she's back.
Why doesn't she come over to eat dinner if she's back?
She must still be sulking about lunch today.
I shouldn't worry about her.
I have to prepare the best boxed lunch ever in order to defeat Kitamura Miyo!
If that means dirtying my hands, then so be it...
For example, I could put some curry in a rice triangle.
Or keep raw fish in a cooler
and arrange them on rice to make a seafood bowl.
Or, I could make a variety of small but colourful snacks.
Hey! Don't make it sound like you're eating leftovers!
Seconds, please!
You want more?!
No, that's not that point!
Leftover...?
Leftover... I tried using leftovers when I made the cutlets.
Then this time, I'll make something fresh out of the oven!
Yes, that must be the only way!
Cheating?
You dumb parrot, you can say whatever you like.
Inzaghi.
Who cares about him?
Filippo Inzaghi.
That's right.
I don't care if people think it's cheating.
I'm going to cross the line!
H-H-Hot, h-h-h-h-hot!
"The Hayabusa bullet train debuts
March 5 on the Touhoku Shinkansen Line,
thrilling rail fans and people living in northern— "
Hmm?
This smell...?
What is this?
What?
Is this...
This sound... but it can't be...
It can't possibly be...
But...
A rice cooker?
For real?
Really?
Now that you mentioned it,
I smell something really nice...
It smells really delicious...
Now I'm getting hungry...
So... why did you do this, Takasu?
Takasu?
Hey bro, don't cook rice in the classroom, yo.
This is too funny!
Wait everyone! Teacher, you too!
How do you even know it's mine?!
Don't accuse me from the get-go!
But you're the only one who would do a thing like that!
All right, I am the one who did it!
I apologize, teach, please don't unplug it!
I-It's almost done cooking!
Please don't!
No!
What?! What's going on in here?!
You moron...
It's over now...
What a waste...
If you switched the power back on, you could still finish it, right?
Boiling it twice would reduce the flavor...
Reduce the flavor?
You already hit rock bottom, man.
Taste of Fall...
Maitake mushrooms, hiratake mushrooms... filled with mushrooms...
I thought I could snatch a  win with freshly made mixed rice...
That's not even a boxed lunch anymore...
I know...
I said that there should be rules,
but I was the one who broke them and got myself disqualified...
You didn't get disqualified.
You just got a little too excited and went over the top.
Here.
I guessed ahead of time that you wouldn't prepare anything decent,
so I'm giving this to you, you stupid dog lost in thought.
These...
You made these, all by yourself?
Of course I did!
Even I can make something as easy as rice balls.
You taught me once before.
Hot!
Cooked rice is like a weapon of mass destruction or something!
Deal with it!
If it's not hot, it won't be as fluffy.
Hey!
What?
I have no intention of giving them to someone who doesn't want them.
Of course I want them!
Let me have one now!
How is it?
Y-Yeah...
Why are you shaking like that?
Too much salt!
Pour some broth on it...
That should make it less salty.
Come on, hurry up!
Just wait a bit.
Put some parsley in it...
Here you go.
Thanks for the food!
Hey, you should break the rice ball up more...
Delicious!
This is so good!
The dried plum makes a wonderful accent!
I'm a frickin' genius!
Now I get it...That's how it is...
I'm a genius?
Yep.
Although the first comic book styled lunch was an exception...
Actually, that one as well...
Miyo's lunches were all made to make Kitamura happy.
The rice balls were at Kitamura's request.
The onion soup was because she knew he had a lunch meeting.
All of her attention was focused on making Kitamura happy.
I, on the other hand...
Thanks for the meal.
You really are the only one who I can prepare lunch for after all.
What?
What are you saying?
Eating this just made me even hungrier.
I want to eat something more filling now.
Hmm, maybe I could eat some cutlets now!
What do you think of cutlets with boiled rice and tea?
Cutlets for the third time in a week?
Well, I have some leftover sliced meat...
That's it: Mille-feuille cutlet!
Let's reheat that mixed rice too;
I want to eat it with other dishes.
All right, let's do it.
Aren't you going to put some tea on the rice balls?
Eh, I'm going to eat them as their are.
It caught me by surprise at that time, but it's not like I can't eat them.
Okay...
Wait, did you just say something rude to me?
Really? I don't think I did.
No, you definitely did!
Apologize by putting some cheese in the cutlet!
What?
I learned the secret of making a good boxed lunch.
A lunch made for someone...
made for someone you care about...
is always...
delicious, no matter what's inside.
Add vanilla salt
Burning Love
If it's too sweet,
we can add some salt
I tell you all these things because
I want you to know me better than anyone else
But nothing works when I have no experience
This is so frustrating
But a love that's purely sweet
isn't quite the love I'm looking for
If you say "white,"
then I say "black"
A small child
who can't be honest with herself
If you say "love,"
then I say "hate"
Why do I say that when I'm actually happy?
It's like adding salt
to sweet vanilla