Narezushi isn't too common here on Hitogashima.
I haven't tried it yet.
Have you?
Huh?
This woman...
I saw her on the ferry!
Th-The shadow...
It's gone!
Amazing.
Do ya have eyes in the back of yer head?
How...
I-It can't be.
Did she really defeat a shadow?
Nice to meet you, I guess.
I lived here as a child, but I've never had narezushi.
I wonder how it tastes.
Who are you?
Oh, how rude of me.
I'm Nagumo Ryuunosuke.
Nagu—
Huh?
Ryuunosuke?
I came to save you.
I'm sorry I took so long,
Ajiro Shinpei.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Maelstrom
N-Nagumo...
This way!
Wh-What?!
It's a shadow.
Ushio!
I told her to stay put!
Wait. It's too dangerous up there.
Shadows are gathering there.
C-Can you tell which are human and which are shadows?
Shadows only wear a lump of flesh in the shape of a human.
Look at the ground.
Their true form is the flat shadow on the ground.
They hate it when people walk on their shadow.
If you try to step on it, just the shadow will move.
I'm going off my sister's hypothesis here,
but I think shadows use light to scan humans and absorb information.
I believe they use this in order to feed.
Shadows live by consuming information about humans.
However, they need to directly eat the flesh for the flavor.
Look.
That stain is from when they ate a human body.
We happen to be targeted by these shadows.
This goes for you too.
The shadows keep increasing,
regardless of how many I've killed these past three days.
It feels as if they're being controlled.
Like they're all working toward a single goal.
A goal.
"In no time, Mother will wake up."
What was that light?
You can kill shadows with that gun, right,
Ms. Nagumo?
That's your name, isn't it?
You're the writer.
Oh, uh... yes.
I knew it!
Please help me!
I have a lot I want to ask you another time, but right now,
Mio and my friends are up there!
Ajiro Shinpei.
Will he really save everyone, Sis?
Toki!
Shinpei?
Thank goodness.
Where is everyone?
Where is Mio?
Toki—
I'm so sorry.
Not this...
I didn't get my hands dirty for this.
Toki?
Stop. Step back.
It is almost nine.
The festival is finished.
I shall bring this final day to an end.
On the shrine grounds,
the humid night air was polluted with the rank odor of blood.
A mountain of corpses of villagers and tourists.
You shall not impede me.
One...
Three...
Five...
Seven...
nine...
Eleven...
I couldn't help but count.
Even my frozen brain could do that.
And...
Sou!
Mio...
R-Run away.
Well, ain't this moving!
Sacrificing his life fer ya.
My love fer ya sure was the real deal!
N-No.
But you were always the same.
Shin this, Shin that.
Sou...
Mio!
What?
That was dangerous.
If you are interfering with this holy ceremony,
you must have defeated Mio.
So you're the boss.
Wh-Who...
Who the hell are you?!
Your right eye.
I knew it.
The right eye Mother lost long ago.
Why do you have the original one?
Perhaps it is possible to reproduce time with that.
Let go of me!
C'mon, now.
What's this?
Don't struggle.
Yer on our team.
No!
I'm a human!
Kofune Ushio!
Idiot.
Yer no human.
Humans ain't capable of instantly recovering from a broken arm.
In order for the boss to defeat the hero who can restart from a save point,
the only solution is to cut off
the power to the game console.
What if a virtual game boss understood a real concept such as electricity?
Watch closely,
Shinpei.
Watch the moment I cut off the power.
No!
Let go!
I'm not one of y'all!
Shinpei!
Take care of Mio!
Mio!
M-Mio...
Mi...
Shin.
Wait for me.
I'm...
Shin...
...coming...
No! Mio!
Mio!
No!
Don't touch her!
Leave Mio alone!
The last meal.
Please eat to your heart's content.
That massive shadow...
Will it merely touching me be enough to swallow me up?
I was the one who was useless, Ryuunosuke.
It seems I was too late.
Give your last ounce of strength to me,
Mother!
Summer Time Rendering
Nothingness lies ahead.
What is that, Mom?
What is that?
Huh?
Hishigata Clinic
It seems she ate a thousand humans...
and was revived.
Look.
The island is being swallowed up by the shadows.
Haine.
Ah.
Delicious.
This is my ending.
S-Sorry...
Mio...
Everyone...
I'm sorry, Shinpei.
If I'd only believed that message earlier...
I was too late.
Far too late.
No!
"I should've done this back then."
"Why did I say that?"
All I had were regrets.
Constant regrets.
But I have no regrets now.
Not yet.
It's not too late yet!
Ms. Nagumo!
Shoot me!
Kill me!
I can redo this if I die!
Shoot my head!
You really say some crazy things.
I can return to the 22nd!
It is futile.
This is my last shot, you know?
Please trust me!
You will just be swallowed up too.
You...
dummy!
If you really can go back,
tell me your name,
and I'll save you.
Darkness.
All gone.
No one is here.
They disappeared.
This scene...
Have I taken a bird's-eye view again?
Stop...
Stop it...
Please stop!
The island...
What is that red light?
A girl?
Our eyes met.
Shinpei.
Ushio?
Ushio?!
Be careful.
There's a limit to the power.
Everyone dies at the summer festival.
I can hear ya clearly this time.
Ushio, where are ya?!
Yer the only one who can stop 'em.
Take care of Mio.
How's Tokyo?
Ya been to Shibuya?! Have ya?!
July 22nd
Shin?
I'm back...
Sh-Shin!
I did it.
Do ya got the chills from falling in the sea?
Mio is alive!
Did ya hit something?
Sh-Shin?
Thank goodness.
I'm okay.
Just a little seasick from the ferry.
My clothes are soaked.
Right.
I fell in the sea when I tried to stop Mio's bike.
She had to save me.
Ya look kinda pale.
Let's rest fer a bit at home after we change clothes.
Thank goodness our phones are okay.
We can't go to the funeral all wet like this.
Ushio told me that there was a limit to the power.
Bistro Kofune
Take a bird's-eye view and look at everything that's happened.
First time was on the ferry.
Second time was after landing.
Third time was after I met Mio.
The starting point for the loop is gradually getting later.
The events that happen before I wake up become fixed.
Toki comes over to do
Mio's yukata.
Sou and Mio come to my room.
Mio, Sou, and Toki and I go
to the summer festival.
Leave from Otomo Beach.
Trek to shrine. View procession.
Explore shops until fireworks.
Get Mio's favorite, candied apple.
Run into Mio's shadow on the
shrine stairs. My shadow.
Nagumo defeats Mio's
shadow with a shotgun.
Go into the shrine with Nagumo
Loop for 3rd time
In other words, there is no way I won't fall into the sea.
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
If I wake up again, it'll be at an even later time.
I can't fail endlessly.
If the starting point comes after Mio and the others are killed,
I won't be able to save them, even if I restart the loop.
Three days.
Three days until the summer festival.
Can I really solve this in just three days?
No.
What am I saying?
Yer the only one who can stop 'em.
I will do it.
July 22nd
Huh?
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Orbital Resonance