It's over!
Homura-chan...
You...
Wh-What the hell did you just do?!
I see. You're that irregularity, huh?
That's some strange magic you've got there.
Get out of the way!
Sayaka-chan!
She's okay. She's just unconscious.
Who are you?
Whose side are you on?
I'm an ally to those who maintain their composure,
and an enemy to idiotic aggressors.
Which are you, Sakura Kyouko?
Wha—
Have we met before?
I wonder.
Not when I haven't a clue
what you've got up your sleeve.
I'll back down for today.
That's wise of you.
You... saved us?
How many times must I warn you?
Just how big of a fool are you?
I have warned you countless
times not to get involved, correct?
But I...
I will not hold back against a fool.
Homura-chan... Why?
At any rate, it's obvious she's planning something.
Be on your toes.
Akemi Homura, could you be...
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I still see it when I close my eyes
oshiyoseta yami
押し寄せた闇
I'll move forward as I cast off
furiharattesusumu yo
振り払って進むよ
this darkness engulfing me
MEGUCA
PRESENTS
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
How long will it be before
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I see that lost future again?
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
I'll walk upon this Earth,
nandodemo saite
何度でも裂いて
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
kono sekai ayundekou
この世界歩んでこう
as many times as necessary
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
toki wa ima hajimaritsuge
時は今始まり告げ
now tells of the beginning
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Let's open the once-closed door,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
with these unwavering feelings
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
muzukashii michi de tachidomatte mo
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
sora wa kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
dakara kowakunai
だから怖くない
So I won't be afraid
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Episode 6
This is definitely wrong
Miki
Now you should be fine for a while.
Wow, it's pitch black.
It's dangerous now. If you taint it any further, a witch might hatch.
It's fine. Give it to me.
It's harmless now.
You ate it?!
That's just another one of my duties.
But in order to keep your Soul Gem pure, you'll need to find a new Grief Seed.
Is it really that important to keep it clean?
Sakura Kyouko was strong, right?
If you have spare Grief Seeds,
you could let loose and waste as much magic as you want in any fight.
That's what makes
.Kyouko so powerful.
But that doesn't mean you can just sacrifice innocent people to get Grief Seeds.
The more you use your magic,
.the more it taints your Soul Gem.
Sayaka, you'll never stand a chance against Kyouko without collecting Grief Seeds.
You think?
Mami-san never had enough Grief Seeds either,
yet she was still able to fight just fine.
Are some magical girls just more talented?
Some definitely are.
Oh, come on!
That's not fair at all!
There's nothing you can do about it.
Kyouko's talented, and she's got the experience to back it up.
But there are prodigies with potential to surpass Kyouko, even without any experience.
Like who?
Kaname Madoka.
Madoka?
Really?
Yeah.
That's why if you really want an edge in your fight with Kyouko, you could always ask her.
That is, if she makes a contract with me.
No, I can't.
This is my fight.
I can't get her involved.
A Note to Customers
Please do not eat or drink while playing.
Entry for the purpose of hitting on people,
solicitation, or otherwise attempting to take
customers to other locales
is strictly forbidden.
Yo. What do you want this time?
I want to leave this city to you.
What's with the sudden change of heart?
Girls like you are fit to be magical girls.
Miki Sayaka is not qualified.
Hmph, that was my plan
from the start, anyway.
But what about that Sayaka girl?
If you just leave her be,
she'll definitely butt in again.
I want to end this as
peacefully as possible.
Stay out of it. I'll take care of this.
You still haven't told me the most important thing, though.
Who the heck are you?
What's in this for you?
The Walpurgisnacht will descend upon
this city two weeks from today.
How do you know that?
That's a secret.
Anyway, once it's defeated, I'll leave this city.
You can do what you want after that.
The Walpurgisnacht, huh?
That'd be pretty hard to handle alone, but we might win if we teamed up.
Want some?
It's no use. Too much time has passed.
I don't see any clues that will lead us to the familiar from last night.
I see...
Hey, Sayaka-chan.
If we keep hunting witches, won't we run into that girl from yesterday?
Yeah, I guess we can't avoid it.
Maybe you should go find her and try to talk things over.
If you don't, you'll end up fighting again before you know it.
A fight, huh?
Did last night look like a normal fight to you?
That was definitely a fight to the death.
Only the first few blows weren't lethal.
Halfway through, we were both
seriously trying to finish each other off.
But... that's even worse!
And you want me to
try to "talk it over"?
Don't be stupid.
She's trying to use human beings as bait just to get more Grief Seeds.
How am I supposed to get
along with someone like that?
Sayaka-chan, you became a
magical girl to fight witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch.
She's a magical girl like you!
If you give her a chance, I'm sure you'll find a way to become friends.
She does things differently, but she's
also trying to hunt down witches, right?
Just like you.
And Homura-chan too.
If Mami-san hadn't
..fought with Homura-chan...
That wouldn't have happened!
You saw her, didn't you?
She waited for Mami-san to get killed before she came to defeat the witch!
She let Mami-san die because she wanted the Grief Seed!
That's not what happened...
That transfer student
.is the same as Kyouko!
They only think about themselves!
But I understand that now.
Mami-san was an exception.
All the other magical girls
are like those two!
No...
That familiar from last night might've been small, but it could still kill someone!
And who knows, its next target could even be your parents!
Maybe even Takkun!
Can you still say you don't care?
Can you forgive someone
.if they just let that happen?
I'm not just fighting against witches.
I wanted this power to fight to protect the people I care about.
That's why I'll fight anyone
worse than the witches.
Even if that person is
another magical girl.
Sayaka-chan...
Kyubey, say something to her...
The only thing I can tell her is
.that she's being too reckless.
Sayaka currently has no chance of winning against Akemi Homura or Sakura Kyouko.
But she won't listen to me.
Settings
Menu
Automatic
Bath
Reheat
Fill the Bath
Time Settings
Timer
Fill the Bath
Time Settings
Timer
Reheat
Fill the Bath
Time Settings
Timer
Welcome Home
There's some potato salad in the fridge
Tomo
Can't sleep?
No. Can we talk?
A friend of mine is in a tough situation.
What she's doing and
saying probably isn't wrong,
but the more she tries to do
.what's right, the worse it gets.
That happens a lot.
It sucks, but you can't expect a happy ending just by doing what's right all the time.
Actually, the more people get stubborn and insist that they're in the right,
the farther away happiness gets.
It's not fair if you can't be happy even
though you're not doing the wrong things.
Yeah.
What do you think I should do?
That's not a problem that can be
.solved by someone not involved.
Do you want to solve this, even if it's not the nicest way to do it?
Yeah.
All you have to do is
make a mistake for her.
Huh?
Somebody has to be in the wrong to
.balance out her need to be in the right.
Do something wrong?
Tell a white lie, or run
.away from something scary.
Sometimes you realize that was
.actually the best choice in the end.
Sometimes when you hit a dead end with no real alternatives,
making a big mistake is an option.
But do you think she'll understand that I'm doing it for her own good?
She may or may not.
Especially at first.
I told you it might not
.be the nicest way to do it.
But would you rather give up on her,
or give her the wrong idea about you?
Madoka, you grew up
to be a good girl.
You don't lie, and you
.don't do anything bad.
You're always trying
.hard to do what is right.
You're already a wonderful child.
That's why you should start learning how to make mistakes before you grow up.
Learning how to make mistakes?
You recover from injury
.faster when you're young.
If you learn how to fall down now, it'll be easier for you later on.
When you get older,
making mistakes gets harder.
The more things you're responsible for, the less mistakes you can make.
I see.
Isn't that hard?
Being an adult is hard for everybody.
That's why they let you drink.
I want to grow up and drink with you.
Hurry up and get older. As difficult as it is, it's fun being an adult.
Oh, Kamijou-san was released from the hospital yesterday.
His rehabilitation was going well, so his schedule was moved up.
I-I see...
Kamijou
Going home without even seeing him?
You've been chasing him around all day.
You...
I know all about it. The little rich boy who lives here, right?
The one you made a contract with Kyubey for.
Christ. You wasted your only chance for a miracle on something that stupid?
Kamijou
What would you know?!
A hell of a lot more than you, dummy.
Magic is only supposed to be used to grant wishes for yourself.
No good comes out of
.using it for someone else.
Didn't Tomoe Mami even
teach you that much?
Kamijou
There are better ways of making a guy you love fall for you.
After all, you've got
.all that magic now.
Wh-What?
Just go in there and break his hands and legs so bad, he'll never be able to use them again.
Make him so helpless that he won't
.be able to do anything without you.
Do that, and he'll be
.yours and yours alone.
Both his body and his heart.
Kamijou
If you don't have the guts,
then I could do it for you.
Just think of it as a favor
.to my fellow magical girl.
It's no sweat.
I will... never forgive you.
I'll take you down this time...
Let's take this some place else, then.
We wouldn't want to attract a crowd.
Somebody has to be in the wrong to
.balance out her need to be in the right.
But how could I...
Madoka!
Hurry! Sayaka's in trouble!
Follow me!
We won't have to hold back here.
It's party time.
Wait! Sayaka-chan!
M-Madoka!
Don't get in the way.
This isn't even any of your business.
No, this is definitely wrong!
Hmph. Annoying jerks sure
attract annoying friends.
I wonder what sort of
.friends you have, then.
Damn.
This isn't what we agreed on.
I thought I told you to keep
.your hands off of Miki Sayaka.
Your method wouldn't
get the message across!
She's not backing down either way.
I'll take her on, then. Stay out of it.
You've got until I finish eating this.
That's plenty of time.
Don't underestimate me!
Sayaka-chan, I'm sorry!
Madoka, what the hell?!
But if I hadn't...
Sayaka-chan?
That was bad, Madoka.
How could you just throw
away your friend like that?
Are you crazy?
What... What are you saying?
Stop it!
What the hell is this...
She's dead!
Sayaka-chan?
Hey, Sayaka-chan?
Wake up! Say something! What's wrong?
I don't want this to happen!
Sayaka-chan!
What the hell is going on?
Hey!
You magical girls can only control your
.bodies from 100 meters away, at most.
100 meters?!
What the hell does that mean?
You normally carry them with you, so accidents like this are rare.
What are you saying, Kyubey?
Save her! Don't let Sayaka-chan die!
Madoka, that isn't Sayaka.
It's just an empty shell.
You just threw Sayaka away.
Wh-What...?
I couldn't just ask you to fight
.witches with a fragile human body.
A magical girl's old body is nothing
.more than a piece of external hardware.
Your actual soul is given a much safer,
compact form that is capable of controlling magic much more efficiently.
It's part of my job, when I complete a magical girl's contract.
I extract your souls and
.turn them into Soul Gems.
What the hell did you do to us?
You bastard! You basically
turned us into zombies!
Isn't it more convenient?
Even if your heart is torn to shreds, or you lose every drop of blood,
your body can be fixed in
no time with magical healing.
You're basically invincible, provided that your Soul Gem is intact.
Isn't that far more advantageous than
fighting with a human body full of vital organs?
That's terrible... That's too awful.
You're all the same.
You always react like this when
.you're told what's really going on.
I just don't get it.
Why are humans so touchy about the placement of their souls?
What?
What's wrong?
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
One day the light of love burning in your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki wo koete
will transcend time
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume wo
and destroy one of this world's dreams
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
as it spirals toward the apocalypse
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai wo nomihoshite
What is it that you seek
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani?
now that you're done hesitating?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
Is there a glimpse of hope for tomorrow
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no?
beyond this greedy admiration?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
I want to be armed with the power
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no youni
to shatter even the darkness in my hand,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
just like the ancient magic in my childhood dreams,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
the next time I see your innocent smile.
微笑む君に合いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In my trembling hands I hold
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
the courage of a plucked flower
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings are all I can rely on;
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari wo yobisamasu
the prayer that awakens
光を呼び覚ます
negai
the light
願い
Illustrated by   Hajime Ueda
You had a wish important enough to commit yourself to a life of battle, did you not?
And your wish came true, didn't it?
Episode 7
Can you accept your true feelings?