The spear!
Regina!
Begone, Precures!
I won't give in...
Until my feelings reach your heart...
I'll stay standing, Regina!
Aww, they ran away.
Why?
None of us could even touch the spear of light.
Could it be...
Hey!
that she's not a Selfish?
Are you listening?
Yes?
I'm hungry.
Get me a noodle sub.
Get the lead out!
Right away!
Oh, she's selfish, all right...
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
I'm glad the Lovely Pad was able to take us back, but...
We didn't expect to have one of the Sacred Treasures stolen out from under us.
We must defeat Regina immediately and recover the spear of light.
Wait.
I won't fight Regina.
Mana!
I'm sure those dark feelings were just planted inside her!
That again?
Not even my Ace Shot could purify her!
She's King Selfish's daughter through and through.
Attempting to reconcile with one who knows no love is—
Right there!
Regina said she loved her daddy.
She believes in him with all her heart.
Doesn't that mean that she knows love too?
Feelings can reach anyone who has love.
That's what I believe.
Very well.
I won't press the matter for now.
Regardless, it seems our Lovely Pad hides yet another mysterious power.
I expect you all to put forth the effort to master it.
Understand?
Getting Our Feelings Across!
Makopi Announces Her New Song!
It seems Aguri feels responsible for letting the spear get stolen.
I think I know how she feels.
I was the one to lose my temper last time.
Compared to you two, Mana seems pretty unfazed.
That's because of how strongly she believes in Regina.
Mana's trust never wavered once.
But me?
I held a grudge against her before.
But now...
I think I understand Mana's point of view.
Doesn't that mean that she knows love too?
I want to believe in Regina too.
But what can I do to help myself do so?
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning.
Morning, Haruna.
What's this?
Fan letters.
Good for you!
They're yours!
You even reading them?
Of course.
You write back?
Well, I... haven't had the time...
What kinda idol doesn't put her fans first?
I answer every one of mine!
Wow.
Well, you don't have to answer them with letters, I guess.
You've got songs, right?
All your fans are waiting for a new one, right?
Thank you, Haruna!
Wait, Makoto!
Yotsuba Music
Want some hot chocolate?
Davi.
You've been really focused. Working on something new?
A bit.
It's cold tonight.
Don't stay up too late.
Wait, isn't that...
the spear of light?
Bingo!
But how?
Well done, Regina!
With one of the three Sacred Treasures within our grasp, nothing will stand in our way!
We shall subjugate the human world in one blow!
Not yet, Daddy.
Human hearts are strong. And nuisances.
We have to weaken their hearts first.
A nice idea...
But how?
Well, we could use...
that!
Huh?
A CD?
Music nourishes the human heart.
So we'll steal their music first.
Kenzaki.
Hey, Makopi! Earth to Makopi!
Good morning.
Got enough sleep?
Yes, I'm fine.
Gotta have your priorities.
Thank you.
And by the way...
Yes?
See me after class.
Yes...
Kenzaki!
Good morning!
What's up with Makopi?
She's been like that all day!
Rachel.
Gotcha!
What are you doing?
Calling an expert.
An expert?
In what?
Makoto seems to be stressed due to her work.
Oh, that's what.
Yotsuba
Library
No surprise.
She appears to be working on a new song, but...
it seems she's been hit by a writer's block.
Sounds like it was a heavy block.
It's not that kind of block.
Makopi.
Girls! Why are you here?
Don't be like that, Makopi!
If you're having trouble, tell us!
Yotsuba
Library
You're writing a song for Regina?
Yeah.
If I write a song that comes from the heart,
it may be able to get our feelings across to Regina.
So I figured I'd try writing a new song, but...
it just isn't coming together.
Then let's all put our heads together.
We all feel the same way about Regina, right?
Yeah.
Girls!
I'd be delighted to assist!
Oh, Aguri.
What are you doing all the way out here?
I-I was simply strolling by...
Perfect timing, then!
Girls, it seems Aguri wants to help, too!
W-W-Wait!
Now then, let's all make a great song!
I-I'm not quite...
Oh yeah, Aguri, what kind of music do you like?
S-Stuff like Songbird...
You listen to my music?
Well, my classmates do...
I'm flattered!
I'll give you an autograph!
Makopi, can I get one too?
Only if you help me write the lyrics.
That's so unfair!
And why did I never think to get an autograph until now, anyway?
From the Heart
This is a new song?
Yes.
It's a song for a friend who's still far away.
Reserve the stage in front of the station for next Sunday.
Huh?
We're announcing your latest single!
Now get everything ready.
Right!
It looks good on you, Makoto.
Thanks.
Will my song touch her heart?
That's what you wrote it to do, right?
Believe in it.
You picked the absolute worst day to sleep in!
Sorry!
I was so nervous I couldn't sleep!
What are you nervous about?
I've been searching for you girls.
Alice!
From the Heart
Wow, this is huge!
If this event goes well, business'll be booming!
No, this is about letting the world listen to the song Makoto worked her tail off to write.
All these people came just to listen to a song?
Music really is dangerous.
That junk's better off gone!
I'll turn you into a splendid Selfish!
CD!
It's a Selfish!
The stage!
Davi!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
I, Cure Sword,
shall sever your ambitions with the blade of love!
Buy my CD!
It's the first print run!
Ooh, not bad.
Regina!
So, where's Mana?
Not here yet.
Oh well.
I'll just play with you instead!
Over here!
That's the princess's spear!
Give it back!
It's mine now!
You and your stupid dodging!
No more running away for you.
Stop this, Regina!
I don't want to fight you!
Really?
But aren't I your enemy?
Selfish!
Self!
Ace Mirror Flash!
Sword!
We're here to save you!
Girls!
Ira!
Mammo!
It won't be that easy.
Mana, there you are.
Regina, release Sword!
Why?
Because we came to this stage for you!
Makopi wanted to write a song to tell you how we feel!
We all helped to write it together!
We were going to debut that song on this stage...
Like I care.
Get 'em, Selfish!
Seeeeelf!
Of course, Regina's right here.
The song might still reach her...
No,
I'll make it reach her!
Davi, can I ask a favor?
Have a handshake coupon!
Heart!
Now, finish them!
Break a leg!
Thank you.
On lonely, restless nights
I sing a song to myself
Even in the cold darkness
Makoto?
What?
What... is this song?
It gives me strength
It makes me feel... strange...
Every single lyric and note
Are like the fragments of a miracle
Self?
If I hum them out,
They spread with a tra-la-la
And the melody echoes into the future
My chest... is all tingly...
I sing from the heart
So my voice can reach the ends of the earth
The flame of my hope lights like it did before,
Why... does my heart keep pounding?
Stop her song already!
And each line takes flight
I won't let you!
We sing from the heart
We'll make you...
Listen to her song!
Shut up!
It's an earsore!
And reach the corners of this big, wide world
Even the tears we now shed
Stop!
Stop it!
Will shine brighter than the stars
Let's make a wish and sing tomorrow
While those I love are still with me
Because I want to see you smile
Brighter than you ever did before
Regina!
Why is my chest...
burning so much?!
You're in danger! Run away!
No.
I won't run.
Heart...
Why would I?
I believe in Regina.
Good point.
Me too!
I do as well!
Girls...
Regina!
The Jewel Lovies!
Ai!
Cure Heart!
Kyupirappa kyupirappa puppa!
Kyupirappa!
This warm light...
What's happening?
Could this be...
The Lovely Pad's true power?
Girls!
Right!
Precure Royal Lovely Straight Flush!
Self?!
Love love loooooove!
Huh?
I'll remember this, Precures!
What's up with her?
Beats me.
Regina...
Sorry, Mana.
My song...
couldn't reach Regina.
No...
Aguri.
Regina's heart wavered upon hearing your song.
Or, so it seemed to me.
I... suppose Regina may possess a heart that can love.
She does.
I know she has to.
Yeah...
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Alice, your childhood dream was to become a florist?
It was!
All right, we're gonna make that dream come true!
Oh no, all the flowers in town are wilting!
Whaaa?!
Is this Regina's doing?
I don't sense a Selfish's presence.
But if this keeps up, we'll lose every flower in town!
Girls, give me your aid!
We must save the flowers!
Dokidoki Precure:
Alice's Dream!
A Friendship Through Flowers
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!