Fall, 1957
Setsuko!
Mario...
What brings you here so early?
I was going shopping.
I figured I'd stop by on the way.
Here, this is for you.
The rent.
I told you that you don't need to pay.
You must already have a hard time getting by on your own.
I have a job, you know.
I can't let you take care of me like I'm a kid.
Right.
By the way...
are you working tomorrow?
Well...
I'm on the night shift tomorrow.
So you're free during the day.
A movie?
A friend of mine gave them to me,
and Turtle and the others are all busy tomorrow.
You don't have to come if you don't want to.
I don't really enjoy movies either.
It's just... I didn't want to waste them.
Yeah.
That doesn't sound bad.
We should go.
To the movies.
Y-Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, I'll come pick you up tomorrow morning.
Are you... going out?
Well, you have make-up on.
Oh.
Well... I have to go out with my parents.
So...
I see.
But... you know...
It... looks good.
Take care, Setsuko!
See you tomorrow!
He's starting to become just like him.
He can't express his feelings directly,
and he's also single-minded...
just like Sakuragi.
S-Setsuko?
I-Is something wrong?
No.
It's... nothing.
Well, I'm one fortunate man.
I never thought I'd meet someone as wonderful as you.
It's like we were fated to meet.
Sign: Toni's Bar
Master, you can leave now.
I'll close up.
Oh, really?
Sorry about that, Mario.
Hey!
Turtle, Joe.
Mario, are they friends of yours?
No, they're just a bunch of idiots.
Who're you calling an idiot?
That's good!
Mario, more!
He's already drunk.
You okay, Turtle?
Shut up!
Man, I'm so glad the Master's so generous.
Right, Mario?
Oh, yeah.
Soldier and Cabbage stopped by the other day.
Really?
So they're still pretty close.
Same goes for you two.
What's Uncovered doing?
He's going to night school.
He sure loves to study.
What he really needs to study is women!
So, what's going on with you, Mario?
With Setsuko.
Nothing, really.
What about the movie tickets I gave you?
You invited her, right?
Y-Yeah.
We're going tomorrow.
All right!
Let's celebrate tonight!
Mario, open up some wine!
Well, Setsuko?
The man has taken quite a liking to you, and he'd love to marry you.
The matchmaker said that she'd even consider
giving us a loan if the arrangement worked out.
Then the factory will...
Hey, are you listening, Setsuko?
Setsuko!
I understand.
Then is it okay to proceed?
Yes.
That was a good movie.
Mario.
You were sleeping, weren't you?
N-No.
You were!
I heard you snoring.
Thanks for taking me out today, Mario.
It was... really fun.
Really.
That's good.
Um...
I'll take you out again.
Yeah.
Hey!
W-Wait a minute, Mario!
What are you doing, Turtle?
You're pathetic.
Man, what's up with you?
You're in an awfully good mood.
No.
I'm just being myself.
Could it be...
that date you had with Setsuko?
Did it go well?
Wh-Why should that matter?
Just hold the sandbag steady, man.
You're blushing.
How far did you get?
All the way to home plate?
That's not it.
That's not it at all!
"To be honest, I wanted to shout from the bottom of my heart."
"I like you."
"I love you."
But Bro still lived in Mario's heart.
Setsuko's sight was always set on Bro.
So he was happy simply to see her smile.
That was all he needed.
I had a great time, Setsuko.
Oh, I did as well.
See you later.
Setsuko.
Yo.
What's up, Joe?
Setsuko's... engaged?
The ceremony's this year.
She tried to tell you after the movie, but...
It's not like I have a say in the matter.
Mario?
We weren't dating or anything.
If that's going to make Setsuko happy...
Are you serious?
I mean, you said Setsuko...
So what if I did?
There's nothing I can do right now.
I'm still on the run.
There's nothing I can do.
Mario...
Whatever. It doesn't matter.
You're done for the day, right?
Stay for a drink, Joe.
Don't give me that shit, old man!
You're going to make me pay for that piece of crap?
Are you?!
I-I'm terribly sorry.
Please don't worry about the payment.
Damn right I won't!
What do you want?
You can't just leave, sir.
You broke those glasses, so you have to pay for them at least.
It's all right, Mario.
Do you work here?
Hiring a stupid punk like you sure says a lot about this bar!
What the hell you looking at?!
Stop, Mario!
Mario!
Two shots.
You can hit me twice first.
Come get me, old man!
You'll let me hit you twice?
Stop, Mario!
Hey, stop!
You shouldn't fight here-
Keep out of this, Joe.
You know, it may not look like it, but I know karate.
One punch will be more than enough to take down a kid like you.
Just one more.
You only have one free shot left, old man.
You son of a bitch!
Ow! Ow! Fuck!
I-I get it.
I'm sorry.
I got a little too drunk.
I won't ever come here again.
Please, spare me!
Please!
Mario.
Why did you do that?
Well, he came up with some excuse to drink for free.
I'm sure he does it everywhere else.
I get it.
Mario, you don't have to come anymore.
Mr. Hayakawa?
I don't... like that sort of stuff.
"It must be improbable...
for anyone to give himself a handicap in a fight."
"Yet no one is even kind enough to applaud."
Mario wasn't exactly smart to think that way,
but that was because of his youth.
Mario had lost Setsuko, and his heart had broken like a shard of glass.
Hey, Mario!
I know you're here!
I'm coming in!
Hey, where are you going?
I got fired,
but I gotta go apologize to Mr. Hayakawa.
Mario...
I'm over Setsuko.
Really.
I thought hard about it,
but I can't do anything as a fugitive.
So... it's okay.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
You took a guy like me in...
and taught me how to work,
but I ended up doing something stupid.
It was really fun working here.
Thank you very much.
Mario...
What do you officers want?
It's him!
He's the one who hit me!
Did you do it?
You're under arrest for suspicion of assault!
Sign: Yokohama Police Department
I'm quite surprised.
I knew I'd heard your name before,
but I never thought you were Minakami Mario,
an escapee from Shonan Special Disciplinary School.
Now that we've found you, the assault hardly matters.
You'll definitely be going to juvenile prison.
You'll probably be eating shitty food for the next seven years.
Seven years...
Man...
Why didn't you stop him?
You were standing right there.
Yeah.
Why didn't you beat the crap out of that drunk instead?
Sorry.
But...
Mario was consumed with Setsuko's marriage and stuff.
Well, let's keep this a secret from Setsuko.
Yeah.
But it's really not going to be easy this time.
Worst case scenario, he'll be in prison for seven years.
Seven years?
He'll be twenty-six in seven years.
Can't we like...
bust him out, like the old days?
Bust him out?
We're not on the inside anymore.
In any case...
We need some information first.
Well, Master, thanks!
Man,
that idiot sure knows how to keep people busy.
G-Guys, wait!
Who exactly are you?
Us?
We're the former criminal seven from cell 2-6, Shonan Disciplinary School!
Shonan Disciplinary School?
Once Mario comes back,
please give him a warm welcome.
He's a simple-minded, helpless idiot,
but he's a very important friend.
Minakami.
An SDF officer named Tohyama Tadayoshi came to pay a visit.
Soldier was here?
But unfortunately for you,
you're not allowed to have visitors.
The family court has decided to hold you for criminal punishment.
Criminal punishment?
Basically, you're being placed back in the hands of the Yokohama Police.
You won't be prosecuted as a youth, but as a real criminal.
No generous reform school for you this time.
You're going to juvenile prison.
Prison?
Mario...
You're not really thinking about doing seven years of time, are you?
Neither are we.
Setsuko's wedding's in a month.
We'll get you out by then.
Are you serious?!
If he falls into the prosecutor's hands, we won't be able to help him.
The prosecutors will indict him for his crimes, and the judge will find him guilty.
Then he'll be sent to prison.
But the prosecutor could just let it all slide.
Are you dumb?
A district prosecutor isn't going to go against the family court.
He'll bring an indictment.
In any case, we need to act quickly.
All right!
I've got an idea-
Hey, Turtle.
Don't think about doing anything dumb like ambushing the police to free Mario.
Hey, Uncovered.
If the prosecutor indicts,
we can't do anything about it.
So the battle has to happen before that.
Our first step is silencing the prosecutor.
Look, I'm saying that's the difficulty.
Hey, Soldier, just go get a tank from the SDF.
I'll show those police a-
I know it's not easy.
But, it's our only choice.
All right, it's settled.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
"Wait for us, Mario."
"We'll get you out, no matter what."
The five made a firm oath.
Until the prosecutor decided whether to indict...
only eleven days remained.
Yokohama District Public Prosecutor's Office
Minakami Mario, age 19.
In 1955, you attacked your homeroom teacher,
and were sent to Shonan Special Disciplinary School.
You caused a lot of trouble in the disciplinary school,
and were put in solitary six times for fighting.
In the same year, you broke out along with several other cellmates from 2-6.
In 1957, while on the run,
you assaulted Kogure Yoshitaka in a bar,
inflicting injuries that may take two months to heal.
Is this all true?
Yes.
But please hear me out.
I had reasons for every action.
Who asked for your opinion?!
It's because of trash like you...
that this country hasn't changed since the war!
I will not tolerate any evil!
I'll make sure you end up in prison.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
The concealed truth.
Mario prepares for the worst.
Now, more than ever, his friends must act.
Hi there, everyone, I'm Satake Uki, the galactic idol.
This man made his debut as a voice actor in Rainbow.
He's Mr. Waki Tomohiro, who voices Cabbage.
We obtained a few words from him.
I'm Waki Tomohiro. I voice Cabbage.
From the very first moment I read the manga,
he reminded me of myself.
He's strong, and he's useful when he has to be.
To me, taking on his role
feels really comfortable,
and I constantly find myself liking this job.
With Oguri at the center,
the work is very lively,
and everyone is friendly.