THE POWER OF ANIMATION
Sound of the Skies
Does the light of the sky reach your heart?
The melody we dreamed of was serene.
Even though the dream is so far from you
Try to recall that gentle voice.
Someone's singing a graceful chord for you.
May the sound of the skies resound,
overcoming sadness with all its might.
Only the real world reflects in your eyes.
Don't let your tears form any more.
Within the overflowing light,
may you play out the morrow.
Why can I not play it right?
Seriously...
Noel?
Rainy Season Sky • Quartz Rainbow
Got your wallet?
Yes!
ID tag?
Handkerchief?
Yes!
Tissues?
Map?
Yes!
Compass?
Ready-to-Eat Meals?
Yes!
Helmet?
Handgun.
Hand grenades.
She's kidding, Kana!
You scared me for a second...
After a moment's thought, you
should have caught on.
That's mean, Rio.
Lately, you two really have
been getting along.
Rio's acting like an overprotective mother.
Here's the list for today, OK?
Listen up! Your mission is to go into town
and purchase the supplies on that list.
Understood?
Yes!
All right, drive safely.
Moving out.
Come back soon!
We're having pot-au-feu for dinner!
Come straight home!
She's like a mom.
This is the first time we've gone into
town like this. Right, Noel?
Yes.
But this is pretty much my
first time going into town...
Wow!
What is that?
It isn't at all like it was
during the festival.
It's so calm and quiet.
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
The first was a Nue,
a roof ornament only found in Trois.
It's used to ward off evil spirits.
The other was a drinking fountain,
modeled after the twelfth
Helvetian Archduke, Akira Arcadia II.
We're here.
You meant what we just saw?
Yes.
I was told to drive safely.
Thanks!
That's really impressive.
Noel, you're really smart!
Girls?
You coming or going?
Make up your mind.
You're blocking the store.
The old lady from the festival!
The lady, you mean.
Pressuring people is wrong.
That's not very nice of you.
How about "Naomi", at least?
Ms Naomi...
So, the next shipment's
next month?
Yes.
By the way, does she know?
No.
You are some weird girls...
Not like any soldiers I've se-
Um...
Wh-What?
About that?
You were staring at it the first
time you were here, too.
You like it?
Um... C-Can I touch it?
A-flat.
This is a fish, right?
What's it called?
That's...
It's not a fish.
Huh? But...
It's a dolphin.
It's more like a human than a fish.
It was a marine mammal,
back when life still existed in the sea.
The sea?
It lived in the sea?
Wow...
The old guy's pretty good
at making those.
He may not look it, but
he's a romantic.
Do you know the person
who made it?
There's a big factory
outside town.
All our glasswork
come from there.
I'd love to see them being made.
It's OK.
What is?
We're going there right now.
I see. You're having them make
parts for the Takemikazuchi.
Yes. Naomi is getting parts
from the old era, too.
But you're really amazing, Noel.
You can fix a complicated
machine just like that!
Just like that?
I have a really hard time memorizing
the codes for the signal trumpet.
It's really not that hard...
Machines don't betray you.
Noel-
Your change is 2,750,000 yen!
We get that much back?
We don't.
It's 2 yen 75 sen.
You're the same as
always, Noel.
Here you go.
She's right.
That morning trumpet...
Is that you?
Y-Yes.
I'm sorry I'm not very good yet...
It's fine. I like it!
It... Well, it really wakes you up!
Stare...
I was thinking I need to improve so
I won't bother the townspeople.
Seiya, that's not fair!
Kanata, I-
Come get it then!
Ow...
Sorr-
You hit someone!
I'm so sorry!
You're...
The girl from the festival!
The clumsy girl!
I'm glad that you seem
to be better.
You murderer!
Seiya, these people have nothing
to do with your parents!
They're all the same!
I hate soldiers!
Get out of our town!
Playing your crap trumpet every morning...
It's annoying!
Hey, Seiya!
I'm really sorry for his rudeness.
I-It's OK.
He's a war orphan.
So he gets really angry whenever
he sees a soldier.
Noel.
It's OK.
He's right. We're soldiers.
So...
Noel...
He's right. We're soldiers.
When I enlisted, I repeated
the Oath of Paradores.
So I thought I understood that...
What am I saying?
I always understood it.
I won't start whining now!
That's right.
I have to get better in case
something happens.
Everyone would be in trouble if there
wasn't a signal trumpet.
We're almost there.
That's the glass factory?
Wow, Noel!
I've never seen a building
that big!
This one's no good, either.
Is the problem with
optical aberration?
I'm sure I've got the
right refraction.
I-I'm the new recruit,
Kanata Sorami!
Nice to meet you all!
Uh, I...
So, how was it until
it put up the error?
The seek time was
essentially the same.
The distortion along the peripheral
area was less than last time...
Sorry!
The boss gets really focused when
he starts to talk about work.
But you know, he's amazing,
old man Carl.
He's one of the five people in the nation
bearing the title of Meister.
He won a competition in the capital, and he
once presented his work to the Archduke!
Maria! If there's time for talk,
there's time for work!
Right! I'm sorry, boss.
I'm not worthy of the
title, anyway.
I'm nothing compared to this.
What is it?
The lens to the Takemikazuchi's
optic sensor.
That's the real one.
I need two to repair it, so I asked
him to make another.
But it's not going well.
It's so pretty, though.
In addition to its primary component
of silicon dioxide,
the lens is infused with sodium
oxide and magnesium oxide.
This corrects for the chromatic
and peripheral aberrations.
In other words, for the distortion
in the captured image.
But we don't know how it's distributed
through the lens.
It's a product of the previous
era's magic-like technology.
I thought glass was just pretty,
but it's complex, as well.
Seize has high-quality
silica deposits,
so it's always had a number of small studios
that primarily made works of art.
This was originally one of them.
However, as the war intensified, the demand grew
for the glass used in military applications.
This factory prospered
because of the war.
Kanata, I like machines.
Yes.
But sometimes machines
hurt people.
I'm sure in the past, the Takemikazuchi
killed a lot of people.
Do you think a machine that killed
a lot of people is scary?
Yes.
But I guess I'm more afraid of the people
who used it than the machine itself.
Because this trumpet...
When I play it, it's awful. But when
Rio plays it, it's so pretty.
I'm sure a tank is the
same kind of thing.
And a while ago, Rio played
me a song from inside it.
It can make such beautiful music!
I'm sure it's a good tank!
I know! Why don't...
Noel.
Let her rest.
I bet she was up all night again.
Noel's working really hard
at fixing the Takemikazuchi.
I know.
She's a real craftsman.
If she weren't, I wouldn't make something
that's as big a pain in the ass as this.
Here, put this on her.
Thank you.
By the way, you guys stopped
by Windmill right?
How's Naomi?
Great!
She said your boss was
a wonderful romantic.
She said so?
Wonderful. Eh, boss?
Shut up!
Get to work!
Oh! He's mad!
Gotta get to work!
But is the technology from
the past that amazing?
It is, yeah.
But the boss always says,
"You know, no matter how amazing
it is, humans just like us made it.
So we could make it, too!"
You agree, don't you?
Yes. Or I'd like to say yes, but...
I see...
You're right. Rio's trumpet playing
is very different from yours.
It's really bothering me.
How can I be like her?
I think I'm practicing
as hard as I can!
My lips, you see, they're
so swollen.
But...
I try and try, but it doesn't
sound like hers.
I guess I really don't have the talent...
Miss.
Yes!
"Talent" is the worst excuse cited
by people who give up.
Give me that.
I don't understand
trumpets, but...
I do know there's a mistake
the young often make.
Miss, are you trying to force
yourself to make the sound?
I'm not trying to make
it this shape.
The glass wants to be this shape.
Thank you, Mr Carl!
Like the sound wants
to play itself...
Morning?
Yes.
It looks like the sun came
up a bit earlier for her.
She's a craftsman
in her own right.
It's a good sound!
Sound?
The sound glass makes
changes slightly,
depending on the number of
impurities and their type.
Even if we can't hear
the difference,
someone with talented
ears could.
I'm going to have you
listen for the sound
that's closest to it from the
samples we've made so far.
That will probably...
Now, listen to their voices, miss!
Yes!
Since she arrived, Noel
has changed a lot.
You think?
Yeah!
You did it!
You did it, Noel!
Thank you.
I've never seen Noel
smile before.
Let's get friendship, love, and other feelings together,
and play out how important they are.
I cried from joy.
I laughed from pain.
But that's all a part of me,
and tells me that I'm alive.
Let's take this slowly.
Everybody singing
Can you tell me how you really feel?
You're just my friend
Even when friendship and love waver,
I know, you know, will be happy
I hope this melody will ring forever.
Can you count my precious flower
Overflowing words are hardly enough to describe it.
This is our harmony.
Can you hear our harmony?
Mountain Hiking • The Ends of the World
Next time:
Mountain Hiking.
The End of the World.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.