The stars are so beautiful...
You are far more beautiful.
You're incredibly sexy.
No, I'm... not ready...
Wait...
Ouch...
What was that just now?
What kind of dream was I hav-
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Underwear Summer Training Camp!
Wow... The Underwear Club can go out for a training camp...!
We're going to have fun!
Yako-chan, if it's a training camp,
we need to do stuff for the Underwear Club.
We could think of some activities for the club.
R-Right, I guess so-
Didn't you put any thought into this?!
Sorry! I kind of held you up.
Oh, Sensei!
Err... can we get the luggage in the car?
Ah, my luggage, right.
Pardon me.
This is bad... The dream I had this morning...
The only one left is Amahara-san.
Hmm... pretty sexy.
Eh?! A student's sexier than I am?
Thanks for driving me over here.
Was that her dad?
It didn't look like that.
Her boyfriend, maybe?
Goodness, here you are.
"Here you are" doesn't work here.
It's already past the meeting time.
Hmm? Amahara-san, are you hur-
That's got to be a love-bite.
She might have spent last night with her boyfriend.
Yako-chan!
It couldn't be!
But Amahara-san does appear very adult-like...
She couldn't have! I can't!
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
Nothing, nothing.
Amahara-san, is that a "love bite"?
Who knows.
Delicious, huh?
Yeah, they're delicious.
It's hard to believe that I'm going on a trip with Senpai...
Tonight we'll be spending time together somewhere!
That's not right- this is a training camp!
I'm here to lead the students!
Sorry, sorry! I haven't driven in a while.
A-Are you all right?!
No, I am not all right.
I'm sorry.
How do you wear your underwear with that?
It's strapless.
Really?!
Let me see.
Isn't it really tight against your chest?
It comes off easily. Here.
Wow, these are pretty heavy.
How different does it feel compared to a normal bra?
Yako-chan, stop touching them!
Komachi-kun, could you get that?
It's... warm.
Everyone, there are guys in here.
Sorry about that, Komachi-kun.
Sensei, are you wearing a T-shirt bra?
Ah, yes.
You're wearing sweat absorbing pads as well.
These were cheap, I bought them online.
It is true that a T-shirt bra won't show through,
and the pads will prevent stains,
but there is no feminine appeal to them at all...
Use this training camp to raise your femininity, okay?
Oh, is it a bug bite?
I've got some itch cream with me.
Well then. I guess it wasn't a love bite.
A long time ago, "Jewellers" used this traditional inn.
Jewellers?
It's the brand of the underwear my grandma made.
Wait, is that us?
Welcome
Under Fellowship
What's an "Under Fellowship"?
What a weird name!
Seems like they couldn't just put "Underwear Appreciation Society".
So we're unpopular here too?
Drawing attention to ourselves would be troublesome.
That might be true, but I'm still a bit sad.
Welcome.
We'll be in your care.
Thank you very much for having us!
Thank you!
You must all be from the Underwear Appreciation Society, correct?
Y-Yes!
We thought that the other customers might be curious about you,
and so we took the liberty of changing your name on the sign outside.
Forgive us if we did something imprudent.
Ah, she was looking out for us...
You must be the granddaughter of Youko-san.
I believe it's Nayu-chan?
Ah, yes!
You've grown taller, haven't you!
Eh?
In the past, you stayed here with your grandmother.
You were little back then, you might not remember.
So that's what it was! I was with Grandma...
The ocean!
Let's swim!
Well, I've got work to do.
I'll be back at night.
Ah, all right.
Let's get changed now and go to the beach!
If you're going to change, be sure to close the door.
Yeah, fine.
Nayu-chan's swimsuit is cute!
Haruka-chan, yours is stylish!
Yako-chan, is that a racing suit?
You bet.
That's amazing. It kind of juts in there.
You can kind of see it-
Are you wearing something underneath there?
Ignore it, ignore it!
Mizuno
Her school swimsuit...
And it's ready to burst.
Don't you have a less objectionable swimsuit?
Eh? But I haven't been swimming for a while.
Regardless...
I'll take off the name tag, at least.
Ah, I have some scissors.
Thank you! You are really prepared.
If we have some time,
I thought that I'd hold some underwear-making lessons.
I brought patterns, fabrics, and a sewing kit with me.
Now we might as well keep cutting. Whee!
What are you doing?!
This will make it look better.
Wait!
We might as well make it into a bikini!
I could never wear something like this!
It looks like she's been attacked...
I guess we went overboard.
We have no choice but to buy a new swimsuit.
Why am I here, too?
We need a guy's opinion.
It's cute, but...
Doesn't it look childish?
How is it, Komachi-kun?
Not... looking at anything...
W-Wait.
Hmm, this is pretty...
No, it's not enough.
Seems as if they're getting...
How about this one?
We can go even further!
...steadily smaller?!
There's none smaller than this one!
Is this covering her?!
I'm going with this one!
You've tried on so many, and yet you choose this one?
White is really the best.
Why "really"?
It's because I'm not married yet...
What...?
I still want to get married, so I want this!
Let me wear this!
It's a sudden shower.
Run for it!
Cold!
Don't give up- this is part of the training!
Training!
Looks like swimming will be impossible today.
Yeah it does.
Perhaps we should go and take a bath.
Okay!
I'll take a bath later.
You just don't want to get in with the big-breasted duo, do you?
That's totally wrong.
You lost!
Shut up!
Ah... Finally I can relax.
It doesn't matter how much you wash them,
once they start growing they're not going away.
I feel kind of violated.
Why would you say that?
It's worse for me...
What? Haruka-chan, you too?!
Let me check!
Checking won't amount to anything, will it?!
I just want to know that I'm not the only one!
Still, that's...!
Just let me go!
Huh? I'm...
The savoury egg custard is delicious!
Why don't you start eating, Komachi-kun...?
It's great...
Did they carry me here stark naked?!
Who put my underwear on?!
Did they see my...?!
Sensei...
May I make some adjustments to the white swimsuit you bought today?
Are you going to cut it to pieces again?!
Oh, no.
I thought that it might be nice to add some beads or something.
Wow, it looks fabulous!
I thought that it'd be pretty if I added some sparkles to the chest.
How is it?
Incredibly beautiful.
Thank you, Hayama-san.
Why don't we put on some make-up as well?
I've never worn colours like these.
Just hold still, please.
Sensei, you look beautiful.
Thank you.
I've been taught by all of you, haven't I?
Saying "I'm fine with how I am", and "staying like this is fine" won't let me move forward or mature...
...as a human being or as a woman.
Let's take a picture of that expression!
Ah, all right!
It'll help me when I put on make-up by myself.
Sensei! Try striking a pose.
Try squeezing your chest!
And for the next one, pretend that you're lying on the beach!
Now spread your legs a little!
What the heck is Mizuno-sensei doing...?
Good, that's great, Tamaki-chan. Next let's-
I'm back.
What are you up to?
Excuse me, may I enter?
Ah, sure.
Pardon me for intruding during the night.
I thought that I would offer my greetings.
Oh, thanks for going out of your way!
Has everyone made themselves at home?
Yes!
It's no surprise that the granddaughter of Youko-san has formed an Underwear Appreciation Society.
When I was young, Youko-san taught me a lot about underwear.
Grandma did?
When I had a part-time job in a shop near the sea...
Thank you for waiting!
Your bra strap is showing.
Oh, pardon me!
Would you like to try on this sample work?
My work is designing underwear.
Take a look.
With something like this, having the strap seen would be fine, right?
With these Western-like designs,
if the bra strap shows, it would be fashionable.
Cute!
You can get this kind of underwear?
And when you're wearing jeans, this kind of underwear won't show.
She taught me that there were different kinds of underwear.
I began studying on my own.
Even better, she taught me that a working woman can still have her prudence.
She was truly a wonderful person.
Grandma...
Nayu-chan is certainly continuing her grandma's work, huh?
It would be nice if I can become more like Grandma.
What on earth is that?!
Eh? I can't sleep in this?
If your boyfriend suddenly stopped by your house to stay over, what would you do?
I'm nervous...
Did she wear that yesterday, too?
It's transparent, which means that it's for showing off underwear, right?
If you wore it around your boyfriend, however,
I think it'd be okay for you to wear nothing underneath it.
But then wouldn't everything show through?!
Must be tough for you, too.
You understand? You understand, don't you?!
She still lacks her "strength as a woman".
Komachi-kun, aren't you going to swim?
I'm fine.
You changed into your swimming trunks, right?
They're tiny. And they're digging in!
What the heck?!
I don't remember packing something like thi-
"Show off your manliness. Good luck. From your brother."
I can't be seen like this.
Komachi-kun, come and swim with us!
I said that I'm fine!
Come on now, let's swim.
Leave me alone already!
That was fun!
It was great having a training camp.
We didn't do a single thing that
should've been done in a training camp.
Weren't we going to discuss the club activities for the rest of the year?
Ah, that's right. How about we discuss it now?
R-Right.
Um... We, the Underwear Appreciation Society,
should spread the belief that
underwear is wonderful even more.
To accomplish this, we...
What should we do, I wonder?
How about we start with the culture festival?
Oh, that's right!
It'd be nice if we could do something at the culture festival.
We could show something about how underwear protects the body and show how wonderful it is,
like... um...
Basically, it'd be like this:
We, the Underwear Appreciation Society,
should teach people to appreciate underwear,
and our goal is to educate people about its functions and history.
Within the club we should participate in activities that help this cause.
You guys!
Komachi-kun, they're just tired!
Well, I'm tired too!
I'm going to sleep too.
How cute.
You were cute, too.
You looked great in that swimsuit.
It was wonderful.
You can't, Tamaki!
You've got to enjoy this blissful moment!
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
It seems women's loincloths have been gaining popularity lately.
What?!
They say that they're not restricting and easy to wear!
It might be nice for when you're asleep or wearing a yukata.
Hey, how about we try and make matching loincloths?
Not necessary!
Seventh
Grade
Summer
Vacation
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra!