Ta-da~! The sports competition event is—
the 50 meter free-style one round contest, suggested by Kawashima-san!
Lucky me!
What did you write?
TL Note: The Katakana on the note says "vale tudo" which means 'anything' in Portuguese
If I win, I'm going to put those impersonation footages up on display.
If I win, Takasu-kun will be spending his entire summer with me at my villa.
You'll be all alone for the whole summer.
Alright, start writing your answers up on the board.
Yes.
Wow, as expected of the class president.
Hey.
Stupid.
Round one of the Takasu competition is commencing?
Ami-tan vs Palm-top Taiga Battle.
500 Chiroru per bet?
TL Note: Chiroru is a type of candy
What the heck is this?
Is this even going to be a good match?
If it's a swimming contest, then Ami-tan wins for sure.
Taiga was drowning remember?
I want to be fought over too... what should I do?
Damn it... These guys...
I'm sorry, but Ami's mine, arl.
Could it be that he was trying to write "all"?
He can't even spell "all"? isn't that pretty awful?
Haruta... you're—
No, that's not it.
Sheesh, everyone just writes as they please...
What did you—?
W-What's wrong Aisaka?
I-If you know the answer, then please come up and solve the problem.
Aisaka-san?
Don't be afraid Taiga. It's the same as washing your face.
Come on! One more time!
You say that, but—
She can't even put her face in the water?
Isn't that way too low level?
Well, the outcome of this competition sure is obvious.
Just ignore the others.
I know that!
I guess she's just going to have to do her best for Takasu's sake.
Who did—?!
Who did what?
Kitamura-kun!
Just keep working with Takasu like that and do your best.
Huh? What? Work together?
Hey, Taiga!
I'm not going to practice during class anymore.
Image training is good enough.
You can start saying stuff like that "after" you're able to put your face in the water.
What's todays dinner?
Sayaendou's egg wrap, tofu steak and miso soup.
There's also spinach and deep-fried—
I want meat; not just bean stuff!
Don't ask for too much; beans are the meat of the fields you know.
Cheapo.
Most importantly, change your mind and make sure you practice during pool class. Think positively.
I can't think positively.
Kitamura-kun's watching too.
That's exactly why you have to do your best.
You know—
Whose fault is it to begin with that I'm working so hard despite the fact everyone is misunderstanding?
Huh... who?
I thought it was to prevent Kitamura from going to Kawashima's villa—
Ow!
Forget it.
Just make my dinner.
Sheesh, what's with you?
Go on, go on. Hurry up and cook!
I'm going to take in tons of nutrition and practice like crazy.
Looks like it'll keep raining.
Guess today's pool class will be canceled.
Just when I was finally able to get my face in the water—
Why can't we use the pool?!
Don't take it out on me.
Huh?
Tickets for the community pool?
Please use them. I'm on Aisaka's side too.
Remember that paper that was passed around?
Since Takasu pushed for Aisaka with so much confidence—
I thought, "Yeah, I'll do it too!"
Y-You bet on me?
Yeah.
W-W-Wh-Why?
I can't even swim.
You're one of those types of people that show strength in the heat of the moment.
The outcome of the contest is yet to be decided.
Can't it be like "this"?
What're you doing?!
S-S-S-Shut up!
Well, good luck. Keep training hard.
Aww man... idiot.
Hey, you want to stop by somewhere on the way home?
Want to go to the Sudobucks?
Sounds good.
What the—What the heck?
Why are you crowded up in a place like that?
You're a gloomy one.
It's this small space that's comforting.
Phew.
TL Note: Dokoisho is something you say when you're about to relax.
Oh my, Takasu-kun. Are you in a tired-out mode too?
Thanks to a certain someone, I've been for a while...
Really? Whose fault is that?
I have no idea.
You know...
Isn't the "jealous" Taiga cute?
What part of that is jealousy?
She just simply doesn't like you.
Are you stupid Takasu-kun?
You're the stupid one.
Anyway, you really need to stop provoking Taiga.
What's this "villa" business anyway?
It's not like you plan on inviting me at all anyway.
I'm serious.
I seriously plan on winning and spending the summer with you.
I'm really thinking about what to do after I win.
I think it'd be fun.
Hey, don't you think we're pretty compatible?
N-No, we're not.
You're mad, you got mad.
You know... sheesh.
You should have your limits when teasing people.
Alrighty~
Later then.
I know...
E-Uh-W-What? About what?
The one who "super-sized" Taiga's swimsuit is you.
Huh? Uh... That is—
No need to hide it, it was a simple process of reasoning, Akechi-kun.
Taiga told me before, " Ryuuji is always there to help me." she said.
Huh?
Cleaning, putting on buttons, ironing clothes...
Oh, those are just small things.
The small things are what's most amazing.
Wha—?
Hey, Kushie— Hmm?
I believe in you. I'm leaving Taiga in your hands.
R-Right.
I can't lend you a hand since I'm the referee, but my thoughts are with you.
Leave it to me.
TL Note: The doll Ryuuji is hanging is a Teru-Teru-Bouzu. It's a lucky charm people make to prevent rain
Alright.
Please, tomorrow is up to you. Please, tomorrow is up to you. Please, tomorrow is up to you.
Thank you Teru-Teru-Bouzu-san.
It looks like the weather will hold out, but...
Look Ryuuji! Doesn't it look like I'm swimming?
I guess it's about time you do some real training.
Ugh... No way. What's with this?
The competition is tomorrow.
What's the point of practicing the crawl stroke at this point?
Our only choice is to use every possible resource.
This is so lame.
Alright, good, now start moving your feet in that position.
Alright already.
Huh? Hey!
Ta-Taiga?
You're amazing Taiga!
I knew it, your kicking strength is way above normal!
You might be able to win with this!
Win? You mean me?
I'm just doing it normally though.
Well, you can't let your guard down of course.
But—
I see.
I can win.
Taiga?
I'll win, okay?
Y-Yeah. That's the spirit.
It doesn't look like it'll stop for a while.
Just when you started to get motivated.
What do you want to do? Want to go home?
You're still going to continue?
I see. Guess that's how it'll be.
Kitamura gave us those tickets. We don't want to waste his thoughts.
That's not what this is about.
That's not it. The reason I'm working so hard is—
I know already. We'll get that Kawashima too.
Forget it. Anything I say is pointless.
Huh? What's with you?
Oh. Could it be me?
Oh yeah. Without me, there'd be no food either right?
I told you it's not that kind—
But you don't have to push yourself.
Even if you lose it'll be settled if I just go to Kawashima's villa by myself.
I'll ask her to leave Kitamura out.
I can also make heaps of food and leave it in the fridge.
So don't worry about unnecessary— hmm?
So you've finally revealed yourself.
What?
You wanted to go to Ami-chan's villa in the first place right?
What are you talking about?
Well, it's none of my concern where, when, or who you pant over, but—
What the hell is your problem? I'm trying to be as caring as I can.
Who asked you for all that?
There's something wrong with you lately.
Even that thing with Kawashima that happened recently—
You still insist on talking about that?!
You—What the hell is your problem?
What's my problem?
I can't stand it when someone imagines what's in my heart and acts like they understand me.
It pisses me off!
Why can't you understand?
Do you want me to understand or not? Make up your mind.
I don't know!
There's no way that someone will ever understand how I feel.
Because... because... I don't even know.
Wh-What did you just say?
Hey!
I said that I won't compete, just like you wished for.
It iches.
It's not my fault, is it?
What what? Ryu-chan?
Why are you still up?
I'm home!
Taiga-chan didn't come?
Why?
Did you two argue?
Taiga said that she doesn't care about me—
which made me mad... I think
Oh, is that so?
But—
You know Ryu-chan, Taiga-chan always says the opposite of what she means.
There's no way that she doesn't care about you.
If she really hated you,
she wouldn't eat from the same plate as you,
no matter how hungry she was.
I think.
Sheesh. She didn't even take her make-up off.
Come on, pull yourself together.
I bet you haven't eaten anything, right?
I really wished it would be sunny. That way you could fight her with everything you've got.
Umm—What I want to say is... no matter what you think I—
I want you to win—
Win, and then I—
The lunch is innocent so I'll be taking it with me.
But—
It was raining so much, my usual swimsuit didn't dry.
I hope this isn't breaking any school rules.
I'm so worried.
That beautiful Ami-tan is about to swim in the pool right?
And that's to take Takasu to her villa right?
Why is it only Takasu? Why, why, why?!
Why, why, why?!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Why is it only you?!
Stop it, you guys!
It's not like it's been decided that I'm going to the villa.
There isn't a chance in hell that Taiga—
You don't know until she tries!
Until she tries...
You don't know...
That idiot. This one has too much meat.
Hey-hey! How long do we have to wait?
It's hot.
Why isn't palm-top Taiga coming?
Oh well. Just pretend that you came here today to see that bikini.
You're right.
Hey, we shouldn't make everyone wait through this heat...
That's true.
What nonsense are you blabbering?
Let's fight, fair-and-square.
Stupid chihuahua morphed into a stupid bikini.
What the heck?
Seriously?
Taiga!
Are you planning on swimming like that?
I though that was armor for a second there.
Isn't it kind of cool looking?
Well then. Here's the 50 meter, free-style, one round contest.
Get into position. Ready!
Look, hair.
Wha—?!
Cra—
Huh?!
I can't believe it! I can't believe it! I can't believe it!
Woah, Palm-top Taiga used a backwards strategy along with horrific brain-play tactics.
Damn you, tiny tiger!
Taiga!
Uh-oh! Has something happened to Taiga?
A chance for Ami-tan!
Damn it!
Are you okay?
Did you sprain your leg?
Stupid, let go!
I can still go—ow!
Come on, you can't like this.
I'm going!
But you—
Doesn't it make you happy?
Wha—?
Not "wha"!
Your master's working hard for you. Be happy about it, you stupid dog!
Alright Ami-tan!
She's finally made her come-back!
Yay!
Alright, then go.
I'll shake my tail or whatever for you!
That's why—
Ami-tan!
Stop pushing!
You idiot, that's dangerous!
Ryuuji!
Huh? Taiga?
--su! Hey Takasu! Are you alright?!
Alright, it seems like he's breathing.
Aisaka! Hurry and take him to the infirmary!
Don't touch him!
But, Aisaka!
Shut up! You're all a bunch of idiots!
Why didn't you notice? Why didn't you help?
Getting distracted by that stupid bikini—
No one did anything for Ryuuji…
Ryuuji's mine! Nobody touch him!
You know. I decided to go to your villa too.
I lost the competition right? Ryuuji's going right?
I won't have anyone to tend to my needs right?
So I decided that I should go—
Hold on a second.
I'm confused by your overwhelmingly selfish flow of words.
Why not? It's more fun if we all go together.
Oh, I see. Could it be that Aisaka-san is worried about parting with Takasu-kun?
"Ryuuji's mine!" Right?
You're right. I'll admit it.
Because... That is—
This guy is my dog.
As his owner, I have an obligation to make sure he doesn't pant around elsewhere.
What? Were you hoping for something else?
Nope, not at all.
Alright, let's decide on the schedule.
Let me see.
I have my part-time jobs around this area and I have my club activities all through here so.
Too bad it's not just the two of us.
But there will be more opportunities.
Wha—?
This is how Takasu Ryuuji's first 11th grade semester ended, with a "stimulating" summer break about to begin.
I can't believe Kushieda's coming to the villa with me.
I'm so happy I might get punished for it, Taiga.
Kitamura-kun's thin, hazy, black seaweed.
Huh?