It was a small incident that happened
to me, Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I believed in the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
The feeling that you can't twist
something you've decided...
The feeling that you don't
want to run away...
I understand those just a little.
That's why, right now, we'll have
our first and last serious battle.
Risking everything we have
on our magic!
I'll tell you over and over.
Because I want to see your smile.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
Mother... My mother...
My mother was always kind.
My mother called out
my name so gently.
See? These are very pretty, Alicia.
Alicia?
That's not right, Mother.
I'm Fate.
Now, come here, Alicia.
See? You're so cute, Alicia.
I guess it's all right.
Because I love my kind mother...
Memories That Lie Beyond Time
It looks like the battle will begin.
Yeah.
But this really is unusual.
For you to allow such
a gamble, Chrono...
Well, it's for the best if Nanoha wins.
But the winner of this battle
doesn't really matter that much.
While Nanoha is buying us
time with her battle,
we'll prepare for pursuit of that girl's
route in returning home, right?
I'm counting on you.
So don't let her get away.
Yeah, leave it to me!
Oh?
But don't you have to tell Nanoha,
about Precia Testarossa's family,
and about that incident?
It's best if she wins.
I don't want Nanoha to be worried
about anything right now.
Photon Lancer.
Divine Shooter.
Fire!
Shoot!
Scythe Form.
Round Shield.
Flash Move.
Scythe Slash.
Fire!
When I first met her,
she was a novice, with nothing
but high magical power.
Not any more.
She's quick, and she's tough.
If I'm indecisive, she'll get me!
Phalanx Shift.
Lightning Bind...
This isn't good. Fate is serious!
Nanoha! I'll back you up now!
You can't!
Miss Aruf... Yuuno...
Please, don't interfere.
It's a duel at full strength between us.
A battle between Fate and me!
But that thing Fate's doing
is really bad!
I'm fine!
Alcus Curtus Agias...
Spears of thunder becoming a gust,
shoot through that to which
you are guided now.
Paruer Zaruer Brouzel...
Photon Lancer, Phalanx Shift!
Hit, and destroy! Fire!
Nanoha!
Fate?!
When you're done shooting,
that Bind thing loses effect, right?
This time, it's my...
Divine...
.«.turn!
Buster.
Direct hit!
But I can withstand it!
Because she withstood my attack too!
Fate!
Try taking this one.
A variation of the Divine Buster...
Starlight Breaker.
Bind?!
This attack is me at my full strength!
Starlight Breaker!
What a ludicrous amount
of magical power!
Wow... I wonder if Fate is still alive?
Fate!
Are you awake, Fate?
I'm sorry... Are you all right?
I won, right?
Yes...
It seems so.
Put out.
Can you fly?
All right, Nanoha,
grab the Jewel Seeds,
and then get her...
No, she's here!
Fate!
Bingo! Caught her by the tail!
All right.
A careless material transfer
will cost lives... The coordinates?
Already determined,
and I'm sending them now!
All armed personnel, mobilize
from the transfer ports!
Your mission is the capture
of Precia Testarossa!
Yes, ma'am!
Just as I thought...
I can no longer physically
bear dimensional magic.
And, with that last one,
they discovered this location.
Fate...
That girl was no good after all.
I guess it's about time to call it quits.
Squadron Two has
completed transfer.
Squadron One has begin infiltration.
Thank you for the hard work.
And... Miss Fate, was it?
Nice to meet you.
I'd prefer not to show her
the scene of her mother's arrest.
Miss Nanoha, please take her
to a different room.
Okay.
Fate, if you'd like,
you can come to my room...
All men have entered
the throne room,
and have confirmed the target!
Precia Testarossa,
you are under arrest
for violation of the time-space laws
and charges of attacking
a Bureau flagship!
Disarm yourself and come here.
Cover that side!
There's something over here!
This is...
Don't come near my Alicia!
Fire!
Shut up.
Look out! Block it!
This isn't good! Recall all agents!
Roger!
Alicia?
Coordinate lock: 012A503.
Locked!
Transfer operation, stand by.
It's no good now. I have no time.
With only nine Lost Logia,
I don't know whether or not
I will reach Alhazard.
But it's fine now. I will end it all.
All the time spent in depression
after losing this child,
and treating a scapegoat of
a doll of her as my daughter.
Are you listening?
I'm talking about you, Fate.
I went through the effort of
giving you Alicia's memories,
but the only resemblance
was your appearance.
You were of no use whatsoever.
A mere doll of mine.
Back in that first incident...
Precia lost her real daughter,
Alicia Testarossa.
In the end, she was
researching the creation
of an artificial life form
different from a familiar,
a being that surpasses all familiars.
And the secret of reviving the dead...
"Fate" is the developers' code
that she had assigned to
her research at the time.
I'm impressed you were able
to find out that much.
You're right. That's correct.
But it's no good.
It didn't go well at all.
An artificial life is nothing but a fake.
It doesn't take the place of
something that you've lost.
Alicia smiled at me more kindly.
Sometimes Alicia was selfish,
but she listened well
to what I had to say.
Stop it!
Alicia was always kind to me.
Fate...
You are, in the end, only a fake Alicia.
I went through the effort of
giving you Alicia's memories,
but you weren't good enough.
Stop! Stop it!
A doll I used to comfort myself until
I could bring Alicia back to life.
So I don't need you anymore.
Wherever you want to go, begone!
Please, stop it already!
I'll tell you one good thing, Fate...
Ever since I made you, all this time...
I hated you!
Fate!
Fate...
All agents have been retrieved.
Big trouble!
Please take a look at this!
Magical responses from all over
the mansion... So many of them?!
What?
What is going on here?
Magical responses from the Garden.
All of them are Class A!
Total numbers, 60.... 80...
The number is still increasing!
Precia Testarossa, what in the world
are you planning on doing?!
I don't want you to
interrupt our journey.
We are going to depart!
To the forgotten capital, Alhazard!
Impossible!
With this power,
we're going to depart,
and take everything
back into our hands!
It's a dimensional tremor!
Mid-size, or even bigger!
Tremor defenses!
Put up the distortion shields!
Nine Jewel Seeds
have been executed.
The dimensional tremor is
going to get even stronger!
Move to an area that
has a smaller affect,
while remaining
within transfer radius!
Roger that!
The Radi coefficient is growing!
At this rate, there will be
a dimensional fault!
Alhazard...
What idiocy!
Chrono?!
I'm going to go stop it!
Open the gate!
The forgotten capital, Alhazard...
The land where the forbidden secret
spells that we have lost all lie.
What is she trying to do there?!
Does she think that she can bring
back the past that she has lost?!
No matter what magic you use,
there is no way that you
can bring back the past!
Alicia and I are going to bring back
all of our past in Alhazard!
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of cellophane
and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying inside
a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining
on the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something
I can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
The dimensional tremor
has been set off.
We head into the Garden of Time
to stop Precia.
So that we don't break many worlds,
including Nanoha's world and ours...
And at that moment, Fate...
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 12:
The Time of the Sealing of Our Fates
Episode 12: The Time of
the Sealing of Our Fates
Lyrical, magical, until
the very end, I'm sure!