This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old!
Last time, she went to the beach,
and met a really cool guy there.
Mitsuki got a boyfriend...
...and I went on a date with Takuto at the beach!
Or, so we thought...
But that guy was actually a womanizing jerk!
In the end, his girlfriend found out...
...and we saved her from his trickery.
Summertime sure is full of perils.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Okay.
We're done.
Thank you very much.
Working as a model sure is busy, isn't it?
Yep!
But it's lots of fun!
Is that so?
Well, it's summer vacation, so don't overwork yourself.
Okay!
What did Dr. Wakaouji say?
He said that since it's summer vacation, I shouldn't push myself too hard.
I see.
A Rival Appears!
Kinda like this?
Yep, yep.
That's perfect.
But... why am I doing a shampoo commercial?
Would you rather do one for makeup?
I-It's too early for makeup!
Your songs are selling...
Your fans adore you...
Now we're signing commercial deals...
This is the next step.
Really?
Once you do a commercial, your face will be all over television and magazines.
It's a little... embarrassing.
But it's the fastest way to get
Eichi-kun to notice you.
That's right...
Eichi-kun...
Okay!
I'm going to do my best!
Good, good. That's the spirit.
So, Ooshige-san...
When's the shoot supposed to be?
Ah... about that...
It's not set in stone yet...
You'll have to audition first.
That would be tomorrow.
You should tell me these things sooner!
F-Forgive me!
Hey.
How's this?
My hair has split ends...
Geez, Meroko.
You have to take proper care of your hair.
A girl's hair is her life.
Hmph.
I don't want to hear that coming from you!
Eh?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Just kidding. I'm just messing with you!
Oh, come on, Meroko.
Sorry, sorry.
Hey.
What do you think, Takuto?
Eh?
Are you against her doing a commercial?
Really?
N-Not really.
Ah.
What's with the attitude?
It's unpleasant...
Why do I have to be so happy if she's going to be in a commercial?
I'm going out for a walk.
Takuto...
What's with him?
He's all grouchy...
...and he's usually the first to be happy for you...
Really...
What's wrong?
Now that I think about it, Takuto said that he used to be a musician.
I wonder if it's about me not focusing on singing...
Hey... you think so too, don't you?
Eh?
Don't you think that Takuto's been awfully strange lately?
Ever since what happened the other day... he's been acting differently.
What happened...?
Ah.
I-It couldn't be...
Hmm?
You know something, don't you?
Nope... nothing...
I-I'm going to sleep!
Something funny's going on with the two of them.
I-It couldn't be that...
...they're doing something behind my back?!
What?!
Meroko's coming to the audition with me?!
That's because...
...Takuto doesn't seem too enthusiastic about it.
Plus, I should get to go out once in a while!
But...
I'm not too sure about Meroko...
I-It's okay every now and then, isn't it?
Eh?
Um...
All right!
I'm so happy!
Takuto, watch the house then, 'kay?
Yeah.
It feels unnatural, doesn't it...
That's because I'm not letting you two be alone together this time!
La la la la la la la.
Going out! Going out!
Takuto... what's wrong?
It's okay every now and then, isn't it?
Ah...
I don't get it...
What's wrong?
N-Nothing at all.
Really?
Yes.
Anyways, I have to keep my mind on the audition right now.
Central Entrance
Um...
Where was it?
Central Entrance
What? What?
You don't know how to get there?
In that case, leave it to me!
Let's see... this way!
We've already passed through here.
It's this way, then!
We've been here already...
Then, here!
Over there!
This way!
We're completely lost.
I wonder if Ooshige-san will come pick me up.
Are you lost?
Eh?
Ah, you're...
We met at the Seed Record audition, right?
That's right.
Thank you for your help back then.
That is...
I... didn't know anyone...
...and when I was feeling lonely... you talked to me...
I guess so.
That's right.
Congratulations on that earlier accomplishment.
Thank you very much!
By the way... where are you headed?
Um...
This place.
Ah.
If that's where you're going, you should take the train to the next station...
...and from there, it'll be faster to just walk.
Hold on a second.
I'll write it down on your map.
But...
...do people go that far for others just like that?
Okay.
Here you go.
Ah, okay.
Wow!
Thank you so much!
No problem.
You're welcome.
I'll do as you said, then.
Good luck.
Okay!
You trust others too much, Full Moon.
Sign: Shinbashi Station
I
If you don't hurry, it'll start!
I know that!
I
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
Ah.
She's here!
Ooshige-san!
You're late, you know.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I got lost...
I would have picked you up if you had called...
I met this nice person on the way who gave me directions.
From Shinbashi...
Shinbashi?
You came from Shinbashi?!
It says to get off at Yurakucho, doesn't it?
Look.
Eh?!
No way!
Why...?
It's that girl...
Ah!
It looks like you managed to get here in one piece.
T-That was mean of you!
Sorry about that.
I was just playing around.
Eh?
I didn't expect you to actually believe me...
Oh well.
I guess you could call it payback for before.
Payback?
You...
...said you didn't have connections...
...but you obviously did, right?
Totally in the dark...
I said all that with the intention of winning...
Wait!
I really didn't have any connections!
Oh...
I wonder if that's true.
In that case... why don't we try this.
This audition...
Let's do this fair and square.
What's with that girl?!
That's Real Music's Wakamatsu Madoka.
As far as I know...
...she's your biggest rival for this audition.
Eh?
Really?
You're going to keep playing dumb, huh?
Back then, I...
...must have looked like a total fool.
But just you watch, Full Moon!
Someone like you...
I'll take you down to your knees!
The other rivals are...
They're all rivals.
They're all people I've seen on TV or in magazines.
You're kidding!
That's Wakamatsu Madoka?!
I didn't notice it until you mentioned it.
Right?
She was so ordinary when she was a child actor.
Yep!
It's almost like she's a completely different person.
Could it be that she had plastic surgery?!
I don't know about that.
But... she sure cleaned up nicely.
I couldn't possibly be like her.
Madoka-san...
She's been in show business since she was little...
What an amazing person...
I wonder if someone like me can beat her...
Hey, hey!
What are you so nervous about?
I guess it can't be helped.
To help you out during the audition...
...I'll give you advice.
Okay?
Be sure to respond sincerely and distinctly.
Okay.
In any case, just relax.
Stand up straight.
Okay!
Your answers should be clear and snappy.
Look straight into their eyes while you're talking.
Yes, ma'am!
Very good.
Let's go then!
Okay!
Huh?
What's wrong?
The door won't open!
What?!
Is it broken?
Hey!
Is anyone there?!
I was sure she'd be here,
now where'd that Mitsuki go?
The audition's about to start.
Ooshige-san!
Mitsuki!
Where'd you run off to?
Sorry.
The bathroom door wouldn't open...
Anyways... at least you made it in time.
This is the new concept that they just handed out for their product.
Look it over at least once.
Okay.
It's that girl.
She had to be the one who did it!
No way...
Don't just jump to conclusions like that!
Also... you will be interviewed in pairs.
That's how the judges have decided to do it.
Well... that's who you'll be with...
The person over there seems happy about it for some reason...
Don't lose!
Okay!
I'll do my best!
It's almost time...
Ah!
Wait!
Why am I worrying about it?!
After the people ahead of you come out...
...please go in and take their places.
Okay!
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
I
I'm finally here...
I'm totally positive that what happened in the bathroom...
...was all her doing.
You're still talking about that...
You managed to get out, huh?
See! Look!
So she did do it!
Is there someone that you like?
Huh?
Stay calm!
She's trying to make you lose your composure before the interview!
What difference does it make if there is one?
The worst thing that can happen to someone doing commercials is a scandal.
The image of the product would be instantly ruined.
That's why...
...if a scandal were to happen during the contract period...
The company behind the commercial would, of course...
...terminate the deal accordingly.
R-Really?
What should we do then?!
She's lost her confidence now.
I wonder if Meroko can handle it...
No.
It doesn't matter.
Of course, I use Mermaid Tear shampoo every day!
All the beauty parlors say Mermaid Tear is great.
It's all I've used since!
I see.
I came, despite not knowing a thing about the product...
If they ask me... what should I say...
Your purity is your strength, Mitsuki.
So just say how you feel truthfully.
Just tell them how I feel truthfully?
Hey, hey!
Don't look so uneasy.
I'll come up with the perfect thing to say!
Meroko... that's...
And... what about you, Full Moon-san?
Ah.
How do you fit the shampoo's image?
Ah...
I...
That is...
Ever since I was little, I've always wanted hair that would bounce!
All right!
Bounce, huh?
Fire!
Oh crap!
It's too strong!
Stop it, Meroko!
I'm trying!
Um...please excuse me.
This isn't really anything...
Um...
Enough!
Ah... it stopped.
U-Um...
Ta-da!
Isn't it bouncy?!
You're quite funny.
That wasn't funny at all...
Or something like that...
Even that worked?
At this rate...
Well, that's it for the interview.
Ah, okay.
Thank you very much!
Ah... by the way...
Full Moon-san...
Shouldn't you tell them about that.
Eh?!
You have someone that you like, right?
How could she say that at a time like this?!
I-I'm sorry!
I said it out loud!
Did I do something wrong?
Uh... not really...
Huh?
What is this?
Um...
Someone that she likes...?
That's...
Say that you don't have one!
Cover it up!
Cover it up...?
Eh?!
But we can't see the moon when it's covered up.
Even if you can't see it...
The power of the moon will show you the way.
So, on nights like these... just close your eyes...
Listen to the sound of the waves...
You can still feel the moon up in the sky, can't you?
Do you feel it?
But...
What?
Then the moon can't play hide and seek anymore...
You're right.
If it's for the promise I made with Eichi-kun...
Why do I have to hide it?
Hiding it feels like it'd be wrong...
It's the truth, so...
What's wrong?
There is!
There's someone I like!
Oh man...
That's the worst thing for an image...
That'll be the end for her...
Mermaid         Tear
Commercial     Audition
Room
Waiting
What?!
You told them?!
Yeah.
Oh well... it can't be helped...
That's just how you are, huh?
I see.
So it doesn't look too good, huh?
Well, don't worry about it.
It's just one audition...
Okay... bye.
So...
Meroko couldn't pull it off after all...
Ah. Meroko, where'd you go?
I got a phone call... from Takuto...
Takuto? What'd he say?
He said not to worry about it.
Really...
But... I didn't tell him you mentioned Eichi-kun during the interview.
We would like to congratulate everyone on a job well done.
Well, now I'll announce the results of the audition.
Eh... the judges have decided...
The Image Character for Mermaid Tear will be...
Real Music's Wakamatsu Madoka-san.
Thank you very much!
We're counting on you.
Okay!
This makes us even for the last time...
Well... we're not done yet.
Village Pro's Full Moon-san.
Yes!
You also fit the commercial image perfectly.
I-I do?!
Yes.
Way to go, Mitsuki!
Thank you very much!
That's all.
We'll change the setup of the commercial...
...and both of you will appear together.
W-What's that?!
Madoka-san.
I'm so glad that I get to work with you!
Let's work hard together!
Please, just choose one of us!
What?
I can't stand this girl!
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
W-Why...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
That place you had to leave for a while...
Sukoshi hanareta basho
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Takuto, you idiot!
Why did you tell Mitsuki that
you were once a human?!
Shove it!
That's my choice to make!
Choice?
Hey Takuto...
You do know what will happen if we Shinigami fully recover our pasts as humans...
I know!
I'm fine!
Leave me alone!
Hey, Takuto!
Wait!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Two Different People
Look forward to it!