Now, as such,
under the aristocratic republic system,
the aristocracy occupy all
of the important offices,
and at the time in Rome,
the aristocrats, called the patricii,
and the common people, called the plebs,
as well as minor farmers,
This is boring. were clearly
divided into two separate classes.
Now, the two consuls, the dictator,
and the 300 senators
were all selected from the aristocracy;
the senate was the highest
legislative and advisory body,
and the senators served for...
What's all this commotion?!
Is that Class A? Omichi-sensei?
What are you all even doing here?!
Mm-hmm, probably.
If you're not here to learn, then leave!
I don't think you have
any desire to learn!
People like you will do no good
when you get out into society!
That's Class A, all right.
What could have happened?
Hey, Tamura, stand up!
Beats me. Maybe Omichi has snapped again.
Stay standing until you remember!
Hurry up and say something, already!
Omichi-sensei, is it possible that
you have the wrong class schedule?
What?
Before you blame us, please check
your notes once again.
Is that Chitanda?
Ah, I see. Sorry.
Okay, Tamura, sit down.
Uh, okay then.
Well, let's resume our lesson.
Let's see, where was I?
The senate, right?
Now, the senate was the highest
legislative and advisory body...
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
Committing a Cardinal Sin
Earth Science Prep Room
Fuku-chan, you're the one who
said you were going to do it in the fist place, aren't you?!
Mayaka-san, um, please calm down.
Chi-chan, you stay out of this.
Maybe you did have a reason, but what's
the big idea?!
I know! Mayaka-san,
It's only natural that you'd at least call me!
would you care for a cookie?
It would have been fine if you'd cancelled, if you
would've only called!
You do have a cell phone, right?!
What were you thinking?!
Um, well, I'll go buy some milk.
You do have a cell phone, right?!
What were you thinking?!
If it only concerned me, that'd be one
thing!
Why are you pulling that face?!
Listen to me!
Ah...
Do you know what trouble you're in?!
Daring move, there, Chitanda Eru.
Just apologizing to me won't get you off the hook!
You're usually so on the ball,
but when it comes to the basics,
You'll accomplish nothing.
You could stand to be a little more nice!
You knew what would happen,
but you didn't do anything, did you?!
Afterward, it started raining,
the wind started blowing,
there was lightning, and then finally,
it even started to hail!
I'll bet you wouldn't have noticed,
even if we did meet up.
I mean, I did pick out
my clothes, at least,
but before I knew it, they were
in shreds! In shreds!
And all of it is your fault, Fuku-chan!
Aren't you worn out yet?
Yes, I am.
Take a breather.
I think I will.
I didn't do it to save you.
Wow, I have to say, you do get mad a lot.
It relieves stress, right?
Fuku-chan, if you had your
head screwed on right,
I wouldn't be building up so
much stress before getting mad.
Yeah, well, you should take a
page from Chitanda-san here.
I've never seen her get angry.
Huh? Speaking of not getting angry,
I've never seen you get angry,
either, Fukube-san,
nor have I seen Oreki-san get angry.
Fuku-chan gets mad.
Yeah, Satoshi gets mad.
Is that right?
Well, sure. I don't get as
hopping mad as Mayaka does,
but sometimes, yeah.
I can't even imagine you ever
getting angry, Fukube-san.
Well, I am human, after all. I do get mad.
You don't say.
You just don't make a big show
of venting your feelings at everyone.
He's not very scary when he's angry.
I'm not? Aw, don't think
much of me, do you?
That does make me
a little curious, maybe.
Yikes.
I'm guessing that before too long,
Chitanda might hatch a scheme,
just to get Satoshi angry.
I look forward to it.
Oreki-san, do you get angry, too?
Ha, there's no way Oreki gets mad.
Because he's so mild-mannered?
Mm-mm. Because as a person, he's too
empty to even properly get mad.
Hey. I don't care who you are,
that's over the line, isn't it?
Oh, look, I got mad.
Hotaro's emotional shortcomings aside,
the way Chitanda-san doesn't get
angry is in a league of its own.
Call it tolerance, maybe.
Mayaka, I wish you could be
more laid-back, like Chitanda is.
That's an easy thing to ask, but it's
not something I can do, is it?
I could never emulate Chi-chan.
Um, I shouldn't take that
as a compliment, should I?
If I had to say one way
or the other, it was one.
It's just an evaluation; it's not
a judgment, good or bad.
Wait, now, leaving not being
able to get angry aside,
not getting angry is itself a virtue.
After all, wrath is a serious sin.
Mayaka, I wish you'd go
a little gentler on me.
Sin?
You mean the seven deadly sins, right?
Yep. Way to go, Chitanda-san.
They're generally known, so Mayaka,
you've heard of them, right?
Yeah. Even I know about those.
I thought there were 108 sins.
Those are the earthly desires.
'Zat so?
Let's see...
there's wrath, pride, gluttony, greed...
Um...
Envy, lust, and sloth.
That's them!
Sloth, eh?
Why is she looking at me?
Then, Chi-chan, that
makes you perfect, huh?
Huh?
You're earnest, and you don't eat much.
I wouldn't say that.
I doubt you're too greedy,
and you're so diligent.
Um...
Not to mention, that is...
not being slutty.
I'm telling you...
There's no way for us
to know if she's envious.
These two are way beyond complimenting her;
now they're just full-blown teasing.
Let's stop talking about it.
Besides, when I'm hungry, I eat plenty.
She doesn't seem like the envious type.
Of course you do.
She seems like she could
be Saint Eru, huh?
"Chitanda Eru" sounds like it could
be an angel's name, doesn't it?
As in, "Uriel," "Gabriel,"
"Chitanda-el (Eru)"?
Please stop, I said!
She's mad.
Moreover, she scolded us.
Sorry, sorry, Chi-chan.
I'm not talking to you!
Look, Fuku-chan, Chi-chan is
mad now because of you.
Mayaka, you were in on it too, weren't you?
I don't think that not getting
angry is a good thing.
I mean, that goes for the
other cardinal sins, right?
I think that pride and greed
are important things.
In what way?
If you think of someone
who has no pride at all,
that's someone who has no
self-confidence, isn't it?
If someone doesn't have any greed,
it must make it hard for him
to support a family, wouldn't it?
If people the world over
weren't envious of anyone,
there would never be any new
technologies developed, would there?
Oh, um... I don't think you need
to listen so attentively to this.
Hmm, I get it. An interesting take.
In other words, it's a matter of degree?
I just don't think we should accept
the term "deadly sin" as-is,
and then apply it directly
to everything in our lives.
So, Chi-chan, you don't think
it's a bad thing to get mad?
That's correct. If you couldn't
get angry at anything,
you probably couldn't grow to
like anything, either, could you?
I can get angry. Mm-hm.
If that's what you think,
then why don't you ever get mad?
Because it's exhausting.
And I don't want to do anything exhausting.
Ch-Chitanda-san has been tainted
by Hotaro! How could this happen?!
We have spooks roaming around
Kamiyama High School!
Spooks that are energy conservationists!
Chi-chan, snap out of it! Chi-chan!
That's right, get it all out, you guys.
I'm joking.
Huh?
I was joking.
Joking, huh? And here I thought
I'd found a kindred spirit.
I beg your pardon. It was just
the spur of the moment.
It's not as though I don't
get angry. Even I get angry.
Yes indeed, such as...
When food gets wasted, I get angry.
A grain of rice is equal
to a drop of sweat.
She's the daughter of a farmer,
all right. Come to think of it...
Speaking of getting angry,
wasn't that you that got mad during
5th period, in Omichi's class?
Ah, that's right!
How could I have forgotten?!
I would love to ask you about
this matter, Oreki-san!
Aw, crap.
I am curious. I am curious.
Well, guess I'll be off.
Please, I would love to ask you
about this matter, Oreki-san!
Did something happen?
Yes. As it happens, during
my 5th period math class,
I got angry.
Oh, yeah? Chi-chan, you got mad?
But I don't know what it was that
occurred that incurred my anger.
Of course, I didn't have to become angry,
but something occurred
which incurred my anger,
only I don't know what
it was that occurred.
What did you say?
I said, something occurred
which incurred my anger...
Anyhow, now I am curious!
Shousho ('The Warming')
The time ere the arrival of summer's heat
Hyouka
Fight! Fight! Fight!
My 5th period today was math class.
Omichi-sensei is the teacher,
and I believe that you both know pretty well
what he's like, Oreki-san and Fukube-san.
I should start explaining what
happened from the beginning.
Let's see...
Sensei arrived at the classroom right about
the same time the chimes sounded.
Omichi
Before entering the
room, he stopped for a moment,
and looked up at the class plate.
That's something he has
often done before, too.
The first thing Sensei did was write
a quadratic equation on the board...
Huh? Yes, the equation was a simple one,
but he included bounds to the value of x.
He then called on Kawasaki-san and said,
"Come up and find the range of y."
Kawasaki-san was clearly perplexed.
Of course he was.
We had not yet been taught
anything about ranges.
Kawasaki-san answered with
"I don't know how."
At that moment, Sensei got mad,
and started to lay into us.
Next, he called on Tamura-san,
who is very good at math.
However, he was unable to answer, either.
It was at this moment
that I finally realized
that Sensei had made a mistake
with regard to his lesson plan.
The other students realized it too,
and the classroom became
a little bit noisy.
Sensei became even more annoyed,
and started raking us over the coals.
Yes, and as if to punctuate his words,
he beat the chalkboard.
There may have been some in the class
who could have solved the problem,
but everyone just looked at their desks.
Sensei finally called on Tamura-san,
made him stand up,
and started berating him again.
That's when I decided to stand up.
I asked Sensei to once again check
our progress in his lesson plan.
Yes, that's when I became angry.
So what happened then?
Well, Sensei turned the
page of the textbook,
whispered "Oh, right,"
and offered a word of apology,
told Tamura-san to sit down again,
and continued teaching like normal.
So that's the kind of
teacher Omichi is, huh?
Absolutely. I mean, thanks to him,
I can't tell you how much grief
I went through after midterms.
We had teachers like him in elementary
and middle school, too, right?
He's not especially a bad teacher.
Besides, your failing grade
is hardly Omichi's fault.
You'd better buckle down on the final.
So that's what happened. What do you think?
Was there anything about it
that was that strange?
Ah! What I wanted to ask you was how
did Sensei make that kind of error?
Sensei doesn't make too many mistakes.
Well, you know. Omichi may
be strict with his students,
but he's also strict with himself, too.
And yet, how did he make such a mistake?
That's what I don't know.
I don't know why, either.
Oreki-san!
Beats me. If you want to know
why Omichi made a mistake,
go and peek around inside his head.
If I could just peek around,
there'd be no challenge.
Oh, yeah? That's a shame.
Well then, give it up.
I'm too curious! Oreki-san,
please think about this with me!
Why me?
If you will just think about it
for me, we can figure it out!
Oh!
Don't talk to me like you're trying
to get a child to do something.
Chi-chan, putting your hopes
in him is a shaky proposition.
The guy was a katydid in a previous life.
Huh?! Mayaka-san, you can tell past lives?!
Yes! Nice going, Ibara.
But right now, I'm more
curious about our Sensei.
Tch! What a headache.
I am curious!
The Calamity in Summer
Sensei makes sure to write a note
in his textbook after class.
What do you think that is for?
So he can check to see how far
he has gotten in the lesson?
That's what I think. In addition,
he looks at the plate before going
in the classroom to double-check.
It would be easy to say
it's a perfect system,
so where is there any room
for him to make a mistake?
His notes are probably something like,
on page 15, he'll write "Class A, July 1."
Otherwise, he'd lose track
of how far he has gotten.
Could he have gotten the day wrong?
In that case, he would have gone backward;
he wouldn't have gone ahead, would he?
Use your brain.
Well, she's right.
Something's bothering me.
Can I ask you something?
Yes, go ahead.
I can understand you
getting mad during this.
I just can't see you deciding to say
anything back to a teacher like this.
So why did you?
I did get angry,
but I don't think I was angry because
he was saying mean things to us.
Then, was it because those who could
solve the problem said nothing?
No. Nobody would have wanted to go
up and solve it in that situation.
Was it because nobody else spoke up
to tell him he was mistaken?
No.
Was it because you felt sorry for Tamura?
I did feel bad for him, but I don't
think I would get angry because of it.
I mean, it's natural for a student
who doesn't remember
the material from the previous class
to get yelled at, isn't it?
But when you ask me why I got angry...
It can be hard understanding
ourselves, huh?
Yeah.
What makes Chitanda angry,
and what makes her happy?
I still don't know her well
enough to be able to say that.
What do you think, Oreki-san?
The part about Omichi writing a note
about the class's progress in his book
is probably right on the money.
And yet, he still made a mistake...
Since they're moving forward,
there would have to be notes on the
pages that came before the right one.
You said that your class hadn't
yet learned about ranges, right?
Yes, that's right.
Supposing you already had
learned about them, then what?
What do you mean?
Omichi teaches math every year.
Class 1-A last year learned this, right?
If you're saying he mistook
them for the year before,
I'm afraid that couldn't happen.
Why not?
New teacher's edition textbooks
are re-issued every year.
Whenever there are slight
corrections made,
It would be inconvenient to have
the two versions be different, right?
In fact, the version that Omichi
is using is this year's 4th Edition.
Is that right?
You sure do have lots of
useless knowledge, as usual.
I am a database, after all.
Hmph.
Hm... Suppose Omichi does have
a habit of writing things down,
and just got them mixed up? But then,
I doubt that would convince Chitanda.
I have to admit, I don't quite get ranges.
It's a chore just for me to
write x and y in the same plane.
If Omichi sets his sights on me,
I'll be in for some real terror.
Just a second.
Hmm?
Is Class D already on the ranges unit?
Oh, mm-hm.
So Satoshi's class is already
on the ranges unit,
but me and Chitanda's classes aren't yet.
So that's it.
That's the look of someone
who's thought of something.
Yeah, maybe.
Chitanda...
Yes?!
You're sure that there was
a note on the page
after where you had
actually reached, right?
Right. I believe so.
But it was one he had written this year...
A note showing how far
the class had gotten.
Yes.
So what if we were to assume
that it wasn't for your class?
What if it were a progress
marker for Satoshi's class?
For mine?
Omichi is in charge of
four classes... A, B, C, and D.
Even if it wasn't for Class A or B,
that doesn't necessarily mean
it was for Class D, does it?
So what if it was for Class D, anyway?
If it was Class D, it wouldn't surprise
me if he mistook it for Class A.
There's no way he could have
mistaken a C for an A, after all.
Huh? Now you're not making sense again.
You wouldn't mistake an A for a D, either.
But Omichi is a math teacher, right?
So?
As a math teacher, there's a higher probability
that he would mistake an A for a D.
Huh?
Let's say that
Omichi wrote on page 10, "July 1, A,"
♪Sketched by Oreki Hotaro
then on page
15, it would be "July 1, D," right?
So what are you getting at here?
There's no
way to mistake those two, is there?
But if he did mistake the A for a D,
an incident like today's might happen.
Yes, but how could it?
Because as a math teacher,
he would write it like this.
Ah! A lower-case "a" and "d"!
I get it!
Mm-hm, that's possible.
Once on an English test,
I lost points because they
couldn't tell my letters apart.
Oh, you, too? Though in my case,
it was "n" and "h."
You're right. That does seem possible.
Whew, that's settled.
An "a" and a "d"... I can't
blame him for mixing those up.
I guess I really may have been
a bit out of line with Sensei.
I've gone and done a bad thing.
Eh?! How do you figure that?!
Omichi was in the wrong, so you
couldn't have been out of line!
You know, Chi-chan, you...
Now, now, look how late it's gotten.
Isn't about time we were leaving?
Huh? But, Fuku-chan...!
It doesn't matter, does it, Mayaka?
The mystery has been solved.
That's not what I mean! Fuku-chan!
The slow-to-wrath Chitanda became angry,
and wanted to know why.
Despite saying that getting angry
wasn't a bad thing, the truth is,
she never does want to get mad, does she?
Hotaro and Chitanda-san, let's go!
So could the reason why Chitanda
wanted to know why she got mad
Oh, right. I'm straightening up now.
have been because she wanted to give Omichi his due,
and to believe that getting
mad was her own fault?
Could that be the kind of
person Chitanda Eru is?
Nah.
What do I even know about Chitanda?
Even if I were able to predict
Chitanda's behavior,
if I thought I could read what's
inside her mind, then...
Well, it's that.
Committing a cardinal sin. It's pride.
Refrain from such, refrain from such.
I mean, how many times today have
I been taken aback by Chitanda?
Oreki-san...
Aren't you going home?
Oh, yeah, I'm coming.
Oreki-san...
Thank you very much. You are
always helping me out, huh?
It's a real hassle for me, though.
What are you two waiting for?
Aren't you going home?
Yes, we'll be right there.
Shall we be going?
Yeah.
I guess I'll pick it up again tomorrow.
Oreki-san!
That's probably true for you, Mayaka.
But think about it a minute...
And so, once again, a day of my
high school life is squandered.
The deadly sin of sloth that I commit
is more than enough for me.
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "Upon Seeing the True Nature."
Upon Seeing the True Nature