Komachi-kun?
What's wrong?
Get the hook in the middle.
Komachi-kun...
Like hell I could do it!
Komachi-kun?
Recruiting translators for the upcoming shows. Visit #ryuumaru@irc.rizon.net or contact us at Ryuumaru.Fansubs@gmail.com
I knew that it'd be impossible for boys to join the Underwear Society.
Yako-chan.
Geez... We're not going to get anywhere if he can't even touch a bra.
Shut up, forehead freak.
Did you say something, cat-eyes brat?!
Calm down guys.
I understand what Yako's trying to say.
I think boys only see underwear as something erotic.
Good morning, Keigo-san.
You'll be wearing summer uniforms starting today?
Does it look good?
It's cute.
So, how many fried eggs do you want to eat?
Two, and I'll toast some bread.
Please do.
Nayu.
The color of your bra strap is visible through your clothes.
What?! No way! I'm gonna go change it.
Well, I think boys wouldn't mind seeing your bra a little.
You shouldn't look at girls with those perverted eyes.
Puberty sure is a rough stage.
Wait. What am I, an old man?
Isn't that girl's bra visible through her shirt?
Obviously she wants people to see it.
Seriously? That's dangerous.
So this is what our classroom's gonna be like from now on?
I don't think I'll be able to study properly.
About that thing on sale next week...
Oh, it's already over.
No way! Seriously?
Geez... Why don't they realize that they are causing trouble for others around them.
It's hard enough trying to get that crappy mock exam out of my head.
Why do I keep losing to that girl who's constantly thinking of panties?
My mock exam score?
Let me see it.
Here.
Panties and bras and panties and bras and panties and bras... Geez!
No! I've got to calm down!
I can't control my imagination!
I don't know how to understand boys' feelings.
What do you want to do after this?
Maybe I do understand how boys feel.
But right now!
Switch on!
They're this spring's new product.
Although they're for teens, the mature design of it makes them great.
I wonder how they feel.
Seems like they are made of cotton, which is perfect to wear in summer.
But the awesome design is still preserved in the luxurious decorations...
N-Nayu-chan?
Haruka-chan, Yako-chan.
G-Good morning.
What were you mumbling about?
I was thinking about various things when I saw underwear in front of me.
I do understand your desire to comprehend the male mind,
but that's no excuse to look up girls' skirts.
There's no connection between your thoughts and actions.
I just lost myself there...
That's just like you, Nayu-chan.
Isn't that...
What? A letter?
I don't know.
Could it be a love letter?
How old fashioned.
There's no way.
T-There's nothing odd about her getting love letters.
She's cute, hardworking, and isn't afraid of having her breasts touched.
Wait, what am I thinking?
The man who expressed his love in words and delivered this letter to you is definitely...
Someone like this!
Yako-chan, that's a bit...
No, the sender might not be a man!
Hayama-san...
It could be a drag queen!
Calm down you two. It's still not confirmed whether it's a love letter or not.
"I'll be waiting for you in the courtyard after school."
A-Amahara-san.
I didn't realize there were men interested in childish girls like you.
More like, your boyfriend would be some kind of an underwear maniac.
I-It isn't like that!
Oh my, don't you think it's important for a couple to enjoy that kind of excitement?
Though little kids might not understand it.
She's turned on again, even though it's early in the morning.
The memory of that labor,
was still pretty strong somewhere in his mind.
I wonder who it is.
I wonder what he likes about me?
Which means...
Based on what we've covered, you can apply this formula.
Seriously, look at those huge tits.
F? G?
You stick with your B's. Don't dream too much!
No, I like A better.
You guys, don't bring stuff like that in the classroom.
Komachi, huh?
What a boring guy.
Stop studying all the time and take a look at this.
Aren't you used to these type of things in that Bra-Panties club of yours?
Bra-Panties Club?
You know, that Underwear Club the girls from Class A put together.
You've gotta be kidding me!
What's with this underwear, anyway?
If she wears such a small sized underwear,
the wires will dig into her, which is bad for her body!
Only you guys would be happy with it!
I can't believe I thought Komachi-kun was a nice guy.
B-But, I guess he does understand girls a bit.
Doesn't he understand underwear better than girls?
He knows a little too much about it. Could he be an underwear maniac?
Damn you, Hayama.
The weird stuff you taught me is causing all this.
What's wrong with you, Class Rep?
N-Nothing. Sorry.
Oh, seems like there won't be any Society meeting today.
Huh? I didn't hear about that.
Apparently, someone is going to confess to Hayama-san after school.
She received a love letter.
She's more popular than I thought, isn't she?
R-Really? Seems like there are some people with weird tastes.
A love letter?!
Sensei, control your voice!
I'm sorry.
Mizuno-Sensei, as the only adult here, please give Nayu some advice about how to be mentally prepared for this encounter.
Y-Yako-chan...
Let's see... A love letter, huh?
These bittersweet memories are pretty nostalgic.
More like, it's the first page of youth.
That's right, your first love tastes like lemons.
Isn't it nice?
H-Hey! Stop acting like you asked the wrong person for advice.
Nayu-chan, you seem to be kinda happy.
Of course she is; it's a love letter we're talking about.
I-It's not like that...
I'm kinda jealous of you.
Oh, nothing.
Nayu, your bra is visible.
No matter how hard you try, you won't be able to see through it.
W-Who would do that?!
But I want to wear cute underwear in the summer as well!
U-Umm, I knew a dark beige bra wouldn't show as much as a flesh colored one.
I was going to change too, but...
It's just... I couldn't find anything cute to wear.
I knew it would show through, but...
But... Umm...
D-Does it bother you that you can see my bra through my shirt?
How can you ask a guy like me about bras and panties with a straight face?
Because of this attitude of yours, people have started to misunderstand me!
Listen, you shouldn't let stuff like this bother you too much, Hayama-san.
If anything, it's perfect to give him a little peek.
Amahara-san, there's a boy here too.
Sensei, you aren't even familiar with show-bras?
Show-bras?
Is that a bra they put in a store for display?
They are cute bras meant to be seen when you wear clothes with open backs or chests.
Let me take a look!
It's so cute.
There are rhinestones in the straps as well!
What's wrong with you?!
I've had enough! I'm quitting the Underwear Society!
You girls can compare your underwear with each other all that you want from now on.
Komachi-kun...
Hey, isn't that a show-bra?
Yeah. Don't you think this lace part is cute?
Actually, I'm wearing one as well...
That's cute! It's covered in beads.
Awesome, I want to wear cute underwear as well, but there's so many to choose from.
In that case, why don't you consult with Class A's Hayama-san?
Oh, the girl from the Underwear Society?
Hurry up and change, First Years.
O-Okay.
Geez, why does she always act like that?
Why don't you realize that I'm not okay with seeing this stuff, Hayama Nayu?
I didn't know that she had such a messed up personality.
She's the only nemesis and rival standing in my way.
I had always thought of her that way.
More over, after years of competing for the first place, why didn't she remember me?
It makes it look like I'm the only one...
She received a love letter.
She's more popular than I thought, isn't she?
Like I care!
What is it now?
What is it, brother?!
Hey, think you could pick some things up for me?
No!
Get me 50 of the protein I always get.
H-Hey!
Even if they're on sale, what's he going to do with all this protein?
Komachi-kun?
For now, how about we apologize to him through an email?
I don't have his address.
T-Then why don't you try calling him?
I called him once regarding the Underwear Society, but...
His brother picked up the phone.
You want to talk to Hiroki, right? I'll go get him right away!
Hey, Hiroki! It's your girlfriend on the phone!
He told me never to call him again and got really mad.
I guess I should apologize to him in person.
But Komachi-kun's so rough with you.
You're right. For now, take this with you.
Junguji-san, that's adding fuel to the fire.
Okay, time's up.
Did you forget? "I'll be waiting for you in the courtyard after school."
B-But I still don't know what to do about Komachi-kun.
Don't worry; just hurry up!
I want to see what kind of person is confessing to you.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much.
Ah, don't worry about it.
There's something I wanted to talk to you about as well.
So? How are things going with Nayu...?
I already told you that before, but there's nothing going on between us.
Also, I don't have anything to do with her anymore.
I quit it, the Appreciation Society.
I see. So you did feel out of place after all?
I guess it's natural. For men, women's underwear is the fuel of fantasy.
I-I don't have any fantasies or anything but...
Suddenly shoving that stuff in front of your face-
When it comes to underwear, Hayama acts without thinking,
and forgets that it's not natural to show off one's underwear publicly.
More importantly, why the hell is she always shamelessly checking everyone's underwear all the time?!
Some men might like that kind of thing, but I don't like it!
When I think about erotic things even for a moment-
K-Komachi-kun, why don't you calm down...
I understand what you're trying to say. Nayu doesn't really understand the male mind...
But she's trying to be considerate of you in her own way.
Just this morning...
Do boys really see underwear as something erotic?
I guess that's the case.
Let me ask you something.
How do you feel when boys see your underwear?
See? If you're embarrassed to be seen, the boy looking must be embarrassed by it as well.
I really am just a child.
Nayu?
I was so caught up in teaching him about underwear that I didn't think about his feelings.
Komachi-kun, huh?
It must be difficult for a boy his age to be part of an Underwear Society.
But, I don't want to give up on having boys in the club so easily.
Komachi-kun was the one who encouraged me to make a place where I could do what I love to do.
After that, she discussed with me about some male-friendly activities for the Underwear Society.
Komachi-kun, if you change your mind about quitting the society, I hope you'll look after Nayu.
Ah, miss! One miso soup shake with avocado in it, please.
Right away sir.
Hayama was doing all of that for me...
But right now, she's...
He put it in the wrong shoe box?
Yeah. It seems like he mistook her box for someone else's.
What's with that obviously predicted outcome?
Well, I knew that there's no way anyone could like a girl like her, who only thinks about underwear all the time.
That's what you say, but I bet you're relieved on the inside.
Who would be-!
Anyway, I've delivered the report, so why don't you two talk it out now?
You two?
Uh, um...
Sorry about yesterday.
Hey...
I want you to stay in the Underwear Society, but if it's really too much, um...
I take back what I said about quitting.
I doubt you'd be able to manage by yourselves.
Huh? Komachi-kun...
But, let me make one thing clear.
As a boy, I'll see underwear as something erotic.
And one more thing.
I'll never understand your world of underwear.
It's pretty easy to deny all of it,
but even the most powerless guy can try to understand it.
Komachi-kun...
That forehead freak is always taunting me,
and I'm the one who said I'd join the Underwear Society.
I-I'll at least try not to see underwear as something erotic.
Okay.
Damn you cat-eyes, calling me a forehead freak again?
But I'm relieved.
I guess so. It'd be pretty lonely if someone like him isn't around.
Komachi-kun, do something about those boys.
They brought another dirty magazine in the class.
What is it?
Why don't you give them a break.
Boys have their own circumstances.
It's the payback for what you just did.
Even you have interest in this, no?
He's a man.
A real man among men has appeared before us!
T-This is a part of training as well.
I've got to develop an immunity to women's charms.
First, prepare your garter belt and stockings.
Once you're ready, place the garter belt around your waist.
Next, pass the stocking clips through your underwear.
Many people get this step wrong.
Make sure you pass the clips under your underwear.
Once you've done that, put on your stockings...
Snugly rolling them from the tips of your toes to your thighs.
Stockings designed to be worn with garter belts are not particularly elastic,
and will make your legs look better than pantyhose.
Finally, attach your stockings to the garter belt...
And you're done!
Preview
What kind of women do you like, Keigo-san?
I guess my ideal is a dainty, sexy, but strong woman.
I'm not sexy, but I'm certainly muscular and strong.
I don't know about that underwear.
My underwear?
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!
Recruiting translators for the upcoming shows. Visit #ryuumaru@irc.rizon.net or contact us at Ryuumaru.Fansubs@gmail.com