Kiss, kiss, kiss!
kiss
mo
u
mu
I can't take my eyes off you.
Sakura
do
ki
Just being by your side
makes my heart throb.
My racing heartbeat
refuses to stop.
Even though we're just friends,
I feel like we should be more.
I don't know what I'll do
if things stay this way.
I've got this burning curiosity in my heart.
So why don't we do something
You're kidding!
nai
ko
to
ga
nobody else would do?
kiss
Won't you kiss me?
kiss
It'll be our special little secret.
I'm always here for you,
so won't you accept every bit of me?
kiss
Can I kiss you?
kiss
It'll be an unforgettable memory.
Picturing a heated kiss between us
makes my lips tremble with anticipation.
kiss
kiss
ha
na
re
I can't take my eyes off you.
West Misato High School
Student
Council Room
There really is no room in this budget...
President
A true shame that we can't do anything for the third years.
I feel you.
President
They've done a lot for us, after all.
If only we could get some assistance...
Hey, I've got a friend who wants to throw some graduation party.
Want me to introduce her to you,
President Sumisumi?
How dare you refer to your president as "Sumisumi"?
She mad.
Sakura-Colored Truth
(Planned) Graduation Party
for President Mitsuki
Things that she likes...
Green Tea!!
Except for the fact that, like Yuu, she loves green tea,
I'm not sure what President Mitsuki likes...
Green Tea
What to do?
She's probably busy right now...
What's your problem, Yuu-chan?
Why don't you just ask me?
Why didn't I?
(Planned) Graduation Party
for President Mitsuki
Things that she likes...
Green Tea!!
How's President Mitsuki been recently?
Let's see...
For some reason, she's started taking baths with me.
Any strange smells?
Oh, and she's making us sleep together, too.
Any strange marks?
I'm so jealous...
Shimmy
Anything else? What else have you been doing with her?
Hey, Haruka!
This is the new student council president, Otokawa Sumi-san.
She said she wanted to meet you.
Mitsuki-senpai!
Your hair's different, you've shrunk down, and your glasses have disappeared...
What on Earth happened to you?
I'm her sister!
On second remembrance, I do recall her mentioning a younger sibling.
Haruka, would you be that sister?
She's Haruka.
I'm Yuu, the sister.
Yup, she's right.
Talk about surprising!
I didn't expect a freshman like us to be the new president.
Nice to meet you!
Don't kid yourself. I'm not a first year.
But wait, you're not a second year until April.
That's for you girls.
Oh, sorry. This school isn't taking applications for students anymore!
Ahh
I'm in my second year of high school, I say!
I'll be a senior next year!
What
You're a year ahead of us?
Why so alarmed?
Don't have a coronary, now.
You talk funny.
Yuzu!
That's no way to talk to your upperclassmen.
This, coming from the person who called me Sumisumi?
As the new president, it's my duty to be a benevolent figure!
Let me share with you the secrets of my speech!
My dear grandfather is a man of pride, I say!
As his granddaughter, ever since I was born, this is how I have spoken.
Get it? Get it? Pretty amazing, huh?
An amazing tale from President Sumisumi!
Seriously? Drop that shiz.
You kinda slipped there.
Oh me, oh my!
So it's intentional...
So? What do you want with Haruka, President Sumisumi?
Can we stop the Sumisumi thing? Please?
I overlearned that you've been planning a graduation party for the third years.
Well, not all the third years. Just President Mitsuki.
Solely for President Mitsuki?
Big
Sister
Yup. Just for her.
Big
Sister
Did she just call out my name?
Wait, no. Relax. You were just walking by.
I suggest we include Sakai Rina, the former vice president, as well!
Former Vice-President
Oh, that's President Mitsuki's friend, right?
They have helped me in so many ways.
Focus when you get to this part.
R-Roger!
It'll be fine, Sumi-chan. Just relax.
Thanks to their support, I really enjoyed being the secretary.
It's gotta show that West Misato was the right choice for them.
You're speaking normally again.
Whisper
In serious occurrences like thus, such mannerisms are acceptable!
Shock
In light of our small budget, you advocated for the ball game tournament.
I was wondering if we could do something in that lieu...
Hey, I know! Let's invite everyone, and hold a sports tournament!
Yuu-chan, what's President Mitsuki's favorite sport?
She kinda hates exercise.
Dead
I wanted to give the Sonoda Yuu cheer squad a last hurrah...
That's awfully selfish, don't you think?
Don't forget, we're doing this for the president's sake. Not ours.
Forgetting sports, is there anything else both President Mitsuki and Vice President Rina like?
Yeah, thinking outside the sports box is smart.
So, Yuu-chan,
what kind of things does President Mitsuki like?
Outside of green tea.
Well, we share the same tastes, so...
Sweet bean soup, topped with lots of beans,
Drool
or maybe even rice cakes, with syrup and sugar drizzled over...
How traditional.
I'm not asking about her taste buds!
Okay, how about a girls night with a focus on traditional sweets?
Too sweet for me.
You wouldn't know, Ms. Yakisoba Bread!
Hey, yakisoba bread is my jam!
Rage
President Sumisumi, you have any ideas?
Truth be told, I didn't talk to Mitsuki-senpai all that often.
All I could do was watch from afar.
Vice President Rina was often enamored with her, too.
I bet she's head over heels for her!
I think we just got some juicy info on who Vice President Sakai likes!
Well, don't you seem happy.
S-Sorry.
Well, Yuu-chan? Anything else?
Um...
What if we went up to the third years' classroom, and see what's the in-thing?
What a great idea, Shizuku-chan!
Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat
Good for you!
All right. Let's go, Yuu-chan.
Let us go together!
Since we haven't been there before,
it's a bit nerve-wracking going to the third year classrooms.
Is that so?
Their shoelaces are colored!
Soon enough, you'll join them.
Since it's the exam season, it makes sense that there's a lot of people studying.
We really don't know any of the third years, outside of those two.
Maybe you should have joined some sort of student organization.
Excuse us.
Oh, sorry!
Man, they feel so mature!
They're so refined, right?
Although,
your boobs are bigger than theirs.
Cover
That's enough out of you!
Huh?
It seems like...
...for a while now...
They're all eating pudding!
All the students up here were eating pudding, weren't they?
Yup! Indeed they were!
But why? Some kind of pudding boom?
Giga green tea pudding...
Sweet!
Gobble, gobble, gobble!
Sakura
I think we can all agree on a giga green tea pudding contest. Capiche?
Sounds good!
Add some sweet azuki beans, and we're golden...
I do believe that Mitsuki-senpai and the others will love it!
By golly, I'm getting excited!
President Sumisumi? Are you—
Talk about soft!
You might even be a D-cup!
Rub
Let me feel your mammies some more!
You sound like a total creep!
Rub
Hey, let's get this straight. Haruka's a C cup.
Yuu too?
Rub
C?
This so feels like a D.
Rub
S-Stop...
A fine pair of melons you boast, Haruka!
And that, ladies, is where I make my leave!
Let's determine a date soon, okay?
She's a unique one.
Yuu-chan...
You know I don't like people touching my breasts, don't you?
Hey, they were calling out to me.
All you want to do is touch some breasts?
Are breasts all you love?
Answer me.
Huh? Uh...
I...
Hm?
Can't say it out loud?
But you're leaving me hanging...
Nope.
Finish the sentence.
I...
I want you.
Please.
You're a bit more aggressive today.
Don't say it!
Hehe
All right, c'mon! We're heading back!
Big
Sister
Okay, okay!
Shock
Little
Sister
Big
SumiSumi is the President!
The End
Hello, everyone.
My name is Takayama Haruka.
With my best friend, Sonoda Yuu-chan,
I do something I'd never do with any other girl.
We've got a special relationship.
Pop
I recognize that hairpiece!
Yuu-chan!
And in a sudden turn of events...
Good morning, Haruka-san.
I can no longer kiss Yuu-chan.
Flashback
We didn't expect to meet President Mitsuki yesterday...
You two...
What were you doing?
What did you see, Rina?
U-Um... They were k-kissing, I think...
This isn't acceptable at school.
Nor is it acceptable between two girls.
Furthermore,
it seems like this wasn't the first kiss you two have had.
Who started this?
She did.
You did!
Which one is it?
Are you two in love?
I won't tell anyone else about what happened here.
Haruka-san, you need to open up your eyes.
I care very deeply about my sister.
I'm forbidding you from kissing her.
Bang
Sakura-Colored Truth
Today's Activity:
Creative Dancing
- Stretches
- Form pairs, and start practicing
- For next week, figure out a theme
- Stretches
- Form pairs, and start practicing
- For next week, figure out a theme
Wh-What do I do from here?
Something on your mind, Harupoppo?
K-Kinda...
Chillax. You'll be able to dance.
That's not exactly what I was worried about...
Kotone-chan might understand my situation, though.
Can you keep this a secret?
Oh dear! I'm gonna get kissed!
Welcome to love triangle city!
No! That's not what I was going for!
And she just made it way more awkward to ask for advice...
Assume that some third party found out about a secret between you and Shizuku-chan,
and they told you that you should stop doing it. What would you do?
I wouldn't do anything.
Huh?
Well, it was a secret, right?
So just make it a new secret!
I get what you're saying.
It's not a problem if they don't catch you.
Haruka.
I was asked by President Mitsuki to keep an eye on you.
What happened? She didn't tell me anything, just that I have to watch you.
Boom, baby!
Slick moves, am I right?
Ta
Da!
Did President Mitsuki seem mad?
I wouldn't call it "mad."
Wait, nobody's paying attention to me! Why?
I was watching.
Yuzu-chan, you're good at dancing, huh?
Thanks, Shizuku-chan!
She's so sweaty...
All right, students!
We're going to practice some creative dancing now.
I haven't been able to talk to Yuu-chan at all today...
I have no sense of rhythm, so dancing's hard for me.
Aw, c'mon! It'll be fun!
Group up with the people you grouped with last time!
Hey, this means...
I can be with Yuu-chan!
Haruka?
So Yuu-chan, we shouldn't kiss each other anymore, huh?
I guess...
Trip
I'm sorry, Haruka! That wasn't on purpose!
I just tripped, i swear!
It's okay!
You have to be more careful, Yuu-chan.
Just watch, Kaede.
There are other people here.
Wow. So impressive.
Besides, Kaede-chan's supposed to keep an eye on me...
I can't see, Yuzu-chan!
Oh my!
You can't see? Let me show it to you again!
Heh
It happened again!
Wait, Haruka! That one was on purpose, wasn't it?
Very impressive.
We can't do this!
It was an accident...
No...
Stop it already!
Mad
I'm gonna exploit your weaknesses from here on out.
I'm sorry... I'm really sorry...
All right!
It's time to protect the sister!
You headed to Yuu-chan's classroom?
Indeed.
Don't think that I'll allow any funny stuff during lunch break.
I won't let them kiss.
They
Already
Did
They already did.
Oh, I know!
I'll go buy Yuu something from the school store.
Yakisoba bread!
Green Tea Pudding
It's the usual green tea pudding! Nice find, me.
Mitsuki-senpai, you've got the pudding fever, too?
Jump
Why are all the third years crazy over pudding?
Sumi! What are you up to?
I'm conducting some research on pudding sales!
It does seem like the percentage of third years is awfully high...
First-Years
Second-Years
Third-Years
But why? But why would this be?
But why?
But why would this be?
Oh, that's...
But why?
But why would this be?
That is...?
Big
Sister
One time, I told Rina that eating pudding before you study helps you learn.
Big
Sister
It seems that rumor spread like wildfire...
It was just a joke, but everyone's taking it seriously.
But hey, if it keeps them happy, then I don't see the problem.
Whoa!
So you're the princess behind the pudding boom!
The Princess Behind
The Pudding Boom!!
President Mitsuki's
the princess behind
the pudding boom!!
Anyway, Mitsuki-senpai, where are you consuming lunch?
I wish to join you!
Oh, please do. I'll be in class 1-A.
I say, that girl...
She colored her shoelaces, I believe.
ea Pudding
And, of course, she's buying pudding.
Planning on studying, I presume?
Isn't that obvious?
Those girls are serious.
Anyway, let's go.
I wonder if, someday...
we'll have big boobs, just like Mitsuki!
If we eat the same foods, then it'll happen.
Seriously. Don't judge a girl by her looks.
I'll take that one to heart.
You know, unlike myself, you're really easy to understand.
I am?
And I do love your serious composure!
I-I see...
Rub
But your soft spots are nice, too!
That changed quickly.
These might be even bigger than Haruka's!
Come on...
Hold on. You know Haruka-san?
Sup.
Kaede introduced me to her.
That makes sense.
Wait, are you implying that you've touched Haruka-san's breasts?
Oh my!
Why are you madraged?
I wish I knew.
Is it my fault?
No, it isn't...
I just want Haruka-san to reflect over her actions.
That might be what's making me mad.
Mitsuki-senpai, is there something you want to say to her?
Just go up to her and ask to fondle those melons!
I'm not out to touch her breasts!
Well, maybe you have some other feelings towards her?
Huh?
You know, there's a lot of things my facial expressions don't get across.
I say, that's why I began being clearer with my thoughtlings.
Come to think of it, you've really changed a lot.
For one, you used to speak a lot more normally.
Past
All right! Sounds good, President Mitsuki!
A dark past of mine, I say! Wipe it from your memory!
Wait, but the current you...
I
say!
Aah!!
I left my lunch in the classroom!
Just run back and grab it.
I-Indeed!
Things I want to say to Haruka-san...
Well, I want her to be normal friends with Yuu.
If we think about things that are always on my mind...
I guess I want us to be a couple!
Whoa! Timeout, me! What am I thinking?
W-Wait... Is this...
D-Don't tell me...
Haruka-san, you need to open up your eyes.
I said that, but...
I'm the one who needs to open her eyes.
Haruka-san, am I...
in love with you?
No, no! How am I supposed to act around her now?
No!
The chime...
Big
Sister
Sakura-Colored Truth
The End
Love!
love
Won't you kiss?
won chu kiss
Kiss and love!
kiss and love
We've spent so much time together.
futari dake no jikan ga
We have secrets that no-one else knows,
futari dake no himitsu ga
and promises made between the two of us,
futari dake no yakusoku
just for us.
aru kara ne
We'll share in our joys.
yorokobi wakachiaete
We'll split our sorrows,
kanashimi wakeaetara
and we'll eventually find the happiness that comes
hitori yori shiawase ni
from being together.
nareru youni
Today was filled with great memories.
ashita mo omoide wo
So let's make tomorrow even greater.
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichauyo ne
Love you!
love you
It's a miracle that we could meet in this wide world of ours.
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
You're the thing that matters most in my life right now.
tokubetsu nano anata janai to dame dakara
There's something that I can't do with anyone but you.
futari janai to dekinai koto dayo
So hold me dear, with your kiss and love!
imasugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love!
love
Next Time
As sakura petals danced in the air,
my friend Yuu-chan and I became high school students.
Through a series of events and encounters, we made new friends.
The time we spent with them went by so fast.
And so, as the sakura petals dance once again,
I...
"Pudding and Mitsuki's Decision,"
Pudding and Mitsuki's Decision
Sakura Trick
and "Sakura Trick."
It's time.