Are you prepared, my people?
Prepare to move forward! Move forward!
Forward!
Where are our comrades?
Left 40 degrees! Prepare to fire from the main artillery!
Distance 400! Gun loader, Load HEAT round!
Yes, Ma'am.
Olga!
Leave it to me!
We've been confined to this tank for three days!
I won't die before I get out of here!
Target locked!
Fire!
Got it!
Anna, inform the reinforcements!
We destroyed one!
Keep doing it!
Yes ma'am!
Felicia, please screen Anna.
Y-Yes ma'am!
I know it's flashing out there, but it's not lightning, so don't worry.
I know!
On our t-three o'clock!
Why...
Second Lieutenant Anna!
TL Note: Hawkers in Japan usually have their own unique song that attracts people to buy their goods. Here, the song is in pieces so it's hard to translate it.
Paper...
A bamboo strip...
Chirping Crickets
Spirits Down the River
Come on, Noël! You have to press harder to get it washed!
So hot!
Even though it's cold in this building during winter, it's so nice to have a cool summer.
Eh? I thought it was Rio-senpai's turn to do the laundry.
It seems that she's pretty busy, so we took her turn.
Whose is that?
Felicia-san.
She said that she had no appetite and we should eat it.
Then I will have it!
What is this? Dinner preparations?
And... What on earth are you doing?
If you play with food, you'll get stung by a bee.
I-I am not playing with it at all!
Obon is a traditional Oriental festival. The gate between Earth and the afterlife opens on the 15th day of the 7th month of the lunar calendar allowing ghosts come to Earth. People worship the ghosts to prevent them from harming people.
It's time for the Obon Festival, right?
Ah? What is Obon?
Fiesta de Lumière.
Fiesta de Lumière is a local festival in southern Helvetia.
It is based on a folk belief, which says that the souls of the dead return to the real world during a certain period of time in the summer.
As a sign of sending these souls back, people let lanterns float in the river.
In different areas, the same festival is also sometimes called Obon.
Thank you for your patience.
Thank you.
Really? Then it's the same thing!
The souls will return...
Wait, wait, what is that?
Do you mean that ghosts will come back?
In some ways...
Lanterns?
Wow, it must be so beautiful!
Even though we do have some kinds of fire lighting back in my hometown...
What?
Those who passed away will go to heaven, and will always be there.
Those who wander the earth must be the bad ones!
Eh? It's not like that!
But the church...
We're back!
Come on, lend us a hand!
You two, when did you go out to do shopping?
Ah, that is...?
They looked delicious, so I bought them.
And this too...
Is this one okay?
No, that's wrong, priest-sama.
It's like this!
Finished!
Daddy and mommy?
Really? That's so good!
Eh? So it's even approved by the church? That fi...whatever.
Yeah. If this was the central diocese, it would be largely disputed.
But this is the countryside.
That's so sloppy...
In my hometown, we make horses and cows out of cucumbers and eggplants for our ancestors to ride on.
And then, in order to comfort the returning ancestors, people will dance.
Do you also make those things, senpai?
Umm. We only watched them last year.
‏It is also a part of our job to maintain good relations with the local people.
If you forget about the stranger parts of it, then it's nothing but a beautiful festival.
Right? Felicia?
Felicia-san!
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
No. I'm fine.
I just screwed up a bit.
But it's pretty rare for the platoon leader to make such a mistake, right?
As she's not Kanata.
Remember? We've had several pretty hot days recently, right?
I can't sleep very well...
I'm going to rest a little bit.
Felicia-san...
The platoon leader seems weird.
Not just leaving her meal, but also buying watermelons without thinking about our food budget.
She must be going through something. Even if it's her.
I knew that I should have... Let me go and...
Stop!
There's something that she doesn't want anybody to even touch.
Leave her alone.
Noël?
You know about it, Rio?
I read her record.
I know about it firsthand.
So...
Felicia.
Keep that position. Right.
Alright, alright.
And then, the monster which looks like the platoon leader came out!
I can't believe that once upon a time, there used to be a lot of creatures living in the sea here.
Have you heard of it?
The world is marching toward its end.
We, humanity, will end up being totally destroyed one day.
That's... only a rumor.
But, if it's true, then what are we fighting for?
So I... am still alive.
Idea...
Sorry.
It would be nice if I could read your last words...
This equipment...
Could it be... from the old time!?
Platoon leader...
Second Lieutenant Olga, Maslina, Anna-san...
Why... only me...
Why... are you crying?
Oh really? I didn't know there were still people living in this world.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Why... do you apologize?
Because... we lost... to those damn things.
We couldn't protect you from them.
I'm really sorry.
The world ended.
Why would that...
You guys are what remain.
You are the last bubble of hope for saving the people.
It's impossible for humanity to return the world to its former prosperity.
Don't just come to whatever conclusion you want.
But that's the truth.
So, let's end it.
In this world full of all the dregs left behind...
Living sadly in despair...
It must be too lonely for you.
No, it's not!
Why?
Is there any meaning in living in a world like this?
That is...
H-Help!
I'm here!
I'm alive! Please, help!
You are...
Sorry.
If my troop could have arrived half a day earlier, it wouldn't have turned out like this.
Your majesty, Princess Iliya.
But I was a little bit surprised.
About what?
Since you ignored Fiesta de Lumière last year...
What's changed in your heart this year?
That is...
What a nice color!
It's from Treize.
I just bought it from the store.
So great!
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful!
Right?
Right!
No doubt, that person used to be my everything.
I'm thinking about protecting the people in the country, just like that person.
But I sometimes think...
What is the meaning of it?
So, if she's really coming back, I want to understand it.
Instead of talking about this, what about you?
Everybody's worried.
Right. I am worrying them.
That's no good for a platoon leader.
Not just them!
Even me... well...
Well...?
Anyway, don't bear that burden alone.
At least, I can be a good listener!
Thank you, Rio.
Then let me be spoiled by your words and tell you all about it.
What?
In fact...
I was worrying about getting "summer fat".
If things continue like this, I won't be able to wear my winter clothes.
I heard that if you only eat watermelons, you will get thinner, so I gave it a try.
And, what's wrong with you, Rio?
Are you still being absent-minded!?
Weren't you the one at the Vingt Battle Line?
Do you think that I was reliving that?
I-I guessed wrong?
So pretty!
Shall we go there too?
Kureha-chan also made one!
I-I don't really believe in souls at all.
It's just a mission. Mission.
Excuse me...
Felicia-san, who are you sending back?
Yukika Miyaaka
Maslina Sysony
Olga Tolstaya
Anna Blume
Something like Dupont
My colleagues from the past, and a soldier whose name I don't even know.
These people helped me learn what's really important.
Do you mean, that person is...
Felicia-san.
If you are worrying about anything, I...
know I might not be able to help at all...
but...
It seems that you are worried about me.
Sorry.
But, it's alright!
That's so sad.
I'm also worried!
Felicia-san's always been worrying about me.
Because I made you worried.
I'm also worried!
Because, I love Felicia-san!
I love you too, Kana-chan.
Please stay who you are...
Please.
Felicia-san...
I always wanted to tell you.
You are never afraid to say what you think.
I think that's great.
Platoon leader...
Felicia... me too.
How adorable... you all are!
Please come back again next year, ancestor-sama!
Dad... mom...
Mom... sis...
That one is...
Hey Rio, you just asked if there's any meaning in this world, didn't you?
Yeah.
I'm the only one that survived. I've been thinking about it.
Why am I the only one who survived?
What does it mean?
And then, I realized...
that there can't be any meaning in this world.
But, isn't that beautiful?
Because, if there isn't any, I can search for it by myself.
And then, I discovered...
the reason why I'm here.
... and then at that time the bishop...
Then? Then?
It's so shitty Yumina-neechan...
I can't let those kids have the same thoughts that I had before.
Right.
Telephone - Emergency Announced!
Next Time :
Telephone
Emergency Announced!