You're an idiot!
It's bad enough you believed
her, but then you gave up?
Please forgive me, Colonel.
You've gotta stay strong...
And don't you ever
give up on living...
I need to know you can keep your
cool no matter what happens.
Sir.
I'm gonna continue to rely
on you to watch my back.
Don't let me down...
[Havoc] Ya oughta think about
takin' your own advice, Colonel.
Since You were the one
who abandoned his post.
Hey, shut up, Havoc!
[groans]
And what the hell?...
Why are we even in
the same room?...
At my rank.. I should have my
own room with a hot nurse.
Try to understand, sir...
It's easier to guard the two
of you in the same place.
Which reminds me...
Why haven't they tried
to kill us yet?
[Envy] What's wrong with you?!
How could you let that bastard
go after what he did?!...
You should've yanked his
spine out of his mouth!
Lust.. he killed Lust.
It's not too late to kill him...
So get to it!
We can use Mustang...
He's worthless if we
kill him however.
[Envy] Use him?.. Hold on...
You mean the portal?
[Bradley chuckles] You don't
need to worry about it...
And forget Mustang.
Father wants me to handle him.
[Al] What if I've
started to rot?
[Winry] Huh?
[Ed] Huh?
I doubt that my body's
getting any nutrients...
Or any sleep either...
So even if we get it
back from over there...
[Al] Brother!.. Winry!
[horrified screams]
[gasp] Is he right, Ed?
[sigh]
Now this is just a hypothesis...
But I was thinking about
the transmutation
and trying to retrace
our processs...
You remember how we mixed
our blood to create
a blueprint for Mom's soul?
[Al] Yeah.
[Ed] Well.. Right after that we
passed through the portal...
Where we were both deconstructed.
It's a slim chance...
but I think it's possible our
spirits might have gotten
tangled up in the process.
[Al] What are you saying?
I'm trying to explain
that our bodies might
be connected somehow
even though I'm here
and your body's over there.
See.. that might actually
explain why I'm so sho...
sho...
Short.
He admitted it!
[Al] He's starting to face
reality!
So.. You think you've been
supplying all the nutrients
for Al's body too?
That seems a little
far-fetched.
Well what's your explanation?
You don't grow because you
refuse to drink your milk.
Don't start with that again!
[Winry] Well it's true.
[Al] It seems like Brother
is always sleeping...
I wonder if his body could be
resting for mine as well?
[Winry] Not until you start
drinking it! You have to!
[Ed] It's not gonna happen!...
[Winry] Drink it, Ed!
[Ed] No!
[Winry] Fine, stay a runt!
[Ed] I'm not a runt!
[Al giggling] I hope so, at least.
[Ed] Never!
[Winry] I'll make you!
[Ed] Just try!
[birds chirping]
[Fuery] Are you here to
visit the Colonel?
[Al] Mr. Havoc is
recovering, too...
We figured we should
pay our respects.
I definitely owe it
to the Colonel...
He saved me right at
the last second.
Are you also dropping
by for a visit?
And bringing a little present.
[Hawkeye] I counted the number
of steps it took to get
to the basement under
the third laboratory...
And I was able to calculate
the approximate location
of that doorway.
It's not exact since
the hallway curved...
but I was able to
deduce a radius
with the lab at the center.
That's Central Command.. But
this is even more alarming.
[Al] It's the presidential estate...
Right above where we
found the Homunculi.
[Roy] Which means that there's
a very real possibility
the Fuhrer is connected
to them.
[Al] But that doesn't
make sense...
Why did he kill Greed
and his group
if he's connected to them?
It's strange he killed
them anyway...
Why would he slaughter them
before interrogating them?
It's strange alright...
Damn inscrutable.
One thing's for sure,
the enemy's infiltrated
high up the command...
So extreme caution is
necessary at all times.
And Fullmetal?...
Watch yourself.
[Roy] The Fuhrer working
with the Homunculi.
This could be bigger than
I ever dreamed.
I'm starting to worry
that it's too big.
[Roy] All the more reason
to pursue it.
So.. I hope you're ready to work
yourselves ragged.
Uhhhh, yeah, about
that, Colonel?...
I think you're gonna haveta'
count me out.
[sighs]
Your work requires legs...
and I can't feel mine.
[shocked breath]
[Havoc] I hate to say
it.. but I'm retired.
Hello.
Hey.. What brings you down here?
Back problems...
My spine can't stand all
the standing that comes
with being coroner.
I got a sinking feeling
when I heard
you were the person that
scorched that thing...
Are you plotting something?
You suspect a plot but you
still ID'ed the "thing" as
Maria Ross. Three cheers for
old war buddies, huh?
Old war buddies my butt...
More like accomplices.
You'd incinerate 'em and
I'd dissect what's left...
We treated them like rats
and Ishval was the lab.
I know you like to
play with fire,
but someone'll get burnt if
you push this too far.
You should've warned me earlier.
Did somebody get injured?
One of my men.
He was paralyzed. From
the waist down.
Damn. They only let me smoke
one of these a day,
and I go and waste it.
Jeez.. Ya know, I thought I'd
retire because of a woman,
but not like this.
So what happens next?
My family owns a grocery store...
And I can at least take calls.
Isn't automail an option?
[Havoc sighs]
The nerves in my lower spine
are completely severed
and they can't make
those out of steel.
[Breda] Tsk.
The retired life doesn't
suit you.
[Breda] Colonel.
Hmm.
There's still hope for Havoc.
Fullmetal passed this onto me,
[Roy] Doctor Marcoh, huh?...
A medical alchemist
in possession of a...
Philosopher's Stone?
Well, sir?.. Should I find him?
Permission granted.
Get going.
[footsteps]
[Brosh] Oh!.. Major!
Hmm.
I didn't expect you
back so soon.
How did you enjoy your
vacation to the east?
[grunt]
Loose lips sink ships, Major.
The scenery was luminous
and the women desirable.
[uncomfortable laugh]
[Brosh] Oh, before I forget...
This just arrived from
the Provost Marshal's office.
[Brosh] It's an urgent bulletin
for all State Alchemists.
Good heavens!
[dogs barking]
[Al] How'd it go?
Easy.. I told them I was
a State Alchemist
and they let me right in with
no questions asked.
[Al] Did you find the basement?
There wasn't one.
Uh?!
But I did find a trace of
some hasty alchemy.
It was stupid of us to think
that they wouldn't
seal up the entrance.
[Al] I guess so.. Where else
are we gonna find
a Homunculus if we can't
get down there?
I'm not sure.. Remember
how they told me
I was their sacrifice and
they needed me alive?
[Al] They told me
the same thing.
Lust told me that when she found
out I opened the portal.
Well there's one piece
of the puzzle...
They're looking for alchemists
that managed to open the portal
and make it back out alive.
But the real question is why
they wanna sacrifice us...
So.. We'll haveta beat
an answer out of 'em.
[Brosh] Edward, wait!
What the?.. Is that
Sergeant Brosh?
I'm glad I found you.
Yeah, why don't you tell
me what's wrong?
You should get back to
your hotel right now.
I can escort you if
you want me to.
[Douglas] Attention all
military personnel...
It has been verified that Scar
has returned to Central...
Three casualties have
been reported.
All confirmed as State Alchemists.
According to eyewitness reports,
he is described as an Ishvalan
with an X-shaped scar
on his forehead.
Other identifiable markings
include a tattoo on
his right arm.
A tattoo.. It was him.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Al] So you're saying that
Scar killed Winry's parents?
I don't know for certain but
that's the way it looks.
Poor Winry.. Brother...
You weren't planning on
telling her, were you?
Of course not, Al.
I couldn't stand to be the one
to make her cry again.
[Al] Neither could I.
It's the last thing I wanna do,
but we have to confront Scar.
To find out if he did it?
Well that is one reason.. But
there's another.
We're gonna lure out
the Homunculi.
Uh!
They need us alive for their
sacrifice, don't they?
So I doubt they're willing
to just stand by
while Scar kills us.
Ya think so? Sounds like a
pretty big gamble to me.
Well it's much better
than doing nothing!
Oh really?
Because Scar literally tore
us apart the last time.
Well..we've..gotten stronger, in
these, past few months.
What happens if the Homunculi
do show up?...
How are you gonna catch one?...
They're super strong and they
pretty much can't die!
Can't die?!.. Was
that hyperbole?
Or are they actually immortal?
[Al] Why don't we lock
the windows?
[Ling] Count us in.. We'd
love to help you guys!
Why's that?
I can't say I care about
the military stuff...
But it sounds like
these Homunculi
are just what we've
been looking for.
[Ling] What's wrong? You
look kinda skeptical.
Don't get me wrong, I am
grateful for the help you've
already given.. but this-
You've got better odds
with more help.
I'm serious about this.. This
could be what rescues my clan.
Alright then.. Just remember...
We're in this together.
I promise not to run off with
them.. I owe you that much.
What for?
Is this for room service?
[nervous chuckle]
[Ed] You're damn right
you owe meeeee!
[window breaking]
[screaming]
Will you guys shut up?!
D'ya know how early I have
to wake up tomorrow?!
Oh! Right, I forgot!...
You're catching the early
train to Rush Val-
Uhh.
Y'know what?.. You
should cancel that...
Why don't you stick
around and relax?
Huh?!
I mean it's just that...
Y'know.. Well...
There's.. always the chance
my arm could get broken...
or even.. destroyed.
Are you planning on
destroying it?!
[Al gasp] I've got your
soul, Brother!
[Winry] I can't believe you.
Just promise you won't do
anything too dangerous.
[Both] Uhh...
[knocking] Hey, Doc...
Are you home?...
I could use your help
with something.
[heavy breathing and grunting]
Damn.
[Roy] Is that so?.. Report
back to base.
Yet another dead end.
[Soldier] Well. If you'll
excuse me.
Who was that?
[Havoc] My mother and an officer
from the veterans council.
I've decided to go ahead
with my retirement.
They don't know for certain if
your wounds are inoperable.
I'm not dumb enough to think I
have a chance.. I'm useless.
You're wrong.
Look, don't say you can use
a pawn that can't move.
And don't you look
at me like that.
Forget about me...
Move on already!
You don't have time
to worry about me!...
You need to think about
the promise you made
to General Hughes instead
of pitying me!
[Hawkeye] Lieutenant Havoc!
[heavy breathing]
Just let me get on with my life.
I beg you.
[Roy] Alright.
You're cut loose.
[Havoc sighs]
I'll leave you behind so
you can catch up.
I've gotta keep moving.. but
I'll see you at the top.
♪ uplifting music
He doesn't give up...
He didn't even think about
turning his back on me...
And I had given up on living.
It's not in him to abandon
others.. He refuses to.
He's a fool.
He's not gonna make
it to the top...
This country'll chew him up if
keeps on acting this soft.
Well, I don't know about that...
This country needs a
fool like that man.
I need you to bring
me my uniform.
But you're not ready to leave
the hospital yet, Colonel.
Just go get it.
Right away, sir.
[Shopkeeper groans] That's my
livelihood, you idiot!
I- I'm really sorry, sir!
[groan] Well. Sorry's not
gonna fix my stand.
[Ed] Looks like you could
use some help.
It's a good thing
I happened by!
Edward Elric! State
Alchemist at large!
Wow, that's amazing!
Thank you very much, sir!...
Please, You have to let
me pay you for this.
Pay me?
That's not necessary,
but thank you.
Could you please help me
with my broken vase?
It's a priceless family heirloom.
Why, no problem at all!
[clap] Ah hah!
[crowd ohh and awws]
That's right! I'm
here to help!...
I'm your friendly neighborhood
State Alchemist!...
Don't forget! I'm Edward Elric!
[crowd cheers]
[sneeze]
[laughing] I'm pretty
sure everyone in Central
knows my name by now.
[Al] Well you were a
little over the top.
[tires screeching]
When did you become so
theatrical?.. Fullmetal.
Colonel?.. Shouldn't you still
be in the hospital?
Probably.
I heard about Lieutenant Havoc...
I'm sure Doctor Marcoh-
Hold on.
People are watching us.. Get in.
On second thought,
let's get out.
[Ed] Doctor Marcoh's
gone missing?
[Roy] Looks like it.. They
probably took him captive.
There's something else
we need to talk about...
I'm sure you've heard
that Scar's back?
So what's with the showboating,
do you want him to find you?
[foot steps]
Yeah, That's exactly
what I want.
I need to fight him and you
can't talk me out of it.
Have you lost your mind?!...
Did you forget the way he
tore you apart in East City?
Ooooo, sounds like the Colonel's
scared of big, bad Scar...
I'm not surprised considering
how useless
you were against him.
[mocking laugh]
That wasn't my fault! It
was raining that day!
[Ed] Was it raining when you got
beat up and sent to the hospital
You're still useless!
Shut your mouth, Fullmet-
♪ suspenseful music
I guess he got your invite.
You okay?...
You'd think it was raining, the
way your forehead's dripping.
Hold it!.. Don't shoot, Lieutenant.
What? you can't be serious?
I'm trying out the
Colonel's sport.
I think I might be able
to catch a few fish.
[Al] We're using Brother as bait
to lure out the Homunculi.
He's too important to them.
They can't afford to
just let him die.
That's crazy!
We're not gonna let anyone
else get hurt!
Using ourselves as bait
was our only option.
What are you gonna do if Scar
happens to get shot?
The MPs might get here
before the Homunculi.
But you can stop that from
happening, can't you, Colonel?
So now I take orders
from you, is that it?...
You've got a lot of nerve.
You had better plan on sharing
what you catch.
Of course!
Sergeant Fuery's townhouse is
close by.. C'mon, Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Anytime now.
Hey get out of the way!
We need a clear shot!
[Al] Don't shoot! You'll
hit my brother!
Dammit!.. Everything's lost
if those guys shoot Scar...
How long can I keep this up?
Way too close!.. Hurry up,
ya stupid Homunculi!
[Roy] Which channel's the
Provost Marshal's?
Got it!.. You haven't
let me down, Fuery.
Attention!.. This is
sector three patrol...
We're under attack from Scar!...
Request immediate backup!...
What?.. No!..NOOOO!
Alright, on to sector seventeen.
[laughing] This is pretty
fun! Come in! Come in!
But that can't be right!...
He's in sector seventeen?
Then what about sector three?
[Underling] Colonel Douglas!...
He's in sector eight now!
What's that?!
MP HQ calling sector eight...
Scar is currently
fighting a young man...
The young man is a State
Alchemist.. Do not fire!
[Radio] False reports
in all sectors!
We have reports of
a fourth Scar!
This is sector three. All
streets are clear.
Sector eight requesting backup!
Currently engaged with Scar!
♪ supsenseful music
Come now, Gluttony.
I smell the Ishvalan! He's here!
I get to eat him, right?
That's a strange presence.. You
can feel it too, right?
Yes.
Then it's time to move.
Which will it be?...
Is he gonna destroy my
body, or my automail?
[Al] Brother!
[yelling]
Luck-y.
[Al] He cancelled out
Scar's alchemy.
How reckless can he get?!
He's got the tattoo!
Bastard! You were the one!
I smell him!.. Time to eat!
Huh?
[Ling] Hiiii! How's it goin'?
That is one pretty unusual
body you've got there.
Just how many people
are inside you?
Who are you?
Don't bother running.. I
sense your presence...
And I can follow it.
Follow?.. Me?
Then I'll just eat you now!
There it is.
He's a Homunculus.
Sooo... You're able to detect
his presence, are you?
Well that's quite the nuisance.
Let's take care of it.
Lan Fan! Run!
[screaming]
No, Lan Fan!
[Narrator] The scream
of the fallen girl
pierces every darkened
corner of Central.
As the anguished debts of
a violent history are
repaid with bloodshed, the
past and the present reveal
themselves to be murderous
reflections of one another.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 22...
Backs in the Distance.
The young man realized.. He'd
do anything to protect her.