[GINKO] Lulu, I failed you
as a friend, and I'm sorry.
I knew how you felt,
but pretended not to.
I lied to you, even though
you were my friend.
Maybe it's too late now,
but I want you to know.
This is what happened the day
I let go of Kureha's love,
and this is why I did it.
[GINKO, LULU]
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Arashi!
[CUB SOLDIER M]
No way she's not done for.
[CUB SOLDIER N]
Either way, she'd slow us down.
Let's exclude her.
[CUB SOLDIERS] Exclude her.
Exclude her. Exclude her.
[GINKO] I had prepared myself
for that day, and so I was
ready to die there, all alone,
without anyone ever finding me.
[GINKO]
But then...
[GINKO gasps]
It's okay. You and
I can be friends.
So you don't have
to be alone anymore.
[GINKO sighs]
[KUREHA]
Did you know, you and me
are gonna be together
forever, now?
My mom told me
that's what happens.
As long as you
don't forget love,
you'll never, ever be alone,
and if you don't give up
on love, even if
you lose something,
you won't be invisible.
[GINKO]
Growl.
I'm gonna protect you.
I promise you I will.
[GINKO sighs]
[SUMIKA]
Is your love the real thing?
[GINKO]
Growl?
[GINKO panting]
[REIA]
Kureha? Kureha!
--Where are you, honey?
--[GINKO grunting]
[GINKO] I am not
going to forget love.
I am not going to
give up on love.
Growl, growl.
[GINKO]
We will never be alone.
[gasps]
[GINKO]
We will be friends!
[GINKO] After that, Kureha and I
became the best of friends.
[GINKO] We shared so many
things with each other.
Love was sweet, and kind, and
made everything seem to sparkle
like the brightest
star in the sky.
I was so happy, but ended
up getting the wrong idea.
I thought the world
had approved me.
[KUREHA, GINKO awed breaths]
[GINKO]
But then...
[GIRL A]
There's that stinky traitor!
[GINKO]
Uh?
[KUREHA]
No, stay in there!
[GIRL A] I heard you're
hanging out with a bear.
Another girl saw you!
[GIRL B]
That's so not cool!
Um, I dunno what you mean.
[GIRL A]
Don't play dumb!
My mommy says bears are gross
and dirty and our enemies.
[GIRL C]
Bears are evil!
Everyone knows we
gotta exclude them!
[KUREHA]
That's not true!
W-We can be friends with bears.
Wait, are you defending them?
That's so not cool!
[GIRL C]
You must be evil, too!
[GIRL A]
Exclude! Exclude!
[GIRLS]
Exclude! Exclude! Exclude!
[GIRL A] Hey guys, she's an
evil girl who defends bears.
[GIRLS] Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude! Exclude!
[KUREHA whimpers]
[GIRLS] Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude! Exclude!
[GIRL A] We have to
exclude all traitors!
[KUREHA]
Please, stop it!
[GINKO whimpers]
Growl?
[GINKO]
Growl. Kureha got hurt for me.
This happened to her
because I'm a bear.
It's not okay for
me to be a bear.
If... If I were a human girl,
would we be able to
be together forever?
Would I be able
to protect Kureha?
Please, Lady Kumaria, tell me!
[gasps]
[bell tolls]
[LIFE SEXY]
Is your love the real thing?
Yes, your honor, my love's
the real thing. Growl, growl!
[LIFE SEXY]
This court is now in session!
Welcome to Severance Court.
The door has opened,
so enter what we consider
the land of enlightenment
for all living things.
Yes, even human and bear.
We shall now pass judgment for
the sake of humans and bears!
Life Sexy!
Life Cool!
Life Beauty!
[GINKO] Is this where
Lady Kumaria lives?
[LIFE SEXY]
Lady Kumaria has been lost.
She became meteors that were
scattered throughout our planet.
Oh, no.
[LIFE SEXY]
Let the Yuri Trial begin.
Defendant bear, Ginko Yurishiro.
Is there anything
you wish to say?
Growl. Yes, I wanna be with
Kureha forever, please!
I want to protect her!
So please say yes. I wish for
you to make me a human girl.
[LIFE SEXY] Very well.
However, there is one condition.
To become human,
you must let your love go.
Which means, she will
forget all about you
and the love you share.
And on top of that, you're
not allowed to tell anyone
what happened here, or else!
Ah, it's just like
The Little Mermaid!
Sparkle, sparkle!
[GINKO gasps]
[SEXY]
When Kureha Tsubaki wakes up,
she will most likely reject you.
Reject me?
[KUREHA]
No!
It's... It's a bear!
Stay away from me! Someone help!
[KUREHA screams]
[sighs]
[GINKO] That's right, Lulu. To
get my wish to be a human girl,
I had to let go of Kureha.
I had to let go of her love.
And then...
[REIA] Someday, I promise,
the time will come
when bears and people
can be friends forever.
[GINKO] I was sent
back to the bear world.
Now, Ginko. Do you still insist
you love this filthy human girl?
Yes, I refuse to
give up on love.
--Growl, growl!
--[CUBS murmur]
Utterly dreadful.
You are hereby no longer
considered a cub of Kumaria.
Be gone, Ginko the
Lone Wolfsbane,
and blight on this world.
For you are a sinful child
who has betrayed our Mother!
[LIFE SEXY] You must wait.
The time will eventually come
when you will find
Kureha Tsubaki again.
[LIFE BEAUTY]
And, if you can find a way
to become friends with her
once more. Sparkle, sparkle.
[GINKO]
My wish will come true?
[LIFE COOL]
Yes.
You must exchange Promise
Kisses with her.
As long as you do that...
[GINKO] ...I can become
a human girl, growl?
[LIFE SEXY] Now, defendant
bear Ginko Yurishiro, I ask you,
will you become human?
Or, will you give up on love?
[GINKO] I'll never give
up on love, Your Honor,
so I'll become human.
Growl, growl.
[GINKO] I waited and waited
for the time to come.
[GINKO]
And then...
...I met you, Lulu.
Yes?
[LIFE SEXY]
Is your love the real thing?
Absolutely. Growl, growl.
[LIFE SEXY]
The Invisible Storm has begun.
The time has finally come.
[GINKO] I understand, and I
will never give up on love!
Lulu's not gonna give
up on love, either.
She'll support love. Ginko.
Lulu will always be here.
[GINKO]
You were true to your word,
and stayed by my side
no matter what.
You gave me love without seeking
anything in return. Lulu...
Thank you so much.
Huh?
We're gonna be fine!
Lulu will protect you,
and help get your love!
Okay, ready? Let's go to
the human world! Growl, growl!
[GINKO] From the beginning,
we hated you,
but also, we loved you from
the beginning, as well.
And so, I became
a human girl.
Kureha, all I wanted was to
become true friends with you.
So, I had to cross the wall.
[sniffs] She's here!
And you're right!
She really does smell delicious!
[GINKO]
Lulu. From the very beginning,
you were my true friend.
[CHOUKO] Okay. We way
know the problem, right?
We have to exclude, like,
both of those bears lurking
in our school! Is everyone,
like, totally ready?
So we're gonna, like,
confirm this one more time.
Who should we way use
as bait for the bear?
Let's search sacrifice!
[gasps]
Ah!
[MITSUKO] Would you like me
to lick your wounds for you?
I would not. Growl.
Oh, great. You're gonna make me
work for it today, aren't you?
Come on now, Ginko.
Don't be that way.
We both want Kureha, don't we?
No one can deny a
desire this powerful.
Let's find her and eat
her. You know you want to.
Couldn't you breathe in that
delicious smell forever?
I love the scent of a girl who
refuses to back down on love.
Delicious smell. Grr.
[GINKO growls]
[gasps, screams]
[MITSUKO]
Nicely done.
These girls need to
learn their lesson.
A hunter is always in danger
of becoming the hunted.
[GINKO]
Growl, growl, growl!
[STUDENT B screams]
[GINKO]
Growl, growl, growl!
[STUDENT C screams]
[GINKO]
Growl, growl, growl!
[STUDENT D screams]
[GINKO panting]
[UKO] This is the Bear-Killing
Beam Truck reporting.
Target Alpha has been sighted.
Now preparing to fire
Eco-Kumagical Gun!
[KONOMI-BOT]
Nasty?
Buzz, buzz, buzz! Nasty, nasty!
Energy is replenishing. We'll
be at full power in, 10, 9, 8...
[KONOMI-BOT] Nasty, nasty,
nasty, nasty. nasty!
No.
[CHOUKO] Wow, they're,
like, still wild.
I can't believe
she way just tried
to take her
bait like that.
So, how did you, like, tame her?
Like, did you tell her you loved
her and then give
her a little kiss?
[CHOUKO chuckles]
You, like, way disgust me!
[beep]
[UKO] This is Bear-Killing Beam
Truck. We fired on Target Alpha
and did manage to scratch her,
but unfortunately she got away.
[CHOUKO]
Damn!
[KAREN]
This is D-Five.
I've been informed that the
door in the lily bed is open.
I'm heading that way
to investigate.
I was right, they're using
that place as their gateway.
Wily bears. Oh, yeah.
I have something fun!
When I, like, searched your
house, I totally found this.
[KUREHA]
The book!
Your mommy, like,
wrote this, didn't she?
A bear and a human becoming
friends? I bet writing this crap
is, like, way what got her
killed by those bears!
[gasps]
[CHOUKO] "Lady Kumaria"?
What are you, like, stupid?
[CHOUKO] There are no gods in
this world. The only thing like,
ruling us is the invisible,
like, atmosphere.
[KUREHA gasps]
[CHOUKO]
Here, beary, beary, beary!
I have your food, like,
waiting right here!
[MITSUKO] That was a
close one, wasn't it?
Wow, when did they get
that barbaric weapon?
Well, what d'ya say?
Shall we go eat Kureha, now?
Like you can help yourself.
The desire to completely
monopolize another is stronger
than anything in
the world, after all.
[footsteps]
I told you.
I won't forget love.
And, I won't give up on love.
[KONOMI-BOT]
Nasty. Nasty.
[UKO]
Uh... Oh, no!
[KONOMI-BOT]
Na... sty...
[GINKO] I've finally
found the real thing.
I refuse to let it go.
Um, what are you
talking about?
You've already accepted me,
silly. Did you forget?
[GINKO] The thing about love is.
It won't be destroyed.
Not by a storm.
True love is much
stronger than that.
And it would never
leave me all alone!
[GINKO] I can hear her.
It's the same as before.
Kureha's calling me!
When I was separated
from the others,
Kureha was the only
one to find me.
She gave me love, and I didn't
even have to ask for it.
So this time, I'll be
the one to save her.
No, don't!
You can't do that. Don't you
know you're still a bear,
or have you forgotten
the reality?
I am your desire,
which is true love.
And I am more powerful
than anything.
[GINKO]
You're wrong!
Desire is nothing, but for true
love, I'll leap into the storm!
[gasps]
You really think
you can abandon me?
That's not possible!
I'm your desire,
you can't walk away from me!
Wait! A beast who loses
her desire will die!
[GINKO]
Goodbye.
I will tear my image to shreds!
Growl, growl!
Silly girl.
Kureha. I've found you.
Growl, growl!
[KUREHA]
Stay away!
[GINKO]
Hm?
Don't come any closer
to me. Just stay away!
What do you want with
me at this point?
Everything that's
happened is your fault!
From the beginning,
we never should've been friends
because humans and bears
have been severed!
We can't be together
no matter what we do!
So you say, growl. But still,
I'm going to become
your friend again,
and there's nothing
anyone can do to stop us!
After we become
friends like before,
we'll be able to share
a Promise Kiss.
That's all we'll have to do
to make me human forever!
As long as you
don't forget love,
you'll never,
ever be alone.
And if you don't give up, then
even if you lose something,
you won't be invisible!
[gasps]
Shut up! It's your
fault everyone died!
Even Sumika!
I won't forgive you!
I'll never forgive
any of you bears!
Stop this. Just go to
the other side, all right?
I already sent Lulu back through
the Door of Friendship.
Go to her, and never
return here again.
[KUREHA]
Don't move!
Ginko! Stay away.
Please stop!
I won't stop. I can't.
I'll never back down on love.
Uh!
[SUMIKA] Kureha, I'll never
back down on my love, either.
[KUREHA cries] No. I don't
wanna lose anyone else!
[GINKO gasps]
Lulu!
Lulu's sorry, Kure-pie,
but she had to come back.
[KUREHA cries]
He, he. Oh, Kure-pie,
you're such a bad liar.
No! Lulu!
She let Lulu escape, said
Lulu wasn't her friend.
But her lie was, it was
super-duper obvious to Lulu.
Ginko. Lulu knows
it will work out.
She knows it. Kure-pie
is going to forgive you.
No, that's not true. Mm-mm.
She already has forgiven you.
Oh.
You can finally be her friend,
Ginko. Isn't that wonderful?
Make your love come true, okay?
You can get a Promise Kiss.
Lulu believes it.
She believes in you.
Here, Lulu collected
this, it's your future.
Lulu is so clever,
isn't she? Growl.
Damn.
[KUREHA gasps]
Lulu, no. Lulu!
[LIFE SEXY]
Defendant human Kureha Tsubaki,
are you ready to
admit your crime?