The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
What's this about an "urban legend"?!
The black motorcycle!
The headless rider!
The one who rides the black motorcycle doesn't have a head.
He doesn't have a head, but he still moves.
Well, it shouldn't really be a tough job, but be careful nonetheless.
I wasn't aware you joined the Justice League.
Seriously...
What the fuck are you?!
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
The headless rider? I've heard of it!
My friend saw it!
Meh, I'm not too interested.
I actually got a picture of it.
See?
The headless rider?
He's right here!
You girls have heard of it before, right?
I think I might have seen it near the Sunshine building.
Seriously?
I'm not really sure, but that had to be it.
Everyone was making such a big deal about it.
Everyone's so talkative.
I heard that motorcycle was seen again.
Wow, looks like everyone's gathered quite early this evening.
Good evening.
Evening
evening gooD
Wow, looks like everyone's gathered quite early this evening.
Good evening.
Evening
evening gooD
But I wonder if it's really true that it doesn't have a head...
I'm sure it's just an ugly rumor.
But I've also heard that it's real!
Wow...
It's impossible not to have a head.
But if it wasn't human...
...it would be possible.
I've heard the people who actually get involved with it becomes silent.
Sorry. I don't really know much.
And what about you?
What are your impressions of the legendary headless rider?
Scary? Cool?
Or perhaps that it may be a nice person?
Or could it be...
...that you don't really know how to react to it?
Today, I want to tell you what I know about the headless rider.
It'll be a long story with tedious detail, but I want you to listen with a majestic heart.
Alone With
Only Your
Shadow For
Comfort
Let me start out by introducing myself.
I'm Shinra Kishitani, twenty four years old.
I work as an unlicensed doctor in this city.
In other words, I'm a dispatched underground physician.
I treat people who were injured with illegal weapons,
and perform cosmetic surgery on people who need to have their faces changed for whatever reason.
Despite my looks, I'm talented. A lot of people rely on me.
Now, to get into the main topic...
I'm home!
That's right.
I live with the headless rider,
Selty Sturluson.
I'm home, Selty.
Welcome back
My job today was a simple, common task.
What about you?
Don't peek.
Oh, my apologies.
I wasn't trying to be indecent or anything. Just careless...
You seem a bit irritated.
Perhaps you need an inoculation of calcium?
Are you telling me to eat an eggshell or something?
Hey, that's not a bad idea!
But you know,
I'm ignorant when it comes to dietetics.
I have no idea how much calcium is in an eggshell,
or how well it absorbs into the body.
But one could also question out how useful calcium could be to you,
since we don't even know where your brain is.
Shut up!
Hey Selty, I know I keep asking you...
...but how does the world appear to you, as someone without eyes?
It's impossible to tell you something I can't understand myself.
Although she doesn't have a head,
she can see, hear, and also possesses a sense of smell.
But it's not like she can see in all directions just because she doesn't have a head.
Apparently, she has a slightly broader view than the average person.
This is just a reasoning of mine,
but that shadowy mysterious SF-like substance that continues to seep out of your body...
Could it be that instead of light, those particles are released around you
and absorb the places they bounce off of, which gives you information about your surroundings?
Of course, objects that are too far away will be indistinct.
Not interested.
I can see and hear, so I don't care about the mechanics.
Selty, you're always like this.
The difference between the world you're
conscious of, and the world I'm conscious of...
...that's what I want to know.
We're not just simply talking about vision here.
I'm also talking about our sense of values.
Not your sense of values as a human,
but the way you value the world as a Dullahan...
...the one and only fairy that materialized in this city.
What's the matter?
If you don't mind, could you tell me what happened today?
Orihara said that your job today wasn't anything tough.
The job itself was completed quickly without any fuss.
And?
Kudos to you as the deliverer, again.
I can get by because you're here, and vice versa.
I don't want to agree with the vice versa.
Come on, don't say that.
I'll be counting on you again from now on.
I want to get along with you.
Forever...
Is it just my imagination that I feel a certain eeriness from you?
Whoa! It's definitely your imagination.
By the way, have you ever heard of a Dullahan?
Apparently, it's a headless fairy in Ireland.
An old street artist that came to Yoyogi Park recently claims he saw one in the past.
And I heard that old man was making a fuss about him losing her head.
Could he be talking about this Dullahan's head?
Is he still around?
I'm not too sure.
So you are curious about it.
Selty Sturluson is not a human.
She's actually a fairy called a
Dullahan, famous in Celtic folklore.
Do you know of a street artist around here?
Oh, that man is gone now.
Hey! Didn't that old man say he was headed for Yokohama?
Huh?
A Dullahan carries their severed head under their arm,
and rides a two-wheeled coach drawn by a
headless horse by the name of coach-a-bower.
They visit the houses of people who are nearing their deaths.
If you carelessly open the door...
...you'll be greeted with a tub full of blood.
Aside from the fact that she doesn't have a head, it's not easy to relate her appearance to such an ominous, deathly legend.
As to why she came to Japan, to Tokyo, and to Ikebukuro,
and as to why she's so particular about her head...
...will be the topic of my story.
This story takes place twenty years ago.
When she suddenly awoke in the mountains,
she found that her head was missing.
And she realized at that moment that many of her memories were lost.
She lost her memories of why she did what she did,
and also her memories that trace back to a certain degree.
However, she knew that she was a Dullahan,
that her name was Selty Sturluson,
and she also knew how to use her abilities.
And what surprised her first...
So I must have never used my head to think...
As stated.
And she also realized that she could somehow feel the presence of her head somewhere.
After thinking things through, she came up with a reasoning.
Her thoughts were originally shared between her body and her mind,
and the memories that were lost must have remained in her head.
And so she decided...
...to get her head back, which holds the truth about the significance of her existence.
That in itself was precisely the current significance of her existence.
It could be that her head separated itself from her body out of its own will.
Even so, there would be no way to know aside from finding her head.
He was no longer in Yokohama.
Then, I went to Tama, then to Chiba...
Wherever I went, I ended up missing him.
You could have just put it off till tomorrow.
I was desperate.
My head could have been right there.
I wanted to get it back, no matter what.
As soon as I could.
I'm sick of living with such a vague memory.
Although she reached this location by tracing the sensation that was still left in the area,
she found out that her head was on its way overseas.
The ship was headed for Japan.
She decided to stow away to go after it, but there was the horse to worry about.
Her horse is a type of a familiar used by Dullahans, and is a spirit possessing the corpse of a horse.
She could have gotten rid of it if necessary,
but then, where would it go afterwards?
The answer to that was probably with her head as well.
With those thoughts in mind, she couldn't take off even though she knew how to get rid of it.
And that's where...
...she...
...found the motorcycle.
And in the end, I was never able to find my head.
But...
Oh, I know that street artist.
He's been in South Ikebukuro Park since the day before yesterday?
Yeah, him.
Want me to come with you?
Won't it be inconvenient trying to talk with him using your phone?
Right?
And, there.
Wow, this is really good!
This makes you look prettier than you actually are.
Hey!
You're really good, sir!
Oh, no.
Even now, I can't really draw what I actually want to draw.
Thank you so much!
You're very welcome.
Let's go.
Come again!
Okay!
Sorry, it's getting kind of dark.
I'm finished for today.
Is it true you saw a Dullahan?
Why yes, yes it is.
I saw her in an Irish mountain when I was young. With these two eyes.
What did you mean when you said you "lost her head"?
"Lost her head"?
No, that's not it.
She didn't have a head.
I just can't imagine her head to draw it.
Take a look.
The Dullahan was a woman. A stunningly beautiful one, at that.
I passed by her on a mountain trail on a misty night.
She flew past me at an amazing speed.
Her appearance was horrifying, but beautiful at the same time.
I had a feeling she wasn't from this world.
When I went back to the inn and asked about it, someone told me that she had to be a Dullahan.
Apparently, she's been living there for a very long time.
Why isn't the Dullahan in your drawing carrying a head?
I can't draw it.
The more I add to it, the more different it feels.
I remember that day like the palm of my hand, but I just can't reach that woman.
What's the color of her hair? Her eyes?
What was her expression like?
If I could describe those, I wouldn't have attempted to draw her.
Now that I recall, a strange man visited me recently.
He insisted that this picture is perfect the way it is.
That she didn't need to have a head.
A strange man, he was.
Why are you so obsessed with her?
That was the best experience of my life.
That night was my life.
I want to retrieve that moment. The memories from that night.
Thanks, old man.
I see.
But you don't recall meeting that old man, right?
Nope.
So that Dullahan may or may not be you.
Or perhaps, he may have misseen.
That was me. It had to be.
Okay...
I wonder where I was headed?
What were the thoughts in my head? What was my motive?
Do you really need to be that concerned about it?
Huh?
You're definitely an elusive, novel character.
Even then, you've still got a long way to go until you reach your goal.
What are you trying to say?
I'll cut straight to the point. Just give up.
Maybe what that strange guy said was right.
Maybe you really don't need to have a head.
Stop looking for your head, and go somewhere with me.
Anywhere.
If you wish for it, I'll take you back to your homeland, despite what it may take.
I'll go there, too.
And we can be together forever-
I don't dislike you, but being like this is already enough for me.
Don't say that...
It's enough!
Then could you at least try to act a bit more like a girl...
That's it!
So could it be that there's a difference between my sense of values and hers?
Getting back on topic, let me tell you the rest of the story.
Her story after she got aboard the ship...
No, our story.
She was able to convince a crewman to let her stow away,
but she realized how much she stood out.
Now that I've known her for a while, it doesn't mean much to me anymore...
But I was shocked when I first saw it happen.
I was four at the time.
I was on my way back to Japan with my father.
Daddy! Daddy! There's a strange woman in the hold!
My father, Shingen, was completely out of the ordinary.
Hurry!
Come on, Daddy!
Wouldn't the proper reaction as a
parent be to laugh the matter away?
But my father was different.
It could have been due to the nature of his job as a
doctor, but he was suddenly interested in what I said.
Madam.
Pardon me, but is it true you don't have a head?
My father told her,
"If you let me perform an autopsy on you just once, I'll provide you with a place to stay."
She agreed to it.
Although she had her own interests in mind, she must have been uneasy about it as well.
Apparently, she doesn't remember much about this event.
The anesthetic for humans didn't work very well,
so it must have been a huge psychological shock for her.
It seems as though she has a sense of pain, but it's far less than that of a human.
She doesn't have a heart.
None of her organs are performing any of their functions; they're just there.
She has veins, but blood doesn't flow through them.
She just has flesh.
She's almost like a living anatomical model.
But look.
How the hell can one kill her?
Isn't he a terrible father?
He told a four year old to dissect her.
But because of his upbringing, I was able to learn what it takes to become a doctor...
I don't know what to say.
What's wrong?
Ever since I saw her, I was attracted to her.
Those feelings haven't changed at all during these twenty years I've spent living with her.
And she's been searching for her head as she works as a deliverer.
I wonder what she's planning on doing once she gets her head back.
What's going to happen to her?
Are all of her thoughts coming from her head?
Or perhaps...
What are you filming?
Well, how do I explain this.
I wanted to talk about a section of our sweet daily life for the future generations to see.
Whatever, just try to keep it down.
I can't sleep.
Sorry about that, Selty.
Well, I guess this is it for today.
I'll tell you the rest some other time.
Wow! This is perfect!
How is it perfect?
Dullahans are supposed to be carrying
their heads under their arms, you know.
Maybe she doesn't really need to have a head.
That's ridiculous.
You can only say that because you haven't seen the real thing.
She was absolutely gorgeous.
I agree.
But I prefer her without the head.
She looks more charming that way.
That drawing is perfect the way it is.
So you don't need to be distressed over it.
It's fine if you can't draw it.
She can stay like that forever...
But I'll still draw.
I'm telling you, she's fine the way she is!
You're a strange one, you know that?
I don't think I'm that strange.
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Cry Wine And Sell Vinegar
Want to know about my ~love love get chu~ and heartbreaking life?
Then show me, the shy and cool Masaomi Kida, the channel of your heart!
Next time: Cry Wine And Sell Vinegar.
Don't miss the chance that comes around once every three hundred years!