Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
Am I the one who is at fault?
A servant like me...
Nishiyama totally isn’t cut out
for cute clothes like that!
Welcome!
Thank you very much!
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
Teru!
Let's play.
Teru! Let's play.
Teru! Let's pla--
Ring the doorbell!
Let's play. We can play cards.
You came here in this
sweltering heat just to play cards?
Yeah, we'll draw for the old maid.
You came just to play Old Maid?!
Anyway, why don't we go somewhere cooler?
"Your Birthmarks Have Faded"
"Shaved Ice"
Oh, it's so cool.
I'm alive again.
Oh yeah, did you do
the summer homework yet?
Yeah, most of it.
You haven't started, have you?
Nope. Let me see yours once you're done.
No. Do it yourself.
Tch. How 'bout you, Miss Yoko?
Miss Yoko?
Is she sleeping?
A-Are you okay?
How rude! Who did it? It hurt!
O-Oh my, how silly of me.
You said that pretty loudly, sleepyhead.
Although you were kind enough to
invite me out, I could not help myself.
It is so nice and cool here.
Miss Yoko, are you tired?
Oh, well, I have been working a lot recently...
Miss Sonobe's shop?
The maid's castle.
Oh, I remember you saying that you would
take on more hours during summer break.
The store happens to be closed today.
Don't overwork yourself.
Do you feel okay?
Yes, I feel fine.
Ah! It's swelling up!
A rich girl shouldn't have a lump!
I see. So that's how it happened yesterday.
However, I hesitate to have you
work in the front like that.
It was an accident, though.
And it happened because she's overworked.
M-M-M-Miss Yoko is hurt?
And on her forehead? On her head?
What if something happens?!
Or if she gets a scar?! How terrible!
You should get it checked by a doctor!
You could go now!
You should see a doctor.
That's wonderful advice, Futaba.
I knew it was too early for
Miss Yoko to start working!
Too soft. Mitsugu, you've
always coddled Miss Yoko.
You're the one to blame!
Miss Yoko, although you're
a part-timer, this is still work.
I cannot coddle you.
I-I know!
So, please go rest in the back room.
Huh?
Taking care of yourself is also part of working.
Sonobe...
Am I the one who is at fault?
A servant like me, making my
dreams come true by opening this store.
Then, it comes to this, all because I hired you?
I'm sorry. It's because
I'm such a capable manager.
Is your head okay?
Hey-- Yamaji?!
Anyway, she said you need to rest, so go rest!
Miss Sonobe, will the shop be all right?
Miss Sonobe?!
What should I do?
How will I get through today?
It sounds like it won't be all right at all!
Oh, that's perfect. Hayama,
why don't you work in Miss Yoko's place?
What, me?!
Come on, you weren't doing anything yesterday.
You're the one who wasn't doing anything,
coming over just to play cards.
Thank you, both of you!
Let's get a move on it, now that it's settled.
Wh--
Ah!
H-Hey!
Why do I have to wear this?
I have an extra outfit.
That's not what I'm asking! Why aren't I
wearing what Miss Yoko wears?!
It looks good on you.
Do you understand Japanese?!
Ah, Futaba. Have you finished changing, too?
Oh, yes. We have Futaba. We'll get to
see her wear these weird clothes--
I'm changed!
Why?!
Futaba wouldn't fit in my clothes, so...
Why not?
Oh, er, I'm not saying that Futaba has
a dynamite figure, but I'm just quite small.
Should that make me feel better?
Ah, you see, I haven't grown since my teens.
More specifically, since junior high.
You're not helping by saying this,
and it's not that specific, either!
Maybe she's saying that you won't
grow anymore either, Hayama.
Let's stop talking about our sizes!
Welcome!
Oh, the usual girl isn't here today.
Yup! We're here temporarily.
This place always has young girls.
What a fun atmosphere.
Thank you very much.
What do you recommend?
Let's see. They're all delicious.
But this roll cake is simple and light,
because it's made of fluffy sponge cake
and buttercream that melts in your mouth,
and it goes surprisingly well with Japanese tea.
This moist gâteau chocolat has a refined
sweetness that pairs perfectly with coffee
The chocolate is rich and dark.
"Strawberry Mousse Cake"
The mousse in this cake brings out the tangy sweetness of strawberry
and interweaves it with fresh cream
for a superb harmony you can't resist!
They all seem delicious. I'll take all three.
Thank you very much!
Sh-She's good.
They're probably just her own impressions.
So, how about you?
Uh...
It's not like I want to compete with Futaba,
but I don't want her thinking I can't do my job.
Welco--
Welcome!
What kind of cake are you looking for?
Wow! You're really dressed as a maid!
Teru, you're so cute!
Oh, Hayama's sister. You're here!
And you look so cool!
Wh-Why are you here?
I told her.
Do your best, Teru!
Here, candy to keep you going!
Oh, is that candy?
Thank you for visiting.
I expected no less from a professional baker.
Or maybe it's a monster's intuition?
Oh, hey. I want to help, too.
I want to make cakes and sweets with Teru.
That's, well...
This is our new gelée.
Full of fruits and containing collagen
and vitamin C, it's great for your skin.
I don't know what to call it yet.
Can you think of a good name for it?
Miss Sonobe...
--She really can't let big sis make sweets.
--I know!
"Derived from Pigs."
"Derived from Pigs"
Derived from Pigs?!
Big Sis! You mean, "Derived from Pig Skin"?
Oh, collagen is derived from pig skin, huh.
But "Derived from Pig Skin" is so hard to say.
On second thought, I'll think of a name myself.
Big Sister! Where are you, Big Sister?
Is it true that you're working part time?
Oh my, if it isn't Takezono's--
Oh! I know you.
Young Master Takezono,
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
Will you please keep it down?
Miss Yoko won't be able to rest properly.
Hi, little boy. Did you come to see Yoko?
Huh? Yes.
I wanted to make sure she was okay and stuff...
You're very kind, Young Master Takezono.
How adorable.
Your bottom is cute, too. Your birthmarks
have faded already, haven't they.
--Wh-What are you doing?!
--She does everything as she pleases.
What the heck! I don't care
if you're her former servant or maid!
I can't let her work here!
Not at this dumb and creepy shop!
Little boy.
No!
You shouldn't be talking like that.
You would be hurt if someone
said mean things to you. Right?
Y-Yes.
He just likes older girls?
Good. You get a reward for being a good boy.
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
Oh yeah. This is for Yoko
so she'll get better quick.
The smell's leaking past the container!
My eyes sting!
Is your sister licensed for these substances?
Does she handle poisonous substances?
Yoko, I have food for you.
Please, stop!
Nishiyama! Wanna go have fun?
Nishiyama!
Hey! Nishiyama! Nishiyama,
Nishiyama, Nishiyama, Nishiyama!
We're all Nishiyamas here!
And how many times did you ring?!
Come on, let's go to a cake shop!
What?
This one! I hear the new gelée is great.
There were flyers all over school.
I can't spend money right now.
Huh? Why not?
A camera.
Camera?
I want a camera to take
cute pictures of my baby with.
Oh, you haven't given up on that yet?
We can be together all day long
during summer break, so I should--
So which looks good to you?
I want this one--wanna split it?
She's not listening...
And two of these gelées.
Two Derived from Pigs, coming right up.
Futaba, two Pigs, please!
Two Pigs, got it!
Derived from Pigs looks like it'll be popular.
No, that gelée isn't--
Miss Sonobe, we sold out of Derived from Pigs!
Derived from Pigs is a hit!
Yeah, everyone buys Derived from Pigs.
Derived from Pigs looks delicious, after all!
I'm glad you recovered so quickly, Miss Yoko.
It's all thanks to Hayama's sister's cooking!
Huh?!
Somehow I've felt...
strangely energetic since I ate it.
And I didn't sleep a wink last night, either!
Is she actually okay?
Well, either way, she's got energy...
Hmm? Isn't that Hayama and company?
Welcome! I'm sorry, but we
just sold out of the new gelée.
Aw, there's no more?
Th-That's not the issue!
Oh, are these acquaintances of yours?
Yes, they're my classmates.
W-Well, well! So you work here,
Hayama? This is a surprise.
Is it?
Why is my heart suddenly pounding?!
Oh, wow! You're a maid!
Y-Yes...
It's that "cosplay," thing, huh!
Hey, do you call the customers "Master"?
This is a uniform, so it's not cosplay.
What? It's totally cosplay!
--Are you listening, Kondo? This is--
--Sh-She's oblivious to the atmosphere!
But I saw this on TV!
I don't work here. I'm helping out.
Me too, but only when it's busy.
They're truly lifesavers!
Wow.
That's right, Hayama is amazing.
She's unfailingly good with customers,
she works quickly, and she thinks quickly.
Very few people her age are so skilled.
No, you're flattering me.
Oh, please. Anybody could do that!
Customer service is a common student job.
I don't want to hear that
from someone who's never done it.
Also, I doubt someone as
overly proud as you could manage it.
T-True, it is bit beyond me...
since I'm not brave enough to wear that.
Yeah, Nishiyama totally isn't cut out
for cute clothes like that!
That's not what I meant!
And you only just started this job!
I'm not sure getting so emotional
suits a customer service position.
Well, would you like to try your hand
at the job? Experience is good for you.
Oh, sorry, my hand slipped.
Five times?!
Please don't do things that
will complicate our lives.
My motives were perfectly pure.
What's wrong with this place?!
Why did we have to go
to a place Hayama works?
Let's hurry home and have tea!
Wait!
Nishiyama!
Wh-What?!
You can have these.
They're part of a special order I made.
Additive-free pet treats.
Give them to your kitty.
Isn't this yummy?!
Yes, that might be
the best patisserie in the area.
But I'd never have guessed Hayama works there!
You want more? Sorry, that's all I have.
We aren't open yet.
Have you decided to work for me after all?
What? N-No!
I prepared everything yesterday,
just in case this happened!
Wh-What is this?
Nishiyama, smiling is the key element
of customer service.
I can't believe I'm doing this...
Come to think of it, Hayama's smile was perfect.
I won't ask you to match her smile,
but try to look friendlier.
There's no way I can't do it, if Hayama can!
Thank you very much!
How was that?
Wait, why'd you photograph me?!
Hmm... Yours just seems unfriendly,
or perhaps I should say unnatural...
Excuse me?!
Hayama told me that you have a cat
you dote on, is that right?
Yes...
Why don't you imagine playing with it?
Playing...
No, that's not a face for customers.
Was my expression that weird?!
One moment, please!
This is hard...
It's fine, no hurry.
J-Just a moment.
Is it your first day? Isn't it great
you get to wear such cute clothes?
I know the truth, Nishiyama.
You pretended not to,
but really you enjoyed putting that on.
Good job, Nishiyama. Bravo!
Wh-What's with the sudden praise?!
She finally complimented me,
even if I don't really get why.
Well, of course! Anything
Hayama can do is a breeze for me.
That's right, I am a capable woman!
Welcome!
Huh?
N-Nishiyama?
Oh, right, they work here... and yet
I let myself be coaxed into wearing this...
A dozen financiers, please.
She acted nice?!
What's this about, Sonobe?
I got curious when you suddenly called
and gave me the day off, but...
Well, Nishiyama said she could do
anything Hayama could do, so.
I-I--
When did you make a new uniform, anyway?
The truth is that I made it for Miss Yoko.
What?
It turned out too tight across the chest,
but it's just Nishiyama's size.
Excuse me!
J-Just a moment!
There are so many customers!
I have to work fast...
Fast...
Nishiyama.
It's difficult for anyone
until they get used to it.
--Strawberry mousse, roll cake,
--Nishikawa...
-and gâteau chocolat, coming right up.
I'm so sorry for the wait.
We'll be right with you.
How about this one? It's new!
Ah, high school girls are joining hands
and making merry at my shop.
I'm sorry, but our star
Derived from Pigs is sold out.
Would you like this roll cake?
Yes, thank you very much!
What a rough day.
Still, I got kitty treats, and...
"Middle Camera"
Hello. Are you here shopping, Nishiyama?
Yes, I need a camera
to take pictures of my baby--
Hey! Why are you making printouts?!
To give you as mementos.
I don't want them!
I see! And by that you mean
you'll continue to work for me?
What?!
Never mind, just delete those
from your phone! Delete them!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative, the poor girl
on a bread-crust diet, and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life
is so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
This is Shino...
...and Selina's next-episode preview!
Nishiyama, you're a capable woman,
so I leave this to you. Thank you.
What?! Well, fine.
"Next time: 'Veggies, Meat, Meat,
Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, and Fish.'"
P-Please watch!
You made me do it, so what's with that reaction?!
"Next time: Veggies, Meat, Meat,
Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, and Fish"