When I grow up, I want to be Prime Minister!
I'll make sure everyone can keep smiling!
That's a big dream.
Anyone else want to share?
Dreams, huh?
I'm still not sure.
But it's cool that you've already picked one, Hishikawa.
Huh?
Being a doctor, right?
Since your mom's one.
Well, she is...
Hm?
Did I want to be a doctor because my mom was one?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Prime Minister?
It's quite like you.
Aw, shucks...
And Rikka wants to be a doctor?
Huh?
Yeah...
What, you don't?
Maybe...
Maybe I don't...
What do you mean?
Well, I always thought I wanted to be a doctor...
but maybe that was just because I admired my mom.
In other words, it wasn't your true desire.
Aguri?
Why are you here?
Long ago, I was drawn to this shop by the harmony of dumplings, gelatin, and brown sugar that is this dish,
and I've been a regular ever since.
Bravo!
What did you mean by "it wasn't my true desire"?
Shouldn't you find the answer to that yourself?
Regardless, it seems your heart is wavering.
This is an excellent opportunity.
If you wish to find your true feelings,
perhaps you should fret over it until you reach them?
My true feelings...
How Do You Really Feel?
Rikka's Troubled Yet Again!
They're baby biscuits!
Cure Ace sure is a mystery.
I still don't know what goes through her head.
But it's true that we all grew stronger thanks to her.
I suppose.
Are you still worried about earlier?
Huh?
No, I'm fine.
Besides, today's the first time Dad's been home in three months!
Mom's getting off early, too!
So tonight will be your first family dinner in a while, huh?
Yeah!
Well, see ya!
What was that for?!
Whoops, I thought you were a stray cat.
That's a load!
It's what you get for bargin' into our hideout!
No, this is our hideout!
But we've taken it for ourselves, remember?
Cripes, yer annoyin'!
Lemme go!
Strike!
Those jerks!
No, you shut up, stupid thunder!
Hello?
Oh, Mommy?
What's up?
Yeah.
Huh?
Oh...
I see.
Don't worry.
If it's for your patients, go ahead.
Huh?
Daddy too?
No, this always happens.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay, bye.
Your mom isn't coming home tonight?
No. Neither is Dad.
His flight got canceled.
That's... too bad.
It's nothing new.
Gotcha!
What's the long face for, Rachel?
Oh yeah!
Get ready, Rachel!
Tomorrow, you're going on a date with me!
Watch it!
But why the beach?
Huh?
Oh... no reason.
I just thought it'd be nice.
Like a driven wave, dashed by fierce winds on a rock am I.
Crushed and all alone, thinking over what has been.
Was that from the Hundred Poets?
Yeah.
It's the poem of a troubled girl who watches the waves crash on the rocks.
Are you troubled too?
I think it really was just because I admired Mom.
Looking back, I became a Precure and joined the student council
because I'd be with Mana.
In the end, everything I've done has been out of admiration of someone else.
So I can't help but wonder where my true feelings lie.
What do I want in life?
That's...
something nobody knows but you.
Maybe.
Huh?
Whoah!
Rikka!
Oh no!
Are you all right?
It's...
Ira!
W-Why is he here?
And he's hurt, too—
Don't get close! He's dangerous!
Huh? But we can't leave him like this!
What should I do?
Should I...
Worrying won't get us anywhere!
He's awake!
Rikka, let's run!
H-Huh? But...
Did you...
save my life?
Thank you so much.
But what was I...
No, first off...
Who am I?
Then you...
No way...
have amnesia?
Where am— ow!
Oh, don't move!
You're injured.
Thank you.
You're kind.
Huh?!
Should we really do this?
Is there anything I could do to help?
Patients only need to worry about their injuries.
I can't make them as well as Mana's dad doe—
Watch out!
Rikka!
Sorry. Is everything all right?
Yeah...
just look...
Not those, I mean you!
I'll... manage.
Phew.
If you're fine, then I am, too.
You're like an angel...
Huh?!
Are you glued together or something?!
Sorry...
Don't worry...
Dinner time!
Does it hurt?
You're injured, so you have to be careful!
Thanks.
You're pretty kind, too.
Huh?
It's probably hard to eat with those injuries.
Rachel, give me that spoon.
Sure.
Thanks.
Now, face me.
N-No, I can do it myself...
You couldn't before!
So don't be shy.
I-I don't think I should...
Geez! I don't care how injured he is, he's getting too pampered!
Rachel!
Charles, Lance, why are you here?!
We figured you'd be free since Rikka's family was home, so...
we came to hang out!
R-Really?
What're you freaked out over?
I'm not freaking out!
Did something happen?
Nothing at all!
I don't buy it!
Neither do I!
Aaaaaah!
Amnesia?
Yeah...
He was injured, too, so I couldn't leave him be.
That's very like you.
But we don't know when he'll strike!
Yes, he's dangerous.
I know he is...
You're being naive.
Cure Ace!
If leaving him be makes the worst come to pass,
will you face the consequences?
An injured enemy is an enemy all the same.
Evil is evil.
Ai.
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
She transformed!
What are you thinking?
Rikka...
Should he heal and his memories return,
he shall certainly return to oppose us once more.
If so, then now is the time...
Stop it!
I'll ask once. Move.
Move!
No!
He's committed many crimes before.
You've not forgotten, have you?
Of course I remember.
But...
if someone's injured and in pain, then no matter who it is,
I want to help them!
I know I'd regret it otherwise!
I don't want to live with regrets!
I'll trust in my beliefs!
Do you agree?
Rachel!
To be honest, I think you're right!
But still!
I'm going to trust Rikka!
Rachel...
I don't fully agree, but still...
Girls!
I feel the same as Rachel.
Found ya, Precures!
Cure Diamond, show me the lengths you'll go to for your beliefs.
Huh?
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Good...
It's dangerous, so stay back!
Girls!
Rachel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Rikka... transformed too?
Wow...
She's blue, feathery, and glistening...
W-What?
Oh poor Selfish who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Pre... cure?
Then I'll take a bite outta your hearts!
What? What in the...
Ira, what're you standin' around for?
Ira?
Get hit for all I care!
Run!
Huh?
What the heck're you tryin' to pull?!
The one who will defeat the Precures...
will be me!
Could it be?
His memories...
I see...
Good.
W-Why are you smiling?
You crazy girl.
Well, I'm happy.
This must be how I truly feel.
Stay out of this, Ira!
Take this, Precures!
I didn't ask for your help!
Oops, my bad.
Huh?
Did he actually help us?
You've shown me your true feelings.
The Precure's Five Vows!
A Precure must trust herself and never regret her actions!
Then, what she did before...
was an act to make me face my true feelings?
Thank you, Cure Ace.
For what, I wonder?
Oh mild mannered glutton,
I, Cure Diamond,
shall cool your hot head down!
Cure Diamond!
Now is the time to fight alongside me!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
What the heck?
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Diamond Shower!
Shaved ice is my favorite food!
That's... surprising.
But if you overeat...
How 'bout that?
Glad you enjoyed it.
By the way, is your head cooled?
Huh?
Ugh, brain freeze! I ate too much ice!
Drat! I'll remember this!
Looks like you've finally powered up, Diamond!
That was impressive!
We didn't get a chance to step in.
I knew you could do it!
Thanks, Rachel.
Excellent work, Cure Diamond.
But you must not lower your guard.
Around Ira, that is.
I'm certain that the next time he appears...
Yes, I'm aware.
Then I bid you adieu.
Hey, coming home safe is what counts!
That's fine, but what kind of souvenirs are these?
I got those from the natives.
They say they're charms that will make your dreams come true.
I see. Thanks, Daddy.
But this is great timing.
For what?
It's a bit embarrassing to say it again,
but I know what I want to be.
You do? Wasn't it a doctor?
Yeah! I want to be a doctor.
It's just...
up until now, I wasn't fully prepared for it.
Something made you?
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
A Precure must be a first class lady!
L-Lady?
As such, I invite you all to join me in an outdoor tea ceremony!
We shall go all out and drill some manners into Mana's head!
What's a tea ceremony?
It's the meaning of the Way of Tea.
It's quite fun!
Aguri, you said we'd go all out, but is it actually fun?
Dokidoki Precure:
It's Out of the Bag?!
Cure Ace's One Weakness!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!