Litter!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Love love looooove!
This is gettin' too routine!
We'll be back!
Ai?
What the?
No way!
My body is flowing with Egogy!
I'm brimming with power!
Allow me!
What happened?
Their Egogy levels suddenly elevated,
drastically increasing their power!
But how?
It's not because of Ai's crying, is it?
We can totally win now!
Precures,
meet your doom!
Cut it out, Bel!
Oh, just forget it!
I guess we're safe now.
But still...
Ai, what troubles you?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Being a Mommy's Tough!
Ai Throws a Tantrum!
Her heart rate appears to be normal.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Thank goodness she isn't ill.
Lancece!
Help yourself to some milk.
It seems she isn't hungry, either.
So why is she throwing tantrums?
And why did Ai's crying give Ira
and Mammo so much Egogy?
I can't bear to see Ai like this.
We've got to get her back to her happy self!
Where am I?
Peekaboo!
Yo! Checka Racka!
Ai, let's play!
Go to sleep,
go to sleep,
in your mother's arms...
Ai, look, this is fun!
Come play with us!
Hello.
Welcome, Ryouko.
I'll have the usual.
Rikka?
Wow, what happened to you girls?
I've never seen you all so pooped.
We were taking care of Ai...
But she was in a bad mood the whole time,
and ended up crying herself to sleep.
She was always so happy before today...
Mom, how do you calm a crying baby?
It's not easy.
There's no surefire way to do it.
Really?
Sometimes, babies just like to be grumpy.
Very true.
But you're a pediatrician, right?
Don't you know everything about babies?
It'd be nice if anyone could.
Babies can't talk, so they cry to complain.
Crying is how babies give you a hint.
A hint?
Speaking of which, Rikka cried a lot as a baby.
I never slept on the nights you cried through.
I held you while you wailed,
and walked through the city all night long.
My arms hurt and my back was killing me,
and you still didn't stop crying.
It made me think I was a horrible mother!
And then I'd start crying along with you.
A horrible mother?
She was a night-crier, huh?
She was wailing?
I'd never think someone as diligent as Rikka would have been such a crybaby...
I-I was a baby, come on!
What kind of baby was Mana?
Mana ate, slept, and smiled a lot,
so she wasn't as much of a handful.
But you wouldn't believe the trouble she was when she learned to walk!
If she fell out of bed, she'd roll off to who-knows-where!
If we went for a stroll, she'd walk off on her own!
She'd try to jump from the top of the jungle gym!
And then she let a jarful of crickets she caught loose in the house...
Stop!
Was there more?
Oh, much more.
You might not have been a big crier yourself,
but you made your poor mother one.
How fitting for Mana.
Even her toddlerhood was filled with epic adventure!
diner
Pig's Tail
Thanks for the help.
Don't mention it.
After all, I was such a handful as a baby.
This is but a fraction of my endless gratitude.
Thank you ever so much.
But your mother wouldn't be a mother without you.
What do you mean?
Raising a child made me worry and doubt myself,
but I learned a lot about parenting.
I feel that both parents and children strive together to become a family.
But a word of advice.
Make sure you smile in front of the baby.
Smile?
If the mother looks disheartened, the baby's sure to worry.
I see.
Oh, she woke up.
I'll finish up here, so go to her.
Yeah.
My baby pictures aren't too flattering.
I'm crying or pouting in almost all of them.
You were always a bit camera shy.
Sorry, Mom.
For what?
For being a handful.
You're a great mother, honest.
What?
I just felt like giving you a big hug.
I'm not a kid anymore!
Oh, no matter how big you get, you're still Mommy's little girl.
My precious little angel.
Sometimes I had Yuuzou care for you when you wouldn't stop crying
while I walked outside for a breather.
But I always went right back to you every time.
Why?
I couldn't stop worrying if you weren't around.
Besides, I'm the only Mommy you have.
That's why I wanted to hug you.
I might not be perfect, but I want to be there for you.
It's funny...
when we're like this, I feel like everything will be all right.
Same here.
Mom, I want to be there for Ai.
Can I go?
Of course.
Good luck.
Gently, geeeently...
That didn't work either!
There there, Ai...
Mana.
Switch with me and take a break.
Rikka!
Thank you so much!
It's all right, Ai.
I'm here for you.
It's all right...
It's all... right...
Bel, what the heck are you pulling?
We were about to mop the floor with the Precures!
Why'd you ruin everything?
Because I never gave you permission.
Insubordination will be punished.
Who died and made you king?
Oh, did you say something?
Why, nothing at all, sir!
My apologies!
Perhaps you'd enjoy a drink?
That said, how curious...
Right as that baby began crying, your Egogy levels soared.
Ira, try making that baby cry again.
Why me?
Understood! Right away, sir!
I'm goin', all right?
Mana!
Rikka, are you all right?
I suppose caring for Ai hasn't given you much time for sleep.
I'm fine, don't worry.
Now let's play our hearts out with Ai!
Ai, here it comes!
Catch!
Ai, look at this!
I see her mood hasn't improved since yesterday.
Should a Selfish appear at this moment, then...
Wh-What are you doing?
Aguri, you gotta smile!
If we look disheartened, the baby's sure to worry.
So be there for Ai with a smile, okay?
Indeed.
We shall challenge the slide next.
Let's go, Ai!
Cripes.
Tests really suck.
I wanna just ride off.
I'd get a sick bike and rule the road!
But I ain't goin' nowhere without a license.
Guess I can't run away.
Aw, just rule the road.
I will grant your desire.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Selfish!
Vroom vroom!
Whoosh!
I rule the road!
A dark heartbeat!
That sounds like...
Move it or lose it!
Rule the road!
Sup.
I'm gonna kick your butts and look cool doing it!
You sure won't!
Girls, let's go!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Ai, let's go!
Ai?
Haha, you can't transform?
Man, that's classic!
Yes!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor bike who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
You tryin' to laugh at me?
I ain't lettin' a baby get away with that!
Selfish, start revvin'!
Popopopopopopopopopop!
Ai?
Now this is more like it!
He's been powered up by Egogy once again!
Ai, please calm down!
So my Egogy really does get pumped up when she cries!
I like it!
Selfish, show me some road rage!
Vrovroovroovrule the road!
He's fast!
Girls, be careful!
The Selfish appears to be powered up as well!
Selfiiiiiiiish!
We can win this!
We can beat the Precures!
That's right, cry some more!
The harder you wail, the more Egogy I get!
Rule the road!
Vrumvrumvrumvrumvrumvrum!
Ai!
Not happenin'!
Selfish!
Rule the road!
Vrumvrumvrumvrumvrumvrum!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Ai!
Nobody can stop me!
Yahoo!
Puttputtputtputtputt!
Resistance is futile!
Ai...
I'm sorry...
You're scared, and you want to cry...
I'm really sorry for putting you through all this.
But please trust us.
I'm here for you, and so is everyone else.
No matter what happens, I swear we'll keep you safe and sound!
So don't worry, all right?
Vroomvrumvrum vroomvrumvrum...
H-Huh?
Uh-oh...
Vroom vrr...
Self?
How dare you make our little Ai cry!
Magical Lovely Pad!
Self?!
Diamond Swirkle!
Seeeeeeelf!
Now is our chance!
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Precure Lovely Straight Flush!
Lovroom lovroom lovroooooom!
Man, now I wanna cry!
Ai's sleeping well.
She looks so much nicer when she's finally calmed down.
We caught a break and won the battle today,
but we might not be so lucky next time.
Why did Ai's tears weaken us and strengthen the enemy's Egogy?
We need to find out and stop it.
Huh?
The Mirror Lovies!
Give it a try!
Dibbity dobbity Davi!
Huh?
The princess!
Princess Ann!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Ai is teething!
Now she'll be able to eat ever tastier sweets!
She's too young for those!
It's best to teach her to brush her teeth first to prevent cavities.
I think I got one before Ai did!
Wait, Makopi, you've got a cavity?
Then we should go to the dentist!
But dentists are scary!
Dokidoki Precure:
Ai's Being Stubborn!
Begin Operation Brush Those Teeth!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!