[RUKO]
I'm serious!
I wasn't going easy on her--
Everything felt
wrong that time!
[RUKO sniffs]
[IONA]
I see.
[TAMA cries]
[MAYU]
Why are you crying?
[crying continues]
[MAYU] Are you thinking
about your friends?
[gasps]
Or more specifically...
...about Ru?
[TAMA]
Huh...?
[GIRL C pants]
Seriously?
Yeah, isn't it
the creepiest thing
--you've ever heard?
--[GIRL C] They're coming!
You see there?
Look, what did I tell you?
[BOY A] Whoa, so it
really is true, huh?
--[GIRL D] Seriously?
--[GIRL E] Yeah!
Akira's on the cover!
[GIRL F]
What, where?!
[GIRL E] Ugh! Do those
two have, like, zero shame?
[GIRL F]
I know!
They were walking side by
side like it was nothing.
[GIRL G]
The Kurebayashi twins?
Is that who you mean?
[GIRL E] Yeah, the two who are
always eating lunch together.
[GIRL F]
On the rooftop, by themselves.
But, come on, is it really true?
They are brother and sister.
Maybe those two
are just really close.
[GIRL E]
Too close if you ask me!
[KAZUKI]
Well, see you later.
[gasps]
[HANAYO (Y)]
Yup.
[gasps]
Hello, Ruko. How is she?
Ah? Um. Good;
she's with Hitoe now.
But they haven't been doing
WIXOSS battles or anything.
I see.
But you are.
Aren't you?
[RUKO]
Um. Yeah...
Why is that?
What do you mean?
[HANAYO (Y) sighs]
Never mind.
Keep battling all you like.
[IONA]
She used to be an LRIG.
She knows.
Oh yeah, she knows
all about you.
Like just how different
you are from the other girls.
[YUZUKI]
What is she trying to pull?
This can't be good.
Well...
What's the matter?
You're spacing out.
[gasps] I'm a bit worried
about Ruko, that's all.
[YUZUKI]
Yeah?
It's just...
I got to thinking, and if what
you said about Akira is true,
she probably will
go after Ruko, and soon.
[IONA]
Don't be ashamed.
I know you want to battle.
[IONA]
I know how much you enjoyed it.
How your blood would flare
and your body would tingle.
I could feel your passion.
[IONA]
Is it because Tama's gone?
Because I'm your LRIG now?
Is it not fun anymore
because you're not with her?
Is that why you can't battle?
It makes no sense.
Don't you realize you're
the most powerful Selector
I've ever known? And I'm
the most powerful LRIG?
It's a miracle that
we've come together
and you're letting
it all go to waste.
[GIRL J]
What? A new pack came out?
[GIRL I]
Yep! I just got it yesterday!
[GIRL J]
Aw, can you show it to me?
[GIRL I]
Sure!
[IONA] That's why you're
still carrying me around.
Isn't it? You hunger for it.
No, I don't.
[IONA] Using me to
find Tama is just the lie
you're telling yourself.
Stop feeling guilty.
Take advantage of me.
Don't say that.
[IONA]
Why?
Take advantage of me--make
yourself feel better.
You want this.
That's not true!
[IONA]
Of course it's true.
Selectors fight to make
their wish come true.
And LRIGs fight to return
to the outside world.
We've always taken
advantage of each other.
[RUKO]
It's not always like that!
Hanayo's still keeping Yuzuki's
wish for her, even now!
[IONA] She wants to live in
the outside world, she has to.
That's not my point!
[IONA] You're saying
she wants to do it,
but how much do you really
know about her anyway?
[gasps]
You don't know anything.
Even about Tama.
But that's all right.
There's no need for you to know.
Let's just keep taking advantage
of one another, okay?
And that way, you can keep
savoring your battles.
[RUKO] I'm telling you,
that's all wrong.
I didn't care about winning
or wishes, or anything.
It's because I was with Tama.
I liked battling
together with her.
We were both a team!
What are you talking about?
It's not the battle
part I liked.
And it's not
the battles I miss now.
I liked being with Tama!
Nonsense.
You just can't admit
you're like me.
You're only making excuses for
your own desire to battle.
I just want Tama back!
Iona.
You promise you
don't know anything
about what happened to her?
I'm begging you,
if you have even one clue.
I'll do anything
to get her back!
And I don't care what it takes!
Do you know where she is?!
Where she might be?!
Anything!
No.
[RUKO] You're not just
saying that to trick me?
Maybe... she's with Mayu.
[RUKO]
Huh?
Wait, what was that?
Never mind. It's nothing.
[MAYU]
Welcome back, Tama.
[TAMA]
Huh?
It would seem
you won your battle.
Uh-huh...
But I had to lie to Ru.
You did.
And I didn't even say
goodbye, either.
So now, Ru is probably
awfully sad and crying, too.
Yes, but Ru lied to you first.
Remember?
Huh...?
[RUKO] So, hey, I can't wait
to go shopping with you, Tama.
[TAMA]
Can we eat dumplings?
[RUKO] I was thinking
I'd buy you some scrunchies.
So you can match the rest of us.
[TAMA]
Ru...
[RUKO]
I love you.
But now, after
winning the battle,
you know... that Ru is a liar.
She abandoned you, chose her
other friends instead.
You're wrong!
Ru was trying to save Tama and
Yuzuki and Hitoe and everyone!
That was gonna be her wish!
And yet, she's given up
on all of you now.
No! It was my fault
that it all went wrong!
I ruined it all 'cause I was
scared about how lonely
I would be if I lost her!
If I knew how she felt, then I--
[RUKO]
Tama! Where did you go?!
Ru...
[RUKO]
Tama!
[whimpers]
[TAMA]
I'm sorry, Ru.
I'm so sorry!
[MAYU]
Do you want to see Ru?
[TAMA squeaks]
[MAYU]
See her and apologize?
[TAMA squeaks]
[MAYU]
I take it you want to return
to the outside world then?
[TAMA]
Yes...
[MAYU]
It's a frightening place.
Both your emotions and your soul
will become
hopelessly entangled.
You will be hurt.
Everyone out there is a liar.
Pain and sorrow...
They're the only things
you can count on.
Listen...
You can hear them...
The people...
They're crying...
Yeah, but some are nice,
like Ru and Grandma--
You're wrong!
Lies!
They're evil!
Awful!
It's scary!
Don't!
I-I don't wanna
leave, Tama!
I can't ever live in that
horrible world again!
[TAMA gasps]
[MAYU]
Stay here, with me, forever.
Aw, you're too strong.
[gasps]
Together...
Just like we were before...
Playing and laughing...
Everyone...
Forever...
[TAMA]
I know her.
I remember her voice.
She's...
[TAMA]
Ma... yu...
Wow, you remembered me?
As for Ru, do you
still want to see her?
Yes.
Really bad.
What if I said
I won't forgive you?
Then I'd say
I still wanna see her.
I see.
Well.
I suppose I'll let you.
[HITOE]
Hold on a sec.
It's like we said
on the phone, Ruko.
She's up to something.
[HANAYO (Y)]
Never mind.
Keep battling all you like.
Is that why...?
[YUZUKI]
What? You know something?
Tell me.
[gasps] Um, nevermind.
Look, here it is!
I was shocked!
[gasps]
You see now?
Akira's looking for Selectors!
[whines]
She's also posting
rumors on the internet.
Look at this.
[RUKO]
Wait, "mysterious LRIG cards
that can grant wishes?"
What could she be up to?
[HITOE] She's not just
drawing out Selectors,
she's also spreading the word
about them to everyone else.
[YUZUKI]
Got more fans than ever, too.
That's already been
retweeted over 5,000 times.
At this rate, she'll--
[GIRL K] The WIXOSS
LRIG cards can speak,
and then you can get
your wish to come true.
That sounds familiar.
Is it from the novel?
[GIRL M]
Even if it is, it's stupid.
Come on.
No one's ever gonna believe
a crazy rumor like that.
[GIRL L] Well, Akira was talking
about it on the internet.
[GIRL M]
Yeah...
See, that's what
I'm worried about.
Do you hear them?
Look, don't worry.
One of them even said
no one'll ever believe it.
[YUZUKI]
We can't be so sure!
We've gotta do something!
[RUKO]
Okay, but what?
I don't know, but we
can't just leave this be.
The first thing we should do
is try to figure out
why Akira is doing this.
[HITOE]
You have to admit,
she is... really pretty.
[YUZUKI]
Hitoe!
We need to be planning,
not praising her looks!
Uh! Right! I'm sorry!
For some reason, she does look
a lot nicer than before, right?
It even seems like
her scar is gone.
[YUZUKI] I'm sure she just
covered it with makeup.
[HITOE]
You think?
I saw it.
It's there.
[gasps]
You what?
Akira's scar.
Yesterday, I... saw it.
[YUZUKI]
You met with her?!
I had a bad feeling
she'd go after you, Ruko.
Well, are you okay?
Yeah...
Don't tell me you--
Yes.
I-I had a battle with Akira!
[YUZUKI, HITOE gasp]
[AKIRA]
Urith...
Urith... Urith...
[URITH (I)]
So, did you beat Ruko or not?
Some guy interrupted the battle,
so we weren't able to finish,
but up until that point,
I was totally kicking her ass!
But don't worry,
next time I play that snot,
I'll squash her like
a bug, and then--
[URITH (I)]
Thank you.
I can't tell you how much
I appreciate you
doing that for me.
No, Urith. I appreciate you.
Thanks to your love, I can show
my face to everyone again.
Oh?
Really?
[grunts] Hey! Stop!
Then why do you hide it?
If you do appreciate
me like you say,
then show all of it to me.
That means all the
unsightly things, too.
The splattered, rotten, filthy
parts that bring you shame.
Or is it... that you
can't show them to me?
I can!
I can and I will, I swear it!
[AKIRA sobs]
You've got it wrong.
I'm not hiding it from you!
I'll show you anything you want!
And I'll do anything
you ask me to!
I'd kill Ruko to make you happy!
So please...
...I'm begging you...
Urith...
...love me...
Turn me from Aki-lucky...
into Aki-lovely...
Please...!
[AKIRA sobs]
[HITOE]
So your battle,
it got interrupted?
[sighs] You're lucky.
No, she's stupid!
What possessed you
to do such a thing?!
Well, I just had a bad feeling
that if I said no to her,
there was a chance
that something
even worse might happen.
Save the lame excuses.
You just wanted to
battle her, didn't you?!
[RUKO]
Ah...?
[HITOE] Now you're
jumping to conclusions!
[YUZUKI]
Am I? Are you carrying Iona?
[gasps]
Uh...
Is that true?
Yeah...
Is it because you
want to find Tama?
Yeah.
[YUZUKI] But if you
lose Selector battles,
you might not get that chance!
[IONA]
How petty.
Your grandma would be crushed
if something happened to you.
[IONA]
Ridiculous.
I know that, but...
[IONA]
She's not like you.
We said we'd work
together to find Tama, remember?
[IONA] Ruko only truly enjoys
life when she's in battle.
[YUZUKI] And that you
didn't have to shoulder
this responsibility on your own.
[IONA]
She's like me.
We should be working together.
Fighting together.
[RUKO]
It's because I was with Tama.
[IONA]
They're misleading her.
They're the reason
Ruko is like this.
It's okay, we understand.
We feel the same way you do.
What?
You know that special
way you feel about Tama?
Well, Hitoe and I, we feel
the same way about you.
We do.
And if you disappeared
the same way Tama did,
we'd be just as
upset as you are.
Yuzuki...
You know what?
When you won that battle with
Iona, I got really scared.
I thought at first that we
might not ever see you again.
And I was really worried
that you were going to be
transformed into an LRIG.
Or, in the worst case, you
might even disappear forever.
[RUKO]
Hitoe...
[HITOE] We know you
wanted to sacrifice yourself,
for Tama and for all the
other Selectors and LRIGs
who are suffering.
Yeah, but Hitoe, you would do
the same thing for Yuzuki.
I would've done anything,
no matter what happened to me,
because we're friends.
But that's wrong.
That's not the way
friendship works!
[gasps]
I finally got it when I thought
you were gonna disappear.
Just think.
If you were gone,
I wouldn't be happy.
What if you had
sacrificed yourself?
Even if it did go
like you planned.
Maybe I could have
had a normal life,
been able to
talk to Yuzuki,
possibly even make
some other friends.
But still, don't you understand?
[HITOE sobs]
If you weren't there to
share those things with me,
well then, it wouldn't
be any fun at all.
Hitoe...
The thing is...
...we talked after your battle.
We talked about sacrificing
ourselves for others,
and agreed to stop
doing stuff like that
'cause it's not necessary.
We'll always be together.
So if we suffer,
at least we're not alone.
If we're sad, we'll
still have each other.
So this is what we'll do,
for as long as we know.
Hitoe...
Yuzuki...
I was... just trying
to get Tama back.
I had no idea how much
I upset you two.
So...
Sorry...
I mean that.
And... I won't
do it again, okay?
No more battles
on my own, I promise.
But still...
I can't!
We understand.
It's all for Tama, right?
And to prevent anyone else from
going through all the suffering
we've gone through.
So, if you have to battle,
to stand up for them...
...we won't stop you.
Just be sure you
tell us first, okay?
Thank you both, so much.
[ALL giggle]
[KAZUKI]
Yuzuki?
Oh. Sorry.
[KAZUKI]
Mm?
[RUKO] Mm, I could eat,
like, five of these!
I guess all of that crying
made us hungry, huh?
[RUKO giggles]
[IONA]
What're you doing?
You do realize we just
left a restaurant, right?
Yeah, I know.
[IONA]
What're you saying?
We were making a sobbing scene;
best to get out of there.
[IONA]
Ruko.
Why can't you see
you're not one of them?
And, y'know, snack away,
because it's not like I can!
Can you smell stuff at least?
[IONA] I became an LRIG
just for you, Ruko.
Hey, come to think of it,
do LRIGs ever get hungry?
Well, no, we don't actually.
But thanks for asking.
[IONA] To become one
with you in battle.
[RUKO giggles]
[IONA]
Do not let me down.
What's the matter?
You guys.
I'm sensing another LRIG!
[HITOE gasps]
[YUZUKI]
There's a Selector nearby!
There is?
That way!
[IONA]
It's her.
[HITOE, RUKO gasp]
Wait, that's...
...Urith!
[URITH (I)]
Hmph!
[IONA]
Hmph. Urith.
[CHIYORI gasps]
Huh?
Chiyori?
Yay! I knew my Super
Selector Sense was tingling!
Well, well!
Looks like the whole gang
showed up today!
Yeah, but why oh why?
Hey, wait! I bet
it's destiny, right?!
Why else would we beautiful
Selectors of love and courage
be brought together, huh?
[ELDORA] Did you just call
yourself "beautiful?"
Ah, we meet again,
Miss Pain-in-the-ass.
Hold on.
What are you doing with Chiyori?
Hah.
Look...
No way.
[URITH (I)]
Well then, Chiyori.
Are you ready to start?
Oh, yeah, let's do it!
It's battle time, ladies!
[gasps]
[CHIYORI, URITH (I)]
Open!
No, don't!
[YUZUKI gasps]
[RUKO gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
[YUZUKI whimpers]
[gasps]
Wha--
Tama...?
[CHIYORI]
Oh yeah! Hoo-yeah!
[URITH (I)]
Lucky us--we get to go first.
Now Grow.
[CHIYORI]
We're like rivals, huh?
[URITH (I)]
Wish Crisis!
[CHIYORI]
Chorizo De Ibéricoña The Second!
Wa-pa-pow!
[RUKO] Next time:
"Those Wild Delusions."