By my third Command Spell,
I order you again...
Don't!
Saber,
destroy the Grail.
What could he have learned about me
from issuing a mere three orders?
After all,
I never even knew
my closest companions.
Perhaps all this
was my punishment for being the king
who could not understand
the feelings of others.
That's...
Impossible...
There's no way!
Kiritsugu...
What's wrong, Illyasviel?
Mother, I had a bad dream.
I dreamed
I turned into a cup...
And inside me were these
big lumps, seven of them...
It felt like I was going to tear apart.
I was really scared.
But I couldn't run away.
Then I heard Justeaze-sama's voice.
A big black hole opened up above my head.
And then,
the world burned.
Kiritsugu was watching it and crying.
Mother, is Kiritsugu okay?
Is he scared and lonely?
Don't worry...
He's fighting for you, Ilya.
He'll make our prayers come true,
so you won't ever have to be scared again.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
Kiritsugu's a hard worker.
He'll finish his important job,
and he'll come back soon.
Hi, Sakura-chan...
Uncle?
I'm here to save you...
It's okay now.
Come on.
Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura!
Kariya-kun.
Aoi-san...
Thank you, Uncle Kariya.
Thank you.
Daddy Kariya!
What a foolish person,
to go against Grandfather.
Where am I?
You really are quite a difficult man.
Digging you out of this rubble
was rather tiresome.
Gilgamesh, what happened?
Who knows?
That black mud spit me out again.
I suppose the heavens must have decided
that I should return and rule
this Earth once more.
You mean to say you have received new flesh?
Begrudgingly, yes.
After how hard we fought for that thing,
thinking it would grant our wish...
This play remained a farce,
straight through to the very end.
I was shot.
There's no heartbeat...
Did you heal me somehow, Gilgamesh?
Let's see now...
You do appear to be dead.
Our contract bound us.
Perhaps when I was reborn within that mud,
you were pulled back
through some absurdity.
You mean to say it gave me life?
We have vanquished the other
Servants and won the Grail.
Behold, Kirei, the result.
If the Grail truly grants the
winner's deepest wish...
Then, Kotomine Kirei,
what you see before you is
precisely what you have sought.
What?
What the hell am I?
What cruelty...
What evil.
This is my wish?
This destruction?
This suffering?
This is my enjoyment?
Could this twisted, filthy thing
truly be the fruit of Kotomine Risei's loins?
Unthinkable.
It's unthinkable!
Could my father have sired such a dog?
Are you fulfilled, Kirei?
No, not yet.
This isn't enough.
True, I finally have the answer
to my life of questions.
However, I've only been
taught the problem's answer,
not how to solve it.
How could I be satisfied?
The bizarre formula used to calculate this answer
should be founded in some
kind of logical principle.
No...
It must be.
I must ask...
I must search.
I will dedicate my life to someday
understanding it.
You never cease to pique my interest.
As you wish.
You could question the very gods unto death.
And I, Gilgamesh, will watch
you find your answer.
Angra Mainyu...
I will find it again,
and next time, I will see it to the end.
I will see its birth.
The proof of its existence.
Emiya Kiritsugu?
I shall face you once more.
What is it, Kirei?
Nothing.
I remember that face.
It was a man,
tears in his eyes,
and joy in his heart at finding
someone still alive.
He seemed so happy.
Almost as if he, not I,
was the one who'd been saved.
You're alive... You're alive...
You're alive!
Even on the verge of death, I was jealous
as the man gratefully said, "Thank you."
Because he was grateful
he'd found someone.
Because by saving even one person,
he'd saved himself.
Episode 25
Fate/Zero
And now, our next story.
Massive Blaze in New Fuyuki
Last night in New Fuyuki...
I wonder if Mr. Alexei
made it to England safely.
He called at the crack of dawn, from Heathrow.
The moron forgot about the time difference.
He did?
I didn't hear the phone.
That's just like him, though.
Hey, Grandma and Grandpa...
Can I talk to you about something?
What is it?
Well, honestly...
I'm thinking of doing some traveling.
My, my! Did you hear that, Glen?
Waver's started talking like Mr. Alexei now.
Anyway,
there's a lot of preparation,
or rather priorities I need to take care of.
To start, I should find a part-time job.
So, um...
What I really wanted to ask was this.
If you wouldn't mind,
could I stay with you until I figure things out?
Of course you can!
It will be delightful to have
you here for longer.
We'll have to throw a party today.
Sheesh...
He's just a ghost.
How can he leave so much junk behind?
Honestly, I wish he could've
taken me with him...
Essentially,
I'm just not there yet.
He never even opened it...
The first-run edition
with bonus T-shirt.
Who even likes these?
Man...
I know that my redeemer lives.
And that, in the end,
he will stand upon the Earth.
And after my skin has been destroyed,
yet in my flesh,
I will see God.
I, myself, will see him, with my own eyes.
I, and not another.
How my heart yearns within me.
Amen.
Rin.
You performed marvelously in your
debut as the new family head.
I have no doubt your father would be proud.
Well done.
Tokiomi's preparations were flawless.
Rin, you will inherit the Tohsaka
family magic, without incident.
Now, why don't you bring your mother?
Yeah, I will.
Okay, Mother, let's go say
goodbye to Father.
Oh, Rin?
Is it someone's funeral today?
Yes.
Father passed away.
Oh, dear...
I'll have to get Tokiomi-san's
mourning suit out.
Rin, help Sakura get dressed.
Oh, what should I do?
I have to get ready, too.
Honey, your necktie is all twisted.
You must take care of yourself.
Rin and Sakura like to be
proud of their father.
I'm going to be leaving Japan for a while.
Do you have any immediate concerns?
No!
I don't need your help with anything!
Rin,
from now on, you are the
head of the Tohsaka family.
To commemorate the occasion,
I brought a gift for you.
An Azoth dagger.
It received it from my master years ago,
to commemorate the completion of
my training as a mage.
I'd like you to have it.
This was Father's...
Here
again.
Everyone...
Lancelot...
Because I
could not stop myself
from loving Guinevere,
I was unable to forgive myself.
But, King Arthur...
You never so much as questioned me
or sought recompense.
You simply stood before us
in your righteousness.
But I...
I wished for judgment at your hand.
Had your anger punished me,
I might not have fallen into madness
in my quest for atonement.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
I...
I am unworthy.
Still, I can say this much with certainty,
King Arthur...
Someday,
I will obtain the Holy Grail.
You were the greatest of kings.
All who served you
It was not I...
shared this feeling.
...who should have become king.
Afterwards,
I tried numerous times to
contact the Einzberns.
But having returned empty-handed,
Jubstacheit refused to lower the
barrier around the forest.
I never saw Ilya again.
But...
After Ilya, no other person
was ever taken from me.
I thought my life would be
nothing but loss,
but everyone is still here,
just as when we met.
I adopted Shirou, the boy I saved that day.
— Five Years Later —
Hey.
Hey, old man...
If you're gonna sleep, go to bed.
Oh...
I'm fine.
When I was a boy, I was hailed as a hero.
What do you mean?
You were?
You gave it up?
Sadly, yes.
You can only be a hero for so long.
When you become an adult,
it's much harder to call yourself one.
I wish that
I had realized it sooner.
Oh...
Then there wasn't any way around it.
Yes...
Yes, you're right.
The moon's so beautiful.
Yeah.
Since you couldn't be one,
I'll be a hero instead.
You're an adult now,
so you missed your chance.
But I can do it.
Leave it to me...
Your dream.
I see.
Yes.
That's a relief.
Kerry,
what do you want to be
when you grow up?
I...
I want to be a hero.