Say, Minami...
What?!
Uhm... I'm sorry about earlier.
Who cares? Why don't
you go get cozy with Mizuki.
Don't say things like that.
Please stop being upset.
And let's think up another strategy.
If we end up fighting a
war with Class B and lose,
Himeji might have to change scho--
What're you saying, you dummy?!
With you, it's always
Mizuki this, Mizuki that!
Why is Mizuki the only
girl you treat like a princess?
Minami...
Then, what am I? Why do
you always treat me like that?
Do you think I'm a guy?!
I-It's not like that...
If Mizuki's parents try to make her
change schools, I'll go talk to them.
Minami...
Don't ever talk to me again!
I don't wanna see your face.
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
Last episode recap. Woohoo.
The Class B rep, Kyouji Nemoto,
was planning to declare war on Class F
since they just finished their suspension
and so their fighting power is low.
So, Akihisa and his friends in Class F
were trying to provoke Class D in order
to get them to declare war on Class F.
If they fight Class D first, they'll
be given time to take recovery tests.
If they rebuild their forces then,
Class B probably won't
come and attack them so easily.
In order to do that, we were going
to have Akihisa and Shimada pretend
to be dating and instigate
Miharu Shimizu's anger.
Well, that was our plan.
That was a total failure, you dumbass.
Who'd think that you and
Shimada are dating after that scene?
Sorry.
I wonder if I should've
given you more acting lessons...
Shimada and Himeji did a good job, though.
Ah... Well... Yeah...
Why do you treat me like that?
Muttsulini, how are things in Class B?
They've currently recovered about 70%.
Some of them have already
started getting ready for the war.
They're moving faster than I thought.
That shows how serious they are.
We need to buy some time.
First, Muttsulini... Feed some
fake information to Class B.
What info?
Class D is preparing for an
ST War. Their target is Class B.
Roger.
Would something like that work?
All Nemoto wants is to
win and retain his position.
I bet he wants to avoid fighting a
series of wars, which can exhaust them.
If he learns that Class D is after them,
he'll probably hesitate to declare war on us.
I see. Yeah, it's not like
they want Class F's equipment.
Next, Hideyoshi...
Bring Miharu Shimizu from
Class D to the negotiation table.
We'll provoke her and
instigate her hostility towards us.
If we can get them to
declare war on us, it's a success.
Why me?
In order to bring her out,
we need to bring Shimada.
Right now, we can't ask
Akihisa or Himeji to do that.
I see. Got it.
Also, Akihisa...
Hm? What is it?
Are you hungry?
Well, yeah, I'm kinda hungry, I guess.
That's not good. You are the
cornerstone of this operation.
We need to have you eat good to
boost up your energy... right, Himeji?
What? Yeah, you're right.
If he's hungry, he won't have energy.
So, Himeji... Could you make something to...
Actually...! Now that I think about it,
I already had lunch earlier, so I'm full.
I can't eat anything else.
Lunch? You mean that?
Hm?
This is good.
Ahhhhhh! How could you...?!
So, Himeji, could you make
something to eat for Akihisa?
Sure! I'd be happy to!
Yuuji, uncle! Uncle!
Akihisa, what do you wanna eat?
What do I wanna eat?
If I make a good choice, it will
reduce the chances of fatality.
Hurry up, Akihisa.
A dish whose ingredients can be identified,
and that won't have
unexpected objects mixed in...
That's right! Boiled eggs!
"Mizuki's Homemade Dish"
"Today's Dish: Boiled Eggs" "Ingredients: Eggs only"
Looks like... Akihisa wants to eat jello.
We can't really tell what's in it, right?!
In order for him to be able
to eat during the operation,
put it in jello drink aluminum pouches.
I can't even check the color like that, can I?!
Okay. I'll do my best!
Wait! At least decide what kind of
jello you're gonna make before you go!
Don't worry, Akihisa.
That's not actually for you to eat.
Huh?
I just needed some weapons
for our operation, that's all.
O-Oh... You should've told me sooner.
But because of what I said, I think
she's probably gonna try to have you eat it.
You're too brutal.
"Cooking Practice Room"
Getting gelatin and sugar ready...
Oh, it seems unexpectedly normal.
Good...
First, dissolve the cocoa
powder in corn potage soup.
Hey, what's she making?
Be quiet! She'll notice us!
An orange or a scallion...
I wonder which one Akihisa would like...
Don't debate! You shouldn't
debate between those two, Himeji!
She's picking ingredients for you
based on nutrition rather than taste.
If I have a scallion,
how about adding natto?
No! No!
Come to think of it,
I've heard that what they said
about natto improving our
blood flow was a lie, wasn't it?
Safe...
But it's still healthy, right?
Ugh! Out...
Besides, it's blue-skinned fish
that will improve the blood flow.
That's a double play...
Why vinegared mackerel? Why is
she putting vinegared mackerel in jello?
She's worried about you being stupid,
so she's trying to replenish your DHA.
Ah! This isn't gonna be good, right?
Good! Himeji noticed!
I have to add mustard for the natto.
Don't notice that!
I'll add some ginger to
vinegared mackerel, too.
Ahhh! Don't notice that, either!
What else can I use as secret ingredients?
Don't make it secret! Make it clear!
Oh, that's right! To give it a
little adultish flavor, I'll add taba--
Let's go. If you hear any further,
you won't be able to eat it.
Wait! Let me at least check
whether it's tobacco or Tabasco!
It's already too late.
Here, please have some.
I'm gonna go clean up the
cooking practice room, so...
What do we do with these?
I think Nemoto is gonna
send a messenger to Class D...
...in order to check if they're
really trying to fight a war.
If he does that, he'll know the
information we circulated was a lie.
So, we'll assassinate that messenger!
What?!
If the messenger gets assassinated,
he'll become distrustful of Class D.
When that happens, it'll make
the fake information believable.
How terrible...
Battles are cruel. Muttsulini, do it.
Got it.
"Crack, crack"
What's that?
"Buzz, buzz..."
"Messenger"
Y-You...!
May God help you.
Mom...
Execution completed.
Good job, Muttsulini.
What fascinating skills you've got.
This wasn't anything special...
How did you keep
everyone from noticing?
You don't have to know.
Nemoto will probably consider this
assassination a warning from Class D.
We can buy some time now, huh?
Hideyoshi, what's going on
with the negotiation with Class D?
We promised to meet
up in an empty classroom.
Shimada has agreed to it as well.
If we can provoke Class D there...
I wonder if they'll respond
to our provocation smoothly.
I've got a special plan.
Just leave it to me.
There's one thing that worries me.
What's the matter, Muttsulini?
I saw Nemoto talking
about something in Class A.
In Class A? That's strange...
What was he doing in Class A?
Yuuji!
Shouko! Wh-What're you doing here?
Why are you still in school?
Huh? What're you saying?
Yuuji... I heard that your mom collapsed.
Huh?! You mean my mom?!
She's so healthy that she
doesn't even catch a cold!
In any case, you have to go home now.
Hey, wait! I have to carry out
an important operation now!
This is no time for that.
Like I said, just wait! How come you...
--Just come with me.
--Shouko! Calm down!
Something is fishy
about what just happened.
What do you mean, Muttsulini?
Normally, Yuuji is the
first one that they'd contact.
Maybe they couldn't reach him?
His cell is being repaired, so...
Then they could've called
him in via the school PA system.
Then, what Nemoto was
talking about in Class A could be...
It was probably the fake
information that we just heard...
What?!
Oh shoot! We were going to leave the
operation to provoke Shimizu to Yuuji.
Have you heard anything about it?
No, nothing.
Why did Nemoto do this?
Don't tell me he figured out our plan?
No, he's probably trying
to buy some time, too.
Until he checks what
Class D is going to do,
he probably wanted to
contain our movements.
Impressive, Nemoto...
It's about time, right?
M-Minami...
I just came because I was needed
for the negotiation, that's all, okay?
What do we do, Akihisa?
What do we do...?
Since Yuuji isn't here, we have no choice
but to do something about it by ourselves!
Idiot Test!
Honey! I wanted to see you!
--Hey, get off of me, Miharu!
--Honey!
Your breasts remind me of
the quiet ocean. They're the best!
That means they're flat,
just like the horizon, right?
I said, get off of me!
I'm thinking about you 360 days a year!
So you don't during obon
festivities and New Year's, huh?
Shimizu, that's it!
Shimada is Akihisa's girlfriend!
Don't intervene thoughtlessly!
There you go!
The start of our operation!
What are you talking about?!
By looking at my
honey's face, it's so obvious
that there's nothing going on
between her and that big jerk!
It's hard to think that that pig jerk
is suitable for her in the first place!
I-It's true that I'm not good-looking
and I'm not smart, either, but...
Looks? Smarts?
I'm not talking about such trivial things.
This is something
more fundamental than that.
What?
I've been watching the
relationship between the two of you,
but your attitude is terrible, you pig jerk.
Your attitude towards Himeji in the same class
and towards my honey are too different.
You're kind and considerate to Himeji.
You treat her as if she's a princess.
On the contrary, you aren't
considerate to my honey. Not only that,
you don't even show the least bit of
kindness you should have towards girls.
To put it plainly, you are a huge idiot
who not only doesn't notice her charms
but who treats her like a guy friend!
Whether such a pig jerk is
suitable for her or not is not a question
of his looks or his academic abilities!
On top of that, to think that you'd
leave her alone and follow Himeji like that
after she told you she liked you,
even though she was acting.
That's unbelievable!
Isn't the truth that you
think she's a guy or something?!
Minami!
What're you gonna do by following her?
Are you gonna talk to her rough
again as if she's your guy friend?
Are you gonna hurt her again?
I'll go talk to her. If you go,
it'll make things worse.
Err... I don't know what's going on,
but I should leave, too, right?
I don't know what you wanted
to achieve with this meeting,
but I'll never acknowledge
you as my rival in love.
It's a waste of time to be jealous of a
pig jerk who doesn't notice her charms, so...
I'm the only one who recognizes her charms.
Shimizu...
Do you still have something to say?
There's something I have
to tell you no matter what.
We, Year 2 Class D, are
going to declare war on Class F!
What?!
What's going on?
Didn't our plan fail?
So what're we gonna do after this?
It'd be hard to win with
our current fighting power.
That was in my plan, too.
Yuuji!
As I suspected, it was fake
information planted by Nemoto.
My mom is doing better than fine.
That's great.
Good job, Akihisa.
It wasn't exactly how I planned,
but if you were able to
instigate Shimizu, that's a success.
So, Yuuji, how are we gonna fight Class D?
If we fight in an all-out
battle, we have no chance.
So we'll settle this with a
battle between representatives.
I'm impressed that you
came without running away.
Same to you.
It's not that I want to fight my honey.
As long as I can beat the crap
out of that pig jerk, that'll do for me.
So she says. It's now
your mission from here.
Go.
Thanks, Yuuji.
You're the one person
I can never forgive! Be prepared!
Teacher! Please give
us summoning approval!
I approve!
--Summon!
I wanna ask you something first.
What is it?
Was what you said a
trick to start this war?
I... see...
My honey was crying.
My words triggered it.
But it's because... it's
because a guy like you exists!
"Chemistry"
Why is a lout like you by her side?!
Why is a vulgar man who plays on
her feelings conversing with her?!
Why?! Why?!
Why does a bastard who lies to her
like it's nothing in order to use her
stay close to her,
pretending to be her friend?!
I'm not... lying!
Even an idiot like me
at least knows there are
some lies you should never tell.
What I said wasn't a lie!
I don't believe it!
I don't wanna believe it!
What I said was
unmistakably my true feelings!
I don't wanna hear it!
Stop right there!
Yuuji! What're you doing?!
From here, just leave it to us.
How dirty! This is foul play!
Call it foul play if you like!
This isn't a game! It's a war!
Yuuji!
Do it.
Yuuji! Sto--
Ahh! Ow, ow, ow...! Why me?!
Ow! Ow, ow...!
Ow, ow, ow...! Ow, ow, ow...!
What?! What?! This
combination of sharp and dull pain
is breaking new ground!
Shimizu... As you can see, the main
cause of all the problems is cleaned up.
Would you forget what
happened this time and forgive him?
Yeah... My fury still isn't cooled down,
but if this pig jerk will be
confined to the remedial classroom,
I'll accept the cease-fire.
Is it possible that you were
planning this from the start?
Well, sorry.
There's no way we can win against
Class D with our current forces, right?
So it's just natural to
negotiate a cease-fire.
When we get right down to it,
you're at fault for hurting my honey!
I-I'm sorry! I'm sorry from the
bottom of my... Ow, ow, ow...!
If what you said was a lie, I wouldn't
have let you get off the hook this easy.
But this time, I'll let
you off the hook with this.
The deal is done. Guys! Let's go back!
Yeah!
Welcome.
Thus, the war ended.
How was it, Muttsulini?
Looks like Nemoto from Class B gave up.
Well, that was expected.
There's already no benefit to him.
Also, I went and collected this.
What's that?
--I don't know what you wanted to achieve with this meeting,
--D-Don't tell me this is...
--but I'll never acknowledge you as my rival in love.
--The wiretapped recording of the summit conference.
H-H-H-H-Hey! What're you playing?!
Hold him down good.
Got it.
Let go of me, Hideyoshi!
I can't do that.
You're too noisy. Shut up for a while.
Do you still have something to say?
There's something I have
to tell you no matter what.
I wanna clear up just
one misunderstanding.
I already know that you
and my honey dating is an act.
Well, I'm not talking about that.
Uhm...
I wanted to say that you're not the
only one who recognizes Minami's charms.
What're you saying?!
You're always saying mean things to her,
and you don't even cherish her as a girl!
It's true that I don't
treat her like a princess.
I might be treating her
just like I treat my guy friends.
But...
But... what?
To me, Minami is someone whom
I can be my true self around...
...who is fun to hang out with...
...and who sometimes makes
subtle gestures that are cute...
She's very charming...
Yeah, she's a charming girl.
Well... that was unexpected.
Yeah, I thought you'd say
things a little more indirectly.
Th-That was a straight pitch.
Th-They heard it...
Of all people, these three heard it...
I didn't realize that you
can say things boldly like that.
F-For some reason, my
heart is beating crazy fast.
How bold...
My life... is over.
Noin, stretch!
Ah, Big Sis! Welcome home!
I-I'm home.
What's wrong? Your face is red!
Haduki, what am I gonna do?
About what? Did
something happen at school?
Say, Haduki...
Yes?
I might've fallen hopelessly
in love with someone.
Flash! Shine! Light bulb, shiny flash!
I'm not making progress.
Someone's interfering... No, no!
The issue is, I don't have
enough common multiples
Okay, I basically get it.
What is the truth... Baby?
If you see this, draw a
diagram and explain it, Baby!
No word or number can describe you
My heart is being shocked by
the magnetic force between S and N
(S! S! Super! Sticking together,
Number! I say No.1 boy!)
Congratulations! From here on
out you're My, ma-my "treasure"
You're special to me,
no matter what happens
I'll hold you ever so
tight and never let you go
I want to be in love, in a
dream you can forget about limits
It's special, right? After all,
we came to know each other
Forgive me for being like this
Flashed! Shined! Right answer, perfect match!
I'm dreading this. What do I say to
apologize to Minami when I see her?
--Hey.
--Hm?
What's with that gloomy face, Aki?
Huh?
M-Minami?!
What?
Well, uhm... Er...
I'm sorry about yesterday.
What? Did you do something
again that you have to apologize for?
Well, it's not like that.
If you cause another problem,
I won't let you off the hook!
Huh?
You dummy!
Question 11.
What do you call those people whom
you were close to when you were small?
Childhood frien-- Ahhhhh!
Fiancée.
Next episode!
"Yuuji, Shouko, and Childhood Memories!"
This will be on the test.