In the year 850, the Colossal Titan again appeared
and decimated yet another barrier between us and them.
Once more, mankind retreated in panic
before the advance of its greatest foe.
Brave soul after brave soul perished.
Eaten alive.
Eren! No!
Eren, himself, fell prey to their hunger.
Whoa, Mikasa is a badass!
How is she going so fast?
No! Mikasa's using too much gas!
I'll do whatever it takes to win!
Whatever it takes to live!
Just when things seemed their darkest for Mikasa,
out of nowhere came the unlikeliest of allies.
There. Got it! The ODM gear's functional.
And I restocked your blades.
Just... Just leave me this one, okay?
It's just that... I would rather
this be my end, not being eaten alive.
Why'd you...?
Armin.
I will not leave you behind.
But... I mean... Titans are everywhere!
You can't jump and carry me on your back at...
Come on. Let's move.
Please. Don't do this. It's not going to work.
Enough people have died on my account.
No!
Hold on! I've got an idea!
What is it then?
Only you two are capable of pulling
this off, so it's really your choice.
This may sound crazy, but I think he might be useful.
Whoa, you mean the Titan?
He only attacks his own kind.
He seems to have no interest in us.
What if we can somehow steer him to HQ
and let him loose on the other Titans?
Look, we know he's taken at least one out already.
We can use him as a weapon!
You have got to be kidding!
How the hell you think we're supposed to steer that thing!
Well, something tells me he's fighting on instinct.
I'm almost sure if you take down the pair
he's tangling with now, he'll go look for others.
That'd lead him straight to HQ.
We're not steering him so much as luring him.
I think it'll work. I really do.
Think? You're asking us to risk
our necks on a stupid gut feeling?
If I'm right about this, we can put down
the siege on headquarters in one fell swoop!
It's worth a shot.
Huh? Seriously?
Better to take a gamble on Armin's gut
feeling than wait around to be slaughtered.
If there's a decent shot, why not take it?
So, basically we're going to recruit a Titan?
Yes. Exactly.
We'll look like morons if we screw this up.
Yeah. But if we don't, look
how many lives we stand to save.
Where there's a will there's a way.
It's still nuts, but what the hell.
Why couldn't I stop them?
I'm the last person that should've been given the reigns!
No! No. This is our chance.
We can get the drop on them while
they're preoccupied. It's perfect!
Let's go!
Make for a break for HQ while they're distracted!
We can do this! Hey, we run out of gas, we're dead anyway.
Give it everything you've got!
Jean!
You really came through for us
there, man; we owe you big time.
Huh?
Don't shrug it off, I'm serious.
We're alive because of you!
Like I said, you make a great leader!
Easy with that crap. We're not outta this yet!
Damn it!
How many... How many of us made it?
How many bodies did I crawl over?
How many of our comrades died on my orders?
Hold on a sec. You guys with the supply team?
Yeah.
Jean! Stop!
You cowards! You left us out there on our own!
People are dead 'cause you
didn't have the guts to do your job!
The Titans were coming at us from every angle!
They overran the supply room, okay?
It's your job to deal with it and back us up anyway!
Hit the deck!
Son of a...
There's too many people! They can smell us!
Run!
Get further in!
We can't all go at once!
Where's Mikasa? Have you seen her?
She ran out of gas. Forget about her. She's dead!
This is it. This is reality.
Of course it is. How deluded was I?
No. No, on some level, I knew it all along.
I mean, when you stop and think for second, it's obvious.
There's no winning. Not against them.
What?
Wha... What the...? My god.
Mikasa, you're...!
Wow. Close one. I was running on fumes.
We made it here, though! Crazy, but we did!
You... I... Am I dreaming this, or what?
You're a certified genius!
From now on, far as I'm concerned, your word is law!
Check it out! We found an Abnormal
that's got a bone to pick with its own kind.
And the best part? He couldn't care less about us!
That's right, you heard me. This big
beautiful S.O.B.'s our ticket out of here!
You mean like fighting fire with fire?
Listen to yourself. A Titan's not gonna help us!
You're out of your mind if you think this can work...
It is working.
For whatever reason he's rampaging against them.
Stand back and let him do it. Trust me. You'll see.
Either way. What choice do we have?
Right now that thing is our best chance at survival.
Look at him go! This guy makes
the others look like total weaklings.
They're not gonna take this building.
Not with him on a rampage out there.
That's all well and good.
But what's to keep him from turning on us once he's done?
Guess we'll worry about that when we're safe.
Yeah, you're right. At least he's buying us a little time.
Good news!
Courtesy of the Military Police.
And covered with a layer of dust.
Are you absolutely sure buckshot is the way to go?
Seems like we might as well throw spit wads.
I mean, c'mon guys. Are guns even effective?
I dunno, but they're bound to be better than nothing.
We're looking at seven Titans in the
supply room of the four-meters-tall variety.
If we time this perfectly,
this much ammo oughta be enough to do the trick.
Step one, we lower a group into the
area via lift to get the Titans' attention.
Step two, when the Titans
come within range, the group
fires in all four directions
simultaneously, blinding them.
Then the hard part.
The moment of truth, as it were.
Before the Titans have time to recover,
seven of us swoop down from the
ceiling and strike their vital regions.
That's it. That's the plan.
It puts all our lives on the line...
We screw up, we're dead.
That's a hell of a risk for one
attack, but it's our only chance.
Seven people have to slay seven
Titans in one blow, at the same time.
We're gonna need the best of you. The seven soldiers
most physically gifted and adept with their paring blades.
You'll be the difference between
life and death for the rest of us.
I'm sorry. That's how it is.
Seems like a sound plan.
When you get right down to it,
the risk is the same for everyone.
Doesn't really matter who goes.
Look, I... I'm willing to be talked out of this.
One half-baked strategy can't be our only option, right?
Hey, don't be so hard on yourself.
C'mon, with what we're looking at?
'Cause for our only option, it's pretty well thought-out.
If we give it our all, we might just pull this off!
It'll be fine. You just have to be confident.
You're a better strategist
than you give yourself credit for.
I'm serious.
That mind's saved Eren and me more than once.
When did I ever save you? That's not...
Alright, the lift's ready to
go. Guns are loaded to the stocks.
Let's go kill some Titans!
You didn't realize it at the time.
We can talk about it later.
Okay. I'm gonna ask the obvious question.
Can we do this without ODM gear?
No problem. These guys are only four-meters tall.
Their weak spots are not too far above eye level.
He's right. Size won't be an issue; the spot's
still only one meter high and ten centimeters across.
Back 'o the head to the nape o' the neck!
Worse comes to worst, you can always
just shove one of these up their ass.
That's the other weak spot.
Are you serious?
That's news to me!
Did I miss a day of training or something?
Come on. Knock it off, Reiner.
You want your final words to be an ass joke?
Good. We're still at seven.
Okay now, nice and easy.
Don't lose your cool!
Fire only when they're all within range!
Steady.
That's right; wait for it.
Our lives are riding on this.
Gotta make this attack count.
Steady...
Almost...
Fire!
Got it!
How're you guys?
Uh... I, uh... I'm sorry. I didn't.
Oh crap.
I didn't mean to sneak up on you.
Sasha and Conny missed!
Lead 'em the hell back!
I... Oh, god.
I said I was sorry!
Mikasa! You saved my life!
Are you okay?
Because of you I am!
Then get up.
I owe you one.
No worries.
Wow.
By the skin of your teeth.
You're damn lucky you didn't end up worse off.
They're all dead! Start loading up supplies!
It worked!
We're gonna make it! We're gonna live!
No more of 'em coming in!
Thank you, crazy-berserker Titan!
I caved. In front of the whole gang.
I'm never gonna be able to face any of 'em again!
Damn it, feel sorry for yourself later! Focus on escape!
Listen, man. What you said
about me bein' a leader and all.
Don't talk to me like that again, alright?
Promise me you're not going to take this the wrong way.
But I don't think you're a
good leader 'cause you're strong.
I think you're a good leader
'cause you know what it is to be weak.
You're one of us.
You're scared out of your mind just like we all are.
It makes you alert; sympathetic.
You made a damn good call out there.
Got me runnin' for my life.
You're why I can say this.
Ready, people? Let's do this!
Mikasa?
What're you doing? We have to leave now!
Look. Down there.
Cannibalism?
Can he not regenerate like the others?
This may sound stupid, but I
was hoping he'd be the key for us.
That he'd help mankind break the cycle.
Turn the tide just long enough
to give us a little ray of hope.
She's right.
He's too valuable to just let die.
There's too much we can learn from him.
I think it's perfectly clear our priority
should be to ward the scavengers off him.
He's no good to us picked apart.
Are you out of your mind?
We've got a path out of this nightmare and you wanna stay?
Think about it. Having an Abnormal as an
ally would be an incredible advantage, right?
A cannon's got nothing on a Titan
who likes to rip apart his own kind.
You... Do you hear yourself? He's not like a new friend!
Oh, no.
It's the one that ate Thomas!
Holy...
What was that you were saying?
'Cause I think it's a moot point now.
Alright, enough of this!
Let's leave while we can!
We're lucky the ugly bastard didn't get bored.
We'd have been next on the menu.
Look, a Titan's a Titan...
Mikasa!
It's him.
But... his arm. His leg. I don't understand.
I watched him get eaten. I watched him die.
I saw...
How is this possible?
Okay. So, uh...
Eren did all this?
The overwhelming desire for revenge;
an emotion powerful enough to
alter even our physical bodies.
When hate transforms you into
the very thing you despise, however;
you might just find the swords
of your allies turned on you.