This may end up being my will.
Things have settled down a bit.
It's too early to let our guard down yet,
but since I have a bit of quiet time,
I thought I'd put my thoughts down on paper.
My name is Sakura Megumi.
I was the Japanese teacher at
Megurigaoka Private High School.
No... I am still the Japanese teacher.
Even if this building no longer
functions as a school.
I realized that for the first time on
that day, up on the roof after school.
No...
It was even before that.
When on that day was it that
I first felt that premonition?
School Living Club
#3
"That Time"
From: Mom
Good morning
To: Megumi
Subject: Good morning
Good morning, Megumi.
Is your work as a teacher going well?
I'm still a bit worried about you.
You've always been a little meek,
which isn't a bad thing, but when
it comes time to do something
for your students, it might
Ribbon, ribbon...
Oh, no!
Again...
I'm driving.
I understand why she's worried.
Mom told me I wasn't cut out to be a teacher.
When I chose to major in education,
and when I got my teacher's license.
So many sirens this morning...
Staff Room
I wouldn't go so far as to say
you're not cut out for it.
Just be careful to maintain the
appropriate distance from your students.
It sounds nice to call yourself their friend,
but teachers and students cannot
be considered as equals.
Not cut out to be a teacher...
Understand?
Yes. I'm sorry.
Don't let him get to you.
The vice principal gives the same
lecture to all the young teachers.
Right.
Look at what's going on here at the scene.
What could possibly be causing
such wide-scale chaos?
What's that about?
The cause is unknown, but let's
hope for a quick resolution.
Scary.
Riots...
Multiple-car pileups in Megurigaoka
Now I'll hand back your tests from last week.
Ishizuka-kun.
Here.
Shoujouji-san.
Sera-kun.
Here.
Takeya-san.
Takeya Yuki-san?
Here.
Look at her hat...
See you for extra lessons after class.
Megu-nee, you're brutal.
Don't call me Megu-nee. It's Sakura-sensei.
Calling myself their friend...
Maybe I am doing that.
Bye, Sensei.
Bye.
Megu-nee's really got it rough.
What?
Having trouble concentrating with me here?
No.
I don't like tests, but...
I don't mind being with you, Megu-nee.
Then let's work through this together.
Yuki-chan, I'll be right back.
I'll be out in the hall,
so just call if you need anything.
I'm hungry. I want a snack!
After you finish your test.
What's wrong, Ebisuzawa-san?
Don't you have practice now?
Um...
I...
Sorry for interrupting the test.
But you're the only one I can
talk to about this, Megu-nee...
Don't call me Megu-nee.
It's Sakura-sensei.
I just don't know what to do anymore.
Or why I feel the way I do
around him.
I see.
Your former senpai who graduated, huh?
I think I get it.
So you want some advice about
romance, then, Ebisuzawa-san?
N-No!
I... guess so...
But...
Well... maybe...
Then what's there to worry about?
I feel a little better now
that I've talked about it.
It's weird. I could never talk
about this with anyone else.
But you're different, Megu-nee.
Thanks, again!
Maybe I'm not cut out to
be a teacher. But still...
Okay!
Took you long enough!
Sorry.
I finished ages ago.
Good job.
All done.
I'm exhausted, Megu-nee.
Don't call me Megu-nee, please.
Maybe I'll get some ice cream and eat it all up.
You shouldn't snack on
the way home from school.
From: Mom
Subject: Emergency
Subject: Call me
From: Mom
Subject: Please call
Sending you a video...
Did you see the news about...
What?
Mass traffic accidents in Megurigaoka
That's right near here...
Massive outbreak of violence at the mall
People walk onto train tracks...
Rail traffic halted
Hey, Megu-nee!
Yeah...
Megu-nee, you weren't even listening.
What're you watching?
You shouldn't peek at people's phones.
Boo.
I'm going home.
Takeya-san!
It looks like the trains aren't running.
Why don't you wait for a bit?
Really?
But I'm starving.
Oh, I know!
Let's go to the roof.
Don't they grow mini-tomatoes there?
They do, but we can't eat them.
Besides, you're not supposed
to go up to the roof.
Then I'll say I'm observing the gardening club.
Would it be okay then?
Oh, very well.
It's unlocked?
I'm sorry!
I forgot to lock the door again.
Would you mind locking it for me?
Wow!
Are you in the gardening club?
As you can see.
Coming to check out the club?
Yeah! Those tomatoes look delicious.
Want to try one?
Can I?
Sure, if you'll help me with something.
Okay!
Yuuri-san, do you always take care
of all these crops by yourself?
No.
For some reason, no one else showed up today.
Why isn't Mom answering?
Call ended
Home
Incoming call
Kamiyama-sensei
Hello—
Sakura-san, are you safe? Where are you?!
Who's that?
Someone with after-school duty?
The roof?
Then lock the door and
don't let anyone through!
The staff room—
Coming! Be right there!
Wait!
Megu-nee?
But we should open it for them.
Someone!
Please, open the door!
Ebisuzawa-san?!
Hurry, lock the door!
He's hurt!
What happened?
Sensei, we need to take him to the nurse...
We can't go down there!
It's too late.
What's that?
Everybody suddenly...
started acting like that.
Then they got to the track team, and Senpai...
Senpai!
We need to get outside
and call an ambulance.
We can't.
I've been trying, but it won't connect!
I don't get it...
Why?
Why is this happening?
Damn! They're here!
The gardening club lockers!
Wakasa-san...
Takeya-san, push that
washing machine over here!
Senpai?
Ebisuzawa-san!
Ebisuzawa-san, run!
Silly...
Why are you crying?
Who are you, anyway?
What a weird hat...
Sensei, at this rate, we'll all...
If the school and the outside
are like this, what do we do?
Sensei. Sensei!
Most who were here lost their lives.
Students and teachers alike.
These girls are the only
ones left in this school.
I want to believe help will come someday,
and protect them as long as I live.
Because I'm their teacher.
School Living Club
Let's dig in!
It's so dry...
I don't mind hardtack, but it
doesn't make for much of a meal.
That's true.
We can't cook today, since the power's out.
I like blackouts, though.
They're kind of exciting.
Our showers are heated electrically, you know.
That means no hot water.
My bath...
You okay?
I hope it rains...
Why?
So I can shower...
Are you a dog?
Maybe.
Even Taroumaru wouldn't do that.
Camping!
What?
We'll go camping!
Camping?
Yeah, you know...
Schools do camping trips, right?
Since we're the School Living Club,
we can camp out at school!
Oh, that sounds good!
So we'll put up tents in a classroom?
I get it.
You don't have electricity
when you're camping.
I think we've got a tent in the
club room that can fit four.
That's just big enough for all of us!
Hey! What about me?
I-It's fine. If we squeeze together,
you can fit too, Megu-nee.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean...
Sorry, Megu-nee!
No, I was just joking.
Someone should keep watch, anyway.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Megu-nee.
Thanks for all you do.
Where'd that come from?
Yes, thank you.
Megu-nee, thanks.
Thank you very much.
Don't call me Megu-nee. It's Sakura-sensei.
Okay!
Feels like the real thing, huh?
Yeah. Ghost stories are great at times like these.
I know I said it feels real, but...
No way!
Do you know this one?
On a dark night, just like tonight...
Chop!
Ouch!
Anything to share that's
not a scary story, Mii-kun?
Not especially.
There's gotta be something.
Right? Right?
I don't really care for physical contact...
Oh? Why not?
Pssshhh
Huh? Mii-kun, you're turning bright red.
Oh, cut her some slack.
Okay, then we'll tell romantic stories!
About our crushes and stuff!
I don't want to...
Do you have any tales of love
to tell, Yuki-san?
I sure do!
Huh? Wait, maybe not.
Which is it?
What about you, Kurumi-chan?
She deflected.
You love that shovel, Kurumi-chan.
And that's a romantic story?
That time when I got rejected...
You were there to comfort me, Yuki.
I was?
Wow, Yuki-senpai. Even you
can come through sometimes.
Actually, maybe I had it wrong.
I thought so.
You meanies...
Megu-nee's back!
She is?!
That was fast!
Now, are there any naughty girls
staying up past their bedtimes?
It's late.
Everyone go to sleep, okay?
All clear.
Megu-nee's on patrol for us.
That was close.
Were you scared?
Megu-nee's nothing to be scared of.
What's wrong, Yuki-chan?
Well, I was thinking... We're all
going to graduate soon, right?
Yeah.
But Megu-nee's still going to be at the school.
Thinking about it like that makes me sad.
I know what you mean. She's a good teacher.
Yeah. Without her, we wouldn't have this club.
You're right.
Yeah! She's so nice, isn't she?
She gives too much homework, though.
And she writes the wrong
kanji every now and then.
Oh, yeah.
But she's still really nice.
Too much homework, though.
Wait, we're back where we started.
You all really like Sensei...
I mean, Megu-nee. Don't you?
Yeah! We love her!
Next Time!!
So, Megu-nee, why'd you become a teacher?
Oh, you want to know?
Nah, not really.
You'll always be the same Megu-nee,
no matter what the reason.
#4
Outing
Next time on Episode 4 of
SCHOOL-LIVE, "Outing."