An errand?
Yes.
A lot of fortune-telling work has come in all of a sudden,
so I'd like you to go in my stead
to pick up the items I ordered.
Alright.
You can count on us!
I'll give this errand my all!
Tell me, tell me! What'd you order?
It's an import I've wanted for a long time!
I've always wanted to use it to tell fortunes!
It's called... the Chinese Porcelain Bowl
with Bats and Nine Peaches!
CHINESE PORCELAIN BOWL
WITH BATS AND NINE PEACHES
Chinese Porcelain Bowl with Bats and Nine Peaches?!
Does it have some sort of legendary
fortune-telling power or something?
That's so cool!
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see a light! Which way? (That way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
Which way should I go? I can't decide!
The path to our dreams is always a big labyrinth
To the left? To the right?
Which way is right? (Which way?)
No matter which way I go
It'll be fun because my friends are there!
That's the right answer!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see the future! Let's walk together!
See, you can see a smile! Which way? (This way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
That looks yummy!
Those clothes are so cute!
Come on, you two, don't get distracted!
We're never gonna get there at this rate-
That's the divining instrument shop Benten.
Isn't it that famous store?
Umm, I heard it's the biggest
divining tool shop in Meirocho,
and they sell any kind of implement that you might need.
That sounds cool!
It'd be fine if it were just cool.
What's that supposed to mean?
I heard something a while back.
Something about the shopkeeper at Benten Instruments.
She uses the guise of an Urara
to control Meirocho from the shadows,
and she's involved in the black market, too.
And she's a really successful gambler, too.
She controls town from the shadows?
She's a successful gambler?
She goes by the name...
The Old Tanuki of Bloque Ten!
Old Tanuki?!
Did we just take on an errand
that's gonna be a lot of trouble?
Anyway, everyone, be extra careful to watch yourselves.
We didn't come here to play around.
Okay!
Let's hurry.
By the way, why're we leashed together like this?
No
distractions!
If I don't do this, we'll never make it there!
Benten
Excuse me!
Wow, there are so many weird things here!
These are all divining tools?
But I dunno what they're used for!
I heard the rumors, but she really does have
an amazing variety of items!
A lot of these I've only seen in books!
This is a seeing stone, also called a Sun Stone!
It's a stone that shows you the right path!
Oh, look, rosemary incense!
It's been used since the time of the Egyptian kings
and it has a powerful warding effect on spirits!
They placed it inside pharaohs' tombs!
She even has an eyeball crystal!
Kon!
We didn't come here to play around.
I-I'm not playing around!
I'm just studying a little...
It... it's just that Old Tanuki's shop is so amazing...
Who're you callin' a tanuki, you little fox?
I'm the owner of this shop, Benten.
Huh?
How're you gonna pay for this?
This eyeball crystal's an extremely rare item.
I-I'm sorry!
Think you can get out of it just by apologizing?
Should I go by the book
and make you pay with your body?
Here we go!
Go right ahead!
I'm sorry!
Why're you doing that?
I meant you'll pay me back with physical labor.
Come on. I've got mountains of work for you to do.
We've got no choice but to do as Benten-san says.
Let's finish this work quick and
take care of Nina-sensei's errand!
Uh-huh!
Stop the chit-chat and change out of those clothes!
Yes, ma'am!
This is pretty fashionable!
I'm glad there isn't much fabric!
It's really loose.
Wh-why am I the only one?!
You're so cute!
I'm so jealous.
Oh, that looks good.
I-I've never worn Western-style clothes before.
You don't like it?
Here.
Huh?
H-hey!
Huh?!
Why do you have all these weird outfits?!
Because my shop has everything.
What do these have to do with divining?!
Excuse me, what kind of fortune-telling
do you do with these rocks?
Oh, those are flints.
It's used less for fortune-telling
and more for protective spells.
You strike the flint like this
to spread sparks and ward off spirits.
My, that's amazing, Miss!
You know so much about these things,
despite being so young!
I'm sure you'll be a promising Urara in the future!
O-of course...
you could always use it as a regular fire-starter,
but I recommend taking it with you on errands or trips
Jeez, why is Kon the only one standing out so much?
because you can also use it as a charm to ward off danger!
Okay, I can stand out, too!
Gotta find something really flashy.
Fire gods are said to be the strongest at protecting the home,
so sparks confer a cleansing power to them...
Oh, I know this!
Wow, what's this book about?
Welcome!
Can I help you find something?
Everyone's doing such an amazing job.
I've gotta do something, too.
But I'm not good with physical labor,
and I definitely can't approach customers!
Be brave, Nono!
Matsuko-san...
Excuse me!
Miss?
W-welcome...
Oh, I thought it was an employee,
but it's just a wind-up doll!
It looks so real!
So cute!
Let's touch it a little!
Do not touch!
Thank you very much!
How long is she going to make us work?
We've got to pick up the bowl and head home soon.
Kon!
Why are you wearing that?
So Tanuki-san doesn't find us.
Come over here!
They're here, Koume!
Oh, good work-
Wait...
One of you looks really shady right now.
What did you call us here for?
Look at this, Kon. I bet you'll be happy to see it.
I-is that Sendai Takao's sword?!
SENDAI TAKAO'S SWORD
It's a legendary item said to increase your divining power
by a thousand... maybe two thousand percent!
Huh? I didn't know it was that valuable!
And that's not all!
All the items I see here are powerful divining tools that
normal Urara would never be able to get their hands on!
Wow!
Wait, Koume, why are you putting that on now?
Huh?
Hey! Why're you slacking off?!
She found us!
I see you're making light of me.
W-we didn't mean to...
I've already known for a while
that you're the new students from Natsumeya.
That's Nina-sensei's...
Not so fast.
I'm holding on to this until
you pay me back for that crystal.
Let's see...
I'll have you work here for a year.
A year?!
We can't! I know it was expensive,
but a year's way too long!
If we take a year off, we'll fail our Urara training!
We'll be exiled from Meirocho!
If you don't want to work, then pay for it!
Or how about...
I take one of your eyes in exchange for that crystal?
They're a rare red color, so I'm sure one will sell fast.
You... you big mean tanuki!
Chiya?!
What? You wanna go at it?
Benten-san, I'm sorry.
But training is really important to an Urara.
We have to get back to Natsumeya soon!
So please let us go!
I don't care how many years it takes,
I'll pay you back for the crystal!
We can't throw away our training here!
P-please!
Alright, why don't we play a game of chance?
Dice?
The rules are simple. Roll the dice,
and whoever has the highest result wins.
If you win, you won't have to pay for the crystal.
But if you lose, you'll work for me for three more years!
Three years?!
It's not knowing how it'll turn out
that makes the game interesting.
Bet your futures on this game.
Well? Wanna give it a try?
Okay, I'll do it!
Hey! Wait, Chiya, you can't!
You'll lose for sure!
Why?
Remember what Kon said?
Benten-san's a really successful gambler.
That's right! It's really easy for her to manipulate the dice!
But we won't know unless we try!
We don't know if we'll win or lose right now.
But Benten-san, we're training
so we can face the unseen future.
So to keep training, we're gonna win
and go back to Natsumeya!
Alright. It's all up to you, Chiya!
It's in your hands!
Roll well!
Now, let's have at it!
There!
Chiya got a four.
Benten-san's turn...
H-hooray!
You were close to never going back again.
Thank you, Benten-san! See you later!
If you'd abandoned your studies over a little threat
like that and run away from a challenge,
I wouldn't have gone easy on you.
Those girls have promise.
But...
They're still blockheads.
What am I gonna do with these?
N-no, Koume, wait...
You gave me a real hard time.
I'm not letting you get out of this.
I-I said no! Ah!
Don't move. Let me do this.
NAPPING
in preparation
for night work
Don't wake me up!
But...
It's okay, it won't hurt.
Ah... but I still think...
Wh-wh-wh-what on Earth is going on
in the room next door?!
Relax a little more. That's right.
Should I stop them?
It's our duty to guide young women
down a wholesome path...
Relax a little more. That's right.
It's our duty to guide young women
down a wholesome path...
Just like that, just like that.
It's our duty to guide young women
down a wholesome path...
No, but... but...
Ah- No, please, don't!
Argh!
What are you two doing?!
Huh?
My goodness! You were making those... those...
confusing sounds just because her hair got tangled?
What was confusing about them, Saku-chan?
Huh?! No, uh...
Staaaare...
I just couldn't get it untangled.
Don't rush, just take your time and it'll come off.
Really?
Let's eat.
Let's eat!
Chiya, could you pass those vegetables?
Yeah, okay.
Here, say ahh!
Huh? Wait, I can do it myself!
Saku Vision
It's okay, it won't hurt.
Ah, Chiya...
Y-you two!
My, what's wrong, Saku?
Chiya's hair is just too long in the first place.
Yeah...
Well, this is a good opportunity.
Come over here, Chiya, I'll cut it for you.
SCISSORS?!
Wh-what?!
They awakened Chiya's animal instincts!
BEAST
MODE
No! I'm gonna fall, I'm gonna fall!
C-calm down, Chiya!
Good girl, good girl, good girl...
She's been acting like this for a while now.
Why? Is there a reason she doesn't want to cut it?
CUT IT?!
Sh-she's really a feral child...
Chiya-chan's very difficult to handle today.
She's acting like a little kid.
Her stubbornness is such a problem.
Wait...
Rather than cutting her hair, why don't we
cut the button off your top, Koume?
No way! I really like this top!
Who's the one acting like a little kid again?
Chiya doesn't want to cut her hair
and Koume doesn't want to hurt her clothing.
This certainly isn't going anywhere.
I can't help it!
This top was made in France,
and it's really important to me!
There's no way I could cut it!
There's no way I could cut mine, either!
Well, they do say a woman's hair is her livelihood.
And, because hair is still alive
even after it's cut away from the body,
it's regarded as a symbol of the soul or life energy.
It's closely connected to fortune-telling and spellcasting,
and it's very important to an Urara.
Really?
Nina-sensei, you're so smart!
I see.
So that's why Matsuko-san's hair was always
growing longer without me realizing it.
Grow... Grow... Grow...
Scary, scary, scary, scary!
Now that I think about it,
Saku-chan had long hair back in the day.
Huh? Oh, yeah, a long time ago.
Saku
(Age 16)
Huh?! Long hair would look so good on you!
Why'd you cut it all off?
I cut it when I became a patrol officer.
I vowed to protect Meirocho with my life.
Cutting my hair was proof of that.
I see.
Sounds like something you'd do, Saku-chan.
Though you're a protector,
you're often protected yourself.
Captain Saku
FAN CLUB
Alright, stay back, stay back!
Saku-sama!
Don't bother Captain Saku while she's hard at work!
We'll protect Captain Saku from the moment she wakes
to the moment she falls asleep!
Right, Captain Saku?
Don't say that.
How did her hair get this tangled up anyway?
That's what I wanna know!
They say that hair has the power of attraction.
That tied-up hair is like the ties of fate.
Tied-up hair is like the ties of fate?
Yes.
Maybe this is proof of the deep bond between you two?
The deep bond...
Well, nothing we can do, then.
As long as Chiya doesn't wanna cut her hair,
we're gonna have to stay like this.
Koume!
I'd say they're connected by reins, not by bonds.
Will those two be alright?
BONDS!
It's hard to move like this.
Try not to bump into me.
Yeah.
Water, water...
Who knows the answer?
Me!
BATHROOM
H-hey, Chiya!
Are you seriously going to follow me EVERYWHERE?
I can't get untangled, what else can I do?
Let's go together!
Wh-what are you talking about?!
Hey, stop! Don't come in here!
Okay, let's go on the count of three!
That's not the problem here!
Well? Have your bonds grown stronger?
I've grown stronger from the injuries all over me.
I have a favor to ask of you two.
Could you go on an errand this evening?
Huh? But we still haven't gotten untangled.
That's perfect!
Your bonds will grow stronger
by staying so close to one another!
Staying
Close!
Chiya, you just stepped on my foot!
You're a really fast walker!
It's MY fault?!
Match your footsteps to mine!
You match mine!
Sweets
ARINSU
Café
Piping hot sakura manju here!
Of course we'd inevitably get a little irritated.
But that means it's the perfect time to eat some sweets!
Thiff ivv Heaven!
Hey, Chiya, why are you so against cutting your hair?
C'mon, lemme hear it.
Here, I'll give you this.
Jeez, why're you keeping it a secret?
I just don't wanna say why!
God, you're so stubborn!
But honestly, when I think about it,
Chiya really is one mystery after another.
She's a harebrained girl who grew up in the mountains,
and she doesn't know anything
about Urara or living in a town...
She's reckless and naive, and she always
looks like she's not afraid of anything...
I really don't know anything else about Chiya.
Even though she's so physically close to me.
Maybe this is proof of the deep bond between you two?
Nina-sensei, you liar.
Koume?
Chiya, you moron!
You can just tell me!
I know we've only just met each other,
but the way we met might've been some kind of fate!
And we're both students at Natsumeya, so...
W-we're already friends, right?!
Friends?
A lovers' quarrel?
They're taking off their clothes and getting close, too.
L-let's go home!
Excuse me, we wanna pay!
Wait, Koume!
Are we really friends?
Why would I lie?
Then Nono and Kon are friends, too?
That's right! Everyone thinks so.
And friends wanna know more about each other.
It's just, well,
normal...
I'm so happy, Koume!
Thank you for saying we're friends!
O-of course we're friends, but we're also students,
wh-which makes us rivals, too.
Right!
We're colleagues, friends, and rivals!
We're so busy!
Jeez, you don't have to get so close to me anymore!
Chiya, you moron!
I'm glad her hair came out!
This high-quality camellia oil will make your hair hurt less,
and keep it from tangling so easily.
Since you're both here, we'll do it for you too, Koume.
It feels weird for only us to be in the bath.
My, but the princesses in the olden days had many
ladies-in-waiting who would wash their hair for them.
Really...?
Those princesses sure lived a luxurious life!
That should do it.
Let's give it a little time.
Koume, will you hear me out?
I wanna tell you why I don't wanna cut my hair.
When I was really little...
Setsu!
What's for dinner today?
Let's see.
Chiya, don't move!
We've got a real feast today!
I'm gonna make roasted white snake tail!
We don't get to have this often at all! How lucky!
Sob, sob... Sob, sob!
A-and ever since,
I've been so, so, so, so scared that if I cut my hair,
blood's gonna go everywhere.
That's why I didn't wanna say why either!
The traumatic experience is so wild
I can barely wrap my head around it.
That's why I didn't wanna say why either!
The traumatic experience is so wild
I can barely wrap my head around it.
A-and I'm so, so, so, so scared of scissors, too...!
It's so not like you to be afraid of something.
Don't laugh at me!
Hey, Koume...
I wanna know more about you and everyone.
The stuff you're scared of and the stuff you like, too.
We all met one another, after all!
Yeah. I'll tell you anything
you want to know from now on.
Is this really Chiya?!
She's sparkling so much, I can barely believe it's her!
Chiya-chan looks like a real princess!
Now there's nothing to worry about.
Thanks, Nina-sensei!
Sure!
Alright, let's start preparing dinner, then.
Nono, could you please clean that up?
Alright!
RAWRRRR
She went from a high-class pedigree
to a stray mutt in two seconds flat!
Jeez, cut it out already! Chiya!
If I turn the corner, I wonder if I'll reach my dream
Getting lost and wandering in circles
It'd be great if I could just run into you!
There are some days when I don't have it altogether 1 to 10
Which way should I go to get a happy ending?
From right to left, from like to love
Uh-oh, I'm in love with love! I'm in such a hurry!
I want it badly, I can't get out of it!
I'm looking
I'm looking for you!
I haven't seen what you look like, but my heart's beating fast
Kiss me in my imagination!
The moment we meet is a crash
It gets a little complicated, that's fate
Maybe, maybe you're lost too?
We can't see the end
The maze that starts with romance
Will you find me in there?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Good and Bad Things are Sometimes Ticklish"!
We'll use dice fortune-telling to see
what kind of episode it'll be, Chiya-chan.
Rah!
The dice are stuck in the wall!
"Good and Bad Things
are Sometimes Ticklish"