I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
Dawn of
Extermination
This is it.
Honestly, you may be able to manage,
since you have the Black Demon Series.
But if we're doing this, I want us to crush them and come out without even a scratch.
So don't act on impulse—
I won't.
Crush them without even a scratch, huh?
I like that.
Then let's move.
Based on that girl's information,
the vampires outnumber us seven to five.
Chances are they're sleeping,
so we're going to charge in at full force.
Keep formation, watch each other's backs,
and stay together.
This is...
The clothes of livestock.
Let's go.
We're heading straight to floor B3,
where the vampires supposedly are.
Why don't they escape
while the vampires' backs are turned?
Because it's crawling with monsters outside.
They're getting protection from the vampires.
In return for their blood?
That's why we're going to rescue them.
Everyone, prepare to attack!
Draw!
Before they call for backup—
You cursed swine...
How does it feel to be killed by livestock, scum?
Burn in Hell.
Seriously?
How many times have I told you
not to act on your own?!
I didn't act on my own.
The enemy was unarmed,
and I waited for the command to draw.
You need to quit complaining on the battle—
Hell yeah.
I've waited four years for moments like these!
Fool.
A wild swing like that won't even graze me—
Wh-What's with that power?
Oh my!
I knew he was strong,
being Lieutenant Colonel Guren's favorite and all,
but I didn't think he'd be this strong.
That was awesome, Yuu!
Still not as strong as me, though.
What?
Let's see you try and do better, then.
You picking a fight?
Do you know what'll happen if I go all out?
Bring it!
Damn straight I'll bring it.
Now, now...
The hell? I'll kick your ass.
Those two...
They're the Lieutenant Colonel's boys—
troublemakers who struggle with teamwork.
Perhaps that's why he thought you could train them.
Stop mucking around.
There are still five of them left.
Here they come.
Let's do this.
Mitsuba!
Eight of them?!
Wh-What's going on?
This isn't what we were told—
Told?
Told by whom, exactly?
I want to show my appreciation.
You used a child to...
Humans are vile.
They'll easily betray their own kind
if it means saving a friend or family member.
Stop!
Forget about me!
Run!
Don't make me repeat myself!
I'm not going to leave a comrade behind!
I'll get you out of there right now!
Go!
S-Stop...
Fall back!
Please, stop...
Pathetic livestock.
He did it!
What was it that you said, again?
"Humans are vile"?
"Scum that betray their own kind if it means saving a friend or family member?"
Looks like someone's done their research.
That's exactly right.
Humans will do anything for their family.
Even if it means shamelessly lying
or turning into a devil or demon.
If that's vile,
then fear our depraved acts, and keel over, vampires!
Christ, he's so damn annoying.
Oh well. Let's do this thing. With all of us here...
...it'll be a piece of cake.
It seems like they're all armed with Class 2 weapons.
Th-They still outnumber us, though.
We went in expecting no less.
So what now?
It's time.
We'll exterminate the vampires!
I see...
Thank goodness.
Um...
I-I'm so sorry!
I...
You were trying to protect your friends.
That's all.
B-But...
You did the right thing,
so don't apologize.
Rescued from her perch atop the tower,
the once damsel in distress
gazes at him passionately.
Destined, the two slowly fall...
Not in love!
Idiot.
What's his deal?
Why does he...
Yuu was held captive
at the vampires' city when he was a kid.
But one day...
Is it true, what Shinoa said?
That you left your family behind at the vampires' city...
That's none of your business.
Keep out of my past.
Wait!
You...
I probably don't have any right to say something like this,
but I don't think you were in the wrong.
Maybe not.
But I left my family behind
in order to save my own life.
That fact still remains.
That's why I'll never...
Tsk. Forget it.
Yuu!
What now? Do you still...
U-Um, so... earlier...
Th-Tha—
Are you going to tell me or what?
Whatever!
I still hate you!
What did I do?!
How long are you two gonna mess around?
Let's get going already.
Sh-Shut up!
No way!
You seriously know how to do that?
Yeah.
Like, for real? Seriously?
That's freakin' awesome, dude!
Shut up already.
You know, I haven't ridden in a car since I was little.
The vampires' city didn't have any,
and gasoline's so precious
that you don't see a lot of it in Shibuya.
Whoa!
Holy crap!
This is so cool!
There we go.
Hey, can I, like... give it a spin?
What? You don't even know how to drive.
Yeah, but just for a little while...
Don't fiddle with anything.
I'll give you a short lesson later.
You can drive, too?!
You're way too awesome, man!
Wh-Whatever. Just hop in the back, you five-year-old.
This is surprisingly good.
It's running.
We'll get to Shinjuku quicker this way.
Wow.
Is it really running?
Grand theft auto is a crime, Kimizuki.
Oh, who cares? Let's get going.
Oh man, this ain't good.
How about this?
What the hell are you—Whoa!
I'm gonna freaking kill you!
Get in. I'll take you guys to Shinjuku.
You're such a pain in the ass! Just get out already!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Shut up!
Seriously, what are they doing?
Well, then.
Let's all get in the Shinoamobile and head to Shinjuku, shall we?
The Shinoamobile?
Hop in, kids!
Eh? Um...
Can you even see past the dashboard?
You're so short, Shinoa!
I see.
Yeah...
We should probably leave
Shinoa's height alone from now on.
For the first time, I agree with you.
What's that sound?
A Horseman again?
Should we take care of it?
No.
If you start killing them now, you'll be at it for days.
If we can lose them, we'll go on ahead to Shinjuku.
Wait.
The sound's coming from Shinjuku.
Stay on the alert for the time being.
Be prepared to handle any kind of situation.
We'll see Shinjuku's defensive barrier after I make a turn at the next corner.
What the...
Don't stop, Kimizuki!
Ram him! He's a noble!
What?!
You...
Drink,
my sword.
No way!
Yoichi!
This isn't looking too good.
Stay in your positions!
The vampire is armed with a Class 1 weapon!
He isn't like the other vam—
Hm, not bad for a human.
Who might you be?
You...
Shinoa.
Yes.
Yuu and Kimizuki will be the vanguards,
since they won't easily fall in a one-on-one.
Mitsu, Yoichi, and I will back them up
and take care of that vampire...
Shoot.
Things just took a turn for the worse.
What now? Do we retreat?
We would if we could,
but I doubt those three would allow it.
So we'll fight with everything we have,
on the verge of demon possession.
However, even with that...
...there's no guarantee we'll all survive. But that's life on the battlefield.
You came in expecting as much, right?
I see. So that's the way it's gonna be.
But I'm not gonna let anyone die.
That's why I have this power.
Right, Asuramaru?
Lord Crowley, what are you doing here?
The Seventh Progenitor
is waiting for you at the front line.
Ferid is waiting for me?
Well, I mustn't keep him any longer.
Just when things were getting interesting, too.
I guess it can wait for another day.
I'll let you go this once.
But the next time we meet, your blood will be mine.
What?!
See you later, my cute little lambs.
G-Good... We're saved.
That guy...
Damn him!
Taking us for fools and playing it cool!
Stop whining.
We need to move immediately before they change their mind.
We'll rendezvous with the Shinjuku Units.
I can't believe this!
There's still this much difference in power,
even with Infernal Arms?
Well, since you own the Black Demon Series,
you can narrow the gap a little by learning curses.
Then hurry up and teach me already!
But what good is it if you're the only one
who can fight a vampire on equal ground?
While you're busy fighting, I'll already be dead.
So will Mitsu and Yoichi.
That's why we need teamwork.
This was a good lesson.
We were also fortunate enough to avoid any casualties.
I was happy that you suggested for us to retreat.
But most importantly...
Thank you for saving my life.
Like Lieutenant Colonel Guren said,
you care about your friends.
Well, um...
I kinda want to go back to Shibuya already.
Same here, but we really can't.
If Shinjuku falls, Shibuya's next.
Your sister's in Shibuya, too.
So let's go.
Let's defend Shinjuku.
Right.
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Vampire
Onslaught
"Vampire Onslaught."