♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
[CHANTING]
A STAR JUST FELL FROM THE SKY.
THAT IS NOT
AN ORDINARY STAR, MY SON.
THAT STAR IS
THE TEAR OF A WARRIOR.
WHAT WARRIOR IS IT?
A LOST SOUL WHO HAS
FINISHED HIS BATTLE
SOMEWHERE ON THIS PLANET.
AHH.
A PITIFUL SOUL WHO
COULD NOT FIND HIS WAY
TO THE LOFTY REALM WHERE
THE GREAT SPIRIT AWAITS US ALL.
[CHANTING]
[BIRD SQUAWKS]
THE REPORT FROM CALLISTO
WENT DIRECTLY TO VICIOUS.
HE IS REQUESTING AN
ARRANGEMENT FOR SOME REDEYE
30,000 WOOLONGS PER GRAM,
7,500 GRAMS TOTAL.
WHY DID HE SEND
YOU TO MAKE THE DEAL?
HE'S A TITAN VETERAN.
WE WERE IN THE SAME SQUADRON.
WHY DOES HE RELY ON YOU NOW?
CALLISTO IS IN
A FINANCIAL DEPRESSION.
WHEN HE CAN'T SEE
THE FUTURE, HE WORRIES.
ALL THE MORE REASON FOR US TO
KEEP OUR HANDS OFF THE PLANET.
IN TRUTH, VICIOUS, ARE YOU
NOT THE ONE WHO'S WORRIED?
IT APPEARS THAT YOU DO
NOT HAVE THE AUTHORITY
TO MAKE YOUR OWN
DECISIONS IN THIS MATTER.
NO MATTER WHO THEY ARE,
THOSE WHO GO AGAINST
THE WILL OF THE VAN
WILL BE SEVERELY PUNISHED.
YOU THINK I'D BETRAY
MY OWN MENTOR?
THE MOUSE CASE
WAS MERELY BAD LUCK.
LIN, YOU SHALL ACCOMPANY
VICIOUS ON THIS JOURNEY.
YES.
WANG LONG!
CALLISTO'S
A FRIGID PLANET, VICIOUS.
YOU'LL NEED SPECIAL CLOTHING
FOR THE ARCTIC CONDITIONS.
COLD CLIMATES
DO NOT CONCERN ME.
TRUE. YOUR HEART IS COLDER
THAN ANY PLANET;
COLDER THAN THE EYE OF
A SNAKE ABOUT TO STRIKE.
VICIOUS, REMEMBER,
A SNAKE CANNOT EAT A DRAGON.
I'LL BE FINE BY MYSELF.
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
THEN, BE AWARE.
IF YOU WANT TO SURVIVE,
YOU'LL HAVE
TO BETRAY ME AT TIMES.
NO, NEVER.
THAT WOULD GO
AGAINST THE WILL OF VAN.
SUCH OLD-FASHIONED THINKING
MAKES ME NAUSEOUS.
THOSE DAMN CORPSES.
I WILL PROTECT YOU
FOR THE HONOR OF THE RED DRAGON.
HONOR, HUH?
WELL, THEN, IT'S UP
TO ME TO SEVER THEM ALL.
AAH!
MAN, IT'S HOT.
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
[BEEPS]
OHH.
WHAT A DEPRESSING GROUP.
[DOOR OPENS]
WHAT'S WITH THE HUMIDITY LEVEL?
IT'S SO MUGGY,
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
WE'RE EXPERIENCING
TECHNICAL DIFFICULTIES.
"IT'D BE TOO HARD TO SEE YOU,
SO I'M LEAVING
WITHOUT SAYING GOODBYE.
PLEASE, PLEASE
DO NOT LOOK FOR ME.
FREE AT LAST."
SHE SUCKED ALL THE ANTI-FREEZE
FROM THE COOLING SYSTEM.
IT'LL BE OFFLINE
FOR AT LEAST HALF A DAY.
AFTER THIS STUNT, WE'RE NOT
GONNA LOOK FOR HER, RIGHT?
SHE EMPTIED OUT THE SAFE, TOO.
UNH!
[ED SPEAKING JAPANESE]
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR FAYE?
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
OR ARE YOU JUST WASTING TIME?
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
TO DO RIGHT NOW?
- AH, SUCCESS!
- IS IT HER?
WHO COULD THIS BE? LET'S SEE.
CODENAME... JULIA!
WHERE'S THAT COMING FROM?
UM, LET'S SEE.
IT'S PRETTY CLOSE.
LOOKS LIKE THE BLUE
CROW ON CALLISTO.
WHO'S RECEIVING IT?
I GOT CUT OFF.
HEY, WAIT!
- BUT--
- HUH?
THERE AREN'T
ANY GIRLS AT THE BLUE CROW?
REALLY? NO KIDDING.
OHH. HEY, SPIKE!
AM I DONE NOW?
HMM. WELL...
[YELP]
[WHIMPERING]
HEY, HOLD ON, SPIKE.
THAT'S A COMMON WOMAN'S NAME.
COME ON, NOW.
WHAT ABOUT FAYE?
WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE HER.
THIS IS A LAWLESS REGION.
A WOMAN CAN'T MAKE IT
OUT THERE ALL ALONE.
YOU KNOW I'M RIGHT, SPIKE.
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT FAYE?
I'M WORRIED, ALL RIGHT
ABOUT THE MONEY SHE TOOK.
I WANT IT BACK.
SPIKE!
I'M GONNA GO LOOK.
YOU'RE NOT.
I'M GONNA
GO LOOK FOR MY WOMAN.
YOU CAN GO LOOK
FOR THE OTHER ONE.
SO, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA HELP ME, ARE YOU?
THAT'S IT!
YOU'VE REALLY GONE TOO FAR.
THEN, DON'T COME BACK.
THERE WON'T BE A PLACE FOR YOU.
THAT'S YOUR CALL, PAL.
HUH?
ANYWAY, AT LEAST
YOU WON'T BE LONELY NOW
NOT WITH YOUR WEIRD ROOMMATES.
MY ROOMMATES?
THAT'S WHY YOU'VE
BEEN STAYING HERE?
YOU'RE BEING STUPID.
IT'S BEEN 3 YEARS
SINCE I TEAMED UP WITH YOU,
BUT I NEVER KNEW YOU HAD
SUCH RIDICULOUS IDEAS
ABOUT THIS THING.
WHAT A JOKE!
AND I THOUGHT YOU WERE
THE ONE WHO WAS LONELY.
I'M GLAD WE CLEARED THAT UP.
GOOD RIDDANCE!
AT LEAST I'LL BE ABLE TO KEEP
SOME FOOD IN THE PLACE NOW.
I NEVER DID UNDERSTAND
YOU, RIGHT TO THE VERY END.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND, EITHER.
GOODBYE!
[SLOW JAZZ PLAYING]
I DON'T KNOW ANY WOMAN!
LIKE I'D KNOW.
NOT EVEN A RUMOR?
I DON'T HAVE ANY LUCK WITH THEM.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
I'D RATHER HOOK UP
WITH A SPINY ARMADILLO!
HAVE YOU HEARD THE NAME
"JULIA" MENTIONED?
YOU SHOULD HAVE ASKED
ME THAT RIGHT OFF.
THERE'S A JULIA OUT IN FRONT
OF TONY'S PLACE EVERY NIGHT.
AHH, YAH!
SORRY, SIRRAH.
I'M NOT JULIA.
JULIUS. MY NAME'S JULIUS.
MY MISTAKE.
WELL, IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
COMPANY, YOU'RE JUST MY TYPE.
THANKS, BUT I ALREADY
HAVE PLANS.
YOU KNOW,
GREN'S REALLY THE ONE
WHO MIGHT BE ABLE TO HELP.
I'VE SEEN HIM
WITH WOMEN ON OCCASION.
GREN?
WOO! IT'S COLD.
YEAH. LET'S CALL IT
A NIGHT. OH, A CUSTOMER.
AFRAID NOT, DARLING.
CAN'T YOU SEE
HE'S STRAIGHT? COME ON.
LET'S TRY ANOTHER CORNER.
WAIT. WHO'S GREN?
WHERE IS HE?
- YOU WANT TO BE MY DATE?
- UGH!
HE PLAYS SAX AT THE BLUE CROW.
AHH.
[SNEEZING]
OHH...
TAKE CARE.
YEAH, THAT WAS
A PRETTY CLOSE ONE.
IF SOMEONE SNEEZES,
AND NO ONE SAYS, "TAKE CARE,"
THAT PERSON WILL
TURN INTO A FAIRY.
THAT'S WHAT THEY SAY
AROUND HERE, YOU KNOW.
THEN THERE'S NO PROBLEM.
I'M ALREADY A FAIRY.
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT?
HMM. HEH HEH.
I'M NOT AS SIMPLE AS
I SEEM, MR. SAXOPHONE.
HOWEVER, THE OTHERS
ARE ALL QUITE INTERESTED.
DIDN'T YOU KNOW?
THERE ARE NO WOMEN IN THIS TOWN.
MMM. THEN I SHOULD
BE VERY POPULAR.
YOU SHOULD BE VERY CAREFUL.
HUH.
THANKS FOR THE TIP,
MR. SAXOPHONE.
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
I'M SEARCHING FOR SOMETHING.
THERE'S NOTHING AROUND HERE
JUST SOME STALE BREAD,
A BROKENDOWN CAR,
AND SOME OLD WHISKEY
THAT TASTES LIKE GASOLINE.
EVER MET A GUY NAMED GREN?
CAN'T SAY THAT I HAVE.
OH, WELL.
[SIGHS]
SO, YOU BOYS NEED SOMETHING?
YOU'RE VICIOUS.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
WHERE'S THE MONEY?
HAND IT OVER,
OR YOU WON'T LIVE TO SPEND IT.
YOU THINK I'M VICIOUS?
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT VICIOUS IS!
[GRUNTING]
START TALKING!
WHY THE HELL
DO YOU THINK I'M VICIOUS?
I HEARD A BIG DEAL WAS COMING
DOWN FOR SOME LUNAR REDEYE.
THEY SAID GREN WAS SELLING IT
TO VICIOUS FOR BIG BUCKS.
I WANTED TO GET MY HANDS
ON THE MONEY! AAH!
TAKE A LOOK. DO I REALLY
LOOK LIKE I HAVE MONEY?
WHY NOT?
ALL FOREIGNERS ARE RICH.
AND THE CODENAME'S JULIA?
HEH HEH HEH!
SOUNDS LIKE SOME SLEAZY
WENCH'S NAME, DOESN'T IT?
YEAH, IT REALLY DOES.
OHH...
YAH!
OOF!
HI, AMIGOS.
ALL 300,000 BOUNTY HUNTERS
IN THE STAR SYSTEM,
HOW Y'ALL DOING?
I WANT A COWBOY.
FORGET IT.
THERE ARE NO BOUNTYHEADS
AROUND HERE.
WHISKEY WITH LIGHT CREAM.
THAT KIND OF COWBOY. RIGHT.
YEAH, YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY
BE A BOUNTY HUNTER, COULD YOU?
UGH.
AND WHO'S OUR
NEW BOUNTYHEAD TODAY?
GRENCIA MARS ELIJAH GUO ECKENER.
WHAT A LONG NAME.
HE ESCAPED FROM
PRISON 3 YEARS AGO,
AND THE STATUTE OF LIMITATIONS
IS ABOUT TO RUN OUT.
AND THE BOUNTY?
SURE ENOUGH,
IT'S NOW DOUBLE HIGH!
DON'T MISS THIS OPPORTUNITY.
THOUGH I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
I KIND OF HATE TO SEE HIM GO.
WHAT A SHAME.
WHOA!
JUDY, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THIS BUCKAROO'S
AN ESCAPED CONVICT!
I'M AWARE OF THAT,
BUT MY WORD,
WHAT A HANDSOME GUY!
OH, JUST LOOK AT HIS PICTURE.
LET'S SEE.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
HEY, SPUH...
UNH!
HEY, LISTEN.
CAN YOU TURN THAT THING OFF?
HEH HEH! CALM DOWN.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
DON'T WORRY.
THAT GUY PASSED OUT ON
THE BAR OVER THERE IS A COP.
YEAH? AND WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
ACTUALLY, THERE'S A BOUNTY
ON MY HEAD, TOO.
THIS PLACE IS A HIDEOUT
FOR ALL KINDS OF FUGITIVES.
THAT'S FASCINATING.
SO YOU CAN REST EASY.
NO WORRIES.
WHO? ME?
[GROANS]
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
I WANTED TO WORK OFF
ALL THIS FRUSTRATION,
BUT NO ONE'S COMING.
OH, YAY! YOU'RE ALL HERE.
MADAM, YOUR APPEARANCE
IS HARMFUL TO THE EYES.
OR ARE YOU TRYING
TO ENTICE US?
OOPS. YOU FOUND ME OUT.
JUST HOLD ON A MINUTE.
IF I DON'T PUT THESE ON, I JUST
MIGHT CHIP A NAIL, YOU KNOW.
HEE HEE!
OK, HERE WE GO.
[GRUNTING]
HURRY.
HUH?
MR. SAXOPHONE!
WHY DID YOU BRING ME HERE?
BECAUSE YOU SAID
YOU WERE A FAIRY.
WHY DID YOU COME WITH ME?
'CAUSE I'VE GOT
NO PLACE TO STAY.
OH. AND YOU TRUST ME
JUST LIKE THAT?
YOU SAID YOU WEREN'T
INTERESTED IN WOMEN.
I COULD TAKE YOUR MONEY
OR TRY TO KILL YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
DESPITE HOW I MAY LOOK,
I'M NOT SUCH EASY PREY.
HMM.
I'M AFRAID IT'S BROKEN.
YOU CAME TO SUCH A SLUMMY
NEIGHBORHOOD ALONE?
I AM ALONE.
I DON'T NEED ANY COMRADES.
THEY'RE NOT WORTH IT.
I END UP WORRYING
ABOUT THINGS I SHOULDN'T
YOU KNOW, ME BEING SUCH
A PRIZE AND ALL THAT.
ALL THE GUYS END UP
FIGHTING OVER ME LIKE DOGS.
THEY SAY HUMANS
ARE SOCIAL ANIMALS.
THEY CAN'T LIVE ALONE.
BUT YOU CAN LIVE
PRETTY WELL BY YOURSELF.
I TELL YOU,
INSTEAD OF FEELING
ALONE IN A GROUP,
IT'S BETTER TO HAVE
REAL SOLITUDE ALL BY YOURSELF.
WHEN I'M DEALING WITH THEM,
I SWEAR IT'S NOTHING
BUT TROUBLE.
AND I GET
NOTHING OUT OF IT,
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF I'M THERE OR NOT, RIGHT?
YOU WERE JUST AFRAID
THEY'D ABANDON YOU,
SO YOU ABANDON THEM.
[SCOFFS]
YOU DISTANCED YOURSELF
FROM THE WHOLE THING.
YOU'RE A STRANGE ONE,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU THINK SO?
I DON'T KNOW
WHY I'M TELLING YOU ALL THIS.
[SIGHS]
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN
A CONFESSION BOOTH.
YOU'RE NOT A PREACHER
BY ANY CHANCE, ARE YOU?
NO.
[SNEEZING]
UGH.
TAKE CARE, FAYE.
YOU WANT TO TAKE A SHOWER?
NO, THANKS.
COULD BE PEEPING TOMS
AROUND HERE.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE
NOT ONE OF THEM.
WELL, I CAN'T REALLY
GUARANTEE THAT, NOW.
HEH.
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
[WATER RUNNING]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
HUH?
[RINGING]
GREN, WHERE ARE YOU?
[GASPS]
VICIOUS!
I'M OUT WITH HIROTU,
ALONG WITH MANKIN
AND THE REVERSE DRAGON.
IT'S 32,000.
I'LL BE WAITING.
[CLICK]
ARE YOU SEEING JULIA
BEHIND MY BACK?
- SPIKE.
- LIN, YOU'VE GOTTEN PRETTY BIG.
HE DOESN'T WORK UNDER
YOU ANYMORE, SPIKE.
THINGS ARE DIFFERENT NOW.
LIKE YOU USING HER NAME
FOR YOUR SCUMMY DRUG DEALS?
I TRULY PITY HER FOR THAT.
IF THERE'S ANYONE WHO NEEDS
PITY HERE, IT'S YOU.
WE STILL HAVEN'T SETTLED
THE SCORE FROM LAST TIME.
- MAKE YOUR MOVE.
- HAH!
UNH...
[GRUNTING]
LIN, GET OUT OF THE WAY.
JULIA WAS HERE,
RIGHT IN THIS TOWN.
UGH!
STEP ASIDE, LIN.
LIN...
OH!
A WOMAN? WHICH ONE ARE YOU?!
I'M BOTH AT ONCE,
AND I'M NEITHER ONE.
OHH...
[THUD]
HMM.
HEY, HOW ARE
MEN AND WOMEN DIFFERENT?
HMM. I THINK WOMEN ARE HIDING
MORE VITAL SECRETS THAN MEN ARE.
UHHUH, BUT THERE ARE WOMEN
WHO AREN'T FEMININE.
AND MEN WHO AREN'T MASCULINE.
WHAT ABOUT THOSE WHO
AREN'T USUALLY FEMININE
BUT SHOW THAT SIDE OF THEMSELVES
IN SOME CHANCE CIRCUMSTANCE?
I LIKE THAT.
- REALLY?
- I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT YOU.
- WHO, THEN?
- MAYBE IT'S ME!
HA HA HA!
NEXT EPISODE,
JUPITER JAZZ" PART II.
MAYBE IT'S ME.