Irisviel.
Are you all right?
They waited for Kiritsugu to leave before attacking head-on.
That lightning, and this frontal assault...
The enemy is likely...
Rider.
Whoa!
Hey, Saber!
Rider?
I came because I wanted to see your castle.
It's kind of gloomy.
And what's with that armor?
You aren't wearing your fashionable suit tonight?
Rider, what are you doing here?
Can't you tell?
I've come to drink. What else?
Stop standing there, and show me around.
Surely you have a garden here suitable for a banquet.
Really, this castle is too dusty.
It is said only the most deserving are destined to hold the Holy Grail.
And the battle here, in Fuyuki City,
will determine who that person is, but...
If it's simply a means to decide,
then there's hardly cause for bloodshed.
If everyone can agree upon a ranking of the Heroic Spirits,
then the matter will settle itself.
Oh?
To start it off, you wish to compare ranks, Rider?
Indeed.
As a pretender to the title of king, you cannot refuse this opportunity.
You might consider this a Holy Grail Dialogue, rather than a Holy Grail War.
The matter of which among us is most suited to claim the Holy Grail
will clarify itself as we drink.
That is quite enough nonsense,
mongrels.
Archer, what is your business here?
Ah, I saw him in town,
so I figured I might as well invite him.
You're late, Golden Boy.
Well, I suppose it stands to reason. You travel by foot, unlike myself.
So you chose to hold a banquet of kings in this depressing place?
How will you recompense me for the rudeness of calling me here?
Knock it off.
Here, start with a drink.
What is this cheap swill?
You really thought we could discern a hierarchy of Heroic Spirits with this?
Is that how it is?
This was among the best I found at the city marketplace.
Only a wine novice would believe that.
You counterfeit.
Behold, and acknowledge your folly.
This is the drink of a king!
A fine treasure indeed.
Magnificent!
My treasury houses only the finest of drink and the finest of swords.
This alone should indicate which among us is the greatest of kings.
Archer.
Your finest drink is, indeed, worthy of the finest vessel.
Unfortunately, the Holy Grail is not a drinking cup.
First, we must hear what wish
you would have the Holy Grail grant.
You are not a ruler here, mongrel.
Already, you violate the rules
dictating that we must fight for the Holy Grail.
To begin with, the Holy Grail should already be mine.
All of this world's treasures, without exception,
trace their origin back to my treasure house.
Then you once held the Holy Grail?
You would know it by sight?
No.
Do not consider me as you would some lesser being.
The amount of wealth in my treasury
long ago surpassed even my own knowledge.
But that it is a treasure also means that it belongs to me.
And any who would take it for themselves
is naught but a thief.
Your words are no different than Caster's insane rants.
It appears he isn't the only Servant to have gone mad.
Come, let's not go that far...
I believe I've got a clue to what his real name is.
But, Archer,
you surely have no true interest in the Holy Grail itself, do you?
Of course not.
But I must administer my judgement
to those who would steal treasure from me.
It's a matter of principle.
Huh.
So then, Archer...
Of what manner of duty and rules do you speak?
Of the law.
The law I set down as king.
You break the law, and I punish you.
There is no place for discussion.
Which means
that we will have to resort to combat.
King of Conquest...
You agreed that the Holy Grail's rightful ownership lies with another,
so will you take it by force?
What makes the Holy Grail so important to you?
I wish for true incarnation.
Huh?
Hey, wasn't your goal supposed to be world conquest—
Idiot.
Even if magic lends us form in this world,
ultimately, we remain Servants.
I wish for rebirth, as a human,
to live within the world in which I've arrived.
And with nothing but my body, I shall defy both heaven and earth.
That is the meaning of conquest.
Thus it begins, then proceeds,
and is finished.
Such is the path of my conquest.
That is hardly fitting of how a king should behave.
Then let us hear what you would say.
I wish for my homeland's salvation.
With the omnipotent wish-granting device,
I shall avert Britain's fate of destruction.
Hey, King of Knights.
Did you just say that you would change fate?
Does that mean you wish to change the past?
Indeed.
Even if it is a wish that a miracle alone cannot fulfill,
if the Holy Grail is truly omnipotent, it will...
Um, Saber...
Surely you do not mean
that you would erase the marks you have left on history?
Indeed!
Why should that bother you? Why do you laugh?
The country that gave me my blade, to which I offered my life, was destroyed.
Why would it be strange for me to find that sad?
Did you hear that, Rider?
What that little girl, who names herself King of Knights, said?
"To which I offered my life..."
Why is that humorous?!
To ensure their country's prosperity, a king should make any sacrifice.
No.
The king does not make offerings.
The nation and the people, offer themselves to the king.
Not the reverse.
What?
Those are a tyrant's words!
Just so.
We are heroes because we are tyrants.
However, Saber,
if a king regrets their rule or its conclusion,
that king is nothing but a fool.
Even worse than a tyrant.
Iskandar, your reign ended with your heirs slain,
and your empire dissolved into three parts.
You have no regrets about that end?
None.
Not if it came to pass
by my judgement and my retainers' sacrifices...
Its destruction was inevitable.
I shall grieve. And I shall weep.
But I shall never regret.
You...
Let alone undo it!
Such an act
would be a mockery of all who fought with me!
Only warriors can find glory in destruction!
Of what worth is a king who fails to protect the powerless?
A just rule, with just laws...
Those are the true duties of a king!
So you, the king, are a slave to what is right?
That is acceptable.
A king is a martyr to their ideals.
That is not how a person should live.
If I rule the nation as king, I cannot ask to live as a person.
King of Conquerors,
you seek the Holy Grail merely for your own benefit.
You could never understand...
You who became a ruler only to satisfy your endless greed.
A king without greed is even worse than a figurehead!
Saber.
You said you would become a martyr for your ideals.
In life, you must have been a pure saint.
A proud and noble figure, certainly.
But who can truly admire the martyr's thorny path?
Who dreams of such an ending?
A king...
The king must be greedier than any other.
He must laugh louder and rage harder.
He must exemplify the extreme of all things, good and evil.
That is why his retainers envy and adore him.
And why the flames of aspiration, to be as the king is,
can burn within his people.
Proud king of chivalry...
The righteousness and ideals you bore
may indeed have saved your nation once.
However,
I'm certain you know what became
of those who were saved, but left to themselves.
What?
You saved them,
but you never led them.
You never showed them what a king should be.
You abandoned your men when they lost their way.
Then, alone and untroubled,
you followed your own petty little ideals.
Thus, you are no true king.
You are only a little girl,
enraptured by a false idol of the king who serves others,
but not themselves.
I...
Assassin?
Is this your doing, Golden Boy?
Tokiomi humiliates himself.
This isn't fair! Why are there so many Assassins?
We are the one, become many.
A Servant who is many and also one.
A Servant who is one, but with many...
shadows.
A Servant with multiple personalities
that hosts each one into a separate body?
R-Rider, um...
Calm yourself, boy.
Even those rude enough to interrupt our banquet
may yet show us which is the greatest king.
So you'll invite them to your banquet as well, King of Conquerors?
Of course.
The king's words are for all to hear.
If they have come to listen,
it matters not if they are friend or foe.
Now, don't hold back!
Any who would speak with us, come forth and take a cup.
This drink is as your blood!
Very well.
As I said, this drink is as your blood.
If you insist on spilling it...
So be it.
Saber! Archer!
Here is our banquet's final question.
Must the king be alone?
The king must indeed be alone!
No, you don't understand at all.
I suppose I'll have to show you
exactly what a real king is.
This is...
A Reality Marble?
That's impossible.
A mental image materialized into the real world?
Here, my armies once rode across the land.
The place all the heroes who stood with me,
through joy and sorrow, will never forget.
I can make this world real
because it still exists within our hearts!
Behold my endless armies!
Their bodies destroyed, and their souls offered to the world as Heroic Spirits.
And still, these legendary heroes pledge their loyalty to me!
My bond with them is my greatest treasure,
my path of kingship!
The ultimate Noble Phantasm that I, Iskandar, possess.
Ionian Hetairoi!
Each of these is a Servant!
It has been a long time, partner.
A king
must live a grander life than any other's,
and stoke his people's feelings of admiration!
Yes!
He who is worthy of all heroes' envy,
and he who leads their way, is king!
Therefore,
the king is not alone.
For his will
equals that of all his followers together!
Yes!
Now, then...
Shall we begin, Assassin?
As you can see, what we have created here is a plain.
Unfortunately, with our superior numbers, we hold the advantage.
Annihilate them!
That ending wasn't as much fun as I'd hoped for.
We have said all there is to say.
I suppose that will do for today.
Wait, Rider. I still...
You, keep silent.
Tonight was for the kings to converse.
But I no longer recognize you as a king, Saber.
Little girl, wake up from your sad dream.
If you don't, you'll someday lose even that modicum of pride
you retain as a Heroic Spirit.
The dream of a king you spoke of is a curse.
What?
You needn't listen to him, Saber.
You are correct.
Follow the path you believe in.
Your pain and trouble...
You bear a burden of kingship; too heavy a weight for any.
It is splendid to gaze upon.
Keep at it, O King of Knights.
It is possible
you may prove worthy of still more of my love.
Saber...
I remember.
There was once a knight who left Camelot,
claiming that King Arthur didn't understand how others felt.
Perhaps
those thoughts were shared
by everyone at the Round Table.
Episode 11
The Grail Dialogue
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
This begins the second stage.
I'm not a normal human.
It is not that simple!
Follow what you seek.
The path is now open to you.
But that is an evil that must be punished!
Next time:
The Grail's Invitation