My, your journey's proven to be quite a long one.
Will you be able to resolve your ordeal in time?
There isn't much time left.
Will you be able to reach out to the truth?
You could call this the moment of truth.
Hide and seek it wants to play again
Like a detective, I won't let it get away
It's constantly costuming with loads of fake
I will strip search if I have to
Though I'm not afraid to know it, don't know how
I am so determined
To chase after what's hidden and seize this day, this moment
WANNA KNOW
Enter key to accelerate
WANNA GO
Ignition turned on
It's about that time to drive to truth
WANNA SEIZE
Stranger than in movies
Ignorance is not bliss
They say that truth will out
Can't keep on hiding
There's no turning back now
I'm gonna go on
I'm gonna go get what I want
I'll take you to a place...
where you can be at peace.
I did the best I could to look into it,
but there's nothing that would indicate the sender's identity.
I see.
Thanks anyway.
Since he personally left it in your mailbox,
it's highly likely that the culprit is closer to us than we think.
We should probably look for clues around that area.
Wow, you're like a regular Sherlock Holmes.
Naoto, you're like a totally different person when you talk about the case.
Huh? Y-You think so?
Who cares?! That's not what's important!
A dangerous criminal found out where he lives.
Who knows what'll happen if we don't do something?!
You're right.
I'm really worried.
Worried?
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
Be careful, Yu.
Give us a call if anything happens.
Yeah, I know.
I may be looking at this differently than everyone else.
What do you mean?
Tatsumi was right earlier.
Considering the situation, I should be concerned for your safety first and foremost.
But I...
I probably have no right to be your friend.
Not when I hold solving the case as my top priority.
That's not true.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, Big Bro!
Welcome home.
Now for our next story.
There's been much conjecture on the origin of the fog,
and some are concerned about its effects on the human body.
Have you lost your appetite?
In response, Mr. Kozai of the Environmental Concern Society
Uh-uh. I'm okay.
Investigation Held to Identify the "Mysterious Fog" in Inaba
visited a local elementary school to investigate the effects of the fog.
Oh, he came to my school!
Is that right?
What are the facts? An interview with Mr. Kozai of the Environmental Concern Society
Today, I spoke with a young student who spoke her own mind,
free from the influence of those around her.
It was an attitude and example that we as adults can learn from.
My head hurts.
You're burning up!
It's because it was cold today.
Yeah. I hate the cold.
It'll be spring soon enough!
Then it'll warm right up.
But aren't you leaving in the spring?
That's right...
I'm going to make snowmen with you when it snows!
Yeah! Let's make a big one.
Promise?
Promise!
Okay!
Let's play a lot!
Yeah, let's play a whole lot!
Who is that?
It's impossible to tell who it was based off that.
Be sure to watch the Midnight Channel tonight.
Yeah, of course.
Something up?
Actually, Big Bro...
Are you okay?
It looks like your fever's gone.
But it's still cold out,
so you should go to bed early tonight.
Aww! But I wanna watch TV!
I feel fine.
You need to hurry and get better.
Oh, yeah!
Oh. So you have a space heater!
Daddy said we could use it if we got cold.
Huh?
What gives?
Is it broken?
Sure looks like it.
Let's go buy a new one later.
Really?
Can we get it at Junes?
Of course.
We can get Yosuke to cut us a deal.
Yay, I love Junes!
Oh, Daddy's back!
Welcome ho—
This was in the mailbox.
It's for you.
Oh, thanks.
To: Narukami Yu
if you dont stop
this time someone
close will be put
in and killed
I'd like to hear what this is all about.
I see. So you don't want to discuss this here, huh?
We're heading out.
Daddy! Big Bro...
It's okay. We're just going out to talk.
We'll be back soon.
Okay. I'll be waiting.
Yu, I think of you as a member of the family.
That's precisely why I should've done this sooner.
Uncle...
You're going to tell me everything.
From what you're involved in to how you got involved. Everything!
I also think of you as family.
So...
I'll tell you the truth.
About everything.
Good.
We've...
been involved in the serial murder case.
We rescue the people who get kidnapped...
by going inside the TV.
Inside the TV?
There are enemies called "Shadows," which we fight using Personas—
It hasn't been long enough for you to trust me like your old man,
but I hoped you'd open up to me a little.
It's a shame.
Uncle, please believe me!
Send this to the lab.
Uh, okay.
Uncle!
Stay here for the night.
Come on now.
Dojima's just worried about you!
That was probably just tough love.
Well, I'll be just outside this room.
Call if you need anything, okay?
Geez, why do I have to pitch in with stock duty?
The 8 o'clock clearance sale has begun.
It's because I'm not working hard enough! There's no getting around it!
I really shouldn't have gotten this for you.
Gotten what?
Here you go.
Hang onto it, okay?
It's your own cell. We'd get worried if we couldn't reach you.
Th-Thank you, Yosuke!
You use it by... Scrap that.
I'll just show you how I use mine.
At Junes, every day is Customer Appreciation Day!
I guess I'll give Yu a call.
Every day's great at your Junes!
I'll try his home phone.
Hello?
Oh, Nanako? Is Yu around?
Nana?!
If it's Nana, give the phone to me!
He's not home. He got a weird letter.
Daddy got mad when he saw it and took him to the police station.
The police station?
Gimme the phone! Gimme the phone!
Someone's at the door. I gotta go.
Nana, it's your bear-y good friend Teddie!
Okay, sorry to bother you. See ya later.
Lemme talk!
Ah! You hung up!
A letter? It couldn't be...
Nanako?!
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
How could it be her?!
She hasn't been on TV!
No, she was on TV.
Nanako wasn't seen, but she was heard.
Huh? What do you mean?
Do you remember the politician who visited a local school
and made the news several times?
In those interviews,
he always quoted a particular student he spoke with.
Oh yeah, I remember watching that.
The child became well-known,
while remaining anonymous.
That girl was Nanako!
No way!
A reporter who took interest in this
released her photo and interview using her real name in today's evening paper.
But even before that, this is a small rural town.
Her identity must've been circulating for quite some time.
Dammit!
I should've realized it much sooner!
But I was so hung up on the idea of people who were "shown" on TV.
Wh-What are we gonna do? Nanako's home alone right now, isn't she?
I'm on my way there as we speak to check on her!
Please let me out, Uncle!
Aren't you there?!
Adachi, open the door!
Fuck!
Nanako... Nanako's in danger!
H-Hey! You can't!
You can't open that door!
Fuck off!
Rawr!
We have to talk to Yu!
Hey, stop right there!
Yu!
Yosuke?!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
Nanako...
Nanako's missing!
What do you mean?!
It's Shirogane.
Shirogane, you there? What the hell's going on?!
I was just at your house.
The front door was open, and there was no one inside.
I'm afraid that Nanako's been kidnapped by the serial killer.
Dojima, surely you must've known.
The case isn't over yet!
The number you have dialed is unavailable right now.
If you'd like, you may leave a mess—
Dammit!
Why?! Why Nanako?!
Uncle...
H-Hey! Where are you going?
I'm gonna go look for my daughter!
But do you even have any ideas or leads on who took her?!
I'll make a checkpoint by the highway.
Th-That won't help.
Shut up!
I'm going too!
No!
W-Wait!
Let go of me!
You know I can't let you go! Yu, be reasonable!
Shut your fuckin' mouth!
Open the door!
Nana's in a bear-y dangerous situation!
We gotta go save her!
Nana's in danger!
What'll you do if something happens to her?!
You gonna take responsibility if something happens to Nanako?!
I'm going to call back-up!
Narukami!
They're multiplying!
Naoto?
Oh no, did they lock you in there?
Adachi, please release him and the others!
No, you know I can't do—
Move aside, Naoto!
I know how you feel,
but if you don't tell me what's going on,
there's really nothing I can do.
Ah, so you agree to release them once we explain the situation?
N-No, that's not what I meant.
Naoto, we don't have time for that!
Please calm down.
Let's all take a moment to stop and sort out the situation.
Perhaps this will help Adachi understand as well.
But...
Narukami,
if we run out blindly, we'll have no idea where to begin.
There's no doubt in my mind that this is a kidnapping by the same culprit who was behind the others.
Now, consider that the front door at Nanako's house was open.
I examined it and found no trace that entry had been forced.
You mean Nanako opened the door herself?
The culprit didn't sneak in. He boldly came up to the front door and rung the doorbell.
Like how it was for all of us.
Um... "For all of us"?
But the circumstances are different for her compared to us.
Remember what Nanako said when we were at the hot springs?
"I always do what my dad tells me, like not opening the door for strangers!"
So is the killer someone Nanako knows?
Huh? What? How'd you figure that out?
It feels like we're closing in on who it is.
But we need more info.
Then let us change our perspective slightly.
His quick work is what stood out to me when he caught me.
You said he threw you in immediately after being kidnapped.
I would go as far as to say that it took place in front of their houses.
Meaning he had a TV out front.
The culprit is taking a TV with him?
Precisely.
In other words, it's highly likely that he drives to the scene of the crime.
And it would take a car large enough to hold a fairly big TV.
A large car...
However, no unusual vehicles have been sighted.
I'd expect someone to notice since most of the victims vanished during the day.
So it's someone Nanako knows who has a car.
But it's a car that can't be seen?
No, it's one you wouldn't notice even if you saw it.
A delivery truck.
Now I remember!
A delivery came! It was a delivery truck!
No one looks twice at a delivery truck, no matter where it's parked.
If it were a local company, it'd be the same deliveryman every time.
So that explains it!
Adachi, is there anyone who fits this profile?
Huh? I don't really know.
Maybe you're not too far off base.
Dojima put this stuff together to reinvestigate the first case,
and one of the suspects for Ms. Yamano's murder was a deliveryman.
I think he was a city council secretary before becoming a deliveryman.
A secretary? That's Namatame Taro.
The guy who had the affair with Ms. Yamano?
Adachi!
Wh-What?
If there's been a break in the case, I'd better hurry to the scene.
I'll just have to hope nothing happens here while I'm gone.
Thank you.
Hang in there, Nanako!
Dojima, where are you?!
On a road by the highway! If this isn't urgent—
The perp! I know who the culprit is!
It's just as you suspected!
It's the deliveryman!
It's Namatame!
Namatame Taro!
Let's leave Namatame's car to Dojima and Adachi for now.
Take us to Junes!
Nanako...
He's headed for the highway via the shopping district's main street!
I'm not letting you get away!
Dojima!
Stop the car!
Dojima, hang in there!
Uncle!
Wh-Where's Nanako?
Hello? We need an ambulance, quickly!
What the hell's going on?
Where's Nanako?
And Namatame?
Please find them.
You got it!
You can't! We have to preserve the crime scene!
Then leave that to me.
Hanamura, pay him!
Dude! I swear, I'm not your sugar daddy!
The door's open.
He's gone!
I found this.
Look!
There really is a TV in there!
Narukami?!
Wait, Master!
I have to go rescue Nanako!
What if you end up somewhere dangerous?
I have to try!
Stop it! If we fail, who's going to save Nanako?
This diary...
They're doing their own thing again...
It probably belonged to Namatame.
"I discovered the existence of a new world."
"Thus, I must save people."
"Save"?
The hell's he mean by that?
This...
Yamano Mayumi
Staying at the Amagi Inn
Konishi Saki
Konishi liquors, Inaba
Central Shopping Destrict
Amagi Yukiko
Lives at the Amagi Inn
Kujikawa Rise
Marukyu Tofu, Inaba Central Shopping District
Tatsumi Kanji
Tatsumi Textiles, Inaba Central Shopping District
It's a list of the victims' home addresses!
Yamano Mayumi, Konishi Saki,
Amagi Yukiko, Tatsumi Kanji, Kujikawa Rise...
Even the victims who survived and were never released to the public are written here!
I note that Mr. Morooka's address is absent from the list.
Wow... Then that settles it.
The last date is today's.
"I can't believe such a small child appeared on it."
"I must save this child, no matter what."
Is that... about Nanako?!
Dear Big Bro
Congratulations on getting
the highest test score!
Nanako
Dear Big Bro
Congratulations on getting
the highest test score!
Yu!
It's your uncle.
Uncle!
Y-Yu...
Nanako...
She's my reason for living.
You can save her, right?
Please...
Please save her for me.
I will save her!
I look at the rustic scenery
along the path to school
we walked together
Campus in spring,
the summer festival
These were the days we spent
shoulder-to-shoulder
laughing together
From past to present
I've always
looked back on these
carefree days
From today to tomorrow
We move forward while treasuring the bonds we've made
You'll be okay now.
Now I shall...
You're just killing people!
We just have to believe in them.
Please, get out of the way!
I'm a savior!
Big Bro...
Stop it. Stop it!