What is with this rain?!
It was bright and sunny just a minute ago!
Oh, well. We'll just have to wait out the rain.
Yeah.
They say "a good and beautiful woman
is unconcerned by rain."
Oh, what are you talking about, Koume?
Koume!
It feels really good!
What about her?
She's a good and beautiful... puppy?
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
Kanaetai yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora hikari ga mieru docchi? Acchi!
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Docchi ni ikou? Nayande kimaranai
Yume no michi wa itsumo kyodai meiro
Migi ka? Hidari ka?
Seikai wa docchi? (Docchi?)
Docchi o erandemo
Nakama to ireba tanoshii kara
Daiseikai!
Kanaeta yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora mirai ga mieru issho ni arukidasou
Hora egao ga mieru docchi? (Kocchi!)
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
This house is pretty old!
It's kinda creepy.
Like a ghost's gonna come out any second.
A ghost?!
D-don't say that kind of scary stuff!
No, but seriously, don't you hear it?
There's a weird sound mixed in with the rain.
S-sorry, I was sneezing!
D-don't freak us out like that!
We sure are unlucky to get
caught out in a sudden downpour.
Yes. Everything we did
during our lunch break was for nothing.
Come to think of it, I broke a teacup this morning.
Maybe it's just an unlucky day.
You know, my mirror cracked this morning, too.
A-and the strap on my sandal broke today!
I thought that could be a sign of bad luck.
What about, Chiya?
It tickles!
No, don't nibble at me!
By her current situation,
I'd say bad luck is drawn to her.
No, don't nibble at me!
A bad omen?
Yeah. We learned about it in class before, remember?
BAD OMEN
GOOD OMEN
A good omen is a sign that good things will happen,
and a bad omen is a sign that bad things will happen.
For example, when your tea stalks
stand up straight, that's a good omen.
But if you see a black cat on the road,
that's a bad omen.
BAD OMEN
GOOD OMEN
The little things in our day-to-day lives
can tell us what the future will be.
Okay! Then what's this?
BAD OMEN
GOOD OMEN
Superstition says seeing a spider
in the morning is a good omen.
A good omen, huh?
Now that I know something good will happen,
I'm getting really excited!
Even though it looks like
a horrible thing is happening right now.
But what if it's the opposite?
The opposite?
A bad omen.
If you know something bad is going to happen,
what should you do?
BAD OMEN
GOOD OMEN
Well, you...
My, it's already that time.
I'll have that be your homework for next week.
Aww, we have to wait?
Ugh, I'm gonna think about it all day!
That's right! She didn't teach us
the one crucial thing: how to deal with it!
True. And it's strange for lots of bad omens
to appear all in one day.
It must mean that something horrible
is going to happen.
O-oh no!
Wow!
Chiya, were you even listening?!
The kitties are so warm!
What kind of horrible thing is going to happen, then?
Maybe this storm is only the beginning,
and even more bad things are going to happen?
Maybe the g-ghosts that live here
will curse us until our dying day!
If we don't get out of here soon,
we won't make it home for dinner.
No! Not that!
That'd be the worst thing that could happen to us!
I got it!
It's storming outside, and four people are
stuck inside an old, creepy house...
That means...
A sudden serial murder case is about to open.
These bad omens point to death.
One by one, they die.
The poor, pitiful girls.
What, however, is the truth behind this incident?!
The murderer is in this room!
Wait, that only leaves me.
A fox spirit! So this was your doing!
I'll eat you, too!
I won't let you!
Chiyataro!
Note: Parody of the fable of Kintaro the Golden Boy.
Whoa there, whoa! Whoa there, whoa!
Why am I the bear?
So what do you think?
Wouldn't that be the worst thing ever?
Who are you calling a fox spirit?
And what kind of story was that?
That scared me!
Now we're getting thunder...
Wait, where's Nono?
Where'd she go?
I found Nono!
Nooo!
Ch-Chiya?!
I-I-I can't stand thunder!
I know it's childish, but I'm really scared of it!
O-oh.
I'm glad you're asking me for help, Nono.
That doesn't happen often. Usually she's stuck to Chiya.
W-well, that's because...
...I didn't bring Matsuko-san with me today.
And you look a little bit like Matsuko-san, Kon-chan.
I dunno how happy I am to hear that.
Anyway, don't cry, Nono.
Kon-chan...!
Leave it all to me.
I've only read about this in a book,
so I don't know if it'll work,
but I'll give it a shot!
What're you going to do?
An ancient ritual to stop the rain.
It's called...
the Rainstopping Dance!
Hyaaa!
Hmblaaa!
Hngraaar!
Forget about stopping it... I think it just got worse!
You tried your best, Kon-chan!
Y-yeah, I'm sure the gods are...
They're mad!
Come on, you two, get it together!
Is this what it feels like to have little sisters?
This "big sister" thing isn't half bad!
Look, look, Koume!
I've got another sister who's the biggest handful!
Chiya
Banner?!
Jeez, you're soaking wet again.
How are you having so much fun with this, Chiya?
We're in a horrible emergency situation here.
Huh? It's not horrible at all!
What?
It's the first time I've waited out the rain in a new place!
It's like an adventure and it's exciting!
If I were alone it might be a little gloomier...
...but it's really fun when we're together!
Isn't that weird?
Now that you mention it, we've been looking for
bad things that haven't even happened yet.
Seeing bad omens makes us
start looking for bad things.
But that's just a trap!
In the end, you're the one who decides
if something is good or bad.
Guess we figured out the homework!
Koume!
You're really warm when you're so close!
It's okay, Nono!
Huh?
Um, what are you...
It's our final form to help you deal with the thunder!
You'll be fine now, right?
Koume-chan...
Oh, there's a flash! Here it comes!
That one was close!
Lightning is quite pretty.
I've never looked at it so closely before!
I-I wasn't scared, either.
It's weird, but watching it with you
makes it feel like fireworks.
What's "fireworks"?
Oh, right. You haven't seen fireworks before, have you?
So... fireworks are these big circles of fire
that spread out all through the night sky!
They sound way scarier than thunder!
K..Koume-chan!
It stopped raining!
Come out, everyone!
Okay, let's go home!
Yeah!
Alright, when summer comes,
let's all go to a fireworks festival together!
Yeah!
Yay! Fireworks, fireworks!
Can we go see fireworks tomorrow?
Like I said, only when summer comes!
Aww, I can't wait that long!
Oh, Chiya-chan!
Meilomancy is one kind of physiological divining,
and it can be used to discern the subject's personality
and future by the arrangement and shape of their moles.
Now, I had you memorize all the meanings
behind the locations of moles for the test,
but from these results,
some of you will have to retake it.
By the way, Kon-chan got a perfect score.
A perfect score?!
That's amazing, Kon-chan!
W-well, of course I'd do well on this...
I'm an apprentice, and I don't want
to bring shame to the Urara name...
You studied all night for it.
Did you fail too, Nono?
Weren't you up late studying hard, too?
Kon-chan, some people can't remember things
even if they study very hard.
H-her face looks like Matsuko-san's!
It's always been like this.
My Big Sister's a star student who can do anything,
but I'm not good at anything.
Calm down, Nono, you've got talent!
Matsuko-san!
I think that ventriloquism of yours sure is a talent.
Alright, then, you three will study for the retake.
Today's lesson will be a self-study period.
Awwwwww!
Moles
You can do it! I'll help.
Thanks, Kon-chan.
Do you want to study with me, Nono?
No, that's okay.
I'll study by myself.
I'll study by myself... I'll study by myself...
Huh? Oh... okay?
Now even Nina-sensei's looking like Matsuko-san!
THREE
SISTERS
One Day,
One Fortune
A mole on the right cheek means they're methodical.
A mole on the lower left shoulder means...
Ugh, I can't remember all this!
How are you supposed to tell someone's personality
from where their moles are?
There are a lot of different theories.
Long ago, moles were written with the characters
for "mother" and "black", and called "mother's marks."
Do they have something to do with your mom?
One theory says that when a baby is born,
her mother leaves marks on her in a way that writes
the kind of personality she wishes for her child.
Huh, that's really nice!
Like symbols of a mother's love!
Another theory says they form
from waste particles in the mother's womb.
Her love is garbage!
Nono has a mole right by her eye.
Let's see, a mole under the right eye means...
"A devilish woman who is popular with the guys."
A devilish woman?!
Huh?
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
I think a mole by the eye definitely feels a little sexy.
DEVILISH
NONO
I bet you'll be a Madonna who makes
all the men cry when you get older.
Huh? No!
I don't really know where my moles are.
I don't, either.
Okay, then I'll look them up and see what they mean!
It'll be a good way to study, too.
Let's start with Kon!
Huh? But it's kind of embarrassing!
What're you talking about?
The only way we learn is by practicing, right?
And you just said you'd help us study.
Guess I have to.
Th-this is to help with your test, okay?
Wow, your tummy's so smooth!
And your skin's so white!
It'll be easy to find your moles.
Alright now, lie down here.
O-okay.
D-don't look so long, make it quick!
Oh, I found one here!
There's one here, too!
One's here too!
What about over here?
Huh? Chiya-chan...
Hey, Kon, if you keep getting red,
it'll be harder for us to find them!
B-but...
Oh! That pose!
Rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub!
Hey, Chiya! Stop!
That tickles! Chiya!
Rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub!
Stop!
What're you doing, Chiya?!
You can't touch people THERE!
I hadn't seen your tummy so close before!
Ever since the day we met,
I decided I'd pet it someday!
You're not making any sense, you crazy feral girl!
Ow!
Jeez, Chiya! Forget about her tummy, look for moles!
You're going to fail the test again if you keep this up.
Okay.
Okay then, let's see...
On the back of the knee...
Huh?
S-sorry, I made a weird sound.
Um, uh...
Wh-why don't we stop things here?
Y-yeah!
Hey, Kon, you have two moles
right next to each other on the back of your neck.
Really?
Moles on the neck mean the person
is serious and responsible,
and a little stubborn, too.
Wow, that's so true!
Wait, you two.
These two moles have a deeper,
even more terrifying meaning.
A terrifying meaning?
LONDON MONTHLY
Look at this!
They look like the bite marks
of the ancient vampire Count Dracula!
That means you're a vampire, too!
I WILL bite you.
Come on, you three!
Do you even want to have a serious study session?!
Kon got mad!
You... you even made me do something
really embarrassing!
Not only will I never be the perfect bride,
but being looked at makes me so embarrassed
I can't even go to the public baths!
You're making a big deal out of it.
And WHOSE fault is that?!
I'm through with you, Koume!
Hey, you're gonna be way more embarrassed
if you leave like that!
You two study!
You're gonna get arrested!
Okay, Chiya-chan, let's do
what Kon-chan said and study hard!
Yeah!
Nina!
Oh, Saku, out on patrol?
Yeah. Don't you have class?
Well, things got a little complicated.
Should I stop in for a moment?
Yes, Ma'am!
It's our pleasure!
We'll accompany you!
I'll be right back.
Keep an eye on things while I'm away.
Yes, Ma'am!
So indifferent!
But I love that about her, too!
Nono, you're really fired up today!
Y-yeah, is that weird?
No, you're a lot more reliable today.
You're like Nina-sensei!
O-oh, please. I'm not like my sister.
Please...
Nono, that tickles!
There's a mole on your back, Chiya-chan.
Huh? I didn't know that!
A mole on the shoulder blade means
you're bold and proactive in everything you do.
That matches you perfectly, Chiya-chan!
You think so?
You're so lucky.
Huh?
U-um, my big sister has a mole on her back, too,
in the same place you do, Chiya-chan.
I guess that's why my Big Sister's always
been bright and happy and popular with everyone.
I've always hidden behind her back.
Big Sis, where are you? Big Sis?
Big Sis...
I'm right here.
B-Big Sis!
My, you sure cry easily, Nono.
But it's alright.
No matter what happens,
your big sister Nina will protect you.
Really?
Really. So don't cry anymore, okay?
Look, your charming mole is going to be washed away.
Huh... your sister is really nice!
Isn't she?
But lately, I've been feeling more and more
that I can't go on like this.
I want to change, just a little.
After meeting all of you
and spending every day with you,
I thought how amazing you are,
even though you're the same age as me.
I told myself I had to get it together.
That's why I wanted to study for this test
without relying on anyone else today.
Hey, Chiya-chan?!
Hey...!
Wh-wh-why are you undressing me?!
I got a good idea!
C'mon, turn around!
Wha-?!
Today was the first day Nono didn't rely on my help.
So your sister's finally stepping away from you, Nina.
Don't laugh, Saku!
It's just a little... no, it's very sad.
Because Nono was always behind me,
I could look forward.
Don't touch it until it's dry!
B-but...
Well, might as well draw a bunch of them!
That tickles!
Nono!
Chiya-chan?
Nono, when we first met you,
you were hiding behind Nina-sensei's back,
and we didn't notice you at all.
I'm really glad I get to talk with you a lot now,
like we did today!
If you wanna change, Nono,
then I'll make a little spell
so you can become the Nono you wanna be.
I get it!
If you don't have moles, you can just draw them on.
It's simple, but it's a nice little spell!
Right?
Maybe I'll do a little spell, too.
I wonder if there are any moles
that would make me an unrivaled beauty!
That would go on the right buttock.
Okay, show us your butt, Koume!
Nooo, Kon!
I'll draw it on you as thanks for what you did earlier!
I'll draw one, too!
M-me too!
You girls! Could you be a little quiete-
One Day
One Fortune
C-Captain Saku!
I can't tell if Captain Saku is an adult or a child.
Let's draw a moustache on her!
Y-you girls!
You're dressed like harlots again!
We're sorry!
Magari kado turn shitara yume ni tadori tsukeru kana
Mayoi mayotte mawari mawatte
Fuwari deaetara suteki
Ichi kara juu made nattenai hi mo aru
Nee dochira e susumeba happy end?
Migi kara hidari e suki kara daisuki e
Otto koi ni koishite atafuta
Akogareru no nukedasenai
Watashi wa sagashiteimasu
Anata o sagashiteimasu
Mada minu sugata ni tokimeku kuusou Kiss me
Deai gashira de shoutotsu
Chotto kojirete unmei
Moshika moshikashite anata mo mayotteru no
Goal wa mienai
Romance de hajimaru meiro
Mitsukete kuremasu ka?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Brides and Gods Sometimes Sneeze"!
To see what kind of episode it'll be...
Kon!
...Arinsu Café has a new
limited-time-only seasonal parfait!
"Brides and Gods Sometimes Sneeze"
W-we'll divine what it is later! Bye!