Seconds!
Got it!
Eh! It's not supposed to be like this!
Huh?
Why did you end up eating breakfast at our house?
Also, why did you accept this so easily?
No reason.
Since Taiga-chan is small, she doesn't take up much space.
Furthermore,
It's more delicious when we all eat together.
Hurry up and hand it over.
Wha?!
I've already cooked 3 pots... how much more are you gonna eat?!
S-sowwiie...
Good grief.
Are you trying to make your pet braver by stressing it?
Stop making it uglier.
Don't say ugly!
But it's true that, "a pet takes after its master."
Why you...
This ungrateful girl!
Treating me like this even though I made your breakfast, dinner, and even lunch!
You sure are annoying, you half-breed.
Half... again, you!
Give me back my lunch! Give me back my good will!
Shut up and rot.
W... wait up, Aisaka!
Since that midnight attack,
Aisaka Taiga has been appearing in front of my dining table more.
I told you to wait!
And then...
Apart from this, you'll do it properly when we get to school, right?
About Kitamura and me, you will properly...
Match us right?
You promised that you would do anything for me like a dog!
It turned out like this.
If you don't do a satisfactory job...
Minori!
You're slow, Taiga!
Great! You have plenty of spirit today too!
Good morning, Minori!
Eh?! No way?! What?!
S-sorry! I didn't know!
I never knew that Taiga and Takasu were "coming in pairs" to school!
That's not it!
No one uses "coming in pairs" these days.
That's not the problem!
Really? Then it's that... right now...
I'm too surprised to think of a better way to say it!
Oh I know, a "couple!"
That's why I said this isn't a big deal!
I only met Aisaka by coincidence.
Right, Aisaka?
What? So it was only a coincidence?
It seems that we live close by.
Really?
Er, erm...
Catch you later, Takasu-kun!
About yesterday's TV program...
So it's like this.
In order for me to go out with Kushieda, I must first let Aisaka and Kitamura...
Just what I had in mind.
Alright! Warm-ups complete!
Next, practice passin-
Hey, Aisaka! Let's team up!
Yes, yes! Let's pair up, Takasu-kun!
Ok!
...-in pairs!
What? Takasu and Aisaka, you two sure have spirit.
Taiga?
The battle plan is simple.
I'll throw the ball lightly at Kitamura's partner.
Next...
You'll exaggerate the situation and take him to the infirmary.
Then the remaining pair, Kitamura and Aisaka will pair up.
Maruo~ Pair up with me!
Fine with me.
However, don't call me that.
But you look so alike!
Eh?
Oi, Kitamura is with a strange women!
What's with this?
Thigh punch...
Kushieda!
Do you want to practice with me?
Ok, lets do it!
Kushieda too...
Nevermind, continue with the operation.
But you...
Gender equality.
And then, the bulging of the elbow muscles...
You, what's up?
Throwing it without using fingers...
It didn't reach, Kushieda.
Hmm, it seems there's a hard path ahead in learning the Satoru-ball.
(TL note: A very slow pass invented by a character called Satoru in a manga called "Dokaben")
Don't worry, as long as someone who understands that exists, it's fine.
Notou, that bastard...
Hey! Pass!
Hey hey hey! Pass pass pass.
I'm passing, Maruo!
Ok!
You have a good feel for this.
What are you saying, Maruo?
No, for a girl, that was a good pass...
Hey, Pass!
What pass...
After all, against a girl...
Pass!!!
Sorry, Kihara... I'll atone for my sins.
Replicate...
Sorry, Maruo...
What happened?
Takasu did away with the palmtop tiger.
C-crap!
The palmtop tiger that bites anyone.
But it's true that she tries her best, even if it's embarrassing.
It's not like I don't want to cheer her on.
Listen up.  No matter what happens, deliver it like it is nothing.
Don't be rash.
I-I understand.
Take it easy, right?
Be modest... informal... fickle...
Let's go.
Huh? Where's Kitamura?
Ah, Kitamura seemed to have some business at B-block.
Takasu!
He just left, so he couldn't have gone far!
There he is!
Go after him!
What?
Make way, Make way, Make way!
It's Takasu!
So fast...
Well, she should be able to catch up at this pace...
Ryuuji.
What about the cookies?
Huh?
Ouch... I knew there was a bump.
Did you find it?
Is it okay?
I-Is that so?
Oi.
Is it because I'm really clumsy?
You didn't realize it?
I wrote a love letter and put it in the wrong bag...
Went to bash someone up but fainted due to hunger...
Got my face hit with a ball during basketball...
Wanted to give someone cookies but tripped and lost them...
Are there any left?
You forgot to put the letter in the envelope.
That's right...
Give me one of those.
Wait... that one is crumbled... and...
Delicious!
You did a great job on it.
Such a pity. Try your best when you get a chance again.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Those two were buying things like onions and carrots in the supermarket.
Their almost like a married couple.
They came out from the same apartment this morning...
And they looked like they didn't get enough sleep.
Also, they were eating homemade cookies together.
Saying things like, "Aah, open up!"
It's like that!? No way!
Hey, Minori...
What's with your friend?
What happened?
Hurry up and enter.
Kya.
Kya?
May I see you for a moment?
The sun... is dry.
What's with Kushieda-san?
No clue.
Takasu-kun.
Yes!
Eh, me?
I leave Taiga to you!
Taiga is my most important friend! Please give her happiness no matter what!
Wait! Kushieda, could this be...
Happiness?
So it was like this.
Congrats, you two.
Kitamura? Why are you here?
I always knew you two were together a lot.
Now I see you two are a great couple.
Aisaka, get a hold of yourself!
Hey, stop laughing!
Takasu-kun.
If you make Aisaka cry, I will never forgive you.
Kushi...eda.
I'm sorry.
It's because I insisted on coming over,
And caused misunderstandings for Minori.
No, that is...
I felt... comfortable.
Staying in your home, that is.
I don't have a good relationship with my parents.
I was given that apartment when I said, "I want to leave home."
Even though I knew they were that type of parents.
Those cookies were very salty, right?
When I saw the crumbled cookies, I felt cursed, so I tried some.
"What's this, it's the worst!"
But you ate it all. You even lied.
Thinking of me even though you're a half-breed. You'll get bald.
You care too much.
Ryuuji, when you think about Minori, are you bothered about it?
Aah, yeah.
That's right...
Aisaka?
Why doesn't anyone understand?
We're already so frustrated.
Why doesn't anyone know?
Really... Everyone...
Everyone, everyone, everyone...
Pisses
ME OFF!!!
Pisses me off! Pisses me off! Pisses me off!
What do they mean by Palmtop tiger?! How can I not mind at all?!
Minori that idiot! Kitamura is an idiot too!
Why won't they listen to me?
My parents also!
No one!
Don't... understand... me...
I'll give you a hand.
Is being short bad?
Don't call me a delinquent!
Is there anything wrong with being called Taiga?
Murderous eyes sure are something!
Hey, are you alright?
Ryuuji, is this thing tilted?
How is that...
It's tilted!
Isn't it?!
Awesome! I won, I won!
Alright, I've decided.
I'll confess to Kitamura tomorrow,
and then end this all.
End?
The dog's service has ended.
From tomorrow, we're only classmates who are neighbors.
Just that.
Bye bye, Takasu-kun.
Oh...
Oh.
Ryuu-chan, isn't today's breakfast a little lacking?
Even though Ya-chan likes canned mackerel...
I wonder if Taiga is still sleeping.
Who knows.
Did you have an argument with her?
I didn't.
It feels kinda boring...
Right?
Eh? Aah, yeah.
Y... yo.
This is...
Ta-Takasu... um...
Sorry for making up weird rumors.
We made Aisaka-san angry.
She said, "There's nothing between Ryuuji and me."
Also she said, "Ryuuji is not a delinquent," and made a fuss.
The Palmtop Tiger sure is scary,
But Takasu isn't scary at all, didn't I say it before?
Eh, when?
Also, wouldn't it be bad if we don't clean up?
Kushieda!
Takasu-kun, sorry.
About what?
Taiga said it.
"I would never go out with Takasu-kun. So don't get me wrong."
She only wanted me to understand this.
That girl had a serious, desperate face.
But...
That is...
Say, Takasu-kun.
Takasu-kun?
What exactly is she doing...?
Isn't she going to confess to Kitamura today?
Is it the time to worry about someone else?
From tomorrow, we're only classmates that are neighbors.
Just that.
Just that, huh?
Kitamura-kun!
I...
About Kitamura-kun...
Hey... right after I arrive?
If this doesn't work out, it's gonna be a hard day.
Wait.
Although I only have a hunch,
I think I know what you want to say.
But before that, I want to confirm something.
Aren't you going out with Takasu-kun?
That was Minori's misunderstanding.
There's nothing between Takasu-kun and me.
Don't you love Takasu-kun?
Not that! I only live close to him...
There's nothing like love involved.
Then, do you dislike him?
I don't... dislike him.
But it's not like that.
Takasu-kun... He...
Right, fried rice!
Ryuuji made delicious fried rice for me.
Urged me on.
Supported me, even resorting to lying.
Staying by my side...
Because Ryuuji's there...
Because he's there...
Thats why...
I can pull out my courage like this.
I... love Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka, you're amazing.
Really?
Don't worry, I think your feelings have been correctly transferred.
Kitamura-kun...
Do you still remember, Aisaka?
The thing one year ago.
Yes.
Since then, you can make so many more interesting expressions.
Interesting expressions?
Yes.
The interesting expression you have when you are by Takasu.
Takasu is such a nice guy.
Also...
I think the Aisaka just now was a great woman.
Like just now...?
What did I say?
Anyway, it relieves me to see that you can get along well with Takasu.
W... wait! This has nothing to do with Ryuuji
I had an interesting expression? No! I mean...!
What do you mean by be relieved?
Eh? NO way! What did I say exactly...
Didn't I say "I love you" properly?
Don't worry, Aisaka. Don't worry.
Wh... what do you mean by don't worry?
You don't even know what I said...
Don't worry. We will definitely become very close friends.
It's not being friends... it's a confession...
Friends...
That's right. Becoming friends.
We're gonna be late for homeroom. Aisaka, you should hurry too.
I thought you'd cry.
Y.. you... wh.. why? D-D-Did you see?
I didn't see it on purpose.
What do you mean by not on purpose?
Never mind that. What are you gonna do?
I'm going back.
Really?
Then I'll make you a meal. You definitely haven't eaten, right?
On the subject, did you eat well last night?
It was definitely from the convenience store or someth-
Stop it.
Why? If you do, the same misunderstanding will happen.
This kind of thing, it's already enough.
I don't understand it either.
But I can't leave you alone!
That's why I said it's fine! You're not my dog anymore.
Thats right.
Right. I'm not a dog.
I'm a dragon.
Thats why I can stay by your side. Ai-
Taiga!
You called me Taiga...
The only thing on the same level as a tiger is a dragon.
I will become a dragon,
And stay by Taiga's side as a dragon.
There's a limit to being shameless! Know your place!
You...
Hey!
Hurry up! I'm hungry.
Also, we need our next battle plan.
I won't give up on Kitamura-kun just like this.
You mean...
I don't care whether you're a dragon or a dog,
Since you said you'll stay by my side, get ready to work hard.
Ryuuji.
Too hasty, huh?
Hurry up!
Ok, ok.
He called me Taiga.
Club girl Kushieda.
Hard working girl Kushieda.
Aah, you're Kushieda.
No matter when or where, you possess a shine.
Come buy one!
Look forward to next time!