Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
I'm getting a high energy reading
inside the target!
What?!
It's accelerating along its edge!
It's being focused!
Don't tell me it's...
No! Take cover!
Pull him in! Hurry!
Target no longer active!
-How's Shinji?
-Alive!
Recovering Unit 01
and routing to cage no. 7.
I'm going to the cage! Hold the fort!
Unit 01 locked down.
Pilot's brainwaves are erratic!
Pulse is faint!
Life-support system to maximum.
-Begin heart massage.
-Yes, ma'am!
Pulse confirmed!
Force-eject the entry plug. Hurry!
-Emergency dump the LCL.
-Yes, ma'am!
Get that hatch open! Hurry!
Shinji!
1/1 SCALE BALLOON DUMMY
Direct hit from enemy particle cannon!
-Dummy vaporized!
-Next.
GERMAN TYPE 12
SELF-PROPELLED SIEGE MORTAR
Type 12 self-propelled
siege mortar destroyed.
So that's how it is.
The data we've collected
so far suggests that
the target automatically eliminates
any threat within a set distance.
The instant something
enters that distance,
its particle cannon takes it out
with perfect accuracy.
Close-quarters combat by an Eva
would be too dangerous.
What about its A.T. Field?
Still active.
It's so powerful that its phase transition
space is visible to the naked eye.
Half-baked attacks with guided munitions,
direct cannon fire, or bombardment
would just backfire horribly.
So, impenetrable and deadly as hell.
It's practically an airborne fortress.
So what about that tunneling shield?
The target is currently overhead,
attacking Tokyo-3 Area Zero.
A giant tunneling shield
17.5 meters across
is drilling towards Nerv HQ
inside the Geo-front.
This Angel must intend to launch
a direct assault against Nerv HQ.
Cheeky bastard.
Estimated time of penetration?
Tomorrow morning
at 0006 hours, 54 seconds.
At that time, it will penetrate all
22 layers of armor and reach Nerv HQ.
Less than ten hours, huh?
Enemy tunneling shield has
contacted armor plate 01.
Unit 01's condition?
Everything up to the third layer
of the breastplate was melted.
It's a small mercy
that its function core wasn't hit.
Three more seconds, and it would have.
Estimated time to breastplate
replacement, three hours.
Roger that. What about Unit 00?
The reactivation itself went smoothly,
but errors remain in the feedback.
-So combat...
-...is out of the question.
Status of Unit 01's designated pilot?
Physiologically, he's fine.
Neural pulses are elevated by 0.8,
but that's within tolerances.
Tunneling shield breach
in nine hours, 55 minutes!
The situation certainly looks bleak.
Shall we raise a white flag?
There's something else
that I'd like to give a try first.
Firing directly at the target
from outside its range?
Yes, our only viable option
is to forcibly breach its A.T. Field
with a pinpoint penetration via
a focused high energy stream.
What do the Magi say?
The Magi supercomputers
gave two affirmatives
and one conditional affirmative.
Odds of success, 8.7%...
That is our highest figure.
I see no reason to oppose your plan.
Proceed, Capt. Katsuragi.
Yes, sir!
You sure came up with a loony one,
Operations Chief Katsuragi.
"Loony"? Don't be rude!
It's realistically executable
within nine hours.
It also has the best chance of success!
"Realistic," huh?
Our positron rifle can't handle that kind
of output. What will you do about that?
What else? I'll borrow one that can.
Borrow one? Now hold on...
Yup, that SSDF Tech HQ prototype.
NOTICE OF REQUISITION
For the aforementioned reasons,
Special Agency Nerv hereby commandeers
this Self-Propelled Positron Cannon
as of 1500 hours today.
But that's... Be reasonable!
We'll do all we can
to return it in one piece.
Thank you for your cooperation
in this matter.
Okay, Rei! Take it away!
It's a delicate piece of machinery,
so be gentle!
But our computations say
it will take at least 180 gigawatts
to punch through that A.T. Field.
Where are you going to get
that kind of power?
Where else? From all of Japan.
We interrupt this program to bring you
the following bulletin.
From 11:30 p.m. tonight
until daybreak tomorrow,
a wide-scale blackout
will be in effect for all of Japan.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We repeat, from 11:30 p.m. tonight
through daybreak tomorrow,
a blackout will be in effect
for all of Japan.
Thank you for your cooperation.
TOKYO-3
Enemy tunneling shield
has breached armor plate 07.
How's our power supply look?
We're 3.2% behind schedule,
but we'll have it ready by 2310 hours.
And the positron rifle?
You have the word of Tech Development
Division Section Three!
We'll have it ready within three hours!
Defensive measures?
We'll have to hide behind
some sort of shield.
This is a shield?
Yes. This is a castoff from
the SSTO program.
It may not be pretty, but the lower hull
has a hyper-EM coating.
It will be able to withstand
even that beam for 17 seconds.
-You have Section Two's guarantee.
-Good enough. And the sniping point?
Factoring in the distance, terrain,
and power substation availability,
this is the best spot.
Yes, that will do just fine.
The sniping location will be
the summit of Mt. Futago!
This operation will commence
when the clock strikes midnight!
It will henceforth be referred to
as Operation Yashima!
Roger!
All that's left now is our pilots.
Unit 01's pilot
has regained consciousness.
His diagnostic values all check out.
Good. The operation will proceed
as planned, then.
Yes, ma'am.
Will he get into it again, though?
Prepare for battle at Mt. Futago!
CENTRAL HOSPITAL, SURGICAL WARD NO. 3
Ayanami...
The following is the schedule
for Operation Yashima,
which will begin at 0000 hours tonight.
"Pilots Ikari and Ayanami will report
to cage at 1730 hours today.
1800 hours.
Units 00 and 01 will be activated.
1805 hours. Depart HQ.
1830 hours.
Arrive at temporary base at Mt. Futago.
Once there, await further instructions.
When the clock strikes midnight,
operation will commence."
Here, your new suit.
Don't forget to dress
and show up like that.
Sorry.
I've done nothing but apologize
since yesterday.
Eat.
I don't... have much of an appetite.
We leave in 60 minutes.
Do I have to pilot that thing again?
Yes, that's right.
I... I'm done with this.
You can only say that because you
haven't been through what I have.
I don't want to go
through that ever again.
Then stay in bed.
What do you mean?
I'll pilot Unit 01.
Dr. Akagi has made preparations
to rewrite Unit 01's personal data.
Ms. Ritsuko did that?
Well, Capt. Katsuragi and Dr. Akagi
are waiting in the cage.
Farewell.
NO SCHOOL TODAY
Geez, what's keeping them?
We need to get to the shelter.
I hacked my dad's files.
This is definitely the right time.
Maybe, but they ain't here.
The mountain's moving!
It's the Evangelion!
That's so cool!
-Go for it!
-We're counting on you!
You can do it!
We're all behind you!
8:11 P.M.
Enemy tunneling shield
has penetrated armor plate 17.
Three hours and 55 minutes
until it reaches HQ!
Transmission grid hookups to Shikoku
and Kyushu regions complete.
Please begin test run
of all cooling units.
Be careful, that's a piece
of precision equipment.
But this wasn't built for field use.
Will it do us any good?
What else can we do?
We're improvising all this.
This will work, right?
Theoretically.
But we won't know if the barrel or the
accelerator can handle it until we shoot.
It's never been test-fired using
such extreme amounts of energy.
Here are your roles in this operation:
-Shinji.
-Yes?
-You're the gunner in Unit 01.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Rei, you're on defense in Unit 00.
This is because Shinji and Unit 01
have the higher synchronization rate.
This operation requires
a high degree of precision.
Positrons are affected by the Earth's
rotation, magnetic field, and gravity,
so they don't travel in a straight line.
You have to correct for that.
Don't forget. Hit the core,
and only the core, precisely.
But I've never practiced
doing something like that.
Don't worry,
just do as the indicators say.
Pull the trigger when the markers
are all centered on the target.
The machine will do the rest.
Also, once fired, the gun will require
cooling, recharging, and a fuse change,
so it will take time
before it can be fired again.
But what if I miss
and the target shoots back?
Focus on the task at hand.
Concentrate on destroying the target
with your first shot.
I'll be in a real jam, in other words.
So I...
-I should protect Unit 01, then?
-That's right.
Understood.
It's time. Both of you, get changed.
Yes, ma'am.
We...
might end up dying, huh?
Why do you say that?
You won't die.
Because I'll protect you.
Why do you pilot your Eva, Ayanami?
It's my link.
Link?
Yes. My link.
To my father?
To everyone.
You sure are tough, Ayanami.
I don't have anything else.
What do you mean?
It's time. Let's go.
Farewell.
At the tone, the time will be 0000 hours.
JAPAN STANDARD TIME
Commence operation!
Shinji, we're going to entrust you
with all of Japan's energy.
-Give it your best.
-Yes, ma'am!
Initiate stage one connection.
Districts 1 through 803,
begin power transfer.
Voltage climbing.
Nearing overvoltage levels.
Set all cooling systems to maximum!
Temperatures stable. All green.
Positrons flowing in. Influx is stable.
Stage two connection!
-Start up all accelerators.
-Forced convergence device, activate!
Directing all power to
Mt. Futago substation expansion.
Stage three connection shows green.
Disable final safety device!
Cock the rifle!
Correcting for Earth's
rotation and gravity.
Plus 0.0009.
Discharge voltage threshold
in zero point two!
Final, stage seven connection!
Routing all power to positron rifle!
Eight! Seven!
-Six! Five! Four! Three!
-High energy reading from target!
What?!
Two!
One!
Fire!
We missed?!
Enemy tunneling shield
has breached the Geo-front!
Ready second shot! Hurry!
Replacing fuse! Commencing recharging!
Commencing barrel cooling!
Another high energy reading from target!
No!
Shinji!
Ayanami!
-The shield won't hold!
-How much longer?!
Ten seconds!
Come on...
Come on!
Got him!
Ayanami!
Ayanami! Are you okay?!
Don't say... Don't say that you
don't have anything else, okay?
Don't say sad stuff like "Farewell"
whenever you walk off, okay?
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
I don't know how I should act
at times like this.
Smiling would be a good start.
TO BE CONTINUED
A humanoid weapon built by
a civilian organization to fight Angels
goes out of control.
Will Misato be able to avert
a reactor meltdown?
Next episode! "The Works of Man"!
Tune in!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming