[Narrator] Alchemy:
the science of understanding,
deconstructing, and
reconstructing matter.
However, it is not
an all-powerful art.
It is impossible to create
something out of nothing.
If one wishes to
obtain something,
something of equal
value must be given.
This is the Law of
Equivalent Exchange.
The basis of all alchemy.
In accordance with this law,
there is a taboo
among alchemists.
Human transmutation
is strictly forbidden.
For what could equal
the value of a human soul?
[Narrator] The town of Liore
had fallen under the control
of Father Cornello, a corrupt
priest who used alchemy
combined with a Philosopher's
Stone to deceive his people.
Ed and Al came to
Liore and put a stop
to the priest's sinister plans.
The Philospher's
Stone, however,
was revealed to be a fake.
Their leader exposed as a fraud,
the hopes of the citizens
of Liore were crushed.
"Stand up and walk.
Move forward."
These were Ed's words to Rose--
words he had once
needed to hear himself.
[footsteps]
[Scar] You are Basque Grand, the
Iron Blood Alchemist... correct?
[Grand] Why? Who's asking?
Foolish alchemists who have
turned their backs on the
ways of God...
shall all be punished.
I see... You must be
the bloodthirsty murderer
who's been making
a habit of targeting
State Alchemists lately...
[clanging metal]
ker-clang
[magic shimmer]
Well this time...
...you've picked
the wrong target!
[electroshock bolts]
kazzzurghzzzzzch
Yerrrr-agh!
[wizardly hum]
[earthy explosion]
crumBLAM
[cannon blasts]
bang bang ba-bang bang
[explosions]
You're fast. Try this!
[electrobolts]
[electrochains]
[running footsteps]
A little more?
[earthy magic hum]
[metallic crash]
Hmph...
That wasn't so difficult.
[footsteps]
Huh?
[explosion]
[Grand]
What?! No! How?!
Now you perish.
[harsh electroshocks]
[splash explosion]
[thud]
ker-thud
[Hughes]
Another State Alchemist dead?
[Armstrong]
This killer is highly skilled.
[Hughes]
Major, you watch yourself.
For all we know, you could be
the next one he comes after.
Understood.
[car tires squealing]
Fuhrer Bradley,
Your Excellency.
What brings you here?
[footsteps]
[Bradley]
I got word of what happened.
Lieutenant Colonel Hughes,
you're the officer
in charge of this case?
Yes sir.
Should you need any
additional personnel, just ask.
The man doing this is
a traitor. I want him stopped.
Sir.
[birds chriping]
chee-chirp chee-chee-chirp
Lieutenant Breda.
Right... Jeez...
The Colonel's sure letting his
work pile up again, huh?
Havoc... gimme a hand, will ya?
I've got plenty to do
over here already.
[Havoc] Next up... Who's this?
[Falman] Lieutenant Yoki.
Remember, the crook who was
using the Youswell coal mine
concessions to line
his own pockets?
Anyway, the Elric
brothers exposed
what that dirty
thief was up to,
and now he's on the run.
[Hawkeye] Master Sergeant
Fuery, how's the radio?
The receiver on this
thing's seen better days.
I think I'm gonna
have to replace it.
[magical hum]
[electricity]
sssszerk
Huh?
[Fuery] Hey, it's
Edward and Alphonse!
[Hawkeye] Welcome back boys...
Go on in, the Colonel's
expecting you.
[groan]
Well done on the Liore case,
you two. Nice work...
I appreciate you
resolving the matter.
No big deal.
It's not like we did it for you.
[Roy] Right.
The Philosopher's Stone.
Another false lead?
Yeah, after all that,
the stone was a fake.
Even so... the power it gave
Cornello was real enough.
He transmuted this huge
chimera right in front of us.
[Al] I still wonder how
he was able to use
the stone to do that.
I'm not familiar enough
with the field of bio-alchemy
to really understand it.
Yeah, I'm kind of curious
about that to...
It might be worth looking into.
Who knows, maybe we'll find
something that could help
us restore our bodies.
[Al] Hmm.
It might help if you
consulted a specialist.
[Both] Huh?
[Roy] The Sewing Life Alchemist,
Shou Tucker... He's done some
heavy research into
chimera transmutation.
I'll introduce you.
[Al] You would do
that for us?
Okay, what's the catch! You want
something, don't you!
[Roy] Don't doubt my motives!
I'm trying to repay you
for your work on
the Liore case.
Doing you a favor is better
than being indebted to you.
[Roy] Two years ago, Tucker
transmuted a chimera that
could understand human
speech. That earned him
his certification as
a State Alchemist.
By "understand human
speech," you mean...
Wait, You mean it talks?
A chimera?!
Right... supposedly.
It only said one thing.
[Roy] "I want to die."
[gasp]
[Roy] After that, it refused to
eat until it got its wish.
[bell ringing]
[Ed] Man, this house is huge!
[swoosh]
[slomo barking]
[Ed, screaming]
[Al] You okay, Ed?
[Nina] Daddy!
There are people
out here! Look.
Nina... this is why I told
you to keep the dog tied up.
[spring sound]
boy-oy-oing
[Tucker] I'm sorry about
the mess. Ever since my wife
ran out, this place
has been a wreck.
I'm not much of a housekeeper.
[sighs]
Now that we're all settled
in, let me say that it's
a pleasure to meet you, Edward.
As the colonel told you,
I'm the Sewing Life Alchemist,
Shou Tucker.
Ed is interested in the field
of biologic alchemy.
He would like to have a
look at your research
if that's possible.
Oh yes, certainly,
I don't mind.
However...
[armor clank, gasp]
If you want me to show you the
tricks I've got up my sleeve,
it's only fair that
you show me the tricks
you've got up yours as well.
[Tucker] It's the code we
live by--equivalent exchange.
Now. Why are you
interested in bio-alchemy?
Oh, um... Ed...
Well, you see, he's--
Colonel.
[birds chirping]
chee-chee chee-chirp
[Tucker]
You transmuted your mother...
...as an eleven-year-old child?
[Tucker] I see...
So that's what earned you
the title 'Fullmetal Alchemist.'
You've had a rough time
of it for someone so young.
I can't say for sure
if it's going to be
of any use to
you or not...
[Tucker]
But why don't you go ahead and
take a look at my laboratory.
[weird animal sounds]
[roaring and growling]
rrrrrro, grrrrrrwl
[more weird animal sounds]
[Tucker] It's kind
of embarrassing.
I'm fairly widely regarded
as an authority on chimeras.
But the truth is...
It hasn't actually been
going that well lately.
[door creaks opening]
[Ed] Ohh... Amazing!
[Tucker] This is my library.
Feel free to look around.
All right, then let's dive in!
I'll start with this shelf!
[Al] I'll try starting
over here.
I'm going to head
back to work now.
I'll send somebody by
to get you this evening.
[scoffing]
They've got some
ability to focus,
I'm not sure they even
know we're here anymore.
Quite a catch, these two...
A couple of prodigies.
[clock ticking]
[Al] Hmm?
[gasp]
[running footsteps]
♪ Playful Music ♪
[giggles]
[childlike laughter]
[Al] Woo-hoo! Way up high!
[both laughing]
Al, what're
you doing?!
You're supposed
to be reading!
[Al] Um.. Nina looked
like she wanted to play.
Well, in case you forgot,
we didn't come here
to play horsie!
[slomo barking]
[Ed, screaming]
Alexander says that
he wants to play, too!
That's what you want is it?
You've bested me twice, dog...
But playtime is over!
I will not lose this time.
I, Edward Elric, will use my
considerable powers
to vanquish you!
[Ed] You mangy mutt!
[laughs]
[Havoc] Hey, chief.
Your ride has arrived.
[panting, happy whimpering]
[Havoc] What're you up
to down there, Ed?
Oh, uh... let's just say
I'm taking a break from
a long day of research.
After all that,
you must be dog tired.
[dog whimper]
[laughs] Why don't you
come on back tomorrow?
You're really going
to come again?
We'll play some more
tomorrow, okay, Nina?
'Kay!
[Havoc] Oh, Mister
Tucker, I almost forgot.
I've got a message for you.
It's from the Colonel. He says
"Don't forget, assessment
day is coming soon."
Yes... please assure him I know.
Right.
[door creaks shut]
[Nina] Hey, Daddy?
What does 'assessment day' mean?
[Tucker] State alchemists have
to report on their research
once a year in order to
keep their certification.
You see, last year, Nina,
your Daddy didn't get
a very good evaluation.
Unless I do something really
impressive this year,
I won't be a state
alchemist anymore.
Huh? No! You'll do
just fine Daddy!
I know you will! You're
always studying so much!
[laughs nervously]
You're right, Nina.
I have to try hard.
[Tucker] Or we'll be left
with nothing... again.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
♪ Sentimental Music ♪
[birds chirping]
[Al] Your mother left
two years ago?
[Nina] Daddy said she went back
to live at her parents' house.
[Al] It must get kind of lonely
with just you and your dad
living in this
big house, huh?
Nu-uh, not really...
Daddy's so nice, and plus, I've
got Alexander to play with, too!
But lately Daddy's been studying
in his lab all the time...
I guess that does make
me a little bit lonely.
[yawn]
My shoulders
are killing me!
[Alphonse] Maybe you should try
to move around some, Brother.
Yeah, not a bad idea, Al...
Hey, you mangy mutt!
[dog bark]
Rooouuughr
Looks like you could
use some exercise.
[Al] Let's go too, Nina!
[laughing]
♪ Goofy Happy Piano ♪
[Edward and Nina
yelling happily]
[Edward] I'm gonna get you!
Look out here I come!
[silly music and laughing]
[Havoc] Don't forget...
Assessment Day is coming soon.
[Hughes] What I want to
know is why this guy
is only targeting State
Alchemists and no one else.
If it's the military
he's trying to hurt,
he could go after
normal soldiers.
Surely soldiers would
be easier to kill
than highly skilled alchemists.
Especially ones who have
been state certified.
[Armstrong] Maybe the
certification is the reason.
State Alchemists are given
high pay and special privilege.
There must be any
number of people
who envy them their
positions... Or, perhaps...
...they feel they have
not upheld their creed:
"Alchemist, be thou
for the people."
Alchemists, who are supposed to
be pillars of science and truth,
are turned into the
military's walking weapons
as soon as they
receive certification.
There are plenty of people,
I'm sure, who have not forgotten
the role that State
Alchemists played
in the Ishvalan Civil War.
[knock at the door]
I have a report, sir.
A canvas has revealed
that yesterday,
at nine thirty...
or right around that time,
a man with a large scar on
his face was sighted in
the Central City Train Station
by multiple station employees.
The Station?
Looks like that
bastard got away.
♪ Melancholy Music ♪
Before I earned my State
Alchemist certification,
our life was terrible.
We were so poor in those days.
My wife couldn't stand
living that kind of life...
...so she left us.
I can't afford to
fail this assessment.
I don't ever want to go
back to those days again.
I don't even think I could.
Don't worry, Daddy,
it's okay...
If those people
do tell you no,
me and Alexander will growl
at them until they say yes!
[Alphonse, laughing]
You tell 'em, Nina!
Hey, Nina... I've got an idea.
Do you want to play
with Daddy tomorrow?
Really?
Yeah.
Woo-hoo!
Alexander, Daddy says he's
going to play with us tomorrow!
[dog bark]
[bell ringing]
ding da-ding ding
[Al] Hello, Mr. Tucker!
Thanks for having
us again today!
Huh?
[Al] Mr. Tucker?
[Ed] Hey! Nina?!
[Al] Mr. Tucker!
[Ed] There you are.
So you are home!
Yes.
I did it boys.
I finally did it.
A chimera that understands
human speech.
[thunder clap]
Here, let me show you.
Listen to me... That person
over there, that's Edward.
That person...
Ed... ward.
Yes, that's very good.
Well done.
That's amazing!
It can actually talk.
Now I don't have to worry
about losing my certification.
That person... Ed... ward.
Big Brother Ed.
[thunder clap]
[Ed] Mr. Tucker...
When did you first get
your state certification?
Let's see...
It was two years ago.
[Ed] And when did
your wife leave you?
That was two years ago, too.
[Ed] I just have one more
question for you...
Nina and Alexander...
Where are they?!
♪ Menacing Music ♪
Damn brat, figuring it
out so quickly!
[Al] Brother!
[Ed] Oh yeah, I figured
it out. You did it again!
Two years ago,
it was your wife!
This time you used your
own daughter and her dog
to transmute a talking chimera!
You can only do so much
with animals, after all.
It's much easier when you start
with a human, isn't that right?!
I don't see what you're
so upset about...
This is how we progress.
Human experimentation
is a necessary step.
I would think a scientist
should understand.
[Ed] Shut up!
Do you really think you
can get away with this?!
Messing around with
someone's life like that?
Your own daughter?!
Someone's life, you say?
Ha ha. You'd know all
about that, wouldn't you?
Look at you,
Fullmetal Alchemist...
Look at your leg,
your arm, your brother!
Those things are also the
result of messing around
with somebody's
life, aren't they?
[Ed] Shut up!
[laughing]
We are the same!
We're the same...
you're just like me!
We're not!
Oh, but yes we are...
The opportunity was right in
front of us, and we took it!
We had to, even though we knew
it was against the rules.
No!
Not me!
Alchemists don't...
...do that!
I'm not... I'm not!
[Al] Brother!
If you keep this up, he'll die.
Edward... No.
Daddy, do you... hurt? Daddy?
[Al] I'm sorry.
Even with all our power,
we can't do anything
to change you back.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Can we play... now?
Can we play now?
I made it just in time...
I get to remain a State
Alchemist. I passed!
[Ed]
Like hell, you're staying a
State Alchemist! Like hell!
Can we... play now?
[Ed screams]
[rain falling]
[Hawkeye] If ever there was
an example of the devil's
work in this world, this case
would definitely be it.
[Roy] The devil, huh?
A State Alchemist
must be willing to act,
able to take another's life when
ordered to without questioning.
In some ways,
Mr. Tucker's actions and our own
may not be all that far apart,
when it comes to interfering
with other people's lives.
We choose our own path, knowing
full well what we're doing.
That's the way it is...
Right, Fullmetal?
You will more than
likely come across cases
like this again
in the future...
And you may end up having to get
your own hands dirty, as well.
Are you going to shut down
like this every time?
[Ed] We may be called
dogs of the military...
We may even be cursed as
devils... It doesn't matter.
Al and I are still going
to get our bodies back.
We know the truth.
We know we're not devils.
We know we're not gods!
We're human.
[shouting]
We're only human!
We can't even do anything to
save one innocent little girl.
[Ed] So what good are we, then?
I wonder why no one's
capable of understanding me.
Nina.
[footsteps]
[thunder]
You're Shou Tucker, correct?
Who are you?
Not military...
Who are you?!
How did you get in here?
There were military
police out front!
Foolish alchemists
who turn their backs
on the ways of God...
...shall be punished.
Daddy's hurting.
Daddy hurts... No, Daddy.
You poor creature. Once you
have been given this form,
there is no way of
separating you again.
At least...
Your passing will be in peace.
[thunder]
[Scar] God...
Hear me... Two human souls
have just been returned to you.
Please accept them
into your loving arms.
Please grant these
poor, lost souls
everlasting peace
and salvation.
[Narrator] The rain pours
down in East City.
Still grief-stricken
over the death of Nina...
Ed and Al are attacked by
the mysterious man, Scar.
In a moment of crisis, Ed
must make a desperate decision,
while the life of his brother
hangs in the balance.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood--
Episode Five. Rain of Sorrows.
What will Edward decide?
And will he be able to live
with the consequences?