Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Fairy Tale Masterpieces
The Hare of Inaba
Author/Tsukuyomi Sasami
Long ago in a land not so far away,
there lived a very smart and lovely hare.
One day, while the hare was puzzled over a river it couldn't cross,
a shark suddenly appeared.
The hare!
Sasami's playing the hare!
The clever hare thought up a plan to get around the suspicious-looking shark.
Hey, Shark!
May I step on you?
Was the Hare of Inaba really that straightforward?
But if Sasami will do me the honor of stepping on me,
then I shall not point out the obvious!
After making a foothold of the shark's back,
the hare was able to cross the river easily.
Thank you, Shark.
According to the story, the shark scathed the hare's skin!
Which means...
since you're human, your clothes would be torn,
and you'd be embarrassed!
Don't lust after your own sister!
Oh? What're you doing, Paparin?
Our teacher is treated poorly even in a parallel world.
Dear gods, may speak with you?
In truth, I—
Nah, it was your fault.
A mere fish speaking to a god as an equal is simply unthinkable.
Me too!
Ah, how refreshing!
Ever loyal to the original tale, the gods left without a twinge of remorse.
The shark was left to die alone and in sorrow,
but he was suddenly wrapped in a warm light.
Shark,
I shall grant you a medicine of great aid.
A kind god appeared in the shark's final moments,
and healed all of his wounds.
Oh, I've never been treated with such kindness before!
To repay you for your blessing, I shall...
I shall...
I shall serve the beautiful and grace
and vow to attend to her for all ete
serve the beautiful and graceful Sasami for all my life,
and vow to attend to her for all eternity—
Sasami?
Would you like to attend school today?
Brother, you pervert!
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 3
Work is for Suckers
Sasami Report, Part Five, Revision 2
Sasami Report, Part Five, Revision 2.
Power of the Supreme God
Power of the Supreme God.
Inside my brother, Tsukuyomi Kamiomi,
lies the power of the Supreme God Amaterasu.
With the power of the Supreme God, one can Transform the world at will.
Just by having a desire,
the gods of the Yaoyorozu will automatically begin a Transformation.
Yes? What is it, Sasami?
Dinner
Dinner.
Yes, right away.
However,
my brother hasn't realized that this power resides within him.
Yes,
he still thinks it lies within me.
My family, the Tsukuyomis,
were the first humans to obtain the Supreme God's power,
and are descendants of Amaterasu's grandson, Ninigi-no-Mikoto.
The Tsukuyomi Shrine is hidden in a Kyushu mountain.
Japan's Natural Beauty
Walking in a Winter Kyushu
Part 1
Wonders
Our goal is beautiful scenery!
For generations, they've passed the power down, protected it,
Athletic Contest!
The top female athlete vs.
the Supreme God in an all-out match!
Regional Digital TV Listings
and used Transformations to preserve what makes this world convenient for humans.
They're a family of wonders.
I was locked within the Tsukuyomi Shrine from birth.
I underwent strict training to become
a container for the Supreme God's power.
My daily training was more like
being tempered in hellfire.
And I thought that my life was perfectly normal.
But one day, unable to bear the pain of training,
I ran away from home.
I found civilization, and I saw my first city.
The moment I snuck into that comic cafe and discovered the internet,
everything I thought to be normal crumbled away.
I was quickly caught and brought home,
but I started to have doubts about the way I'd lived until then.
Since then, I snuck out every now and then to learn about the real world from the internet.
I also hid from reality within virtual reality.
And so, with my knowledge of the outside world, I found my brother and...
What do you need, Sasami?
I'm out of Red Blue.
Right, I'll buy some immediately.
I found my brother and...
I've returned!
He's fast!
I'll put the rest in the fridge.
I found my brother and...
What might you be writing?
Don't look, pervert!
Oh?
Are you writing something so embarrassing that I can't look?
Siblings have nothing to hide from each other!
Now, get naked and tell your brother all the juicy details of your maidenly woes!
Get out!
Now then...
where was I?
Oh, I remember.
I found my brother and ran away from the Tsukuyomi Shrine with him.
But the Tsukuyomis aren't simply letting us be.
Right now,
even though we've hidden our trail of Transformations,
after the commotion of the Valentine Tragedy and Eight-Forked Serpent SNS incident,
they're likely tracking us.
My life is peaceful and doesn't ask much of me,
but it could end so—
What? What's going on?
What's happened, Sasami?
Brother, what do I do?
Oh, the day for my love to be rewarded has finally arrived!
I understand. Your brother will take care of you.
Now, to the bed...
Shut up, moron!
Listen to me here!
Get your head out of the gutter!
Huh?
So you're saying you didn't want to sleep together because you had a bad dream?
Huh?!
Oh, I was imagining something else...
But that's not the point!
Look here.
What happened to me?
Hmm...
this is quite puzzling.
You're already in high school, but they haven't grown a bit...
Brother!
I can feel with it.
Cutting it off might hurt.
Now what's gotten into you, Sasami?
Brother, do you know what this is?
It's an arm, what else could it be?
Transformation
A Transformation...
My brother can't recognize that anything's changed!
I'll call this arm a tumor for now.
Sasami Report, Part 13.
P.S.:
My Lineage.
The Tsukuyomis have lived short lives for generations.
To protect what makes their bodies perfect containers for the Supreme God's power,
the Tsukuyomis repeatedly intermarried, weakening their bodies.
The females were made shrine maidens and trained in their spiritual power.
They managed the Supreme God's power.
When the time came,
I became the successor to Amaterasu's power,
and it resided in my body.
And to ensure I wouldn't use that great power for selfish or evil pursuits,
I took a medicine that muddled my spirit and stole my desires.
The males of the family became servants to the shrine maidens,
protecting them with their lives, attending to their needs,
and being expended as tools used to make children.
My brother hid his face,
and lived in the shadows like a ninja or a stagehand.
My brother had no misgivings about his role.
Just like a robot.
If I commanded it, he'd gladly bite his tongue to death.
And I've always abused that servitude of his.
My brother is the only one who would never betray me.
My brother is the only one who would never hurt me.
My brother is the only one who would ever love me.
No matter how hideous I might be,
or how worthless a failure I might be,
my brother would always worship me.
He'd support me. Protect me.
That's why, when I ran from the shrine,
I took my brother with me.
I could never return again.
I didn't care about the fate of the world.
I couldn't take it anymore.
The night I ran away,
My sins, my fear, and my regret made me shudder.
But my brother still held me in his arms.
He rarely said a word in the shrine,
but he didn't stop talking until I fell asleep.
"It's all right, Sasami."
"Please, don't be scared."
"Please, don't cry."
"You're free now."
"Take pride in that,
and live in whatever way makes you happy."
"Push your pain,
Push your pain,
pain,
"Push your pain, your regret, your guilt,
and everything else you hate onto me."
"I'll bear them for you."
"That is my duty."
"That is what I live for."
And so, he fulfilled his duty.
Why is it moving on its own?
H
e
l
o
Hello
Yes. You and I have a different consciousness.
What... are you?
a different
consciousness
"I was hidden inside you by those from the shrine."
"The medicine split your consciousness in two,
and in an emergency, my consciousness would activate."
he medicine split your consciousness in
gency, my consciousness would activate
They did that to me?
"Worry not. My duty is to protect you."
"Now that I have introduced myself, my duty is done."
"You are now safe."
Safe?
"Your pursuers from the Tsukuyomi Shrine pose the greatest threat."
"Should they capture you, you will never escape again."
"Their medicine and brainwashing will forever isolate you from society."
"But those of the shrine want the Supreme God's power more than anything,
which does not lie within you."
"The location of the Supreme God's power is..."
No, you can't!
[Secret] Sasami
Report
Supreme God Amaterasu can Transform.
Inside my brother,
Tsukuyomi
Kamiomi
Inside my brother, Tsukuyomi Kamiomi, lies the p
me God, one can Transform the world at will.
Without actively thinking it, just by having a desire, the gods
my brother hasn't realized that this power resides
Where it should be...
he still thinks it lies within me.
ily, the Tsukuyomis, are the first humans to obtain the Supreme God
descendants of Ninigi-no-Mikoto, mediums ruling this country from underground.
Without actively
my brother has
where it should
within me
Tsukuyomis, are the
of Ninigi-no-Mikoto
thinking it, just by having
still hasn't realized
should be...
"If he so much as sees one of these reports while you sleep,
I guarantee he will jump to his own conclusions."
"And to protect you, the shrine will see—"
Someone, please...
just for today...
Just for today, help me...
Brother, you idiot!
Dammit!
Sup.
You all right?
Girls shouldn't let their faces get scarred.
Lemme see.
Don't cry. At least you tried.
I didn't... try at all.
I thought I could live without doing anything...
I thought I'd be happy as long as I had my freedom.
But I just pushed it all onto my brother.
He's bearing everything that burdened me!
Don't push yourself.
I'm... horrible.
He's my brother, but he still bore everything!
He doesn't even recognize how far he's taken it!
I'm still just pushing it all onto him!
I haven't done a thing for him!
There's a difference between trying hard and overdoing it.
You're still a kid.
It's okay if you need a hand sometimes.
You're not abusing them.
You just have faith.
If you're having trouble at home, come talk to me.
I'm your homeroom teacher.
Where are we?
The Tsukuyomi Shrine?!
Haven't been here in a while.
You've been here?
We can talk while walking.
True, I used to be able to destroy anything whenever I felt like it,
but they've been handling all those pain-in-the-ass gods in my place,
so I just left it to them.
You mean...
Long ago, the gods of creation, Izanagi and Izanami, gave me the task of managing this country.
You're...
the Supreme God, Amaterasu!
But gods can't do whatever they feel like, you know.
If you wanna go hide in a cave, someone'll drag you right out.
I got sick of it, so I transferred my power to Ninigi-no-Mikoto and went into hiding.
God of Rice, bountiful in harvest, Ninigi-no-Mikoto...
my ancestor.
I thought I'd have to go back to work when lil' Ninigi died,
but surprisingly, he found a way to transfer the power to his descendants.
Intermarriage...
If they made children with someone genetically close to them,
the power would be passed down.
But the world humans built for themselves was fine as is,
so I stepped down to watch over it.
Just like you.
Making sure the bearer of the Supreme God's power doesn't do anything stupid,
but also being lazy and leaving the boring bits to someone else.
You don't want it back?
I'm tired already.
When I finally get my power back,
I want to leave it in the hands of someone younger.
That'd be her.
Tama?
Yay, food!
That was yummy!
I cut a part of myself off to give birth to a new god.
Since she was a part of me, I call her my little sister.
I just told her that the Supreme God gave birth to her.
So she calls my brother "Paparin" because he has the Supreme God's power...
Say your prayers, for this is a shrine!
Kagami?
You are but sacrificial lambs,
for this is a shrine.
Kagami's kinda similar.
Long ago, I severed a part of me that an enemy had cursed,
which an evil human later discovered and raised.
She got armed with cursed tools and modern weaponry,
and was built as spiritually powered robot.
A robot built from a god...
I couldn't bear to see her used for evil,
so I swiped her and raised her.
I pray upon you,
for this is a shrine.
I switched "prey" for "pray" back there.
So then... what are you doing here?
We're blowin' this shrine to pieces.
Why'd you think we showed up?
What?
Normally, we gods are one with the earth, so humans can't perceive us.
Ever wonder why you could still see us?
See you?
Because you wished for us,
the three Yagami sisters.
For an ally to protect your peaceful, everyday life.
That's why we'll protect that lazy lifestyle of yours.
Now let's take that Tsukuyomi idiot home,
and take back our fun, chaotic life!
Yeah!
Sister, we have a problem.
I cannot find a trace of Mr. Tsukuyomi anywhere.
I thought he was here because it smelled like him,
but he's nowhere!
Hey, I need to ask you something!
Madam Sasami, you've returned?
Hey, where's my brother?
If you mean Kamiomi, he came here a short while ago,
but he was driven out by the family head.
If I recall,
he said he had the Supreme God's power,
and babbled about wanting to be a shrine maiden in your place.
We inspected him just in case,
but there wasn't a trace of spiritual power or divinity.
Regardless of him kidnapping Madam and being disowned,
he still came back spouting such nonsense,
so the head got mad and tossed him out.
So that means...
what does it mean?
I had been gravely mistaken.
Apparently, the Supreme God's power lied within me the whole time.
It was my desire.
For my brother to live in happiness.
The gods responded to my desire by granting all of my brother's wishes.
Currently Out
I got the impression that I had lost my power,
since I couldn't use it myself.
The pain I felt whenever I went outdoors was apparently the doing of some evil god.
But...
I'm fine now.
From now on,
I'm going to live in this bright, sun-drenched world!
Introspecting
Now, let's go,
Sasami.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
From now on, I think I'll really try!
When trouble is near, the star appears!
It's your very own Tsurugi!
Supporting Sasami's lazy lifestyle is our duty as the Yagami sisters!
Anyway, we'll be singing this time,
so Sasami isn't getting her mic back!
Just do whatever.
Tsurugi, I wanna help!
I love singing!
All right!
Let's sing together!
The only place you'll hear the Supreme God Amaterasu of lore sing
is on "Sasami@Ganbaranai"!
Yay!
Teacher,
I cannot sing, but it matters not.
Well, I'd like you to join in if you can,
but somehow, I get the same feeling from you that I get from Sasami...
Please don't group me with such a failure of a human.
What I mean is,
I'd like you to tell Sasami to try harder, too.
I think she might listen to what you have to say.
What do you mean?
I think I'll have to wait until next time to explain,
since it seems the song is already over.
Good work, everyone!
In that case, may I go home?
Who Cares Cooking
Time for Who Cares Cooking.
Today's dish is your standard beef stroganoff.
Beef Stroganoff
Your ingredients are:
beef, an onion, mushrooms, a tomato, red wine, butter, bouillon, and paprika,
Beef Stroganoff
Feeds four
Beef
Onion
Mushrooms
Tomato
Red Wine
Butter
Bouillon
Paprika
280g
1 (in half)
200 milliliters
1 tsp
To Taste
so just send someone to buy them, wait a bit, stomp your foot,
and it'll show up in front of your door.
It's pretty simple, so try it yourselves.
Next time, on Episode 4:
Next Time, on Episode 4
Family Leech
Family Leech.