Dammit!
Did you really think you could get away?
Buzz off!
Who the hell are you, anyway?
Me?
I'm just a guy who's a hero for fun.
What kind of hero looks like that?
You…
You're gonna pay for that.
Do you have all of my money yet, mister?
Not quite…
What will you do?
It's due tomorrow, you know.
You do know what'll happen tomorrow…
…if you don't have my money?
Damn it!
I did it again.
ROAD TO HERO
ONE PUNCH
THREE, TWO, ONE, KILL SHOT
JOIN THE FIGHT, CERTAIN VICTORY, THE STRONGEST EVER
SANJOU, HISSHOU, SHIJOU SAIKYOU
WHAT WAS THAT? FRUSTRATION
NAN DATTEN DA? FRUSTRATION
THERE'S NO STOPPING ME
ORE WA TOMARANAI
ONE PUNCH, IT'S OVER, VICTORY AFTER VICTORY
ONE PUNCH, KANRYOU, RENSENRENSHOU
I WIN, I ALWAYS WIN, OVERWHELMINGLY
ORE WA KATSU, TSUNE NI KATSU, ASSHOU
POWER, GET POWER
RIGHT TO THE VERY LIMIT
GIRIGIRI GENKAI MADE
HERO
PEOPLE SHOWER ME WITH PRAISE
ORE O TATAERU KOE YA
BUT I DON'T DO THIS FOR THE FAME
KASSAI NANTE HOSHIKU WA NAI SA
HERO
SO I JUST FIGHT EVIL IN SECRET
DAKARA HITOSHIREZU AKU TO TATAKAU
(NOBODY KNOWS WHO HE IS)
COUNTLESS ENEMIES FILL THE SKY
SORA OOI OSHIYOSERU TEKI
BUT I WON'T TURN MY BACK AND FLEE
ORE WA SE WO MUKE WA SHINAI
HERO
I'VE MADE UP MY MIND AND I WON'T GIVE IN
NARABA YURUGINAKI KAKUGO SHITA TAME
A FIGHTING HERO
TATAKAU HERO
A SOLITARY HERO
KODOKU NA HERO
I WANNA BE THE STRONGEST HERO
I WANNA BE A SAIKYOU HERO
Tailor Shop
Could you please give me just a little more—
Are you busy?
No, we were just wrapping things up.
Bye, old man.
See ya tomorrow!
Sorry about that.
Don't worry about it.
You're probably low on funds yourself.
Sort of…
Lately, I haven't been getting many clients.
If I don't do anything,
my arms are gonna get flabby.
But seriously, what did you do this time?
Did you run into someone really powerful?
Yeah.
He was a little bit stronger.
He almost beat me.
I see.
Sorry, but I can't get this done today.
I'll have to hold on to it.
Oh, I'll count on you then.
Oh yeah! There's something I have to show you.
You're always tearing up that tracksuit, right?
So I wanted to make a special one
from a special material.
Heroes are all about the
transformation, you know!
Oh!
A hero suit?
Exactly!
A suit that won't tear apart, a super suit!
Man, this sucks!
The idea came from the Montsuki Hakama.
He gave it a name?!
Montsuki Hakama
Well?
How should I put it?
He obviously included his own tastes…
Nah, but thanks for the offer.
You don't need to
worry about the money.
This has been my childhood dream.
Crap…
I don't really know…
What should I say?
Could it be that…
…you already asked a different tailor?
Hmm? Eh, umm…
I see how it is…
No, that's not it!
It's just that, uh, I thought I'd decide about it
after I've made a name for myself as a hero.
He's done so much for me…
There's no way I can turn him down.
Look…
Do you know why I always
wear that same tracksuit?
It's because I don't want
to forget about my origin.
Until I've made a name for myself,
that tracksuit will remind me where I came from.
I see, so that's how it is.
Nice! He's buying it!
On top of that, it's too early
to call me Montsuki Hakama.
Is that so?
When I'm a professional hero,
I'll come to you myself.
You're right… right now,
you only do this as a hobby.
Tailor Shop
Anyway, I'll be back tomorrow.
See you.
Ah, one more thing!
I know it's just a hobby, but try not to
get too deep into this "hero" work.
Tailor Shop
Lately, things around here
have been really rough.
Tailor Shop
Really?
Yeah.
Tailor Shop
Just have a look around.
All these shops…
All closed down due to lack of business.
He told me he still doesn't have the money.
I see…
In that case, that store will be mine.
But boss, why do you want that old store?
It's not like it'd get you any business.
I'm well aware of that.
I'm not concerned about the money.
The impulse…
There's something inside me,
driving me to destroy everything I can.
Boss, I got the papers for that candy shop.
Nice, good work.
I feel so good.
I can tell it's close…
Just a little more…
For Sale
The tailor was right earlier.
A lot of stores have gone out of business.
And now that I think about it,
crime is really common around here.
On the streets,
in a house,
and that store earlier today.
In just a week, I captured three delinquents.
Is this area really not safe anymore?
What you see here is
the transformation of a rhinoceros beetle.
Wow, it's already started
to transform, professor!
Didn't I tell you that it looks
totally different in its larva form?
How Beetles Transform
Oh, really?
Didn't know about that.
Who is it at this hour?
What a bother…
Do you have the rent?
You do realize you haven't
paid in 3 months, right?
Uh, you see, the thing is,
I don't have the money right now…
I don't know if you're a hero or what…
…but I'm sure there's a way
you can make money with that.
Don't say stuff like that.
Anyway, if you don't pay
the rent by tomorrow…
I'll kick you out for sure.
Crap.
Tailor Shop
You're still young,
why don't you work part time?
It's not that simple.
Don't beat yourself up.
After all, it's cheap, right?
Here you go.
Your tracksuit.
Oh, thanks!
But this tracksuit makes you look
less like a hero and more like a hobo.
Try and be more careful.
I won't be able to help you anymore.
Today's the day, old man.
Alright then, I'll take this as payment.
See ya later!
Who was that guy just now?
I'll have to close down now.
I mortgaged this shop for a loan.
He's from the Niya Niya Loan group.
For some time now, they've been
taking money to insure the shop.
I can't keep up with the
fees and interest anymore.
So you were cheated?
In any case,
the shop closes today.
Why don't you go
to the police for help?
The police wouldn't be able to help.
They operate out of that apartment…
…where even the police can't interfere.
You've probably heard about it.
Nope, what is it?
Huh?
You haven't?
Go straight along this shopping district,
and you'll see a sign that says "Stop, Danger."
Turn left at the junction where you see that sign.
Keep going and you'll see a supermarket.
Got it?
Yeah.
The place is at the end of the narrow
street next to that supermarket.
Listen,
Stay away from those apartments.
That apartment building, now the resting den
of some evil organization, is also known as…
…the house of crime.
Just as I thought.
This is where I live.
No wonder the rent's so low.
You do know what happens
if you can't repay your debt, right?
Hey! Do you know where
to find Niya Niya Loan?
Huh, you need a loan or somethin'?
No, that's not it.
I have business with them.
What the—?
Then find it yourself.
I'm busy right now, dumbass!
Oye, didn't you hear what I just said?!
Is this their base of operations?
Huh? Who is it?
Did you come to pay the rent?
That was close!
I had no idea who was in that room!
Niya Niya Loan, you said?
Yeah.
I heard they operate
from these apartments.
Well, not from this room.
Hey, you!
I don't know whoever it is you're after.
But be careful which room you visit.
Not everyone in this building is as nice as I am.
O-Okay.
I see.
Time to check the other side.
No one's home?
Hold on a second.
Who are you?
Money
Factory
I'm a tenant here.
Tenant? Of these apartments?
Yeah.
I live on the other side.
I'm a hero for fun.
Really? Keep at it, then.
Wait, did you say hero?
Crap. This is bad, big bro!
I think he realized we're counterfeiting!
I get it.
You want to beat us up for the bounty, right?
Bounty?
I don't know if you're a hero or what,
but I'm sure there's a way
you can make money with that.
I see.
So there's a bounty!
No doubt about it, I can see it in his eyes
that he wants to catch us!
Fine…
Catch us if you can!
Huh? That guy…
What?
That guy…
…is kinda freaking me out.
I've gotta warn the boss!
Oh, it's you.
Do you have my caramel macchiato?
Who is that guy? Police?
No, but he beat up a bunch of our guys!
What did you say?
I think he's here.
Money
Is it you?
The dangerous guy that's
been beating my men up?
You… why are you dressed like that?
Are you really the boss of
those Niya Niya Loan guys?
What's it to you?
This is about the tailor shop.
I've come to ask that you return
the store papers to its owner.
I'll be in trouble if there's
no one to fix my clothes.
Don't fuck with me, kid!
You think I'm gonna return them
just because you asked?
Looks like you're pretty
confident in your strength.
But do you really think
brute force can solve everything?
That won't be necessary.
What do you mean?
I think I pretty much get it.
I'll go and talk to them about this now.
Hey, did you hear what I just said?
Yeah. That's why I said that
I'll bring back your papers.
After all, if you close down,
who'll fix my clothes?
Hey, that's not why I brought it up.
Don't worry about it.
I know what I'm doing.
Look at this.
Listen.
If you have overpaid, feel free to contact us
If we're talking about the
maximum legal interest rate,
the tailor's debt has already been paid.
Also, if it goes over the legal maximum,
it's called "overpayment."
In that case, you'll need to return the overpayment back to the shop.
Besides, there's no law that says
you can just take his store.
So please, give back the papers.
You beat up all of my men,
just to tell me this shit?
Huh?
Oh, no.
That was just an accident.
Interesting, isn't it?
Not bad… Not bad at all!
I have a bad feeling about this…
I really should've stopped him.
But, they're not the kind of people
who will understand these things.
Well, I'll see how things go.
And what if something happens to you?
I won't be able to forgive myself.
Like I said, I'll see how things go.
Don't worry.
It may be a hobby, but I'm still a hero.
See ya!
Don't do anything reckless.
Haven't you heard about it?
People like me, who take evil to a whole
new level, we transform into monsters.
Finally, the moment has come-gyu!
Are you speechless from fear?
I see.
I've never seen this before.
I've transformed into
the super strong monster of the sea!
I've become the Fish of Darkness!
No, you haven't transformed.
You're just a pervert.
I learned yesterday.
The caterpillar that hatches from the egg
becomes a pupa until adulthood.
How Beetles Transform
We call this…
Did you say… pervert?
Yes, scientifically speaking.
Me? The Fish of Darkness?!
But you were already
a pervert to begin with.
And when a pervert
gets even more perverted…
You just become a total pervert.
A total perv—
In other words…
A hardcore pervert.
Don't fuck with me-gyu!
I'm a badass villain, not a pervert!
You're not half bad!
Right back at ya.
I think I've reached my limit.
It's not for nothing that I've got an
A-class bounty on my head.
A-class?
What's with that look?
Did you come to pay the rent?
I don't have money.
But I can give you these guys.
Money laundering,
underwear theft, and counterfeiting.
In any case, they all have
high bounties on their heads.
I've already called the police.
That should be enough to pay the rent.
You, do you realize what you've done?
They were my main source of income…
If I wanted the damn police,
I would've called them myself, jackass!
That old lady…
really kicked me out.
I'm glad you're okay, Saitama.
I see.
Well, I'm sorry about that.
I didn't like that place anyway.
I only liked the rent.
What are you gonna do now?
Well, for starters,
I have to find a new place to stay.
There's a rumor going around…
At the edge of City Z, there's a "ghost town"
that's so dangerous it's practically deserted.
Nobody wants to live there anymore.
People say that all the
utilities still work, though.
I see.
That's good.
Saitama!
Thank you for protecting the store.
Yeah, you can count on me.
I'm still closing the store.
For a while now, I've been thinking.
I'm too old for this.
I see.
Then I guess it was inevitable.
I know it won't change much…
Of course, you don't have to
wear it if you don't want to.
But I want you to have this.
This is…
I can finally feel satisfied with my work.
Now that I think about it,
I was looking for an excuse to retire.
This is my greatest achievement.
My masterpiece!
I can already see a real hero in you.
You inspired me to make this suit.
Won't I look like a weirdo in this?
So that's how it happened.
For a while, I was embarrassed to wear it,
so I wore my tracksuit over it.
But I got used to it.
Anyway, it's something important to me.
I see!
So, in order to become a true hero,
you need to have something very
important to you, like you do.
What?
However, Master,
I think it is about time for a new suit.
If it's okay, I'd like to give one
to you as a present, Master.
I don't want it!
Seriously, were you even listening?
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
When my worries keep me awake under the crescent moon
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
All I can do is close my eyes and think of you
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I want to see you, I feel like crying
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I feel so romantic
romantikku na kibun
I hope my feelings reach you
todokete kono omoi
I know so very well
datte zutto shitteiru no
how hard you always work
ganbatteru koto takusan
You're the one I love
daisuki na hito ga
You're so strong, yet still I worry
tsuyokute shinpai
Only I ever see your weakness
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
I'll find you before the stars
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
Come right back home
massugu kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne