Ya came back.
But Ushio's presence disappeared.
I'm so happy that little pest is finally gone.
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps god's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Made in Black
Haine!
Crap!
Akari!
Ya can't come with, Big Bro.
Ya ain't that tasty anyway.
Immunity?
Ya know, Shinpei, since ya just came back,
yer right on the edge.
The event horizon.
I'm right on the edge after looping.
It's all over if I die here.
This is bad!
She was after this result!
Did she turn into a crow and watch me the entire time?
It's useless.
I can't defeat even one alone.
Big Bro!
It's okay, Akari.
I'll protect ya.
No good.
Don't give up.
It's all over if I die.
Get a bird's-eye view of things!
Wait. Stop!
If ya make me loop, ya won't have copied Akari either.
Are ya okay with that?
Or is it that ya can pass over the data ya copied too?
Didn't ya eat all those people at the festival that day?
It's all yer fault.
I used my power to chase after ya that time.
Yer life ends here.
Damn it...
Bye-bye.
Wait!
They stopped?
Damn you!
It flew away.
D-Does this mean the danger is gone fer now?
She disappeared? The strays too?
Why were we saved?
This is...
Dammit!
Wh-What's wrong?
Nothing.
History
Alain
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
I have to call everyone.
Alain
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
But...
Ushio died?
Yes.
The situation has changed.
Let's meet and review our strategy.
Okay.
Where?
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
How about Torajima on the northeast of the island?
That small island you can only reach during low tide?
Yes.
Low tide is in 30 minutes.
I told Mio and Sou too.
I'll meet them at Bistro Kofune before we head out.
Understood.
Let's meet at Torajima in 30 minutes.
Okay.
See you then.
No service
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Your connection is unstable.
Please try again in an area with better reception.
Damn it! I can't get a signal!
Let's get off the mountain quickly!
It's dangerous!
R-Right!
I need to tell everyone that Ushio disappeared!
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Call ended
When did ya copy that body, Haine?
Ya need to think bigger.
Ushio had no memory of it.
It's a hole in their pseudo loops.
Wonderful.
I won't allow Shinpei to survive until tomorrow's ceremony.
Ya got work to do, Shide.
Leave it to me.
Bistro Kofune
We're back!
W-Where's Mio?
She went out with Sou to meet ya.
That was about 30 minutes ago.
Did they say where they were going?
I didn't hear anything about that.
Shinpei! What happened?
Please watch those kids!
Are ya hungry?
W-We...
I'll have some mixed fruit juice, please!
The number you dialed is either out of service,
or their phone is turned off.
Meeting me?
Is there a shadow of me?
Why?
I wasn't copied this time.
I already prevented my being copied at the funeral and at Koba Mart.
No.
That's wrong!
Ya wanna copy him too?
No. He's already been copied by Mother.
It was Haine who copied me!
Haine came from the end of the festival in the third loop.
My shadow from then is being used now!
But I don't get how she used my phone.
Even if she copied it, she has to eliminate the original.
Shin?
From my room?
Why are ya here?
Mio! Who did this?!
No way. So that call...
Ow...
Ya coulda taken 'em out more gently.
S-Sorry.
I'll give ya my memories.
Mio?!
Sis died.
We can't risk her hacking getting reversed.
Ya heard what Shin said!
She might become our enemy again!
No way.
Mio did it?
Ya called her and told her Sis died.
Is that true?
Yes.
But I didn't call her.
My shadow tricked them.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect Mio, though.
I knew yer shadow existed.
I saw it in Sis's pseudo loop.
I also heard ya say that Shiori, which is to say Haine, copied ya and created it.
Right.
But I can't believe my phone and a copy can work and exist simultaneously.
I was careless.
I just remembered.
During the third loop, it also copied my phone.
That was sucked into Haine's body at the end.
I see.
So Haine brought it over to this eighth loop.
This is bad.
Haine knows Ms. Nagumo's memories and her phone number.
Where'd Mio and Sou go?
Ms. Nagumo.
Hello?
Yo.
It's me.
My voice.
How's it feel to get a call from yerself?
Haine?
How do ya have Ms. Nagumo's phone?
What happened?
Come see fer yerself, Observer.
Hizuru and the others are on Torajima.
Mio and Sou are in Alain's field.
It's up to ya which group ya wanna save.
W-Wait!
Hello?
It hung up.
Calm down, Shin.
Think about different possibilities.
I know!
Haine is thinking with yer mind right now.
She's also taking a bird's-eye view.
Take a bird's-eye view.
Why would Haine go through this effort?
Searchlight Ruins
Navy Listening Station Ruins
First Battery Ruins
Third Battery Ruins
Hitogashima Elementary School
Hitogashima Junior High
Hitogashima Lighthouse
Transmission Tower
Mt. Takanosu
Hishigata Clinic
Bistro Kofune
Second Battery Ruins
Omoto Beach
Hamaji Market
Club Miyako
Koba Mart
Alain's Field
Hitogashima Port
Ja River
Shinja Pond
Funeral Home
Crematorium
Graveyard
Shrine Grove
Fourth Battery Ruins
Hito Shrine
Torajima
Quarry Ruins
Do I go for Mio or Ms. Nagumo?
She may be lying and everyone is dead.
Even still, I can't just do nothing.
It's better to regret doing something than regret doing nothing.
Gather everything that can be a weapon!
Everything!
Summer Time Rendering
10 minutes earlier
Alain's field
Why are ya here,
Mr. Karikiri?
Such impressive cucumbers.
Alain is so good at growing vegetables.
Ain't that right, Mio?
Get back, Mio!
I usually like rice bran pickles,
but I got the taste fer vinegar pickles after eating 'em here.
Nothing like the taste of France.
What'd ya do with Shinpei?!
But Mother hates both.
What a pickle.
How do people taste?
Simultaneously
Torajima
What happened?
This terrain is dangerous.
Wh-What do ya mean?
Hizuru, was it really Shinpei on the phone?
Even Ryuunosuke can't tell if it's a human or shadow on the phone.
It certainly came from Ajiro Shinpei's phone.
Ushio was killed, right?
Maybe Shinpei was already killed too.
Yes, that's possible.
Shinpei's loop may've been cut off and
we've entered the world observed by Haine.
That doesn't change what we must do.
Kill Haine.
That's all.
Can you call Mio?
No.
We don't have any signal here.
Alain said before that Mio and my brother went out to meet Shinpei.
Hopefully, they're headed this way.
Mio.
I'll cross to Torajima alone first.
Can you shoot from here, Nezu?
Yeah, but only on the southern part of the island.
That's enough.
I'll send you a signal if Shinpei is a shadow.
Tokiko, charge in with Gil and Rose when that happens.
I understand.
Then Totsumura...
Why are you here again?
What?
Whatever.
Just survive.
Huh?
O-Okay.
What about yer weapon?
I have this.
Don't let your guard down.
I'll come back here if I confirm that it's really Shinpei.
Gotcha!
See ya soon, Hizuru.
You're so tactless, old man.
Don't raise them death flags so quickly.
What? Flags?
I'll write a novel about my experiences here once this battle is over.
I've never written non-fiction before.
Lightly, but surely, it echoes in my head.
A sound that grinds on the nerves, like nails on a chalkboard.
I feel it.
A shadow.
No, this is Haine.
I need to draw it toward me for Nezu to have a shot.
Can it read my mind?
Ms. Nagumo!
I'm glad you're okay.
Where's everyone else?
Quit your lousy acting, Haine.
I can see you transformed.
Where is Shinpei?
I said I'd kill ya the next time we met 14 years ago.
That was right here.
Goodbye, Ryuunosuke.
Impressive.
Are you Shide, Karikiri Masahito?
But you're human.
I don't sense a shadow in you.
Did you sneak up behind Ushio and kill her like that?
Oh my. This trick didn't work.
Yer powers of precognition are quite impressive,
Minakata Ryuunosuke.
So you knew my secret.
I copied Minakata Ryuunosuke 14 years ago.
However, my human personality at the time couldn't face the guilt of eating my friend's brother.
Part of me exploded,
and Ryuunosuke's data went along with.
But things went slightly wrong.
The coordinates were a bit off when they got printed.
Coordinates?
Ow.
Not of space, but coordinates of time.
There's a two-second gap, to be precise.
Oh my.
He's moving Hizuru's body from two seconds in the future.
Is that right, Hizuru?
I know ya can hear me, Hizuru.
Ya got close to Haine and confused her.
It's yer fault that she was deeply hurt.
She got weaker.
Now she can only survive here fer a few months.
This is yer fault, Hizuru.
Haine's having to leave.
Yer precious brother's death.
It's all yer fault, Hizuru!
What was that?!
I won't let ya hurt my sister anymore!
Ya can't beat me, Ryuunosuke.
Haine's eye can observe the next two seconds and tell it to me.
This means yer two-second advantage is meaningless.
This is mud.
Formerly shadows, but now just nothing.
I'll tell ya about my abilities.
Games must be fair to be interesting.
This changes shape as I will it.
How disgusting.
How many people are in that?
What would Sis call that?
Globs of corpses?
No.
Because it's no one, it has no weakness.
An armor of corpses.
It's time to take this seriously.
I knew it.
Sis was right.
Ya want to make me dodge and then strike me after.
But Shide can't see where I am two seconds ahead.
Haine sees it and tells Shide through telepathy.
There's a tiny time lag.
I need to move quicker.
Even quicker!
I just need to move quicker!
Amazing how ya can move like that with a human body.
But it appears ya pushed yerself too far.
Ya reopened yer wounds.
I gave ya that one last night.
Ya had to cover Shinpei.
That ain't all.
There was a fracture in my right arm.
My muscles are also torn.
Sis's body can't take much more.
As much as it pains me, just running away is impossible.
I sent the signal.
If I can get into Nezu's range,
he can provide me some cover to escape.
Wait.
Sis?
Don't run away.
Don't run away, Ryuunosuke.
Is that Hizuru?
Wh-What?
Why am I awake while Sis is controlling the body?
I'm talking with Sis in real-time fer the first time!
No way! Is this a dream?
Hey! Why?
Jeez, just shut up!
This is an emergency.
I'm out of options.
Sis!
I'm so glad.
Listen closely, Ryuunosuke.
We can win.
As long as Ajiro Shinpei may be alive, we need to fight.
We'll just die tomorrow if we run.
But—
Don't think.
Let me do the thinking.
You saw it.
That material goes beyond common sense.
However, he's just a human if we can remove that armor.
Listen.
You're the only one who can pull this off.
I'll give you control of the body.
Give it your all, Ryuunosuke.
Yer holding back to avoid harming me, aren't ya?
I ain't worried if my body is destroyed.
Use it to the fullest!
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time