Koto.
I know what you've kept secret from everyone until now.
I better should as your father.
What brought this on?
It isn't fair, though...
Well, let me tell you one of my secrets in return then.
What is it?
That.
That's my secret.
What do you mean?
I don't get it, Master.
It's okay.
It's gonna work out.
I hope you're right...
I love you, Koto.
I know, Dad.
I love you too.
I know.
Comic Movie of Crazy People Living Every Day to its Fullest.
Chapter Twenty Eight
Present (22)/ Laws
I'm not going to apologize.
Koto,
I love you.
I love you and Koto,
Yakushimaru, Yase and Kurama.
I love all who inhabit my world.
You taught me that word long ago.
Thing is, I can't love myself the same way.
I keep doubting myself,
Koto.
God
Our father entrusted the perfect
world he wished for to my brother,
God
and governing it means keeping the things in it as they are.
So what's my job?
I can create life.
Rebirth and devastation are in my hands.
My power contradicts my role as an observer.
Why would our father give me
this power and then leave me be?
What is he expecting from me?
Do you know anything about that, Koto?
Tell me!
Just like when you suddenly showed up!
Tell me, please!
Can't a buddha have mercy on a god?
You have no self-control. It's like you're a child.
All you do ends in drama.
You're free, selfish, and rebellious.
You do whatever you want.
You're a cold troublemaker,
but you also indulge in the love of others.
Greedy and sad.
The buddha said my love could save you,
but I still don't understand you.
The cruel world you broke was you yourself, wasn't it, Head Priest?
To let your wish reach the heavens,
you gave your heart to Koto, didn't you?
You wanted to change darkness into light,
so you gave your beads to Yakushimaru, didn't you?
You're not very smart, are you?
You didn't have to go to such lengths.
You could have told them that they are your hope incarnate.
But who'd ever want to be told something like that?
Yakushimaru definitely wouldn't.
They totally hate me.
What now?
That's the side of you I love.
It's the reason I could leave Koto in your care.
She knows
what your love and doubt are like.
Don't worry.
Yakushimaru, Yase, and Kurama, all your children, know.
Go back and help them.
The world will end for good otherwise.
Yakushimaru... might not be strong enough to carry your beads just yet.
Dear?
I risked myself
so that I could love myself eventually.
I can't stop here.
Don't worry.
The world won't end from this.
Worst case is that I will vanish.
They call me a god,
but I couldn't rescue you from this prison.
Koto overtook me.
I'm sure they will make my wish come true, even if I can't.
Before I met you,
the world was no more than a fleeting illusion for me.
But then there were you and the children,
and I finally had my own world.
Don't disappear, Koto.
You must live.
Koto?
Don't you dare make Mom cry!
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Chapter
Twenty
Nine
(Past ->)
Present (23)/
Thing (Koto)
Hey...
Are you crazy?!
Accepted life yet?
Isn't that what using the beads represents?
You just use saving the Mirror Capital as an excuse.
Honestly, I have no idea.
But this isn't the time. Not just yet.
I can't die just yet.
Neither me nor the Mirror Capital.
Amazing...
Where are we?
Dunno...
In Heaven.
Your faces tell tales about how clueless you are.
Your brains control everything in this wonderful place.
Welcome, my dear grandchildren.
I'm happy to see you.
Who are you?
Your
father's
father.
What does the head priest's father have to do with this?
I smell a scolding because Myoue failed!
Fear not.
The world was rebuilt and the thirteenth planet was accepted. All is well.
That is why I summoned you, my grandchildren.
God
Replace my son as the next god.
Chapter Thirty
Present (30)/ Here
No problem!
Huh.
Something wrong?
Impossible
It's just...
But I caused so much trouble...
Duty
(tentative)
Grandad called us here and all.
One thing troubles me, though.
What exactly does it mean to replace Dad?
Once the decision is made,
the soul will be inherited,
the laws of nature will change,
and my son will be erased from existence.
Then I'll pass.
Huh?
I don't want Dad to vanish.
But this is his wish.
Really? Like, really?
True
False
Really really.
True
False
Really really?
Really really.
Where and when'd he say that?
Which cycle of the planes?
Just leave it be.
Dad never says what he really means!
You know that too, Myoue!
He'd never truly wish to be erased!
Koto...
I'll go ask him.
I'll go and ask him directly!
You wouldn't want to get him erased on a whim, right?
Yup.
Hang tight for a sec, Grandpa!
We just gotta talk to Dad real quick.
Sorry, the rest...
...will have to wait.
Present
Past
Future
Present
Past
Future
Present
Past
Future
Present
Past
Future
Present
Past
Future
Present
Past
Future
Present
Past
Future
Present
Past
Future
What's going on?
Holy me on a pogo stick.
Myoue,
I've been wondering.
Can we stay together a little longer?
We've come all this way and even came back to life and all.
I can promise I'll finish everything off.
Let's stay together just a little longer.
Live, Myoue.
Just live.
Even if you'd rather not,
just give it a try for me.
That'd sure make me happy.
Dad!
Mother?
Let's be happy!
All of us together, as best we can,
until we bite the dust...
I'm sure when we pursue happiness,
we can always start over.
Here!
Dad!
There you are!
Yakushimaru?
Hey! Koto!
Are you trying to kill him?
Stand aside!
Yakushimaru!
He told us
that you want to leave your job to Myoue and me and just get yourself erased.
Couldn't you at least pretend to care?
I just hate my karma...
Are you okay, Yakushimaru?
Worry about yourself, Mom.
Yakushimaru?
I don't get it.
Gramps!
Didn't you return to talk with him?
I have some questions too.
What are they even doing?
You can't tell?
A child is arguing with her father.
It sounds really nice when you say "I love you,"
but you have no idea what's going on!
Then do you, Koto?
We used to
watch the sunset together, right?
We used to eat together, right?
That! Is! Love!
Fighting about unimportant things,
laughing at stupid jokes,
or coming home five minutes early!
That! Is! Love!
Laughing and crying and anger and happiness...
We used to share all that, didn't we?
That! Is! Love!
You taught me that...
Then why
would you want to disappear alone?
I don't want that!
I love you so much!
Don't go away, Master!
Mom!
Yase!
Bro!
Koto!
A! Un!
Decision time.
Your children will inherit your soul and you get to stay.
Dad?!
Shift's over.
I get to stay?
But I won't have anything left!
I'll...
Dad!
What's wrong with just being?
I'd say that's enough of a reason,
my son.
Dad!
Take your stuff back.
Now give it to me.
Have you come to like being alive?
Dunno.
But I hope I will one day.
I'll think about it when I die again.
Who even says "when I die again"?
Can it.
Dad,
I don't think I could ever replace you.
But I'll stay by your side and help you as much as I can.
We can eat and joke and laugh together.
Just like until now.
That's all I can show you about the world.
I told you she'd be fine.
She's your daughter after all.
You raised her.
Koto!
You did great, cutie.
You taught a lesson to your stupid father.
So many selfish people here.
I don't want my family to disappear!
So Dad!
So Father!
Come back to us!
I've taken your beads,
but the Mirror Capital is your home, and you built it.
Right, Dad?
It's been a while since I last saw you cry.
You never did, in fact.
I did!
No.
Yes, I did!
Very rarely.
Even I get fed up with my job sometimes.
Why would you say that, sir?
It is thanks to you the world is not reduced to nothingness.
I just did my job.
Too gloomy.
Want to sit in my chair?
I'll pass.
Only you can sit there.
Will you return?
I'll drop in.
Freedom is nice.
You're my age, aren't you?
I can accept this place as my home, just as any other
Goodbye, Sun
Night falls to draw me in
We'll be fine, because this world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we followed.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up