Don't worry about it, Haruka-chan.
Nayu-chan...
Don't rush it.
Tie!
I stayed awake all night thinking about this bra-unhooking competition,
and figured we might be able to use it for the cultural festival!
There's no way in hell that'll fly!
You're a bit slow, Timpani!
Aww, I messed up, what should I do?
This needs a bit more work...
The general public's gonna see us at the cultural festival!
If you're not careful, the boys will come sniffing around for something erotic!
Don't worry, I got a great idea.
I shall call it "The Heart-Racing Bras for Boys" corner!
It sounds like a lot of people will come thinking of something else.
The best way to understand underwear is to actually try them on!
There are also bras for men too.
Men's bra?
Yes. It's a bra designed for men.
It supposedly feels great when worn.
Senpai.
Tamoki, will you help me put on bras from now on?
Of course! It would be my pleasure!
W-What?
Don't stare at me.
Hey! You guys are thinking something weird, aren't you?!
Hey, do you have any ideas, Amahara-san?
Are you about to perform some finishing move?
It's just a form of exercise.
What's with this all of a sudden?
Nothing, really. It doesn't really matter what it is.
I know it's a bit late to tell you, but I won't be able to participate in club activities for a while.
I've got to get ready for the photo-shoot.
Photo-shoot?
My mom's designer is releasing a new underwear line for teens.
And I'm gonna be the catalogue model.
WHAT?!
You're a model?! Wow!
This is the first time I've heard about it!
That's amazing!
Your mom's an underwear designer?
I didn't tell you guys? She's Orarisu Apparel's president.
What?! By Orarisu, do you mean that Orarisu?!
You've heard of it?
Of course! Orarisu's underwear are sophisticated and glamorous!
Please let us help out with the photo shoot, Amahara-san!
Please!
Pleaseeee!
All right, if you insist. I'll have you help me...
With a lot of things.
Thanks! I'll do whatever you ask!
Alright then, I'll use your skills to push them up.
Huh?
So this is one of those push-up bras I keep hearing about?
Don't push, Amahara-san!
It's crowded in here!
I've never seen anything like this.
That's because you don't need something like this, Shiraishi-san.
That's not what I meant...
Oh, it has pads in it.
It raises the breasts up from the bottom.
The pad on the opposite sides lifts your breasts up and gives you more cleavage.
It sounds so high-tech.
That's far from being high-tech.
Hurry up and put it on me!
There you go.
Hey...
Eh?
What is this? Is this as high as they will go?
Even if you say that...
T-That's because you don't have any extra skin on your under arms or on your back...
Well, whatever.
My breasts will grow if I leave this on, right?
Uh, I don't think so...
What, you want to make your breasts bigger?
O-Of course not!
I just want to look my best for the photo-shoot!
Get out now!
This place is brimming with thin fabrics to encase the female form!
Umm...
Are you looking for something?
I've been on a search!
We need to find suitable underwear for these costumes!
We don't have anything like that here...
How we have searched! All that awaits us is darkness and despair!
Our short-lived days filled with hope have disappeared!
Angela! You mustn't forget that all you have to do is reach out your hand and I will be there!
Charles-sama, you are the sole light that pierces my darkness!
Bravo, Angela!
Bravo, Charles!
They're wearing our school uniform...
They're exactly the type I don't want to get involved with.
Bravo!
I'm really sorry, but I won't be able to help you with just this picture as a reference...
Oh, my beloved Angela!
Let us steel our hearts and overcome this darkness!
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Underwear that suites these costumes, huh?
Who're you?
Nayu! Amahara-san's calling for you!
But I was still talking to them!
We can't get you to shut up when you start talking about underwear!
Alright!
One, two, criss cross.
Circle circle three four!
One two, one two!
One, two...
One....
Two....
Keep it up!
What are they doing?
There's no change...
What the hell is going on?!
They're not growing at all even though you tried so hard...
Why don't you try pulling on them as hard as you can with a vacuum cleaner or something?
There's no way in hell that'd work!
It hasn't gone up or down...
She really tried the vacuum cleaner...
You could also try manipulating your hormones by looking at pictures of macho men or something.
Are you an idiot?! You sure seem to come up with a lot of crazy ideas!
Still no change up or down...
She really did look at pictures of macho men...
Finally, the photo-shoot is tomorrow!
You did everything you could, so you'll be fine!
I'm sure you'll do great!
Of course I will, I don't need you to tell me that!
But, well... You guys really did help me a lot.
Ahh, being young is great!
What're we gonna do about the cultural festival?
I sure am looking forward to tomorrow's photo-shoot.
Amahara-san really tried her best.
In fact, it's the first time I have seen her work so hard.
I've changed my opinion about her.
Up until now, she's kind of been...
Keigo-san?
You're burning it, Keigo-san!
Geez... Get a hold of yourself...
Ah, I really am looking forward to tomorrow's photo-shoot.
We're all set over here.
She must be pretty nervous.
This is way different than us taking pictures with our digital cameras.
Of course it is.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Amahara Reika, Kiyono's mom. I've heard all about you from my daughter.
T-Thank you very much for letting us be here today!
I love underwear, and umm... My brother also works in the underwear industry.
Umm... Would you be Hayama-san?
Yes!
And by chance, is your brother Keigo Amahara-kun, Paradiso's underwear designer?
The one who formerly worked for Jewelry's...
Yes!
What's Jewelry's?
Oh, you're ready?
It's Hayama-san's grandmother's brand.
All of their designs are superb.
It was a great brand.
Thank you so much!
Let's get some test shots!
You look a little stiff.
That's much better.
Okay moving on! I'm going get some close-ups of your chest.
Turn your body.
Look this way.
Ah, Suzuki-san!
Done already?
Thanks to you, yes.
Isn't your bra a little loose?
It really is loose.
That can't be.
Is it the wrong size?
But that's what it said on the application form...
Kiyono! Did you write down a size bigger than yours?
I'm sorry, let's take a break.
What's going on?
It seems like a huge fuss.
You really do such pointless things...
Go get changed right n-
Kiyono?!
Amahara-san...
Amahara-san, can we come in?
This sucks...
Amahara-san...
Even though he was here...
I'm going home!
W-What do you mean going home?
Everyone's waiting for you.
She's right.
Leaving right in the middle of something violates the warrior's code of-
Leave me alone!
Whatever I do is no concern of yours, is it?!
Hey, what's with your attitude?!
What are those?
They're prototypes, not something I'm supposed to wear.
But these are much better.
Huh? Something that lame?
But they look much more comfortable.
That's got nothing to do with it!
There's no point if guys don't find them cute!
But we're still too young for underwear like that.
Are you trying to say that I'm childish?
That's not what I meant.
I just think these would suit you much better.
No way!
I'll just disappoint guys if I wear something like that!
A decorated cellphone...
I've got it!
I think it's fun to decorate your own underwear!
Please let us try!
I see.
Alright then.
I'll leave it up to you girls.
I'll get what you need right away.
Thank you very much!
Ahh, these are so cute!
Check this one out!
This one would look great on her!
A-As if! That's way too lame!
It'll be alright.
This would make a great strap.
Cute! Is there a color it'd go with?
Ah, that one!
This ribbon's cute too. We could use it to decorate something.
Why don't we try combining it with lace?
We could do a one point stitch on this.
That one's nice too!
Ah! I just happened to see it by chance!
I don't really have any plans for it-
Hurry it up, will you?!
Patience, patience!
Designing your own underwear, huh?
This could make a good article.
Its not like I don't know how you feel.
It takes courage to get naked in front of people.
Especially for girls like us.
What are you trying to say?
Well, ya know...
I'm just saying good luck.
It's done!
How cute!
It looks great on you.
Really? It's not lame?
Definitely not!
Its not childish either?
It is not!
This is great!
Its strong, mature, and cute.
Yeah, she looks much more mature than before.
Great job!
We got some great shots.
Thank you very much.
That was really great, Amahara-san!
Well, how did you like the design?
Well, its not bad considering you made it.
Hey! Thank Hayama-san!
Thanks...
Please allow me to show my gratitude as well.
Thanks to you, I was able to learn what kind of underwear teens want to wear these days.
Oh, it was nothing...I might have gone a bit overboard...
Not at all.
You certainly are Hayama-kun's little sister.
I'm really grateful.
Oh yeah, speaking of which, Hayama-kun got picked for a huge project at such a young age.
Could you convey my congratulations to him?
S-Sure. Thank you!
Also,
if it's alright with you girls, I would like to give you some of my new products as a present.
WHAT?!
Can we really have them?!
Yes. They're in the anteroom. Pick whichever you like.
Thank you very much!
Let's go try them on!
Hey!
Wai-! Nayu-chan! You don't have to rush us... !
But, there's stuff that'd look great on you two...
I wonder if she'll be going to Kyoto too...
Huh?
Haven't you heard? Hayama-san's brother...
No way...
Hey, isn't this amazing?
She really is stylish when you look at her like this.
M-Master!  Could it be that our master was at the photo-shoot as well?!
Like hell I was!
And who are you calling "master"?!
Hey, isn't that...
Yeah, she really gets me going!
Even her walk is great!
Should we ask for her autograph?
We saw the magazine.
The Underwear Appreciation Society is amazing!
No, not really...
This really bothers me...
Yeah, all they are is a bra and panties club.
I'm surprised they're still active.
I've finally found you, angel of the cloth!
W-Well.....
Carry us to heaven with your shining wings and dazzling eyes!
We, the Acting Club, need your assistance.
We learned that your the girl who spoke to us in the underwear store,
is also running the Underwear Appreciation Society from reading this magazine.
And what do you want with us?
Please have a look at this!
This is the picture from before...
We've plunged deep into the Promised Land of acting, only to lose our director!
Ah! We were lost strangers!
Lost without guidance, our days were darkened by despair!
Then you descended before us!
You angels of the cloth!
Umm....
They mean that even though we've sketched up a rough drawing of our costumes,
we know absolutely nothing about underwear.
Can humans and angels understand one another, Charles-sama?
There's nothing to be afraid of, Angela.
I'm sure they will respond to your pure intentions!
Yes, Charles-sama!
So, we were wondering if you would help us out with this for the cultural festival.
Does that mean we could participate in the cultural festival?
Nayu-chan.
The answer is pretty obvious, isn't it?
Yeah!
Please allow us to help you!
We did it, Nayu-chan!
Let's all do our best!
Yeah!
Then it's decided! We'll be participating in the cultural festival.
Oh? That's great.
It's finally the Underwear Appreciation Society's time to shine.
M-Maybe.
Oh yeah! You also had something good happen to you, didn't you?
Huh?
I heard it yesterday from Amahara-san's mom.
You got chosen for a huge project, right?
So you found out about it?
It means I have to go to Kyoto...
Huh?
Don't you think boys would want to wear underwear trimmed with lace, ribbons, and frills?
Like hell they would!
Why not?
Huh? I wonder why?
You guys are utterly hopeless.