I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but then a small incident happened.
What I believed in was my courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
Even if your feelings have been shattered,
even if your wishes are far away...
...please don't forget the kindness of those nearby.
Many people are supporting your heart, and many
people are waiting to see your smile.
So fill yourself with your feelings,
and put your wishes on the line.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
Dimensional disturbance outbreak!
It's rapidly increasing in size!
At this rate, a dimensional dislocation
will occur in less than thirty minutes!
The items that act as the energy source for the Garden
are similar to the Jewel Seeds, the Lost Logia.
She's performing a very strong, forced activation on
them to compensate for the lack of other materials.
Well... we were planning on this being
a one-way trip since the beginning...
Chrono-kun! Where are you going?
I'm going where the action is.
If we don't strike this down at the source...
I'll go with you!
Me too!
Understood.
Arf, stay with Fate.
Y-Yeah.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Chrono, Nanoha-san, Yuuno-kun, I'll be there shortly.
Until I arrive, you three are to focus
on arresting Precia Testarossa!
Understood!
The Time of the Sealing of Our Fates.
There's a lot of them...
This is just the entrance.
There'll be even more inside.
Chrono-kun, what are these things?
Simple robots programmed to attack
any enemy within range.
I see. Everything's fine, then.
You don't need to waste your
time on enemies of this level.
Stinger Snipe.
So fast...!
Snipe Shot!
Break Impulse.
Don't just stand there staring! Let's get going!
Yeah!
Also, you guys should be careful
not to step in the black areas.
They're imaginary paths. All magic, without exception,
will stop working if you enter one of them.
They'll also nullify any aviation magic you can
use, so if you were to fall into one of them...
...due to the strength of the gravity here, you'd fall...
...and never escape.
I-I'll be careful.
We'll split into two teams here.
You two head to the top floor and work
on sealing the energy source.
What about you, Chrono-kun?
I'm going to see Precia. After all, that's my job.
I'll carve out a path for you, so you two...!
Yeah!
Blaze Cannon.
Chrono-kun! Be careful!
I'll also be heading out.
I'll forge a distortion shield within the Garden and
suppress the emergent dimensional distortion.
I'm worried about those guys, so...
I'm gonna go help out a little too, okay?
I'll be right back. And then, once everything is over...
...even if it takes a long time, you'll return
to the real Fate I love so much, okay?
Because from now on, you can use
your time as freely as you please.
To the end, Mother never smiled at me...
I wanted to live... because I wanted
Mother to accept me...
No matter how often she told me I wasn't good
enough... no matter what bad things she did to me...
I just... wanted her to smile at me.
Even though she's so clearly abandoned
me now... I'm... still clinging to her.
Arf...
Arf, who's always stayed by my side...
I've probably made her so sad, since I never
listened to anything she had to say...
And that white-clad girl I've run into so many times...
She was the first person who could fight me as my
equal and face me with such uprightness and honesty...
We've met many times already... and fought...
And she called out my name countless times...
Time and time again...
I wanted to continue living because
I wanted Mother to accept me.
I thought that was the only reason to live.
I thought that if that wasn't possible,
I might as well stop living.
I can't just throw away everything
I've done up to now, right?
I can't even possibly think... of running away now.
For me...
For us, nothing has begun yet...
I wonder if that's really so, Bardiche...?
Maybe I haven't even truly begun yet...?
Get Set.
That's right... you've always been
by my side too, Bardiche.
I can't just let things with you end like this, right...?
Yes, sir.
I'm not sure if I can pull this off,
but let's give our best together, okay?
Recovery.
Nothing has even begun between us yet...
That's why, in order to start anew as my true self...
I'm done with the way I've been up to now.
Geez! There's so many of them!
Well, we'll be okay if this is it, but...!
I need to do something about this!
Nanoha!
Thunder Rage.
Get Set.
Thunder... Rage!
Fate?!
One of the more powerful models...
it has a strong barrier!
Yeah... and those things attached to its back...
But.. if we fight it together...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go, Bardiche!
Get Set.
Us too, Raising Heart!
Stand by. Ready.
Thunder...
...Buster!
Divine... Buster!
Here we go...!
So, they've come...
But they're too late now...
Right, Alicia...?
Alicia...
Fate-chan!
Fate! Fate!
Fate!
Arf...
I'm sorry for worrying you.
Please let me finish things here.
After that, I can finally start anew... as the true me.
Just a little longer...
You can head to the source from
that elevator over there.
Yeah! Thanks.
And Fate-chan, you're going to where your Mother is?
Yes.
I... um... I can't say it very well, but...
Good luck.
Thank you.
Chrono's heading that way alone!
If we don't hurry, we may not make it in time!
Fate!
Yeah!
Amy!
Nanoha-chan and Yuuno-kun have successfully
infiltrated the power core...
...while Fate-chan and Arf are heading towards
the lowest level of the Garden.
It'll be fine. I'm sure we can do this.
Yeah.
I'll take care of our defense.
You concentrate on sealing them, Nanoha.
Yeah. Just like always, right?
Yuuno-kun, you've always been by
my side... protecting me, right?
Sealing Mode.
That's why I can fight.
Because I always have such warmhearted
friends watching my back!
Let's go!
Divine Shooter! Full Power!
Shoot!
Precia Testarossa.
This is the end of the line.
I am suppressing the dimensional disturbance.
Your source of power will soon be sealed,
and my head Enforcer is heading this way right now.
The forgotten capital, Alhazred.
We don't even know whether the hidden technology
that supposedly lays in wait there even exists.
It's nothing more than a legend.
You're wrong.
The path to Alhazred is in the
interval between dimensions.
As soon as dimensional space is shattered,
the brilliant glow that surges out of that interval...
...the path is certainly through that!
That's an unlikely bet you're taking.
What do you even plan to do there?
You say you wish to reclaim your lost time
and rectify the mistakes of your past?
That's right. I will take it all back.
The past and future that belong to me and Alicia!
I'll regain it all...
It was never meant to be this way...
not any bit of this world I'm living in!
The world... is always filled with things
that were never meant to be!
Since long ago, at any time, or whoever's
involved... that's how the world is!
Do you plan to run away from a reality that
wasn't supposed to be? Or will you face it?
It's up to you!
But no one has the right to interfere
with other people's lives...
...just because of her own selfish sadness!
Mother!
What did you come here for?
Disappear. I no longer have any need of you.
I've come to tell you something.
I...
I... am not Alicia Testarossa.
I may just be a doll you created.
However, I... Fate Testarossa...
was born by you and raised by you.
I am your daughter!
So what? You expect me to think
of you as my daughter now?
If you wish...
If you wish, I will protect you from anyone
or anything in this entire world.
Not because I'm your daughter.
But because... you're my mother!'
I'm not interested.
This is bad!
Captain! You can't stay there!
The Garden is going to collapse!
Please return to the ship!
A dimensional dislocation won't be
able to occur after the collapse!
Chrono-kun and the rest of you, please escape too!
There's no time left before it completely caves in!
Understood!
Fate Testarossa!
FATE!
I'm going... to Alhazred!
And I will regain everything!
Both my past, and my future!
I will regain the single happiness I once had!
Mother!
Fate!
Let's go together.. Alicia.
We won't be separated this time...
Fate!
Everyone, please! Escape! Hurry!
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
The end of our performance
has finally come.
The conclusion is finally upon us,
as is the time of farewells.
But an ending is always...
the beginning of something else.
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Final Episode:
Call My Name.
Lyrical Magical.
We'll see each other again, right?