[sighs]
[sneezes]
Look at this, he mentions
that phrase again here.
Yet another term for gold,
it's gotta be some
kind of pattern.
[WINRY]
What are you trying to do?
We believe there's
a chance these notes
were written in code.
You think so?
Alchemists are
typically very protective
of their research and methods...
They bury the
meaning of their notes
beneath a layer of
metaphor and allegory...
But these are almost straightforward...
There's something
else going on.
[MAY CHANG] We noticed that
he uses several different terms
for gold and immortality
across various passages...
So we're checking to
see if they're connected.
[WINRY] And you think...
that could be the code?
[MAY CHANG]
We're hoping so.
[AL]
Where am I?
[WINRY]
Al!
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse!
[WINRY]
Thank goodness you're okay...!
I was so scared you
might not wake up--
I didn't know what to do.
[AL]
Oh... Sorry...
I didn't mean to
freak you out like that.
So where are we...?
And why am I in pieces?
[WINRY]
And that's basically it.
[SCAR]
As for why you're in pieces,
you were too heavy
to carry whole...
So we had to dismantle you.
[AL]
Ah. That makes sense...
Sorry to put you
guys out like that...
[WINRY] Has this ever
happened to you before?
[AL]
Just once...
When I was trying
to find you guys.
Well then...
I can't imagine
it's very comfortable
being scattered
about like that...
Why don't we start
putting you back together?
[AL]
Please... If you don't mind.
Can you hold onto
this while we fix him?
Now let's see.... This goes...
Isn't that a part of
his right shoulder?
Oh, yes seems to be...
I guess we should
reassemble him correctly.
[MAY CHANG]
Reassemble...
The pieces...
What are you doing, May?!
What have you done?
How could you be
so careless, May?!
[MAY CHANG] We need to
rearrange the pieces.
What if we try
connecting each occurrence
of the words for
gold and immortality
by physically overlapping them?
"An immortal being"...
This phrase appears
earlier in the notes.
[MAY CHANG] "A true being"...
That overlaps here.
[MARCOH]
Now where did I see this...
Here!
[SCAR] Let me take a look at
those other pages, Marcoh.
[MAY CHANG] "Golden"!
That connects over here.
[SCAR]
And what about "aurelian"?
[MAY CHANG]
Oh, yeah... Right here.
[MARCOH]
That's the last one.
[MAY CHANG]
Oh...! I wonder if we...
It can't be!
[AL] It's the countrywide
transmutation circle.
It's too late for
this to help us now.
Wait, are you saying
what I think...
You mean these
damned research notes
are completely
useless to us?!
No way, you
can't be serious...
But what about the--
What's gonna happen to
our families, our country?!
I'm sorry...
I should've known
this was nothing
but an act of futility...
It was naiÃ ̄ve to think someone
else's research could save us.
[SCAR]
Brother...
Is this really all that
you were trying to tell me?
After all of your research...
You couldn't see
a way to stop this?
[AL]
We're missing something.
We've only broken
the first code...
And I bet there's more...
There's gotta be some other
message hidden in there!
[sneezes]
Whoa, can't you cover
your mouth, you idiot!
Well thanks for caring
that I'm getting sick...!
I can't help the fact
that I'm catching pneumonia!
Who cares?!
You can't even tell
which side of the page
is right side up anymore.
[AL gasps]
[GERSO]
Good job, moron...
You blew the whole
damn thing upside down.
[AL]
That's gotta be it!
You take a bad situation
and turn it around...!
There's two sides!
We've gotta put it back
together and then flip it over!
[AL]
Well?
You were right, Al.
This is it... It's a new
Amestrian transmutation circle.
But it's activated through
Xingese Alkahestry instead.
There's no evidence
that someone's come
through this way...
I might've taken the
wrong path after all...
Guess I'll turn back.
And what do we have here?
They must've been
using this place
to dispose of the excess rubble
from the tunnel that
Sloth has been digging.
[PRIDE] You must be the
Crimson Alchemist...
It's a pleasure to meet you...
My name is Pride.
[KIMBLEE] Can I help you
with something, Pride?
[PRIDE]
Any new developments with Scar?
[KIMBLEE]
I'm actually pursuing him now.
[PRIDE]
Worry about him later...
As for now...
Go ahead and carve the
crest of blood at Briggs.
[KIMBLEE]
With all due respect, Pride...
The soldiers of Briggs
are much stronger
and more resourceful
than you might realize...
It's not exactly a simple task.
[PRIDE] Then use their
strength to your favor.
Sloth is nearing
completion of the tunnel...
So there's little time left.
[KIMBLEE]
So it's an urgent matter...?
Well if you insist that I carve
the crest of blood at Briggs...
I'd be happy to oblige you.
Welcome back to
the fort, Major.
[MILES]
Any changes to report?
None since we spoke...
The situation is
still normal here,
but we've heard that
Kimblee has gone missing.
[KIMBLEE]
You heard right...
There was an explosion in
one of the mine shafts...
No one's heard from Kimblee
or a few others since then...
We did a thorough
search through the rubble
but no bodies turned up.
Are the other men that
are missing Briggs soldiers?
[MILES] No... They were
two of Kimblee's men...
And the Fullmetal Alchemist.
[BREDA] Is that so...?
Fullmetal's missing.
I hope he's alright.
Me too... So are
things any better there?
[BREDA]
Afraid not.
The border war at
Pendleton was a massacre.
If the military was
hoping for casualties,
they sure as hell got them.
It's just like you said...
They're sending men
in to be slaughtered
for this transmutation circle.
[FALMAN] What's going
on in the south...?
Have you spoken with Fuery?
We talked on the phone...
A while back.
It's just as bad down there...
They're locked in
combat with Aerugo.
Keep moving, Thomas...!
Just don't stop...! Thomas!
Damn ittt!
I'm gonna survive this...!
I'm gonna live!
I won't die for this!
That's terrible.
[BREDA]
I guess it's to be expected...
The higher-ups aren't
our biggest fans...
Have you been in
touch with the Colonel?
Yeah...
We've been using a messenger
connected to the
Armstrong family.
Good to hear...
Just be careful with
everything going on up there.
I am... well,
I'm trying to be.
Bradley's got his soldiers
everywhere up here...
Working around the clock
to create hell on earth...
And the worst part is
there's nothing we can do.
The tunnel's... connected.
I'm all done working...
Does this mean I can rest...
Can I, Pride?
[FATHER]
The time draws near.
The day of reckoning is
almost within our grasp.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[ROSE]
Hey, everyone!
Go ahead and line up...!
It's time to take a lunch break!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
[RESIDENT 1]
Y'know, Rose...
I'd love to try your
three-meat pie sometime.
Well I promise to make it
as soon as we get some meat.
[RESIDENT 1]
I'll try to be patient.
Uh, pardon me...
I confess I haven't
been able to do any work,
but would you please give
just a little bit of
food to these children?
Well, of course
I'll feed them...
But you have to
eat too, okay?
[LITTLE GIRL]
It looks delicious!
[RESIDENT 2] Hey ya,
Rose... Pile it high.
You know I can't...
Everyone gets
the same amount.
[HOHENHEIM]
Ummm... Excuse me, Miss.
May... May I
have some food...?
If you don't mind.
Thank you...!
You saved me...
Literally... Thanks so much.
Where are you from?
If you don't
mind me asking.
I'm not really
from anywhere...
I tend to travel mostly.
And what brings you
all the way out to Liore?
We don't mean to pry...
We're just surprised
to have a tourist.
Most people tend
to avoid Liore...
There isn't much left
here after the riots.
Your cooking is a good
enough reason to visit.
That's sweet of you to say
but I don't know about that...
I just wish there
was more I could do
to help out around here.
Don't underestimate yourself.
A delicious meal and the smile
of a lovely young
lady are more help
than you can imagine.
[HOHENHEIM]
By the way...
I hate to impose any
further than I already have...
but can you point me
towards the church?
Which church?
Well...
I'm actually looking
for the church of Leto,
where the riots started.
[OLDER MAN]
This is what's left of it...
There's nothin'
left inside either.
[HOHENHEIM]
Do you know if there's
a passage that
leads underground?
[ROSE]
Uh... Yeah...
I can show you where it is.
[HOHENHEIM]
And what's this?
[ROSE]
The water turned toxic...
No one's really
sure how it happened.
I get the feeling
that this was put here
to keep people from
going any further...
Sooo.
Wait!
Hey! What are you doing,
that stuff'll kill you!
It's some kind of miracle.
That's no miracle...
But I know what it is...
That's alchemy.
[HOHENHEIM] I'm gonna
go a little farther in...
Would you mind waiting for me?
It's enormous.
I'm impressed...
They certainly went
all out making this.
Found it right off
the bat, didn't I...
Well... That didn't
even slow it down.
Okay then...
Let's see if I can trap it.
Oh, dear...
I'm afraid that's all I've got.
Ow!
[crash]
Something wrong...?
Aren't you going to attack me?
[PRIDE]
You look just like...
You must be Van Hohenheim.
So I'm assuming that this
must be the edge
of your container.
You'll die if you pass it...
Correct?
You can't survive outside of
your container, can you...?
It's not much different
than your flask, is it?
I'm guessing that you
can only move freely
within these tunnels
and Central City...
Am I right?
I'll take that as a yes.
What's wrong...?
Why the silent treatment...?
Did I hit a nerve?
Are you angry?
[PRIDE]
I'm never angry...
Anger does not exist within me.
I have no need of such things.
I left all unnecessary
emotions within Father...
All but one...
My name is Pride.
Pride The Arrogant...
That makes sense,
I can see your conceit...
[HOHENHEIM] There are seven
deadly sins within man.
Lust.
Greed.
Sloth.
Gluttony.
Envy.
Wrath.
And of course... Pride.
You're obviously the first
one that he separated...
Pride was his
strongest trait...
And the mere fact
that he took the time
and energy to give you
his original appearance...
That act alone shows how
egotistical he truly is...
You are the pure
essence of your father.
[PRIDE] I insist that you
come with me to see Father.
Don't try to rush me, Pride...
I don't need an
invitation to call on him.
But you can give
him a message...
Tell him Slave Twenty Three
will be dropping in quite soon.
Just tell him to be patient
and relax in his
chair beneath Central...
I'm coming.
[FATHER]
I am waiting, Van Hohenheim...
Yes... I am waiting for you.
Oh... Here he comes.
Did you find anything?
Yes... Dangerous
and disturbing things
not meant for ordinary people...
Please tell everyone to
stay far away from here.
What exactly were
you doing in there?
Sending a declaration of war.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 10]
You're relieved.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 11]
What took you so long...?
We've been miserable
in this storm.
Well, anyway...
I think some terrible
coffee should warm us up.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 10]
Enjoy it.
No... way...
What the hell...?
It couldn't be...
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 10]
It's Drachma!
[ANNOUNCERR]
Drachma is launching
an attack from the north...!
All men...!
Prepare for combat...!
I repeat...
Drachma has declared
war and is approaching!
All men!
Prepare for combat!
We are rather fortunate the
"Northern Wall of Briggs"
has been called away...
Good timing, Mr. Kimblee.
And, on top of that...
I've got a number of my top men
already stationed
inside the fort...
They'll spring their treachery
when the fighting starts...
The ensuing chaos should
weaken them from within.
My country has long dreamed
of the day when we
could breach the walls
of that abomination...
Fort Briggs will belong
to Drachma by nightfall.
Well... Let's send
a declaration of war.
What do you say we give them
a nice fireworks
show for starters?
All cannons...!
Prepare to fire!
Fiiirrrre!
Yeah... Yeah, hello...?
This is Zampano
reporting in...
I'm one of Kimblee's soldiers.
Dr. Marcoh and
Scar are hiding out
in the slums of
Asbeck Village...
[ENVY] You made the right move
by telling me this, Zampano.
And I promise that
you'll be protected.
[ENVY LAUGHS]
Dr. Marcoh...
Things are starting to look up!
[NARRATOR] The wicked
longing of a corrupted soul
is destined to wreak havoc
on the world around it,
but both pride
and determination
are also capable
of leaving scars.
None of it can be avoided.
Not if one is to be reborn.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 43, "Bite of the Ant."
The snowy field is
stained blood red...
The color of defense,
and of desperation.