Shut, Lock...
For servants crafted from my own soul,
they were ever so foolish.
But you, Close... I was right to resurrect you.
You've served me well.
I couldn't be more honored!
Now return to me.
To craft a new world of despair!
Lady Dyspear...
Now, the time has come...
What?!
Let us return.
Return, we shall.
To our true form!
Lady Dyspear...
To all who still bear their foolish dreams...
the dream is over.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
The Showdown with Dyspear
The Birth of the Grand Princesses!
This is Dyspear's true form!
What the heck is she?!
It's the moment of truth.
Let's reclaim our school!
Defeating Dyspear should bring an end to this battle between dreams and despair.
We didn't come all this way to lose.
Our dreams have only just begun.
You won't end them...
on our watch!
Cherry Blossom!
Dance, O cherry blossoms!
Precure!
Cherry Blossom Turbulence!
Coral!
Rage, O coral!
Precure!
Coral Maelstrom!
Galaxy!
Sharanla, O Galaxy!
Precure!
Galaxy Chorus!
Towa!
Right!
Sun!
Ignite, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Prominence!
You can't hope to halt my despair with such meager attacks.
Close?!
Don't tell me she absorbed him!
What?
Dreamy Shore...
It's not just Dreamy Shore!
Not just Hope Kingdom, but this world too?
Was that Dyspear's aim?
When will she cease her spread of despair?
When every dream has ceased to be.
Have you ever wondered why I was in Hope Kingdom,
the land of hopes and dreams?
Because where there are dreams, darkness is certain to follow.
Deferred dreams, vanished hopes...
disappointment, regret...
They all give way to despair.
The thorns...
are covering the world!
And so the despair born from that kingdom...
slowly warped into the forest of thorns and formed me!
That means you're...
Yes! I am the very embodiment of despair!
The force that shall seal away all dreams.
What should we do?
Only la true princess can defeat Dyspear.
La girls must become Grand Princesses...
Grand Princess?
Then let's do that!
How do they become one?
Moi doesn't know.
After all le growth la girls have shown, what could votre be missing?
Then we can't—
What about my dream of becoming an idol?!
If this is global, we've got bigger problems!
Haruno!
Don't worry... your dreams...
are under our protection!
But they're so hurt!
How can they keep fighting?
How can they look so determined?
Because they're chasing their dreams.
This is the resolve they've been fighting with this whole time.
She caught me off guard before...
but looking again, she couldn't be more Haruno.
She didn't change a bit.
No.
Haruka's always her honest self.
Perf!
We're gonna fight too!
Now hit Dyspear with all you've got!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Girls!
You can no longer pose a threat to me.
Is that...
the Gate of Despair?
Now...
it's the birth of a world... of despair!
The dreams...
...are being absorbed...
Stop...
Don't...
Dooooooon't!
Your hopes and dreams are for naught.
The plants wilt and the skies blacken.
The sea has lost its shine.
No...
Their dreams...
We failed them...
Let the despair begin.
Girls...
The world is in despair.
All that's left is for you to follow.
Not... while we're still here!
Haruka! Minami! Kirara! Princess Towa!
Cheer up!
Look out!
This is nothing!
Saving princesses is a Royal Fairy's duty!
And that's who we are!
So we won't lose!
You're right.
Even if despair befalls the world...
our spirits are still here!
Haruno.
You can really kick some butt.
You're amazing.
All four of you.
A little cold of you to keep it secret from us, though.
Thank you for all you've done.
Now it's our turn to fight.
But you all...
I want to do something...
to help!
We'll never give up on the dreams our friends fought to protect.
No matter how you try to cage us,
we'll always break free!
Look out!
We won't lose!
Light?
What the?
What's this?
It's most likely a Princess Rod fragment.
They materialized by binding to your dreams.
To our dreams?
Dreams give the Precures power...
Girls!
Take the power of my dream!
So these...
...can help Minami?
Guess it's down to me.
Kirara can do it.
Towa...
I dunno what's going on,
but it's all yours, Haruno!
What's this?
What a warm...
...and uplifting light...
This is the power...
of everyone's dreams!
The Perfumes!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
What?
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Four doors?
A door...
...means these keys...
...can open them, right?
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's go!
Right!
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
Go on, ma princesses!
We'll hold them off!
We sing happily and go into the world
Got it!
Girls...
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
Go for it!
and find the strength to jump forth
What's that light?
Everyone...
...is pushing us forward!
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid! Positivity is the key
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Shut! Lock!
No! I'm...
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Kuroro!
Buwaaaah?!
I'm just lending a hand for a bit, 'kay?
Your tongue hasn't dulled.
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
Shut! Lock!
Dally not!
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Perf! Aroma!
Everything will be all right
We've got this!
Keep going!
Nice shot!
Just a bit further!
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
This is what la girls have been
training their hearts to become.
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
From princesses who protect dreams...
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
to princesses who guide all dreams toward hope!
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
I'll become a princess!
You can.
Precure.
Princess Engage!
Could it be?
Grand Princess!
This feeling...
We're brimming with strength!
We've finally reached our goal, Flora!
Yeah!
We did it... We've finally made it!
You finally show yourselves...
Our hands that guide dreams shall never fold to despair!
Those dreams trapped in their cold cages...
...shall be released at once!
Now!
Do prepare yourself!
I'll stop you, be you Grand Princesses or no!
Crumble!
What?
I swear... we'll lead...
everyone's dreams to the future!
Is that...
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Our dreams...
Will overcome despair!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Precure!
Grand Libération!
Never forget! Despair always...
Adieu...
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Mermaid!
This grand blue sea is a mirror
reflecting my heart along the southern winds
I want to know the answer lying within my chest
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
So much has happened until now...
There has been joy, tragedy,
and many chance encounters!
But our dreams aren't over!
A new dream, and the future that lies beyond...
Yeah! We'll keep going with strength, grace, and beauty!
Go! Princess Precure: the finale!
Toward a Distant Dream,
Go! Princess Precure!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Tochigi Prefecture - Harune (Age 6)
Yamaguchi Prefecture - Rion (Age 5)