ADAMAS
[breath steaming]
[heavy metal music playing]
GRACE ABOUNDING
[Ares] Just feel that pressure!
I've never seen him transform like that.
[Hermes] If Zeus were in top shape,
he could sustain that form
for 12 or 13 minutes.
But with the damage he's taken,
he'll barely last five.
Don't get too rowdy, old man.
Heaven is breakable, you know.
[narrator] Zeus had compressed
his muscles to their very limits.
They screamed
with the effort of containing
such an enormous amount of energy.
Adam subconsciously raised
his fists in defense,
as if his instincts were warning him of
an encounter with a yet unknown creature.
Zeus' final form, Adamas!
Adamas's killer move allows Zeus to store
up energy by compressing his muscles,
then unleash a single high-speed punch.
The move's simplicity is what
gives it its unparalleled power.
God's True Right!
GOD'S TRUE RIGHT
DIVINE REFLECTION
[Heimdall] Incredible!
Adam even managed to copy
Zeus's mighty straight!
God's True Left!
Whoa! Zeus doesn't miss a beat!
Once more, Adam returns the blow!
- [bones cracking]
- [squealing]
Wait, another right?
DIVINE REFLECTION
- [bones cracking]
- [squealing]
[growling]
[Heimdall] It just keeps going!
Throwing out punch after punch!
Even though Adam's flurry
comes right back!
I'll admit this is a heck of a battle,
but talk about wasted effort.
Adam's Divine Reflection
can see through anything and everything
old man Zeus tries to hit him with!
Adam's got this in the bag.
- [gasping] Oh no!
- Huh?
[crackling]
[grunting]
Huh? What's this?
Adam's dodged every attack,
but his nose is bleeding!
Wait a minute.
Why does Adam have a nosebleed?
- His mind and body are overheating!
- [gasping]
All this time, Zeus has been
throwing out different punches.
So many, I didn't realize
he'd started using his killer move.
All those punches Adam just evaded
are supposed to be impossible to dodge!
He's gotta be in agony.
Since the outset of this battle,
Adam hasn't stopped using
Divine Reflection for a single second.
Seeing through a god's attacks
is devastating his neural circuits!
So if the fight keeps going like this,
is Adam going to make it through?
I can't believe he found a way
to beat Divine Reflection
just by powering
through it like a gorilla!
That stupid, fucking, knuckle- dragging,
over-the-hill, piece-of-shit, old bastard!
[ravens] Overheating?
Yep. That human isn't
gonna last much longer.
Then that would mean Zeus's victory
in this fight is all but guaranteed!
[cawing] Serves you right,
you copycat bastard!
[laughing]
[Loki] Ah, ah, ah.
Don't count your chickens, bird.
Take a look.
No! No, it can't be!
His muscles will explode into
tiny pieces like birdseed.
That rush isn't gonna
last forever, you know.
The old man's body
is at its breaking point.
He's also on the edge of overheating.
I've never seen
Zeus fight for his life before.
How beautiful.
[snapping]
Let me explain
with a little visual aid here.
Which of these glasses' lifeblood
will spill over first?
It's all a matter of endurance.
[Zeus straining]
[grunting]
[Loki whistling]
Ooh, it's close.
They're both so close to bursting open
I can almost taste it.
All it'll take is the tiniest little push...
[slurping]
...and their glasses will overflow.
[narrator] Though Loki predicted,
it was only a matter of time...
DIVINE AXE
[smashing]
...even against the pressure of Zeus's
onslaught of killer moves...
[both grunting]
METEOR JAB
Adam stood strong, unflinchingly returning
the god's every attack.
How lame.
They're both still hanging in there.
[narrator] The purity of these
two warriors fighting for their lives
captivated the onlookers.
Before anyone had realized it,
the beauty of the fight inspired god
and man alike to rise to their feet.
- Listen, Hermes.
- Yes. What is it, brother Ares?
I never knew that a mere fight
could be a thing of such splendor.
Indeed. I never knew either.
[Göll] Sis... Sister...
I can't... I can't stop crying
for some reason.
[Brünnhilde] Adam...
[male god 1] Hey, Adam!
Your attacks won't do shit against Zeus!
- [humans] Father! Father! Father!
- [man1] Hurry up and die, Zeus!
Hey! Don't you dare stop now.
Don't ever stop, you hear me?
You can do this, Adam. I know you can.
Please let Papa win.
Please, Zeus, I'm begging you.
[Cain] Die, die, die, die,
die, die, die, die, die!
Just die, and let this be done with!
Father! Father!
The Valhalla Arena
had reached a fever pitch,
but the first person to realize
just how things would play out,
was none other than Adam himself.
Most things that happen in this world
are set in motion by small events.
Often much smaller
than we can even imagine.
Even a raging, furious storm
can have its roots in the smallest,
gentlest of motions.
[splashing]
[shattering]
[Heimdall] A clean hit!
Zeus's fist finally
makes contact with Adam!
[Zeus grunting]
[Heimdall] Whoa! Adam takes another hit.
Zeus follows up. He unleashes
a violent barrage of punches.
Adam tries to block, but Zeus
makes him his personal punching bag!
But Brünnhilde, Adam isn't moving.
He's not moving!
It's likely taking everything he has
just to keep blocking.
I doubt Adam's eyes can even see anymore.
[Loki] Huh?
Looks like Adam was the first one
to overflow after all.
There's no way
he's coming back from this one.
Yeah, it's all over now.
But I sure have to give
that Adam guy some credit.
He was one hell of a man.
Hm? Uh, not that I'm rooting
for him or anything.
DIVINE AXE
We can't lose again.
[whimpering] Adam, no.
Please. Please stop this.
Father, that's enough!
You don't have to keep on fighting.
Dad, you idiot.
Dad, you have to give up.
Just surrender already!
- This has to stop!
- Isn't the outcome clear enough?
- Somebody has to end this.
- Please stop hurting him.
[narrator] The human race cried out,
yet in his darkness,
Adam had a single thought.
[baby crying]
[Adam] Oh,
there's a baby crying somewhere.
There's no need to cry. Don't worry.
[crying continues]
You don't have to be afraid
of those bad guys.
Your dad's gonna take care of all--
TO THE VERY END,
FATHER WAS DETERMINED TO WIN.
Huh?
Bastard.
Now I've got you.
[ravens shrieking]
Ooh! [giggling]
He let Zeus land that hit on purpose,
just to grab a hold of him!
This guy is nuts.
[roaring]
[screeching]
[narrator] It looked as though their
fist fight could have gone on forever.
But the end...
IT SUDDENLY HAPPENED
[gasping]
[Heimdall] It appears that Zeus
has collapsed to the ground!
[Heimdall shrieking]
Eh. Huh?
[panting]
Uh! Impossible.
[ravens gasping]
[gasping]
This... This can't be happening.
Uh, Zeus?
[exhaling slowly]
The battle is over.
[Heimdall gasping]
[humans cheering]
Hell yeah! You kicked his ass, Dad!
- All right!
- Amazing, darling.
[Zeus breathing heavily]
Huh?
[gasping]
- Huh?
[Heimdall] He... He's dead...
Somehow, Adam has died on his feet!
[sorrowful music playing]
[Zeus chuckling] Took you long enough.
Huh?
Adam breathed his last
long before I fell. [chuckling]
Even still, he stayed standing.
[breathing heavily]
An impressive feat on its own,
but that's not all he did.
[Zeus] Even after his death,
that stubborn human,
he never stopped throwing punches.
Well, kiddo,
looks like it's gramps's ass
that hit the ground first.
But what a fight.
Never met a man so impressive.
[all sobbing]
[glass shattering]
[Zeus sighing] If this were
purely a contest of endurance,
victory would have been yours.
[humans screaming]
The second round of the battle
between god and man, Ragnarok,
has been decided!
The winner is Zeus!
[narrator] Two losses in a row.
The humans now faced
a desperate situation.
But did any one of them despair?
They did not.
Their father, Adam, had bestowed upon his
children a vitally important precedent.
Adam showed them for the first time
that humanity could fight back
against the gods.
ZEUS VS. ADAM
TIME: 7 MINUTES, 13 SECONDS
WINNING ATTACK: FISTS
WINNER: ZEUS
Brünnhilde, what happened out there?
Start talking, Brünnhilde!
Göll, you need to calm down now.
Hrist... You saw it too, didn't you?
Those brass knuckles didn't even
have a single scratch on them!
HRIST
SECOND OF THE 13 VALKYRIE
She did her job and fought her hardest,
so why did our sister Leif have to die?
[sighing]
In truth, the act of Völundr
merges human with Valkyrie.
They become as one,
united in both body and soul.
A Valkyrie doesn't merely transform
into a weapon through Völundr.
Her fate is bonded to her wielder's.
We fight together, and...
we live or die together.
[whimpering]
[sobbing]
Please don't cry, Göll.
Leif was prepared for this.
She knew how dangerous
her battle would be.
Every Valkyrie does.
A time may come when you too
must prepare to follow in our footsteps,
and put your life on the line.
But I never even got the chance
to say goodbye,
to tell her how much I love her,
do something kind for her.
- Göll...
- Hrist...
- [squishing]
- Ow, ow, ow, ow...
That hurts, Hrist.
Why are you squeezing me so-- [squealing]
I'll get my revenge on those
piece of shit gods.
Once I'm through with them, there won't
be enough left to scream for mercy.
[Göll shivering] That's right. I forgot.
Hrist is the only one of us Valkyrie
with two powers
and two personalities in the same body!
[narrator] "Hrist."
The name has two meanings.
"The trembling one"
and "the thundering one."
Ah! Let's all simmer down now, Hrist.
If that's okay.
[chewing and slurping]
[growling]
[Göll exclaiming fearfully]
Stupid wrinkly old bastard!
Thinks he can get away
with eating my apple, does he?
That's not good.
She's eating her gross,
salty licorice pies again.
She always starts
wolfing those things down
whenever she's stressed out
or in a really bad mood.
[Brünnhilde] If we lose the next one,
it'll be three in a row.
We have to win. We have to
win this next round, no matter what!
[phone beeping]
- [gasping]
- [dishes shattering]
Whoa, what did
you do that for, Brünnhilde?
Is something the matter, sister?
[Hrist and Göll] Poseidon?
Then they intend to break
our spirit as soon as possible.
Wait, they're sending in Poseidon already?
Why are the gods bringing out
the big guns in round three?
Like, let us warm up
before you steamroll us.
[Göll crying]
Oh no, I just remembered that Poseidon's
actually Zeus' older brother!
I bet that guy's totally unstoppable.
Why did it have to be him?
Hey, are you doing all right, big sister?
It feels like we're done for.
Also, is it just me or do you think
the gods are trying to end this early
- with a seven to zero score?
- Göll...
Could you please shut your adorable
little mouth for just a second?
If you don't, I'm afraid I might have to
cut your cute little head clean off.
[sobbing]
[Göll] Her voice is so sweet,
but her words are so scary!
I thought Hrist had a messed up
personality but Brünnhilde is worse.
[dinging]
[Brünnhilde] We're at the cliff's edge,
and the gods just keep pushing us back.
So who?
Damn it, who?
Is there a human in history
who could stand against Poseidon,
the lord of the seas?
- Uh?
- [gasping]
When did he...?
It would be my honor.
- Huh?
He's sure?
When you say "my honor,"
you mean that you're Sasaki Kojiro?
For real?
I mean, you look totally
different from your picture.
Not to be rude, but you're kind of,
I don't know, old and shriveled.
What the heck's going on here?
I thought when a soul
was summoned to Ragnarok,
no matter how old
that person was when they died,
they would be summoned in their physical
prime, not as some crusty old geezer.
Isn't that how it works?
That is how it works.
And yet, this man claims to--
[whooshing]
Ugh.
Oh.
Cow's milk, was it? Ah yes. Good stuff.
Hm?
Oh.
Mm. What is this?
Ah! Whatever it is, it's delicious. Mmm.
He's loving that crap.
Okay, yeah. There's no way
that this old weirdo's the real Kojiro.
Hm, I must say. That was a real treat.
[Brünnhilde] He's certainly not
what I expected.
But still, right before our eyes,
he moved with the grace of a master.
The man before us is the real thing.
Hm.
It's been 400 years since
I was called up to heaven,
Since then, I have tirelessly worked
to hone my swordsmanship.
The nature of my Ganryu
has never stopped evolving.
[shimmering]
In other words, this old Kojiro
is a swordsman in his prime!
[Japanese pop ballad playing]