A town. That's where people gather, are born,
grow up and live out their allotted lives.
Honda Bookstore
Green Mart
MARUKO SHOPPING DISTRICT
However...
As if there is an error on the gods' behalf,
there are those whose works are disrupted.
PUB
KURAGE
Hotori, food is ready!
Hotori, can you hear me?!
Street No. 12
"Soremachi"
And Yet the Town Moves
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
A rainbow colored sunset falls
Kaze wa nandaka suzushige
And the wind is a bit cool
Doyoubi no yoru wa nigiyaka
Saturday night is bustling
Kurai kimochi sae
Even the gloomy feeling
Suguni harete
Brightens up right away
Minna uki uki
Everyone is in high spirits
Uki Uki
In high spirits
Downtown e kuridasou
Let's go downtown
Uki uki
In high spirits
Seaside
Wow, so this is where you work, Hotori.
What about your club activities, Senpai?
The Table Tennis Club...
I ditched it. Can I order?
Yes, go ahead.
Katsu curry without the katsu,
and iced coffee without the ice, and hot.
Huh?!
In other words, a curry and coffee, right?
Tsk, I didn't say it to you.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm a maid as well, you know.
What is this, what is this?
The atmosphere is tense right now.
She's my senior from middle school.
She's pouting because I didn't join the Table Tennis Club.
She's a chicken who ran away
because she couldn't beat me.
Even if you came to me now, I'm not going to let you in.
Aw, don't fight over something so petty.
I know, let me show you both something good!
Fountain magnifier!
At first glance, it's an ordinary magnifying glass.
But behold, the other side is a fountain pin!
It's "pen," fountain pen.
KON-SENPAI IS A MORON
It's heavy, but you can write with it.
When two different tools are combined into one,
it becomes this great detective item!
So, you two should make friends as well.
Note: The story in which the sons of a Japanese warlord were each tasked
to break an arrow; easily done singly, but harder to break all at once.
Oh? I thought this would round out smoothly,
like the story of Motonari Mouri's Three Arrows.
Moral: Individually weak; gathered with brothers, a mighty force.
But your reactions are very poor.
You didn't buy this yourself, did you?
Well, there aren't any high school girls
who buy just a fountain pen either.
It was given to me as a gift by my uncle
when I entered high school.
It's a Mont Blanc...
Oh, unfortunately, we don't have Mont Blanc pastries,
but we do have coffee jelly.
No, no... This pen... You modified it?
That's right! It deserves a patent!
I cut the back of the pen and
super-glued a magnifying glass to it!
If you did it while you were aware of it, that's fine...
But a Mont Blanc pen is very high class.
I'm sure even that one pen had cost
ten or twenty thousand yen.
What?!
Hotori, I'm sorry to tell you this, but there is an item
similar to your invention already in existence.
See...
The cap of the ball-point pen is a magnifying glass.
It's famous amongst the elderly.
What?!
You can go home for today already. Take it easy.
I knew I had something good here...
Found it.
Here, I'll give you a whistle.
Cheer up!
Don't you have to change?!
Seaside
Pyororororo...
Isn't that the long way around?
That's the appearance of a human being
who lost a place to lean on...
It's like a painful dousing...
The treasure she's looking for is hope in the darkness...
(I'm home...)
Pyopyoupyo...
Incoming Call
Ayatori Residence
Hello, this is the Arashiyama residence...
Uncle?!
Why, you called at the perfect time...
"That"? You mean the fountain pen...
Am I using... yes, I... I don't let it leave my side.
Even now...
B-by the way, how many tens of thousands of yen is this?
Ten!
Note: 100 thousand yen, or about $1300
Yes... S-summer vacation? I would love to go...
Thank you.
Mom, there's a call from the Ayatoris.
Okay, okay. What about your part-time job?
"Come visit during summer vacation or something."
"I'll refill the ink for you."
Urgh, the case of the amputation of the expensive pen...
Moving forward for now...
Next time I meet my uncle, I should come up
with a trick that'd let me lie through anything.
Trick, when it comes to trick...
Mystery... when it comes to mystery...
I wonder when Mr. Hiroto Shimabe's
new volume comes out...
Was there any information in
this month's Mystery Illustrated?
Monthly
Mystery Illustrated
Oh, that's it!
Th... th... this!
Mystery Illustrated
Mystery Novel Contest
Descriptions
Second Place             Grand Prize:
(Few winners):              5 Million Yen
2 Million Yen                 in prize money
in prize money              PC with word
Notebook PC                processing software
The grand prize winner receives 5 million yen!
It'll be enough!
The deadline is approaching soon.
But the announcement is 3 months from then...
I can make it in time.
I can purchase a fountain pen by summer!
In any case, the best way to put this pen to use
is to write a mystery novel and win the money!
What if I win the grand prize?
Writing in progress, do not open.
Gifts welcomed.
I was eating some jelly on the deck of the ferry.
Little did I know that a terrifying crime
was about to take place.
Jelly Island Murder
I'm starting to see Jelly Island.
So that's Jelly Island, famous for its jelly.
There's a legend about a monster
called Jelly Man on that island.
I'm scared!
Welcome everyone. I am the owner of Jelly Island.
Here, have some jelly.
I want strawberry jelly.
That person could be Jelly Man.
It's a very tasty jelly.
Hm. Jelly from Jelly Island is delicious after all.
What's going on?!
Oh no! Tatsuno is dead!
She's been decapitated!
What a cruel thing to do!
The legend of Jelly Man is true!
Everyone, let's all gather in one place!
The culprit may be in here, you know?!
The culprit is Jelly Man!
There's no way I can trust you people!
I'm going to be alone!
That was Kon-senpai's scream!
Kon-senpai was killed, too.
With this, I know who the culprit is.
I was wondering where our first victim
Tatsuno's body disappeared to.
The truth was the complete opposite!
The culprit is you...
Kon-senpai!
But she's already dead!
This red is not blood, but strawberry jelly.
Look at this.
She was just buried!
The only one killed was Tatsuno, just her alone!
Darn it, I killed her because
she didn't join the Table Tennis Club!
Here, come to the precinct.
Once again, a good job, Arashiyama.
Officer Moriaki ♥!
It was a terrifying incident.
However, Kon-senpai may have also been
the victim of a monster called "Society"...
The End.
You're in a good mood today.
Recently you looked like you weren't getting much sleep.
Kon-senpai...
Jelly
Island
Arashiyama-sensei, is your
latest work not coming out yet?
Sensei! Can I have your autograph?!
Jelly
Island
Arashiyama, if possible, may I as well?
Jelly
Jelly          Island
Island
Jelly
Each of you, prepare your praises and line up for me.
Even if I become famous, I'll still hang out with you.
Huh?!
However, one week later
Arashiyama
I'm home.
Oh?
Hotori
Zip 167-00xx
Tokyo-to, Suginami-ku, Kami-Igusa
Bldg5F
Mystery Illustrated
There's something from Mystery Illustrated.
But the announcement of the grand prize
is still a long way away.
Ah, "Thank you for your entry to the novel writing contest.
After careful consideration,
we are writing to inform you that your work
did not pass the preliminary round."
Careful
Work
Preliminary Round
Please don't be discouraged by this;
we are cheering on your future success.
Th-that...
That can't be!
I took two weeks to write that thing! How could you?!
Hey! Little girl!
A-are you okay?!
A-ambulance!
I'm sorry I fell onto the road... I think I'm okay.
We called an ambulance just now.
Wait, don't move her!
I didn't do it on purpose.
Huh?! Is this... Could this possibly mean...
That it's a pretty bad situation...?
I'm translucent!
Wh-whoa, I'm starting to float!
Hey...
You've got to be kidding me!
The you-know-whats are here!
What are you doing? Shoo, shoo!
Hey, no, this is a problem! Wait! Let me down!
You! If you're not into it, then could you let me go?!
John
Hey, that!
What is that poorly made storybook?
Is it supposed to be my life flashing before me?!
Oh!
Amongst the people who do business in town,
there are times when a certain person
can disappear without notice.
Put your heart on the scale.
If you heart is lighter than this feather,
you shall go to heaven.
If it's heavier, then to Hell.
My heart can't be lighter than this feather!
Argh! The holy feather!
Compare it to something that's not as bad,
like a can of coffee or something!
Guide
What are you doing?!
You're Japanese, so you need to get in the Japan line!
Wh-what?
Hold it right there! I'm going to throw her into Hell!
Applications
Reception Area for the Deceased           Wandering spirits,
Residual ghosts,            Please wait silently until called.          please take a number
please wait to be seen                                                                from the ticket dispenser.
by an attendant.
Arashiyama, Hotori Arashiyama.
Okay. Um, Hotori Arashiyama?
Is this the first time you've died?
Yes.
Cause of death was an accident; no criminal history.
Okay, that's enough.
There seem to be no problems,
and so your proof of residence in Heaven
will be done in about 2 to 3 weeks.
Oh.
It seems like a job at a government office.
Hi, we met earlier.
I act as a guide to all newcomers as well.
So ask me anything.
Is this really the afterworld?
It's different from what I had pictured.
Don't you have halos and those triangle things?
That was discontinued a long time ago
during the Showa Era. We had to cut costs.
Hmm...
It may not be enough for a substitute, but here you go.
Oh ♥!
It fits you well.
It's a Gardenia.
A dead person has no mouth...
Note: "Gardenia" in Japanese is kuchinashi （クチナシ）, a homophone for 口なし,
meaning "no mouth." It's part of the proverb, "shinin ni kuchinashi," which means
"No mouths for the dead," or "Dead men tell no tales." His pun can also mean,
"A gardenia for the dead."
Just kidding!
I always wanted to say that!
How was it, how was my joke?!
Are you trying to kill me?
I just died and I'm nervous about it.
Be a little more considerate!
Heaven District Number 21
Scallops
Seven-colored
Discs                FANS
Spring
Store             Heavenly Specialty
Skewer-Grilled
Soba Noodles
Porn
District 21 - Heaven Station
STEAMED
SHRIMP
BUNS
USED
BATTERY
STORE             Comet
HEAVENLY THEATER     SEEKING
10 MANGA DRAFTS
TO BE PUBLISHED IN
SHONEN ANGEL
SEVEN                               Resort Inn
Soybean
Paste                                                                                          URGENTLY
Amusement Center
For young boys, dads,
and high-school girls
Arcade 4F
Korean Barbecue 3F
Yoga Studio 2F
What is this? An arcade center?
This is a play area and the only place
where you can meddle with the world below.
Let's play around for a little bit. It's my treat today.
A photo sticker for my memory of the afterworld?
A photo sticker? This is what I mean.
You're such a person from the world below!
It's as if you're treating me like someone from
a rural area that just came out to the city...
This is a spirit photo shop.
You can turn a photo from the world
below into a haunted image.
That sounds like fun!
If you have a desired target, please let me know.
Kon-senpai!
SEARCH RESULTS FOR FUTABA KON                               1 HIT(S)
THERE ARE PHOTOS BEING DEVELOPED
The full name?
Futaba Kon.
Nice! It just so happens that she has
a roll of film to be developed.
PLEASE CHOOSE YOUR MATERIALS
CHANGE TRANSPARENCY                                THIS IS OK
You purchase materials like a hand or a face
and paste it onto a photo that you like.
Hey, hey! Do you have one of a peace sign?
Wouldn't it be funny to have
a haunted photo with a peace sign?
Oh, custom material like that is expensive.
Normal people like me can't afford it by a long shot.
You're right. A face or a palm or a light is cheaper.
No wonder all of the haunted photos look similar.
PLEASE CHOOSE YOUR MATERIALS
Oh well, then, I'll go with this hand.
We went through the trouble
of making a haunted photo,
I'd like to be able to see Kon-senpai's reaction.
I see, that's true.
A Heart-Pounding                                     Bouncy Bouncy
Tale
Then, next why don't we do this?
If you put in 100 yen, you can see
the world below for a while.
Oh! I can see.
It's a communal bath.
WOMEN
MEN
Oh, wow!
Oh?
Mosaic?
You can't see private places. Like baths.
Speaking of which, what happened to my body?
A black market telescope may let you see.
But it's also expensive... and illegal.
Maruko
Hospital
Oh, it's Mom.
So... Hotori is going to be like that forever?!
It's very hard for me to say this but I don't think
her consciousness will ever come back.
That can't be! You have to do something!
Oh, where's Dad going?
Oh. Takeru, Yukiko...
Don't cry Yukiko, don't cry.
Even if you cry, it's not going to change anything.
I told you not to cry!
Why... Why?!
What did Arashiyama do to deserve this?!
It's okay...
Hotori is going to get better and come back.
How do you know that?!
I do know!
Don't say something so irresponsible!
How could you be so sure in saying such a—
Because...
Because, there is no way Hotori can die!
Yes. Is that so?
Please don't lose heart.
Yes. Goodbye.
Seaside
Naito
Dental Clinic
It doesn't matter! Bring me that driver right now!
Yeah! I'll run him over the same way with our truck!
Please calm down everyone!
What, are you on his side?!
Depending on the circumstance,
I won't let you get away with it, damn it!
Why don't we stop this?
Hotori-chan won't like it, you know?
Thank you, then if you'll excuse me...
Zenji... Please protect Hotori... Please...!
I'm sorry Uki... I can't be of any help...
Why, why, Arashiyama?!
I... didn't tell her anything yet!
I haven't told you...
...anything yet!
Why?!
God, please give Hotori back!
She's only lived for 16 years!
It's not too hard for you to do something like that, right?!
This is the most I've made them worry until now.
From now on, I'll be careful and fix my carelessness.
That's right. There is no "from now on"...
There is no more...
I wanted to be with everyone a little longer.
I wanted to live more...
You're fortunate to be able to think that.
There are people out there who would
take their own lives in the world below.
Besides, this place isn't so bad either.
Everyone will come here eventually.
If you work hard, you'll meet them very soon.
Right?
That's true.
TANBUSAURUS
FUTABASAURUS                                                                Tale
I'm going to work hard here and make money.
TANBUSAURUS
A Heart-Pounding
FUTABASAURUS                                                                Tale
So I can make lots of haunted photos with
"peace signs" to spread to the world below!
TANBUSAURUS
FUTABASAURUS                                                                Tale
A Heart-Pounding
That's the spirit. Now that that's been decided,
I'll help you look for a job.
You're young, so what about the job where you
dress up as an angel and pick up the deceased?
Oh... that...
My son does it, too.
Miss Hotori Arashiyama, please come to the Government Building
Immigration Control Department immediately.
That's me.
What?!
I can go back?!
Yes, that's right.
Since, in your case, the body in the world below
remains almost completely unharmed.
Your brain miraculously revived.
So if you desire, you may go back.
Pumpkin
Boxed
Underwear           Lunches
Cotton
Candy
Heavenly
Kokeshi Doll
Wholesalers
Door
Hinge
Shop
Cold Drinks
Mister, I'm sorry I'm the only one...
Sometimes there are people who come back to life.
Don't worry about it, and go.
When I come back to life, I'll go visit your grave.
Unfortunately, your memory from this side will be erased.
Is that so...
Then, when I come again, I'll be in your care.
Let's get going.
The title "Guide" sounds nice and all, but in reality,
making a person come to grips with death
is a most cruel and disadvantageous job.
Having that girl go back to the world below
served as an unexpected reward for me.
We should go back to work, too.
Seems like I'd been having a weird dream...
What is this?! A new type of candid camera?!
Doctor! Doctor, it's Arashiyama!
A town. That's where people gather, are born,
grow up and live out their allotted lives.
However...
As if there is an error on the gods' behalf,
there are ones whose works are disrupted.
From Tatsuno
And yet...
Hotori!
Oh, Kon-senpai!
I was worried about you, moron!
And yet the town moves.
Dad said after he put in about 3400 yen
into the offering box, I woke up.
"You're 3400 yen!" he said. Man!
It's an appropriate price.
And, the fountain pen in question?
Yeah.
I consider it crushed underneath
the truck that ran me over.
In places like those, your brain works really well.
Hey, Hotori...
I think maybe the reason why
you got into this mess this time...
...is because there's something bad possessing you.
Huh?!
Where did that come from?! That's so out of left field.
Anyway, just take a look at this.
Here, the photo we took together!
At your shoulder!
What is that?! Scary!
And yet the town moves.
And Yet the Town Moves
Hi, Fu, Hi, Fu, Mi, Yo!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Taikutsuya rock damashi tazusaete
I'm so bored, I have the heart of Rock n roll
Hitorigurashi no bakuon jinsei
Living alone a life of loud music
Tennen no chouchin fugu na hoppeta de
I'm oblivious with cheeks like a blowfish
Machi wo kaosu ni kyo mo makikomu
Today again, the town to chaos will I drag into
Tsundere wa intelligence no akashi nari
Being tsundere is proof of my intelligence
Kyou mo kareni wa naze ka kokurezu
Again today, I'm unable to confess my love to this man
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
I gave my life to table tennis
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatako
To strengthen my legs and hips when I play the drums
Konna band mo yarase ja ne
This band isn't a scam
Konna member rock ja ne
This band isn't rock
Mezashite iruno wa ondo ja ne
We're not going for an ondo dance
Tadori tsuku no wa nehan ja ne
We're not going to arrive in Nirvana
Warera wa Meido "Yeah!"
We are the Maids "Yeah!"
Meido sugata de
Dressed as maids we
Sanjo sanjo!
Are here, we are here!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kokora wa meido "Yeah!"
This is Hell "Yeah!"
Jiken genba wa
The crime scene is
Sanjo sanjo!
A terrible sight, a terrible sight!
"Ach-ahhhh..."
"Oh no!"
Muteki no meido "Yeah!"
We are the invincible Maids "Yeah!"
Benpi wa nanzan
Constipation is a difficult delivery
Kancho kancho!
Enema, enema!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kiyoku tadashiku isagiyoku
Pure and right and frank
Seaside wa zessan! Eigyouchu!!
Seaside is, with rave reviews, open for business!!
"Meido arigatou gozaimasu!"
"Thank you always for your business!"