No matter what you do, nothing will change.
You should just quit while you're behind.
You don't get anything out of facing reality,
and there's no way to change it either.
It's better to just ignore it
and believe only what you want to believe in life.
Doesn't that sound a lot easier?
It'd be awesome if everyone's life could be that easy.
There's nothing great about the real world, is there? It's just dull and annoying as hell.
No one accepts that's the way things are.
They're just stuck with it because they can't deny it either.
Those who actually succeed in life... They just happen to be born
with the magic ticket called "talent."
Once you realize that, all you have left in life is despair.
The ultimate game over.
So wouldn't it be better if that kind of reality was wiped away?
That's complete bullshit!
One day you'll see.
You'll be faced with the boring reality that boxes you in, no matter where you go.
Honestly, we don't need our world anymore.
Better to let it be swallowed up and for mankind to turn into Shadows...
That's what all those people who're scared to death really want.
So it's my duty to see that they get it.
Keep your bullshit to yourself!
If you want to disappear, then go ahead! But leave us out of it!
Hey, are you okay?
Brats like you are so damned naive.
I get that you're all afraid and gotta act tough to cover it up, but geez...
I'm telling you all this based on my own experience in life.
What are you...
What's that?!
What the hell is that thing?
Soon...
Soon the worlds will merge into one!
It looks like a huge collection of energy!
It's coming down fast!
There's no need to be afraid.
Once everyone turns into Shadows, they'll still keep on living.
They'll just be oblivious to all the things around them.
Yukiko!
So how's that different from the way things are now?
No, this'll make things much easier for everyone.
No matter who you are, your lifespan is about 80 years or so, right?
Then it'd be easier if we all just became Shadows.
No need to hold back anything...
No more pretending we don't see things.
Nobody wants anything like that!
Geez! I'm going bear-serk over here!
Everything Adachi says is just nuts!
Don't you remember what it was like when your Shadow came out?
It must've been enjoying life far more than you!
Those things move on pure instinct.
They go wild because you defy them!
Scared?
I've always wanted to use this.
I joined the police so I could carry a real gun, and I thought it'd be fun, but honestly, that was a wash.
Everyone around me was such an idiot.
You guys don't know when to quit, do ya?
What do you want so badly that you'd put yourselves in harm's way?
Is it some innate sense of justice?
I bet you just wanted something to spice up your dull lives.
How are you any different from criminals who get their kicks from murder?
You just loiter around Junes and play guessing games!
So, how many people out there actually think about what's real, or what's right and wrong?
Next to none, I bet.
Namatame was the one behind those serial murders.
That's what's real in everyone's eyes.
Even if you managed to catch me,
what do you think would happen?
The answer is simple.
Everyone's view would shift...
But in the end, no one actually cares who the real killer is.
That is the truth you've been searching for!
That isn't...
...the truth!
Oh, come on! I just told you everything there is to know.
It's your stubborn ignorance that makes you kids so annoying.
Enough of this!
You don't even have the balls to shoot me!
What?
I'm sick of your bullshit!
No matter what you say,
you won't get away with this!
That is the truth!
Your twisted logic is that of an immature, egotistic brat!
People can't live alone!
If you give in and sever your ties to human society,
it will naturally become hard to live in it!
What would you brats know?!
You're the brat!
Living is too painful for you,
but you don't want to die?
Of course no one would understand!
You're just throwing a tantrum like a kid who can't have his way!
Shut the fuck up!
Chie!
I'm gonna say it flat out!
"Favored by the world" my ass!
You're just a worthless criminal!
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
I'll kill you.
I'll fucking kill you, just like I killed everyone else!
You're wrong!
Shut up!
You will pay for your crimes.
Just looking at you pisses me off!
Shut up and get lost!
You can't even stand on your own unless you deny everything I've said!
That's what you get for...
We saw the truth in things we never wanted to see just to get here.
Go fuck yourself!
You naive high school brats don't know anything!
You have no idea what kinda shit I've been through!
You're not the only one who's suffered.
What the hell?
I'll kill you...
There's no way I can lose!
Face the music!
What the?
This is no fun...
Well, whatever.
Our world's gonna disappear soon, no matter what.
I didn't have anywhere to go back to anyway.
Adachi, are you okay?
Man, what a pain!
Don't!
All humans will become Shadows.
And I shall descend upon the united world as the master of order.
You're from back then?!
Both this world and yours will soon be enclosed in a fog that never lifts.
Who are you?!
I am Ameno-sagiri.
One who rules the fog. One awakened by man's desires.
Do what you will, but your world's erosion cannot be stopped.
It is an inevitability.
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Junes is invading! Nooo!
What is that eyeball?
Ameno-Sagiri
Inside                       the TV
Reality
Fairly
Strong
It's pulling the worlds together.
It's pulling them together!
At this rate, the two worlds are going to collide!
That can't be!
This is what creates the fog!
Mankind's desires are my desires.
I am the one who shepherds humans to their true desires.
Humans are the ones who tore down the wall between image and reality.
That is why I decided to expand this world.
You played your part well, stirring up the will of the masses into madness.
But even that is coming to an end.
Mankind will soon become Shadows,
and live on in the darkness of the fog, oblivious of their reality.
Shut the hell up!
This is part of the sea of unconsciousness that exists within human hearts.
It is a hollow forest...
born from bloated desire and false imagery.
You're sayin' you're the one who created this nasty-ass world?!
I bestowed power onto those who could brave the hollow forest.
It was I who made it possible for you to bring about this destiny.
You mean the power to enter the TV?!
Like I care!
Humans choose to see only what they wish.
This is a world filled with desires...
Viewed through a window, from which one sees what one wishes to see.
The Midnight Channel?
So that's why those who got famous suddenly appeared on the Midnight Channel?
It was all in people's minds?
That's been bothering me.
The Midnight Channel we saw in Namatame's hospital room
wasn't Namatame's true intentions at all.
It came on because we were all thinking,
"This person must be the killer. He can't be forgiven."
We may not have seen the exact same thing when we watched it by ourselves.
The more false images one yearns for,
the more one stops yearning for reality.
And so the forest grows on.
That is the expansion of this world.
When did we wish for that crap?
To hell with that!
We kept fighting and fighting like morons to get where we're standing!
Yes... That I did not foresee.
The ability to master your own Shadow that emerged to kill you,
and use its power...
A new and uncertain facet of mankind...
Is it worthy to put my trust in, or not?
It must be tested.
Now everyone will turn into Shadows,
and the world will begin anew in its true form!
I won't let our world come to an end!
Why do you defy me?
What can a single person accomplish?
I...
am not alone!
Human bonds are unstable.
They are not worthy of your trust.
Were humans not the ones who departed from reality of their own volition, craving more false images?
You're wrong...
Reality isn't so bad!
That's what they taught me!
I made it this far...
because they were there with me!
If I'm with them,
I can change the world.
We will never give up!
Yu?
Yu!
The power of your Social Links
created a miracle!
Narukami!
Yu!
Master!
Master, it's showtime!
Hey, I'm counting on you!
I love you, truly!
One shot, one kill!
I believe in you, Narukami!
Okay! I'll leave the world in your hands!
I'm counting on you, partner!
Persona!
Is it over?
You have proven to me human potential.
Mankind's desires are my desires.
If mankind so wishes, I will return at any time.
Farewell, children of the new potential.
Get outta here. I'm done for anyway.
The Shadows will finish me off.
You came here to kill me in the first place, didn't you?
No, dumbass.
Your stupid game's over.
Live and face your punishment.
That's how it works in our world.
Let's go home, Adachi.
Daddy...
I had a dream...
Big Bro and his friends beat up the bad guy.
They saved us all.
That right?
Only cruel words flood the town at random
Never more will that sad voice flow by
I guess this is it.
Casual days bid their goodbyes
It's way too soon to cry.
But...
Big Bro, I don't want you to go away!
We have lost our
When I grow up, I'm going to marry you!
irreplaceable days together
Nanako...
The misty rain hides the sun
I'd welcome you with open arms.
But hands off while she's underage!
and steals our light
Didn't you promise you wouldn't cry?
I was worried,
Y-Yeah...
having lost everything I believed in
I'll leave your room as it is.
You're as much a part of this family as Nanako.
Thank you.
But I will never forget
the days I spent with everyone
Master, I'm going back home, too.
Never more will I be
I'm going to work bear-y hard to protect that place.
Sounds good.
alone in the darkness
The train will be arriving momentarily.
For your safety, please stand behind the white line.
I will find everything dear to me
While boarding, please do so promptly.
I guess you better go, huh?
that I've lost
Yeah.
Well, I'm off.
Never more, for I am sure that
your voice will lead the way
But I will never forget
the days I spent with everyone
Never more will I be
alone in the darkness
I will find everything dear to me
that I've lost
Never more, for I am sure that
your voice will lead the way
I still remember
The night...
Welcome to the Velvet Room.
You've had quite the eventful journey for someone your age.
This is a crystal of power which you have nurtured through your journey.
An orb that repels fabrications of all sorts, dispels lies, and shines upon the truth.
You have formed bonds with those dear to you as you reached out to the truth.
I'm sure you'll continue to do so.
Now go. You'd best be off.
This is a crystal of power which you have nurtured through your journey.
It is... a story of reality
There's something I have to tell you.
Don't forget about me, Big Bro!
We don't need reality.
Even if it is an illusion,
as long as we're all together, that's enough.
That's what I believe.
Ma-Master!
Yes! Yes!
Someone, help me!
Who the hell are you?
It's unfortunate it all had to come to this.
Farewell.