[footsteps]
[Narrator] Scar had once again
made an appearance in Central.
Ed and Al worked together
with Ling to draw
the murderous Ishvalan's
attention in an effort
to lure out the Homunculi.
Their strategy paid
off... Before long,
the Homunculi Wrath and
Gluttony appeared.
However...
[scream]
No, Lan Fan!
Clever... You took a swipe at me
with your kunai.
Can I eat her now?
Just make it quick.
[excited yell]
Lan Fan! Please, stay with me.
[grunts]
If you thought you could escape
from me that easily,
I'm afraid you'll find you're
sorely mistaken.
[clanking swords]
Hmm... I see you're no
stranger to combat.
All this jumping around... He's
trying to stay in my blind spot.
Gluttony!
Yeah!
Uhhh...
[breaking glass]
♪ fast pace, tense music
[struggling grunts]
Excellent... We should have
some privacy in here...
If you don't mind.. I
have some questions.
First I'd like to know who
you people are...
and how you found out
what's inside Gluttony.
You looking for an
escape? Even now?
You don't give up, do you? You
might stand a fair chance
of getting away if you'd only
abandon the injured girl,
because she's just excess
baggage at this point.
Excess baggage?
[Ling] I can see all those
stars on your uniform.
You're the ruler here...
Fuhrer King Bradley,
unless I'm mistaken.
A ruler's duty is
to his people...
Without them, he is
no king at all!
King Bradley!... You're
no true king.
Not now or ever!
Naiïve boy!... Don't
you understand
that there are no true
kings in this world!
[explosion]
That ought to hold him.
[running footsteps]
Judging by the draft...
there's the exit!
Uhhh...
Nice try.
But your flash bomb didn't
succeed in blinding this eye.
[birds chirping]
[Winry's father] Winry...
We won't be away too long... You
be a good little girl, okay?
Take care of things
while we're gone.
[whimpering]
[footsteps]
[Gracia] Winry...
Here we are.
♪ somber music
Watching Mr. Hughes
leave that day
was like the last time
I saw Mom and Dad.
Just their backs as
they walked away.
[Gracia] You'll come and visit
once in awhile, won't you?
After all... we wouldn't want
him to get lonesome here.
Yes, of course I will.
[soft gasp]
♪ heart-warming music
[busy street chatter]
[Man 1] I hear the Elrics
are wreaking havoc.
[Woman] What?.. Again?
[Man 2] The MPs have been
running around like crazy.
They're in another fight?...
Good grief.
[Man 1] It seems they're after
that guy who's been
killing off State Alchemists.
[Man 2] Seriously? They haven't
caught him yet?!
[Woman] What is the military
waiting for?
♪ suspenseful music
No... not again. Please...
[explosions]
[grunts]
It's a dead end.
[heavy breathing]
Damn! What now?
[gasps]
[screams]
[grunts]
Nice one, brother. 'Preciate it!
[Al] We need to get
out of here now!
Permission to fire?
Not yet!
Why the hell not?
[screams]
[heavy breathing]
[Al] Ling hasn't fired the
signal flare yet.
And brother is getting tired... I
have to buy us some time.
Scar!...
You say you believe that
alchemists have defied god...
Isn't that hypocritical?... You
use alchemy just like we do!
I explained it when we met in
East City... It's Balance.
Where there are creators, there
must be a destroyer.
[Al] That's a lie!
You're using the name of your
god to justify murder!...
Revenge is all you care about!
When you killed Shou
Tucker and Nina...
I suppose you believe you were
doing god's work then too!
Interesting... You two saw that
abomination as well, did you?
Alchemy created that
tragic creature...
So. that's the science you would
spend your lives following?
[Al gasps]
[Ed gasps]
[Tucker] Look at
your brother!...
He is the result of messing
around with somebody's life.
That chimera was made because a
man thought he could create,
when creation is the
province of god alone.
[Al gasps]
Maybe you're right... But why
did you have to kill her?!...
You stole what little
life she had left!
Foolish as you are, you must
still have known that
chimera could never have
returned to her human state.
[gasp]
It would have lived out its life
as a laboratory specimen...
treated as a test subject, but
never again as a human being.
[Al] He's right...
Even then we knew that Nina
would be sent off to live
in a laboratory... We knew full
well what would happen to her.
[Ed] We didn't want
to think about it...
We knew there was no hope.
[Al] So we did nothing.
[Ed] Nothing.
[footsteps]
[sigh]
[groaning]
[Ed] It's true...
State Alchemists have made
some serious mistakes.
But despite what you think...
That doesn't make
what you're doing right, and
we can't let you continue.
[angry exhale]
[footsteps]
[Ed] You're so self-righteous...
But do you remember
two Amestrian doctors
named Rockbell?
[gasp]
The order came down to
end the uprising and
exterminate Ishval. But
that didn't stop them.
They kept right on helping
your people.
[Al gasps] Wait, Brother!
Don't you remember
them?!... Those doctors
saved your life!...
And you killed them!
[gasp]
Brother!
What are you talking about, Ed?
[breath] Winry. I, um...
You mean he's the man...
who killed them?...
My parents... he killed them?
What's worse... They
helped save you...
and you killed them?
[whimpering]
Why did you?...
They were my mom and dad...
What did they ever do to you?
They were doctors...
They helped people...
They didn't deserve to die!
[crying]
Give them back...
Give me back my mom
and dad, you monster!
[crying]
[gasp]
Winry!...Hold on! You can't!...
Don't do this!
[Al] Winry!
Don't do it!
I know the animosity you feel...
But your vengeance will only
sow the seeds of further
violence. What you're doing
is senseless revenge
and it's feeding
a fruitless cylce of death.
You must end this cycle
once and for all.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[crying]
This girl is the doctors'
daughter?
[crying]
You have the right... Shooting
me would be justified.
Brother! Brother!
Listen... The armed forces
have almost arrived.
This is no time to be looking
at your notes!
Just a minute more.
I'm almost there.
What are those tattoos for?
Oh, these things? The
basis of alchemy is
understanding.. deconstruction...
and reconstruction.
My right arm deconstructs...
My left arm reconstructs.
I studied the alkehestry
they use in the east...
and then added my
own touches...
I discovered something
else in my research.
The alchemy of this land
is quite unusual.
None of that stuff
matters anymore!
Didn't you hear me?
The army is here.
[Countryman] Stop.
[Scar] Why are you interfering?
We have to get away
from here now!
[Countryman] Please!...
Calm down and listen.
Your brother's alchemy
might be the only way
we have of saving Ishval!
What?!
You must've heard... The enemy
has State Alchemists.
They're weapons... Using
their dirty magic to
cut a path of destruction
through the country.
Eventhough we're Amestrian
citizens just like them.
I've heard all about
the military dogs...
but what do they have to do
with my brother's research?
Your brother is the
only one who can
stand against the
State Alchemists.
If he can match their
power with his,
he could find a way to
annihilate the military.
The threat to us
would be ended!
Kill them.. before
they can kill us.
Take them down.. With alchemy,
we'll beat them at
their own game.
Pay them back in blood!
[Scar gasps]
Do you see this, Brother?...
This is the science
that you would spend
your life following?
You may think it's for
the greater good...
that it could help our people.
[angry breath]
You don't even see the
evil you're creating!
[mortar shots]
Run!
[explosion]
[frightened screams]
[soldiers marching]
[gasp]
[gun shots]
[raging fire]
So this is your alchemy, brother?
[menacing laugh]
Uhh.
[grunts]
This is the great power?... This
is going to save our people?!
[grunts]
[Scar] This science
causes nothing
but destruction and slaughter...
It can't save us!
[explosion]
[gasp]
Oh no!
[running footsteps]
[heavy breathing]
Father!... Mother!
Are you all right?
Yes, we're both okay... Luckily
we were already prepared
to flee from here in
case we needed to.
Sorry I'm late...
There were some
important notes I
needed to compile.
What do you mean?
Here, I want you to
hold on to this.
Why? What is it?
These are my research
notes... This is all
that I was able to bring... Take
them and get away now.
Hold on a minute.
If anything happens to me,
I don't want my research
to have been for nothing.
Why don't you just take it
and run away yourself?
Because, you're a warrior
of the Ishvalan people...
You've been well trained.
Let's be honest here, You're
a lot more likely to survive
this than I am. Just look.
My legs won't stop shaking.
Some big brother.
You will survive.
[gasps]
[crowd gasps]
Is that a soldier?
Look at his hands! He's
a State Alchemist!
[screams]
Get back!
[yelling]
♪ somber music
[painful groans]
Stay with me!...
Don't you die!
[labored breathing]
Damn, I can't stop
the bleeding!
His arm... Where's my brother's
arm?... Where is it?!
Father...
Mother...
Someone...
Anyone!
♪ climatic music
Don't die... I won't let you.
[Man 2] I have to
keep fighting!
Let me go back out there!
[Winry's Mother] No. You're
staying right where you are.
[WInry's Father]
That's right...
We didn't treat you just
to let you die.
[Youngster] Doctor, you and your
wife should get out of here.
[Winry's Father] Young man,
we're not going anywhere.
[Scar] Brother...
[Scar's Brother] Get back!
[Scar] What happened?... Why did
you protect me?
Brother...
[Winry's Father] Anyone who can
move on their own, go now!
[Youngster] He's awake!
Don't move or you'll
open your wounds...
Come here!... Dear, come here!
You aren't well enough to move
around on your own yet.
Somebody!.. get a cart!
Take this man with you.
He needs help!
Brother's tattoos.
You're alive!... Brother,
you've made it--
[gasp]
What is going on here?!
[screaming]
Sedatives!
[Winry's Mother] There aren't
any more. We used them all up!
[frightened gasps]
[Scar] State Alchemists...
Amestrians...
You will pay!
[boy gasps]
All of you!...
All of you will pay!
[Patient] Dr. Rockbell!
[screaming]
[painful breathing]
[Scar] Go on, shoot.
[Ed] Don't do it, Winry!
Put down the gun!
[Al] You know you don't want
to do this!.. Winry!
Shoot, girl... But know... the
moment you pull the trigger...
there's no going back.
You will be my enemy.
Scar!
If you think I'll let you hurt
one hair on her head--!
Will you kill me?... That'd
be fine with me...
until one of us dies, boy.. this
chain of hatred will continue.
But don't ever forget!
Don't ever forget it was
the Amestrians
who first pulled the trigger
during the civil war.
It was your people!
[whimpering]
Winry... don't shoot!
[Al] Just put that gun down
and get out of here!
Winry!
If you can't shoot... then
do as the boy told you.
You're in my way!
[grunts]
Don't shooooot!
Get back!
[Scar] My brother...
[Al screams]
[grunts]
[Al] Ed, you idiot, what
are you doing!?...
Both of you will get killed!
Hurry and get Winry
somewhere safe!
[whimpering]
Winry... let go of the gun.
[Winry] I couldn't shoot.
I know you couldn't...
and it's okay.
But that man...
You said he's the one who
killed my mom and dad.
He tried to kill you and Al
too, Ed. But I couldn't...
Why not?!
[Ed] Remember In Rush Valley...
you delivered that baby...
you saved two lives.
And you gave me an
arm.. and a leg...
to replace the ones I'd lost.
It's your hands... They
weren't meant to kill.
They're meant to give life.
That's why.
[crying]
[Narrator] What happens when
someone must give something
up in order to protect it?
Will his resolve falter?...
Will he crumble beneath
the weight of sacrifice?
Or will his heart
remain strong...
ready to do whatever
is necessary.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 23...Girl on
the Battlefield.
You must not show any
tears of sorrow...
That is part the promise.