Guilt all gone?
Fight!
One more! One more!
Isn't Kushieda-senpai
acting a little strange?
You're right.
She's always been odd, but she has
been spacing out a lot recently.
What am I doing?
(My Silky Love)
Every time I think of you
MY SILKY LOVE nijuu yojikan zutto
(My Silky Love)
for 24 hours straight,
MY SILKY LOVE kimino koto omoutabi
(My Silky Love)
It only makes me feel
MY SILKY LOVE modokashii kono kimochi
(My Silky Love)
that much more impatient.
MY SILKY LOVE tada afure kaetteku
It's so simple just to say I love you.
But when you come close to me,
sukito ieba kantan nanoni
kimiga maeni kichauto
my own emotions go awry
and get in my way.
kyaraga sobie watashino
koto wo jamashiteru
I can bring myself to do anything.
That's who I'm supposed to be.
itsumonaraba tsuyoki de ikeru
sonna seikakunanoni
But I just can't break this
wall down no matter what.
donna ganbatte mitemo kabewa kuzusenai
Please understand these feelings for you.
sasshite hoshii kono kimoch iwo
That's why these gazes of mine,
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimini
they tell my love for you.
daisuki dayoto okuru shisen
Now gather up my courage!
saidaino yuukide
A fragile heart made of silk,
yabure souna shirukuno haato
I realized that by meeting you,
kimini atte kizuita yatto
I was so clumsy when it comes to love.
ainiwa bukiyou dattan datte
A forgotten scar left in my heart,
wasure kaketa koino kizuato
and I suddenly felt it sting deep inside.
kyuuni uzuki dashitano kyunto
I have to say that I love you someday...
itsukawa watashi rashiku sukito iwanakya
Or it'll keep making me weaker.
imayori yowaku nacchauyo
Mercury is Retrograde at Christmas
Oh, the big year-end sales
are coming up soon.
And then it's spring cleaning time.
I'll be free to scrub those typically
hard-to-reach places,
like the backs of cupboards
and under tatami mats...
No, no!
You should be thinking about
Christmas! Christmas!
Oh, I can't wait!
I'll have to be a good
girl for the time being.
He's probably approaching
Japanese airspace about now.
Who?
Shouldn't that be obvious?
Santa! As in, Santa Claus!
- Gimme that! I'll carry it for you.
- I looooove Santa!
- Are you...okay?
- Do you, now?
Uh-huh!
I hope he comes to our
house again this year.
- Uh-huh!
- What's wrong?
You see, I love Christmas!
I gathered that much.
But my question is, why?
Do I need a reason to love Christmas?
The whole town is all pretty and sparkling...
Everybody's all smiles...
Hey, no eating sweets before dinner!
I know!
That's why I'm only having one.
Then you don't know!
We're celebrating the end of
your suspension tonight.
And I'm using wild-caught
amberjack for the hot pot.
Damn, it was expensive.
You could at least feign excitement.
Yay, yahoo, amberjack hot pot.
A little more!
Lots of amberjack, yipeekiyay!
Not quite there yet!
So?
Did you get any closer to Minorin
while I was suspended?
No progress, huh?
Man...
Way to waste the perfect chance,
since I wasn't around to bug you.
B-But it really wasn't my fault...
While you were gone, Kushieda didn't
come to our usual meeting spot,
and she ate lunch with some other girls.
Plus she's busy with practice after school—
So what, you gonna wait
forever, like Hachiko?
Think if you wait passively long enough,
she'll make the first move?
You stupid, idiotic, blockheaded mongrel!
Or that's what I'd normally say.
You just did.
I guess I can't blame you
for making no progress.
All right!
I'll do something about it.
Christmas.
The lovely angel of romance,
Taiga, will lend you her aid.
Cr-Creepy as hell...
Say what you want.
But I am a living Buddha right now.
A Buddha? Aren't you supposed
to be an angel?
Yeah, sure.
Lovely angel Taiga is willing
to shed a layer or two...
or even go buck naked in order to
bring everyone a happy Christmas!
Just leave this to me!
Well?
Don't I look like an angel?
Nope.
And you're dropping crumbs on your head.
Gross!
Brush them off!
She's here!
It's the Lady Tiger!
Lady Tiger has returned!
Lady Tiger, we appreciate your service!
What's with you people?
We became fans of Lady Tiger
after watching her fight!
The Boss vs. Palm-top Tiger showdown
ended in victory for you, right?
Once you learned that The Boss
was going to study abroad,
you wanted to settle things
once and for all, right?
Lady Tiger!
Tell us about the fight!
Silence!
It was a very difficult battle!
I faced peril many times!
However!
The last person standing, wins!
Which means!
I am the true victor!
Come on, just ignore them.
Let's go, Taiga.
Tensed up thighs!
Quivering muscles!
Wh-What's going on?
Minorin!
I'm back at school!
So stop singing weird songs,
and give me a hug!
Release me! I am a human being!
I missed you so, so much!
Why weren't you at our usual meeting spot!?
Oh, I overslept, so I had to dash to school.
My thighs are all banged up now...
But how did I get to class
before you, if I was late?
R-Right...
Well, actually...
We were surrounded by a bunch of weirdos.
So anyway, Kushieda—
Silence, child!
What'd I just say?
Did I make a bad joke!?
I've done it now!
Yowzers! Sorry! Forget it!
'Sup, Takasu?
Oh, and Tiger. Been a while!
Yay! Doing good?
Huh?
Kushieda snap again?
I should shave my head for real...
What a failure...
I'll be sporting the bald look for now.
Uh, why is a girl in high school
wearing a bald cap?
Aisaka!
Wh-What is it now?
Good morning, Aisaka.
O-Oh, Ki-Ki-Kitamura-kun?
- And good morning to you too, Takasu.
- G-Good morning...!
Wh-Why...?
Because it's morning?
Not that! Your pose!
Oh, this?
It's...the ultimate form of prostration!
Pro—?
Prostration!
Getting on my knees would be insufficient
to express my gratitude to Aisaka!
So I went with full prostration!
Aisaka!
Yes!?
Never get in another fight,
no matter who it's for!
If you're ever facing an insurmountable
challenge, come talk to me first.
Sure...
- But then, I saw him.
- Right...
That teacher's assistant, walking
out of a pachinko parlor.
Oh, that would confirm it.
He said he was late for
your date because of work,
but he was actually gambling.
Yes...
Broadcasting Room
And then...
I texted one of my girl friends.
My TA boyfriend is being
absolutely horrible to me.
What should I do?
And then...
I learned something incredible.
A thrilling turn of events?
The teacher's assistant position
no longer exists.
They're called junior professors now.
Which would mean...
He was lying about his job!
And I haven't heard from him since!
Why are you making our
teacher cry, Kitamura?
We should pretend we don't know it was her.
- Yeah...
- Oh, well.
This was Kitamura Yusaku, Patron
Saint of Broken Hearts,
with Cheering Your Love On.
What's this Patron Saint
of Broken Hearts thing?
Well, after his big confession,
Kitamura's become a romance guru.
Or at least, worshipped by people
looking to do the same.
Kitamura shoulders all their baggage,
and that somehow makes him...
the lucky patron saint of broken hearts.
That's so stupid.
Kids in this school really love
to believe in legends.
Isn't this broadcast annoying?
Why is he talking about studying for exams?
Wasn't the title of this show
Cheering Your Love On?
Shut your mouth!
Tiger's listening.
She won't be able to hear Kitamura's
profound broadcast.
Hey, Tiger, you good?
Hearing everything okay?
Uh, sure.
I'm good.
Actually, you seem awful quiet today.
Desks and chairs would normally
be flying by this point.
And Haruta would be a dead man.
You noticed?
You're right. I'm being a good girl.
Good girl?
Yep. I'm going to be a good
girl for Christmas.
After all, Santa is watching us.
What did you say?
Are you an idiot?
I never expected "Santa" to ever
come out of your mouth.
That's so not you!
Dumb-chi!
It's almost Christmas!
Santa won't visit your
house if you're naughty.
Something's definitely wrong with you.
What happened while you were suspended?
Wait, is this a death sign?
Are you going to die tomorrow?
Why would I die!?
Could you two knock it off?
Thank you for listening!
Remember...
Once those painful exams are
over, it'll finally be Christmas.
And so, I have an announcement
from the student council.
After the last assembly on Christmas Eve,
there will be a voluntary party in the gym.
Couples are naturally welcome to attend.
But if you're having difficulty in love,
or finding it hard to approach
that special someone...
...why not take this opportunity
- A Christmas...
- Party...?
to invite them
to a romantic Christmas Eve extravaganza?
Hear that, Ryuji?
This is your chance.
You have to invite Minorin to
that Christmas Eve party.
What...?
Don't give me that! Tell her
straight up how you feel!
T-T-Tell her how I feel?
I-I couldn't possibly...
You should.
I mean, it's Christmas Eve—the holy night.
And lovely angel Taiga
is a messenger of love.
A child sent from Heaven on Christmas!
The ideal obedient child!
Because Santa's watching me!
So I'll play Cupid to make
sure your love is fulfilled.
No thanks.
Now, now.
Wh—? H-Hey!
Well?
Don't I look like Cupid?
Uh, like I said before...
You don't.
Hot Guys Only
Jeez, you're late!
The exclusive Christmas party
for hot guys is through here.
Merry Christmas!
Ooh! Look, Nanako!
That boy's a real cutie!
I'm perfectly fine with
the intellectual type!
Heya!
What a wonderful gentleman!
This will be a long party!
Why not munch on this to keep you going?
Hey, where are you going?
What's wrong?
Am I not any fun?
Here I waited so we could entertain each
other, it being Christmas and all...
Yes!
Entertain each other!
Naked!?
We're naked!?
What?
You're looking for a cuter,
sexier, pretty Santa?
Are you...
talking about me!?
That's how my dream went.
Sick perv. Gross.
Please, Haruta-kun...
Didn't I get screwed over the most?
Anyway, we should talk about the real party.
We need to select a committee.
How about you, Tiger?
You keep saying how much
you love Christmas.
Oh, sounds good.
I-I-If you're all going to nominate
me, I-I'm willing to take the job!
But you're joining me, sugar-slug-dog!
R-Right...
Wait.
What kind of dog is that?
Minorin, join in!
Let's do this together!
Sorry.
I'll have to pass.
Huh? Why?
I'm actually not in the mood
for a Christmas party.
I don't have time to be merry.
What's wrong, Kushieda?
I made an unbelievable softball error.
It basically cost us the game.
It was so embarrassing.
If I attend a party after that, I'd lose
the respect of my teammates.
And we have another game after
New Year's, so I need to practice.
Minorin...
Uh, um...
Y-You can still come to the party, even
if you don't have time to be on—
I won't go.
Oh, fine. I'll join in her place.
Huh? Ami-chan?
Then count me in!
Doesn't a party sound fun?
We'll use the power of 2-C to fire things up!
Yeah!
Oh? What's with that look?
I'm not good enough for you?
Let's make this clear, Takasu-kun.
It's in your best interest to be nice to me.
Why?
I specialize in planning these things.
The success of this party,
and the odds of bringing a certain someone
out of her gloomy shell, lie solely with me.
What? Come again?
You decided you want to join in?
You're always welcome!
I already said that I can't.
Oh...
Minorin!
Wait up, Minorin!
What, you're going out?
With Taiga-chan?
Yeah.
Going to study for finals.
At the usual restaurant with
Kitamura and the gang.
There's a salmon steak in the frying pan.
Heat it up before you eat it.
What...?
I'll be totes lonely, yo.
D-Did you just say "totes"? And "yo"?
Haven't you heard?
It's a new fad.
One of the newcomers at work told me.
Dis is how people talk now, yo.
Cray-cray cute, yo!
- I'm like super-duper smart, yo-yo.
- Yeah, let's stop that.
You're totally butchering it.
What? Dis isn't wrong, yo!
Dis is so totes awesome, yo!
- Inko-chan, look after Yasuko for me.
- The super-duper bestest way, yo-ya-yo!
You're the only one I can count on.
- Impossible! Im-Impossible!
- Sh-She's turning on me!
What's wrong, Inko-chan?
What happened to your sweet
and lovely nature?
Oh, I know.
It's the book you borrowed.
Special Christmas Menu
Homemade Chicken Dinner
I'm sorry, Inko-chan!
That was very insensitive of me!
I'll never roast poultry in this house!
I swear!
R-Really?
Of course!
N-Never?
Never, ever!
What are you doing?
Well? Did you bring them?
Yeah, of course.
Got 'em right here.
The prize for winning
the Mr. Lucky Man contest,
also known as The Boss's notes.
They'll make studying for exams way easier.
But technically, these also
belong to Kushieda...
We won together, after all.
She said she can't study with us because
of work, so it doesn't matter.
Stop dwelling on the past like an old man.
I wasn't dwelling on the past...
Then start walking.
We're studying where Minorin's working.
Try to talk with her
before the others arrive.
R-Right!
Kushieda took the night off.
Please use the button to call me
when you're ready to order.
Hey, Ryuji.
Is Minorin avoiding you?
Wh-Why would she!?
You barely talk at school.
And I was the one who invited
her to study with us.
Because you told me to let you handle this.
So, have the two of you even talked lately?
N-No...
She was obviously lying about
having work tonight,
and she won't be coming to
the Christmas Eve party.
That's because she's feeling down
about making a mistake in a game.
And isn't this where you're
supposed to come in!?
But...
Something's not right.
I'm not sure how I'm supposed to help now.
You and Minorin have changed.
The two of you used to be more...
Yo, Takasu and Tiger.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm starving...
H-Hey...
Yo.
It's really cold today.
It's all about down!
Down coats are the best
for keeping you warm!
You should buy one, Maruo.
Kihara?
This is unusual. Why are you here?
I wanted a copy of The Boss's notes.
Plus, I don't feel like studying by myself.
Come on, let's sit.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll take this table.
Hey, Tiger.
Stand up!
Haruta sits on the inside.
Gotcha.
Kihara goes next to Takasu.
Wait...
There you are.
And I sit next to Haruta.
Kitamura's over there!
Wh-What? H-Hold on!
I want to sit over there!
Er, well, um...
Girls should sit together.
Right, Tiger?
Let's do that.
Don't be so selfish.
You don't want to sit next to Taka-chan?
No, no.
That's not it.
Let's order.
Everyone's okay with the drink buffet, yeah?
Sure, but there's no point in
making everyone get up.
I'll get our drinks.
U-Uh, I want something hot.
Yeah, yeah.
Tiger, help him grab the drinks.
Sure is chilly today.
Hey, what are you up to?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb.
Why are you throwing Taiga
and Kitamura at each other?
Jig's up, huh?
Oh well.
We want you to help.
I think Kitamura and Tiger
make a good match.
Ooh, me too!
And you know how Kitamura's heartbroken
after The Boss shot him down?
Don't you think a new love
would be the cure?
M-Maybe...
Tiger seems to have a thing for Kitamura.
And she's got it bad.
Knowing you, you probably didn't notice.
Yeah, you're surprised, right?
I was all, whoa...
Especially when you're the one who's been
closest to Tiger and looking after her.
Yep, yep. Only natural to be surprised.
You're so wrong...
About what?
Um...
N-Nothing...
You're right...
Wow!
This is amazing!
You're really excited about this.
Look at how beautiful it is!
Taiga is in love with Kitamura.
But I've known that the entire time.
So...
Why am I...?
- Hey, Takasu-kun!
- I don't get it...
Hello!?
Oh... Hey.
How do you feel about this, Takasu-kun?
Do you think the tiger and Maruo
should be a couple?
Well, that's...
A little sudden...
Right!? Don't you think!?
And no matter what they
say, it's not true, right?
Hold on...
What do you mean?
You don't want the tiger and
Maruo to date, do you?
They all say it's just 'cuz you're nice
and like to take care of others...
But the truth is that you love Tiger, right?
I'm rooting for you! For real!
Are you in love with Kitamura?
Hey, Kihara!
Hurry it up!
I'm coming!
Takasu-kun.
You can't give up!
Hey!
You're such a pain!
I said I'm coming!
Ohashi Shopping District
Grand confusion, Guns N' Roses, yo?
In those sleepless nights,
nemurenai yoruni wa
I lay there sighing all alone.
hitoride tameiki
What about everyone else?
minna wa dounano
It just feels so lonely.
nandaka samishii
A tiny little seed in this huge Earth.
hiroi daichini hitotsubu no tane
Stretch out those roots,
nekko nobashite
and bear a fruit that's still unripe.
mada aoi miwo tsuketa
The fruit that wants to
hurry and turn orange.
orenji ironi hayaku naritai kajitsu
Showering in your light
kimino hikari wo abite
only nurtures bigger ideals and dreams.
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
Why won't you notice?
kizuiteyo nee
I ate the orange today but cried
because it was still too sour.
orenji kyoumo tabete mitakedo
mada suppakute naita
It reminded too much of me,
watashi mitaide nokosenai kara
so I finished the whole thing.
zenbu tabeta
I love you. It makes me cry.
sukidayo nakeruyo
I love you. I love you.
sukidayo sukidayo
Underneath the Fir Tree
I'm sure it'll be fun!
It'll cheer you up!
So you have to come
to the party, Kushieda.
Can't undo what I've done...
Definitely... Probably...