Irisviel...
You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
So that nobody would have to cry ever again
we all scream and pray on fields stained red with blood
yet our pleas reach no one
I will be able to leave my solace behind
The moon's beautiful light
shines on all that makes up
the beginning
With eyes kept barely open I still see you far away
and trust your grief
Have I already lost them?
If I can't see them,
I'll sense them.
A chariot?
I have you, Rider!
Rider, look.
Isn't that her following us?
Well, if it isn't Saber.
Saves us the trouble of searching for her.
Actually...
Hey, boy,
are motorcycles normally this fast?
That's a motorcycle?
No, that's impossible.
But with Saber's Riding skill...
Perhaps it really is possible.
This will be fun.
I'll have to make this interesting.
We're going down?
Change of plans.
I shall race the girl to settle things with her.
Fine, but...
Take it seriously, okay?
Don't worry.
Nothing in Heaven or on Earth can stop me!
This is bad...
I'm reaching the machine's limits.
At this rate...
I'm so close.
Invisible Air!
No way...
She's closing the gap!
She'll catch up to us!
For a mechanical contraption to go so fast...
Splendid.
But this is a chariot!
It may be a fair race, but it needn't be polite.
Eat my dust, Saber!
Excellent!
You really are the proud King of Knights...
Truly the flower of the battlefield!
Don't underestimate me, King of Conquerors!
Rider!
Prepare yourself!
Irisviel...
isn't here?
No...
That was definitely Rider...
Then, where is Irisviel?
Did you think to trick me by imitating a Servant?
Rider's master lacks the intel-gathering skills to have found that place.
Tohsaka could not possibly have attacked.
By the process of elimination,
only the Matou could have kidnapped Irisviel.
Answer me.
Where is Irisviel?
I-I don't know.
I don't know anything!
Then where is Matou Kariya?
Kariya?
I don't know where that fool is!
I don't know!
I really don't know anything!
He left this morning with some guy
who said he was a supervisor from the Church!
A supervisor?
Kotomine Kirei...
I did not expect the real Rider to appear.
A fortuitous development.
Luck certainly favors you on the battlefield, doesn't it,
Matou Kariya?
Father,
was this little deception
really worth the use of two Command Seals?
Worry not, Kariya.
Now, hold out your hand.
As long as you work with me,
you may use your Command Seals without hesitation.
Even so...
That transformation ability...
A Noble Phantasm of this caliber is wasted on a servant of the Berserker class.
There are many stories about him becoming another,
in pursuit of some heroic deed.
So even with the Command Seal's control, that is the best result.
Your Servant's fixation on Saber is impressive.
Enough.
Begone, Berserker.
This woman...
Is she really the Grail's vessel?
More accurately, its contents.
Don't worry, Kariya.
I shall give you the Holy Grail.
But before that,
you made me another promise, Father.
Oh, that?
Everything is arranged.
Come to the Fuyuki church tonight at midnight.
You will find Tohsaka Tokiomi there.
Don't forget, Kariya...
Tonight, at midnight.
And your wish will be fulfilled.
Now, then...
We're alone.
I don't know who you are,
but show yourself.
So, you sensed me.
You are indeed a veteran Executor.
Matou Zouken?
Correct.
Hey, Rider...
We're really going to attack from here?
From this range?
Straight on?
The sword of light we saw at the river
has a delay before activation.
We'll strike then.
Why would you choose something so crazy?
Because it is crazy.
If she loses after all this, her defeat will be complete.
She may decide to be my retainer, after all.
You want to win her so badly?
On the battlefield, she is like a star.
But only as a part of my army
will she truly be able to shine.
Never was he interested in his opponent's power or wealth.
Without destroying or degrading them,
he sought to rule their souls.
Thus was he the King of Conquerors.
Very well, Rider...
Win by whatever means you wish.
Kid, it seems you finally begin to understand conquest.
Glory lies beyond the horizon!
Let us go...
Via Expugnatio!
Wind!
Ex...
calibur!
What do you want,
Matou Zouken?
Hmm...
I was quite interested to see what clever trick
you'd use to destroy Kariya.
You're willing to let the Matou's chance of victory dwindle away?
In truth, I enjoy watching him suffer.
I shall never tire of that.
Victory for the Matou, or a miserable end for him?
I'm honestly not sure which I'd prefer.
You enjoy watching your son suffer so?
I'd thought that you would have understood.
What?
You and I have the same scent.
That of a maggot,
attracted by the rotting meat of Kariya.
Oh, scary, scary.
Inexperienced or not, you are a dog of the Church.
Even teasing you endangers me.
We'll see each other again,
young one.
By our next meeting,
see that you allow your true nature to have ripened, to the point that it rivals my own.
Rider...
Sorry, boy.
I screwed up.
Rider!
Use Ionian Hetairoi!
The chariot is all I'm willing to expend on Saber.
But still...
She's gone.
A motorcycle, huh?
A magnificent vehicle.
Hey!
Those are your first words after defeat?
Hey, Rider...
How do we get back to town?
Well...
We'll have to walk.
Yeah, I guess so...
How many more days do I have?
how many more times can I fight?
But I'm still alive now.
I'm still...
Tohsaka...
Tokiomi!
Did you think you'd killed me, Tokiomi?
You were wrong.
Until I make you pay,
I'll keep coming back!
Tohsaka...
What?
Kariya?
Aoi?
No! It wasn't me!
This was...
Are you satisfied, Kariya?
Now the Matou
are sure to win the Holy Grail.
I...
Why?
Was it not enough to take Sakura from me?
Of all the things you could have done,
you killed him in front of me?
Why?
He...
It's because of him.
If it weren't for him,
no one would have had to suffer!
You...
Sakura...
You could have been happy!
Shut up!
What could you
possibly know of it?
You...
You've never even loved anyone!
I had someone I loved.
Warm and kind...
I wanted her to be happier than anyone else.
For you, I would throw away my life.
That's why I've endured this pain until now.
Endured...
Endured, endured, endured, endured, endured, endured, endured...
Endured it all!
You can't deny all that!
If you do, I'll never forgive you!
A lie, a lie, a lie!
I do have someone...
There is someone I love!
Who did I do this for?
Whose fault is it?!
If I'm going to die,
I may as well...
That was a terrible play.
But not so bad for a first attempt.
Well, Kirei?
What do you think?
The wine's taste...
It's different than I remembered.
Then I see that you begin to understand what it means to expand your horizons.
If it would taste this wonderful...
then I would dearly love
to sample it again.
Episode 21:
Knight on Two Wheels
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
By my Command Seal, I order you...
Open your eyes, and behold!
Tonight, I shan't hold back.
He must be eliminated at once.
How do he and I differ?
If he doesn't doubt, then what?!
Who am I?
Next Time:
All the Evil in the World