This isn't... isn't over yet!
Eat this!
What?
I-I did it!
W-Winner, Class A.
Eh? What? Rep?
What?
The Summoned Being Exam War is now over and a new morning has begun.
These can't be...
Drawing boards and matts.
I didn't think it could get worse than cardboard boxes.
It could have been a lot worse.
Totally didn't see it coming.
Sorry, Himeji-san.
No, there's nothing for you to apologize for, Akihisa-kun.
The Summoned Being Exam War was fun.
Himeji-san.
Geez, stop pouting. We lost and that's it.
We can still take classes using the drawing boards.
You have to make these things work, right?
It makes it feel more fun, sort of like sketching, right?
What's wrong, Mizuki?
Um.. Well, I can't see the bottom.
What are you doing, Minami?
What else? I'm gonna start another Summoned Being Exam War!
Just let it go, Shimada.
We can't declare war for another three months.
But I hate these drawing boards!
Your breasts won't get in your way, and plus, it looks good on you.
And my joints can't be bent in that direction!
I feel like I haven't been attacked for a long time.
What do you mean, "It looks good on me"?
Almost... Almost... Almost.
Hm?
Almost... Almost... Almost... Almost...
I can almost see, almost see...
Almost, almost, almost...
You're on fire. Fire! Ninja Pervert!
Whoa, the fire's gone.
What's wrong? You're already down, Ninja Pervert?
Kudou!
I went through the trouble of putting on a bra just for you today, Ninja Pervert.
It's a cute one.
Hmph. Your point?
Your body's being more honest.
Don't worry! I know, Ninja Pervert!
Awaken!
Ah.
Sorry, Ninja Pervert, I forgot that the Black Iron Bracelet broke.
Where are you going, Ninja Pervert?
Please give Akihisa approval to summon his Summoned Being.
What's it for?
To take off someone's bra.
I can't approve that.
I wonder if this is all we have after all.
Well, something to that extent.
But I can't accept how we lost.
A defeat is a defeat.
We fought using our fighting skills instead of our test scores.
Both sides were on the same terms.
However, they were able to attack us without being distracted by the surrounding situation,
so they had a slight advantage.
We lost because we let our guard down.
But—
That's how it is. The result is all that matters in the end, so...
Did something happen, Aki-kun?
You said that diligence is only a means to an end, right?
Yeah, I did.
I couldn't get the results. I wonder if I'm really just an ordinary idiot after all.
It's true that you're a fool if you take pride in your own efforts.
However, it's not a bad thing if others praise your efforts.
Nee-san...
Aki-kun, I think you did your best. I'm proud to have you as my little brother.
Thank you, Nee-san.
It's okay for you to dwell on your loss for now.
What? Don't people normally cheer other people up by saying "Don't dwell on it"?
It's important to accept a defeat as a defeat.
If a person had never experienced the emotional impact of defeat,
he neither learns how to stand back up after he falls nor how to move on.
So dwell as much as you like.
But when you're done, stand up and move on towards your future.
Okay!
While you're still dwelling on it, I'll be there to comfort you.
I could sleep by your side or take a bath with you.
Huh?
Which would you like?
Neither.
Don't hold back—I'm your sister after all.
That's exactly why I'm holding back!
When I'm done dwelling, stand up and move on towards my future.
Sign - Idiot
My future.
I wonder if there's still something I can do...
Okay, I've decided!
So we're taking a bath together?
That's not what I meant.
So that concludes the Summoned Beings Exam War report.
Who is it?
What did you come here for, Yoshii?
I have a request: please let us have another Exam War with Class A.
That's not possible. If you want to declare another war, wait three months.
I can't wait that long!
That's the rule of this academy. We can't change it.
Please.
I just can't... accept it ending like this! Please!
I'd like to ask for that too.
I can't accept the way we won either.
Class A did happen to win;
however, I hate to admit it, but they had us on the end of our ropes during the battle.
Kinoshita-san? And Kirishima-san?
You two...
That was not how Class A, the class that represents the Academy, should have won.
I don't think the students from the other classes accept it either.
That's why...
I'd like to request for a rematch, too.
All of you.
Do you know why this academy implemented the Summoned Being Exam War System?
We cannot bend the rules. But...
we do still owe you for the system's malfunctioning.
I'm also responsible for letting you use the prototype bracelet.
If you are that insistent, I suppose I'll make an exception.
Exception?
Do you really want to swap setups with Class A?
What?
If not, there's another option for you.
What?!
Fight Class A again?
We can fight?
I can't believe that hag approved such a thing.
This is amazing, Akihisa-kun!
Y-Yeah...
All right! We'll crush them for sure this time!
Shall we come up with a new plan?
Well, Yuuji, it's a little different this time.
Hm?
What?!
You'll duel?!
Yeah. It's been decided that I'll fight Class A's Rep in a test.
With Class A's Rep... Shouko?!
If I win, although we can't exchange setups,
they said they'll grant us a small request.
Your opponent is the top student of Second-year, you know that, right?!
Can you win, Aki?
Are you going to be okay, Akihisa-kun?
I'll be fine.
I won't cause you guys trouble.
Then Akihisa, what happens if you lose?
They'll grant the other side one request.
If I win, I'm asking for my marriage registration form back.
It wasn't yours to begin with!
You bastard! You said you wouldn't cause us trouble!
My life is at stake here!
Life
It's nothing of importance!
Once the war is done, we'll go on our honeymoon right away.
No way!
Yuuji, how many kids do you want?
Akihisa, you bastard. Win at any cost! Don't you dare fucking lose!
Shouko, go easy on him!
I remember that you told me not to hold back.
Damn it! My life is over!
You already decided that I'll lose.
But it's true.
Even though I can fight again, fighting against Kirishima-san all by myself is...
Stupid Onii-chan!
Hm?
Hazuki-chan!
Here, a present for you!
Whoa, you can bake cookies?!
I learned it in home economics class!
I'm not very good at it though.
Thanks Hazuki-chan.
All right! Can you do your best now?
Eh?
I see. Thanks, knowing I have your support will help.
Yeah, these taste great.
You might have a talent for this.
Thank you! I couldn't bake them very well, and I ended up burning them several times.
But I didn't give up and I kept on trying, so I was able to do it eventually.
Okay!
What's the matter, Onii-chan?
I'll try hard and won't give up either!
I don't have anything to lose. I'll try my best. Thanks, Hazuki-chan!
Yup!
I'm home.
Welcome home, Aki-kun.
I'll cram overnight, I'll do anything I have to!
I'll become able to answer as many questions as I have to!
wn
Due to the special exception,
sh owdown
the battle between Class A Rep Kirishima Shouko
Test Sh ow
and Class F student Yoshii Akihisa will now begin.
Test Sh owdown
The duel will follow Sudden Death Rules.
Sudden Death Rules
The rules of Sudden Death are:
the students are both given the same question to answer at the same time;
the game ends after the first mistake;
Sign - Lose
and the one who made the mistake loses.
In other words, the first one to mess up is eliminated.
At Fumizuki Academy, you are given an unlimited number of questions in tests,
but the questions get harder with time.
That means that the duel will be decided early on.
Akihisa-kun...
Well then, let's begin!
Good luck, Akihisa!
Yuuji...
I believe that you can win!
You, too, believe in your own ability and do your best! Fight!
So he gives his earnest support when his future is at stake, huh?
Question 1:
Write the proverb that means the following:
"To fail at something which one is good at."
This one's easy.
Unless Akihisa is beyond stupid, he won't mess up at the beginning.
Oh! He's already stressing out!
What?!
How's that?
Accidents happen to the best of us
Even monkeys fall from trees
All right!
Both are correct.
Don't scare me like that, Akihisa!
I'm nervous. What can I do?
Question 2:
Answer how to calculate the area of a circle.
Radius x Radius x Pi
Yes! Kirishima-san made a mistake!
Huh? What? How come?! Why?!
I'm surprised you were able to enter high school like this.
Well then, question 3.
It's not like it can't be eaten, but it's still not quite there yet.
Aki must be fighting hard now.
I hope I can make something that could be called a reward.
I'll try hard as well.
Question 30:
Name the year that the Twelve Level Cap and Rank System was established.
Both are correct.
Whoa...
Good going, Akihisa!
You can do this!
Phew, I managed to guess right on the topics to study for, so I've been doing fine so far.
But she wouldn't make a mistake so easily, would she?
All it takes is one question and I'll lose.
Question 31:
Name the person who defeated the last king of the Achaemenid Empire of Persia
and started his eastern campaign in 334 B.C.
Another history question.
This one's hard.
Akihisa-kun...
Alexander the Third
Alexander the Great
Both are correct.
Whoa! He got it right!
Nice job, Aki!
Even I wouldn't make a mistake on Alexander the Great now, would I?
They'll be done with the easy questions soon.
So things will gradually get tougher for him, huh?
Akihisa-kun...
Question 32:
Japan's very first imperial era name was "Taika."
Name the year the Taika Reform took place in the Christian Era.
Whoa!
This question is...
A free right answer.
Obviously, they both will get it right.
We have to wait to see who wins until the next question.
What's the matter, Akihisa?
T-Taika Reform... Which year was that?
What?!
What the hell? You bastard! You don't know it even after all of this?
That's exactly why I got confused as to which one was correct!
Stop messing around, you idiot!
The key word is "reform." I know that much.
Reform... Reform...
645... or 625?
Re-four-m.
Reform... Reform... Reform...
Akihisa-kun.
Aki...
Which... Which one?!
If I make a mistake here, it'll be all over...
Aki!
Akihisa-kun!
Damnit!
Aki!
Akihisa!
That idiot... He's given up!
No, he hasn't! That's...
That's Striker Sigma V!
Go!
Stop it, you idiot!
That's the wrong answer!
What?!
It's over... My life is over...
Winner, Yoshii Akihisa, Year 2, Class F.
What?!
I-I got it right?
You did it, Aki!
Good job, Akihisa!
Akihisa-kun!
Shouko, why'd you do that?
Because I promised...
Hm?
that I'd never forget.
I'm sorry.
Besides, I got what I wanted, so...
Huh?
I'm going to City Hall now.
How'd you get it?
A kind person gave it to me.
Don't tell me...
Kindness never goes unrewarded.
I never imagined that you'd win.
Principal...
So then, as promised, we'll grant your request.
Thank you very much.
What did you request, Akihisa-kun?
Well it's...
Okay then, Himeji. We'll give you another placement test.
What? Akihisa-kun... Don't tell me...
This was the whole reason I wanted to start the Summoned Being Exam War.
Even if we couldn't, I at least wanted you to be able to study using good equipment, so...
Then...
You can go to the class that suits you.
Isn't that great, Himeji?
That's...
Akihisa-kun...
What is it?
Are you...
Are you okay with this?
It'll be a bit lonely without you, but if it's good for you, then that's the best.
I see...
Thank you very much, Akihisa-kun.
Yup!
Second Placement Exam
Well then, begin!
There're tons of people who're only good at academics in this world.
But no matter how high one's individual ability is, there's always a limit.
Those who only worry about their own strength never exceed it.
When I was in school, it was only natural for everyone to work hard together.
You don't gain much by working hard only for yourself.
What's important for now is that you understand that.
That's it!
Looks like you did well. This'll be enough for you to go to Class A.
Yes sir.
We'll let you know the results.
You can go home now.
Um...
What is it?
I made one big mistake. Please let me fix it!
The test is over. You're not allowed to change anything.
But...
Don't worry. You answered a lot. This should be enough.
Please!
Hm?
No matter what...
No matter what, I have to fix it!
Please!
Good morning, Aki.
Morning, Akihisa.
Morning.
Good morning.
Yoshii.
Ah, good morning, Kirishima-san.
I took the form to City Hall, but they rejected it.
Shouko's Imagination
City Hall
In Japan, men must be 18 and above to get married.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Akihisa-kun.
Aki, have you seen Mizuki yet?
No, I haven't seen her today.
I see.
It'll be harder and harder to see her when she's in a different class.
Yeah.
Did you hear, Akihisa?
What?
Himeji's placement test score. I hear it's pretty certain she's going to be in Class A.
I see...
Was it really okay?
Yeah, Class F isn't where she should be.
She should study comfortably in the furnished Class A.
If that's how you feel, we're fine with it, too.
But Akihisa... It doesn't look like things are as you planned.
Good morning, Akihisa-kun.
Himeji-san? What're you doing here?!
Did you forget something?
No, this is my classroom.
What. I thought it was certain you were going to join Class A.
About that...
To tell you the truth, I forgot to write my name so I got a zero.
So I've been placed in Class F again.
Himeji-san...
So, I'm looking forward to studying with you again, Akihisa-kun!
What's the matter, Aki?
Are you crying for joy?
I'm happy for you, Akihisa.
Happy ending.
That damn hag!
You damn old hag!
What'd you barge in here and call me a damn old hag for, you brat?
This is wrong, isn't it?
Why does Himeji-san get a zero?
She forgot to put her name, of course she'd get a zero.
That isn't right! Since she took the test alone,
even if she didn't write her name, it's completely obvious that it was her!
You didn't even realize that? You idiot!
I never thought I'd be called an "idiot" by you.
In any case, please give her her points back.
Or let her retake the placement exam from the start.
You really are dumb, aren't you?
Huh?
What?
Idiot.
A real idiot.
Akihisa-kun, you really are an idiot.
What?! Y-You're saying that too, Himeji?! Why?!
Idiot!