Stop moving!
I don't need any...
You can't do it without this!
This is the Miss Contest.
It's a beauty contest.
How cute do you really think you are?
In the end...
Taiga's old man didn't make it to the pro-wrestling show.
Kushieda, who always encourages Taiga...
Didn't even come to the dressing room.
Class 2-C, you have twenty minutes.
Oh crap!
I need to prepare as the emcee.
Takasu-kun, what about the costume?
Y-Yeah...
It's done.
I just changed a few things to something Taiga already had.
It looks great, Takasu-kun!
Really?
The image was... Yeah, Juliet's dress.
An Empire Silhouette.
Loose and flowing...
Takasu-kun's kind of... Dangerous?
Maybe his scary looking face is not the only thing frightening about him.
There are some accessories as well.
Taiga, could you try...
Are you still waiting for your dad?
Surely he's not coming.
I'm not waiting for him!
Since he's probably late because of work,
I thought I'd get him to buy me something to apologize.
But, don't you think you should change your lines when you come on?
They don't have to be changed.
Just do it exactly like we discussed.
But...
Kawashima-san, it's time!
Sorry! I'm coming!
Hey, seriously, it's okay?
Stop asking!
I see.
If you say so.
Hey, what was that about just now?
Nothing.
Takasu-kun, we're going to change now, so you need to leave.
Got it.
Aisaka-san too.
Yeah.
I can't just smile and watch my friend get hurt.
I absolutely can't.
Taiga's old man...
Is definitely coming, right?
Even if he's incredibly late...
He'll come running, right?
That's what fathers do.
It's time for what you've all been waiting for.
The Miss Ohashi High School Contest!
Ami-chan, those fish-net stockings are nice, nice!
Ami, Ami!
Ami Ami, nice!
Order, everyone.
If you don't quiet down, I just might punish you!
I said be quiet! You idiots!
Pigs who can't fly are nothing but dead meat!
Just kidding!
That girl...
Even though she's the emcee, she plans to steal all the scenes?
Let's continue!
Entry number 1.
First year, Class A, Mitsu Yuriko-san!
W-
Welcome home, Master!
You're a very cute maid!
Are you portraying a Victorian maid?
Yes!
Thank you!
No one's listening.
Let me introduce the next contestant.
She's also in a wonderful maid's outfit.
Mail?
Entry number 2.
You're kidding me... Right?
I've got something I'd like you to tell Taiga, is that okay?
I've gotta leave because of work.
Some things came up and we can't live together either.
Could you apologize to the Princess for me?
Thanks.
Why...
Did I believe him?
I tried to convince myself that...
"This is a good thing."
"I've got to support Taiga."
But...
In reality, I was probably lonely somehow.
Taiga's father showed up.
Taiga was going somewhere far away.
I didn't want to see that pathetic me...
What the hell is that?
You've got to be kidding me.
That's right.
Everything was because of me...
I...
Takasu, you okay?
You don't look too good.
Takka-chan?
How do I tell Taiga?
What kind of expression should I have?
Everyone, thank you for waiting.
Second year, Class C. You already know her as Tenori Taiga.
It's Aisaka Taiga-san!
That's Tenori Taiga?
Wow...
She's cute.
Today, would you believe it?
I'm told that Aisaka-san's father is in the audience!
The lines she mentioned in the dressing room!
If you please, Sir, a word of support for Aisaka-san!
He's probably not here!
Next, next!
Tai-
H-Hey...
Aisaka-san?
Are you okay, Aisaka-san?
Hey, Yankee Takasu-kun is cheering on his partner!
But, she really is cute, Tenori Taiga.
You're doing great!
Tenori Taiga, you're the best!
Don't worry about your dad!
Hey, wa-
Hey!
That kind of father...
I already crushed him, d-dumped him, and threw him away!
I'll do your "appeal time"!
Hey! Bring that!
Y-Yes!
Close it!
Don't lift it!
Open it!
Yes!
I...
Can't do anything for her.
This year's Miss Ohashi is...
Aisaka Taiga-san!
That's great, Taiga!
With everyone's support, Taiga...
No.
That's not it.
She's all alone up there.
Takasu?
I need to go.
I need to go to her.
I might not be what she needs.
Even so!
What is it?
It's dark!
What's going on?
Hey!
The Miss Contest is over!
Now it's time for the Mister Contest!
This is how it's going to go!
It's Mister Lucky Guy!
Mister?
Lucky Guy?
What's that?
A course has been prepared on the school yard.
Just run!
The first one to reach the goal is the Mister Contest winner.
You're going to make us run a race at the Cultural Festival?
I don't really feel like it.
By the way, the guy who wins...
Will be able to crown this year's Miss Ohashi with this tiara, ask her to dance...
And get all of my notes from all of my classes over the past three years.
Questions from class and answers to all the exams.
The president's notebooks!?
Dance with Taiga, seriously?
No way that's going to happen.
I want them!
Taiga...
I don't need the prize.
It has nothing to do with being the "Lucky Guy."
Right now...
No matter the method...
Everyone, be careful not to injure yourselves!
Before anyone else can...
Before anything can happen...
As fast as possible!
Scary!
Yankee!
He's going to kill us.
On your mark!
Ready!
I have to go to where Taiga is!
The goal is one lap around the park!
Run! Run!
Run all the way!
I got him!
Takasu is down!
Alright! Now's our chance!
Those bastards...
I won't lose!
They're here, they're here!
Good luck!
Takasu-kun's come back!
I get it now.
I...
Sorry!
That hurt!
Pain in the ass!
Takasu-kun? How?
On the fence?
Why would he go that far?
Shut up!
I've got a lot going on. Leave me alone!
I definitely...
Can't lose!
This is no time to be impressed!
You too!
They're here, they're here.
The leaders have come back...
Ryuji.
Mi-
Kushieda!
Why is a girl...?
Kushieda?
Is it okay?
It doesn't matter! Girls can participate too!
Takasu-kun, when you met that man, were you really looking at him with both eyes open?
Were your eyes really looking?
She was absolutely right.
I was trying to ignore all the signs.
Even the fact that he used to just send money to pay for her living expenses every month...
Saying whatever he wanted, pulling her every which way without thinking about Taiga's needs.
Even when he had to apologize for breaking his promise...
He just left it all up to me in an email.
He wasn't thinking about Taiga from the start!
And...
I couldn't see through that.
I'm a huge idiot!
Ryuji.
Minorin.
Crap.
Track and field pride!
Kushieda!
And you call yourselves men?
Kushieda-senpai!
Take this!
Alright!
Takasu-kun, please go!
For Taiga's sake, please go!
What are you...
Now's our chance!
Hey!
Shinaba morotomo attack!
Go!
Before anyone...
Before me...
You...
Don't have to worry so much.
You saw me, right?
Even by myself, I can get up.
That's why...
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me all the time.
I'm okay!
Because I can get up by myself.
I can live...
By myself.
Our classmates!
The Miss Contest and the Lucky Man!
Our class took everything!
The festival was a big success.
Yes.
Your last Cultural Festival.
I'm glad I was the student council president of this school.
I'm glad I was with you guys.
I still have things to do.
You go have fun, Kitamura.
But...
After all, you were the one that worked the hardest for this festival.
I...
I'm going!
From the very beginning...
I never really cared about that guy.
Really.
Not at all.
But...
Taiga, you...
More importantly, getting first place with Minorin...
You just suddenly decided to make up?
You really...
Minorin!
Taiga! So this is where you were.
Minorin, Minorin, Minorin!
I like you, I like you, I love you!
Okay, okay, I got it, I got it, I got it!
You're cute, Taiga.
The tiara looks really good on you.
It's the tiara you gave me.
Takasu-kun too, right?
I know nothing! I saw nothing! I heard nothing!
That Stupid Chihuahua is in heat again!
Hey!
Hey, what're you doing?
A year ago, the same thing happened.
Taiga's father just showed up.
I was happy.
He said, "Let's live together!"
But...
Like this time, her father...
Suddenly disappeared.
I'm sorry, Takasu-kun.
Why?
No matter how you look at it, I'm the one that has to apologize!
No, it's me.
I knew what her father was really like, but I kept it from you.
Taiga didn't tell me anything.
To me...
Taiga's someone I care for dearly.
I suppose... I was just jealous...
Of you.
I wonder why Taiga didn't tell you.
Because if she had told, I would have gotten mad.
Taiga doesn't want people to think badly of her father.
So, since that event a year ago, she won't say anything about her family...
Not to me.
Where did she go? That Stupid Chihuahua.
Aisaka.
Are you by yourself?
Would you like to dance with me?
I guess I can't, since I'm not the Lucky Guy.
Again...
Why are you...
Always...
Aisaka?
Nothing.
Thanks.
Well then...
I wonder how you dance...
You take each other's hand, look into each other's eyes...
And keep going round and round until you get tired of it...
Probably.
I might... Like girls better.
Sometimes I think that...
I... Hope that's not true...
Yeah, you're right.
I'm...
Talking normally.
Whaddya doing, Takasu-chan!?
You're so cold! Let's all have fun together!
After all, we're the best class!
That's right!
Kitamura and Taiga captured!
Taiga.
Alright!
Let's dance!
It's the night of the Cultural Festival!
This night is... Special...
A lot of feelings are all mixed up...
And every time I laugh...
My heart hurts, just a little.
But when this night is over...
I'm sure...
Probably...
Everything will be alright.
To everyone watching!
Would you like to decide fate?
I'm going invoke the legend of Happy Tenori Taiga with some incredible magic.
"And as always, it's my turn."