When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
A Happy New Year!
The first thing of the year.
We'll start the...
Hayate no Gotoku's customary activity,
She means for the first time.
New Year's Hidden Trick Competition!
Shouldn't the host be Ma***aki?
The set was reused from Laugh! Big ****** Battle.
Here's the first skit.
The Red Team!
Live music of various instruments and a jump through a ring of fire!
It's hot! It's hot!
10 points, 10 points, 10 points, 10 points, and 10 points.
Followed by the White Team.
Standup comedy in various languages and a jump through a ring of fire.
I can't do this!
It's impossible!
You're being unreasonable!
I'll die from this!
10 points, 10 points, 10 points, 10 points, and 10 points.
A word of comment please, head judge.
It's idiotic.
Isn't there anything better on New Year's?
"Osechi is good, but eat ***** too," they say.
Oh, if I remember correctly, a new show starts today.
Really?
Hayate no Gotoku! Giant!
"Giant"? Is Hayate going to get big?
Then that'll make this show the same as an old show that made the hero a giant to counter the viewing rate.
Shut up!
Wow! Silver Mask!
Did you all know there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
Happy New Year's to you all.
Hayate no Gotoku Giant is starting.
Not!
It's New Year's Eve.
This year's finally coming to an end.
Would you like to go to a shrine for the first worship?
What? Stay home and read manga, play MMOs, and watch anime.
That's the Japanese style New Year's we proudly present to the world!
I guess so, in a way.
So you've regained your memory!
Oh right. I got sucked into Baltra Space and sent to Kujyuukuri.
Look, Dionimes. It's the dawn of mankind.
Now that you mention it, today's the New Year.
For the first sunrise seen with one's destined man to be the New Year's sunrise...
How romantic...
I guess it's not such a bad idea.
Songs speak to the world and the world speaks to songs.
This year is finally coming to an end.
A lot of things happened since coming to this mansion.
It's all thanks to Milady that I was able to spend the year alive, so I must be thankful to her.
If you say that so straightforwardly, it's embarrassing.
Milady! Where did you come from?!
Besides, what are you doing here?
Well, it's not such a big deal, but well...
I wanted to see the sunrise.
Note: "Asahi" means sunrise and is also
the name of a major newspaper in Japan
What? This show is by Shougakukan.
Note: Hayate has a relatively minor sports newspaper and seems interested in the UFO article.
Are you trying to sell out the show?
I see, I see. So is that head of yours what made you think of that stupid pun?
I'm sorry.
Gosh! You don't understand me!
I'm saying let's go view the first sunrise of the year at a beautiful beach!
Just you and me!
What? What's the point?
Shut up, you idiot!
Quit blabbing and get ready!
Y-Yes!
Um, we're going by bike?
Yeah. It's a secret from Klaus,
so we can't use a car or a helicopter.
Um, you mentioned a beach. Which one to be exact?
Kujyuukuri Beach.
What's wrong?
Um, the beach is 100km away, roughly speaking.
Wouldn't you  make it there in about an hour?
One hour would be a little...
Is it?
Oh well all we need to worry is making it there by sunrise, so let's take our time.
No, really. Wouldn't it be better to go with Maria-san and everyone else?
SFX: Ahaha~
Like using a car or helicopter, perhaps?
I said I want to go with you.
Or what, you don't want to be alone with me?
Absolutely not.
Tandem bicycle riding is a violation of traffic law, but Nerima Ward is pretty much entirely Sanzenin property, so it's not a problem.
What a convenient anime.
It's adult reasoning.
If you look back, it's hard to believe that I had a debt of 150 million yen dumped on me by my parents...
...and was almost sent to a resort island by very kind people.
Yeah, since it really was an unbelievable setting.
I-I guess.
But, we were able to meet thanks to that.
B-By the way, Hayate.
D-Does this bicycle come with a heater?
Huh?
My legs are starting to get cold.
I think you're asking for the impossible.
Your idea of going to the beach in the middle of the winter on a bicycle was a little reckless.
What? It's not reckless.
If I had instrumented a better skirt,
this project would have worked out.
Look at you. You'll catch a cold at this rate.
We have a long way ahead, so how about coming up with a new instrumentality project?
I guess you're right.
This is the legendary diamond pear card that exceeds the famous, non-limit black card.
No matter how amazing a card it may be,
it'll only be a convenience store or Don Q***ote.
W-Welcome.
Welcome.
No way!
Isn't this the prestigious department store?
It's usually closed at this hour!
I'll pay for everything with this.
Most certainly.
Milady, this is...
What, you don't even know what a chariot is?
Usually cows pull this.
They even attached it to the bike.
I'm the cow?!
Nagi? Nagi?
Where did she go to?
I don't see Hayate-kun around, either.
She left her manga out again.
Love at Kujyuukuri?
Could she have...
Shiwasu.
Shiwasu: December in old Japanese.
It means everything is busy and even teachers run around.
And, the debt-ridden butler was running, too.
Financial Drift!
This anime follows the speed limit.
This is amazing, Hayate!
There's no one that matches your ability on highways.
That's right. No one can possibly catch up to me with my boots on maximum output!
Hey, but are we allowed to get on the highway on a bicycle?
Good thing I bought the highway in advance.
Adult reasoning.
Yeah, exactly.
Flashing?
On the highway, that's the signal for the start of the race.
Hayate.
I know.
A miracle is just about to begin!
What will you do, Michael?
I have faith in you, CHITT.
Nobody!
Drives in front of me!
I can see time...
It's the deadly high speed curve! 600R!
I will wipe him out of my rearview mirror at this corner!
Like you have a rearview mirror.
27.8% chance of clearing the curve at full throttle.
I have faith in you, CHITT.
Don't spill, Michael.
I can do this...
Secret technique!
Ditch Run!
What shall we do, Michael! Michael?!
Chitt, use the rocket booster!
That's ridiculous! You must be an idiot!
Michael! Michael!
One man can change the world!
You hate to admit the mistakes you make due to youth.
This anime is  obeying the speed limit.
It's pitch dark, but it's the ocean!
It's the ocean!
I can't go on anymore...
Looks like we can watch the first sunrise of the year together.
Ocean!
A-Anyway, I'll go buy something warm.
Yup. I'll wait right here.
Ocean!
Come to think of it, I didn't bring my wallet with me.
Here you go.
M-Maria-san!
Even for you, it's dangerous to go at that speed with someone in the back.
I'm sorry. I was pushing the speed limit.
We'll take care of the bike and the chariot, so please use that money to come back.
I'm sorry...
Really... For all the trouble I cause you...
Not at all. I'm the one who should be thanking you.
You're protecting and guiding Nagi well.
Of course, there are still tiny problems.
I'm not doing much.
She has looked happy ever since you've come.
And so have I.
Oh, also-
Happy New Year, Hayate-kun.
Happy New Year to you, too.
I hope we get along well this year, too.
Yes!
Milady!
The sun will rise soon.
Here's an oshiruko.
Also, Happy...
...New...Year's...
Happy New Year's, Milady.
Karuta asobi demo shimashouka?
Karuta asobi demo shimashouka? = Shall we play with karuta cards?
Karutaka... Kattaru
Karutaka... Kattaru = Karuta cards, eh... So lame.
Night on New Year's day.
It's heavy snow before you know it.
It's covered in white out there.
By the way, Sakuya-san called saying she'll visit for a New Year's greeting.
What? Saku's coming?
Actually, why are you dressed up?
Oh why can't I? Since we don't do any New Year's activities.
New year... Heavy snow around the world... Global warming...
We never know when our peaceful life might end.
Humans must pay attention to ecology while reflecting on great prosperity.
It's not persuasive at all to hear you say that
while playing a portable game in a warmed room.
It's portable, so I'm playing a role in the ecology.
Oh my, we're having a black out?
Are you both all right?
Ah, Hayate-kun. I'm fine, but Nagi is...
Be... Because it got dark all of a sudden...
I see. The electrical line must have fallen due to the snow.
The emergency circuit should come on at times like this.
The circuit breaker in the annex could be down.
We'll have to go turn it back on.
Then go do whatever you need to with the breaker.
I'll die if it's this dark.
Milady...
Could you do something while the battery in the game she's playing to distract herself lasts?
Roger that!
The time limit is about three hours.
Tonight's mission is to bring the electricity back.
The destination is the power plant about 1km away from this main building.
In any case,
it's a butler-like job I get to do once in a while.
I've got to do my best!
SFX: GHOOOOOOOOOOOO
By the way, outside is a blizzard.
Wow...
I-It's blowing harder than I'd thought.
This is supposed to be Tokyo.
We're in middle of Nerima.
Is this the famous tsundere?
The Earth must be becoming tsundere.
You mean, becoming like tundra.
For your information, tsundere is...
Anyway, let's go take a look.
I won't go anywhere, so please don't pull, okay?
If you do, I'd start spinning.
Y-You said Saku was coming, didn't you?
You're right. Where could she be?
It'd be funny if we found her stranded in the yard.
No, that's not funny at all.
B-But, this blizzard might really leave me stranded here.
However, I must get the electricity back for the sake of Milady, who's shivering in the dark.
I can't lose!
I can't lose.
I can't lose to snow like this!
Wait! This is a snow blower!
And what are you doing here?!
Hey.
"Wait! This is a snow blower!"
Good job. Nice jab.
Don't tell me you were waiting at this really cold place just for this, Sakuya-san?
Pretty much.
Nice jab!
What's the point of this?
He's getting better.
What happened to your butlers?
When I plugged the thing in, the mansion's building went out, so they went running to fix it.
This is the cause of the blackout?
Sorry.
At any rate, you'll catch a cold if you stay here for so long.
Please hurry up and go inside.
I'd like to, but...
Which way inside?
We might really die here.
SFX: GHOOOOOOOOOOOO
Anyway, this isn't a snowy mountain or anything.
We will manage.
Please follow me.
Hey, you're surprisingly reliable.
An hour has passed.
SFX: GHOOOOOOOOOOOO
Hey, can I take my words back?
Can you not wait for just a little longer?
What?!
Yeti! It's a Yeti!
Perfect! I'll go ask for directions.
A Yeti must know the way around the snow well.
He was kind enough to tell me.
What?
I take back saying I take back my words.
He is pretty amazing.
This is the power plant. Pika.
My jacket's soaked.
Yes. We're literally soaked.
It took more time than expected to get here, so I better turn the breaker on and switch to the emergency circuit.
You don't get wind blowing in here, but it's still really cold.
I see. It's a geothermal power plant.
Looks like this place has an onsen, as well, so how about a dip?
SFX: BLUSH
Onsen?
Onsen at a place like this, with just the two of us...
That's embarrassing...
How so?
What was that for?!
Shut up, you fool!
That one seriously pissed me off!
So, why?
You want another smack?!
Get your ass over here.
Why are you doing this?
Shut up!
Please stop!
Stop moving.
So, how about it?
Like I've been saying, what is?
I am the oldest sister, so don't treat me like a kid too much.
I don't want to hear that from a person who does something like this.
How dare you! Then take this!
I was joking!
I'm not treating you like a kid.
O-Okay.
Great, I put myself in a bad situation.
I think I'm going to be dizzy.
What should we do? The breaker is still far from here.
Seeing how soaked we are,
we might freeze to death before we get there.
But I can't make Milady wait any longer!
I'm sorry. Should I come with you?
No, I think you shouldn't.
Since, you are a girl, after all.
I'll be going now.
Is that the waterproof cell phone ******** advertising?
Hey, Makita?
Is Kunieda there, too?
Two hours and fifty minutes into the mission.
Five more meters to the breaker room.
But, the drenched debt-ridden butler was facing the verge of death.
Oh no... My sight's starting to fade from the cold.
I might have done better if I'd gone naked.
That's visually a bad idea.
I'll die at this rate.
But... Just a little more...
Just a little more and I can provide the electricity for Milady...
But, I'm... already...
Milady...
Oh no, the lamp's light went out.
What?
Could... Could something have happened to Hayate?
My Gladi**** is dead.
Could this be a sign?
I think that's because you looked away.
The light's back.
So Hayate must be all right!
But your Gladi**** is dead.
I managed to get the breakers back up, but I can't get any strength in my body.
Oh man... It's so cold, I can't take another step.
Milady...
Maria-san...
I'm...
I had a good life.
Hayate!
You can't give up! Get yourself together!
Sakuya-san?
We're here to save you.
You're fine now.
Look at you, you're freezing.
Your hands are really warm.
You did well.
I was thinking wrongly of you.
You are an amazing guy.
Yes, but, since it's winter, this chilly weather...
I'm sick of it.
Just kidding.
Makita! Kunieda! We'll leave that idiot here!
Yes, ma'am.
Wait, Sakuya-san!
Oh no, the lamp cracked.
Looks like my Gladi**** is completely dead.
On another note, is Hayate really all right out there?
This is how the first night of the new year ends.
Next week, we'll fight against sudden farewells.
Nagi and,
Hayate's
Butler Network!
Summoned and appeared. I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
A new development begins starting this week.
With a new enemy to face, the tension is building up again.
Next week, a mysterious rival character will transfer in.
To spoil you, he joins our side close to
the final episode and fights against evil.
Did you watch the show, Milady?
It wasn't making that kind of turnaround at all.
Oh, it wasn't?
The fourth season is filled with episodes comic fans will be happy to see.
Not like we can trust it too much.
Have a good year.
Good morning.
Hey there. If you chitchat too long, you'll be late to school.
Katsura-sensei is acting differently than usual!
She looks dazzling.
Sadly, life is filled with sudden goodbyes.
You idiot, Onee-chan!
I don't care about you!
You can go die on a street in the middle of nowhere!
Next time, Sensei Farewell Despair Graduation Special.
Make sure to jack into Hayate no Gotoku next week, too.