Why are you asking about them?
You aren't thinking about joining them, are you?
What the hell?!
And besides! Why the heck is my head on another body?!
Or maybe it's a fresh corpse.
This is gonna be fun!
So fun! So fun!
What do you think will happen to us if the cops see that thing?
I don't care if it's dead or alive.
If you have no other choice, destroy it on the spot.
Looks like I won't be able to afford any luxuries this month.
Next, I need a kitchen sponge and...
Have a nice day.
It's the black bike!
It must be around the corner!
Ouch...
S-Sorry.
Are you okay?
You're...
Help me!
Please!
Whoa! It's the black bike!
Is this for real?
This is so cool!
Gotta take a pic!
This is unreal!
Oh? So you bumped into this beauty on the street,
who was being chased by this evil girl on a bike,
has amnesia,
and had fallen asleep from fatigue by the time I got here.
Are you asking me to believe a story I'd only have in my wildest dreams?
Dude, I'm serious! Really!
However, if this had happened in the morning and made you late for school, it'd be stereotypical. {try keeping that archetype and stereotype in next line for the pun explained later OR (preferably) find something better}
Oh, and if she'd been a transfer student, it'd be archetypical!
And if she'd been the princess of a kingdom, and in truth, your childhood friend, it'd be perfect.
Did you get my "stereotypical" and "archetypical" pun?
You know, you ruined it by explaining it.
I don't know what to do. She lost her memories,
but she doesn't want to go to the police.
Uh... Well, let's wait and see how things turn out.
For now, let's wait till tomorrow,
and we'll decide what to do after hearing her out.
Yeah.
Anyway, catch you tomorrow.
Good night.
The girl on the black bike might remember my face.
That black bike, considered to be an urban legend...
What can I do against her now that she's my enemy?
I hated my easygoing life.
I wanted a different life.
Maybe that's why I brought her here.
But there's something Kida-kun doesn't know about:
her scar.
It's as if someone decapitated her and then forcefully sewed her head back on.
This is an announcement from the cafeteria.
The jumbo melon breads have sold out today.
'Sup, Mikado!
What happened to that sleeping beauty in your run-down apartment?
Keep it down, Kida-kun!
Oh? A beauty?
That word doesn't go unnoticed by me.
You know...
When Mikado rounded the corner,
he bumped into a babe who was being chased by a baddie.
And now, he's living together with her.
Oh... It's just Mr. A/C's fantasy.
It's Ryuugamine, not "Mr. A/C."
See?
Anyone want to buy me meal tickets?
There's no need to worry. No one will believe you!
So, how's the chick doing?
She was still sleeping when I left.
Guess she's really tired.
Anyway, let's get down to business.
Business?
The reason why I ate lunch early, in fourth period, is because I'm trying to use my lunch break effectively.
Dollars Probability Predictions...
This is all the rage in our class right now.
The whole Dollars story is veiled in mystery.
So at school, we go,
"Doesn't that guy look like one of the Dollars?"
and vote on it.
Looks like you guys have a lot of votes.
Well, each person can vote for several people.
This Takiguchi guy from Class 1-D only has one vote.
Oh, you noticed.
I, Lord Kida Masaomi, hath given him that vote.
I'm actually in the same P.E. class as him.
I'm strongly convinced that Takiguchi Ryou is a member of the Dollars.
What makes you think that?
Instinct.
So, I'm gonna go check him out.
Hey!
'Scuze me!
Is Takiguchi Ryou-kun here?
He's not here.
Is he in the cafeteria?
Dunno. Maybe the roof?
I think he usually goes up there during lunch.
Maybe he's having a smoke break.
Shouldn't we... not do this?
There might be scary people up there.
I'm just kidding, dude.
Smoking on the rooftop during lunch is only in those ancient, clichéd comics.
But if you just ask him if he's a member of the Dollars,
I doubt he'll honestly say, "Yes, I am."
Dude, leave it to me.
I have a plan.
Let's see.
H-He's smoking.
Hey, Takiguchi!
'Sup.
Oh, you compose songs?
Well, yeah.
What's up?
Need something?
There's something I want to ask you.
Go ahead.
Are you a member of the Dollars?
Kida-kun...
Yes, I am.
I knew it.
I was absolutely sure.
See?
I've got great instincts!
This is my childhood friend.
I'm Ryuugamine Mikado.
So you're that famous guy.
Me? Famous?
Your name.
Want some?
Thanks.
Uh, Takiguchi-kun...
Why did you join the Dollars?
Hm... Now that you ask me out of nowhere...
I think it was six months ago.
Some stranger invited me via a text message.
He said that they didn't have any rules or restrictions.
At first I was like, "No way,"
but then I thought it'd be pretty fun if it were true.
You know...
I don't like to order or be ordered around.
So, what kind of group are they?
Well, you could say they're colorless.
Colorless?
Yup.
Unlike the Yellow Napkins and Blue Squares, they don't wear the same color
or try to expand their influence.
Blue Squares?
They're a color gang that was pretty well known when I was in junior high.
I don't really know much about them,
but they disbanded after causing some incident.
Kida-kun?
So you like them, right?
Yep.
Have you met the other members?
Well, not really. You just know their nicknames,
but I've met quite a few of them.
Sometimes at work, or bumping into them on the street.
They were all coincidental though.
Well, if you think a person is a member, it's usually true.
What do you mean?
Well there's no tell-tale sign.
Just ask around like you asked me.
Most of them will tell you.
Crap.
See ya!
Ever since I found out that Takiguchi-kun was really part of the Dollars,
I decided to keep it to myself.
I'm sure he wouldn't like it if other people made a fuss about it.
Okay, take your seats.
I think only those who ask should know.
Rise.
Bow.
That concludes the representative meeting.
I wonder if the disciplinary staff that Kida-kun's a part of is still meeting.
They should be finishing up soon.
Hey, wait!
Harima Mika-san, who was stalking Yagiri Seiji-kun,
has been missing since the first day of school.
Have you learned anything new about Harima-san yet?
No, nothing.
Ryuugamine!
Kida said you should go home first.
Why? Did something happen?
Looks like he's busy debating at the disciplinary staff meeting.
See ya.
Uh...
Shall we go then?
Okay.
I wonder what he's debating about.
Maybe about uniforms and hair styles?
Mikado!
The princess' commands are absolute, got it?
Also, make sure to introduce me to her next time! See ya!
"Princess" is the name of a French person I met at Russia Sushi.
Uh...
S-She has a piercing on her nose...
Uh, so he's gotta be arguing about that.
I've known you for a long time.
When I was turning in my entry registration,
the information desk had a list where you could look for your name.
I saw yours and thought, "That's a pretty cool name,"
and then you happened to be in my class.
Then I thought it'd be nice to be a class representative with you.
Hey, hold on a second.
Isn't this like what happened with Harima Mika-san and Yagiri Seiji-kun?
Shit, stalkers are dangerous.
Well, if it's a cutie like her it's okay... Or not.
No way, no way.
If I screw up...
s-she'll stab me to death!
N-No, maybe she'll be a pyromaniac and burn my place down.
Wait, what if she takes my family hostage?
But if she has a good personality, being a stalker shouldn't be a...
No, no, no.
The fact that she's a stalker means she doesn't have a good personality!
I was just kidding.
I'd just be a nuisance to you.
No, that's not true.
Please don't worry. I'm not a stalker.
No, I didn't think that.
Sorry.
Don't be. I was just teasing you.
Please don't apologize.
Uh...
Um.
Then...
Let's continue our good relationship.
Yes, of course.
Takeshi, it's him!
Who? Not me, right?
I'm talking about you, damn it!
Stop acting so innocent!
Um... Who are you?
Thanks to your friend, I had to buy a new cellphone!
Uh... I'm not sure I'm following you...
So you're the pal of the guy who broke my girlfriend's cellphone, eh?
We aren't really friends...
Then who is he? Your dad?
Your co-signer?
Huh? I can't hear you!
That reasoning is a little off...
You trying to hold a sermon or what, you little asshat?
I'll teach you about social hierarchy, you little dipshit!
You brought him here because I don't hit girls.
Aw, how considerate of you.
I'd love to make you my girlfriend, but I'm afraid you're not my type.
Buzz off!
You jerk!
Bye!
Well then, Ryuugamine Mikado-kun.
I was waiting for you near the school gate because I wanted to see you.
I wanted to talk you about something.
By the way, why is the black bike here?
She must be looking for that girl.
Ah, darn! I completely forgot!
I'm in a rush.
Good-bye, Sonohara-san.
This is way too surreal.
At this rate, they're going to follow me back to my place.
And then...
Help me!
U-Um...
Uh...
I-I will hear you out here.
I can wait till the black bike's finished her business.
Hello?
Ah, nice to hear from you again.
T-There's something I'd like to ask.
What is it?
So she can communicate.
Who are you?
I'm looking for my relative's missing daughter.
I found her yesterday, but for some reason, she ran away.
S-She's a terrible liar.
I'm afraid I don't believe you.
How much do you know about me?
Uh... You're an urban legend...
and you ride a bike without an engine or headlights.
And...
You don't have a head.
Do you believe that?
Um... Could you show me...
what's behind that helmet?
I never imagined I'd have the guts to say that.
Just don't start screaming.
But I had the feeling that I'd been waiting for this moment all my life.
I still don't know how to describe what I felt.
I was repeating, "I knew it! I knew it!"
deep in my mind.
Thank you very much.
After that, she told me the real reason she was chasing that girl.
She told me that her name was Selty, and that she was a Dullahan.
About how she came all the way to Japan to look for her missing head.
And the girl with a scar around her neck had a head that looked just like it.
Usually, no one would believe a word of that.
But for some reason, I believed her.
Are you her friend?
No, I just met her yesterday.
I asked her about what happened,
and she said she lost her memories.
Selty-san?
Can I meet her?
I think she's scared of you because you started chasing her so suddenly.
I want to see her!
Can't we clear up that misunderstanding?
Okay.
Nothing beats a milkshake with fruit!
I'm convinced that this development is a sign that Shocker will become the heroine!
No! This decides Himegami as the heroine!
What the fuck?!
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?!
That motherfucker...
He scratched my car!
Chill out, Togusa!
That motherfucker is dead!
The light turned red!
Please wait here for a moment.
I'll explain the situation to her.
I don't want her to see you and think that I'm betraying her.
Okay.
He's pretty cautious.
Huh?
This is the first time I've heard your name.
I didn't expect you to be a foreigner.
Bullshit.
The next time you throw a rock at my horse, you'll be in trouble.
So that's a horse.
By the way, don't you think he's taking too long?
Would a cleaning service visit an apartment as run-down as this?
No way!
Like I said, I just want to know where that girl is.
This strand of hair on the floor is hers, isn't it?
I really don't know.
P-Please let me go...
You've already seen our faces.
We have to dispose of you here.
Hey, someone's coming!
I'm saved!
You don't have to chase them.
I know where they're headed.
I recognize that van.
I believe it's from Yagiri Pharmaceuticals.
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals?
Yes.
Lately their profits have been plummeting, and they're about to be absorbed by a foreign company.
The girl with a scar that went missing...
A Dullahan...
People going missing...
Harima Mika...
Yagiri Seiji...
Human trafficking...
And... the Dollars...
What's he doing?
I hated an easygoing life.
To be honest, I wasn't really sure...
Please, help me a little.
I wanted a different life.
I've gathered all the pieces.
That's why...
Bullseye!
I will...
I hated an easygoing life.
I wanted a different life.
I didn't expect my little wish to affect so many people.
Next time: Storm and Stress.