When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
If you have a match-making meeting,
do you always get married?
Huh? What's this about all of a sudden?
Well, uh... actually...
Saki went out drinking
with her friends two nights ago
and she was out late, so she stayed
the night at her parents' house.
Then, she came back yesterday morning and...
Video Rental V Tachibana
Oh, back already?
You don't go home much,
so you could've spent more time there.
No, I did not wish to cause you any worry,
so I came back as quickly as I could.
Like I said, I wasn't worried or anything.
I-Incidentally, there were men
at our get-together last night, too.
I don't care about that stuff.
Also, my mother suggested I go
to a match-making meeting.
Hah! That's great!
Oh, Mother? Please set up
that meeting as soon as you can!
Yes, full speed ahead.
What? Oh, wait, Saki?!
All right, I understand.
So, tomorrow on Sunday,
I will be going to a match-making meeting.
Therefore, I will be taking some time off.
I assume that will be fine?!
What?!
So, she's been out since this morning.
That's unexpected to hear,
but she's going to the meeting
because she wants to get married, right?
The look on your face shows
an awfully self-centered disgruntlement.
Wha?!
No helping it then.
I guess I'll help you out.
What?
Well, well, a match-makin' meetin', huh?
It'll be chock full
of opportunities to make jabs.
I've never witnessed a match-making meeting.
Then why don't you all go
watch the match-making meeting?
Wha?!
Yes! That's a good idea!
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Who gives a damn?!
Now's not the time for that!
Saki just might end up leaving, you know!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Match-Making Meeting
Everyone should be there about now.
A match-making meeting
in this day and age!
It could be nice with a certain charm to it.
Then, we shall leave it
to the young couple from here on out.
Sounds good!
No!
Please have mercy, my lord magistrate!
Oh, no!
Come, come, it will be fine!
Someone, please save me!
Oh, my! What am I thinking?!
More like, that's not
a match-making meeting.
Damn. A match-making meeting?
What the hell is that?
This is one of the most
distinguished restaurants in the city.
I'll have you know,
we are not reusing Isumi's house.
Darn it! To think Saki's
having a match-making meeting
with some strange guy somewhere in there...!
I got it!
It seems Saki is participating
in their standard Young Couple Time.
What the heck is that?
In other words, they take
a stroll around the garden alone
and jabber on about
their hobbies and things.
Like doin' a married couple comedy routine.
J-Just the two of them?!
But the garden here is so vast,
it's called the Forest of the Lost.
And it seems women who have
participated in match-making parties
have gone missing here.
What?!
Saki and her guy may have
become skeletons by now, too.
We're finding them at all costs!
No matter what, they won't turn
into skeletons so quickly.
No, no, this degree of tension
just makes it more interesting.
It's so nice and fatty!
N-Nice to meet you!
I am Kyonosuke Kaoru
and I teach at Hakuou Academy!
I am Saki Kijima.
Allow me to explain.
Kyonosuke Kaoru has appeared
as a minor character,
but he's had a piddly number of lines.
Now, he's going to talk his head off.
I-I apologize for dragging
you out here today.
N-Not at all. I feel the same way...
Um, uh... What are your interests?
What should I do?
I build Gundam models on occasion.
I got carried away and I ended up here,
Uh, did you know that back in the day,
but I have no plan to get married...
you could buy an Elmeth
for 300 yen before tax?
An Elmeth is a Gundam model, by the way.
I feel terrible for doing this to him...
The Federation feared
the Elmeth as the "tricorn hat"
and it was also known
as the Ghost of Solomon.
Though, when it was first released,
it was packaged under the name
"Elmeth", just like in the show.
Well, I sure was young back then...
Or rather, I must explain
how things ended up this way.
Pub Charm Droplets
Cheers!
So? How are things these days, Saki?
What?
That's right, how are things?
"H-How are things?"
That's what I should be asking you.
What's going on with
your job search, you two?
I-Is being unproductive a crime?!
We're working on self-realization!
You know, self-realization!
Sorry, I was wrong. I won't ask anymore.
No one cares about that stuff.
When girls get together and say,
"How are things lately?"
it's about men, of course!
Wh-Why are you so intent on this?
I have no need of a boyfriend.
Besides, I'm too busy with work
for that sort of thing.
What a terribly mundane response.
No attractive man is going to
pay attention to you like that.
Not to worry.
I believe I get plenty of attention
from an attractive man.
What was with that comment?!
So you do have a boyfriend?!
N-No, uh...
Give us the details!
So, I mean, uh...
Shoot. I didn't think I'd be out so late.
There's no train that goes back
to Nakano-Sakaue at this hour...
I have no choice.
I will call the Young Sir
to make sure he does not worry
and I will stay the night
at my parent's today.
Oh, okay, so you're not coming back.
Uh, um, you sound rather happy about that.
Really?
It's not like I'm thinking I won't
get scolded for staying out late.
W-Well, anyway, I apologize
for causing you worry.
Huh? I wasn't worried.
What?
Uh, um, for a girl to go out drinking
and come home in the morning is...
Looks like I'll be getting
a peaceful night's sleep tonight!
Thank you for the meal.
Wait, Saki, are you always
this grumpy at mealtime?
I was born grumpy.
Oh, my, what a thing to say!
Honestly!
I'm coming back in the morning
after going drinking
and he's not worried at all?!
Well, as you can see, nothing happens.
Well, then, I am going back!
Wait, Saki! Hold on!
What is it?!
Um, so Saki dear, do you have any
interest in match-making meetings?
Huh?
Incidentally, this kit does
not come with a figurine!
However! It comes with Char's
custom Gelgoog and 10 bits.
Mention a match-making meeting
in that situation and anyone would have...
Incidentally, the scale is 1:550!
Um, am I boring you
with my Gundam model talk?
Oh, I-I'm sorry. I was just
thinking about something...
No, I can tell by the glum
look on your face.
Oh, um...
I'm 28 already and my parents
are really getting on my case.
What?
They keep telling me to get married.
So I reluctantly wound up coming
to this match-making meeting...
Oh, um, me, too.
What?
I was sort of forced into it
and got carried away.
I-I am sorry!
Oh, no, I'm no better than you!
M-More importantly...
What?
Where are we?
This is...!
Where in the world could they be?
This place looks like there
really could be wild animals here.
Please do not worry! I shall
protect you at the risk of my own life!
Darn it! Which way could they be?!
But Wataru, don't you care about Isumi?
Wha?!
Oh, my...
Huh?! What's Isumi got to do
with any of this?!
Good point.
In a typical romance, the pattern goes...
If ya drag yer feet, unable to confess
yer feelings to yer sweetheart,
yer sweetheart starts gettin' offers
for match-makin' meetings and stuff.
It's not like that!
Then just leave Saki alone.
She's of age, so she's got
a right to find happiness.
Th-That's true, but...
Ya don't make any sense.
Well, not that it matters.
It's already weird, since I'm your
betrothed and I'm helping you here.
Then, fine! I don't need any more help!
Oh, there she is! Saki!
What?!
Where could we be?
I have no idea.
Do you suppose that's the way back?
Who the heck is that?
I've seen him somewhere before.
Oh, that's Mr. Kaoru!
Oh, that Gundam model freak!
I can't hear them, but they
seem like they're hitting it off.
They certainly do.
Damn it! That Saki!
Don't tell me she's serious
about a guy like him?!
If only we could hear them somehow...
I'll bet even the all-purpose butler
can't do anythin' about this.
Please leave it to me!
What?!
Please leave it to me, Miss!
I thought such a need might arise,
so I learned lip-reading with the SPK
and I will use it
to read their conversation!
The truth is, um,
there's someone I care for.
What?
"The truth is, Saki,
you are the person I care for!"
What?!
O-Oh, someone you care for?
Yes.
"O-Oh, I also care for you!"
So, who is this person you like?
She's a childhood friend.
She used to be really cute
way back when, but...
Yukiji
This is ultimately the subjective
vision of a man in love.
As she grew older, she became more
of a mess in terms of her personality.
Actually, she was a mess to begin with...
"So, what is it that you like?"
"What I like about you is that you'd
make a child wife and how you're cute."
"I just want to mess you up.
Actually, I want to mess you up big time!"
But you still like her?
"Th-Then do as you like with me!"
I don't know what she thinks of me,
but how you feel is something
that's hard to change, you know?
That's true.
How you feel is...
"I'm more of a skilled operator
than you'd think,"
"and I'll change things so it feels good!"
"That's great! As long as it feels good!"
I can't put up with this anymore! Saki!
Ya moron!
Ya jump out there without a plan
and she'll just end up hatin' ya!
Yes, she has a point.
Th-Then what am I supposed to do?!
How 'bout ya knock her out
with a whack with this from behind.
I-I don't know about that.
As a globally standard method,
how about creating a critical situation
and once you've highlighted
her partner's worthlessness,
you go out there and resolve things?
Th-That's my Hayate! That's good!
Oh, please...
That's too much of a cliché, right?
This is the Heisei era, not Showa.
Even Wataru won't go for a plan like...
You're amazing that you can come up
with a plan like that, Hayate!
Right?! My butler is a genius!
Yeah, he's a genius!
Oh, please...
Wataru probably doesn't watch
cliché dramas of this sort, so...
But assumin' we use this
totally cliché method,
how're we gonna create
the critical situation?
We're going to use Tama.
Tama?
Rarr.
What's he doing here?
He heard Maria talking to herself
and couldn't resist coming.
Rarr...
So, I end up staying alone at home again.
Well, I'll just sing
to my heart's content then!
Let us stop the...
More Kinoppi than Kaakun.
(Kaakun yori Kinoppi.)
Do you like century eggs?
(Piitan osuki desuka?)
I suppose I'll get some cleaning done.
That actually made me feel more lonely.
Well, that's what's going on,
so you leap out of the bushes
and scare them a little.
I don't mind doing that,
but what do I get out of it?
Let me think...
If you don't do as I say,
how about I reveal
that you're a talking tiger
and sell you off to the circus?
A-All right already! Damn it!
I believe I have Tama's
cooperation now as well.
Ya can communicate with tigers?
Yes, in a way...
That's my butler!
Yeah!
Sheesh! That Hayate!
He looks so sweet, but
the things he says are nasty. Man!
Right then, Tama became aware
of a terrifying menacing aura!
Wh-What's this aura?
They say animals instinctively
known when approached
by a beast that's stronger than them, but...
So, my instincts still hadn't
forgotten how to do that!
Th-This vicious beast's aura...
I-I can't move...
I must apologize.
Not only did I make you come
to this match-making meeting,
but you also had to listen to me
selfishly talk about my life.
Not at all.
She's selfish and capricious,
and she gets offended easily,
but they tend to be the ones
that are the hardest to ignore...
Selfish and capricious, and easily offended?
The truth is...
Huh?
Um, there's someone
I find hard to ignore, too.
I'm envious.
What?
Of that person who has your affections.
Mr. Kaoru!
Ooh! That was superbly agile for Tama!
Now's yer chance, Wataru! Get goin' already!
R-Right!
Saki!
You okay, Saki?!
Young Sir! What are you doing here?
Oh, no, uh... What am I...?
Never mind that, we have to run!
But we can't leave Mr. Kaoru behind!
Leave it to me! I'll save him!
That's good, that's good!
This is getting to be quite
an exciting turn of events!
Yeah! I guess clichés
can be good sometimes.
Well, I was going to attack those guys,
but I sensed the aura
of this terrible beast,
so I thought it was dicey and I came back.
What?!
What's wrong, Hayate?
Um, it appears that beast
we saw wasn't Tama...
What?!
Th-Then what's over there?
It may be a real wild animal...
What?!
Young Sir, it is dangerous!
Saki, you run!
Young Sir!
Come on out, beast! Let Mr. Kaoru go!
Or I'll destroy you!
Wataru,
the thing in there isn't Tama,
but a real wild animal.
Take that! And that! And that! And that!
Stop that, you idiot!
Young Sir!
Voltes Kick!
Saki!
Miss Katsura?!
Y-Yukiji, what the heck are you doing here?
I was told I could drink all I want
at the match-making party,
so I'd been drinking since yesterday,
but they told me to knock it off
and kicked me out!
I got lost in the woods
and I'm hungry and I'm on edge here!
It's only natural
that she'd get kicked out...
I haven't had nearly enough to drink!
I agree...
For starters, we're going to Kabukicho
and get back to drinking!
You're treating!
Help me! I'm going home!
Did you come out of concern
for my match-making meeting?
Th-Things are busy at the shop.
There's no time for match-making
meetings. We're going home!
Come on!
You are right.
I will not be able to get married
for a while at the rate things are going.
D-Damn straight! You dummy!
Good grief. He's like a little brother
who needs a lot of looking-after.
Agreed.
But does Wataru like Isumi?
Or does he like Saki?
What's up with him?
Well, with boys,
there are all kinds of "likes".
I don't really understand,
but boys are more
complicated than I thought.
Yes.
This doesn't really matter,
but was your lip-reading accurate?
Actually, I'm pretty
confident of my abilities.
After a storm, relationships strengthen.
Well, not that we care
about the happiness of others.
More importantly, next time,
they'll be fighting against suspense!
This Week's Butler Battle
Hayate Ayasaki, huh?
That boy has quite a lot of potential.
Hakuou Academy Superintendent
Kirika Kuzuha
That boy...
Make him wear outfits like this or that...
And put cat-ears on him...
Honestly! Mistress Kuzuha!
Superintendent's Personal Butler
Sion Kuresato
What's so great about a guy like him anyway?
Sion, do not be so jealous.
You, too, wish to make
Ayasaki weep, do you not?
Mistress Kuzuha!
So, um, how long do I have to wait?
I know.
Mysterious Butler of Darkness No. 1,
defeat Hayate Ayasaki
and make him one of us!
Yes, my lady!
Here you are, Mistress Kuzuha.
He will come to realize just how
frightful my assassin can be...
Another peaceful day.
My turn!
Wh-Who are you?!
My name is Duel Butler!
My turn! Draw!
Wh-What the?!
Wh-What is this?!
Huh? What's this?
Now, fight me, Hayate Ayasaki!
I don't really understand, but here I go!
My turn! Draw! Magic card!
Summon White-Haired Demon Klaus and attack!
Klaus
But even when crushed,
they come back to life!
That vitality is
the true strength of my deck!
Activate the Shield Trigger!
Not so fast!
Drawing yet again!
I'll finish you off with
the rare Hayate Ayasaki card!
Here we go, partner!
Okay, my alter ego!
Wha?!
Me?! Killed in one turn?!
Huh? What the...
Damn it all! Just you remember this!
What in the world was that?
This Week's Butler Battle
The End
"This Week's"?!
Don't tell me this is going
to keep happening?!
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Butler Report
Summoned, I pop out, I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I'm Maria.
Oh? What are you doing here, Maria?
When the story takes place
outside the Sanzenin estate,
I tend to have few scenes,
so it seems I get to do this instead.
I see, that's an alarming situation.
But the majority of this show's viewers
must be watching mainly to see me,
so there should be no problem.
What? Do you think so?
I'd like to see more scenes
with Maria in them.
Oh, Hayate!
See you later!
Preview
Sh-She's dead?!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
I confess, I already have
a good idea of who the culprit is.
What?!
She sees through to the one and only truth.
With the looks of a snooty softy
and the brains of a societal bum.
Her name is Great Detective Nagi!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"The Beautiful Rich Great
Young Detective Lady Saw It!
"The Case of the Murdered Female
Teacher Amidst Clouds of Steam".
It will be full of fan
service scenes as well.
I hope you enjoy it with your entire family.
Next Hayate the Combat Butler
The Beautiful Rich Great Young Detective Lady Saw It!
The Case of the Murdered Female Teacher Amidst Clouds of Steam
Did you know?
Looking at a cast list in the newspaper,
the 3rd or the 5th on the list
is the most likely to be culprit.