I've done it!  The manga I drew, I managed to sell a copy!
Yay!
Now that I've got my foot in the door, I'm gonna draw like crazy!
Huh?
But you've got twenty-nine copies left over.
But you know...
Honestly, the printing fee's nothing to sneeze at.
You're always wearing cute clothes, aren't you?
Justice makes them for me!
May I ask you a question?
What?
Why don't you call out to Najimi?
Because I'm following her.
If I could ask you to explain this to me...
A job?
Don't worry, I'm good.  Thanks.
Didn't you say you had to make some money to pay off the printing fee?
Actually, I already found a job.
What kind of work is it?
That...
Is a secret!
I see.  That would certainly interest you.
That's why I'm following her, to find out where she works.
Roger!
Still, is this okay?
It's fine.
I could tell just from her embarassment that it was something she really wanted to tell me about.
Besides, Najimi is an M.
M comes from S&M, Sadism & Masochism.
M?
Of course. If it's an embarassing job, she'll be relieved when we find out.
Bingo.
But if she's selling something which shouldn't be sold again...
Again?
You were under the wrong impression the other day, that's all.
Didn't I clear it up for you?
For Najimi, who through selling a single copy of her manga has been thoroughly enraptured by doujin...
For her moral judgement to waver and to choose something like that...
No.  If that happens, I, Justice-
Will bring her back to the path of righteousness!
I thought that you'd wait for me at the station.
If we had done that, we would've lost sight of Najimi.
Rather, you and Najimi are alike.
Thank you.
I wasn't complimenting you.
You did well in finding our location.
It was thanks to these signs.
Beads?
You dropped these for me while walking, didn't you, Sora?
Yep!
Thank you, Sora!
Justice!
I'm going on ahead.
Oh, it looks like she just came to buy some perverted manga or games again.
Strange.
From what I heard, it's about time for her to start work.
Maybe she's just killing time?
I can't see Najimi, who stops to pick up one yen coins out of puddles,
Doing something as wasteful as that.
If that's the case, maybe she's an employee.
But then hiding it would be strange.
This place exists, funnily enough. Drop by the Akiba Toranoana if you're ever in Tokyo. http://www.toranoana.jp/with_cat/
A catgirl cafe?
Welcome back, mas-
Ter.
I'm-
I'm home.
You guys, what have you come here for?
Uh, well...
I... I might have taken my woman's intuition a bit too far.
Trying to explain yourself?
Well, maybe.
Not maybe!
I...  I'm sorry.
It's okay, none of us mind.
Well, I do!
I'd have been better off not seeing this.
You bitch!
Luna-chan!
Yes!
Luna-chan?
Shut up!
Is something wrong?
No, nothing!
Najimi, that wasn't nothing at all!
Luna? What is Luna?
Master, you're causing me a degree of annoyance.
May I ask you to be quiet for a while?
I'm going to say this once!  I'm working here!
Oh, because you like these outfits?
Sora!
At times like these, even if that's what you think...
So in order to work off the printing fee, you picked a place where the hourly wage is high, didn't you?
Yeah.
Though, could you pretend to accept this just a bit better?
Anyway!
My reasons for working here are...
Well, who cares.
Two coffees and an omelette rice, yes? Thank you.
I bet she did this so she could wear an outfit like that.
Well, there were probably other places with as high of an hourly wage.
So in other words, Najimi's a shy person?
A shy person...
That...
Is against the rules!
Welcome back, Master!
I'm-
I'm home.
A table for one in the non-smoking section, right?
Yes! Thank you.
That guy, he's...
The one who bought Najimi's manga and became her first customer.
Najimi, may I ask you something?
What is it?
Though it looks like the two of you are familiar, does that guy come here often?
Hoshi-kun? Yeah, every day.
Every day, you said?
Yeah, he comes a lot every day.
It seems that he's started working upstairs.
So he comes down here on his breaks.
How long ago did he start working?
Probably about two days after I started here.
Luna-chan!
Yes, I'll be right there!
So that's how it is.
It's difficult to think of this as a coincidence.
Sorry for the wait.
Yay, omelette rice!
I can draw a picture or message on the omelette with ketchup if you'd like.
Would you like one?
The drawing would be like THAT, so a message, please!
Then, what kind of message should I write?
Hmm, what should we do?
You decide, Tsuyuri!
Lets see...
Osana Najimi is...
Najimi is...
And then?
A dirty girl.
Why do I have to write something like that about myself?
Yourself?
You're Luna-san, aren't you?
Got it, I'll write it already!
A dirty girl.
Also, an extreme M.
Is that what you were getting at?
For crying out loud, eat quickly and leave!
She's a tsundere after all!
That was a good
Want some, Justice?
I can draw a picture or message with chocolate if you'd like.
Would you like one?
Th-then, if it's okay with you.
If I could get Luna-san's real name,
I, uh...
Eh?  I'm sorry, I couldn't hear all of that.
Don't get cocky, kid.
Uwaah! That was surprising!
I was just asking Luna-san to write a message.
What's your problem, anyway?
I'm her childhood friend!
That's unfair!
I have taken baths with her.
A childhood friend!
Wait!
Add "back when we were kids" to that already!
I-I can work magic on Luna-satoreruton!
Magic, you say?
Luna-san, Promotion Magic, if you would!
Cafe with Cat has a card-based point system. Promotion Magic, is redeemable at a "magical power" of 40C (i.e. 40 stamps).
Cer-
Cerrtainly.
Um, it says that you can have a two-shot picture taken with a waitress to commemorate the event!
Ahem.
S-Squishy squishy magic promotion-nyan!
If you've got something to say, then say it!
Actually wait, please don't.
Could you please move over a bit?
What is this? This sense of defeat?
Leave it to me.
Okay, nyan-ko!
Hoshi-kun, was it?
We'll be leaving now.
So, until we meet again.
I see.
I'm here every day, so come again any time.
Every day?
Now see here, stop stalking her everywhere she goes!
Stalking, how rude!
It'll definitely bother Najimi!
I see, so Beauty Love-san's real name is Najimi-san, is it?
What a wonderful name.
I guess this is what they mean by losing a battle but winning the war.
Excuse me.
Well, till next time, Najimi-san.
Yeah, thank you very much.
Najimi!  Quit working here at once!
Huh?
I won't let a man like that make you his bride!
What are you talking about?
Now see here, I'm working here because...
If I go upstairs, I can access a lot of material.
By learning what's popular, I can research what kinds of doujinshi are in demand.
So, in other words.
That's right!  I think this is a good environment for a doujinshi artist to be in, so I won't quit!
To draw better doujinshi!  Najimi!
So it wasn't just the outfit!
But if that were so, you should've just gotten a job upstairs.
Don't come to see me!
Seeing friends here is embarassing, after all.
And there's her soft side!
Understood.  I'll stop coming here to see you.
Instead of coming to see you, I'll come here to work!
Where is the manager?
I'll have you hire me right this second!
S-Stop!
Out of the way!
J-just hang on a second!
I have to do this!
Thank you very much!
We'll be waiting at Akiba's Toranoana!
I wonder, have you noticed the little pranks in the subtitles yet?
Stay oblivious for a bit longer.