Bullshit!
I was wrong about you, traitor!
Richie, wait!
Listen to me!
Don't touch me!
I don't wanna listen to you!
I don't need you anymore.
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
My feet feel so heavy.
Just like the first time I climbed up this slope.
Kaoru...
Would you like a rice ball?
Why? I'm fine.
I'm already stuffed.
Half a thing of bread ain't gonna be enough to fill you up.
I guess I'll have one...
This is good.
What's in it?
Let's see...
Clams boiled in soy sauce—
Shoot! Stupid!
I'm such an idiot!
Why bring that up?!
Say, Ritsuko,
I can't help but notice that you've been awfully close with Nishimi lately!
Be honest with me.
Are you going steady?
N-No!
Would ya look at that, she's blushing!
You don't have to hide it from us!
We're rootin' for you!
But we're not...
U-Um...
It's the truth. We're not dating.
Mukae and I are just close friends.
So,
please don't get the wrong idea.
Crap. What did I butt in for?
What a surprise...
Y'know, Nishimi, you hardly ever talk, so I pegged you as completely unapproachable.
For a sec there, I coulda sworn you were gonna blow your stack at us.
M-Me too...
Hey, maybe you could tell us. What's the trick to getting good test scores?
Yeah, I wanted to ask you the same thing.
Oh, I just...
Oh, we've put him on the spot...
Hey,
what d'you know? I don't feel sick at all...
Hey, Richie...
Don't ignore me!
Just listen to me for a second, ya blockhead!
Wow, what a pad, Yamaoka!
Completely separated from the house...
This is where we're gonna practice every day from now on!
Huh?
Don't look so down, Kawabuchi.
You're not having second thoughts, are you?
Don't be stupid.
If I say I'm gonna do somethin', I see it through.
That's the way to be.
We better hurry up an' decide what songs we're gonna do.
What'll it be?
Well, I wanna fit the Spiders in there.
The Ventures, of course. And then...
Hey, what about the Beatles?!
What's with all the different genres?
I think the girls will dig it more if we play a variety.
That ain't what you said before!
Ryunosuke...
We picked up a roll cake.
Why don't you share it with your friends?
Mama! Get outta here!
Oh! Thank you, Mom!
We'd love some roll cake!
Let's discuss this over a snack, okay, Ryunosuke?
Kawabuchi, you comin' with?
Nah.
I'm gonna stay here an' practice some alone.
Oh...
Pops...
What're you doin' wearin' a tie on such a hot day?
Oh...
I'm in mourning.
Who died?
John Coltrane.
N-No way! Coltrane died?!
You didn't know?
Well, I guess it's only natural that a rock and roll star wouldn't get wind of the news...
Please don't bust my chops about that, Pops.
That said, have a look inside.
I know I've seen this babe around before.
Y-Yurika?
Oh my. It's been quite a while, Sentaro...
I heard that you're going to be in a rock band for the school festival.
I just can't wait for it.
Yurika...
Chet Baker...
If you're interested, wanna listen to it?
Sentaro...
I...
Please, don't say anything.
I can't...
Because...
I...
W-Who's there?!
Down below.
Oh, sorry.
Didn't mean to interrupt, Sen-boy.
Brother Jun?
Don't pay me no mind.
Carry on.
Dammit!
I forgot to tell him about Junichi!
Yurika!
Hey, Sen-boy.
Your woman forgot something.
Sen!
Not bad at all.
What's that look for?
Want some more?
Wait, Sen.
Junichi's had a bit of a breakdown...
Brother Jun?
What's wrong?
Tell me.
What happened? Sentaro...
Sentaro, wait!
Okay, everyone...
I'd like to figure out who'll be on the committee for the festival.
I'm open to volunteers or nominations...
Okay!
I'd like to nominate Nishimi and Mukae!
I'm sure they'd be responsible and do a great job!
The sounds like a great idea!
No objections here!
East High
Festival
Talent
Show
Sign-Ups
Oh, the brass band...
Could you jot down the program and member names?
Um, can I get an application?
Here you go.
You're all set!
I'm sorry, Kaoru.
The new term just started and you've been thrown into such busy work.
Actually...
Since I was always moving from school to school, I never had the chance to do stuff like this.
I'm having a pretty good time.
Kaoru,
have you talked to Sentaro recently?
Nah.
Then you probably didn't hear about it.
The other day at the shop,
Sentaro punched Brother Jun.
I didn't see it myself, and I dunno what it was about...
But I heard that Yurika was at the shop that day.
Could you two bring the completed applications to the student council office?
Sure.
Be right there.
Kaoru, stay here in case someone comes.
Okay.
Oh, Ri'ko, good timing.
You're on the committee, right?
Do me a favor an' fill out an application for me, would ya?
Forget it!
The reception desk is in the stock room.
Head on over there and fill it out for yourself.
I can't accept a scrap of paper.
Do a form.
Could it have really happened?
Is he taking it all on himself, suffering in silence?
Hey—
That band name...
You're spelling it wrong.
It's "The Olympus," not "Duh Olympus."
"Duh" sounds better.
No, it doesn't.
No, that isn't what I want to tell him!
Sen—
Excuse me! Is there still time to sign up?
Y-Yeah.
Whew! Good!
Duh Olympus
The Olympus
Somewhere within my heart, there was still some hurt and regret.
As the festival drew closer,
I became busier with the committee, and before I knew it,
the distance between us had grown immensely.
I even thought fondly of that silly conversation.
But it feels like it was ages ago.
18th
School
Festival
At long last, the day of the festival arrived...
The Olympus is next!
I'm gonna go sit in front!
I can't wait!
Are you ready, ladies?
One, two, three, four!
Look at him with that smile on his face
Now which of the girls is he gonna chase?
Kaoru...
After the festival's over,
you two will be playing again back at my place, right?
Hey...
You're not gonna watch inside?
Things are kinda weird between me and Sentaro right now.
It's my fault.
I gave in to loneliness and betrayed him in the worst way imaginable.
What the—
You're on the committee, right?
Come with me!
What happened?
There's no sound coming from the amps all of a sudden!
No good...
The main electrical system is fine.
Sorry, but could you help see where the problem is?
We'll split up.
Boy, what a bummer, huh?
Hey, second-year!
You suck pretty hard without electricity, so quit actin' so big!
Keep showin' off the fancy shmancy electric twanger yer mommy bought you!
How's rubbin' your money in our faces workin' for you?!
Just get off the stage!
Th-That's not—
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but him an' I are poor and we had to borrow the instruments.
He may be a flashy guy,
but he's got a real dream here,
so I'm gonna have to ask you guys
to stop talkin' just to feel better about yourselves.
Kawabuchi...
It's like you're a nice guy after all.
I'm seeing you in a new light.
Whaddya mean?!
I'm always nice!
Ow! Y-Yes, of course, of course!
B-But it's such a surprise.
I really never thought you'd join the band...
Yeah.
I was gonna refuse at first.
But I changed my mind after Matsuoka told me he wanted to become a star
so he could support his family.
I know what that sorta desperation is like.
Wanting to be useful...
U-Um...
Kawabuchi, would you ever consider staying with the band?
Nah.
This was a one-shot deal for me.
Jazz is more up my alley.
Besides...
I'm keeping my partner waiting.
They can't fix it, huh?
Let's just go...
No, don't leave!
Wait! Wait!
Please!
Don't panic.
I'll keep them occupied for a little while.
But you better be ready to go as soon as they fix it.
What's he doing all of a sudden?
He's wearing an armband, so he must be on the committee...
This song...
Can we get it all back?
Hey, what's goin' on?!
Kawabuchi...
But... it sounds totally different now...
It's like two princes arguing in jest, while they're on their way back home.
Richie!
What the heck?!
They're running away?!
Awesome...
My body feels so light...
Almost like I've been reborn.
I feel like...
I've grown wings...
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change