There's something in this world that no one has ever seen.
It's a stinkin' lie.
These are just...
What is this? It's friggin' molding!
And I just cleaned the mold the other day.
It's something kind and very sweet.
Rags, I need a rag...
If it was something that was visible, people would probably want it.
That's why the world hid it.
So that it wouldn't be so easy to attain.
Darn, it won't come off.
But if I use this, maybe then...
However, it will surely be attained by someone, someday.
The single person that's supposed to attain it will be the one to find it.
That's just how it is.
Eco, eco, eco, ecology~♪
TL Note: Inko (鸚哥/いんこ) literally translates to "parakeet."
Inko-chan, are you still sleeping?
It's morning already...
Meow~ I gotcha!
Ryuu-chan, you're so cold.
I told you last night, I have school starting today.
Oh, the entrance ceremony, huh?
Congratulations on passing your grade.
Is that the kind of attitude you should have towards your son whose going into a new school year?
Hey, this room is dark. Could you open the curtains?
They're open.
Eh?
Ah—That's a huge apartment, isn't it?
I wonder what kind of person lives there.
Ever since THIS was built, we've lost the grace of the sun.
So the laundry dries poorly.
Every single day there's mold, mold, mold—
Those piercing eyes! Ryuu-chan, you look more like your papa.
...more like your papa.
Don't put me in the same boat as that—
Oh my, so cool!
Now you look even more like your papa!
Huh? Ryuu-chan, you're leaving already?
What about my breakfast?
It's in the usual place.
That was...
That was the one thing I didn't want her to tell me.
Thanks to these piercing eyes that you compliment me about— I...
I...
Hey, wait up!
Crap!
Woah!
Huh?
Ta-Ta-Ta-Ta-Takasu! Why did you do that man?!
Eh? What? Wh—
It's not that I meant to!
Please let us off the hook on this!
Huh?
This is all we have right now!
It's the truth!
See, we're not making any jingling sounds, are we?!
No, that's—
PLEASE FORGIVE US!
He's so scary!
Those are a killer's eyes...
I'm...
Again? Sheesh, you pick up a lot of wallets, don't you?
Yeah...
Hey, I hope we get in the same class again.
Yeah.
There it is!
Yes! We're in the same class again!
I'm scared!
That's a killer's eyes!
He's going to kill me!
Crap, this again?
Yo.
I guess we're in the same class this year too, Takasu.
Kitamura.
And this concludes this year's entrance ceremony.
Go to your respective classrooms and prepare for homeroom.
A new class. I have to start by clearing up everyone's misconceptions again.
It's alright.
At least it's not everyone.
I understand you.
Yeah, thanks man.
He's right; there are people who understand, like him.
Besides, in this class is—
Heya, Kitamura-kun!
We're in the same class this year, aren't we?
Well, if it isn't Kushieda.
So you're in Class C too?
Takasu-kun, right?
Do you remember me?
We've always passed by each other around Kitamura-kun.
K-Kushieda Minori...?
Wow, you remember my whole name?
I'm glad!
Well then, well then. Let's enjoy our youth together, eloquently and cheerfully!
Sure.
Y-Yeah...
And then it—
What's wrong, Takasu?
Nothing, I just need to use the restroom.
Is that so? I'll just go on ahead.
Is there going to be a major battle?!
Takasu Ryuuji and Aisaka Taiga! The two most powerful cards have suddenly made their moves!
Is this going to be the deciding battle!?
What the?
She sure has a small body. She's like a doll.
But, something—
But, something feels strangely overbearing.
It's like she might just snatch me up and eat me if I let my guard down.
Um... this is...
You're right!
Delinquent Takasu-kun and the Palmtop Tiger are—!
Idiot!
Palmtop... Tiger...?
I get it.
Palmtop Tai—
What the hell... it matches perfectly.
Okay, that will be all for today.
If you haven't submitted your career choice form, come to the teacher's office later.
O-Okay, Takasu-kun?
Uh-Yeah.
Are you alright, Taiga?
You were late, too.
I went to see the doctor for nasal allergies.
Something about house dust or whatever.
Oh, a modern day allergy.
That must be quite a bother.
Palmtop Tiger. So she's friends with Kushieda Minori.
Sheesh, the one that's bothered is over here.
Are you alright man?
Hey. Yeah, I guess.
But yeah—
Wasn't that amazing?
I mean Aisaka-san and Takasu-kun.
Palmtop Tiger is as strong as I thought.
Plus Takasu-kun is just scary looking, he isn't an actual delinquent.
Really?
It looks like their misconception will be gone quick.
Yeah...
Taiga?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
T-Takasu-kun, is it possible that you've lost the path that you want to chose?
Huh?
B-B-But you see, you have to submit a career form. Everyone other than you already has...
Oh, I'm sorry, I just—
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I bet you don't want some single person, who's wasting time on her path, to be preaching to you!
I'm sorry for being so vain!
I'm late.
My time saving is going to be ove—
A-Are you alright?
My bag... my bag...
I guess I'll just leave her alone for now...
Y-You!
Wha-What-What are-Wha-What are you--?
What do you mean?
Look, I'm just here to grab my bag.
Your bag?!
Your seat is the one next to—
Could it be that the let—
L-L-L-L-Le-Let go!
L-L-L-L-Le—Let go!
LET GO!
Why do you want my bag?!
Hey! Give it a rest alread—
You know—!
A-Aisaka?
Hey!
Dumbass!
This is so messed up.
So messed up.
Your papa's in heaven, you know.
He was such a cool person!
He always had a magazine in front of his chest in case he were to get stabbed.
It gives me tingles!
Just because I look like you,...
I'm having alot of trouble.
If I didn't have a face like this... Everyone wouldn't be afraid of me...
Palmtop Tiger wouldn't pick a fight with me either.
I would be able to have more confidence in myself.
Then I could—
The career choice form...
Hm? What's this?
To Kitamura Yuusaku-sama.
Aisaka... Taiga.
I see...
"You put this in the wrong one, right?
I didn't look at its contents at all so I have no clue what's in there but—
I'll just go ahead and return it to you!"
Oh crap! I have to stick it back on!
Could it be that she's... a major klutz?
I'm going to bed.
Huh? Yasuko... isn't home yet, is she?
Go, go! Mirano-chan!
Alright! I'm gonna chug it all!
Heeey...
The window's—
THAT HURTS!
W-What in the--
Huh? This size...
Somewhere...
AISAKA!
USE A TISSUE!
What...
Wh-What...
...are...
...you...
...do...
...ing?!
Forget it.
Huh? Forget it?
Ohhh, that let—
-ter...?
Now that it's been found out, I can live no longer... I must die!
Then why are you trying to friggin' kill me?!
I don't want to die, so I have to kill you!
Otherwise, completely forget about it!
That's impossible!
Don't you worry.
It may be impossible to kill you with one strike to the brain, but it should at least wipe that memory of yours.
Don't wipe it! Alright, just listen!
That letter—!
Shut up.
SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
You saw it, didn't you?! You read it, didn't you?!
That's why I'm saying I—
I'm not going to listen to you...
That's why, about that lo-lo-love-love letter...
FORGET EVERYTHING!
IT WAS EMPTY!
Em—pty?
Right, so I don't know anything about the contents.
You were lucky that Kitamura didn't get it.
You didn't have to go through a blunder.
H-Hey.
How starved are you anyway?
I got bored with the convenience store.
The convenience store?
Why? Don't your parents make your mea—
I suppose everyone has their own household issues.
Here.
If you would have just handed the bag quietly back then, this wouldn't have happened in the first place.
How are you going to take responsibility for this?!
There's still some on you.
Hearing that from a guy whose sole purpose in life was to put garlic flavoring into this fried rice...
Now look here—
What's wrong with a love letter?
There's nothing shameful about it at all, you hear?
Just wait there.
Take a look.
What's this?
Do you know what that is?
I bet you don't.
That's a list of songs I would play if I were to put on a concert for the girl I like.
That was something I just happened to make for her.
Mini-discs that I'd play while driving with her.
Of course, I don't even have a driver's license.
I've planned something for all seasons of the year.
How's it? Creepy, isn't it?
If you don't have the courage to ask them out, all you can do is fantasize like this.
It certainly is pitiful... but I still don't think it's shameful!
You need to have some confidence in yourself, okay?
You didn't stick with fantasizing and actually moved into action!
Just look to the future, keep a positive attitude, and do it and cheerfully!
"I offer this to Miss Kushieda Minori."
Right, just like Kushieda Minori.
You like Minori?
How offensive.
You should know your place.
Shut up! You're one to talk!
What's wrong with you?! You just told me you'd forget—
Shut up! Cold, it's cold!
I'm sorry Inko-chan. Did we wake you up?
Why are you showing me that disgusting thing?!
What did you just say about one of my precious family members?!
I— I—
Alright, Inko-chan! Introduce yourself to the guest!
Today will be the day when you finally say your name!
I~
In~
In*po*
Inko-chan isn't on top shape today, I swear.
Crap, it's already this late!
Anyway, we're in the same situation!
I won't tell anyone about that!
Isn't that okay?!
No.
Why not?! Hold on, you even ate here, just go home already!
No, please leave.
My mother who's ill, in a matter of speaking, is about to come home.
NO WAY!
I can't trust you anyway.
Plus... Is a love letter alright?
Is it something you'd do now-a-days?
You can't suddenly get so fidgety at a time like this!
You can consult me with any love problems, but it's really late right now!
So wait till tomorrow, 'kay?
Really? You'll help me?
I will.
I will, I will, I will!
I'll do anything!
You'll do anything... like a dog?
You'll obediently do anything for me?
I will. I swear!
So let's just drop this, alright?
Right?
I wonder how she got through the window?
Well—
Oh, I'll take you back.
It's alright. I'm close anyway. Plus I have a wooden sword.
No... That's what's dangerous...
Hey, that hole.
Oh... Well, I can get away by sticking a piece of paper if it's just that.
This note...
You can use it if you'd like.
If it's going to cost you money, I'll properly pay you later.
See ya later, Ryuuji.
R-Right.
Did she just call me by my first name?
Yes, this is the Taka—
HURRY AND GET OVER HERE! YOU'RE—!
Yes...
You just hung up, didn't you?
Where is it that you want me to hurry to anyway?
What?
Veranda... Why...?
Why?
Didn't you say that you'd do anything, just like a dog.
Wait a second! What I meant yesterday was that I'd help you with the Kitamura issu—!
You know what's going to happen if you don't get over here?
Or if you want I can help you understand...
Well... Could you wait just 10 minutes?
The rice is going to finish cooking around 10 minutes.
Three?
You want some too?
Amazing...
E-Excuse me.
Huh?
It's open?
What is that SMELL?!
Aisaka-san, I'm coming in.
That's a horrible smell.
AISAKA!
Aisaka! Aisaka! Aisaka!
Please! Please let me—!
CLEAN THE KITCHEN IN THIS HOUSE!
What this?
She went back to sleep?
She's like something that was man-made.
The sleeping Aisaka was really like a doll and—
She made this lifeless house look like a toy house set.
But it's too big for a doll's house.
I'd say about 15 minutes.
Alright!
What's this?
Hey.
I'm still in the middle of it, but its pretty clean now isn't it?
It was horrendous!
The water that accumulated in the sink had begun rotting.
And the drain was filled with sludge, mold and rotten food, a picture of hell.
The rooms were so dusty—
Trespassing... and cleaning without permission.
You didn't leave your markings everywhere, did you, you dog!
Dog?
Oh wait, that would be an insult to dogs.
Even though you're a dog, you're a mutt.
M-
M-U-
M-U-TT.
This woman has no sense of gratitude. I just went through all this—
Hey, aren't you going to say grace?
God of rice and everyone that produced it, thank you!
You know...
Hey, your nose stopped running.
Well, it's probably because this rooms all clean...
Eh? What did you just say?
Shut up!
A tedious pact.
The misconceptions that begin.
The power of genes.
Taiga, you're such a klutz that it's almost admirable.
Shut up... and rot!