I still think it's mysterious even now...
...but I also get the feeling it's not.
Anyway, it was something that changed my life.
And yet, it seems like nothing's changed at all.
It was something very, very strange,
and, at the same time, something everyone experiences.
It all happened here in Ikebukuro.
I-I-I-I'm so...rry.
I want to go back home.
Please, don't laugh.
I was absent for both my elementary and middle
school field trips, so I've never left my hometown.
See you!
Now, at fifteen years old, I'm in Tokyo for the first time ever and I'm confused.
It was a really great trip!
That's me, Ryugamine Mikado.
So, why am I darting my eyes around near
the gates for Tobu Railway's Tojo line?
That's because I'll be attending Raira Academy in East Ikebukuro starting this April.
The school's not that prestigious,
but it's beautiful and has great facilities.
Anyway, what really persuaded me to come here was
that my best friend from elementary school wanted me to.
My parents wanted me to go to a local public school, but I've always wanted to go to Tokyo.
Mikado!
Huh?
Kida?
Is that a question?
Then I'll happily answer it.
Pick from one of three choices.
Number one: Kida Masaomi.
Number two: Kida Masaomi.
Number three: Kida Masaomi!
No way! That's really you, Kida?
You're going to ignore a joke I've been working on for three years?
Long time no see, man!
You've changed so much I couldn't tell it was you.
I didn't think you'd dye your hair.
Oh, and that joke was pretty bad.
Well, it's been four years.
Anyway, you haven't changed since elementary school, Mikado.
And don't just casually tell me my jokes suck.
Yep, this is my best friend Kida Masaomi.
I hadn't seen him since he transfered out of my elementary
school, but other than his appearance, he hasn't changed a bit.
Alright, let's go.
Let's get above ground.
I'm in an unmistakably "go west" type of mood.
I'll trick you by faking going to the west
exit and really take you to the Seibu one...
His jokes aren't very good, but he's a great guy.
I don't feel very distant from Kida since we chat online every day.
But after reuniting four years later, it's obvious we grew up in different towns.
However, he's the same as he's always been, bad jokes included.
Is there anywhere in particular you want to go?
Umm...
How about Sunshine 60...?
Already?
If you want to go there, we should at least bring one girl with us.
T-Then, how about the Ikebukuro West Gate Park?
Just call it "West Gate Park."
Huh? But don't all Ikebukuroers call it...
What're these "Ikebukuroers" you speak of?
Hm? What, you want to go there?
Uh, w-w-w-wait!
Let's not go.
It's already night!
We'll be killed by a gang or something!
You're seriously going to have a bad time if you keep acting like that.
Besides, it's only six.
Man, you're still as cowardly as ever.
Tanaka Taro has entered the chat room.
Good Evening.
'Evening.
Ah, Setton.
Actually, I'm going to live in Ikebukuro starting tomorrow.
Whoa, nice.
You might move to my neighborhood.
Yeah, I might.
I'm still signing on from my parents' house,
but starting tomorrow I'll be logging
in from an apartment near Sunshine.
Welcome to Ikebukuro.
Amazing...
This world I've only seen on the Internet
and in comics is finally right in front of me.
This is cooler than Kamizakura-machi Ginza.
Then I'll take you to Shibuya sometime.
Or, if crowds of people amaze you, I can take you to a horse race.
Gang activity is down recently, too.
They were all over the place last year, but they got into a fight with some Saitama guys and a bunch of people got arrested.
Also, the cops started cracking down on any
group where everyone wore the same colors.
Does that mean Ikebukuro's safe now?
Well, I've only heard things second-hand, so I don't really know.
There are tons of other dangerous people around, so be careful.
I see...
Anyway, this is 60th street, also known as Sunshine Street.
Maybe it really was called Sunshine Street first.
I-I'm sorry!
It's Kida.
Ah, if it isn't Karisawa and Imazaki.
Hello.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Yo.
How are you, Kida?
Long time no see!
Who's the guy with you? A friend?
Yes, he's a childhood friend. He just moved here today.
Huh, I see.
Her name's Karisawa.
He's Yumasaki,
And over there are Kadota and Togusa.
Uh, umm...my name is Ryugamine Mikado.
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
Is that a psuedonym?
Why would a high schooler use a psuedonym?
Ah, maybe he's on the radio or in magazines.
No, uhh...it's my real name.
No way, that's your name?!
Awesome! That's so cool!
It's like the name of a protagonist in some comic!
C'mon, you're embarrassing him.
What should I do? I can't keep up with their conversation.
Are you on your way back from shopping?
Right.
Dengeki released some new pocket editions, so we bought about thirty in all.
Dengeki releases that many books in a month?
No, of course not.
We both bought one of each series.
And then...well, we bought ten for various reasons.
Various, indeed.
What do they mean by "various reasons"?
Do they mean like, one to preserve,
one to resell, another to read, and such?
Well, we better get going.
See you again soon.
Alright, see you.
We should put this thing in head-first.
See you.
Hey, don't ram that into the car!
They're all pretty weird, but once you get to know them they're really nice.
Hmmm...so you also hang out with people like that, Kida?
Well, I know a lot of different people.
So I know lots of good shops, where to find cheap second-hand clothing...
What kind of experiences has he had in the four years we've been apart?
All this while I was holed up in my hometown.
If you know enough about lots of different things, you can make conversation with almost any girl.
How vulgar.
I told you already.
Are you sure that's her?
She matches the description you gave me exactly from head to toe.
Roger.
Let's go.
Okay.
Make sure to put enough in.
If she doesn't wake up,
she's going to be worth a lot less.
She's a teenage girl, so we'll get fifty percent more than usual.
More like twenty percent.
We haven't had a teenage girl in a long time.
Yeah, thanks to the info we got.
Good evening.
Kanra!
You're online?!
I had to take a call.
Ah.
I just finished reading the log. You're coming to Tokyo?
Congratulations.
Can we meet offline sometime?
That sounds good to me.
Totally.
Ah, speaking of offline meetings...
Lots of people meet offline to commit suicide, right?
Yeah, it was popular for a while.
They'd meet online, then make a suicide pact...
What an unpleasant topic.
But those kinds of stories haven't made the news lately, have they?
People might have failed to kill themselves...
Or there might still be lots of incidents,
but no one's noticed they're still happening.
Maybe no bodies have been found...
Uhh...
That's inappropriate.
Speaking of which, there have been
lots of missing persons cases recently...
Huh?
Like they made the news?
Umm...
Most of them have been illegal aliens...
...or kids who've run away from home...
But apparently many of them occur between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
Excuse me.
Yes...?
Are you Miss Magenta?
Yes, I am.
Are you Mr. Nakura?
Great! I knew it was you.
Nice to meet you.
Please take care of me.
It's nice to meet you as well.
Let's go.
Okay...
It's right this way.
Two people should be there already.
Ah.
That's it.
Hello.
Are we in the clear?
No one's around.
Well then, sorry to deceive you!
You're in a place like this by yourself?
Kida continued talking without a single pause.
I was starting to get tired.
I didn't know whether I was tired from all the walking or from
having to keep up with his jokes, but it was probably a bit of both.
After finally seeing you, I feel like no matter how much I talk, it's not enough.
Y-Yeah, me too...
Right now I feel like I've only talked about 5/400ths of what I've been thinking!
And 4/400ths of that was used up on Karisawa and her friend.
Just as I was debating whether or not to play
along with his joke, it appeared before my eyes.
Hey, missy, long time no see.
A black guy dressed as a chef was passing out flyers to customers...
No, a huge black guy was dressed as a chef...
No, some guy dressed as a chef was
handing out flyers and happened to be black...
Long time no see, mister.
Hey, Simon! It's been forever!
Ah, Kida.
You want to eat some sushi?
It's good.
I'll give you a discount.
Sushi's good.
Forgive me, I don't have much money on me.
I'll eat here once I get paid, so make sure to give me the discount then.
No, that's no good!
If you do that, I'll disappear into the seaweed plains of Russia!
Seaweed on land, huh?
See you.
Long time no see, mister.
Do you know him, too?
Yeah, that's Simon.
He's a Russian of African descent, and he
works for that sushi place owned by a Russian.
Uh, sorry. What part of that is the joke?
No, I'm serious.
His name's really Semyon, but everyone just says it like the English "Simon".
Oh, hey, mister...
I don't know too much about him, but apparently
his parents are seeking asylum here or something.
And now that a Russian's started a sushi bar, he's been working to pull customers in.
Don't get on his bad side, okay?
One time he broke up a fight by lifting up a guy his size with just one hand.
Oh, and one more guy you shouldn't make an enemy of is—
Huh? What's that?
Ah, speak of the devil.
Anyway, don't go near Heiwajima Shizuo.
If you just go about your business, you'll probably never run into him.
W-What sort of person could he be?
Aw, they're still not here.
That's weird.
The higher ups are horrible at this.
They need to get their act together.
Whatever. We've got time.
You're right.
Sometimes you just need to take a break, eh?
You need some time to cool down
when you lead messed up lives like we do.
Oh yeah, I saw it today.
The black bike.
A black bike?
Yeah...
You don't know about it?
Everyone in Shinjuku and Ikebukuro is talking about it.
It used to be considered something of an urban legend, but recently lots of people have taken pictures of it...
Oh yeah, I heard about that.
Isn't it just some normal biker gang?
Although it's not like there are lots of them who get together and ride in a convoy.
It's idiotic enough to ride around on a bike without headlights.
At least, if would be for a human...
What do you mean by that?
Um, well...to tell you the truth,
it's kind of like a monster.
Hey.
Um, are you one of the higher ups?
There's no way they'd look like that.
Then who is it?
You're being pretty rude, don't you think?
We're in the middle of something...
If you're going to interfere, do us a favor and die!
N-No way!
Oh shit!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Stop! Stop it! Stop it!
And that's why I told you to stop it.
This is bad...
This is bad!
Really bad!
W-What is that?
What the hell is that?!
What do you mean by "monster"?
Dotachin says he's the grim reaper.
Dotachin?
Who's Dotachin?
Anyway, about the guy who rides the black bike...
You're not going to tell me about Dotachin?
Damn it!
You're roadkill now, you piece of shit.
Huh?
He doesn't have a head.
His head...
...seems to move fine even though it's completely gone.
H-Hey, what the hell are you?
Wh...What the hell are you?!
Hey, are there any other people I shouldn't go near?
Hmmm, gangs or the yakuza go without saying,
but there is a guy named Orihara Izaya.
Orihara Izaya?
What a weird name.
You're one to talk.
He's really dangerous, so definitely don't get involved with him.
He hangs out in Shinjuku, so you'll probably never meet him.
Oh, and you shouldn't get involved with a group called the Dollars.
"The Dollars?"
Yeah, "dollars" from "one dollars".
What are "One Dollars?"
I don't really know much about them.
Anyway, there are a lot of them, and I hear they all have short tempers.
They're supposedly a gang, but they don't have any gang colors.
They can't get together so they'll probably disband soon.
I see...
Oh hey, are you okay?
Are you alright?
Uhh, umm, I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
Umm...
No.
No! No!
Hey!
What's with her?
She didn't even say thank you.
I wonder what happened to her.
Well, anything can happen in this city.
You're lucky.
In one day you've been able to meet Kadota and his friends, Simon, Shizuo who can throw vending machines, and you ran into that beautiful girl.
I don't know if you can call that good luck...
I'm happy.
Huh?
I'm happy you're here and we're going to the
same school. I can hang out with you again.
Me, too.
You really are lucky!
You're about to lay eyes on a real urban legend!
Kida!
What, Tanaka Taro? You saw the black bike?
Was it around nine o'clock at night?
How did you know, Setton?
Well, I was there, too, so...
Huh?!
What do you mean by "urban legend"?!
The black bike!
That headless guy's here!
At that moment, I noticed I was trembling.
It wasn't because I was scared.
I think...it was because I was moved.
I'd seen something amazing.
Here, in this city, I'd experienced something I couldn't even have dreamed of.
I felt as if an unbelievable reality that I could
never reach was unfolding before my eyes.
This probably contradicts what I said in
the beginning, but that's what I felt back there.
I was trembling at the feeling that a new reality had begun for me.
Really?
Then we might have walked passed each other without even knowing it.
Maybe.
By the way...
Who's Dotachin?
Somewhere, a mysterious girl catches a glimpse of a reality she's never known.
A reality where it seems anyone can run into someone else, yet no one does.
What did his girl who's supposed to have died actually see?
Next time: Between Truth And Lies.