I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
We're All
Sinners
It's started.
Don't let them get away!
Take no prisoners!
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
Lieutenant Colonel.
There's something I'd like to ask you later.
Whatever it is, I'm not interested.
Save your breath.
Lieutenant Colonel!
Halt.
This is a restricted area.
I'm from the Japanese Imperial Demon Army's
vampire extermination unit.
That may be so,
but company officers and below are prohibited from entering.
What is this facility used for?
I'm afraid I cannot—
It's a lab for the guinea pigs.
Watch it.
What's the harm in telling her?
Every other troop in Shinjuku already knows.
Care to elaborate?
They're probing vampire bodies for exploitable weaknesses.
So, human experimentation?
Sure, if you count those bloodsuckers as human.
In any case, please let me through.
Once again, company officers and below are—
How about now?
The Hiiragi crest?!
Thank you.
Pardon me, but...
why would a member of the
Hiiragi family remain as a sergeant?
"Sergeant" has a nice ring to it, don't you think?
I also hold no interest for the trivial
power struggles you see within the military.
That's how my sister died, after all.
For five days, I've looked for you.
Is that so?
Well, my bad.
I have a question I'd like to ask you.
And I'd rather you not.
Scram already.
Yuu is still unconscious.
What have you done to him,
Lieutenant Colonel Guren?
Or rather,
what are you planning to do with him?
You ordered me to give Yuu a special cocktail of drugs
because his Infernal Arm was unique.
But didn't he go berserk because of those very same drugs?
What exactly were they?
Please answer, Lieutenant Colonel!
It's not like you to get so riled up.
Are you upset?
Oh, well.
So, what answer would you be satisfied with?
Would an "I didn't do anything"
give you peace of mind?
Don't give me that!
There's no way you haven't done anyth—
Or should I admit to human experimentation and make you angry instead?
How can we, as the frail species we are,
survive in this collapsing world?
What of eliminating the Horsemen of the Apocalypse?
Exterminating the vampires?
Just how many were sacrificed
for your older sister, Hiiragi Mahiru,
to finish her life's work on the Infernal Arms?
Could we, as a species,
have survived in this world without them?
It's a little too late to act like we're above such things.
Or could it be...
that you're infatuated with Yuu?
What's with that face?
Frankly, I couldn't care less about
what happens between the two of you.
But I'm not here to give you love advice, so get out.
Please wait! Answer my—
I said, out.
Oh, and those drugs?
They take five days to wear off,
so he'll be awake soon enough.
If you love him, you'd best stay by his side.
Yuu...
Please, wake up.
Infatuated, he says? There's no way...
But please hurry and open your eyes...
Yuu.
Time to fall back.
Let go! I'm...
I'm going to save Yuu!
I know how you feel, but it's just not possible right now.
Take a look.
Look at him being smothered
by all that sickening human greed.
Damn them...
Damn them!
Damn those humans!
Well? Are you finally seething with hatred for the humans?
Shut up!
You despise both humans and vampires alike.
So, what are you supposed to be?
I can't wait to find out.
It's time to go home.
Don't touch me!
All right, playtime's over.
That's enough fun for one day.
Not a single peep out of you, child.
Curse detoxification is complete.
These are the first tears I've shed ever since I became a vampire.
I gotta say, that one human
sure did a number on us.
How's your injury, Mika?
You got the worst of it.
Silent treatment again, newbie?
Speaking of, what was that monster?
Who knows?
It's been raised as a concern
within the Progenitor Council.
What?
Something about the humans studying
forbidden magic that could end the world.
I think they called it...
the "Seraph of the End."
Apparently, our true goal in Shinjuku was to retrieve that scary thing.
Oh?
So I take it the mission was a failure?
No idea.
Lord Ferid was in command,
but I sometimes haven't the
slightest clue what's on his mind.
I don't know much...
but maybe you do.
You know who that monster was, right?
That's why you're Queen Krul's favorite.
Hyakuya Mikaela,
just who are you?
If you don't feel like answering,
we can just find out for ourselves.
Who am I?
Good question.
Y-You're not human anymore?
Shouldn't my looks give it away?
I'm just your average, ugly vampire.
The hell?
Hyakuya Mikaela.
Third Progenitor Krul Tepes wishes to see you.
Please make your way to the
Royal Audience Chamber immediately.
Would you look at that?
The queen's calling for her pet.
Hey, Yoichi!
Wake up!
What's going on?!
Yuu! I've been waiting for you to wake up!
Same here!
What the hell happen—
Thank goodness!
Hey!
Answer my quest—
I need to let the others know.
I'll be right back!
Hey, hold on!
Are they...
Is everyone okay?
Is that concern I see?
Not really, I'm just...
Don't worry.
Everyone else is fine.
I see.
You were in a coma for seven days.
Seven days?!
Seriously?
Seriously.
So I'm gonna let everyone know, okay?
What a relief...
They're okay.
I'm glad.
Mika...
You being alive wasn't a dream either, right?
I can't believe it.
You're really...
Is this the crybaby's room?
I guess it is.
It's fine.
It's okay to cry.
You found your family, after all.
I'm glad that you're awake.
What's going on?
I don't...
remember anything.
Nothing at all?
Yeah.
I see.
Well, basically, you said you were sleepy and took a nap during the fight.
What?
Are you serious?!
Of course not.
You suddenly fell unconscious,
and we were all on the verge of annihilation.
But then reinforcements soon arrived,
with Lieutenant General Kureto
and Major General Shinya leading the main unit.
And the vampires?
Nobles aside, we were able to deal with many of the normal ones.
We also captured a few,
but many were able to escape.
Then...
Wondering about Mika?
What happened?
Mika was...
Feel free to just say it.
Whether Mika's a friend or foe,
as long as he's alive, that's enough for me.
So just give it to me straight.
Mika was...
taken by the vampires.
I see.
Yes.
Got it.
Thanks.
Or so you say, but don't let me catch you leaving
the hospital to raid the vampire city all on your own.
Yeah, yeah.
Right now, knowing he's alive is enough for me.
Good to know.
I'll carry him there!
Where do we need to go?
For now, the temporary base.
Hurry!
Mika...
and Yuu...
Family, huh?
Shinoa.
Oh, yes?
Thanks for worrying about me.
You're welcome.
You...
Wh-What? Wait...
This injury...
Are you okay?
Oh, that?
Um, yes, they were just feeling a bit thirsty.
'Sup, idiot?
Finally awake, are...
you...
Y-You two!
What the hell are you doing?!
Um, no, it's not what it looks like!
I was just showing him where the vampire bit me.
Wait, didn't you get bitten too?
Are you okay?
So that's what it was...
Quiet in the hospital.
Who do you think you are?!
What the hell's this?
You look perfectly fine to me.
I'm sorry I worried you.
What?
Why would I worry about you?
Oh, please.
You were fussing and hovering over him the entire time.
What?!
Don't make shit up!
When did I do that?!
You totally were, Kimizuki.
What was that?!
Mind if I say something, guys?
What is it?
Sure.
Yes?
Thanks. Sorry for all the trouble.
I'm glad you're all alive.
I've been blessed with good friends.
Wait, what?
I don't think he's recovered yet.
It's clear he hit his head or something.
Oh, no. Yuu was a gentle, kind soul from the start!
I sure wish he would stop acting like a saint.
I'll take you all on!
Anyway, stay in bed for now.
We're still on a break.
A break?
Yes.
Until you make a full recovery,
the Hiiragi Shinoa unit will be taking a few days off.
A break, huh?
I understand you want to rescue Mika as soon as possible, but...
Nah.
I don't want to cause any more trouble,
so I'll behave myself and rest.
I'll go fetch us some drinks.
That's our Kimizuki!
A loving brother and friend.
Oh, shut up.
I'll come with you!
Meanwhile, our girl Mitsu here hasn't lifted a finger!
That's rich, coming from another girl
who hasn't done crap!
I'm babysitting the entire unit, so I'm excused.
Analytical Report
None of my friends died.
Mika is alive.
Really? What did I do to deserve such good luck?
But if he's alive, then I can rest easy at night.
Mika...
Yuu...
I swear I will...
...save you.
Well, I must say.
It's almost amusing how smoothly things are moving.
As always, the greed of the human species
spirals out of control,
just as we vampires fall prey
to our own arrogance.
Don't you agree, partner?
Oh, lighten up.
This is our research data.
Ah, that's right. I almost forgot...
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu