We will now begin the 57th sortie beyond the Walls!
Onward!
The Reconnaissance Legion's quest for a route to Shiganshina
instead leads it to the Eoten Fatale, a human Eoten like Eren.
This is no abnormal Eoten.
It's a human in an Eotenes body!
As the slaughter of the soldiers continues unslackened,
the humans fly into the Forest of Titanic Trees
following orders not yet understood.
If Squad Levi won't take that bitch out, who will?
Decide.
Believe in yourself.
Or believe in the Legion and in me.
I'll continue on!
Fire!
Which reminds me,
I wanted to ask you something.
Mind if we slice off your hands and legs?
They just grow back, right?
I'm talking about your real hands and legs.
We do need you... alive...
This enemy
was willing to sacrifice everything.
I never expected her to allow herself to be devoured by fellow Eotenas
simply to deny us information.
All troops, retreat!
Back into your formation!
Return to Karanes!
Erwin...
Why'd you order Levi to resupply?
There was no time.
Our target was eaten.
But did you see the person inside being devoured?
I sure didn't.
So you mean...?
That's right.
If your hypothesis is correct,
and they can still move to a degree after regaining human form...
And if they'd prepared a set of Gear in advance...
Then the person inside her is wearing our uniform right now.
Corporal Levi?
No, it's—!
Who are you?!
Gunther!
The enemy is now disguised as one of our soldiers.
O, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
O, my friend!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel
We will kill
The enemy is huge
We will jump
In our hands we hold blades of glory
We sing of victory
On our backs we have wings of freedom
We put our iron determination into our hearts
We slash apart the circle of idiocy
We fly through the endless blue
on wings of freedom
the eotena onslaught
Crushing Blow
57th Sortie Beyond the Walls ( 5 )
When the Behemoth Eotenes' body vanished,
whoever was inside must have been equipped with a set of Maneuver Gear
which they used to escape amidst the steam.
Don't you think the same strategy could be used in this situation?
Is that really possible?
Based on our observations of Eren's emergence from his Eotenes body,
it doesn't seem feasible.
His equipment had been destroyed, and his uniform torn off.
Most importantly, Eren was so weak he couldn't even get to his feet unassisted.
Our target had the ability to summon other Eotenas with her cry.
We failed to predict this, and thus the operation failed.
If experience determines a human Eotena's abilities
then we were short-sighted to use Eren, a total novice, as our benchmark for the Eotena's capacities.
If we are to outwit our enemy, we must not fall prey to our own preconceptions.
So does the withdrawal order mean the mission was a success?
If so, we may already have learned who was inside the human Eoten.
Now there's a face I'd love to see.
But how'd the Commander know
that the enemy'd come chasing after Eren if he left the Walls?
I think it's because of the last onslaught's mystery.
The Eotenas suddenly halted their attack when it was only half-completed.
Even though they'd managed to break through Trost's gate,
they didn't even try for the inner gate.
And when Eren sealed the gate, the human Eotenas let him.
It could mean that something else drew their attention...
Something else?
Something more important to them than breaching the Walls.
Something completely unforeseen.
Eren's transformation into an Eoten?!
I think that's the only reasonable answer.
Then that means...
Wait... So...
Someone who was there, someone who saw Eren transform,
must be the Eoten Fatale.
Gunther!
Eren, don't stop!
Onward!
But Gunther—
Who is it?
Defend Eren!
Shit! Now what?
Elad, where should we go?
There's no time to retrieve the horses!
Head for HQ as fast as you can!
Is it the person from that Eotenes bitch?
Or is there more than one spy?
Damn you.
How dare you?!
Come at me!
I may die, but I will end you!
That human Eoten?
Impossible. Why?
Didn't we catch it?!
If the enemy has the ability to retain its strength,
it may be able to transform once more.
I knew it.
It's coming!
It is that Eotenes bitch!
Damn you.
How dare you!
This time, I'll take her down!
No!
The three of us will destroy this target.
You will continue to make directly for HQ at top speed!
Here is the lesson to draw from this battle.
If we focus solely on building a strategic superiority,
we will never overcome our opponent.
When necessary, we must be willing to risk everything we have,
and, perhaps, to lose it all.
I'll fight too!
No!
This is the best response.
Your power is too risky!
Starting to doubt us, you shitty brat?
Is that it, Eren?
Have you so quickly
lost your faith?
Unless we change the very way we fight,
Mankind shall not overcome!
I believe my squad will grasp its victory.
Fight on!
We've taken her sight.
For at least a minute, she'll be in total darkness!
This is the moment to destroy her!
Fuck capturing it.
Kill it now!
Die now, in shame eternal!
Make that bitch of an Eoten pay!
We won't let your eyes regenerate!
We'll slice off so much muscle around your shoulders,
you won't be able to keep your arms up!
Slice and dice...
Till her arms...
...fall down!
They're down!
Now for the neck!
Slice off the muscles that support her neck!
Then we can strike her weak point!
That's strength.
The Eoten is totally on the defensive.
How can they wordlessly coordinate their attacks like that?
It must be the strength of their faith in one another.
They've overcome so many trials through that faith.
That's why they're so strong, even right after losing Gunther.
I'll continue on.
If I continue on in this faith, without looking back, then...
I'm sure I'm doing the right thing.
I finally understand!
I don't know the right answer.
I never have.
I can only decide to trust in my own abilities
or the judgment of those I trust.
But no one ever knows how it'll turn out.
Go for the neck, now!
Elad!
But how?
She can't possibly see!
It hasn't even been thirty seconds.
Only one eye?
This bitch prioritized one eye to accelerate her healing.
Is that even possible?
Petra!
Hurry and regroup!
Petra, now!
Hey.
Die!
What's this?
My blade can't pierce it.
You...
You bitch...
I'll kill you!
Eren?
Wait, what? Mikasa?
That voice. Don't tell me—
Reconnaissance Legion Horses ( 1 )
The Legion's horses were specially bred
for expeditionary use, and stand around
15.2 hands, weighing between 450 and 500 kg.
Reconnaissance Legion Horses ( 1 )
The Legion's horses were specially bred
for expeditionary use, and stand around
15.2 hands, weighing between 450 and 500 kg.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Reconnaissance Legion Horses ( 2 )
The top speed of these mounts is between 75 and 80 km/h,
and they can maintain speeds of 35 km/h over long distances.
Horses are the most effective means of escaping an Eoten.
Reconnaissance Legion Horses ( 2 )
The top speed of these mounts is between 75 and 80 km/h,
and they can maintain speeds of 35 km/h over long distances.
Horses are the most effective means of escaping an Eoten.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
I made the wrong decision.
I wanted to have faith in my comrades.
My faith killed them all!
If I'd only trusted myself from the start. If I'd only fought.
If I'd only killed it in the beginning!
At that moment,
if I'd transformed into an Eoten...
No.
Even before then.
If I had decided to fight.
Corporal Levi was there, too.
We would've won.
Maybe we could've captured it.
You aren't in the wrong.
If you wanna do it, do it.
I...
I made my decision.
And it killed everyone.
Their blood is on my hands.
But for all that,
it's still your fucking fault!
I'll rip you up.
Once my hand heals,
I'll tear you apart. I'll shred you like meat.
Slice you and dice you
and eat you up!
Eren!
Wait. Eren.
Don't go.
Give...
Eren...
back!
Give him back!
Give Eren back!
Why can't my blade penetrate her?
I know
you're alive.
Eren! I know you're alive!
No matter where this bitch goes, I'll kill her,
slice her apart,
and pull you out of her filth.
I'm sorry, Eren.
Wait just a little longer.
Wait for me!
Wh-What?
Fall back for now.
Maintain this distance.
She may be tiring.
The bitch seems to be slowing down.
So she bit him right out of the Eotenes' neck?
Is Eren dead?
If we assume that I am not truly who I think I am,
then how can you claim that you are yourself?
A castle of sand guarded your heart, and it fell apart
Can you gather the pieces and repair yourself?
The voices of others calling you
are just a ringing in your ear now
It's like time has stopped
Now, wake up
I want to escape the darkness
I want to flee like a raging storm
We lived like corpses, as though already dead
Let us meet again
outside the walls
where maps reach terra incognita
Eren is alive.
Give Eren back.
The Eoten Fatale snatched Eren away from Mikasa before her very eyes.
She joins forces with Mankind's greatest soldier, Levi,
to challenge the Eoten to a fateful battle.
The Defeated
57th Sortie Beyond the Walls ( 6 )