When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Having become a butler
for the Sanzenin family,
Hayate Ayasaki was given a top
secret mission in the last episode.
A mission to infiltrate the super
prestigious Hakuou Academy.
Hayate, I understand that you
like high places already,
so quickly dispatch the
enemy and get to Nagi.
Evil, therefore kill!
Evil
Therefore
Kill
Prepare to meet your fate!
CLANG
Hina?!
Honestly! Another one of
your nonsensical antics?!
Hayate escaped the Academy without mishap.
However...
A new crisis was already drawing very near...
It's so early in the morning...
What could the commotion be about?
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Nagi, I'm gonna get a good look
at yer new partner's abilities.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Thoughtless Jokes and
Kindness Bring Misfortune
Miss, it's morning! Please wake up!
Here you are, Miss. Your towel.
Mm.
Here you are. Your soup.
Here you are. Your bag.
You must change quickly and get to school...
Hayate, it's a delightful morning, is it not?
I agree. A delightful morning.
On a delightful morning such
as this, you absolutely must...
Go back to sleep.
Wait! Wh-What do you mean, go back to sleep?!
Pardon me, Miss?!
Oh, dear, it seems we have a problem.
Maria...
She just went yesterday,
so I wonder if she means to stay home
for most of this school term now.
She was like that all of last year, too.
Why is the Miss so terribly...
Rather than a dislike of school, she
has an extreme dislike of going out.
What?
Ever since Nagi was little,
her life has been targeted on a daily basis
as the only daughter of the Sanzenin family.
And all the adults who approach her
are only after her vast fortune.
I see.
And that is why she has
grown to be so difficult.
Of course.
Look at me. Even the way I
first met the Miss was...
...because of my ulterior motive to
pay back my 150 million yen debt.
But now, I am a butler, who
serves the Sanzenin family!
I must put my heart and
soul into protecting her,
so that the Miss may spend every
day with a smile on her face!
Um, Hayate, the contents of your
monologue is completely audible.
Yes, hello? Sanzenin resi...
Oh, it has been so long! How have you been?
Yes, she's here. Please wait one moment.
Nagi, you have a phone call!
From whom?
Sakuya!
Saku? Tell her I'm not here.
That will not work. I already
told her that you were here.
Sheesh! You're hopeless...
Oh, hello? Is that you, Nagi?
Ping. This phone number
is currently not in use.
If you would like to state your business,
leave a message after the beep
and your house will be engulfed in flames.
FOOL!
Don't you hang up without
waitin' for a response! Fool!
It doesn't gimme a chance to talk!
Um... uh...
Shoot. I guess the spacin' was a
tad too far there. Just a tad far.
Gotta keep the spacin' tighter or
it'll make even funny things unfunny.
All right, time to review. Y'all
hurry up and sit down, too.
Hey, Maria, I want Earl
Grey. Get me some Earl Grey.
That's hot! That's seriously hot!
DVD Extra!!
That's no good! That's
boilin' hot! Boilin' hot!
If ya don't make it a little cooler,
it's hard to react good! Seriously!
You're reacting plenty, so don't worry.
And while you're at it, please die.
That's my future partner! Yer
straight talk jabs are merciless.
Yah!
Um, who is this?
Miss Sakuya Aizawa.
The eldest daughter of the Aizawa family,
which is related to the Sanzenin family.
And a childhood friend of Nagi's.
Childhood friend...
So? Why are you here?
Besides, today is a weekday.
What happened to school?
Don't you worry. Today's
Foundation Day for us.
So I took advantage of it and
came all this way to check in.
Check in... on what?
Yer butler.
I heard you've been stayin' home from school
and havin' the time of yer
life with yer new butler.
So I came today to check in on him!
To see just how funny a guy he is!
Hah! Why would I need you to check up on him?
Besides, you already saw Hayate just earlier.
Huh? Earlier?
The new butler's...
...an ornamental knick-knack?!
No, no, swing the camera a
little more to the right!
Or rather, you're doing this
on purpose, aren't you?!
Wh-What?!
You mean that fella who was just
standin' there's the new butler?!
Cyclamen
I wonder if it's possible that
girl came to see the Miss,
because she was worried about her.
Ah! But we sure have great
weather again today!
Considering how warm it is,
maybe it'll be midsummer by
the time Golden Week is over.
Then maybe we'll get to see autumn leaves
by the start of the rainy season!
Well, no way, right?
'Course not, ya fool!
Smack Smack Smack Smack Smack Smack
Ya think a weak jab like that at
yerself'll make that joke work?!
Don't you underestimate comedy!
For every joke ya crack, ya gotta
jab like yer life depended on it!
Um, if you keep that jab going any
longer, Hayate is going to die...
Huh?
Shoot! Am I a murderer at this tender age?!
Makita! Kunieda! Emergency treatment!
Certainly, Miss.
Wh-What are you doing?!
He has come to.
Good work.
Damn.
You, what's yer name?
What?
It's Hayate Ayasaki...
What an ordinary name!
Startin' today, call yerself
"Mukitaro the Soybean Lover".
What?!
He's not your butler!
Don't give him a name that sounds
like a two-bit entertainer!
Impressive. Everyone with hair tied
in two parts and who has that voice
sure are merciless when it comes to jabs.
Eh? I not know what you mean!
But of all of Nagi's past partners,
he looks the poorest of
'em all and that's a fact.
I-I see...
Looks like I've got no choice but
to become sorta like the master
and form a trio comedy group along with Nagi.
How in the world do you twist things
around so we end up doing that?!
A butler doesn't need to be funny!
Wow, so butlers are required
to have comedic talent, too.
What're you, a fool?!
No, they are not. Usually.
Ayasaki, do ya know what yer
missin' as an entertainer?
Huh?
He's a butler, damn it!
It's impact!
For example, havin' villains out to getcha
or havin' no problem bein' run over by a car,
or havin' an all-out battle
against some bizarre robot.
It's that kinda impact that yer lackin'!
I've pretty much done all
those things, though...
Don't you talk back to yer master!
Smack Smack Smack Smack Smack Smack
Ridin' the comedy boom...
Get a li'l popular, and ya think you've
conquered the world already?! Eh?!
You'll never become the second
Ni-Ni or Downtown like that!
M-Maria, is it possible that she's...
Just like Nagi, she absolutely hates to lose.
I-I see!
Maybe in the Miss's world, this
is a normal thing for them.
But I've become a butler now, too.
I have to come up with some
routine that'll satisfy everyone!
I understand, Miss Aizawa.
I will perform a special one-off
joke, so if you find it funny,
let us say that I've surpassed my master!
Mutter... Mutter... Mutter...
A one-off joke?!
Will Hayate be all right?!
That is setting the difficulty too high!
Then, here I go.
Get...
Just hang tight
for a sec, okay?
Ya fool! Not only did ya steal
that line, but it's frickin' old!
I-I apologize!
But well, I can't fault ya
for yer go-getter attitude.
What?
Ya sure have found a fine entertainer, Nagi.
He's a butler, damn it!
With that kinda go-getter attitude,
I'd say Nagi's in good hands.
Miss Aizawa...
So, you really did come
out of worry for the Miss.
N-No! I'll have ya know, it's not
like ya have my approval yet!
First up, one-liner jokes till ya drop!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Hey, Hayate!
Honestly! He doesn't need to go along
with this so conscientiously...
But when he's smiling so guilelessy,
Hayate looks more like the boy that he is.
Comaneci!
Gachoon!
Fo!
Swing yer hips more!
Popping eyebrows!
Hey, you two!
It's getting kind of cold,
so let's get back inside!
Good idea.
Yes, Miss!
Man, I've got the chills.
But still, it really got
cold all of a sudden.
It was the right decision
not to go to school.
What kinda reasonin' is that?
Anyway, it's all 'cause that butler's
jokes were so lame, they left me cold.
Maria, would you go make us some tea?
The thing is... We seem to have
run out with the last pot we made.
What?!
This is a problem. We're to have
an important visitor soon, too.
Huh? Who's comin'?
Isumi.
C'mon now, what're you two
doin', both skippin' school?
Not to worry. Unlike Wataru, we get
top grades, so it's not a problem.
But is it gonna be all right?
With what?
Knowin' Isumi, ya sure
she hasn't gotten lost and
stranded somewhere again?
What? On an errand?
Would you please go for me?
This is the shop.
The purchase has already been paid for
and if you let them know you're
on Sanzenin family business,
they will know what brand
and what amount to give you.
I understand! I will go right away!
Oh, hold on a second, Hayate.
Yes?
When you go outside on business
for the Sanzenin family,
please make sure to wear that coat.
Um, this coat...
Could it be... cashmere?
My! I'm impressed that you were able to tell.
Are you sure about this?
If I should get it dirty outside...
This coat looks so expensive...
What are you saying, Hayate?
The coat doesn't just look expensive.
It is expensive.
What?
After all, 100 of those coats
could easily pay off your debt.
So please be absolutely
sure not to get it dirty.
Y-Yessir.
Smackity, smack, smack!
(Pachi pachi panchi)
Blood sacrifice, hurray!
(Chimatsuri wasshoi)
Miss!
Miss Isumi!
Did you find her?
No, she is not over here!
Hey, you two!
I found this horrifying
letter in the Miss's room!
What's this?
"I am going to visit Nagi at her home.
I will be back by dinner. Isumi."
This is terrible! She has
gone outside by herself?!
She even gets lost on the estate
here on a regular basis...
Yes, and I heard the daughter
of the Sanzenin family
was almost kidnapped just
the other day, too...
Damn it, find her! Find her!
If she's about to get kidnapped...
Beat the culprit to a pulp!
Wearing an expensive coat
like this makes me nervous.
Well, I'm only going out to buy tea,
so I doubt anything will
happen to get it dirty.
Released Every Week on ***day
Shonen Yonday
Oh, I am so sorry!
I dropped paint that would leave
a permanent stain on cashmere!
Wha... P-Please be careful.
Oh, watch out!
Buckwheat noodle dip that would
leave a permanent stain on cashmere!
Ah, thank you. That was close, lad.
It was nothing. Please be careful.
Whoa, this is terrible!
A truck piled with octopi that spit ink
that would leave a permanent
stain on cashmere!
Th-This is bad.
These cliché dangers are coming at
me, as if they're targeting me...
Loser Park
If I walk through an empty park like this...
Yes, I should be safe for now.
Come to think of it, this is
the park where I met Miss Nagi.
Right, just around those vending machines...
Please insert bills here.
Accepts the
new 1000 yen bills.
Please insert bills here.
Accepts the
new 1000 yen bills.
The machine... is broken.
Um, you have to put in
bills there, not talismans.
This is terrible.
Pardon?
My friend told me that I mustn't carry
on conversations with strangers,
and yet, I am...
Oh, pardon me for that.
But it's all right.
This friend of mine is a kind person,
so I am sure I will be forgiven.
Is that so? What a relief.
Hayate's instincts, which had never
been wrong with this sort of thing,
told him that if he got involved
with this girl right now,
a great misfortune was certain
to befall him today...
Well, I'll be going now.
But to think that I have gotten
lost in a place like this...
What?
What in the world... am I to do...
I must run away. I must
run away. I must run away.
I must run away in order to avoid misfortune.
I must run away. I must run away!
Um, if you'd like my help, it's yours.
Are you well acquainted
with the roads around here?
No, I'm not very well acquainted, but...
If I leave a girl like you alone, I
feel like you might get kidnapped.
My friend always says the same thing to me.
Then, I would like to
take you up on your offer
and ask you for a bit of direction.
Yes, please go ahead.
Where am I going?
What?
There she is! Over there!
What?!
Who the hell are you?!
You hand over that girl without a fight!
Who are these suspicious people?
Who is this suspicious boy?!
Could it be... Kidnappers?!
With this Japanese sword, which
slices through cashmere coats,
I'll strike you down!
Get him!
Hang on tight!
What a fast getaway!
Um...
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
So... don't worry.
But...
What's wrong?
I feel as though... the area underfoot
is incredibly precarious...
A pond that makes cashmere coats
really dirty if you fall into it
It's a pond that makes cashmere coats
really dirty if you fall into it.
So please be absolutely
sure not to get it dirty.
But I can't drop this girl into the pond!
All right!
A-Are you okay?
Thanks to you.
Wh-What'll I do? This super
luxury cashmere coat...
It was brand new and Maria
told me not to get it dirty...
We have a careless protagonist.
Shut up!
But what should I do?
To start with, I'll be honest and
explain what happened to Maria...
And successfully get yourself fired.
I told you to shut up!
What in the world should I do?
Uh, um...
Like I said, shu...
Wha... uh... um...
No, that's not... I mean...
So, shu... shu... shucks, what
do you think of "Ultraman"?
What?
Um...
I like Bemster.
What? You will?
Yes, your precious coat has
been ruined because of me,
so um... I will pay for it...
Thank you.
I appreciate the thought, but I can't accept.
What? But...
This was my responsibility to begin with,
and while things just sort of happened,
I'm the one who promised to protect you.
I'll protect you from those
evil men in black. You'll see.
Evil men in black...
Yes.
No, those people are...
I know.
They're probably an evil organization
trying to capture you,
so they can use you to make money.
Um Um Um
Oh, no, um...
Don't worry!
Organizations of that sort tend
to have extensive spy networks,
so I won't do anything careless.
Um Um Um
No, that is not it...
I may not look it, but I've
faced a lot of dangers myself,
so you don't have to worry.
If we do not get you dry, you
will catch a cold and die.
Thank you.
But I'm fine.
I-It was too late...
No, no, I'm not dead yet.
Anyway, right now, I have
to get her somewhere safe.
Wait, I know of just the place!
What? This is...
Surprised?
But I know the person who
lives here, so it'll be fine.
The mistress of this estate is a
little girl about the same age as you
and she's a little spoiled and headstrong,
and she can be an unmanageable
bundle of energy sometimes,
but she's a very kind and adorable girl.
I am sure I will also be able to
become very good friends with her,
as if I have known her since we were little.
The only thing is, I can't go
inside due to various reasons,
so I'll leave the rest to you!
What?
Ding dong dash!
Uh, um...
The cost of playing for the
super luxury cashmere coat...
The threat of being fired...
And new enemies due to a groundless
assumption and misunderstanding
all descend upon him!
Next time, he will fight all of the above
along with the various symptoms of a cold,
such as coughing, fever, and sore throat!
Say, it's not a big deal, but I'm hungry.
Patience! Be patient until Isumi gets here!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
Preview
Honestly! Catching a cold all of
a sudden! How weak can you be?!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
While the fact that Nagi shut
him out was the final blow,
the original cause lies with me, so...
It is true that the Miss delivered
the final blow, but...
Grr. All right!
In that case, I will specially make
some dish called "rice porridge"!
What?
What was with that? You
didn't sound very happy.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"You Say You Can See Time,
You Say You Can See Time, But That Is
Probably Your Life Flashing Before Your Eyes
"But That Is Probably Your Life
Flashing Before Your Eyes".
Could it be that she used
this, mistaking it for oil?
You will see the tears of time.