We have come to the last
day of Golden Week.
Did everyone enjoy the holiday?
I'm about to die from boredom...
Man, it's all because of that
worthless mongrel...
It's not my fault you didn't
get to see Kitamura.
He warned us he'd be busy with
practice and student council stuff.
Isn't it your job as my dog
to make that happen?
Not like you'd be able to hold an actual
conversation if you did see him...
Burn in hell!
Ah! I got some on me!
What did you do?
Hurry! Get me a cloth or something!
Jeez...
It's your fault for saying stupid things!
So loud...
Oops, we woke her up.
Here, use this to wipe yourself.
You were gonna eat rice omelets
by yourselves while I slept!
I wrapped yours up and put it in the fridge!
Did you write my name on it?
"Yasuko," in ketchup?
I'll write it!
So stop crying.
Sniff...
Okay, I'm going back to sleep.
Man, what should I do?
It's gonna leave a stain.
It'll come off as long as
we treat it properly.
I'll get the stain out.
So as thanks...
Jonny's again?
Why not? Come on...
I can't go by myself.
Can't you give me a little
help with Kushieda?
Oh, shove it!
I'll flay you!
How would you!?
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
donna kanji sonna kanji
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Ami Kawashima
Kushieda's not working today...
Even a workaholic needs
a break now and then.
Or maybe you're being punished for
putting your own happiness first.
I didn't do anything! Unlike someone with
her chain of confessions and vice vers—
- My eyes! My eyes!
- Stop saying such humiliating things.
Man, what are you doing?
This is cute.
Hmm? Let me see.
Need a few more inches to wear that...
I was talking about this bag! The bag!
R-Right...
Welcome.
So I'm a midget with short legs...
At least I've never had to be
a bother to other people...
What's up?
Ryuji! Look!
Th-The bag, right?
Not that! The model!
Model?
Look, over there.
Oh!
It's her, right?
You're right.
Her name is Kawashima Ami.
Daughter of Kawashima Anna, the actress.
What is she doing here?
Sorry, Ami.
I kept you waiting.
What!?
Ki-Ki-Kita-Kitamu...
Why if it isn't Takasu and Aisaka!
What a coincidence.
Wh-Why...!?
L-Look! They're coming this way!
S-So what!?
Why are you grabbing at each other?
Aren't you two all chummy!
N-Not at all!
What is it, Yusaku?
Well, I was about to introduce you.
Yusaku?
This is Kawashima Ami.
She used to live in my neighborhood.
I guess you could call us childhood friends.
- And this is Takasu Ryuji, and Aisaka Taiga.
- Childhood friends...
H-Hi there.
Nice to meet you.
Is that...?
Oh...
R-Right, uh...
We were just looking at this.
- And...
- Omigod...
Now I'm ashamed to let
you see me like this!
I should've spent more time selecting
my wardrobe and doing my makeup.
I get a little lazy about my looks
when I'm not on the set...
Not true!
Y-You, uh, c-could've fooled me...
Since we're all here, why don't we hang out?
That okay with you, Ami?
Of course!
This place sure brings back memories.
We used to come here all the time.
Yep, with our families!
Here you are, Takasu-kun.
Oh...
Do you prefer artificial sweetener?
No...
Or, I meant...
You take your coffee black?
Wow, you're not being very thoughtful.
I'm so sorry!
I saw Yusaku put some in his, so I just...
I-I don't mind...
There I go again...
People always tell me I'm a clumsy airhead.
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
I like things sweet!
Thank you!
You're so nice...
Omigod, what am I doing?
Oh, s-sorry about that.
Please! Why are you apologizing?
Well, I need to hit the men's
room real quick.
Wait, uh...
Um...
I, uh, need to go too.
Good lord...
Can't stand the awkward silence...
I knew you'd leave the table.
Didn't you go to the bathroom!?
Wh-What is it?
Be straight with me.
What's your impression of Ami?
I didn't have time to form one!
You threw me for a loop, showing up with
a cute girl out of nowhere like that!
I agree, she's cute.
And really nice too!
She's kind of an airhead, but
she sounds so innocent...
Just wait. You'll see.
Ugh, what a drag.
Hey, you.
I'm out of iced tea.
Get me another.
Tsk, ignoring me?
What's with the attitude?
Oh, I know.
I'll get your boyfriend to do it.
He seems willing to do anything I ask.
You mind if I steal him?
Not that I even want him!
He's not my boyfriend.
Oh.
I didn't care anyway.
And there it is. Ami's true nature.
Spoiled, selfish, and bossy.
Your typical princess.
I can only think she's been
possessed by a demon.
Well, I'd assume the rest of the men in
this backwards town aren't any better.
Hey, you.
How tall are you?
I just noticed how you seem
to be out of scale.
And wow, do they even sell
clothes in your size?
- Do you hem your jeans? I've never had to—
- I'm amazed Taiga's putting up with this...
Wh—?
There was a mosquito on your face.
Oh, it was a fly.
Now look here!
Come on now, Ami.
Time to get going.
- Yusaku!
- I know, I know.
Sorry about that, Aisaka.
We have to be on our way.
More!
There isn't any left...
You ate two and a half bowls.
It's all her fault.
That nasty wench.
Thinking about her makes my stomach growl.
Churn, you mean.
But Kitamura was a little distressed.
Wh-What should I do?
Will Kitamura-kun hate me for what I did?
I highly doubt that.
Kitamura was watching the whole—
I hate that girl.
Don't cry over it.
And you!
You were fawning over her!
I-I was not...
Besides!
No one in their right mind would brag
about being called an airhead!
Forget it.
I'll never see her again.
So I'll be mature and swallow my hatred!
Hey! That's mine!
Shaddap!
Kawashima Ami
I just transferred here today.
My name is Kawashima Ami.
But please call me Ami!
Whoa! Isn't she...?
The model from Can Vi!?
Wow... She's so pretty...
An angel has graced us with her presence!
Praise be to God.
Let's all make her feel welcome, okay?
Let's start by finding you a seat.
Here! Next to me!
What!? How about next to me?
Wow...
Jackpot!
I'm so glad I'm in this class!
It's kind of embarrassing
to stand out like this.
Why?
It's fine! You look great!
Yep, and you have a wonderful figure.
I wanna wear the same uniform
as everyone else!
Ami-chan is cute and has
a fab bod, for sure...
And yet, my cute-girl-detecting
Minorin Radar isn't reacting at all.
Minorin?
Are you okay, Ami-chan?
Jeez...
How did I trip over nothing?
I'm so lame.
You're pretty clumsy, huh?
A little airheaded, too.
That's not true!
Although, people do sometimes
call me an airhead...
Thought so.
But they're wrong!
Yes, yes. We know.
Honest!
It's true, I swear!
She's really something.
Yeah, she's mastered the art
of winning people over.
Why didn't you tell me she was
transferring to our school?
If I'd mentioned it, Ami wouldn't
have shown her true nature.
And that would defeat the purpose.
What are you talking about?
To be honest, I have no problem
with Ami's true nature.
In fact, I want everyone to see it,
and like her for who she really is.
Uh, that's—
Even if they end up hating her,
Ami will be able to accept that.
- I don't want her to keep living a lie.
- Really?
I saw it too!
Thank you.
Kinda weird to look at a swimsuit edition
when the model's here in person.
That's a little funny.
For real...
Me first!
I didn't know there was a
vending machine up here.
Why...?
You left class right when fourth
period was about to start.
I got a little curious, so I followed you.
Don't let her fool you.
Her true nature is...
It's against school rules to buy
drinks outside of lunch hour.
Guess that means we're partners in crime.
I'll pay.
No need.
This is to make up for yesterday.
F-For what?
I was so surprised this morning.
I didn't know we'd be in the same school.
And Aisaka-san's here too.
Yusaku never mentioned it.
So...did Aisaka-san say anything
to you about yesterday?
Like what...?
What happened yesterday was all my fault.
I'm a bit of an airhead, and I think
I may have ticked Aisaka-san off.
We were just chatting,
and all of a sudden she said I
was being vain and conceited.
And then...
But it wasn't her fault!
That never would've happened
if I had more common sense.
It's not that unusual, running into
other girls who hate me.
It doesn't bother me, though.
I always persevere.
I get what she's doing.
So I don't want you to mention what
happened yesterday to anyone else.
I...
I get what you're trying to say.
So let's go back.
Thank you!
We should hurry.
"The sun was still high as they
departed with minimal fanfare."
This first part refers to how the sun had
reached a high position in the sky.
"Why'd you and Kawashima Ami rush into
class at the last second together!?" -Taiga
Why...?
- The key here is that they're total strangers.
- Jeez...
To: Takasu-kun
From: Minori
Takasu-kun.
I am very angry!
Something's fishy about you
and the transfer student!
Are you cheating? Are you!?
If you dump Taiga...
I reckon there'll be a whippin'!
D-Damn it...
Why do I have to suffer for this?
From Takasu, to Kushieda.
Sorry to change the subject,
but what do you think of people who
refer to themselves as airheads?
Right.
Anything so far you don't understand?
What's wrong with you people?
Hey, Takasu.
Haruta's going to introduce us to
three first-year track members.
You in?
Wouldn't I just scare them away?
Nuh-uh.
If you don't, the ratio will be all—
Besides...
The Palm-top Tiger!
There you have it.
How did you manage this?
It wasn't on purpose!
I tripped! It's not my fault!
I'll go get a cloth.
You can head home.
It's okay.
I'll wait in the classroom.
Ryu—
Ew, why are you still here?
You're a total eyesore, just so you know.
Stay away, you damn brat.
Scaaa-ry.
No wonder the teachers are sick of you.
I was in the faculty office earlier, and all
the teachers were saying how cute I was.
They were worried that
"Aisaka" might bully me.
You're really unpopular around here, huh?
I'm going to enjoy seeing how long you
can maintain that double personality.
It'd be so simple to expose your true nature.
But that wouldn't be any fun.
I'll be keeping an eye on you.
After we change classes...
After graduation...
Just like a stalker.
You're such an irritating twerp!
I bet that's why you have no friends.
Oh, right. You have one.
Takasu Ryuji.
He looks all tough, but I can tell
he's head-over-heels for me.
Nasty!
But that means you'll be all alone now.
I sure feel sorry for you.
Even bighearted Yusaku can't stand you.
What did you say?
I told him all about what
happened at the restaurant.
He probably hates your guts now.
It's all over for you!
Kawashima?
Hey, move.
We're having Ryu-chan's pork cutlets!
Man...
Food tastes best when
it's fresh off the stove.
If you're so worried...
go and get her.
Aw, it's all blurry.
Taiga?
I'm coming in.
Oh.
You are here.
You didn't turn the lights on.
Hey, Tai—
Why are you here?
What kind of question is that?
Dinner's ready!
Ta-Taiga!
You okay?
She said...
that Kitamura-kun...
hates me now.
That wench told him everything...
I... I...
It'll be fine.
How will it be fine?
Kitamura knows everything.
Kawashima's true personality...
What really happened at the restaurant...
The fact that she was lying...
Everything.
Really?
Yep.
Besides...
Kitamura's not the kind of guy who'd
hate someone for such a silly reason.
You should be well aware of that.
Then, why am I so small?
Why do I have a weird name?
Um, uh, that's—
So what!?
So what if she's 165 centimeters tall!?
So what if her name sounds
like some blue sailor scout!?
So what if she's been friends
with Kitamura for years!?
Sorry.
You okay?
Still, I didn't realize you were so
concerned about that pointless—
I'm sensitive, unlike you!
Hey now...
Ryu-chan!
How can we have pork cutlets
without the sauce!?
Pork cutlets...?
- Gimme sauce! Ryu-chan!
- Berkshire pork.
Hey, what about pudding?
We're only buying sauce!
Notice: Kawashima Ami-chan will
be taking a break because of school.
Huh?
Hey, let's head back.
We're going to make Yasuko late.
Ryuji, look at this.
Notice: Kawashima Ami-chan will
be taking a break because of school.
What is this?
So she stopped working?
Is our school worth taking time off for?
Isn't that...?
It's that wench...
That's Kawashima Ami, right?
What's with the getup?
And those bags are stuffed with junk food.
Is she hosting a party or something?
No, she's not.
That's...
Heh. We got to see something interesting.
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
Ugh, what a pain.
If you keep following me around,
I'll kill you in a heartbeat.
From now on, you're "dumb Chihuahua!"