Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
Mommy! Mommy! I've been chosen!
I'm gonna be an elite pilot
that protects humanity!
I'm the world's greatest!
It's supposed to be secret!
But I'll share it just with you, Mommy!
Lots of people are gonna be nice to me!
So I won't be lonely!
So I'll be fine even without Daddy!
I won't be lonely at all!
So look! Look at me!
Did you hear me, Mommy?
Synchronization rate, zero.
No longer qualified as Second Children.
There's no reason for me
to be here anymore.
Nobody will look at me.
Not Mom, not Dad, not anybody.
There's no reason for me to go on living.
Asuka Langley Soryu?
Intelligence Section 2 reports that
the Second Children is now in custody.
I see.
It's not like them to not only lose her,
but then take seven days to find her.
I bet it was intentional.
You know, to mess with us in Operations
Maybe.
And Asuka's replacement,
the Fifth, will arrive today.
The timing is way too convenient.
Rei Ayanami...
So that feeling I had was true?
Her seeming maternal.
Rei Ayanami and Mom...
What are you using them for...
Father?
Commander Ikari.
My cat died. My grandmother
had been looking after it for me.
I hadn't given it
a second thought in ages.
But now, suddenly,
I'll never see it again.
Why did you destroy the Dummy System?
I didn't destroy the dummies.
It was Rei that I destroyed.
I'll ask you again. Why?
Because having you make love to me
doesn't make me happy anymore.
Why don't you have your way with
my body? Just like you did before!
I'm disappointed in you.
"Disappointed"?!
You never had any hopes
or expectations for me in the first place!
You wanted nothing from me!
Nothing! Not a thing!
What should I do, Mother?
Where did you go, Asuka?
But even if I saw her, what then?
Talk to her about Ayanami?
Tohji and Kensuke...
Everybody left to find somewhere else
to live after losing their homes here.
There's nobody... There's nobody
here that I can call a friend now.
Nobody.
I can't even go see Ayanami.
I don't have the courage.
I don't know how I should treat her.
Asuka, Ms. Misato, Mom... What should I...
What should I do?
Aren't songs great?
Songs enrich the heart.
They're the crowning achievement
of Lilin culture.
Don't you think so...
Shinji Ikari?
-You know my name?
-Everybody knows you.
No offense, but I think you should
be more aware of your importance.
I should?
Um, who are you?
I'm Kaworu. Kaworu Nagisa.
Like you, I'm a child whose path has
been set out. I'm the Fifth Children.
You're the Fifth Children, uh... Nagisa?
Call me Kaworu, Ikari.
Um, call me Shinji, then.
I'm told that the Fifth Children
just arrived.
Kaworu Nagisa. All background
information has been deleted.
Just like Rei.
What we do know is that his date of birth
is the day of the Second Impact.
This boy was directly sent by the Council.
I'm sure there's more to him.
The report from the Marduk Institute
regarding the Fifth is being withheld.
I was curious, so I did a little hacking
into Intelligence's files.
Hey, that's seriously dangerous!
It was worth it.
I found out where Ms. Ritsuko is.
What do we do about
the Fifth's synchro tests?
Let's play it straight
and see what he can do.
For today, anyway.
-Try lowering it another 0.3.
-Yes, sir.
You're certain that
these readings are correct?
All monitoring systems
are operating properly.
No sign of any data errors
on the part of the Magi.
To think that this boy can synchronize
with Unit 02 without replacing its core.
It's astonishing.
Sir, I just can't believe it!
I mean, it's fundamentally impossible
on a system level.
And yet it's a fact.
First you accept the facts,
then you try to explain them.
So you're the First Children?
Rei Ayanami.
You're just like me, I see.
Who are you?
I'm told that the Fifth
has made contact with Rei.
I see.
The Magi are going all-out,
sifting through his data.
In spite of that, his true nature
remains a mystery.
Who in the world is that boy?
NO UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
Shinji hasn't come home yet, either.
Some guardian I am.
The Central Dogma is currently closed.
Please use Route 3 for transit.
Hello. Were you waiting for me?
Uh, no. Not really. I wasn't trying to--
Have plans today?
Well, our regular testing is over.
So all that's left is to take a shower
and go home.
But to be honest, I don't really
want to go home these days.
Having a home,
a house to return to, leads to happiness.
-That's a good thing.
-It is?
I want to talk to you some more.
Mind if I go with you?
To the showers.
Isn't that where you were going?
-Uh, yeah.
-You don't want me to come?
It's just... Um, you can come if you want.
You certainly go to extremes
to avoid making first contact.
Are you afraid of intimacy with others?
If you avoid other people,
you'll never be betrayed.
You won't hurt each other, either.
But you'll also never stop feeling lonely.
Humans can't permanently
be free of loneliness.
Because man is ultimately alone.
But people can go on living
because they're able to forget.
Closing time.
Already?
Yeah. We'd better get to bed.
Together?
No! I think they've set up
an apartment for you, Kaworu.
A separate one.
Oh.
The human heart is in constant pain.
The heart is sensitive to pain,
so that makes living feel painful.
Hearts are as delicate as glass.
Especially yours.
-It is?
-Yes. You're worthy of my grace.
Your grace?
It means I like you.
Nerv, the organization founded
to be Seele's execution agency.
It was put in place
to carry out our scenario.
But the agency has become
the personal plaything of one man.
Indeed. We must reclaim it.
Before the promised day comes.
We must return Nerv
and the Eva Series to their original form.
Ikari, you will be held to account
for your breach of Seele's trust.
The time we were allotted is running out.
But the Spear of Longinus, which stood
in the way of our dream, is now gone.
The final Angel will soon appear.
Once it's destroyed,
that dream will be fulfilled.
It won't be long now, Yui.
Why am I here?
Why am I alive again?
For what?
For who?
The Fifth Children...
I sense that he's the same as me.
But why?
Good thing we're in the suburbs.
You didn't get caught in the blast.
But next time, we might be so lucky.
So the Horakis are gonna look after you
starting tomorrow, okay?
We're gonna have to say goodbye
for a while, Pen Pen.
I insist, let me sleep on the floor.
No, that's okay. I was the one
who asked if I could stay over.
I'm fine down here.
What do you want to talk about?
There's something that you want
to get off your chest, right?
I've been through so much
since I got here.
Before this, I was staying with a teacher.
Days there were quiet and uneventful.
All I did was take up space.
But that was fine with me.
There was nothing that I wanted to do.
You hate being around other people?
Not exactly.
I don't think I cared either way.
But I did hate my father.
Why am I talking to Kaworu
about this stuff?
You know, I might have been born
so that I could meet you.
So... Did you manage to get his files?
Here. I "borrowed" this from
Lt. Ibuki without her knowing.
I'm sorry, I keep asking you
to sneak around like a thief.
What the hell?
It's no surprise that Maya
can't show this to anyone!
It's theoretically impossible!
Yeah... The mysteries around this kid
just keep getting deeper.
He can set his synch rate
with an Eva to whatever he wants?
And do it at will?
I guess I have to resort to
extreme measures again...
I'm surprised to see you.
I need to ask you something.
Anything you say in here will be recorded.
I don't care.
That boy, the Fifth...
Who is he? What is he?
He's probably the final messenger.
Let's go. Come along, alter ego
of Adam and servant of the Lilin.
ALERT
Eva-02 has activated!
It's what?! Where's Asuka?!
In hospital room 303! I have confirmation!
-Then who's at the controls?!
-It's unmanned!
Unit 02 doesn't have
an entry plug inserted!
It's unmanned?
Then the Fifth isn't doing this?
A.T. Field generation detected
in the Central Dogma!
-Is it Unit 02?
-Negative! Pattern Blue!
-No doubt about it, it's an Angel!
-It's what?!
That boy... He's an Angel?
Target passing Level 4! Still descending!
It's no use!
Unable to cut power to the maglev!
Target passing Level 5!
All Central Dogma blast doors,
emergency lockdown!
Buy us some time. I don't care how much.
Emergency lockdown of all
Malebolge levels! All personnel, evacuate!
All personnel, evacuate!
I can't believe Seele would
send one directly at us...
The old men are trying to skip a step.
Using us to do it.
The final Angel has penetrated
the Central Dogma.
It is now descending.
Exactly as planned.
Ikari, you were a good friend
who shared our goal,
as well as a collaborator
of great insight.
This is your final task.
Let us hope Unit 01
will carry out the task.
Eva-02 is breaching the armored bulkheads!
Target has passed Cocytus No.2!
-Have Eva-01 pursue.
-Yes, sir!
Use any means necessary
to prevent the target
from entering the Terminal Dogma.
But why did the Angel take Unit 02?
Does it intend to merge
with Unit 02, perhaps?
Or to bring about our destruction.
It's a lie! A lie! A lie!
Kaworu's a... He's an Angel?!
That's not true!
Facts are facts. Just accept it.
You need to launch. Ready?
What's keeping you, Shinji?
Eva-01 descending Route 2!
In pursuit of target!
You betrayed me! You betrayed my feelings!
You betrayed me, just like Father!
Eva-01 has arrived at Level 4.
About to make contact with target.
There he is!
I've been waiting for you, Shinji.
Kaworu!
Asuka, I'm sorry!
The Eva Series...
Creatures born of Adam which are
abominations in the eyes of humanity.
The Lilin resort to using even
such things in order to survive.
This is most perplexing.
Kaworu! Stop it! Why are you doing this?!
The Evas and I are made of the same flesh.
We are both born of Adam, you see.
If it weren't for its soul,
I could merge with it.
Especially since Unit 02 here
is closing off its own soul right now.
An A.T. Field!
Oh, right. That's what you Lilin call it.
That sacred region which none may violate.
The light of the heart.
Deep down, you Lilin must know.
The A.T. Field is the inner wall
that we all possess.
How would I know that, Kaworu?!
-Both Evas have reached lowest level.
-Target will reach Terminal Dogma in 20.
If we lose Eva-01's signal
and detect another change...
I know, ma'am.
I'll trigger the self-destruct.
It's better than letting
the Third Impact happen.
I'm sorry.
I don't mind dying. Not if it's with you.
Thanks.
Humanity's fate...
Man's hope is lined with sorrow.
What was that?!
The most powerful A.T. Field
we've ever recorded!
Light, EM waves, and subatomic
particles are all being blocked!
-Unable to monitor situation!
-It's a damn containment field.
The target and Eva 01
and Eva 02 are off our scopes!
Unable to contact pilot!
Kaworu!
Come back!
Final safety device disengaged!
Heaven's Door is opening!
So an Angel finally made it.
Hyuga.
What's that?!
-Status?
-It's an A.T. Field!
A field of equal power is being generated
near the earlier Terminal Dogma field!
It's breaking through
the containment field!
What? A new Angel?
Unknown! Unable to verify!
Wait, it's gone!
It's gone? The Angel vanished?!
Adam, mother figure to my kind.
Must those born of Adam return to him?
Even if that means dooming humanity?
Wait, this isn't...
It's Lilith!
I see... So that's your plan, Lilin!
Thank you, Shinji.
I had hoped that you would
stop Unit 02 for me.
Otherwise, I may have been
able to live on alongside her.
Kaworu, why are you...
It's my fate. It dictates that I live on.
Even if mankind perishes as a result.
But I can die here if I want.
Life and death hold equal value to me.
Choosing to die is
the one absolute freedom.
What's that mean? Kaworu,
I don't understand what you're saying!
They're my last words.
Now, go ahead and destroy me.
If you don't,
you and your kind will disappear.
Only one lifeform can avoid extinction
and be granted a future.
And you aren't someone who ought to die.
Your kind needs a future.
Thank you.
I'm happy that I met you.
Kaworu said I was... worthy of his grace.
That he liked me.
That's the first time anybody's
ever said they liked me. Ever.
He was similar to me. And to Ayanami.
I really liked him.
If only one of us could survive,
it should have been him.
He was a way better person than I am.
Kaworu should have survived!
You're wrong. Only those with
the will to live get to survive.
He craved death.
He abandoned his will to live
and clung to a false hope.
You didn't do anything wrong, Shinji.
That's really cold, Ms. Misato.
TO BE CONTINUED
NEXT EPISODE
The final Angel has vanished.
But Shinji agonizes over it.
And Misato and Asuka bare their hearts.
While they seek salvation in others.
While they accept that this is
but one form of the end.
Next episode! "The Ending World"!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming