The blossoms scattered by the rain
signaled the end of the
short cherry blossom season...
How are you, Lilly?
This is Cabbage's apartment.
He's doing a wrestling tour,
so you can take it easy here
and think about what to do next.
What can I possibly do?
Prostitution is all I've ever done...
What can a useless woman like me...
...ever possibly do?!
That isn't like you, Lilly.
Don't talk like that.
You worked hard to make
it this far on your own.
Now you have our help too.
So don't give up.
Why do you and Noboru go
to such lengths for other people?
--It's what Anchan taught us.
--Anchan?
The one the MPs shot...
We're filled with his
teachings right in here!
We're indebted to you, too.
Where could Turtle be, anyway?
He said he was going
to drop by this morning...
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga, Chandy10
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
Man, I didn't know he
lived in a place like this...
"Marutaka Rice Shop"
He really kept it a secret...
Turtle!
Hey, Turtle! I know you're in there!
I'm coming in.
Hey...! Turtle!
--Noboru!
--Turtle!
What's the matter, Noboru?!
Say something!
Lilly! I'll take him to a hospital!
--Huh? A cold?
--Yes.
He had difficulty breathing
due to his high fever,
but the antipyretic I gave him
should help him feel better.
Just to be safe, we'll keep him
here a few days for observation.
That's all.
Is there something else?
Is it really just a cold?
What do you mean?
There wasn't anything
else wrong with him?
Sheesh! Don't worry us like that!
Sorry...
Something good to eat
would perk me back up!
Okay, then...
I'll peel an apple for you now.
You should be grateful.
Thanks a bunch.
Oh...
In that case, a small
clinic like this won't do.
You'll need to try a bigger hospital
to find out anything for sure.
--Yeah! It's good!
--Of course it is!
Say, Lilly...
Have you thought about
what you're gonna do next?
Brooding over it won't solve anything.
It isn't so bad when I think
of it as making a fresh start.
I managed to earn a living
all this time. All on my own, too.
So things will work out for me!
That secret stash of money
you kept from that military guy...
What were you planning to do with it?
I didn't have anything big in mind.
I just thought it'd be
nice to own a small shop...
My own castle where I can survive
without having to rely on men.
Just a meager little dream.
How much?
How much would it cost
to make your little dream come true?
Don't be silly! You shouldn’t
ask questions like that, kid!
--What's the matter, Mario?
--Huh?
You've been looking glum since we left...
Do you think it's really
just a cold Turtle has?
But that's what the doctor said...
What are you getting at, Mario?!
Is something wrong with Noboru?!
He's... an atomic bomb orphan...
You mean... he's having
aftereffects from the blast?!
I don't know, We need to get
him checked at a big hospital...
...but I don't have the money
or connections to take him to one.
Tell me, Lilly...
What can I possibly do now?
Mario...
I can't do anything for Turtle...
I'm pathetic...
No one cares about his
friends as much as he does.
Turtle is so nice because he bears a
more painful past than anyone else.
Mario was filled with frustration
that he could only stand transfixed
with fear of this invisible threat...
Good morning, Mr. Maeda!
It's time to check your temperature!
Lilly...!
What brings you over so early?
You want to take Noboru
to a big hospital, right?
Then come with me.
Why are we at an
American army base, Lilly?
I thought we were going to a hospital...
Mario.
America made the atomic bombs.
Well, yeah...
America also had the most advanced
medical expertise in the world.
There's no better place
to get Noboru's illness looked at.
"Cafe Milonga"
There's 100,000!
That's everything I have!
I offer it and myself as collateral!
Use me as you see fit! You don't
even have to pay me for my work!
Just, please! Lend me some money!
How much?
300,000...
I only lend up to 3000 yen
at a time. No exceptions.
Then, please allow me to use this
100,000 to start a business like yours!
Oh? You, a 1% lender?
If I lend 100,000 to start,
that's 1,000 yen a day in interest,
30,000 in a month.
A month later, that 130,000 yen
will become 169,000 yen.
You're free to choose
any line of work you want.
Then...!
I've no reason to stop you.
Do as you wish.
Thank you!
In exchange...
Come with me.
There's something I want you to learn.
Man, why are we at a public bath?
Quickly, now. No dawdling.
Surely there's nothing wrong
with scrubbing an old man's back?
So, can you talk to the
hospital to take a look?
Lilly. Who are these people?
They used to serve under my boyfriend.
Hey! You can do something, right?
Get outta my sight, geisha girl.
That old fart's no longer in Japan.
You're no longer the superior's girl.
Or, what? You'll play with
me like you did with the man?
Then why don't you join
me in my bed later tonight?
--The hell I will!
--Lilly
Let go! These guys have to pay!
It's useless. There's no
point trying to talk to them.
Let's go, Lilly.
Let go, Mario! Let go!
We can figure out another way, Lilly.
Hey. Wait a minute.
You're Mario Minakami, right?
How do you know my name?
You don't remember me?
See if this will shake up your memory!
You're... from that...
Now you remember me?
Yeah, I'm the Jeffrey you knocked out.
Oh, you're...!
That left...
Man, that really worked me out...
Anyway, about that doctor...
I can pull some strings.
What?! Really?!
He says he'll ask them
to take a look at Noboru!
Seriously?!
--We appreciate it!
--Thank you so much!
But... there's one condition.
Mario. I wanna box
with you one more time.
Lilly...
He just said he wants
to box with me, didn't he?
Yes... That's his one condition...
All right. But it has to be right now.
Mario... Are you...?
Mario! That's enough!
Wow, that Jap's got some moves.
Oh, please! Stop them!
Ma'am?
Stop!
Stop, Jeffrey. It's over.
But, Sarge! It's not over yet!
No, it's over.
The girl told me everything.
Jeffrey, do you really
want to beat up a cripple?
Sir, what are you saying?! He's a
good boxer! He knocked me out!
The hospital will take a look
at him tomorrow afternoon.
--Really?!
--Yes.
That's great! They're going
to take a look at Noboru tomorrow!
Really?!
We need to tell him!
Thank you.
We're in your debt.
Thank you, Jeffrey...
No problem.
So that somebody is worth that much?
Someone who is so precious
that you would box with that fist?
Thank you, Jeffrey...
As the saying goes...
Borrow with a smile, repay with a scowl.
People are quick to offer
gratitude when borrowing money,
but glare at you like the devil
as soon as they have to pay it back.
Would you scrub my back?
I was given those scars
shortly after I became a moneylender.
And this one...
...and these ones...
All the other scars during my
ten years as a moneylender
were given to me by people
who borrowed money from me.
If you lend to the wrong person,
you'll lose not only your precious
100,000, but your life as well.
Will you still be a 1% lender anyway?
Yes!
With his scars, Mr. Sugi showed
Turtle the viciousness of his profession
and that there are beats in the
world that repay kindness with hate.
Being a 1% moneylender is
not for regular, honest people.
In his heart, Turtle felt
that there was no better job
for someone as risk-taking as him.
How many decorations would be
carved into his own minuscule body?
You said earlier that you
offer yourself as collateral.
Were you serious when you said that?
I was!
Then I do have one request for you...
I'd like you to get the person living
here to repay the money he owes...
Money?
If you can do it, I'll agree to
your 300,000 yen proposition.
Really?!
But, if you're not careful, you could
end up with the same scars as mine...
Will you still do it anyway?
Mr. Sugi!
Have 300,000 yen ready when I get back!
Let me ask one thing...
What do you need so much money for?
Women? Your family?
Yeah, you got it.
Yes! It's for my family!
He ran off?!
He was long gone when we
checked him this morning.
What does Noboru think
he's doing in his condition?!
That idiot...!
Let's search for him, Mario!
Mr. Igarashi! Are you home, Mr. Igarashi?!
What's all the noise! Try selling
me anything and you'll get hurt!
Who're you?
I'm a messenger for Mr. Sugi.
Sugi?
Oh, that old geezer moneylender?
--C'mon! Hurry it up!
--Yeah
Lilly... This isn't for just you...
It's also my chance
to take a step forward...!
"Standing around won't solve anything.
You gotta use your body
and mind to move forward.
There's no point in being
born if you can never be happy!"
Anchan's teachings
pushed Turtle forward...
same ta manazashi
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it; its now
a far off distance
Feelings intersect.
Turtle's kindness leads
Lilly to prepare herself...