Meet Mitsuki Koyama, 12 years old.
Her dream is to become a singer.
But, poor thing,
she only has one year to live.
We're a couple
of Death Spirits and
we were sent to make sure
her destiny doesn't change.
But somehow we ended up turning her
into a sixteen-year-old
and we helped her win
a singing audition!
Do you think that counts
as changing her destiny?
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
U-Umm... I'm home.
What's with her?
That was really unfriendly!
Okay, tomorrow I'll make a lot of sweets.
Which do you like,
bean jam or soy flour?
Oh, or...
I'm home.
Umm... Mitsuki just got home.
Here, I'll put her on the phone!
Hello?
You're finally there.
I was wondering how long
I'd have to talk to Ms. Tanaka.
Dr. Wakaoji?!
What happened?
Why are you calling me?
Actually, it seems they've decided
who will be your manager.
What?
Manager?
You're too loud!
She's pricked up her ears.
Why at your place?
Well I'm tentatively
your guardian, aren't I?
I was contacted not long ago.
The manager said she's going to come
and meet with you and me.
Mitsuki, can you come to
the hospital now?
Yes!
I'll be right there!
Along Came the Manager
Dr. Wakaoji is coming for
a house call tomorrow, isn't he?
Yes, that's true.
But he wants me to come
to the hospital right away.
Umm... I have some shopping to do,
so shall I take Mitsuki to the hospital?
Yes, please do.
Stop it, Meroko!
Not yet!
Mitsuki is still changing!
It's all right now!
Well, it doesn't really matter
what you change into.
You can't meet your manager
looking like that, anyway!
Oh, that's right!
So, when we get to the hospital,
make me sixteen, Takuto.
What?
Wait a minute.
That's okay for the manager.
But as for her guardian,
she'll have to meet the manager
with him, won't she?
Isn't that right?
What will the doctor think
when he sees her
after her transformation
into a 16-year-old?
What are you doing?
What do you mean? Umm...
Times like this call for
the Death Spirit Handbook.
Just as I thought.
We'll tell them everything!
These are the Death Spirits,
Takuto and Meroko!
Takuto transformed my 12-year-old body
into a 16-year-old's body.
And at that time,
my throat got healed, and now
I can sing to my heart's content!
Well, well, is that what's going on?!
I have no problem
with that either!
Yeah!
- Don't say, "Yeah"!
If you could get away with that
then there wouldn't be any hassle!
C'mon! Hmm... Umm...
Meroko, can't that handbook
be more helpful?
All right! I get it!
Soon I'll show my true power.
Oh, okay. Show me.
What kind of ideas do you have?
Th-That's...
To the manager...
Say, "I'm Mikatsuki, her little sister"
or something to fool him!
Won't that Wakaoji guy think it's strange?
T-That's why!
Mikatsuki is gonna be
the stage name for her modeling work.
That's it! Let's do that!
Well, let's try that.
Yeah.
- You have to do your best!
Okay!
This is the place.
Yeah.
Shall I go with you?
If she does that
it'll really be a pain—
A pain?
What will be a pain?
It would be such a pain
for you to do that.
Please go ahead and go shopping.
Well, I'll come back to pick you up,
so please wait in the lobby.
Okay!
Meroko...
Oh, that was bad...
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
It was my fault for speaking so loudly
when I was in that form.
Do everything just
the way we said, okay?
Okay.
Is that so?
She's here?
Excuse me...
We were waiting for you.
This is your manager, Ms. Oshige.
Say hello.
It's nice to meet you,
I'm Oshige from Village Pro.
She's a woman.
And this is...
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Mitsuki Koyama!
Huh?
Fool, what are you saying?
You have to do it exactly
as we discussed it!
Oh! No I'm not,
I'm her younger sister Mikatsuki.
Younger sister?
Oh, well...
That's it!
Mitsuki! Take Dr. Wakaoji outside!
First you have to talk to him!
Y-Yeah.
Doctor, could I have a minute?
That's right.
So Mikatsuki is your stage name.
Yes, that's right, that's right!
Well, what about being
the "younger sister"?
What?
Well that's...umm...
because you'll be introduced
on the premise that
you're the younger sister of
another talent at the agency.
Hm? Is that right?
No, that's not it, but say it is!
Oh, okay!
It seems I'll be introduced as
the younger sister
of another talent at the agency.
Oh, I see!
But...
Is there something else?
Well, that's okay.
Hang in there, Mitsuki.
For things to work out well,
the first impression is always important.
The manager will take care
of you from now on,
so go and greet her properly.
Shall we return?
I'm sorry.
I hadn't listened closely to
what she had to say before.
Oh, don't worry about it.
To start over, this is Mikatsuki.
The younger sister.
A pleasure to meet you.
A pleasure.
Well then...
So, where is she?
Where is "she"?
Umm... Well...
That's it! School!
Tell her, "She's at school"!
Is this gonna be okay?
It's okay!
At school.
Oh, at school.
Yes, she's going to school
just like she should.
See! Both of them
are satisfied with it!
Well, certainly.
Well, what shall we do?
Shall we wait?
Who should we wait for?
Say she'll be here soon!
Umm... She'll be here soon!
Okay.
Well, her guardian Dr. Wakaoji is here
so I'll roughly explain what's going on.
- Oh, yes...
- Dangerous, dangerous...
I wonder if it's okay like this.
Ms. Oshige, I'd like to
ask you something.
What would that be?
From now on she'll be busy...
You're worried about
the priority of her education.
Yes, there's that, too.
And your throat.
That is no problem.
We have many kids
who are her age.
Essentially, we only have them work
after school or on Saturdays.
I'm relieved to hear that.
For the moment,
her debut will be the biggest event.
She was chosen at a massive audition
and she's a newcomer, so we want her
to debut as soon as possible.
We're working on it now.
And to achieve that,
there will of course be voice training
and dance lessons,
she'll receive basic training like that.
What?
Wait a minute!
Voice training and other stuff,
it's like she's becoming
a singer or something?!
Things are getting hairy!
Doctor, that's...
Yes?
What are we going to do?
Umm... Umm...
Not this.
Hello...
What's calling going to do?!
Telephone?
Oh, could you call her?
Yes! Do that,
and we'll go away temporarily!
H-Hey!
Just now...
A belly roll?
Somehow I don't know
what's going on anymore.
You are so slow.
It's simple, isn't it?
Ms. Oshige is the manager and
she thinks that Mitsuki
is her little sister Mikatsuki.
Dr. Wakaoji thinks that Mitsuki
will make her debut
with the stage name Mikatsuki.
It's going well so far.
But if Dr. Wakaoji finds out
that I'm going to be a singer...
Then everything will get
all messed up.
We have to do something
about that.
Just like we thought,
I should tell Dr. Wakaoji the truth...
There's no reason for him to suddenly
believe something ridiculous like that.
Right!
You're the only human who can
see Meroko and me, right?
That's right.
How is he going to believe
that we're Death Spirits?
But that's the only way...
Oh, what shall we do with you?
Mero-Mero Change!
How about it?
There are two of me.
Meroko, you...
I'll just have to
do something about it.
As the leader
of Green Onion Ramen,
the Death Spirits who can
quiet even crying children.
I can handle it!
Doctor...
Mitsuki.
I was worried.
Where did you go?
Sorry, I don't feel so good.
Then shouldn't you
lie down for a little bit?
No! I'm just fine now!
Really?
Then I guess it's all right.
Her voice is a little different.
Oh, no.
And her personality
is different too.
Oh no,
it's just your imagination.
By the way, Mitsuki.
Yes?
Something Ms. Oshige
said is not quite clear.
What is it?
From the story I heard,
I can only think that you passed
an audition to be a singer.
That's...
That's it, a commercial!
She's talking about a commercial!
Oh, really?
Yep.
In it, I play the part of a girl
making her debut as a singer.
Well, let's get back quickly
to Ms. Oshige,
since we're in the middle of
talking and everything.
Oh, I see.
Well done.
Thinking of things
one after another.
Somehow I feel like things
are gonna start coming apart.
The doctor is satisfied with it.
What in that look on his face
says he's satisfied?
Well, then I have another good
move up my sleeve.
Oh?! Dr. Wakaoji, over there!
Huh, what?
You have an urgent patient, hurry!
An urgent patient, hey!
Huh?
H-Hey! Hey!
While the doctor is gone,
I'll use this chance to...
Mero-Mero Change!
How do I look?
Meroko, again?
Anyways, I'll go ahead and
take care of that manager.
I mean, I will see to
the manager.
Don't talk like that now.
Well, if we're going to do anything
that would be the quickest...
I wonder if this is really okay...
Huh?
Umm... Do I look strange to you?
N-No. The girl is...
Oh, it seems that she's
not feeling very well.
Huh?
However, right now
she's resting, so it's okay.
Oh, I see.
Your language is strange again!
I know!
But more importantly,
I've decided!
I trust you, Ms. Oshige,
and I'm going to leave everything
about Mitsuki up to you!
I feel the same.
How are we going to explain this
to that doctor?
That's...
Oh!
Yes, this is Wakaoji!
Yes...
Yes, yes...
I understand!
Ms. Oshige, there's someone to
see you in the parking lot.
To see me?
I wonder who...
Hey!
Again?
This way, the whole mess will be settled.
I'm so tired.
Just as I thought.
It's not good to leave this thing
just to Meroko and Takuto,
I'll come clean with
what's really going on!
Oh, Mitsuki!
That urgent patient call
was absolute nonsense.
D-Dr. Wakaoji...
Now what?
A fire or something?
Or there's a wolf around here?
That's not it!
Umm... It wasn't a wolf but...
Umm...green onion ramen...
Just as I thought,
shouldn't you lie down?
Death Spirits
called Green Onion Ramen...
What are you two doing there?
Well, come on in.
All we can do is
leave this up to Meroko.
Doctor Wakaoji...
Yes...
Mitsuki is awesome...
Umm... Extremely?
Anyway... She's a good girl and I think
she is quite the talent!
Oh, really?
Please! Trust me and
leave Mitsuki in my care!
Y-Yes.
Oh, progress...
There was no guest
there to meet me!
What do you mean a guest?
Well, you said it earlier,
Dr. Wakaoji.
I did?
Well anyway!
From now on please take good care
of Mitsuki Koyama!
The same goes for me.
And the same for me.
Yes!
Well I really want Mitsuki
to do her very best.
As your doctor,
all I can do is give you medical advice.
But above all,
I intend to be there for you
like a surrogate father.
Doctor...
Work hard.
Dr. Wakaoji!
Mitsuki! Come here...
Are you okay, Meroko?
It's all because
this is the first time
she's made this many
transformations in one day!
I think she's reached her limit.
I'm still fine.
Who should I
transform into next?!
I think Takuto would be good.
Umm... Dr. Wakaoji?
Yes?
I'm sorry if I'm mistaken,
but didn't you play keyboard
for "Route L"?
Yes, well...
I thought it was you.
I was a big fan.
I see...
I was a really big fan.
One time we passed each other
in some studio.
Of course at the time,
I wasn't behind the scenes,
but an idol.
But then I got nowhere.
That's right!
Would you mind signing
something for me?
Oh! Does Mitsuki have a cell phone?
Oh, Mikatsuki.
Y-Yes?
Is Mitsuki still at school?
What? Yes...
Actually, I was supposed to
give her a cell phone today.
If she doesn't have this,
we can't contact her, right?
Yeah...
That's right...
Well...I'll go to the school
and give it to her.
Oh, just in time.
Well, goodbye.
What are you going to do?
Even if she goes to school,
Mitsuki's not going to be there.
Takuto, please, make me sixteen.
I want to speak to her myself, properly.
That's what you have to do.
Now I can greet Ms. Oshige properly
as 16-year-old Mitsuki Koyama!
Ms. Oshige?!
Mitsuki?
Yes! I'm sorry I'm late.
I heard from my sister that
you would be here, Ms. Oshige.
Yes, I'm glad we could meet.
Yes!
A pleasure to meet you...
I'm Mitsuki Koyama
A pleasure to meet you too,
I'm Masami Oshige from Village Pro.
You're going to get really busy
from here on. Are you prepared?
Hm?
I mean, you're a newcomer.
I'll guide you
from the very first step.
I'm depending on you!
Okay. Anyway, let's work hard!
Yes!
Eichi! I have a manager!
It's finally starting!
I'm going to be a singer!
Well, the day has finally come for
Mitsuki to make her debut as a singer.
The producer is Kohei Takasu
He's really famous.
Wow, that's impressive.
But she doesn't like the song
that he got for her
and has decided that she wants
to write all the lyrics herself.
But what does Mitsuki know
about songwriting?
Don't worry.
As long as she's with me,
everything will be OK.
But you gotta use your soul
to write songs...your soul!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Thoughts on a Song"
- Look forward to it!