[heavy metal music playing]
THE SWALLOW GAZES INTO THE ABYSS
[gods cheering]
[intense rock music playing]
[Heimdall] Ouch! It's happened.
First blood has been drawn.
Poseidon has wounded
Kojiro with his trident!
[breathing heavily]
The biggest loser in history
is living up to his namesake.
The big fish has been reduced to a small
fry before the frosty tyrant of the ocean.
[exhales deeply]
[chuckling]
[Kojiro] You gotta be kidding me.
I knew this fight would be a tough battle,
but I didn't think
I'd get hurt this quickly.
Such ferocity.
So this is the power of the gods.
[chuckling]
[male god 1] Hell yeah!
That's why they call him the god of gods!
[male god 2] GOG!
[all] The dreamiest god ever!
[male god 3] No matter how hard they
train, they'll never be a match against--
[male god 4] You're the king, Poseidon!
[gods cheering]
The almighties are getting loud!
Their encouragement
vibrates through the arena!
[gods continue cheering]
- [music stops]
- [cheering stops]
[male god 5] You idiot,
you took it too far.
[male god 6] Don't look him in the eye.
He'll skewer you!
His aura is so intimidating!
I'm shaking in my boots right now.
[shuddering]
Huh. Bunch of shitstains.
My, aren't you a feisty one.
Your comrades are cheering for you.
At least show some gratitude.
I don't see a point in that.
Huh?
A god needs no armies,
nor to resort to betrayal,
for a god is complete.
That's how it has always been.
We have embodied perfection
since the beginning of time.
Why show thanks for the irrelevant?
Huh?
Hmm.
Is that how you operate?
How peculiar.
Huh.
Don't mean to be rude,
but it seems pretty depressing.
[gasping]
[straining]
Away with you.
[straining] Hya!
[yelling]
- Huh?
- Chione Tyro Demeter!
CHIONE TYRO DEMETER
Whoa, he's bearing down
like lightning from the sky!
There's no doubt he'll stop at nothing
to deliver the killing blow!
What a mesmerizing display of his agility.
His speed is a genuine wonder to behold.
As impressive as his pace is,
the human can still dodge his attacks.
The sole reason
he evaded anything thus far
is because Poseidon's only used
an inkling of his total strength.
When it comes to
the full depths of his prowess,
not even the gods can fathom such a force.
For that matter, neither can a human.
Hey, gramps, come on,
don't lose out on us!
Because you have to win
this battle for Hrist, okay?
[narrator] With each assault,
his game sense evolves.
[Kojiro] I know this.
This too.
I read these moves just a few seconds ago.
[narrator] The technique...
Senju Musou!
It's that same strategy.
He's predicting Poseidon's moves
at every opportunity.
This is crossing the line.
It's almost like
he can infiltrate the mind.
I'm curious, how deeply can he penetrate?
Fascinating creature.
[narrator] Kojiro's swordsmanship
was supernatural.
[blade ringing]
Crossing the threshold...
into the realm of the gods.
[Kojiro] Where's he going next?
Over there.
[narrator] However,
there was one obstacle...
[gasping]
his opponent was Poseidon.
[Kojiro grunting]
Eesh.
A fake-out.
He ambushed me from my blind spot.
The more I try to chase after him,
the farther I get pushed away
at the last second.
Into... the water.
Damn.
I'm drowning.
Still...
I refuse to go under!
There he is.
- [Poseidon] Hm.
-[Kojiro] Oh yeah?
I've got you!
- Huh?
- He switched!
I see what he's doing.
[Kojiro] Ganryu Hiou...
Torakiri!
[grunting]
[shattering]
Let's not get carried away.
Little fish.
What did you do to Hrist, you monster?
[Heimdall] A sudden
critical turn of events.
Kojiro's trusty Bizen Nagamitsu
has been shattered to pieces!
[gods cheering]
Ah...
- The old man's done.
- Hm.
[whimpering]
[narrator] The match was over.
The crowd went silent.
With the divine weapon rendered unusable,
Kojiro's loss was practically ensured.
Fine.
I surrender.
Damn.
If only I could say that now.
But it's too bad.
I'm not giving up today.
This reminds me of old times.
Don't you agree, Musashi?
[Brünnhilde] April 13th, 1612.
Funashima Island.
In a part of Nagato,
later called Ganryujima,
it was 9:00 a.m.
This was the site of Kojiro's duel
with Musashi.
At least, according to the Nitenki,
the last remaining record
of the events which happened that day.
Musashi was late to the engagement.
He watched Kojiro throw his scabbard
into the sea in frustration.
To which he then said...
[Musashi] Don't you realize
you've already lost, you fool?
A champion would never
cast away his sheath so carelessly.
[Brünnhilde] So the legend
apparently goes.
However, the Nitenki was written more than
150 years after the duel took place,
rendering the account
no more than hearsay.
As for the truth...
[breathing heavily]
[growling]
[Kojiro] This man is unbelievably strong.
I'd expect nothing less
from such a warrior.
I cannot best him in my current state.
If I continue to fight...
I shall be overtaken at once.
I surrender.
[scoffing] At least, that's what
I wish I could say right now.
But I'm ready to give it my all.
I'm having way too much fun here.
'Cause if I didn't take this chance,
I'd miss out on future prospects!
Is this a game...
or a business deal?
You speak strangely.
Yet I sense the words
of a swordsman prepared to die.
Then come, Sasaki.
Let us bludgeon each other
to our heart's content!
I'd be honored!
[Brünnhilde] And so they fought,
the exchange of blows that followed barely
lasted more than a few meager minutes.
[blades ringing]
Yet, it was significant.
A passionate moment between two souls.
TSUBAME GAESHI
One loved the blade, and exalted
the whole of creation as his teacher.
While the other walked a lonely road,
aiming to become
the Number One Under the Sun.
[Kojiro] Ha! So much fun!
It's the thrill of a lifetime!
Who would have thought
that I'd ever face a blademaster like him!
[both yelling]
[uplifting music playing]
[Kojiro] Ah... So this is it, huh?
It's a shame...
I never wanted this struggle to end.
[Brünnhilde] For both of them, it was
the happiest moment of their entire lives.
A gift. The most meaningful
connection they would ever make.
[Kojiro] What a fight. Right, Musashi?
Huh.
Hey, listen up, you ocean tyrant.
You mind if I ask you something?
Tell me...
have you ever lost yourself
to the swing of the blade at night,
training until the sunrise?
Or burst into tears of solemn gratitude,
for someone who made you stronger
than you were before?
In the heat of battle,
have you admired your foe so much,
you'd die for them?
Hmm.
You know what?
No.
My apologies.
You haven't gone through any of that.
Look at this blade.
See how it shines?
It stands for countless hopes and dreams
of all the fools who wield it.
All the time that you've been alive,
I bet you've never stood
for a single thing.
How unjust.
I won't lose
to a selfish bastard like you!
Ah!
Wait, what's happening?
The broken shards of Kojiro's weapon
are glowing brightly in his hands!
Ah, it's so shiny!
[grunting] But how is he...?
I can't believe it.
What, Papa?
He's... He's doing it.
Incredible.
[gulping]
[shrieking] Sasaki!
[yelling]
[gasping]
[both Hrists] Hey, Re-Völundr!
RE-VÖLUNDR
NI
TEN
GAN
RYU
NITEN GANRYU
KOJIRO SASAKI
Incredible! The blade fragments
have become two separate swords!
[crowd gasping]
Hm. Here we go.
Thank goodness,
sister Hrist is still alive.
It's a miracle.
I seriously thought
she was a goner back there.
What a relief.
But how? The weapon
was restored even after it broke.
[Brünnhilde] That's Hrist for you.
It's the power bestowed unto her name,
which has two meanings, remember?
"The trembling one."
And "The thundering one."
As the only Valkyrie
with dual personalities,
our sister is unequalled.
[chuckling]
Wow, you totally saw
this coming, didn't you?
That must have been
why you paired her with Kojiro
when you were planning everything out!
- Luck. Yes! [laughing maniacally]
- [screaming]
[Göll] What does luck
have to do with anything?
Are you saying
this whole thing was a fluke?
Hope they're ready!
[Göll] Where did that come from?
- Let's go.
- Go where?
Go, Kojiro Sasaki! Ha! I choose you!
Uh...
[Kojiro chuckling]
Sorry, our quarrel's not over.
How about we put our hearts into this?
Show me what you're made of.
You lowly worm.
[both inhaling deeply]
Huh?
[clanging]
[Iori] Papa?
It's only Kojiro, but still,
he looked just like Papa for some reason.
Why though? Those are your movements
he's using out there, aren't they?
So how does he know them?
- Ha! Isn't it obvious?
- Huh?
He must have
kept fighting me in the afterlife,
at least a few thousand times.
No, tens of thousands of times.
Challenging me again and again
till he got his fill.
Burning everything he learned
into his body.
Wait, I don't get it.
Even if he's trained himself
to imitate your attacks properly,
is that gonna give him enough
of an advantage to defeat the gods?
He's doing much more
than swinging a couple of weapons.
- Pay attention, Iori.
- Huh?
Master Toda's kodachi.
Shinkage Yagyu footwork,
flowing fluidly as water.
The brute force of Itto-ryu!
Take it in, the dynamic style of
Sword Saint Nobutsuna Kamiizumi!
Ahh!
Golly, I love it.
- He drew blood?
- You're kidding me!
Scary, owie!
[blade ringing]
[rumbling]
[Musashi] There it is!
It's my Niten Ichi-ryu!
He isn't knocking us off, son.
It is the essence
of our legacies that live on within him.
After years of discipline,
generations of master swordsmen now
bear witness as he pierces the heavens.
The Niten Ganryu of Kojiro Sasaki!
The true Number One Under the Sun.
Oh dear, I've never
seen anything like this.
Master Poseidon, that's right,
the fearsome frosty tyrant
of the ocean himself,
is bleeding like a raw steak!
- [male god 7] No way!
- [male god 8] Poseidon is defeatable?
[male god 9] He's mortal.
[narrator] With every attempt mankind
had made to challenge the gods,
their hopes were dashed.
[man 1] You've got this, Kojiro Sasaki!
- [man 2] We're counting on you!
- [man 3] Our future is in your hands!
[woman 1] You can do it!
[narrator] Will humanity
succeed this time...
and slay god?
[Japanese pop ballad playing]