The girl is only one in the world.
That made her the God of this world.
She found herself on an island when she began to understand things around her.
There was nobody else around.
She had nothing to do.
That was the everything the world offered.
A
The furigana next to it says "Ouse," which means "Date."
Good afternoon, Chihiro.
Ah, Renji-kun.
How far have you gotten?
I haven't made much progress on it.
About 30 percent of the whole thing.
I can't do it alone after all.
May I take a look?
"One day, the girl tried to light a fire on the beach."
"Because there was an episode in a book about a person who lit a signal fire after being stranded on an island."
"A white line rose up to the deep, blue sky."
"She thought, 'What's this thing that's just like a cloud?' and she put her face near it."
"Her eyes and throat hurt badly."
"She backed off in confusion and gazed at it from a distance."
"She understood that it was useless."
"Likewise, she began to understand one thing after another."
"She understood what 'understanding' meant."
I see.
How is it?
Yeah, this girl is cute.
Cute... eh?
Should I rewrite it after all?
Which part?
Everything up till now.
Wait a minute. Why?
Because you said she was cute.
I don't think she should be described that way.
It's okay. A small episode like this is interesting.
That's wrong, Renji-kun.
This girl should be more abnormal.
Abnormal?
Because the girl is taking things that seem to be a joke seriously,
the reader should get a sense of uneasiness and discomfort.
If she's thought to be cute, it means the girl isn't described properly.
Hoh...
My, an obento?
Chihiro-chan's share too?
It doesn't matter, does it?
As a housewife, it helps me that you're good at cooking, but as a mom, my feelings are more complicated.
Why?
Because if you're better than the girl you're dating, you won't be able to receive a love obento from her, will you?
She's not my girlfriend.
You and Chihiro-chan aren't lovers?
We're not.
Geez, you're so timid.
Do I have to be your lover after all?
Th-That's dangerous. That's dangerous, I said.
A
The furigana next to it says "Fuan," which means "Anxiety."
What's the matter?
N-Nah. I was thinking about my career interests.
Career interests?
A survey of what we want to do in the future.
Really?
I received a career interest survey at school.
What's the matter?
Nah, nothing.
What should I do?
I think you should just do what you want to do.
I wouldn't be stressed if I knew what that was.
You don't have any idea at all?
I don't have any special talents.
Your cooking is good.
I'll give it some more thought.
A
The furigana next to it says "Fuman," which means "Discontent."
Morning.
Hm, good, good.
You're keeping it up.
You mean with the obento?
Yeah. Or should I say with Chihiro-chan?
Well, you could say so.
It's helpful of you to save me the trouble of making breakfast.
Hey, you two still aren't lovers yet?
We're not.
Really?
What?
I just thought that your response hadn't really changed somehow.
I say...
Say, this is just "if."
If Chihiro became my girlfriend, would you be happy?
Hm? If you're happy.
Do you enjoy being with Chihiro-chan?
Th-That...
There's no need to get mad.
I'm not mad.
You're a guy, so you should go out with her with a sense of responsibility.
Responsibility?
Passion is like a downhill slope.
Once you take heart from it, it's unstoppable.
However, love is like an uphill slope.
You have to carry the pains and difficulties while climbing it.
Ah, but the ones who go through difficulties are just couples, while the unstoppable ones are lovers.
Love and passion are exact opposites.
A
TL Note: Toufu 【豆腐, bean curd】 literally means beans that have gone bad, while Nattou 【納豆, fermented soybeans】 literally means bad beans.
It's something like the inversion of the spelling of "Toufu" and "Nattou."
Yes, yes.
A
The furigana there says "Giman," which means "Deception."
Most of the lines in this part of the story can be found in the opening animation.
"She painted a human being."
"She painted a boy."
"So, she decided to add a figure of a boy into paintings of landscapes she had painted."
"She put up those paintings in the same places where she painted them."
"There was not a single place on the island she did not paint."
"The girl was with the boy everywhere."
"It meant that the girl and the boy looked at each other every time she looked at the paintings."
"But the girl had no feeling of achievement."
"Would it be a 'human'?" she thought.
"No. This was the 'painting of a human being.'"
"He did not move. He did not think. He was simply there."
"Lonely?"
"Finally, she could ask herself by finding the word. She was not lonely."
How is it?
I think it's good.
With this, you've made it to about 70 percent, right?
Probably. Isn't it almost over?
Have you decided on the ending?
What should I do?
Wait.
We've come up with two ideas so far.
First, the girl enters the world of the paintings
and leaves behind the paintings of the boy and the girl living a peaceful life.
It's a fantasy-type ending.
Second, the boy appears in her reality.
Even though we haven't decided on the ending yet, it should be a happy ending.
Well, the first idea can turn into a happy ending or a sad ending, depending on your interpretation.
Really?
What's the matter?
Ah, nothing.
You can write the story of her entering the paintings as a fantasy,
but you can also think of it as her escaping from reality in order to run away from loneliness.
You can also think of the girl escaping from reality in order to run away from loneliness.
In other words, she breaks down?
In other words, she breaks down.
Yeah. It depends on the way you put it, but yeah.
I see.
Is this what you've been worrying about this time?
Yes. I think she'll break down.
The girl shouldn't know about loneliness.
I see.
But, if we decide to end the story like this, there's something I don't like about it.
Really?
Doesn't it feel like God is playing with her?
If I try, I can do it after all.
I was surprised myself.
Before I realized it, the story had already gotten much longer. It's fun.
It's all thanks to you.
I didn't do anything.
I feel depressed that I wasn't able to do anything.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Erm, Renji-kun.
What is it?
Nah, it's nothing.
Erm, thank you very much.
Ah, yeah. You're welcome.
Erm...
What is it?
Renji-kun, do you want to... kiss me?
Do you want to kiss me?
You can go ahead.
I don't think I would say that to just anyone.
And it doesn't seem there was anyone else I've been this close to before.
I think I've continued to meet you till now because I trust you.
Besides, it seems you like me too.
That's why you can kiss me as a lover.
I think this is the scene where we should kiss.
Why?
Why am I hesitating?
I... Chihiro...
If she's thought to be cute, it means the girl isn't described properly.
This girl should be more abnormal.
That's not true.
That's not true. It's not like that.
Something is wrong.
But how come Chihiro doesn't look happy?
How come she's not shy about it?
How come her expression doesn't change?
How come she hasn't said a single word about liking me?
How come?
That's because God is playing with you.
It's not like that.
I'm sorry. I...
It's not like that!
It's not your fault.
Wait, Chihiro!
Please don't write down what happened just now in your diary.
Please don't write it down... no matter what...
Everything... was wrong.
The girl is only one in the world.
That made her the God of this world.
Found it.
I found it.
I thought I didn't need it.
I thought I wouldn't be able to get hold of it.
I gave up. But we met.
That's my whereabouts.
Ah, I wonder if this is a bit too daring.
It might be too stimulating for Hirono-kun.
I'm leaving.
Just kidding.
Papa. Mama.
Ah, the preparations for tomorrow.
This will work.
This is a place where sound has vanished.
One day, Mom vanished from Dad's heart, and Dad also vanished from Mom's heart.
Ah, Mama?
Ah?
What's wrong, Ma...
After that, sound vanished from this house.
After that, conversation vanished.
All color vanished from my world.
Before I knew it, even I vanished from their hearts.
Ever since then,
I've been living in a world with nothing.
At last, I've found a world with sound.
I've found a home with color.
I don't need to shut myself in anymore.
I can't answer your call right now.
Please say your name and what I can do for you after the "beep."
Yahoo! Hirono-kun, this is Miyako.
Have you woken up yet?
I'm about to leave home. I'll get to our meeting place at noon, so don't be late.
Bye then.
Oh, what a heroic battle royal.
The rule of wild nature is harsh.
Oh, it's time.
Yahoo! Hirono-kun, I'm already here. Are you on your way?
I won't forgive you if you're late.
Hey, you're late.
You should arrive ten minutes early when you go on a date.
It's a guy's obligation not to make the girl wait.
You're late. You're late, late, late!
How long are you going to make me wait?
As punishment, everything is your treat today.
Okay. Hurry up and run here.
What's wrong? Don't tell me you're sleeping?
If you overslept, I won't just let it go.
Hi-ro-no-kun! This is Miyako.
You're still not coming? I'm waiting!
Geez, what are you thinking?
How many hours do you want me to wait?
Are you really planning on coming?
I will wipe you out from Onii-chan's heart.
He will then say farewell to you.
And then, it will be over.
I will end this.
I'm going to disappear again?
Hello, Hirono-kun?
Have you possibly mistaken our meeting place?
It's the bench in front of the fountain. You should know, right?
If you're lost, call me. I'll come and pick you up.
This is Miyako. Are you all right, Hirono-kun?
You didn't have an accident on your way over, did you?
Contact me right away after you hear this.
Enough of this! At least contact me!
You can at least give me a call!
I'm worried about you!
This is Miyako. Hirono-kun? Pick up the phone.
You're there, right?
You're actually listening to this, right?
Pick up the phone. Let's have a talk.
Talk to me.
Why don't you come?
Why don't you pick up the phone?
Why don't you answer my call?
Why?
Why are you silent?
Hirono-kun? Please contact me.
I'm not really mad or anything. I'll wait till we meet.
I'll keep waiting till I hear your voice!
Please, I beg you......
Come and see me.
I just need to see your face.
I just need to hear your voice.
Please......
Hirono-kun, you will come, right......?
I...... should keep waiting, right......?
I believe you...... I believe you......
Please...... answer me......
You can answer me by mail too...... even a single word is fine......
Please...... don't leave me alone......
I will wait for you...... I will keep waiting for you......!
Why...... why......?
Even though you promised me...... even though I believed you......
Why.....?
Am I no good......?
Am I no good perhaps......?
Do you hate me......?
If that's the case, please tell me so......!
If you hate me, just say it!
Don't just stay silent! Say something! I beg you!
I beg you, please say something!
...... I'm sorry...... I'm sorry that I said something weird......
Are you mad......? You're mad, right......?
I always have things my own way...... say things as I like...... abuse you......
I'm sorry...... I'm sorry......!
I didn't manage to fall asleep.
I was looking forward to today's date.
When I thought about you, my heart kept pounding......
This is my first time having this feeling......
I didn't know what to do.......
I want to see you...... I want to see you......
Help me, Hirono-kun......
Help me......!
I don't want to disappear...... I don't want to disappear......!
I don't want to disappear from your heart!!
Can you walk?
I'm all right. It's really not a big deal.
I'm going to the convenience store. Do you want something?
Garibori-kun.
I meant dinner.
Should I make it?
Don't frighten me.
That's mean! I've been practicing my cooking recently.
Ask me again when you don't need to practice anymore.
Can I just buy what I see fit?
Yeah, I'll leave it to you.
What? Isn't it right here...
Deleted.
Colorless colors are pure and cold.
Next episode, ef - a tale of memories: Clear Color.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?