In this ever-changing world
Where should we float off to?
286 VIEWS
I'll turn off the AC.
Alright, let's hit it.
Ok.
Playing.
Oh, come on!
It's hard to sing music
that was made for Vocaloid, huh.
You know Tomo-chan, I feel like
you're better at writing music,
so don't you think we should find a
vocalist who can do it justice?
I already told you I don't want to.
Right...
I guess we'll have to make do.
Forget I said anything. Let's keep making
music together as we always have.
I'll take out the trash.
Rupa.
Yeah?
Do you really... think we should give it a shot?
Look.
22,738 FOLLOWERS
If you're really serious
about chasing our dream...
AIM FOR THE BUDOKAN!
6: Hymn of the Outcasts
So, how's your throat?
A... bit better.
A bwit bwetter?
Subaru, come to the sauna.
You too Nina, it'll help with the throat.
I swear, you can't keep losing
your voice every time you sing.
Right?
Does it hurt?
No pain, no gain!
It's all part of the experience!
Ouch.
Still, that was one hell of a show.
It was fun though.
And Nina just went wild!
Like you didn't get carried away too.
And she's Drum Player-chan!
Hello, I'm Player!
You know I can't use my real name.
You need to make up a character.
I'm the high school cutie, Play-chan!
I'm... leaving first...
Still, she's totally hooked now, huh.
- You mean Nina?
- Mm.
That a problem?
- That's not what I meant.
Mo-mo-ka-san!
What?
Allow me to read the
comments from our concert.
"DD really isn't the same without Momoka-san."
"It was definitely more authentic
Rock than whatever DD's producing now."
Ooh, they're even calling
you cute Nina, isn't that nice?
Cool, thanks.
My point is, all customers agree
the old DD was way better.
So?
What are you gonna do, call them out
publicly that they're all frauds now?
That we're the real deal,
so people should follow us instead?
What's wrong about that?
Are you serious?
Have you seen how many followers DD has?
Look it up.
200k...
And counting...
And how many do we have?
500...
That's reality.
So what do you suggest we do then?
Nothing, really.
Let's keep practicing whenever we can.
Make music. Throw concerts.
And then what?
What's our goal as a band?
What happened to college?
I'm asking what your goal is!
Pain in the ass.
I just took a bath to relax,
leave me alone.
But I wanna know too!
You used to be a pro, right?
Isn't it a bit weird
For someone like you to team up
with a pair of amateurs like us?
Makes one wonder what you're really after.
Nothing, really.
So you've got no goals?
Yep. None.
God, she pisses me off!
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!!
Watch it with the rice.
What gives?
Anytime you try to have a conversation,
she's always, always, ALWAYS...
It's because you're so aggressive about it.
You're like a bull beefing with a bullfighter.
Beef... Gyudon...
She's never gonna open up
if you don't give her some space.
Then what do you think I should do?
Try to make her feel
comfortable enough to open up.
But you need to be patient.
Liar.
I'm being honest here!
It's just... I wonder what
she's really feeling right now.
Momoka aside, what is it that
you want for the band?
That's...
To triumph over Diamond Dust?
That's quite the lofty dream.
They're pros with a company
backing them, you know?
And what about you?
I'm home...
"Band Goals"...
"How to become a pro band"...
- You want to go pro?
- Yes.
What, did you get an offer?
It's not that, it's just that...
I was curious.
Well, back in the day you were
hoping to be scouted at performances,
Sending a demo reel,
going to auditions...
But these days, it's the bands that
hit it big on the net that get scouted.
Is it that big of a deal to get signed to a label?
Well, yeah.
Nowadays you can self-publish online, but...
It makes it a lot harder to get
collabs, promos, and all that.
For starters, you should try matching
what DD reached on their own back then.
Those girls built up 10k followers
while in their hometown.
That's when a label noticed them.
So it's all about the numbers.
Pretty much.
Each follower is a potential attendee.
The bigger the number,
the better the chances.
471 FOLLOWERS
It... went down?
"I'd rather nothing change than risk losing anything."
"I'd rather nothing change than get hurt."
I don't think it's a bad idea to let go of it.
But if you do, just please take off those stickers.
It's just silly.
Rupa... do you think it'll work out?
I'm no prophet.
Even the best of friends can end up arguing,
And even the most toxic relationships
can somehow work out.
But when I see those three...
I feel like you'll fit right in, Tomo-chan.
How?
Just a feeling.
Wanna practice a bit longer?
I think we should call it a day
so we can wrap up.
Right, I guess so.
You cool with that, Nina?
Nina...?
Uhm, would it be okay to take some time
to brainstorm the outfits for our next show?
I don't mind, but...
You picked them last time too, right?
Yes, but I thought...
We could go with something
slightly cuter this time.
Cuter?
Oh by the way, do you mind if I upload
the pics I took of you earlier?
Ooh, nice stuff!
Dazzling!
We're gonna rake in the followers--
Of course you can't!
I thought since you seemed so into it...
Post your own mug then!
Sorry. I just thought that... uh, our fans
would be grateful and appreciative?
And what if my grandma sees it?
Are you that desperate for followers?
We need to cultivate an audience.
Then let's maximize the marketing
by dressing up as schoolgirls
and rename ourselves to "Shin Kawasaki School Idol Club".
But you're too old, wouldn't that count as fraud--
Let a woman dream.
Wanna fight?
But I mean, if that gets us more followers...
Are you kidding me?
Come on. You'd be no different than
the current Diamond Dust then.
I know that...
But it'll be difficult to reach
their level if we don't go pro
And to do that we need to build more fans.
Since when did we agree on that?
Because if we don't,
we're gonna lose to Diamond Dust!
Again, since when have we been competing?
I've already told you.
I've got no beef with DD, so--
I don't want to lose.
I don't care.
Don't drag the whole band into your petty daydreams.
I understand.
But even so... I don't want to lose.
Look Nina, I get how you feel, but...
- I know, but...
- Good evening!
What's with the sudden obsession for going pro?
It's not like I think going pro
will solve all our problems.
And I don't think we can beat
Diamond Dust even if we go pro.
But... I don't wanna give up without even trying!
Because I don't think we're wrong!
Medium without the onions, as usual.
A medium, please.
Understood. Two mediums--
What?
Welcome to the team!
Girls Band Cry.
You're musicians?
Let me introduce us.
I'm Rupa. And she's Ebizuka Tomo-chan.
We've been making music for a while,
just the two of us.
Oh, this rings a bell.
It was a pretty popular hit.
I didn't recognize you
since you didn't show your faces.
That's really cute...
Thank you.
Wait, so the reason you reached out...
You wanna do a rock battle?
Not quite.
- Murder?
- Not really.
- Oh, I know! We're your store's 10,000th custom--
- Not that either.
You're slow on the uptake.
We're scouting you.
- Like, for the army?
- Not that either.
WE. WANT. TO. SCOUT. YOU.
Scout?
Who wants?
Scout who?
Don't tell me, you want us to do sexua--
No way!!
Look, we want to make music
with the three of you!
- No way.
- Indeed.
We came to your show the other day.
No way...
And so the two of us
talked it out and agreed
That we want to give this
a shot with you three.
No wayyyy!!
Sellout.
But... we don't really have an established audience.
Nor many fans or followers.
We could say the same about us.
We're the same then.
Even so, we got an offer from a label once.
Wow.
I know, but...
Once we started negotiating with them,
We felt they weren't really thinking
about what we truly wanted out of this.
In the end, they only care if it sells.
If you want to put it bluntly.
Let's just say it wasn't
what we were looking for.
So where do we come in?
Right. When we saw your concert, we felt...
Like you're the types who only
sing what you want to sing.
We thought you'd share our vision.
You mean it?
Am I wrong?
Not at all, that's exactly why I sing.
Oh Nina loves sharing visions.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you for having us.
Give me a second
while I turn on the lights.
Sure!
Over there?
Don't go touching anything!
Anyone home?
Huh? What's this?
- Wow, a lizard!
- It's called a gecko.
"Aim for the Budokan", huh?
The Budokan?
S-so what? What's wrong with dreaming a little?
Not at all! If anything,
I think that's really cool!
I've never even dreamed of something like that.
Same here.
So is the Budokan like a big deal?
What, haven't you heard of it?
I know it's a really important venue from TV, but...
Bumpkin.
Tomo-chan, you're from Sendai though.
Sendai, Kagoshima?
I'm from Kumamoto next door!
Huh? She meant the Sendai, Miyagi.
Oh...
Since you came this far,
wanna go see it together?
Jeez, do we have to go at this hour?
Now now, I think it's important
they see it with their own eyes.
BUDOKAN
If we sing here...
If we sing here, maybe we could
prove we weren't wrong.
That we aren't losing to Diamond Dust.
I'm sure of it.
AIM FOR THE BUDOKAAAAAN!
So, what do you wanna do?
Let me call Momoka-san ASAP!
- Are you a dumbass or what?
- What's wrong now?
Momoka-san said we needed
a bassist and keyboardist, right?
But to dream of the Budokan...
That's the same as going pro.
You think Momoka-san will just agree with that?
Then what are you saying we should do?
Who knows.
I have to tell her.
Gotcha!
Can't you think of anything else,
you self-righteous freak?
But it's not like we have any other options.
What?
You do?
Promise you won't call me a liar.
I'll tell you if you promise me you won't call me a liar!
They're good.
It's well mixed and well paced too.
Right?
And they play the bass and the keyboard!
I thought we could try collabing for a song.
What do you think?
What do they think?
They're cool! Even more, they wanna--
For starters, they offered to
practice together this Sunday.
You free?
Probably.
Then let me know later so I can confirm!
- Liar!
- I call it strategizing.
What she say?
Well, it's not like she's not against not not doing it.
What does that even mean?
This is just my impression, but...
I feel like there are two Momokas.
The one that when it comes to music,
she pours her heart into it,
To make the best music she can.
Someone who wants her music to leave an impact.
But when it's not about the music itself,
she comes back down to Earth.
She's already given up on the industry once.
So she likely wonders if there's any point
in trying seriously again.
I see.
Who cares about that.
Is she in or not?
I can't say.
If we can show her we can make
a proper band, she might change her mind.
She's a musician at heart after all.
I see.
I understand now.
We gotta practice already? What a pain.
Huh? Practice now?
Just be a good girl and follow my plan.
SOME DAYS LATER
Ready?
A proper studio is something else.
Hey, there's something up with this cable...
Detective Granny?!
Hold up, this photo...
Is this real?
Where did you get it?
Don't tell me...
Yep!
Tomo-chan's such a big fan
she's seen the series three times over!
She's always bawling her eyes out.
They don't need the details.
Still, you're lucky to have this.
Awa Tendo is known for not
interacting much with fans.
Wait... Awa?
You called?
- I demand an explanation.
- 'Sup.
Oh?
You're late.
I'm Rupa, the bassist. Pleasure to meet you.
And that's Tomo-chan, our keyboardist.
Wait... you're from the gyudon place...
Thank you for your continued patronage.
Order something other than a
medium and a beer, I'm begging you.
Good to meet you,
I'm Kawaragi the guitarrist.
The legendary Kawaragi Momoka
of Diamond Dust fame!
We are not done talking, you and I.
So, what are we playing?
How about the song
from our last concert?
I'm cool, but will these
two be able to play it?
Yes, we rehearsed a bit before you arrived.
I'll spice it up a little bit though.
- Is that okay?
- Just a sec.
We won't know how it'll
come out 'till we try it.
Alright then.
Alright, I'm good.
One, two, three, four.
Wow... what is this? Oh my...
This city flows down a whirlpool of truths
Where should we float off to?
In this ever changing world
What should we raise up?
Look, Momoka-san.
The truth is, we actually wanted to ask
if these two could join our band.
I wanna give it a shot!
I know you're not wrong.
I know your music won't lose.
I'm serious about this!
Music festival?
Our first step should be
to make a big impression.
They've got a division for amateurs as well.
If our application gets picked,
we get a big stage and a lot of eyes on us.
And hope a big label notices us then?
Exactly.
A festival is the biggest gathering
of music talent there is, so,
I guess it's a prime location for scouting.
To find the diamond in the rough.
We'd be playing...
Alongside Diamond Dust?
Next: Select Your Name