You bastards...
What? What happened?
There's another sniper...
No way...
Where?
Where did he shoot from?
Don't tell me...
Mission completed.
Very well. Withdraw via route C immediately,
and wait for instructions.
Yes, Master.
A shot that didn't hit anyone but stirred up mistrust.
Now, how will the heroine improvise her way out?
You called us all the way out here to get shot.
What the fuck is this?!
You guys will pay for this, right?
What are you talking about?!
Weren't you bastards the ones who shot?!
Oh? Then...
Kill them all!
You can't, Mr. Godoh!
You scared me...
Ray...
I... I...
Wanted to...
There's another sniper.
But...
Reiji...
Reiji!
What's wrong?
Nothing, let's retreat.
I see. All right.
My subordinate has successfully erased the threat.
There's no need to worry about snipings anymore.
What they hell are you playing at?
Mr. Godoh, I present to you Issac Wisemel's head.
The head of the person who has been plotting to kill you.
What did you say?
This traitor, who only cares about personal profit, was killed by me.
Traitor?
Can you give me an explanation?
A reason for shooting our own people.
This sniping was plotted by Wisemel.
If you confirm the identity of the sniper who my subordinate stopped,
that would be unshakable evidence.
Nice set-up.
This is the Inferno way of settling things.
The hotel sniping occurred after I killed Randy.
That wasn't part of Wisemel's plan.
There was another sniper.
That sniper was also Wisemel's subordinate.
He's the type that's extremely determined.
Then why did the sniper only fire one shot and didn't continue to fire?
Wisemel's objective should have been to kill Godoh Daisuke.
You sound like you're the only one who knows the truth.
Killing or not killing... didn't matter.
That sniper's true objective was...
...to stir up mistrust between the two groups there.
To mess up Inferno from the inside.
Did they even predict that Claudia would kill Wisemel?
Stop.
The whole thing is a conspiracy stirred up by that bastard Wisemel.
That's why Clau finished him off according to her own judgment.
Don't think too much.
We're just soldiers.
There's no point in thinking that deep.
Lizzy's correct.
We don't need to know the truth.
Besides, if Wisemel takes the blame for everything that happened,
the whereabouts of the 5 million becomes clear.
The money that the Godoh Clan lost...
...will appear in Wisemel's mansion.
This will put an end to everything.
The deaths of the yakuza, avenging Judy,
and...
...my very own assumption.
No.
That's not it.
She can't be alive...
Hey, I heard some rumors.
Is it true that Issac of the Bloodies died?
Yes, it is.
The person you killed was Issac's man and also the one who killed Judy, right?
Yeah.
Then avenging Judy is done...
I see.
Hey, so how was it?
How was my assassin training?
If it's fine with you, I can help you with your assassinations from now on.
No more assassinations.
No more...
Then does that mean I'm fired?
However...
I wouldn't want to miss your cooking.
For the time being, I'll let you be my kitchen maid.
Really?! Yay! A maid!
I've always wanted to try that!
Maid clothes are really cute, aren't they?!
You don't need to go that far.
Eh?! No maid clothes?!
No.
I guess it's okay as long as I can stay by your side.
What a fabulous report.
This sums up that Issac Wisemel was behind everything that happened.
The Godoh Clan has no reason not to consent to this.
However, to be able to see through all this in the middle of such chaos...
You really are excellent.
You'll be taking Issac's place from now on.
Then...
Don't disappoint me, Claudia McCunnen.
Understood.
Potential?
Yes. She has a rare quality about her.
You could call it talent.
Talent... I've heard such words before.
So you mean you want to train that girl into a hitman?
Yes.
If she doesn't show any results...
You know what to expect, right?
Yes.
Then let's see what she's made of.
There won't be any more dangers now.
I should find an excuse and...
...send her off...
But yet,
I feel at ease when I'm here.
Cal.
I'm going out.
I might be coming back the day after tomorrow.
I probably should have told you earlier.
No, don't worry. Have a good trip.
Be careful, okay?
You too.
Seems like you're already used to the office work.
Stop joking around.
How about just spending your days like this?
You're already an executive.
There's no need to wander around.
It still hasn't ended.
This is just the beginning.
What else do you need?
Being too greedy will do you no good.
Well, I know you won't listen.
But be careful where you tread.
Do I seem that much of an idiot to you?
Just let me give you some advice. It's my hobby, after all.
Cal, I didn't really get it...
Is this the full one you-
Cal.
Welcome back! You're home already?
Cal, where did you go?
You bought it!
Chicken served with this is really good.
Should I just let this go on?
Should I...
Reiji.
What's up?
You know,
I really want to become your assistant.
Cal, that's...
I know that you don't want me to become an assassin.
Because you know the pain of an assassin.
But I want to become useful.
Being weak, being poor, and not being able to do anything without relying on others.
I'm tired of living like that.
Cal, you can walk whatever path you want. Do whatever you want...
But why do you want to become an assassin?
Do you hate assassins?
Yeah.
Does that mean you hate yourself too?
Yeah, I do.
Killing is like my second nature and I can't go back.
That's why I hate myself.
But Reiji...
I'm already broken.
Do you want to become like me?!
Sorry Reiji... I...
Cal, I said too much.
Sorry.
But it's true.
I don't know how many have died because of me.
If I weren't there, they would still be living.
They could have all gone back to their families and lovers.
It's not your fault.
You just accepted a job that was going to be done either way.
It's not as pretty as you described...
Then, do you really want to kill?
Do you shoot just because you want to kill?
Do you like to kill?
You don't, right?
You feel bitter, full of pain, sad, and unforgiving to yourself for doing such things.
You want to kill yourself.
You don't pull the trigger simply like the people that killed Judy.
You live while enduring it all.
That's why you won't make mistakes.
You won't kill the innocent.
If those guys back then had been you, then Judy wouldn't have had to die.
But Cal...
When you kill your first person, the whole world changes.
Everything you see... everything you hear... everything changes.
You won't be your kind self anymore.
I don't want you to become like that.
This isn't where you belong.
You shouldn't come into the world that I'm in.
But... But you'll always stay in there, right?
If I go there, then I'll always be able to stay with you.
Cal...
I don't want to leave you...
I want to stay by your side forever.
I want to help you.
I just...
...want to be with you.
I get it now. I...
...really do want to go back.
By doing that, I can stay with you.
There's no need. I'll go to your world.
I'll go to where you are.
Let me go... Let me go back...
Back to the world where you are.
Cal, I was like a dead person before I met you.
If we get split up, I'll turn into a dead person again.
I'll forget how to laugh and cry.
The things you made me remember.
Don't tell me, this guy is...
Do you know him?
There's no doubt about it. It's that brat!
I was shocked.
Ms. McCunnen should've been helping you people join Inferno.
Where was the plan changed?
How would I know?!
Contact the boss immediately! Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Your turn should be over soon, Ms. McCunnen.
Let me give you a flower that's suitable for the end.
Hello?
Phantom, can you dispatch right away?
Why so sudden?
The remnants of the Bloodies are making some weird movements.
I want to settle it without causing a ruckus.
Can you help me?
All right. Where do we meet?
The usual train station at 20:00.
Understood.
Work?
Yeah.
I thought we would be together for the whole day...
What are you talking about?
Aren't we going to be together forever from now on?
Huh?
We have plenty of time.
I need to regain my own self.
For Cal's sake,
and...
Elen's sake.
Don't call me Elen. I'm Ein.
No matter now or before. I'm just Ein.