Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
Onee-chan, wake up!
Where'd you put that hair accessory you bought?
Let me borrow it!
Geez!
Onee-chan, you fell asleep with your glasses on again!
How many times have I told you they'll bend—
Ouchies...
"The President is a Big Sister"
I can't believe you!
Those glasses are like a part of my body!
Sorry, Onee-chan.
Haruka told me she knew a good optician,
so I'll ask her if she can get them repaired for you.
Haruka-san again?
You never stop talking about her.
I hear her name more now than I did when you were in middle school.
It's not like you're dating her or anything.
Human stovetop.
Wow, impressive. Mind heating mine up too?
Just what is she hiding from me?
Something's fishy.
S-Stop spilling crumbs everywhere.
I'm pretty sure this girl's been here quite a few times since Yuu's second year of middle school...
Memories?
It'd be bad if you caught her cold, so I'll introduce you next time.
S-Sure.
But I was always sick...
Sick with a cold
High School School Trip
Or on a field trip with my class...
I've never even seen her face before.
Note: Artist
Impression
All I've seen are...
...her shoes.
Just what do you look like, Takayama Haruka?!
What the heck're you doing?!
Our staff enjoyed the leftovers afterwardsd
Our staff enjoyed the leftovers afterwards
Ah, our class rep is back!
What'd our teacher say?
She wants us to decide on our class's representatives for the sports fest.
Sports fest?
I heard that because there were only three first-year classes,
it wasn't cost effective to do a full athletics festival.
They seriously cut the athletics festival?
Today's such an unlucky day!
Lucky Day
Unlucky Day
Unlucky in
the Morning
Trial Day
Unlucky except
around noon
Lucky in
the Morning
I even broke my sister's glasses this morning...
Sorry to kick you while you're down,
but you've got supplementary classes after school today.
Yuu-chan!
My festival...
My athletics festival...
Yuu-chan, you really care that much?
Yeah.
What's so bad about it being a sports fest?
Because...
I can't do it at a sports fest.
Be head cheerleader.
Yeah, that's horrible.
A total travesty!
Oh yeah, and I didn't know your sister was the student council president, Yuu.
She asked me to say hi to you for her since we're in the same class.
That true?
Yup.
I just realized that I've never actually seen your sister before.
She was the one who gave the welcome speech at our entrance ceremony.
I was asleep for that...
You serious, Haruka-san?
The rest of you saw her, right?
Sorry, we were asleep too.
Come on now.
There you are, Sonoda!
Supplemental lesson, now!
Coming!
Ah, and there she goes.
Yuu-chan...
I let one slip away.
From what?
I also needed to ask if any of you would become a committee rep.
No way!
That's it, Harupoppo!
If you became a rep, you could bring up Yuu-chan's cheer thing at today's meeting.
Ah!
Yeah, that's a good idea!
The teacher also said that those who join might find their gym grades getting a little boost...
I'll do it!
Me too!
Well, if Kotone's doing it...
Hey...
After school
Student Council Meeting Room
I'm so glad we could use Yuzu-chan and make it in.
Yes, now I have to give my all to help Yuu-chan.
Use Yuzu-chan...
Class 1-A, Takayama Haruka?
Sports Festival
Committee members from each class
Class 1-A
Ikeno Kaede
Takayama Haruka
Noda Kotone
Class Committee Member
Action Committee Member
Haruka! Could it be?!
Rina, a moment?
Yes?
Which one is Takayama Haruka-san?
Takayama-san?
I think she's the one over there with the shoulder-length hair.
I can't see without my glasses...
Who is it? Reveal yourself!
Sports Festival Committee Meeting
I am the student council president, Sonoda Mitsuki from class 3-C.
Student Council President
Vice President
Secretary
Vice President Sakai Rina, also from 3-C.
And I'm the secretary, Otokawa Sumi from class 2-B.
To start with, I'd like to thank you all for taking on the responsibilities of representing your classes.
Student Council President
Vice President
Secretary
As I'm sure you're all aware, we will not be holding an athletics festival this year.
So that's what Yuu-chan's sister is like.
They're nothing like each other.
I've got butterflies in my stomach!
Kotone-chan, are you trying to cheer me up?
Whoa, look at them shake.
shake
She's playing with me!
Soccer
Basketball
Volleyball
Dodgeball
Softball
Student Council President
Vice President
Secretary
Now that we're decided on what events to have,
does anyone have any comments?
In addition to the regular sports, we should have cheerleading as well!
This'll work!
That's, uh...
Yes, class 1-A?
Thank you.
President Mitsuki looks really mad for some reason!
She's so blurry...
I can't do this!
How dare you turn my sister into used goods.
Well, I...
Harupoppo, don't you fret. Just repeat after me.
Okay.
Student Council President
President Mitsuki.
President Mitsuki!
Yes?
Please give.
Please give...
Your sister.
...your sister...
To me.
That's not it!
My sister? We're currently discussing the sports festival.
Please leave all other matters until after the meeting.
Th-That's not what I meant to say.
Oh no, I really made her angry.
No, I can't back down now.
Harupoppo, fight!
I'll have to bring out the big guns to lighten the mood!
pop
P-President Mitsuki, haven't you ever wanted cute girls to cheer you on?
If so, then what do you say to having cheerleaders at the sports fest?!
Student Council President
Secretary
Cheerleading, huh.
While I do think that would be interesting, it's out of the question.
Our school is going to shut down in three years,
so our funding has drastically dropped.
That's the whole reason we had to run a low-cost sports festival this year.
I do feel bad that those in your year won't ever be able to experience an athletics festival,
but we can't overturn this decision.
But you know...
President Mitsuki spent a whole month going to the teachers' offices
trying to find a way to hold an athletics festival.
Please recognize that she's done everything she could.
That ends today's meeting.
Here.
Kotone-chan.
Why did I even join the committee?
I embarrassed myself for nothing.
Harupoppo.
There won't be an athetlics fest next year or the year after.
And definitely not after we graduate.
If you let this chance slip by, Yuu-chan will never get to be a cheerleader.
But there's nothing I can do.
You know how I'm living with Shizuku-chan?
Everyone was against me doing that at first.
But I fought until they gave in.
We'll never live these three years again.
Let's not leave any regrets.
President Mitsuki!
squeeze!
Wh-What are you doing?
W-Well...
I want to have cheerleading more than anything else!
My friend was really, really down about not getting to be a cheerleader,
so I'll do anything to give her that chance!
Hey, you...
Since our second year of middle school, this friend has helped me out so much.
Now it's my turn to help her!
Please let us have cheerleading!
I won't let you go until you say yes!
She's so weird.
Why would she go this far for her friend?
Got it.
I'll try talking to the teachers about your cheerleading.
Thank you so much!
What's your name?
Takayama Haruka from class 1-A.
Y-Yo—Taka...
O-Oh no! She completely froze up!
P-President Mitsuki!
Some
later day
Is President Mitsuki here?
She is, but she's studying for college entrance exams,
so she'll blow a fuse if you disturb her.
But I even brought extra green tea
cream puffs for President Mitsuki...
Green tea puffs?!
I'll stick them in the fridge!
Haruka-san?
Your strawberry one looks good too! Split it with me!
Split it, split it!
Give me some!
Oh, fine.
I changed my mind.
Are you sure? Then I'll just keep eating.
So sweet!
Oh yeah, today's the last day they're making these.
I guess you'll have to wait until next year, Yuu-chan.
Oh, but who knows if they'll even make it again? Too bad.
That hurts, Yuu-chan!
Haruka.
Kaede-chan told me.
She said you're the one who got them to bring cheerleading back.
You never were the type to sign up for that sort of committee.
In fact, you're normally really
bad at those kinds of things.
Thanks.
Let me know what the strawberry one tastes like.
Let me take a bite.
I'm going to melt...
Just like the cream...
It really is sweet.
More...
I want to melt with Yuu-chan...
But you're even sweeter.
I want to get another look at Haruka-san.
Who knows when I'll get another chance.
Big Sister
She went and got my glasses fixed.
Yeah, I still haven't thanked her.
Calm down, play it cool.
I wonder what they're talking about.
Wait, what's that sound?
Wh-What?! Is my heart really beating that loudly?
I can't believe myself...
I'm just here to get a look at her; it's no big deal.
Yuu, Haruka-san? I brought you some drinks.
I'm coming in...
boiling
point
"The President is a Big Sister"
The end
"A Promise Made While Cleaning the Pool"
Haruka, I left my swimsuit at home.
Oh my.
I could've sworn I put it in here this morning.
Ta-da!
I thought something like this might happen, so I brought an extra!
Haruka
Thanks so much, Haruka!
Yuu-chan
Haruka
What is this?!
I stayed up all night making it!
You really shouldn't have.
Huh, but why?
If I actually wore this, people would start to get suspicious about us.
Haruka
Yuu-chan
Who cares? Look how cute it is!
That's not the point!
Can you seriously wear that?
Oh Yuu-chan, you're such a handful sometimes.
Do you want to wear mine instead?
I wonder if it'll fit okay.
I just have to rip it off before I wear it.
No, stop! How could you?!
I'll rip it off yours too, so give it here!
They're not gonna find out from just this!
If our secret gets out, our
relationship's as good as over!
Our relationship isn't that weak!
Their flirting today is really something special.
But anyway—
How did we end up cleaning the pool?
But in return, our class is going to
get to use the pool first.
When's that?
Tomorrow.
Really?
Really really.
Then let's get this thing done!
Alright girls, grab your tools and start the cleaning!
Yeah!
Oh~
Hey!
Man, they're all revved up to play.
Just let them be. We don't get to do this that often.
Playing volleyball is A-ok.
Save that for the beach.
Burying A-ok.
You mean at the beach.
Enjoying a getaway—also A-ok!
You're supposed to do those at the beach!
Yuu-chan!
Check this out.
See?
It's so pretty! Do you think it'd make a bigger rainbow if you made the water stronger?
Want to give it a try?
Yuzu-chan, I'm sorry!
I'll get her back for that.
Take that!
I'll drag you down with me.
You're mine!
Geez...
Haruka, cover yourself! It's showing!
Yuu, what're you doing?
They can see!
What's going on?
N-Nothing at all.
Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan.
Look over here.
What're you flashing at them?!
Huge.
No, I didn't mean those.
Look closely.
Here, at this.
I'm looking...
It's really okay! You two don't have to play along!
Haruka's a D-cup?
She's a C!
Hey, over there.
The number of beach queens doubled.
When did that happen?
Seeing Kotone-chan and Shizuku-chan in their own little world makes them seem really mature.
How does fried chicken sound for dinner tonight?
Didn't we just have chicken yesterday?
Though all they're really talking about is dinner.
Yeah, but even so.
Yuu-chan and I wouldn't lose to them if we really tried.
Haruka!
There's a water strider over there!
Yuu-chan is so dense!
We're not ever gonna finish at this rate.
Hey, Yuzu.
Yeah?
Don't you think your thighs have gotten a bit chubby?
It might be better to slim down some before summer really gets here.
From here
Doing some laps probably wouldn't hurt.
To here
Let's give it a try!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Wow, the five of us getting paper made that easy.
Yuu-chan, have fun cleaning the storage shed.
Aw, but I wanted to play in the pool more.
Wait up a second, girls. Mine was actually scissors disguised as paper.
I think this calls for a do-over, right?
Then let's put the two who didn't throw paper together.
Enjoy cleaning the shed.
So that's how you're playing it.
Pool Equipment Shed
You can really tell our school's shutting down soon.
I can't see us finishing this today.
Okay Haruka, here's your broom and dustpan.
Thanks, you really came prepared.
I'm supposed to pick up all the trash? What about you?
I'll be in charge of spraying water.
Let's try looking at reality now.
There's so much dust.
We should get some ventilation in here.
Where's a window...
Way up there?!
Yuu-chan?
Wai—
Yuu-chan!
Let us proceed forward!
Sh-She's heavy! No, my swimsuit is getting wet...
Haruka, just a little closer!
I can't!
Ah, there we go!
Sakura?
But they all should've fallen by now...
No, look closer. These are fake ones.
Artificial flowers?
I guess the old swim team did all sorts of fun things when they were still around.
There are all these sakura petals fluttering around despite how close summer is...
It feels kind of mysterious.
And it reminds me of back then.
Yuu-chan, your nose.
Yep, they're flowers.
TN: Nose 鼻 (hana) sounds like flower 花 (hana)
Not that, your nose.
Flower?
Listen, I'm talking about your nose!
My flower?
Yuu-chan is totally oblivious.
I have to do it for her.
Yuu-chan.
Th-That's not what I intended!
Forgive me.
Got it!
There was a flower petal stuck there.
On your nose.
You didn't seem to understand when I told you.
Yuu-chan?
Yuu-chan.
I think that made her angry.
There's still one more on your face.
Turn this way.
Tell me where. I'll get it myself.
Right here.
Take this seriously, beach queens!
We are, we are!
Spray some water over there.
Where do you think you're aiming?!
They told me she was staying late to clean the pool...
Take this!
I will not.
We're seriously not gonna finish.
I can't see Yuu anywhere.
Huh? Haruka-san's missing too.
Just give up, Kaede.
Big Sister
Don't tell me they're skipping to do that sort of thing again!
swish
No, I mustn't think that.
Big Sister
There must be something wrong with me.
Yuu probably just has extra lessons again.
I worry far too much. I'd better get home.
Oh, someone's litter?
Haruka
Yuu-chan
"A Promise Made While Cleaning the Pool"
The end
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai deaeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!
Next Episode
Iizuka Yuzu here!
And I'm Ikeno Kaede.
Hey, are my thighs really that fat?
Don't worry, there are people who like that kind of thing.
I don't want anyone who loves me for just my thighs!
At least you have something. There's not a single part of me...
Y-You shouldn't compare yourself to people like Kotone or Haruka.
I don't need your pity!
Next time, Trick 4:
"A Sour Plot?"
"Could This be a Test of Courage!?"
"A Sour Plan?",
and "Could This be a Test of Courage!?"
Look forward to it.
I knew those tears were fake!