- Empty Classroom}
- Front}
- Passageway}
- Men’s toilet}
<Sign: Baseball field >
Incinerator
So what are we going to start with?
It took me a while to think it over,
but I think we should start with Yui.
Who?
You know, the girl who does vocals for the guerrilla live concerts in the cafe.
Don’t you remember her?
She’s always so energetic, laughing away while she bullies Hinata.
She does the band’s vocals and anything else she likes doing.
I think she’s already found peace.
If we just give her a gentle push,
she’ll be able to leave this place.
That’s what I think.
If you think so, then alright.
You agree?
Okay, then let’s do that.
So, how's it going on your end?
Well, it took some time...
Hand Sonic, version 5.
This is Hand Sonic version 5.
It looks more evil than angelic...
I made it like this because you told me I’m playing the cruel Angel, so I had to make it look mean.
No good?
No, that’s great. Really unpleasant.
Unpleasant?
No no, I mean really good.
Could you also grow wings?
Wings?
What would I do with those?
It’d look cool, wouldn’t it?
I have to look cool?
No, I just thought it would make you more Angel-like.
I’ll think about it.
Thanks.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Oh, right.
Let’s do this —
You appear while she’s in band practice,
then you tell her,
“Another club is complaining about the noise.”
Then you point at Yui and say,
“Your guitar is especially bad.”
“Because of you, the band is dead.”
“That being the case, I’m confiscating that guitar.”
Then you take her guitar and leave the scene.
Of course, Yui will give chase.
Just run, and head to the inner garden.
At that point I’ll pretend to bump into you, and then you let go of the guitar.
I’ll take it, so just run away at that point.
This way we can create a situation where I can be alone with her.
Understood.
Alright!
Now we just wait for the start of rehearsal and go!
Study block A - Empty Classroom
Stop!
Yui, don’t just keep going when you mess up the rhythm!
Don't you think you should concentrate on just singing or playing?
Yeah you’re right, it sounds bad right now.
No way!
Iwasawa-san sang and played at the same time!
That’s because Iwasawa was good at both.
I’m trying my best too!
You’re all too strict!
Our concerts are popular aren’t they?
But this is a new song.
Angel?!
Because of your guitar, the band is dead.
She discovered the band’s weak point in an instant!
We can’t underestimate her!
She knows music!
No way! I thought nobody noticed!
That being the case, I’m confiscating that guitar.
Hey, Yui!
Are you okay?
Here.
Why are you alone?
She didn’t chase me.
See? Without the guitar you don’t go off beat.
But doesn't it sound kind of weak?
We need a rhythm guitar.
Should we get another side guitar player then?
What I want to say is...
The band has the most impact with the vocals also on guitar, dammit!!
Why you...
She made Hisako-san angry!
I'm gonna go get my guitar back!
Crap!
Hey! Dammit, Yui!
Here she comes!
Where did she go?
There she is!
Wait up!
Whoops, sorry!
Idiot, that’s too high!
My guitar!
It’s fine, not a scra—
Senpai protected it from Angel for me!
Where did she go, dammit!!
Geez, what’s with the “dammit!”
I see you’re doing whatever you want, as usual.
Whatever I want? Not really...
You got the vocal position in the band, didn’t you?
You’re even playing guitar.
Oh that’s nothing, it’s just one of the things I wanted to do.
There are other things?
Yeah, lots of them.
“Lots”...
No wait, let’s talk somewhere else.
So, what else is there?
Main Dining Hall - Front
Do I have to tell you?
If you don’t want to talk about it, that’s fine.
That’s okay, I’ll tell you.
I have more things I want to do than most people.
Why do you think that is?
Because, I guess...
You couldn’t do them when you were alive?
Yep, exactly!
When I was small, I got hit by a car from behind.
After that, I became paralyzed.
I was completely bedridden.
I couldn’t live without assistance.
I was constantly relying on my mother.
I was always thinking it wasn’t fair to her.
I was able to watch TV, so when I saw bands on music shows I thought it’d be great if I could do that too.
I see. That turned out well then.
Yeah!
So what else do you want to do?
Well, I watched baseball matches a lot.
Did we already play baseball at the tournament?
I didn’t get a hit though.
Hit?
A home run!
You won’t be happy till you hit a home run?
Not at all!
Once I become better in the band, I’m thinking about putting in some real practice.
Keeping both of those up will be tough.
I guess I’ll ask, what else was there?
Soccer!
Soccer?!
It was popular, right!
Well it was, but...
She has too many interests!
In what world does a person try to be a musician, baseball player, and a soccer player?
I don’t suppose there are any oth—
Pro wrestling!
I don’t understand her!
In what world...
Wait, everything she wants to do comes from TV...
But this is going to be hard...
Granting all of those dreams for her...
Alright.
I’ll fulfill those dreams for you.
Let’s start with something easy.
How about we go with pro wrestling?
Pro wrestling?
What move?
German Suplex!
There’s no way you can pull off such a flashy move!
Do a pin or something you can actually pull off!
But I’ve always wanted to do the German Suplex!
And then I'll win with a sleeper hold!
Don’t say such violent things so innocently!
Okay.
Let’s try it.
Really?
Yeah.
Alright!
You’re stronger than I thought!
You can do this!
Owww!!
I guess it’s impossible for a girl...
No, you almost did it!
That was close!
Really?
Then can we try it again?
Y-Yeah...
Can we go somewhere with grass first?
Otherwise I’ll die.
You can’t die!
No, I wasn’t joking.
I'm not going to make it.
Sorry! I’ll get it right next time!
This really is the last time.
I’m going back.
Senpai!
Are you even able to pull off a bridge?
I can!
Let’s see it.
So this was the root of the problem...
Thanks to this I nearly lost consciousness several times.
We’ll start with bridge training then.
What? Boring!
Just do it!
Come on, try harder!
That’s terrible, come on!
But I’ve never done this before!
If you can’t do this, you won’t be able to do the German Suplex.
I’ll do my best.
Several hours later
I’m doing it, just about!
You're shaking all over the place, but that’ll do.
Here I go then!
Bring it!
Her arms are fixed firmly around my waist!
There’s no escape from this!
It's perfect!
Perfect!
German Suplex!!
One...
two...
three!
Ding ding ding!
Match over!
I did it... I really did it!
Yay!
Banzai!
How much more of this am I going to have to deal with?
How about we do soccer next?
Study Block - Passageway
A one on one penalty kick should be fine, right?
No, I want to do a dribble shoot against 5 people!
You know, Maradona.
Well, I know that...
Okay, fine.
Leave it to me!
Hey TK, know where Matsushita 5th Dan is?
He can’t dance in my world right now.
Don't let me cry!
I guess so...
So where?
Secluded mountain training.
In the mountain.
Secluded mountain training?
He’s gone pretty far off...
So he won’t be back for a while?
Ah whatever, you’ll do.
Could you gather up 4 other members for me?
Keep this secret from Yuri, but I got this letter from Angel.
Study Block C - Men’s toilet
You can’t even stand up to a single girl.
It is absurd to think you call yourself a man.
I’m surprised you know a word like “absurd”.
Were you cured of idiocy?
No, even idiots can read this.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
I’ll beat your girly ass till you learn some guts for the sake of sportsmanship.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
I’ll be waiting after school at the soccer grounds.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
It is absurd to think
you call yourself a man.
I’ll beat your girly ass till
you learn some guts for the
sake of sportsmanship.
I’ll be waiting after school
at the soccer grounds.
Angel.
What the hell!?
I don’t really get it...
Did she really write this?
The Angel now isn’t like the one before.
After having all those minds mixed into her, she's taken to writing challenges as idiotic as this.
I can’t deal with this stupidity.
I’m going to go tell Yurippe.
I said keep it a secret from Yuri!
Why?
If you tell Yuri, it’ll develop into another bloodbath.
Look, it says “for the sake of sportsmanship” right?
She’s saying she wants to fight fair and square with sports.
That’s why this challenge is directed at us guys.
Telling Yuri would damage our pride as men.
I see, that’s a good point.
I guess the five of us will go then.
Kiss you!
That’s the spirit!
Soccer field
What?
Look over there.
Someone’s there.
Isn’t that Yui?
What’s she doing?
So you’ve come.
Kick off!
She started dribbling the ball...
Here I come, you bastards!
I get it!
She’s the one who wrote the letter!
She must have gotten annoyed with us always being so useless that she was driven to doing this!
Alright, let’s defend the goal!
We’re not losing this fight!
Us men will win!
I don’t really get it but...
I get it!
Don’t look down on us!
I kiss you!
Hinata, take goalie!
Alright!
Outta my way, damn idiots!
What a pathetic dribble.
You’re full of openings!
Take this!
Alright, one down!
What the hell was that?
What are you doing, Noda?!
Number two!
Ref, that’s a red card right there!
Safe!
Who’s that supposed to be?
I’m still going, bitches!
Get her, TK! Otonashi!
Easy come, easy go!
Leave it to us!
Number three!
Alright!
Woo! Here we—
Whose side are you on?!
Looks like you’re the last one!
You’ll have to kill me to take this ball!
What kind of sportsmanship is that?!
Like I care!
Here I come!
Ultimate Killer Shot!!
I can't tell whether she wants to kill me or score a goal with this shot!
It’s a miracle!
Hinata!!
It went in?
Yay!
I did it!
I scored a goal!
No way...
We lost?
To Yui, by herself...
Scrambled it trouble down.
That was bad...
Let’s keep this a secret.
Yeah...
Though, she lost the ball, didn’t pass the goalie and went all over the place...
Well, whatever.
Alright...
Let’s move on to the next one!
Baseball field
Before that, how far are you trying to hit this home run?
Beyond the fence, of course!
Seriously?
Well for now, hit it as hard as you can.
I hit it!
Just hitting the ball doesn’t mean much...
Watch the ball carefully and hit it with the center of the bat.
You’re hitting too high on the ball.
Now you’re too low.
There’s no way you’ll hit it with your eyes closed!
This is weak...
Come on, try harder!
I am!
One more time!
Huh?
You’re hopeless.
You’re too tired to grip properly.
There’s no point continuing further today.
You’re not going to do it just by yelling.
I’ve got more!
Aw man...
Huh?
Let’s stop here for today, I can’t see the ball anymore.
We’ll start again tomorrow!
What are you guys doing?
Yo!
Want to try? Serious baseball.
Full swing, huh?
Haven’t done that in a while.
I guess this kind of thing’s okay too.
Come on!
You’re not hitting them at all!
Are you okay?
Let me see your hands.
No.
Show me!
I guess this is why...
I can’t do it after all...
This is enough for this dream.
Don’t give up!
Thanks for everything.
Why are you doing this for me?
Well, because you wanted to do it.
See it through to the end!
Me getting a home run would be a joke.
And even without hitting one, I was able to use my body to this extent.
That’s more than enough.
It felt like going to a club every day.
I had fun!
I told you, right?
I was paralyzed in the past, so this was amazingly fun.
So they’re all fulfilled?
Fulfilled? What is?
Everything you wanted to do when you couldn’t move.
Oh...
There’s one more.
What?
Marriage.
The ultimate happiness for a girl.
But I can’t do housework or cleaning or anything...
Actually, I can’t do anything by myself.
I’m nothing but trouble, dragging everyone else down.
I guess no one would want to take me...
God is pretty mean....
My happiness...
It was all taken from me.
That’s not true.
Then, senpai...
will you marry me?
I...
I’ll do it!
Hinata...
I’ll marry you.
I’m serious.
But...
You don’t know the real me...
No matter what happens to you in the real world,
I’ll marry you!
No matter what kind of sickness you have!
I can’t walk or even stand...
I said no matter what kind!!
Even if you can’t walk or stand,
or even if you can’t have kids!
I’ll still marry you!
I’ll always stay by your side.
The Yui I met here isn’t fake.
It’s the real Yui!
No matter where or how I meet you, I’ll fall in love with you.
If I can meet you again, against the 6 billion to 1 odds,
and even if your body can’t move,
I’ll marry you.
We won’t meet...
I’m always in bed at home.
I play baseball you know.
One day, I’ll smash a baseball through your window,
and when I go to get it, I’ll find you.
That’s how we’ll meet.
We’ll end up talking, we'll get along, and before I know it I’ll be visiting you every day.
What do you think?
Yeah...
Hey, when that happens...
My mom’s always working hard by herself to take care of me...
Could you help her out?
Leave it to me.
umaretekita koto mou koukai wa shinai
生まれてきた事も　後悔はしない
I have no regrets over what has been born
Thank goodness...
matsuri no ato mitai samishii kedo soro soro ikou
祭りの後みたい　寂しいけどそろそろ行こうー
Like the feeling after a festival, it’s sad but we should move on
doko made mo yuku yo koko de shitta koto
何処までも行くよ　ここで知った事
I’ll go anywhere, you know that
shiawase to iu yume wo kanaetemiseru yo
幸せという夢を　叶えてみせるよ
I’ll grant your dream of happiness
kimi to hanaretemo donna ni tooku nattemo
君と離れても　どんなに遠くなっても
Even if I’m parted from you, no matter how far away,
atarashii asa ni atashi wa ikiru yo
新しい朝に　私は生きるよ
I’ll be born again with the new morning
megutte nagarete toki wa usuroide
巡って流れて　時は移ろいで
The twists and turns of time will change
Are you okay with that?
mou nani ga atta ka omoidasenai kedo
もう何があったか　思い出せないけど
I don’t remember what happened anymore
Of course.
What are you going to do now?
me wo tojiteireba dareka soba ni ite
目を閉じていれば　誰か側に居て
But when I close my eyes, someone’s beside me
I’ll help you out till the end.
There are still lots of our friends who need help.
naze ka sore ga ima ichiban no takaramono
何故かそれが今　一番の宝物
Somehow right now, that’s my greatest treasure
I see.
What the hell did I just cut?
A shadow?
Explain it a bit more clearly.
That’s the only explanation I have.
Noda-san just ran here and defeated it.
Oyama-san by himself was in danger.
Danger?
What?
This world is developing an abnormality.
He did something again?
For him to drop his glasses...
Something’s coming, Otonashi-san!
Is this a bad dream?
I tried to save them too!
I don’t need backup!
This is too irregular..
Even being erased by Angel would be better than this!
You’ll disappear!
Dammit!
Yurippe!
I’ve got one!
Well, if we can, we’ll meet again.