One Two Three Four Fly
Fly
And cut!
Your next concert has already sold out,
and you're getting requests for encore performances...
Makoto?
Should I...
really keep singing?
This whole time, I was singing to find the princess,
but my music made no difference in the end.
That's not true!
It wasn't just for the princess.
What about all of your fans?
Every one of them enjoys your songs.
Cure Ace...
She was strong.
I can't imagine what we would have done without her assistance.
But Sword was the only Precure left in Trump Kingdom.
In that case...
who was she?
Well, she looked younger than us outside of her transformation.
Probably a third grade—
Fourth grader.
Oh, hello there, Cure Ace.
Hello.
And my name is Madoka Aguri.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Shocker!
Makopi Announces Her Retirement!
Ai!
You're wooking cute today!
Back to you all...
Yes?
What is this?
Sebastian's signature peach roll cake.
Please, help yourself.
Then I shall.
A-Are you okay?
It's scrumptious!
The sponginess of the cake shows it was baked to perfection!
The fresh cream is rich, but not overpowering!
The ripe peaches are luxuriantly scattered throughout!
It's all held gently together, and tastes of the first day of summer!
It's truly...
a harmony of love!
Outstanding.
You can sure tell a lot from a single bite, huh.
You must be a connoisseur of sweets, Aguri!
Your work could put the most skilled bakers to shame!
I could feel the love you have for delighting the eater! Bravo!
You honor me.
What's more, you gracefully accept a sudden visitor with no reservations.
Truly a professional butler!
Compared to that...
are you truly a professional?
I listened to your singing on TV yesterday.
To be honest, I was disappointed.
Hey, hold on!
Makopi's a super-popular singer!
Even critics recognize her talent!
She's the number one singer in Trump Kingdom!
I care not what the public thinks of her.
All I know is that I did not feel an ounce of love from the performance I saw.
Instead, I felt...
uncertainty.
A true pro would be ashamed to sing so half-heartedly.
Makopi's trying whole-heartedly!
She's a singer and a Precure!
She's an amateur at that as well!
Had I not saved you all before,
those Selfishes would have defeated you.
Am I wrong?
Well...
You girls are amateurish in every way.
You haven't the slightest chance of victory against King Selfish as you are now.
Thank you for the cake.
I will take my leave for today.
Huh? Wait!
Cure Ace!
Makopi, I'm really excited for your next concert!
I'm a failure of a pro...
Cure Ace was right.
I've been so uncertain lately.
I worry that there's no point in singing now that we've found the princess.
And I know that I shouldn't sing with my heart so clouded.
I'm going to quit singing.
I'll announce my retirement at my next concert.
Hold on, Makopi!
You can't quit!
I've made my choice.
I won't sing anymore.
And that's final!
Is she serious?
She can't do it!
She absolutely positively can't quit singing!
Um, are you really doing this?
Of course!
Operation "Make Her Want to Sing" is a go!
Makopi...
Makopi, you must not resign from singing.
You absolutely positively cann—
Mana, what are you doing?
Well, uh...
I figured you'd rethink your decision if the princess stopped you...
What gave me away?
The princess doesn't call me "Makopi."
My fatal flaw!
No, I think you had plenty.
The Yotsuba Philharmonic Orchestra shall provide live music!
Now, could you please sing?
I told you I'm not singing!
So, Operation "Live Band" failed too?
I thought the music would make her subconsciously want to sing...
No, it just makes it harder to.
I have to get in shape to beat the Selfish!
GoOOo to SLEeeEp, gOooO to sLeEEep,
ooOOn MoOommy's...
Oh, what should I do, Ai?
Makopi!
Ai just started crying.
Could you sing a lullaby?
I won't sing anymore.
I already told you.
But why?
Everyone wants to hear you sing!
There are other singers out there.
But wasn't it fun, Makopi?
You always look like you're enjoying yourself when you sing.
And somehow, seeing you like that warms my heart, and I have fun...
We don't have time for fun.
And I don't have time for singing.
Do those girls realize they're supposed to be Precures?
Everyone just wants you to keep singing.
Does that include you, Davi?
I want you to do what you want to do.
I'll be with you a hundred percent!
Now, goal!
Tastes awful.
'Cause you're not supposed to eat it.
What hick doesn't know what bowling is?
Who says we don't know?
Now be a dear and go find the princess at once!
Since when do you order us around?!
Since our orders came from King Selfish!
Very well. We'll go.
I'll remember this!
Intriguing...
Huh? Makopi isn't here yet?
She isn't answering her phone.
The concert is starting soon!
Sebastian!
On it.
Let's search too!
Makoto, it's time for the concert.
Yeah, I should go.
I'll go, and I'll announce...
my retirement.
Is there some trouble backstage?
I've got to get behind those scenes!
No, no, that'd be against the rules.
Aw, just get in.
I shall grant your desire!
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Hello, everyone!
Your host for tonight shall be yours truly, and...
Me, Selfish!
You all feelin' selfish tonight?
Yeah!
Hm, tough crowd.
Show's over!
Let's go!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
Oh poor mic who has lost its love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
There you are, Precures.
Investigate!
This is Makopi's stage!
Seeeeeelf!
It's a Selfish!
Girls!
Precure behind-the-scenes interview!
Are you dating anyone?
Huh?
What did you get on your last test?
That has nothing to do with our fight!
How much money do you have?
Hmm...
I've never counted.
Please answer honestly!
What is this, an interrogation?
Quite the invasion of privacy!
But this Selfish is strong!
Girls!
Ow...
Ai, why are you...
Here.
A Lovies?
Put that in me!
Dibbity dobbity Davi!
Kyupirapa kyupirapa!
A mirror?
Sword.
Princess! You've awakened?
No, not yet.
I speak to you now through Ai's powers.
I do not have long.
Cure Sword, you sang for me even in this world, did you not?
Both your songs and your feelings touched my heart.
Is that true?
I may be unable to move or speak,
but something gave me hope on the brink of despair.
Sword, that was your singing.
Hearing your songs warmed my heart and brought me cheer.
Thank you so much.
Princess...
I may not be able to awaken yet,
but I'll be fine with Jonathan by my side.
So I ask you, please, sing for your own sake.
My own... sake?
Enjoy it as you once did.
Your happiness gives me joy, too.
Please sing, Cure Sword.
Mana and the princess told you the same thing!
Mana, the princess, and even I all love your songs!
We want to hear you sing with joy!
I...
want to sing.
I'm with you a hundred percent!
Thank you...
It seems it's curtains for you Precures.
It's not over yet!
We shall never give in!
We'll never, ever let you ruin Makopi's concert!
Sword!
You girls have done so much...
Thank you.
Why do you sing despite being a Precure?
Can you call yourself a Precure?
I'm a singing Precure!
What could singing possibly accomplish?
It makes no difference in the end!
It might make no difference, and it might be pointless,
but... it's fun!
It makes me happy!
I love to sing, so I'll keep singing!
I love your singing, too!
Singing because you love singing?
Sounds rather selfish to me.
Maybe.
But there are people who support me regardless.
So for their sake, and my own, I'll keep singing!
It seems your love has awakened, Cure Sword.
The Precure's power is born from love.
Pursuing a passion with all your heart is love as well.
Love...
Your uncertainty hindered the power of your love,
but you've overcome your troubles,
and unlocked a new power with an even deeper love!
Well done.
The Precure's Five Vows!
First!
Love is meant to be given!
Your songs give love to the world.
Please, continue to let the world listen to your songs of love!
Sure.
Ai, let's go!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Beauty is the mark of the righteous!
With a single wink,
I shall pierce your heart!
What's your favorite sna—
Hey!
I'm the star here!
I will not be upstaged!
Your lukewarm show need not go on.
Your performance has no love!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
I'm stuck-fish!
Sword, now is your chance!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Selfiiiiish!
Love love loooove!
Not bad.
This might be fun.
Makopi really is amazing!
Her songs can make so many people smile!
They can.
And smiles make Egogy disappear.
Makopi's songs might be saving the world!
Her singing is overflowing with love.
Bravo!
I love to sing!
Singing makes me feel ecstatic, happy, and blessed!
I want you all to feel the same way.
So I'll keep singing!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Breaking news!
Alice's butler created an artificial Commune!
Artificial Commune?
It's an amazing invention that turns anyone into a Precure!
My name is Cure Sebastian.
I am here to be of service to Madam.
Wow!
He really transformed!
Huh? Another heroine shows up like a bolt from the blue?
Who's she?
Dokidoki Precure:
A Gorgeous Transformation!
A New Heroine Arrives?!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!