[NARRATOR]
Backed up by the newly restored
and automail equipped Lan Fan,
Ed battles the Homunculus
known as Pride.
As the fierce battle rages
towards the Promised Day,
Ed manages to safely retrieve
Al from Pride's clutches.
Faced with the possibility
of losing the fight,
Pride devours Gluttony in order
to obtain his abilities.
Elsewhere, Colonel
Mustang joins up with
Lieutenant Hawkeye to lead his
subordinates on a mission
to kidnap the Fuhrer's wife
and take her as their hostage.
[HOHENHEIM]
Al... Can you
hear me?
Come on...
Wake up!
Alphonse!
[PRIDE SNIFFS]
I know that smell.
[PRIDE]
Tell me something, Edward.
Do you think your
father would step forward
to save you if I chopped
off one of your limbs?
[ED GRUNTING]
[ED SCREAMING]
[ED YELLS]
[ED GROWLS]
[PRIDE LAUGHS]
Look out!
[ED YELLS]
[GREED GRUNTING]
[LAN FAN]
Young Lord!
Not quite.
The name's Greed.
[LAN FAN GASPS]
It's you.
Give the Prince
his body back!
Now why would I wanna do
something like that...?
Oh, boy.
Heads up!
[LAN FAN GROANS IN PAIN]
[ED]
You alright?!
[LAN FAN GASPS]
[LAN FAN YELLS]
[ED GRUNTS]
I didn't ask
for your help.
Oh, shut up...
Your arm obviously
hasn't healed yet.
[LAN FAN GASPS]
I can take care of myself.
Then prove it to me and
start acting like you can.
We're gonna need
your help tomorrow.
[LAN FAN GASPS]
[HEINKEL GRUNTING]
[GREED YELLS]
Get him
out of here!
Sorry I couldn't kill
the little bastard.
[GREED LAUGHS]
Don't sweat it.
I can't exactly
fault you for that one.
Even I consider
him to be a monster.
[HOHENHEIM]
Wake up... Alphonse!
[AL]
What...? Dad?
Hey.
[METAL CLANKS]
So uh... Wait, I thought
you were in... Is this Kanama?
That it is.
But I was in the east...
So how did I...
[AL GASPS]
That's right...! Pride!
Dad... The Homunculus Pride...
He took control of my body!
I know... Mr. Gorius
told me all about it.
[DARIUS]
It's Darius.
It was... it was like he
was manipulating my soul...
I feel violated.
The Homunculi are
basically your relatives.
They're like second
generation clones of me...
So they might be able to
interfere with your seal
since we share the same blood.
[BUSHES RUSTLING]
[AL]
Old man Fu?
[FU BREATHING HEAVILY]
Can you clean and
dress this man's wounds?
How's everything
going over there?
[FU]
I'm guessing you
must be Edward's father?
That's correct.
[FU GRUNTS]
That shadow monster devoured
the fat Homunculus whole...
and he's overpowering us.
Greed and Edward are doing
everything they can...
but I don't know how
long they can last.
[AL THINKING]
This is all my fault...
None of this would've happened
if I hadn't let Pride catch me.
[FU]
The fires have given him all
the light he could wish for
and I'm out
of flash bombs...
We need a new
plan and fast.
And not
just for us.
[DARIUS]
The slum dwellers
are gonna be
headed straight for
Pride any minute now.
[AL]
Hey, Dad?
You're a pretty
brilliant alchemist, right?
I guess...
I know a thing or two.
I've got an idea,
but I'm gonna need
your help to pull it off.
[ED AND GREED YELL]
Now then...
I can see you more clearly
without those trees in the way.
[LAN FAN GASPS]
There's not much point in
trying to hide from me...
I can smell
each move you make.
[GREED GRUNTS]
[GREED]
Dammit... You still
breathin' over there?
Does wheezing count?
This isn't really the time
to worry about others,
is it, Greed...?
As soft as
you've become...
I wonder how much
longer you can survive?
Shut up, you beast.
What a horrific thing to say
to your own brother, Greed...
Honestly...
I might have to eat you.
I promise that I won't
go down easy... Brother.
[PRIDE SNIFFS]
[PRIDE]
Oh... So you've chosen
to show yourself.
Eh, Hohenheim?
The hero always waits
until the last second
to make his move.
Hero...? Interesting...
You must think
you can defeat me.
[HOHENHEIM]
No, I'd never think that.
I'm not dumb enough
to try and fight you.
[PRIDE THINKING]
What could he possibly
be thinking...?
He must be
plotting something.
Here he comes!
[AL YELLS]
Are you joking...?
This was your pathetic plan?
You should have run
when you had the chance.
[LOUD THUD]
[METAL CLANKS]
Al, no!
[PRIDE LAUGHS]
[PRIDE]
It seems as though your son
enjoys being held hostage.
It's either that,
or he's supremely stupid.
That's crossing a line, Pride.
Don't ever mock my son.
[LOUD ELECTRICAL SOUNDS]
[ED GASPS]
[PRIDE GASPS]
[PRIDE GRUNTS ANGRILY]
Hohenheim!
[GREED]
That's amazing.
He actually managed
to confine Pride.
[GREED LAUGHS]
What the hell are
you doing...?!
Al's trapped in there
with that monster...!
How could you do
something like that?!
It wasn't my idea.
Al was the one
who suggested this.
[ED GASPS]
[AL LAUGHS]
[AL]
You fell for it...!
You can't use your
powers in this darkness.
I don't see why
you're laughing...
You're trapped inside
this thing too...
As soon as you try to
make an opening to leave,
I'll slice you into
little pieces...
[AL]
I don't remember saying
anything about leaving.
Let's have a little test
of endurance, Selim...
Oh, sorry. Would you prefer
to be called Pride...?
Ya'see, Pride, my body doesn't
need oxygen or light or food.
I'm perfectly
comfortable right here
until the Promised Day is over.
And I'm gonna make sure that
you stay put no matter what.
[HOHENHEIM]
It would've been nearly
impossible to defeat Pride...
And it was only
a matter of time
before the fight
spread to the slums...
Since we knew we
couldn't defeat him...
I acted as a decoy
and we imprisoned him.
We've bought
ourselves enough time
to figure out how
to destroy him.
[ED]
Well you could've at least
told me what you were--
Your brother
told me not to...
He said that you'd be
against it... Okay?
[ED GASPS]
Al came up with this plan
because it was the only way
to make sure everyone
would survive...
Try to understand.
Now... Let's get to work
putting these fires out.
[ED]
Al!
[AL GASPS]
[AL]
Brother!
Hey, Al!
[AL]
Sorry, Brother...
it's not much of reunion, huh?
But... This is all my fault
so I had to do something.
And besides... I only have to
stay in here for one day...
I promise I'll be
okay, Brother.
So Lust is dead...
Envy's gone... Gluttony's eaten.
Wrath is at eastern command...
and they've got
Pride under lockdown.
[GREED GRUNTS]
So that means
Sloth and Pops
are the only ones
watching over Central.
Hey, Greed...
What the hell are you planning?
[GREED LAUGHS]
[GREED]
I've told you.
I'm planning on
ruling the entire world.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[HOMELESS MAN 1]
Am I going crazy, or
have you guys noticed
all the Ishvalans
around lately?
No, you're right. There's a
small army of them holed up
in those buildings out
to the west of town.
And speakin' of Ishvalans,
ya have to wonder
what ever happened
to that fellow
with the x-shaped
scar across his face.
[ALL THREE MEN GASP]
[HOMELESS MAN 1]
Well, I guess you
can ask him yourself.
[HOMELESS MAN 2]
Speak of the devil
and he shall appear.
[SCAR]
Any of you know how to
get to the Kanama slums?
[HOMELESS MAN 1]
Yeah, sure... Kanama is
just south of the city...
right on the outskirts
of the forest.
Is that so...
thank you.
[HOMELESS MAN 2]
Did that little girl ever
meet back up with you guys?
You know,
the one that always
carried that cat
around with her...
She passed through here
again just a few weeks back.
She did what?
[GERSO]
It sounds like she didn't
go back to Xing after all.
[ZAMPANO]
What the hell
is that girl doing?
[HOMELESS MAN 4]
Well, well... You boys
out celebrating tonight?
Why...? What's
to celebrate?
You can drop the act...
I know you were behind
blowing up the train
Bradley was on.
What was that?
So you...
You weren't behind it?
[SCAR]
It's news to us.
Well, huh...
I just assumed you must've
led the other Ishvalans
to take your revenge
on King Bradley.
All that stuff about
them bein' terrorists
is nothin' but
paranoid nonsense.
My brothers would never lower
themselves to such cowardice.
They're your allies...
And this country will soon see
them as heroes, not terrorists.
[KIMBLEE HUMMING]
[KIMBLEE]
I need to learn to
draw the line somewhere
when it comes to my job.
I spent a fortune having
this suit tailor-made
and now it's filthy.
And the fun isn't even scheduled
to start until the sun's up.
[AL]
That's pointless.
I doubt my dad would've
made the walls thin enough
for a child
to tunnel out.
It's not that hard
to surprise you
when you think so
little of us humans.
You think you've got
us all figured out.
But you don't know
a thing about us...
You're too arrogant to see that
things might not go your way.
Like your plan
to use us...
It was too sloppy
to actually work.
And how's that?
Well... The plan
needed us, right...?
As your
sacrifices...?
The whole thing hinged on
us doing what you wanted...
But what if we
had simply decided
to run away to a
different country...?
That's all it
would've taken,
and your entire
plan falls apart.
[PRIDE]
True... And there are some
humans selfish enough
who would've done exactly
what you said... But then...
Not all...
Just look at Wrath's wife.
There was a time when we
took a trip to the city
and I was almost run
over by a car...
The car swerved of course...
but not before
she risked her life
trying to shield
me with her body.
She had no idea that I could've
easily protected myself...
but I was genuinely shocked
by her selfless
concern for my safety.
I've always known what
it was to have a father...
but I have never had what
you would call a mother...
I was quite intrigued by her
and how she cared for me...
And I realized what it was
like to have a mother.
When you say Wrath's wife...
You mean Mrs. Bradley, right?
Yes, that is correct.
[METAL CLANKS]
How could you
deceive her all this time?
I won't deny that I was
just playing house with her.
[METAL CLANKS]
But I also can't deny
that my time spent with
her has been pleasant.
I quite liked it.
[AL]
But then--
[PRIDE]
As I was saying...
There are a handful of
humans like Wrath's wife...
They're willing to
give up their own lives...
In order to protect the
things they care about.
[METAL CLANKS]
And one step up from them we
have you and your brother...
chosen to be sacrifices
for the infinite strength
of your spirits...
You never would have fled
and abandoned this country...
In fact, you even went so far
as to bring the fight to us.
[METAL CLANKS]
So explain to me again...
How were our plans so sloppy?
[METAL CLANKS]
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel?
We should start
getting ready.
[ROY]
Right.
[HAWKEYE STAMMERS]
Alright then...
Let's move out.
[ZAMPANO]
What happened here?
It's been cleared
to the ground...
the whole area...
And what
caused that?
That's not natural.
[DARIUS]
Hey, is that
Gerso and Zampano?
[ZAMPANO]
What the.... Darius?!
[LOUD THUD]
Let me take a guess...
Kimblee ordered you to
track us down and kill us,
now didn't he?
[DARIUS]
Huh?!
You're joking, right...?
You can't really still think
that we're working for Kimblee?
No way,
of course not...
And as soon as we start
trusting you, you'll kill us.
I would
never do that!
[GERSO]
I'm not fallin' for it...
I bet Heinkel's hiding
around here somewhere,
just waiting for
a chance to ambush us.
[ED]
Dr. Marcoh!
[DARIUS]
You idiot!
[GERSO]
You're the idiot!
[MARCOH]
Oh, Edward!
So you're still
working with Scar.
I'm sorry to have to spring
this on you right away,
but we really need to get--
Hey, Piggy,
Gorilla, and Fatty!
Shut up
and stop fighting!
[ALL THREE MEN]
You wanna mess
with us, shorty?!
[GERSO]
So you really did quit...?
I guess we all ditched him
around the same time then.
Yeah, sounds
like it...
It was all too
obvious that Kimblee
considered us
to be expendable.
[ALL THREE MEN]
That's the truth.
We may be considered
fugitives now,
but you know what...?
I've got
no complaints.
Same here...
And no matter what...
...I know for
a fact that these guys
would never
abandon us.
[GERSO]
Once the sun comes up...
things are gonna get rough.
I know...
Let's just hope that everyone
makes it through the day alive.
[HEINKEL]
Huh...?
Looks like they've
wrapped up their meeting.
[DARIUS]
Where'd the old
guy head off to?
He's gonna do
some recon in Central.
By himself?
Yeah...
He pointed out
that he's the only one who's
kept his identity hidden...
So it'll be easier for him
to infiltrate the city.
[ED]
He also said that he'd
do his best to update us
on Colonel Mustang's actions.
But I'm kind of
getting the feeling that
he's mostly
concerned about Ling.
Sure... That
makes sense.
So you're all finished
discussing things
with Scar
and the others?
That's right.
We've figured
out our strategy.
That so...?
It's almost time, huh?
[GERSO]
Your younger brother's
sure got some serious guts.
[DARIUS]
Trapped in total darkness
with that monster?
I think that I'd lose my
mind if I were in his place.
Yeah.
Al's doing everything
possible to keep us safe...
The rest of it...
Well that's up to us.
[ED THINKING]
The sun has risen...
The Promised Day's begun.
[BROSH'S SISTER]
Brother! Get up, Brother...!
It's time for you
to wake up, Denny!
Pipe down already...
[BROSH]
What time is it?
You have to
get up now...
And hurry up or
you're gonna miss it.
What am I missing...?
Other than sleep?
The solar eclipse!
A solar eclipse?
Oh, man... It's not as
late as you think it is...
I've got plenty of time to
sleep before it starts.
Hey, don't look at the sun...!
You'll blind yourself!
I'm not stupid, Denny.
[BROSH AND HIS SISTER SIGH]
Hey quick,
come check this out!
It looks like there's
a building on fire!
[BROSH GASPS]
[EXPLOSION IN THE DISTANCE]
Do not go outside
the house today, alright?
[EXPLOSION]
[SUBORDINATE 1]
Cedi Squad is currently
engaged in combat
with Mustang's group
in the western sector.
However...
It appears that they've taken
the Fuhrer's wife hostage...
Which has left us
unable to retaliate, sir.
So...?
Go ahead and attack.
Sir?
The only one we need
alive is Roy Mustang...
The Fuhrer's wife
is expendable.
Eliminate her along with
Mustang's subordinates.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[HEAD SOLDIER]
Freeze!
Are you going to shoot?
The only one we need
alive is Mustang...
Kill the rest.
[BRADLEY'S WIFE GASPS]
[GUNSHOT]
[MORE GUNSHOTS]
[NARRATOR]
After living in peace for so
long, the citizens of Amestris
are blind to the impending
peril beneath their feet.
They can't even begin to
imagine their approaching doom.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood,
Episode Fifty:
Upheaval in Central.
The weak shall lie
down and surrender
while the strong trample
over their bodies...
This is the simple fact of war.