Negi has learned of the vampire girl’s sad past.
Should she get her hands on Negi’s blood, her magic imprisonment will disappear.
And the vampire girl will be set free to live outside of the Academy borders. The vampire will be set free in a peaceful town.
We must not let her free.
Takamichi…
What are you thinking, Negi?
Geez, you need to stop lazing around, Chamo!
How dare you underestimate me, Takamichi!
So you came after all, Evangeline.
I can’t let you meet Negi-kun.
I’m not the one you should be after.
They were still roaming around campus at this hour.
So I showed them that playing in the dark is dangerous.
Takahata-sensei!
Get off me! Hey!
No means yes...
You should get rid of this ring!
Hey! Give that back!
We will give it back if you win a game of old maid, Sensei.
What in the world are you talking about?!
Negi-kun!
Let go of Iinchou-san and the others now.
That's up to you.
Don’t be fooled! A vampire’s magic naturally disappears at dawn!
Shut it, Takamichi!
Run! Run while you still can, Negi-kun!
You think you can run away?!
Negi-kun…
Geez, we came because you said it was an emergency!
Well, isn’t it?! They released a used copy of it!
And I finally bought it! Zombie Rider: Son-in-Law Chapter! I’m so happy!
What do you mean “I finally bought it!”? You borrowed the money from Konoka-ojousama!
I said I’d pay her back next month!
Calling us out for something like this…What are we to do if we stay past curfew?!
Konoka, have you played this before? It's awesome!
Ah, no, I’m okay…
Listen to me! If Konoka-ojousama’s character is damaged from this, you’ll be held responsible!
You can become the Master of Zombies if you take over the castle, and you'll get 108 Bonnou Boys as your henchmen.
Even if you say that…
Would you just LISTEEEEEEN?!
Ah, Negi.
Eh? Negi-kun? Where?
Ah, no, no! I mean… I forgot to buy some spring onions!
Sorry, I gotta go get some. You’ll have to head on home without me!
Ah, I’ll even leave this to you!
Wai-! Asuna!
Geez, she’s always leaving me behind…
But oh? She doesn’t even know how to cook; what she want with spring onions?
Whaddya think, Secchan?
Ah ha, the Bonnou Boys signifies the amount of Bonnous.
But why a son-in-law?
Secchan?
Er, I mean… What’s a Master of Zombie, anyway?! Sounds like a bunch of stupid stuff. It really is…! This thing!
That’s Asuna’s…!
Eh?! Oh my gosh! I’ll get it back!
Secchan, if you wanna play the game, then don’t be afraid to honestly say so!
Son-in-law...
Negi… When we went together it was last night’s…
So you wanna try to run away and learn the truth, eh?
I’m not running away; I just wanted to talk to you personally.
Talk to me, eh?
I’ve heard about your form from Takamichi. He even said that my father used his magic to imprison you.
Really now? …So?
Evangeline-san… I don’t mind giving my blood to you.
Oh?
But, I want you to promise me something.
Promise what?
Even if I manage to set you free, promise me that you won’t attack anyone ever again.
It’s been 15 years…since they took away your magic power.
They wouldn’t even let you go past the barrier they made… Wasn’t that painful for you?
So please, allow me to free you! I want to set you free!
Aren’t you the kind one. Alright…
Really?!
…or so I’d like to say. I’m sorry you have to pity me, little one.
Did you really think I’d promise you?! Don’t make me laugh!
Listen here; I’m a vampire!
That freaking hurt!
Is that a shoe?!
Negi!
Asuna-san!
Hey, Dracula! Let go of Negi right now!
Why you… don’t interfere!
W-why you...! Not the face!
Didn’t I tell you… to let go of Negi!?
Wah! No! Stop it!
She’s really gonna throw that?!
Power!
Take that!
Asuna-san!
Negi! Are you okay?
Yes, I am! Thanks a lot!
Um… Sure, I guess.
How dare you underestimate me.
Evangeline-san!
Evangeline? How’s that her?
She’s transformed herself into a vampire, thanks to her magic.
It lit up!
That’s…
The lake…
She can use frost spells...
Don’t think that I spent these 15 years here sitting around peaceful and quiet!
Watch out!
Ow!
Asuna-san!
Owww…
Are you okay?!
Good grief, that was dangerous, Evangeline!
I don’t care if you’ve got this hot bod from your magic; there’re still things you can and can’t do!
This is payback!
Chachamaru-san!
What? You can move now?
Yes. Thanks to you.
Let go of me, Chachamaru! Hey, let go!
Those who try to hurt my master will be eliminated, regardless if she’s a classmate.
Asuna-san!
Hmph. So he’s the type to run away when he can. Let’s go, Chachamaru.
Yes, Master.
Asuna-san! Asuna-san!
Asuna-san! Get a hold of yourself!
You have no choice but to do a provisional contract, Aniki!
There you are, Chamo-kun!
I was waiting for the right moment.
In any case, Aniki, do a provisional contract! Do it!
A provisional contract? With Asuna-san…?
Eh… but…
No time to be hot n’ bothered! The enemy’s nearing!
You’re right. We probably have no other choice.
Asuna-san…
That’s my Ane-san! You’re quick to pick up!
Negi, if we don’t do this we can’t win. Make a provisional contract with me!
Um…
HURRY UP!
Okay!
Ack! Up there!
I found you~
Can’t run now!
Uhyaa~ My feet are so cold!
Hmm? Here, use my shoes.
Like hell I’ll wear ‘em!
Ah, I’m sorry.
But… thanks anyway.
Asuna-san…
Great mood! Okay, let’s get started on that provisional contract asap!
PACTIO!
Wow, it’s so warm…
Magic from the heart gives off heat.
Wow… it feels great!
Save the explanations! We’ve got something to take care of and fast!
Oh, that’s right.
Now, Ane-san! Kiss him! Kiss him! Just kiss him already! Kiss! Kiss!
Stop it with the “Kiss kiss” crap, you stupid rat!
I told you, I’m not a rat! You violent girl!
Enemy detected.
Good.
Um… I’m sorry. I mean it.
Asuna-san, it’s coming!
Eh? Oh, crap!
WROOOOOOOOONG!
You can’t kiss him there! Give him a real kiss! It ain’t gonna work if you don’t kiss his lips!
Eh? His lips?
Forget it!
Does it look like I care?!
Think about other people! This’ll be my first kiss, you know!
No way. Ane-san, how old are you?
Noisy brat!
Oh, crap!
Aigh, Geez!
Whoo! You did it, Ane-san!
Provisional Contract Line!
Hmph. Exchanged a provisional contract, eh?
Wait a sec! I haven’t changed a bit!
No, you have.
Partner: Kagurazaka Asuna. Show me the power within you!
Contract… Activate!
Uwaaah! Freaking awesome!
This is… I feel like I’m full of power all of a sudden!
I can win. With this, I can win!
You’re pretty damn good.
Why, thank you.
You’ve done it now!
You think you can run away?!
W-wait! Ane-san!
Wait, Chachamaru!
Ane-san! Where’re you going?! What’re ya gonna do if you just leave your partner Negi alone?!
Oiiiii!... she’s gone.
She's always doing what she wants and leaves us out of it.
No point in doing a provisional contract now!
What a dependable partner you have, eh Negi?
Now… shall I take your blood now?
You wouldn’t keep that promise, would you?
I live the way I want to. That’s the freedom I wish for.
Fine…
Aniki!
Chamo-kun, it’s going to get bad, so steer clear.
Yessir.
You may be the son of the Thousand Master… but in the end, you’re still a mere child.
Now, allow me to take it… I can finally indulge in my newfound freedom!
Aniki!
Ow ow ow ow ow!
Why you little-!
That hurts!
Evangeline-san!
Thousand Master! I’ll never forgive you!
Mark my words, I’ll get my revenge someday!
Open your eyes, Evangeline.
Live in the light. Feel the light. Your future lies there.
The light… it’s so warm…
Why did you save me?
Well, you are my student, aren’t you, Evangeline-san?
What? It’s over already?
Dean, Takamichi.
Evangeline, now you understand why you were put here.
Though, your heart already knew.
What do you mean?
Why, last night, you brought the damaged Chachamaru in for repair. You would have never done so in the past.
Um, School Dean, I don’t think I ever-
Live in the light. Feel the light. Your future lies there.
The light, eh?
Asuna-san!
It seems her energy has drained.
Waah, I’m hungry! I can’t move!
Chachamaru, we’re going.
Yes, master.
Evangeline-san!
Don’t get the wrong idea, Negi. It’s not like I gave up in getting your blood.
I suggest you be careful on the next full moon.
Evangeline-san…
It’ll be fine, Negi-kun.
Takamichi…
In any case, Negi, do something about that!
Negi, it seems like you’re working hard and doing just fine.
I’m actually kind of surprised.
You may be a little angry if I said this...
but I thought I’d get a letter from you right away, saying that you’d want to go back to Wales.
I’m so glad that you’ve met wonderful people over there. It makes me happy to know.
Oh, that’s right! I got a letter from Anya, who is in London right now. She seems to be happy and doing just fine as well!
She said that she’d never lose to you, Negi.
I should conclude this now. I hope your training goes well! I love you, Negi.
Onee-chan…
Good morning, everyone!
From here on out, you are all 9th graders!
It’s a pleasure to be with you for another year!
The pleasure’s ours, Negi-sensei!
Negi Springfield, child middle school teacher and mage extraordinaire!
This is where our story begins!
Why? Why can’t I ever finish my introduction?!
Man, don’t cry…
We don’t have time for this, de gozaru.
We still have an enemy waiting for us, aru!
For the time being, we should summon a robot.
But me! I’m just… I’m just a…
Okay! Makie, how about you start out the introductions? Right?
Oh, that is a great idea...
I can lead the introductions? Really?!
If you want. We’re not gonna fuss over a minor order change de gozaru.
Thanks, you guys!
Now then, one more time!
Mahora Sentai Baka Ranger!
Everyone gets along! Baka Pi-
The robot has arrived.