Five million dollars!
Fucked around in my territory and stole five million.
There's no way I can forgive whoever did it.
Catch whoever did it and bring them to me at once.
If needed,
kill them.
Thanks, Reiji.
This has always been my dream!
Making a mountain of burgers and stuffing myself full with it!
Anyway, Cal,
back to what we were talking about.
You saw the person who killed Judy?
You know, I'm thinking about what I should do about that.
What?
Can we really avenge Judy?
How?
I mean, they have machine guns.
You don't believe in me?
Well, you don't look strong at all.
I see.
So you don't believe in me.
But don't worry.
I won't be the one doing it.
I'm going to ask my friend.
Friend?
Yeah.
You have a friend who's capable of doing it?
I might not seem like it, but I know a lot of people.
As long as my friend knows the offender's looks and clothing, he can find them.
So tell me about the killer-
I want to see it.
What?
I want to see the moment when Judy gets avenged with my own eyes.
Hey, Reiji, can you let me meet your friend?
No.
Why?
Let me ask your friend with you!
Can I?
This isn't a world that outsiders can interfere in.
But-
No means no.
Sorry, Cal, but...
OK, fine, I lose.
I'll see if I can get my friend to see you.
Really?
Yeah, but-
Then we'll talk about this when we see your friend.
But those people can't be contacted on a whim.
Tonight, I'll try and find their contacts.
We'll continue our conversation tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Is something wrong?
I got kicked out this morning because Judy owes a lot of rent.
Can I stay at your place tonight?
How is it, Lizzie?
Is the investigation going well?
Phantom went to search for that girl.
I'm doing my own thing by myself.
Well, just wait a little longer.
I'm looking forward to your good news.
Who is it that's interfering with our business?
The Godoh Group is absolutely necessary for me to gain a standing in Inferno.
I can't stumble because of such things.
So this is where you live.
Somehow it makes me feel lonely.
It's more than enough to live in.
It's empty.
What are you doing?
Throwing away these leftover hamburgers is a waste.
Don't tell me you're going to stay here until you've finished them.
Is something wrong?
No, your bedroom is over there.
This bed is yours.
Someone used to live with you before?
Why do you ask?
I just have a feeling.
It was a long time ago.
Your girlfriend?
No.
Oh yeah,
can I borrow your shower?
That means I just have to pretend to be that friend of yours, right?
Yeah, please.
All right. Having you owe me one isn't a bad thing.
So, does that girl really know something about it?
I don't know.
What? That's such an unreliable answer.
Reiji!
Sorry, I forgot my towel.
I'll get one for you right now.
What?
Nothing.
It's just that the idea of the great Phantom being toyed around by a little girl is funny.
Don't try anything funny just because you're letting her stay at your-
He hung up.
What are you investigating by sneaking around in my backyard?
So? Lizzie?
Really?
Yeah, it looks like she's going to meet us.
She'll contact us tomorrow.
Thank goodness...
Hey Reiji, do you have any family?
Family?
They're in heaven.
Really?
Yeah.
Just like me.
Are your parents already...
I have no idea.
I ran away from my bastard old man,
and then Judy took me in.
If she hadn't, I'd be dead already.
So that's why you're siblings?
Yup, she's my only family.
But Judy died...
Sorry.
It's all right.
What's going to happen to me now that Judy's dead?
Where should I go?
What should I do?
I don't have any idea.
I was like you once, not knowing what to do.
There are many ways to die.
There are people who die in pain,
and there are also people who are slowly forgotten without anyone grieving for them.
Judy has you crying for her, so that means she's blessed.
Really?
Yeah.
What's going to happen to me now?
Where should I go?
What should I do?
I don't have any idea.
So is the witness in here?
Your place is a pretty ugly sight.
Don't you think so, Phantom?
May I ask what business you have here?
Don't act so cold.
I saw Lizzie sneaking around getting some street rats to investigate,
and I found out quite a few interesting things.
Let me talk to that girl. I'll make her spit out everything she knows.
Is she in there?
She doesn't know anything.
Move.
An outsider like her shouldn't be able to see anything at such a dark place.
She lied about seeing the killer.
Move.
Phantom!
Oh?
So you're going to protect her even if it means you have to cause a bloodbath?
Now I want to see her even more.
This is exactly what I thought.
You and Claudia are definitely plotting something.
That's a misunderstanding.
Come to HQ tomorrow.
At ten.
I'll have you guys spit out everything in front of McGuire.
We'll find out who the real traitor is.
Sorry, Phantom.
I couldn't back my way out of it.
Don't worry.
But isn't this bad?
How are you going to convince them tomorrow?
I'll try my best to explain.
So that girl really doesn't...
Yeah, she doesn't know anything.
I see.
You don't know anything, right, Cal?
Tell me in detail.
On that night...
Judy?
Judy?!
And that's all I remember...
As I expected.
So you saw through my lie.
That guy just then was Isaac Wisemel, right?
The Bloodies' leader.
Yeah.
Why did you cover for me?
Everyone called you Phantom, right?
I heard about it from Judy's friends.
You're the one that kills people in American gangs.
So you're a true assassin, right?
You're an assassin, right?
The assassin, Phantom.
Yeah, that's right.
Cal?
This is...
This is the money that the yakuza was carrying.
There's five million here.
So you stole it?
I didn't steal it!
I didn't even use a cent of this dirty money!
I was searching for someone like you.
Someone who'd help me as long as they're paid.
Reiji, you're Phantom, right?
Please! Kill them all!
The guys who were at the alley last night, the guys who shot,
and the guys who were supposed to retrieve the money.
Kill all the people who caused Judy's death...
Can you do it?
I won't charge you that much.
We'll talk about this tomorrow.
I'm sorry for lying.
Same here.
The situation is tilting toward the bad side.
The shooters weren't found, but the five million were.
If the organization finds this money, I'll have no excuse.
Kill all the people who caused Judy's death...
What should I do?
How can I reconcile with both Cal and the organization?
What is this, Reiji?
I can't explain to you here.
If we talk alone, we'll just provoke Wisemel's suspicion.
I'll explain in front of everyone.
Let's hear your explanation, Phantom.
Yes.
First, let me resolve this misunderstanding.
What do you mean?
There is no doubt I was hiding the so-called female witness.
However, she's just a relative of a victim who happened to be passing by.
She doesn't know anything.
Why are you so sure?
I am Phantom, and thus, I am skilled at such things.
What a cheap excuse.
I think so, too.
It's pointless since there's no evidence.
Did you use truth serum?
No.
Recording data?
None.
That means you're asking us to trust you on your word?
Yes.
Give up, Phantom.
Ms. McCunnen, what do you think?
That's all you've got?
I have a reason why I didn't use truth serum.
Oh? Is that enough of a reason to make you point your gun at Isaac?
Yes.
Let me hear it.
I don't want to ruin her.
Don't give me that humanism crap.
No.
I saw a different kind of potential in that girl.
I didn't want to ruin that.
Potential?
Yes. She has a rare quality about her.
You could call it talent.
An intense desire to kill.
Hell-like isolation.
A ghost without a place to live.
Talent... I've heard such words before.
So you mean you want to train that girl into a hitman?
Yes.
She might be able to become a worthy assistant in the future.
And the proof of that girl's talent?
Just a hunch.
Quit fucking around, you bastard!
This isn't something that can be explained by words.
Perhaps it can't be understood by humans who have high suspicions and are blindfolded.
Phantom!
I have a question.
Do you really want a new assistant that much?
Are there any problems with working with Lizzie?
Well, there certainly are a lot of problems.
Phantom and I are on totally different levels.
Phantom is a great genius and I'm just an ordinary person.
If there's a partner he can set his eyes on,
I'd like to switch places as soon as possible.
The prostitute who died with the yakuza is named Judy Devens.
Are you sure she's not related to this event?
Yes.
She's as innocent as Snow White.
I've looked into it thoroughly.
What do you think, Isaac?
Are you asking me to agree, Ray?!
If she doesn't show any results...
You know what to expect, right?
Yes.
Then let's see what she's made of.
What an interesting stage play, Reiji.
You won't fool me...
Don't think for a second that you've fooled me...!
You're that fox's bitch!
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, it was my fault anyways.
But...
I know.
There's no way you want to churn out more people like you.
It's a lie to cover up for that kid, right?
But the responsibility goes to you for selling her so much.
I know.
In the end, I didn't settle anything.
The shooters... The five million...
Avenging Judy...
What should I do?
That girl is most likely a genius.
But should I let her walk the same path as me?