Sensei, bye-bye!
Good-bye!
I guess... Evangeline-san didn't come to school today after all...
I guess they didn’t recover from yesterday’s damage…
Are you okay, Master?
That level of magic will have no effect on me.
That bastard…
For a fairy to have power so strong it can manipulate…
Maybe it does have some relation to the fact that the Star Crystal was stolen…
I have a feeling that some evil organization is lurking in the shadows.
Let’s investigate it, Chamo-kun.
Agreed, Aniki.
Hmm? What’s up with you, Honya-chan?
Honya-chan?
by Konoka
Ugh, I’m so tired…
Well, then!
Now that classes are officially over, I’ll try my damn hardest for the rest of the day!
the day!
So Asuna’s day starts after school.
Not listening in class anymore has made her pretty stupid.
Hey, Konoka, you’re gonna join me in a chupa-search, right?
Oh my, you’re always going at your own pace!
Ojou-sama, your fortune-telling studies are today.
Oh? Do I really?
Yes. And, Ojou-sama, you shouldn't be so involved in a dubious research society such as this one.
What do you mean “dubious”?! What part of a Chupacabra Research Society is “dubious”?!
Yeah, tell us! There was even a spotting of one in San Antonio!
I am responsible for Ojou-sama's safety and well-being.
So, Ojou-sama…
Okay, I’ll see ya later. Okay, Asuna?
If we discover a chupacabra, we're never gonna show you!
Well now, what am I supposed to do?
The traces of magic seem to be disappearing.
Don’t let your guard down, Aniki!
You’ll never know when the enemy will strike!
Wha-What the heck; it’s just Jou-chan!
You scared the crap out of us!
What’s wrong, Nodoka-san?
Uh… um…
Negi-sensei… what should I do?
Eh?
That is… I mean… since I’m your partner and all…
That’s right! Since you became a partner, we should tell you, Jou-chan!
Yes!
But, Chamo-kun, I don’t want Nodoka-san to be involved with dangerous things…
As yet, you let Asuna-anesan do it.
Well… you have a point, but…
Um… Tell me everything! If I can be of some help to Negi-sensei, I…!
Nodoka-san…
Oooh!
Here it is; the pride of the Astronomy Club - a planetary orbit model.
Whoa! What a device!
Such an exquisite mechanism…
This planetary globe will align the planets according to the time and date you enter.
C’mon, Chizuru-san; let me borrow it!
What are you doing, Ojou-sama?
I just figured I could use this to study my fortune telling is all.
‘Tis fate to get it right… ’Tis also fate to get it wrong.
Make~ it rain~
So is this how fortune telling is done?
Perhaps.
But, stars aren’t actually in the sky...
Natsumi, it’s all in your heart.
So don’t worry; you’ll be fine.
This isn’t turning into an answer, Chizu-nee!
Today, I would like to discuss a chupacabra’s favorite words!
Favorite words?
In order for us to lure the chupacabra out of hiding, naturally we have to say something to appeal to its sense of hearing!
You do have a point.
I agree-de gozaru.
Wait a sec…
When the heck did our group increase?
I knew it…
The era is leaning towards that of the chupacabra, you know!?
you know!?
I don’t think so, though.
It’s not like we all have a lot of free time.
What about you, Yuna?
Me too! I just took a break from basketball practice.
Then I would like to move forward!
What... does... a...
CHUPACABRALIKETOSAY!?
Effort!
Future!
Fighting Spirit!
Hmm, now…
50 yen discount!
50 yen discount?
Two for the price of one!
I kinda like that!
"Justice comes before personal feelings!"
Annals of the Three Kingdoms; I love that book!
Master Grade!
So you make model kits?
Maple grove leaf…
Like it’d know anything as old as that!
You just basically do what you saw yesterday.
Everything else is based on your talent.
Is that alright with you, Nodoka-san?
Yes. I’ll try my best!
Then here I go.
Partner: Miyazaki Nodoka. Show me the power within you!
Contract, activate!
Glasses?
Chamo-kun, what’s this…?
The Cosplay Card!
According to the Matsu-Take-Ume scale, this card's probably in the Take rank...
Is this… a diary?
I wonder what this is…
"I think there could've been more to that costume".
Chamo-kun wanted me to wear a slightly sexier costume!
"Why!? Why are my thoughts being revealed like this"!?
"Dang it, all my thoughts are gonna spill!
Chamo-kun’s getting distracted!"
"Ah! Oh crap! The more I worry about it, more thoughts come out!
Like the time I ate Aniki’s pudding
or the time I wet Ane-san’s bed
and blamed Aniki for it all!
Or the time I tried to propose to a pretty ermine, and she said, “Your hair sucks!”
and I felt so shocked from the rejection that my hair got that much worse!
Ah!! STOP IT!!! DO NOT REVEAL ANY MORE!!
Are you okay, Chamo-kun?!
When you do this… it's so relaxing.
Nice job, Jou-chan!
Your attack of words will even destroy rocks!
I can’t believe you can understand a target’s thoughts so well!
Wow… this is so much fun!
Ah… I wonder what Negi-sensei is thinking…
Seeing Nodoka-san with glasses on… she’s so cute!
What’s wrong, Nodoka-san?
N-nothing!
P-Perhaps… if I use this, will I be able to read Negi-sensei’s true feelings?
Negi-sensei!
Yes?
What is it?
Nodoka’s smiling face is so pretty!
Aaaaah, w-w-w-what do I do?!
Negi-sensei!
Yes?
Aigh, this is such a pain… if I like it, I should just tell her already!
Goodness gracious, poor Jou-chan is suffering from labor!
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
Negi-sensei’s feelings…
Nodoka-san is such a pleasant person. Like Nodoka-san, I-
Guess you’re at your time limit.
I wanted to read the rest of it, too…
She’s outta fuel!
Now, from here on out, it’s my turn.
Perfect! Today, Chiu is pretty, pretty, pretty!
Usually, a 9th grader such as myself doesn't stand out much...
But behind all that, I'm a super hacker who controls the internet world…
I’m the number one ‘net idol, Chiu!
In the personal studio which I built in my room…
I make self-portraits!
Then I use Photoshock to skillfully make my skin paler!
And then… I upload them to my blog!
Okay, all you freaking males; take a good look at ‘em!
All the world is praising me…
I’m so loved! Oh, the bliss!
My Net Idol Ranking is, of course…!
Rank... 1?
IT’S NOT!?
Who the hell surpassed me?!
“Cute Girls on the Block”?
Don’t tell me they’re real idols…
Eh? Mahora Academy Festival?
MIYAZAKI NODOKA!
She surpassed me…
I wasn't expecting such an ambush.
If that’s the case…
I'll just have to use my true skills.
I'll show you what a number one idol can do!
It’s no use…
If that’s the case…
I’ll obtain new software to counter all of this!
Better watch your back, Miyazaki Nodoka!
Whenever I activate the contract, it seems that you get hungrier.
I guess the partner’s brain power relies on the calories they consume, huh?
What’s up, Aniki?
Just now I felt…
Could it be that…
Ah! Negi-sensei!
Did I just doze off?
What are you all doing?
Tortoise Shell fortune telling.
Huh?
Konoka-san, in place of a turtle shell, put a chicken’s egg over heat and the egg exploded.
So, where is Ojou-sama?
She went back to her dorm. She said she was gonna change her clothes...
and get another egg.
My, my, I never thought that egg would explode on me!
I know; what a shock!
I think it exploded because there was only one there.
Next time, I’ll try and heat three at once!
No, don’t do that!
What’s that?
Konoka!
Asu… na...
Negi!
I wasn't expecting this!
Asuna-san!
Gotcha!
Partner: Kagurazaka Asuna. Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
It’s the Suka Card!
Suka Card?
Out of the three cards that are formed, one of them is a total hit-and-miss.
Eeeh?
Whaddya mean “hit-and-miss”!? I’m still strong with this on!
Just as I thought; it was that fairy’s doing!
What do we do, Aniki?
Setsuna-san!
Ojou-sama!
Se... cchan?
Negi-kun! Are you a…?
Are you alright, Konoka-san?
Yeah. Where’s Secchan?!
Secchan!
Are you okay, Secchan?
Yes; Do not worry about me.
Do you have any injuries, Ojou-sama?
Secchan…
Aniki, yet another person caught you using magic!
I couldn’t help it… it was an emergency…
We just have to make sure that those two don't know about it.
We saw it-mya!
Shi-Shichimi-san! Motsu-san!
Looks like someone unintentionally found out about your magic, mya!
Looks like we’ll have to send you back to the Magic Academy, mya!
Not only will we take away your mage certification, we’ll turn you into an animal, too!
In a good way!
No, please…!
Is that really, Negi-kun?
Negi-chan, you should become a cat, just like Shichimi, mya!
A frog’s lonely life is surprisingly fun. In a good way.
No, it’s not…
Wait just a second!
The truth is, these girls are Aniki’s partners, too!
They exchanged provisional contracts!
Lie…
Chamo-kun!
This excuse was also okay last time.
Oh really, mya?
Eep!
You said the same thing last time, mya.
Eep Eep!
Now I really wonder if those girls are really your partners, mya.
We’re not gonna take it this time unless you got proof!
In a good way.
Proof…?
We’ll have to see the power of your partner, mya!
W-What do we do?!
It’ll be okay, Aniki!
Chamo-kun!
If you turn into an ermine, I promise I’ll look after you.
Chamo-kun…
Is this enough evidence?
This isn’t much, but...
Please accept our apology.
Why, thank you; I’ll take care of it!
Effort!
Future!
50 yen discount!
I guess the chupacabra isn’t here…
Time sale might be better than a 50 yen discount! He might come out in a hurry.
Oh yeah!
New discounted prices for only 30 minutes!
I still have some time before Softmacho closes.
I have some points left in my card; it should be enough to buy new software.
So you can use magic after all, huh, Setsuna-san?
That was my ki. It's what the Shinmeiryuu techniques use; I have no affiliation with magic.
...and that's how Asuna-anesan and Nodoka-jouchan both became Aniki’s partners!
Oh, so that’s how it is!
Well, that's just the course of events...
Well, because of that course of events, both of you kissed Negi-kun!
Negi-kun! Make me your partner, too!
Really, Jou-chan?!
If I become your partner, I can use magic and fight, right?
Negi-kun, make a provisional contract with me! Should I pay something like a deposit?
No, you mustn’t!
Ojou-sama mustn’t stain her hands for such things!
Why not?
Because you have me already!
The Sakurazaki family has ordered me to protect you, even if it should cost me my life!
You have no reason whatsoever to obtain power in your hands.
Really?
Yes, really.
So if I’m in danger, you’d save me by volunteering yourself no matter what?
I would.
No matter what?
For sure.
I see.
Well, if that’s the case, then you leave me with no other choice!
Negi-kun!
Yes?
NOW!
Pactio!
Contract complete!
Ojou-sama, how could you-?
You see… I’m always putting you in some kind of trouble…
Ojou-sama…
I… want power, too…
If I did… I’d be able to protect you as well, Secchan.
What was that?
It’s coming.
Aniki! Over there!
Kaede-san!
Yuuna-san!
Chisame-san!
What’s up with all of ya? And what’s with the outfits?
What the heck? What’s going on?!
Aniki… this is a subordination spell!
A subordination spell means… vampires and… the Star Crystal!
The girls have been put under someone's control, and are pointing their blades at Negi and the others.
Will you fight them, Negi? Or will you save them instead? Now, what will happen!?
You will just have to find out next time. Waaaaaaaaaku! Waaaaaaaaaaku!
A whetted mind is as sharp as a whetted blade.
Next time! “I’m sorry… can it be on the forehead or cheek instead?”
by Setsuna
Such an elegant shine… cuts through…
Do I know about the chupa chupa?
“Do I know about the chupa chupa?”…
I’m a happy, cheerful chupacabra!
Number two!