I'm off...
I'm really drowsy today...
You sure are.
You don't look drowsy at all.
I'm a morning person, so I'm fine.
That's nice...
I'm jealous!
I'm not a morning person at all.
Huh?
What is it, Run-chan?
Something's wrong with that birdie. What should I do?
Say, Tooru, that birdie keeps spinning.
Do you think it's okay?
Run-chan, that's just a weather vane.
I'm worried...
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Kilogram
Silky, long hair!
A firm, slim waist!
Arms as long as a giraffe's neck!
Are they fighting?
Aren't there other good qualities?
Slender legs!
More good qualities!
Voluptuous E-cups!
More, more!
White skin, the colour of tofu!
More! More!
What are you two up to?
We're iterating your merits, Yuuko.
How did their conversation end up like this?
Pores that you'd need a microscope to see!
A face as small as a water flea!
You're really focusing on the exterior.
I'd like them to mention some inner values too.
More!
Erm... Outstanding sense of style!
What happened, Tooru?
Run-chan...
Run-chan only likes to praise Yuuko-chan.
I'm pitiful... getting annoyed and trying to get sympathy.
That's ridiculous, you have your own merits, Tooru.
For example?
Uh... Erm...
That's right! There's s-small breasts fetish!
Slender is in right now.
You're in the strike zone for that!
What is it?
Stop it!
So what if she has a nice figure!
Yuuko-chan is like a model.
Crap!
I forgot!
My goal this summer is to lose 3 kilograms and attain a figure befitting of a model!
No, wait. There's still time.
If you're talking about true summer, then you mean August.
Summer hasn't even started yet for high school girls.
Another month...
In another month, I can make it happen!
[Today: Beautification of the entire school campus]
[Pool]
I fail...
I forgot again...
Summer starts today for high school girls...
Changing into our swimsuits just to clean the pool is such a hassle.
But cleaning in a swimsuit sounds fun!
Nagi-chan, you think so too, don't you?
What's up, Nagi-chan?
I-It's nothing.
This is tight!
Have I gained weight?
No, that's not...
Do you think these swimsuits shrink?
It's a little tight!
We're still growing...
...in a lot of ways.
Cut it out.
I see!
The swimsuit shrank!
Isn't Nagi acting weird today?
That's her usual self, you know.
the courtyard
In charge of
Nooo~
Tooru-san.
Are you making progress?
Ah, Yutaka's friend.
You can call me Miho.
To tell you the truth, I'm also a fan of yours, like Yutaka.
Fan?
So you see...
I've never had the chance to ask, but I've been wondering about something.
Woah!
It's soft!
Is this natural, or do you do something to it?
It's natural.
Toorun!
Mipo-rin, that's unfair!
You're bothering Toorun yourself!
I'm not clinging to her like you do, Yutaka.
It's not fair that you get all the fun!
I'm gonna touch her too!
You're just...
Toorun!
By the way, you two seem close.
Did you go to the same middle school?
Yeah, though it's a bit unfortunate.
She keeps looking at her watch.
Well, 3 minutes have passed.
Get off Tooru-san right now, Yutaka.
What? Already?
Mipo-rin, you're cold-hearted!
I'm used to it, so if Yutaka bothers you, tell me immediately.
During middle school, her nickname was "Remote."
Don't think that's totally lame?
Do you know the origin of that?
I have no idea.
Yutaka!
Excuse me. Sorry.
If you understand, that's fine.
I'm sorry.
But I've really wanted to touch Tooru's hair...
[Trash bag]
Tooru-san, I'll hold that trash bag for you.
No! I'll hold it!
I'll leave it to you then.
Wait up! This is heavy!
Mipo-rin!
Remote...
The sun... shining brightly.
The poolside...
Does it feel like a resort?
Not at all.
It's too hot!
It's hot in the pool.
It sure is.
There's nowhere to escape from the heat of the sun.
Anyway, let's get this over with!
Careful!
What is she doing?
I have no idea.
Yuuko-chan, Nagi-chan, it's really slippery here!
You're right.
That's dangerous, you know?
What if you fall and hit your head?
I'll be fine!
Nagi, you tell her too...
Nagi!
What...
Yuuko-chan, gotcha!
You're dripping wet!
I see... If that's how you want to play...
Run!
Caught you.
Hey!
Take that.
mizushibuki kakatta pichapicha pitte
水しぶきかかった　ぴちゃぴちゃぴって
I'm splashing water, splash, splash, splash.
You...!
marude tokonatsu puuru saido
まるで常夏　プールサイド
Almost like an endless summer at the poolside
Ouch!
kirakira kagayaku sora
キラキラ　輝く空
Sparkle, sparkle, the sky shines
onna no ko minna asebamu hada
女の子みんな　汗ばむ肌
All the girls are covered in sweat
mizugi dake ka na ? boodaarain
水着だけかな？　ボーダーライン
In nothing but swimsuits? That's borderline.
mujaki ni asonde hoshii
無邪気に　遊んで欲しい
We just want to play innocently!
bishonurega suki sugi de kodomo mitai ni
びしょぬれが好き過ぎで　子供みたいに
We love getting wet, like children.
itsuka yume mita rakuen wa rizooto kibun kimi to nara
いつか夢見た楽園は　リゾート気分　キミとなら
The paradise I once dreamed about is like being at a resort with you.
senobi shite mita himitsu
背伸びして見た　秘密
I saw the secret while stretching.
fui ni shirimochi o tsuichatte tsururi
ふいに尻もちをついちゃって　ツルリ
And then suddenly slipped and fell on my bottom.
dojina mainichi sa
ドジな毎日さ
It's our clumsy everyday life.
naitari warattari shinagara ne
泣いたり笑ったりしながらね
All the while laughing and crying,
itazura shite mo nakayoshi sa
いたずらしても仲良しさ
even though we tease each other, we're still good friends.
dokidoki de rabuna shunkan wa minna no takaramono
ドキドキでラブな瞬間は　みんなの宝物
Everyone treasures those heart-racing moments of love.
subesube ano ko no o hada ni wa
スベスベ　あの娘のお肌には
As an experiment,
jikken shite miru mizu kakete
実験してみる　水かけて
let's splash water,
picchipichi ni hiite kurechau
ピッチピチに　弾いてくれちゃう
on the smooth skin of that girl.
There, there, there!
dakishimetai nureta mama no gaaru
抱きしめたい　ぬれたままのガール
I want to hug that girl while she's wet.
Tooru, what are you looking at?
Caught you!
Paradise...
Not paradise at all...
Had to stay behind
since they didn't finish
I'm home!
I'm beat...
I probably should have put on more sunscreen...
It's all right, I worked my ass off all day today!
I'm sure I've lost weight!
Maybe even more than that!
Perhaps I've reached my goal of losing 3 kilos already!
You know what I want, scale.
Gained
Now that I think about it, it's fine because I can subtract the 1 kilo that my clothes weigh.
How about that, my weight hasn't changed at all.
Lost to my nerves...
Basics of Dieting
First, form a one month plan, huh?
I guess the foundations are limited food intake and exercise.
"No snacking between meals."
"A light, early dinner."
"Use mostly vegetables and non-greasy foods."
"Keep exercising every day."
"Exercises such as jogging, skipping and stretching are effective."
Sadistic, huh...
Thanks for the food.
I should keep the fact that I'm dieting a secret from everyone else.
They'd just whine about it anyway...
If Run knew...
Stop it! It's bad for your health!
Yuuko would...
You're fine the way you are now!
Ahh... They would say that.
Tooru...
This is delicious! Delicious, isn't it?
Want some? Take as much as you like
Just thinking about it makes me want to eat.
Nagi!
Without meaning to, I jumped.
Tooru is really perceptive... I have to be careful.
What's wrong?
Diet...
What are you-
Hey, you're on a diet, right?
I don't know what you mean.
Where are Run and Yuuko?
They went to the bathroom.
How did you know I was dieting?
Back in spring, you said that you were going to lose 3 kilos before summer, remember?
You remembered that yesterday, didn't you?
Well... Can't you just forget about stuff like that?
Will you tell everyone?
Nope.
So you want money to keep quiet?
What are you doing?
They're not here, huh?
Even though you eat loads of candy, you're really thin, huh?
It's because I run around all the time, isn't it?
On the other hand, there's isn't enough nutrition getting in here...
I see.
I've heard they shrink if they shake too much.
That means I can't skip or jog, solely because I'll lose my breasts!
All right!
If you're that worried about it, why not ask Yuuko?
She could've been working really hard to get what she has.
There has to be a secret to her figure.
I see.
Without a doubt!
Right!
They're not here either.
Did we miss each other?
Tooru, you're sweating!
These are tears of sadness, because I can't see Run.
Don't push yourself.
You're sweaty because we've been walking around.
I'm not sweaty!
By the way, it's already summer and you're still wearing long sleeves?
I don't want to show my arms if I don't have to.
You're going to get heatstroke.
Take it off!
You're this unwilling?
Well then, let's all open the textbook to page 52.
Hm? If I do something to maintain my figure?
I-I really don't mean anything by it.
I just felt like asking.
Hm...
Let's see...
I don't hold back on the things I like and I sleep a lot, I'd say.
I don't do anything, I guess.
What kind of model are you?
Don't mess with me!
You're no help at all!
Huh?
What?
Maintaining your figure?
Are you talking about dieting?
So you were talking about dieting!
Did you start one, Nagi?
Yeah, I did.
No reason to hide it at this point.
Have you tried a diet, Run?
Not properly, I guess.
I don't want to limit what I can eat.
Neither have you, Yuuko-chan, right?
I haven't. Why?
Yuuko-chan, you keep a pet, right?
A pet? What are you talking about?
It's got a name like a surname...
A tapeworm!
TL Note: Sanadamushi is Japanese for tapeworm and also sounds similar to a surname.
It's the power of the tapeworm!
I don't keep one, and that's not a pet either!
PC.
If you search on the internet, I'm sure you'll find a good diet.
I see.
Why did we come all the way to the library?
We could've used the one in the classroom.
Researching this on the PC in the classroom is a little...
There are lots of different diets, huh.
"After I used this, I lost 60kg", it says.
That's way too much!
Sounds like a scam.
If you lost that much, your weight would be negative.
You'd be able to float!
Yeah...
Your ghost would be.
Thanks for the meal.
Nagi-chan, you're done already?
Yeah.
Controlling what you eat is one of the basics of dieting.
Don't overdo it, Nagi.
I'm perfectly fine.
That was just enough.
You're overdoing it.
That didn't happen!
Pretend you didn't hear it!
But that's impossible, because I heard it.
Then forget it!
I guess you really get hungry around this time.
Hey Nagi.
It's bad for your health if you start dieting all of a sudden.
Stop it.
Start off more slowly, then...
You can just make it your goal for next year.
That's right, Nagi-chan.
Take your time.
You're right.
There's no point in overdoing it.
I'll try it at my own pace, without rushing.
That's right!
Let's go eat ice cream!
Yeah, let's go!
Wait a sec...
Isn't it strange, with this flow of conversation, to suddenly move to ice cream?
I want chocolate chip and strawberry.
Vanilla, cheese and yoghurt.
Those are all white!
Look here...
I think I'll take mint and raspberry.
What about you, Nagi?
Rum raisin.
Dieting just isn't gonna happen right now.
Let's go, Nagi.
Ah... Wait...
It's fine the way it is.
Nagi, you're okay the way you are.
Cute enough!
Wha... What embarrassing nonsense are you spouting, all of a sudden?
Yuuko, wait up!
Hurry up!
Look, look!
All new socks!
Hey, neon yellow.
That's gonna stand out.
I like it.
Good morning.
Tooru!
What are you doing wearing loose socks in this day and age?
No, no, those are her new knee socks.
They just don't hold up very well.
Just how slender are you?
I'm using stoppers and they still drop.
Wanna use sock touch?
Yeah.
I want to gain a little weight.
I just heard a sentence I can't ignore.
Never mind.
There we go. Done.
Thanks.
I want to gain weight.
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
Here we go, summer in full force!
Summer, that means "pool",
and of course "beach"!
We've come to the beach!
And when you're talking about the beach, it's all about tight swimsuits!
No, I just can't get enough.
Are you sure you're a high school girl?
I suppose you're all very much interested in how Yutaka looks in her swimsuit.
I don't think so.
Next time, on A Channel: "Beach."
Next Time!
Beach
The only thing I'm interested in is Tooru in her swimsuit!
Me too, me too!
What? You're not going to scold me?