They may have been disguised as students,
but I still can't believe they broke in so easily.
There are ninja-detecting devices all over campus.
Slipping past the detection network is no simple feat.
You must have realized that
someone is directing this attack.
Someone who is, or was, one of us.
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't be strong
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Like a spiral, this red trap coils around us
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Dress yourself in the rampant shadows
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
You really are good. I'm glad.
You're glad?
I wanted to fight against someone as good as you are.
Here goes!
Secret Ninja Art: Tornado Spindel!
How 'bout that?!
But I hit her directly...
You see now? Best hurry and give up.
I'm not through yet!
Damn!
You're wastin' your time.
Why can't I hit her?
How did you—
Secret Ninja Art: Thrust!
Give it up. You can't beat me.
I'm not... done yet...
Don't worry. I wasn't ordered to take your life.
I... won't be beaten!
It's the difference in our abilities.
What's with those eyes?
What of it?! I'm only beaten when I believe I've been beaten!
You thick? How's that change the fact that you've been beaten?
That one hurt, right?
That does it.
I-I'm not done yet.
I don't get it.
You're nothing but a spoilt little girl after all. That was a cinch.
Oh no!
Why, you!
Brace yourself!
Hmph! You really enjoy looking down on others from above, huh?
Hien!
The grief... The misery of just barely getting by in life.
You'll never understand how it feels for as long as you live.
Dad brought you, right?
You've got some nerve.
You think you're a part of our family?
What's this?
This is the sword Hien, a family heirloom.
As my daughter, I'm entrusting it to you.
It can't be! That much power?
Let me tell you one thing.
What is it?
My grief... My misery...
I've sealed it all within Hien here.
All that is left within me now is the pride that has been entrusted to me!
Secret Ninja Art: Phoenix Fire Hien!
H-How dare you...
How dare you! How dare you!
Even with my secret ninja art, that's all it did?
What strength.
Are you going to run away again?
I told you, you can't run from me.
I'm not running from you.
I just want to defeat you.
Secret Ninja Art: Leg-sweeper!
A squid?!
Yagyu! Are you okay?
Damn, it didn't work.
Interlocking Battle Spheres
So we really are under attack.
Even after defeating my opponent, I was just expelled from their sphere.
Is there any way to break into a battle sphere?
Battle sphere!
Now we can battle to our hearts' content.
No one will interrupt us.
I'm not so sure of that.
Eh?
If someone inside the sphere calls to an outsider strongly enough,
it's not impossible for the other to force their way in.
You can call for outside help?
Er, well, this is forbidden, you see.
Physical damage?
The sphere causes an adverse reaction, which exerts a powerful force on the intruder.
Enough to put their life at risk.
Ah, I just had a good idea.
A good idea?
A sphere is formed with the mind, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Then if more minds were linked, maybe a larger sphere could be formed.
It's an interesting idea, but I've never heard of such a technique.
I can do it.
Mm-mm.
Or rather, I'm going to show you, Mr. Kiriya.
After all, I'm going to be a super-ninja.
Several months later,
she really did manage to devise a technique to interlock sphere spaces together,
through application of puppeteer techniques.
Yes. That was what first triggered it.
As a result, she...
lost her life.
Yes...
She really is dead.
Yagyu!
Hibari's sensitivity is the strongest out of all of us.
I'm sure my mind will reach her.
Stop! Forget what I just said!
I will protect Hibari.
Don't do it, Yagyu!
Hibari! Sense me! Hibari!
You don't have to be so afraid, little bunny.
I-I've gotta defeat her somehow.
H-Hang in there, Hibari.
Oh, my.
Actually, I just want to be friends with you.
S-Secret Ninja... Art...
Ninja Bunny Boom!
Thank you.
Thank you, indeed.
That was quite a technique. Fancy and cute, just like you.
Let me show you a few Serpentine techniques in return.
No, th-th-that's all right.
Mockery Meta-Applications!
Greed Vectors!
Angles Traced By Inevitability!
I'm done for! I'm sorry, everyone!
I'm sorry, Yagyu!
Hibari... Hibari!
Sense me, Hibari...
Yagyu?
Call to me! I will protect you!
Hibari, call to me!
Help me... Yagyu...
Perhaps I spanked you a little too hard.
What?!
I-It can't be!
Senran Kagura
Hibari...
Yagyu? Is that you, Yagyu?
Are you all right?
What about you, Yagyu? You're hurt.
It's no big deal.
But...
Who do you think you are, suddenly barging in like that?
How dare you attack Hibari. You'll pay for this.
Are you thinking of snatching my puppet away from me?
Graphic Lines of Death!
You can't even avoid that respectably, can you?
You didn't realize what would happen after you forced your way into the sphere?
You mean, you got hurt just so you could come in here?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! This is all because I called you, Yagyu!
You're wrong. I'm the one who called you, Hibari.
Yagyu...
I'm so sorry.
I can't stand to watch this trite melodrama.
Secret Ninja Art: Death Kiss!
No!
Such a detestable girl.
Unworthy of being even a puppet.
Please! Let Yagyu go!
All right.
In light of your own adorable bravery, I will spare her for you.
In return, you'll be my friend.
Y-Your friend?
Yes. This will be a token of our friendship.
Well, see you later.
Is that all you've got?!
I'm not done yet!
Secret Ninja Art:
Twin Sword Slice!
That's quite an attack, huh?
My secret ninja art didn't work? Oh, no...
We've been training a lot harder than you guys!
Do you see?
Pushovers like you are no match for us.
Are all Serpentine girls... this strong?
What about the others?
Are they all right?
Can you afford to be worrying about your friends right now?
This is why you're pushovers!
You should only rely on yourself!
Is that... what you want?
What?
You'll be alone forever like that.
Will that make you happy, Homura?
Now you're lecturing me?!
What do you take me for?
The sphere?
What's going on?
Wh-What?
We're falling back.
We're falling back?
The sphere's collapsing?
Mirai has been taken out.
The sphere link has destabilized because of that.
It will be difficult to maintain it any longer.
We've accomplished our goal,
so we'll withdraw immediately.
Take care of it, now.
That token of our friendship.
That's enough for now.
Homura!
I can't accept that a pushover like you calls herself a ninja!
This is all I'll say: you are not fit to call yourself the legendary ninja's granddaughter!
It looks like the sphere has dissipated.
Ikaruga!
They ran off, didn't they?
Katsu!
Thank goodness!
Hibari! Yagyu!
Yagyu!
You're badly wounded!
Shake it off, Yagyu!
Yagyu!
Is everyone all right?
Oh no!
Stay with us!
Yagyu... Yagyu!
The National Ninja Hospital: an unofficial state medical facility
where treatment of ninja injuries and illnesses takes place.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Yagyu.
You went through all that... for my sake...
Don't worry about it, Hibari.
But, Yagyu...
I should be discharged tomorrow.
It's raining.
It was raining the first time I met you too, Yagyu.
Do you remember? It was at the enrollment ceremony.
Hanzo Academy Enrollment Ceremony
Splishy, splashy!
There was a girl laughing merrily there.
The girl was the spitting image of Yagyu's sister.
However, there was no way she could be her sister.
Do you like the rain too?
Y-Yeah.
Ah, the enrollment ceremony is starting!
They'll be mad at us if we're late.
Yeah, I remember that.
Yagyu's little sister had her young life tragically cut short by a traffic accident a while back.
Hibari...
What?
If you will stay at my side, that's all I need.
Mm-hmm. I'll stay with you all night, okay?
Okay.
I am the one at fau for allowing the enemy to break into our school.
Don't look so down.
It isn't that.
We were just too...
Yeah, we were... no match for any of them.
We thought we were training as hard as we could.
And yet, it has all been for nothing.
In that case, you just need to get even stronger.
Grandpa!
Master Hanzo!
Were you here all along?
Mm-hmm.
A cat came and told me there was trouble.
A cat?
You know, young girls are at their cutest when they're eating my sushi rolls.
Grandpa.
Listen...
What is it?
Actually, never mind.
Such a funny little girl.
Not even their secret ninja arts worked, huh?
I believe that the enemy has gone through considerable training.
It's said that the students of the Serpentine Academy
risk not only great injuries while training, but even death.
You're kidding.
They're unconfirmed reports though.
Still, if those girls are the literal survivors of such a harsh ordeal,
they would have an extraordinary amount of power for their age.
Kiriya, it appears that the time has come to choose a successor for the top-secret ninja art.
The top-secret... ninja art...
Welcome home!
We're back!
Now that we're all together, I need to talk to you all.
Secret Ninja Art
Top-secret ninja art?!
Top-Secret Ninja Art
Secret Ninja Art
There's something beyond a secret ninja art?
Top-Secret Ninja Art
Sounds amazing.
Secret Ninja Art
And only one person can inherit it?
A sole inheritor, huh?
Ooh, that's so cool!
All right, I'll be the one to inherit it!
You're not the one who gets to decide.
Hmph, I know you want it too, Ikaruga.
Wh-What are you talking about?! I—
I want it too!
Now, hold on.
Right now, none of you are qualified for this.
Y-You don't have to tell us that!
But then, all we have to do is stick with our training, right?
Until we're able to use that top-secret ninja art?
It's not that simple a matter.
The inheritor of the top-secret ninja art is chosen by none other than the scroll containing the art itself.
The scroll...
...chooses the person?
You made them use their secret ninja arts, right?
Yes, ma'am.
And you made them realize that your powers were greater than even those, right?
All right, good work.
But we were unable to defeat them all.
What's worse, one of our own...
This mission was not to exterminate the enemy.
Even so!
Mind your place, Homura.
We ninja are to execute our orders; no more, no less.
Yes, I understand.
Will you be happy alone forever?
This humiliation...
Why, that little brat...
I'll make sure she pays for this!
I just... don't get it...
That spoilt little brat!
Next time... I'll see that she knows the taste of sprouts!
This should be good.
Next Episode Preview
Victory!
Huh? Wh-Who are you?
War trails in my wake!
Um, are you...
Behold, the mountain of training is aflame!
Victory!
Next time, "Hiking Terror."
Hiking Terror
Come get it like your life depended on it.