The seagulls soaring in the sky!
The shining sun!
And of course...
the shimmering sea!
Oh, Haruka.
You've seen Dreamy Shore's beach plenty of times before.
I can't blame her.
We're at a private beach on an island that your family owns.
And to top it off...
Hello, my new home away from home!
...it's got its own villa.
Talk about luxury!
Beautiful...
The sunset above the sea is beautiful as well.
I'm certain you'll love it.
Uh, Haruka?
Give me a sec—
to blow this up—
and I'll be—
ready to play—
Either talk or blow, not both!
I've been looking forward to going to the beach with Towa since forever!
Haruka...
And we get to spend the whole day in such a beautiful sea!
It's simply splendid!
Let's swim our hearts out!
S-Swi...
C'mon, Haruharu, one thing at a time.
We've gotta drop off our bags and get changed first.
Then let's get to that.
Right!
All right, let's have a blast!
Swim?!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Hmm, it's still not enough.
I wonder if there's a greater power out there that could top this off in one go...
The Dress Up Keys...
And guess who's got 'em.
Our Hearts Are One!
The Sunlight Shining Upon The Precures!
Perf!
I'll tie your ears for you.
Gotcha!
Gotcha back!
Towie!
You're wide open!
Then I shall counter!
Hey, three on one isn't fair!
You should be fine now.
Sorry for the wait, girls.
Okay, now that we're all together...
Swim our hearts out!
Pardon!
Haruka went through the trouble of inflating it,
so perhaps we could play beach ball?
Take it!
Point for Team Kirara and Towa!
Nice, Towie!
So, what're we doin' next?
I do believe it's complete!
It's Perf-ect!
Next, let's...
Goodness Perf, you must be famished!
In that case...
Okay, keep going straight!
Now! Go for it, Towa!
So, what should we do next?
I think we did everything you can do on the sand.
Then I believe it's time for...
Towa?
Huh? O-Oh, where might Perf be?
This is so much fun!
Perf, when did you—
Perf's goin' for it!
We can't let her outdo us!
It's time for us to join!
Haruka...
Truth is, I'm a terrible swimmer.
Oh, you are?
Yeah, so I'd like to walk around and draw the scenery while we're here.
So don't mind me and have fun swimming.
Aww...
Well, have fun!
Um—
What's up, Towa?
Well, I, er...
I-I forgot something back in the villa!
Girls, please, go on and swim without me!
Okay, gotcha loud and clear!
Oh, how pitiful!
Why can't I simply tell them?
Just say that I can't... I can't...
You think...
Towie can't swim?
It seems that way.
Huh?!
I mean, it's weird how hard
she's trying to avoid the water.
Huh? Oh...
I had no idea and just tried to have fun.
Maybe that made it harder for her to say...
Perhaps it did,
but it seems Towa still keeps her guard up around us.
Why can't I tell them such a trivial thing?
If I came clean, I'm sure the girls wouldn't...
Towa!
Yui! Why are you here?
I forgot something, too.
Isn't this a drawing of the festival?
I draw pictures of all our everyday events.
I guess you could call it a picture diary.
Picture diary?
It's quite splendid.
There's so much I want to remember.
Including this trip.
Even though I can't swim, just coming to the beach with everyone has been so much fun.
If I could be as honest as you...
Huh?
I'm... envious of you.
And I'm pretty envious of you.
I love you all, really.
I just wish... I could do more for you.
So it'd be nice if I were like you...
and could become a Precure...
That's just a thought I've had now and then.
But I realized something.
I'm the one who watches you all protect our dreams the closest.
I might not be able to fight,
but one day, I want to tell the world about you!
As a friend, that's what I should do!
A friend...
It's filled with all the times we've shared...
because you girls share every day with me.
Together...
Even me?
Havin' fun, 'kay?
Lock!
And I found just the dream I need, 'kay?
You. Show me your dream, 'kay?
Yui!
I won't let go of my dream!
Not bad for a mere human, 'kay?
But...
I'll become a picture book author and tell the world about the power of dreams!
I'm gonna throw that dream in the cage of despair, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Get goin' Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
It's Yui!
Dyspairvil, wrap things up for me, 'kay?
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Prepare yourself this instant!
Dyspairvil!
Was that sound a Dyspairvil's?
Yuiyui and Towie are over there!
Hold up.
Can't let you go there, 'kay?
You think you can take us on alone?
Alone?
You sure 'bout that?
Sorry for the wait.
Now let the game begin, 'kay?
Cute Updo!
Lock...
Three of him?!
That makes it three on three.
If you wanna save your friends,
you've gotta go through us first, 'kay?
Precure!
Princess Engage!
Dyspairvil!
Wait for me, Yui. I'll save you soon.
Dyspairviiiil!
Dyspairvil!
Fireworks!
Ignite, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Illusion!
Surge, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Flame!
Dyspairviiiiiiil!
'Kay, you got a little stronger,
Princess of Budding Flowers!
What are you after?
Good question, 'kay?
Just because it's one on one doesn't mean I'm letting you beat me!
Who's going to win this game?
We'll just have to wait and see.
Scarlet!
Are you okay?
Dyspairvil.
That's Yui's—
Dyspairvil!
Yui, it's thanks to you...
that I realized what's truly important to me.
Haruka, who first extended her hand to me.
Minami, who gave me the courage to never fear the darkness.
And Kirara, who taught me the joy of laughing together.
Dyspairvil!
You were always by my side!
I could never hold back a blissful smile when you were near!
Haruka, Minami, Kirara, and Yui...
being with you girls is where I belong!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Scarlet Violin!
Phoenix!
Soar, O wings of flame!
Precure!
Phoenix Blaze!
Burning!
Adieu.
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Mermaid Ripple!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
Adieu.
Huh?
Game over.
Oh! Huh?
Later, 'kay?
Open!
The door to your dream!
Guess you saved me.
But of course.
We're friends.
Thank you.
It's...
A Dress Up Key!
And it's a brand-new, never-before-seen Key!
Thank you, Yui.
Your watchful eyes are what pushed us on.
You are the warm sunlight shining upon the Precures.
The Precure's... sun?
A solar Dress Up Key... the Sun Key!
I hope my heart can give the Precures strength.
Pardon!
I, er...
The truth is!
I can't swim at all!
Towa!
What is it?!
We've been waiting for you to tell us.
We saw through you from the start!
Right, Yuiyui?
Yeah!
Did you really?
When you were looking that sunken, yeah.
Sunken? Before she got into the water?
Goodness!
How could you girls?
Do you... do you have any idea how conflicted I've been?!
Oopsie!
Halt, I command you!
Hey, don't leave us behind!
But I sure was surprised to see a Dress Up Key appear!
Yeah! We've got a lot now, huh?
Huh?
What's wrong?
My Keys...
It couldn't be...
Looks like...
I won the game, 'kay?
My Keys were stolen!
Wha?!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Twinkle!
When the shimmering stars dance
the night sky seems like a twinkling barrier
But if you leap into the spotlight
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
The scent of the Dress Up Keys is in the academy's forest!
Oh?
Good nose, Haruharu!
No, that's just what Perf told me!
For now, let's search within the forest.
Huh? Who are those girls?
I've never seen them in class...
I sense a great power from them!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Mysterious Girls?
Successors to the Legendary Keys!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Nara Prefecture - Riko (Age 5)
Tokyo - Shiho (Age 6)