There are more of them again...
The flow of the river is ceaseless,
yet the water is never the same.
The foam that floats on stagnant pools,
now vanishing, now forming,
are not long in their duration.
So, too, it is with man and
his dwellings in the world.
They are the blink of an eye.
Mii-kun!
What's up?
Staying late again, Yuki-senpai?
Yeah, classic literature is hard for me.
I actually really enjoy it.
Do you want some help?
Really? I can't believe you
understand this complex stuff.
An Account of My Hut, huh?
My friend really liked this.
Isn't this awesome, Mii-kun?
What is?
I mean, this is a letter someone
wrote a long time ago, right?
About 800 years ago, yes.
It's more of an essay than a letter, though.
800 years!
The feelings of someone from that
long ago are still getting through to us.
Letters are amazing!
I can see how excited you are, Senpai.
Okay...
Let's get started.
School Living Club
#7
A Letter
The wind is so brutal at night.
I know.
We're okay for now, but we'll have
to be ready before winter hits.
Winter... It doesn't feel real.
Is Yuki already in bed?
She was studying until late today,
so she's sound asleep.
I see.
Why don't we get some sleep, too?
Hey, do you ever think this is all a dream?
That tomorrow we'll wake up
in our normal old school?
I have that dream every night.
Yuki-chan.
Yuuri-san and I decided something.
You and Rii-san?
Yes. Something really fun.
How can anything be fun now?
We'll start a club.
All of us, together.
A... club?
Yes.
We'll create the School Living Club.
Yuki-senpai?
Time to get up, Senpai.
Morning, Mii-kun.
I had a scary dream.
What kind of dream?
I forgot.
What the heck?
Breakfast is ready.
The other two are already there.
I see, I see.
Wait, what about Megu-nee?
Um...
Oh, good morning, Megu-nee.
That should do it.
The School Living Club will do
its best again today, Megu-nee.
This looks delicious!
Let's eat!
Yum! The gardening club's onions are so tasty!
It was nice of them to share, wasn't it?
Yeah!
The udon is so delicious.
Uh... Huh?
As usual, she's inhaling it so fast,
she isn't listening.
Come on, you're not Taroumaru. Slow down!
Taroumaru
No, Taroumaru has better table manners.
It's amazing what you can store
without refrigeration nowadays.
The udon's all springy!
Another win for science.
Yes. We can eat hot udon
thanks to the solar panels
and power storage units.
Most schools aren't equipped with those.
All finished!
Rii-san, I want seconds!
Sorry, Yuki-chan, we don't have any more.
We had to ration the stuff we
brought back from the club outing.
Oh...
That was such a fun outing, though!
We got to make friends with Mii-kun!
Th-Thank you.
That was a rough time.
It sure was.
Coming home with the four of us and
Taroumaru crammed in that little car...
I fell asleep right away,
so I don't remember the ride.
Yeah.
I was driving, Rii-san was up front with me,
and Taroumaru was bouncing
all over the back seat.
I can't believe you two slept through all that.
Huh?
It was just us two in the back?
That's weird...
I know... the car seated four...
Yeah...
Me, Rii-san, Kurumi-chan,
Mii-kun, and Megu-nee...
The four of us...
Huh?
Senpai...
What about Megu-nee?
O-Oh, you were asleep,
so maybe you didn't hear,
but Megu-nee's house was nearby,
so she walked home instead of riding with us.
Yes, that's right.
She... did?
Yeah!
Right?
Yes...
Yuki-chan!
I'll go ask Megu-nee!
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It's no one's fault.
Yuki-senpai...
She can't keep going like that.
Miki-san?
I realize her smile is what
keeps everyone going,
but it's no excuse...
Yeah...
I'm sure Megu-nee feels the same way.
Megu-nee...
You're here, right, Megu-nee?
It's okay.
No matter how faint my presence is,
I'm not going anywhere.
But I get scared sometimes.
There are things I can't
remember clearly, and I...
All people's memories are vague.
That's why you need to do things like
talk to people and keep a journal.
That makes memories become more tangible.
At least, that's what I think.
Even if the person it's about...
goes away...
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best, Megu-nee.
I'm back!
Hey.
Welcome back.
Mii-kun!
I told you, physical contact isn't...
But you seemed kinda lonely, Mii-kun.
I don't know what you mean.
Mii-kun, you smell kinda funny!
Hey! That's rude!
No, no, it's just Taroumaru.
There, there. What's going on with you?
Taroumaru doesn't want to take a bath.
I see.
Then I'll give him one.
Hey, wait!
Come to think of it, humans and dogs
see the world completely differently.
Really?
Dogs don't see color like we do.
They live in a world of sepia.
But instead, they can see at night,
and they can even see part of
the ultraviolet spectrum.
We can't detect the smells they can,
and they can't tell what color our flowers are.
Wow... I didn't know that.
Gimme my hat back!
Somehow, though, doesn't it seem like
those two see things identically?
It does.
Right?
I know we don't see things the same way...
Taroumaru, come on! Wait up!
Yuki-chan!
You okay?
Ouch...
Senpai, please don't overdo these things.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
What... are these?
Are they Megu-nee's things?
What a mess.
I'll help.
Thank you.
You're a member of the club now.
You don't have to thank me.
Okay...
Look!
Hey, look at this!
Why don't we write a letter?
Writing letters is fine and all,
but how will we send them?
Oh, right. The post office is outside the school.
You didn't think of that?
Then why don't we just mail
them straight from school?
When you think of mail,
you think of carrier pigeons.
And where are we going
to get a carrier pigeon?
We'll go catch one now!
But how are we going to catch one?
With this.
You're gonna mince it?!
Nah, I'll hit it with the flat side, like this!
And this!
Maybe this won't work...
And this! And this! And this!
She'd never land a hit.
Balloons
If we're sending letters, we can use these!
Aren't those from the test of courage?
They won't float if you blow them up with air.
Oh, dear.
Balloons
If only we had some helium...
Oh, there might be an old tank
that the scuba club used.
We had a scuba club?
A long time ago, yes.
I'll go check it out.
Wait.
You can't carry an air tank by yourself.
I'll go with her.
Rii-san
Mii-kun
But...
I'm a club member, too.
Okay. Thank you.
Sure.
Me, too!
Yuki-chan, why don't you write your letter?
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna write a really good one!
Do you think there's anyone
out there to receive our letters?
I do.
There's no way the whole
human race has gone extinct.
Y-Yeah...
There's always that one in a million chance.
I'm counting on that.
Right!
What's wrong?
Writing an actual letter is kind of embarrassing.
My handwriting is so messy.
It's okay.
Let me see.
What're you doing?
Oh, paper dolls? How cute!
Yuki-chan, if you picked up a
balloon on the side of the road,
and it had a letter attached,
what would you think?
I'd be surprised!
And excited!
Would you think the sender's writing was messy?
No, I'd be happy just to get the letter!
You see?
Yeah!
We're back!
Here we are.
We found the helium tank.
We brought traps, too.
Haven't given up on the carrier pigeon idea, huh?
Nope!
C'mon, Mii-kun, you write a letter too!
Yes, yes.
Hey, Yuki, check this out.
Huh? What's up?
This trap will knock a pigeon dead in an instant!
I don't think we want to kill them...
Okay, I'm off to catch a pigeon.
Good luck!
Let's move the tank to the wall.
Yeah, good idea!
Sakura
Mii-kun?
Oh... Yes?
What're you gonna write?
Uh, well...
What should I write?
Kyaah
Hold it!
What should I write, though?
Anything you want.
Write about yourself, your plans
for the future, things you like...
The future, huh?
If I don't decide between college and
work soon, Megu-nee'll yell at me.
I think any teacher would, not just her.
True...
We'll have to leave this
school someday, won't we?
Indeed.
Graduation... That's it!
My Dream
...so many things,
...can't write them all
Let's write about what we want
to do after graduation!
Our dreams for the future?
Yeah!
And we'll talk about how we're happily
working toward making them come true!
My Dream
...so many things,
...can't write them all.
When I graduate...
Can't sleep?
There's a lot of activity around the entrance.
I guess they don't like to be out
in the rain, even in that state.
I found this earlier today.
Sakura
"Sakura"... Isn't that...
Megu-nee.
May I have that, please?
It may be useful to us at some point.
Please.
Thank you.
I know we'll all get out of here someday.
Yes.
You think the rain will let up soon?
I'm sure of it.
All right!
It's finally time.
Good luck, Hatoko-chan.
Hey, who're you calling Hatoko-chan?
Her! She's Hatonishiki Hatoko-chan.
No! His name is Arnault!
But I wanna name it, too!
I caught it!
Hatoko-chan is cuter!
He's totally an Arnault!
Please stop, you two!
She has a "Hatoko" face!
Speak up, Arnault!
What if we compromise and
call it Arnault Hatonishiki II?
Oh, fine.
Official Name
Arnault Hatonishiki II
Okay! Your name is Arnault Hatonishiki II.
Where does the "II" come from?
Okay, Arnault Hatonishiki II, take flight!
On the count of three, okay?
Ready...
One!
Two!
Three!
To Kei
Kei, how are you?
I've found a new place to live,
and I've made new friends.
I'm doing just fine. Taroumaru is well, too.
It's all thanks to them.
Is just staying alive enough?
Yes. It's a great thing to be alive.
The dew may fall and the flower remain,
or the flower may wither before the dew is gone.
What was that?
A line my friend was fond of.
I see.
I hope it reaches her.
Whatever path I walk, I pray that someday,
I'll meet you again along the way.
We are happy
Next time!!
Yuki
Taroumaru
Where do you think Arnault is now?
If he's a second generation, maybe America?
Whoa, go Arnault!
He's a Hatonishiki, after all.
You know the family?!
Next time on Episode 8
of SCHOOL-LIVE, "Future."
#8
"Future"