All done.
Finally your first day on the job, eh?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So you decided to dress up at home before going to work?
Won't you feel hot on the way?
Oh, but I guess getting tortured by
the sun sounds nice in its own right.
Only to you.
This uniform comes with a learning curve. Plus, the place isn't too far.
Besides...
Kawai stares at me passionately this way.
I know she's only looking at my outfit, though.
It's raining incessantly outside
But I don't mind since I feel at ease here
I'll turn over a new page to face
The unpredictable future lying in wait
Every morning feels incredibly bright
When I'm woken up by the hustle and bustle
And you're always right there
Standing next to me
Show me your world
And what it can be
Because look
Even your most casual of gestures
Shoots an arrow into my heart
What should we talk about tomorrow?
Let's go see how this story unfolds
The Kawai Complex Guide to Manors and Hostel Behavior
Episode Eight
Happideath
This café is housed in a remodeled home from the Meiji era.
You'll be working in the guesthouse, though.
Put on your nametag.
Anekouji
We're going with this?
Morning.
Hello, owner. So you found someone to work in the guesthouse?
That's great.
The unspoken "good luck" in their
eyes doesn't fill me with confidence.
Hey, those people were dressed in normal uniforms.
They work at the bistro.
I'd like to work there too.
There were girls and everything.
Now, now.
You mustn't inconvenience the lady.
Are you Anekouji's successor?
Great. I've already run into someone who just screams "eccentric."
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yamamoto.
Huh? That's a normal name.
Maybe I shouldn't judge the book by its cover.
Yamamoto's your real name, right? I'm—
Of course.
I hail from a village at the foot of the mountains,
which is the meaning of "Yamamoto."
There are a lot of nobles who think commoners don't have surnames.
I'm from a poor family in the sticks, but...
Figures.
His real
name's Houjou
His real name fits the part more.
What's your name, by the way?
You see,
he's going to succeed the Anekouji name.
Show him the ropes, okay?
Oh, so you're Anekouji's little brother?
He's told me a lot about you.
Not only did he send your brother abroad to study the languages,
but he also took you in and
allowed you to use his name?
Lord Anekouji is truly a philanthropist.
Suddenly, I have an entire backstory...
Don't let him down, okay?
Why don't you leave it at that, Yamamoto?
You're bothering him.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kurokawa.
That's my real name, of course.
I go by Saionji here.
I'm Usa.
I look forward to working with you.
Though I'll only be here through summer break.
He's got a strange aura about him.
Our uniforms are a little unusual,
but our work doesn't really differ in any way from a normal café.
Oh, that's good to know.
Before this, they were more like monk's robes.
But he seems like a gentle, decent person.
That said,
my guardian spirit is related to Kouda Rohan,
so maybe that's why I was drawn to this place.
Meiji Era Author
How many times must you get your hopes up only to see them crushed? You idiot!
He was the grandson of an old man that
lived in the same neighborhood as Rohan.
A stranger!
Hey, but you're the same.
What?
I see.
What?!
Natsume Souseki is related to you, you know?
One of your ancestors once
wanted to go to Souseki's school.
A complete stranger!
This is bad, Usa!
Evil spirits are forming a line behind you!
Could this guy stop talking about spirits?
It reminds of Hayashi and my Oddhand days.
Knock it off.
You're always spouting nonsense, Saionji.
Thanks, but you're one to talk.
Mr. Natsume's still teaching at the
Tokyo Imperial University, is he not?
How dare you talk about him as if he were dead!
Wow, so that's the angle you're taking.
Weren't you going on about dark clouds gathering in the world soon after the Russo-Japanese war?
Hadn't Souseki stopped teaching by then?
Your background research is sorely lacking.
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
At the very least,
he's no longer
at Imperial U
Well, your stupid spirits have nothing
to do with the historical personalities!
Oh yeah? Well, what era is your stupid hair style from?
Like that would—
Settle down, you two.
Calm down.
Whose side are you on, Anekouji?!
"Whose"?
C-Customers?!
Come to think of it, they were in the private room...
Sorry to disturb you.
Welcome back. How was it?
I realized once again that my life is stuck on hard mode.
How enviable!
Shut up.
Don't go calling your life "hard mode" over such trifling matters!
You know, I found out that one of my juniors was planning a mixer while trying to keep me in the dark!
And you find that hard?
You're totally easy!
Why would you want to go to a mixer that badly?
Just thinking about it...
What a pain.
High school mixers are just karaoke and stuff, though.
What, you got plans?
Of course not.
Not that I'd tell you if I did.
Tagami
Getting called in by the Oddball Squad?
Hell no! It's just my friend!
Hey, Usa, wanna go to a mixer?
Well?
Tagami...
The demon lord's breathing down my neck, so I'll call you back.
Tagami
The demon lord?
What the hell? LOL
Do you live in the underworld or something?
According to Tagami's text,
he was hanging out with a friend from junior
high when he got to know a girl from East High
and decided to have a mixer.
It'll be at the obvious choice: karaoke.
I can't go. I've got rectal prolapse.
At least come up with a decent reason to refuse!
Oh, it's a follow-up text.
"You went to West Junior High, right?"
R-Right.
"I'm with the girl who's setting this whole thing up."
"She says she went to West Junior High too."
"I'll send you a pic."
Here's the pic
Check out the pic attached
She's showy, but she's also pretty cute.
Did someone like her go to my school?
Oh, this is one of those typical
"fresh start in high school" stories.
She realized she was cute?
Wrong.
She's the type of girl who realized she could make herself cute.
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
And the
type who
overdoes it
One of your kind, huh?
Eyelid glue
Removed
She's gone overboard in messing with her eyes.
Eyeliner
Removed
Fake lashes
I bet she had single eyelids and smaller irises before.
Black contacts
Removed
She probably ignored her eyebrows in the past, too.
Eyelid glue
Removed
Eyeliner
Fake lashes
Removed
Black contacts
Eyelid glue
Removed
Eyeliner
Fake lashes
Removed
Black contacts
Eyelid glue
Removed
Eyeliner
Fake lashes
Removed
Black contacts
Eyelid glue
Removed
Eyeliner
Fake lashes
Removed
Black contacts
Eyelid glue
Removed
Eyeliner
Fake lashes
Removed
Black contacts
Eyelid glue
Removed
Eyeliner
Fake lashes
Removed
Black contacts
Eyelid glue
Removed
Eyeliner
Fake lashes
Removed
Black contacts
She doesn't know where to
draw the line when doing them.
This hairstyle covers up the shape of her face...
Hers must be round, then.
Hairstyles as flashy as this one tend to be an extreme reaction to having black, unfashionable hair.
And her name's Hayashi. Let's see...
Hayashi?
It's Hayashi?!
Usa, a lot of ghosts
have gathered here!
Hayashi, you're terrifying me more now than you ever did in the past!
Usa, a lot of ghosts
have gathered here!
The supernaturally-attuned girl who used to
follow Usa around back in his Oddhand days?
Maybe she'll put the moves on him during the mixer, too.
I mean, she didn't stick out or get bullied thanks to you dealing with her, right?
No, she stuck out like a sore thumb.
I'm sure she's very thankful to you.
What do you think, Ricchan?
Maybe so.
No...
Another follow-up text.
My bad.
When I told Hayashi about you, she flat-out
refused to set the mixer up if you were coming.
Sorry, but forget I said anything.
Actually, what did you even do to her?
When you compare it to Usa's suffering,
I guess not being invited to a mixer isn't such a big deal after all.
Thanks, bro!
It was never a big deal!
Also, you only "guess"?!
Tagami and gang must be done with karaoke right about now.
Not like I wanted to go anyway,
but that was awful of them.
What if I keep getting the short end of the stick and never find any happiness in life?
What if I never make any progress with Kawai?
Let's not go there.
We've got customers.
Welcome—
It's an apprentice, for real! Hilarious!
Usa?
Man, I'm so bored.
So right at this moment, your junior could be wearing her best underwear on a date after scoring big at the mixer,
and you're gonna spend your Saturday lazing around in an old, worn-out bustier, eh?
Okay, time to test out the effectiveness of my new facial cleanser.
On her face, that is.
Shiro, get me some sandpaper and thinner.
I don't think so.
Stop fighting, you two.
If you've got time to kill, why
don't we drop in on Usa at work?
Sounds good.
Oh, that sounds like a better way to spend my
time than unmasking—I mean, exfoliating Sayaka.
This isn't the time for exfoliation.
You too, Ricchan.
I don't really...
They have lots of old literature there, you know?
Why do I have to wear this?
Why not?
Don't you like these outfits?
I do, but it's not like I want to wear them.
Hayashi... and Tagami...
Usa?
What are you doing, dude?
Wait, this is where you're working?
What's going on? Is he a friend?
Do you know him as well, Hayashi?
Y-Yeah. He was my classmate back in junior high.
For real?
One of the apprentices you wanted to see turned
out to be a former classmate? Sounds like destiny!
S-Stop that. We may have gone to the same school, but we never interacted much.
A...
Bad news, Usa!
Your guardian spirit has fallen to the dark side!
I seem to remember one of us was all about interaction!
Long time no see, Hayashi.
Are you still hanging out with—
Let's hurry up and go inside.
Are you sure? He looked like he wanted to talk to you.
It's fine!
Hey, what's wrong?
Sorry about this, Usa.
We started talking about this apprentice café toward the end of the mixer,
and the girls thought it sounded interesting—especially Hayashi.
My friend's got her in his sights, you see.
We'll leave as soon as possible.
Actually, you fit this place strangely well.
Were you always into this kinda stuff?
I never was! What are you even talking about?
Welcome.
Allow me to show you to your room upstairs.
Huh? Aren't you gonna say
"Welcome back" or something?
We're not that kind of café.
And here I thought I was a "master."
You're an idiot!
We haven't had unpleasant customers like that in a while.
They're the kind of people I could never get along with.
The guys are just getting carried away trying to impress the girls.
Their guardian spirits are all good-for-nothings too.
Defeated
warrior
You seem like you'd get along just fine with Hayashi.
Might not be possible with the current version of her, though.
I don't really want to take their orders.
I'm sorry to say this, but me neither.
One of them was my classmate in junior high, so it's awkward.
Very well. I'll go.
No need to worry about me.
I can handle a bunch of rich kids living
large on their parents' money, no problem.
Now I'm really worried.
How rude!
That was fast.
What is wrong with that group?
They're looking down on me as though I was just some poor apprentice from the sticks!
They must be jealous because I'm such an
excellent student and Master treats me well.
You enjoy customer complaints too, huh? Now I'm jealous.
Come on, apprentice. Take our orders!
Wait, you're the guy from earlier.
Good timing.
C'mere.
Wow, this café looks pretty good.
Come on, Ricchan. Chin up!
No way.
Everyone's looking at you, you know?
That's even worse!
So should we call you Anekouji?
Sounds like an escort name!
What're you, some Japanesque host?
Your orders, please.
Do girls who are into roleplaying request you personally?
I bet they totally do!
Are you into that stuff, Anekouji?
No. Can I take your order?
Hey, Tagami. Was he the guy you were gonna invite to the mixer at first?
Gulp
For some reason,
I gulped too
You were so against the idea, Hayashi.
Is he an ex of yours?
N-No!
That's totally suss!
Did something happen back in junior high?
Tell us, Anekouji!
Usa used to be a bit strange, okay?
P-People used to call him "Oddhand" and stuff.
Oddball
Handler
Thanks to you, yeah!
What the hell?
So what, were you always into roleplay?
Or do you have some weird kinks?
You sure found the perfect job, huh?
Sorry I asked if he was your ex, Hayashi.
I had no idea he had a few screws loose.
That was totally rude!
Sorry!
Hey...
Nah, man.
I'm sure you'll meet a girl better suited to you, Anekouji.
One who's got a few screws loose herself.
The hell is that?
Why isn't he saying anything?
He should be setting them straight.
What am I doing here, again?
Oh, right. I need to take their orders.
It's okay.
This'll be over before I know it.
Come nighttime, I'll be able to laugh it off and be all,
"Man, I didn't know what to do" while I tell the others about this. And I'm sure they'll laugh with me.
Oh, but...
This is a bit hard to take.
I wonder if I can get Sumiko to make my favorite dish for me.
And what about Kawai?
Will she laugh at this?
Kawai...
Usa.
Usa!
Kawai?
What's with the getup?
Sumiko made me wear it.
And Sayaka did the makeup.
So...
So cute.
We're all seated at a table downstairs.
You should come too.
Er, to take orders.
Maybe being a roleplaying nerd isn't so bad after all.
Yeah. Maybe I should get a job at this place.
I'll come as soon as I'm done here.
Come now.
Requesting him personally, huh?
It actually happens!
Insulting me is one thing, but don't you dare talk trash to her—
Yep. That's right.
Personally.
So hurry up.
I'll be waiting for you there.
Okay.
Good.
Yeah, Usa. Hurry up and come.
I'm so lonely without you around.
Uh, you two...
I'm only here because of you, you know?
You're always helping me out, after all.
Mostly at night.
Night
Well, duh. You're at work during the day.
I'm not an ungrateful wench who'd bite the hand that fed her, you see.
Huh? You've got something on your face.
It's black!
A bug?
It's a bug!
Wait, isn't this...
Oh no.
I'm so sorry. I got the wrong idea.
The thing is, I've never seen fake eyelashes before.
I had no idea they'd be so stiff.
You like wearing bugs on your face then, I take it?
I'm going home!
Sorry I couldn't take the hint.
Was that...
One of Professor Sayaka's spare tools of witchcraft.
Also, the professor plans to kill some time by setting all those men up.
Look, you should drop the "Mr. Nice Guy" act once in a while.
I got pissed off just watching that crap.
Well, she was really scared back there.
And while Hayashi might have caused tons of trouble...
Huh? They're still on.
...I don't hate her.
You damn well should.
Whatever.
Let's go to Ricchan.
Oh, yeah.
She's waiting for me.
Sure!
Ricchan left just now.
She didn't wait
After all she said earlier?
Mayumi, why are you showing so much skin?
This happened, and then this, and then this...
Oh, so that's why.
She came back with this scary look on her face...
Ricchan?
What's wrong?
But then...
I-I'm going home!
Why?
That's right.
She doesn't like being in the spotlight
or talking to people she doesn't know,
so she gets really embarrassed afterward.
And yet...
Usa.
Oh, he's back.
Were you all right?
Did they say mean things to you?
Don't get so depressed.
No need to let them get to you.
That's right.
We should be laughing at the privileged class for resting on their laurels!
Could you not make things any more complicated, please?
I love Kawai so much!
I'll die of happideath!
Happideath
You're happy?!
An old-style fashionista?
She just came running out of the apprentice café!
How cute!
I...
I'll die of embarracide!
Embarracide
Salisbury steak!
With melted
cheese on top
And I'm sitting next to Kawai!
Pay my respects
This is amazing!
So salisbury steak is to you what
chicken-and-egg bowl is to Mayumi.
Usa.
Yes?
About the books I lent you the other day.
Sorry. I haven't read them yet.
Yeah, I figured.
You should read the third book first. The one with the green cover.
Why?
It's the funniest one.
Er, does that mean...
It must be hilarious if you even you found it funny.
Sorry for being such a robot.
I said nothing of the sort!
She's trying to cheer me up...
I guess I'll start on it tonight, then.
I'm looking forward to it.
Sorry, but you're mistaken.
I'm eating my favorite food tonight...
to celebrate something nice happening to me.
Boing.
Did having your face buried in my boobs make you that happy?
Did you think this episode would end on a good note?
Well, too bad!
You get me instead!
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can hold our heads high and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
I have to disagree
I may be alone, but I'm not lonely
Only a special man can lay claim to this beauty
I feel bad that you fell for it, but we're just getting started here
Be it in order or chaos
We need only be ourselves
I don't care
But I can't stop thinking about it
There's a little pity in the air
I poke my nose where it doesn't belong
And applaud your eccentricity
We offer a tired mind some respite
And a lonely heart some warmth
There's always trouble brewing
And never a moment of peace
But that's the kind of place we call home
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can smile at each other and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
Preview
Egad!
What's wrong, Mayumi?
One of them showed up!
Them?
They're called "centipedes" in English.
"Call a doctor, quick!"
"You're back home already?"
"I was just about to put my shoes on."
This thing shows up in stories like that.
Oh, a centi—
Not another word out of you!
Just hearing the name disgusts me!
Do you hate them that much?
Of course I do! I'm a girl!
Come on, Mayumi.
You're wasting your time and effort trying to show off your feminine side when there are no hot men around.
Aren't you scared of them, Sayaka?
Not really.
Sayaka grew up in the sticks, after all.
Episode Nine
The Forbidden
Country upbringings are scary!
Stop talking about that, or I'll smack you.