This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki.
She's 12 and dreams of becoming a singer.
But unfortunately,
she only has one year left to live.
We, the Shinigami, were sent to tell her
about her inevitable fate, but...
Today, she became an adult...
...and she performed incredibly at the audition.
Aren't we changing her destiny!?
Well, then...
I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
Be sure to watch TV in a well-lit room
and a safe distance away.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Full Moon wo Sagashite
Original Subtitles by a.f.k.
Searching for a Full Moon
The road to love is far too long for me.
Toosugiru koi no michishirube
There's no way for me to love you any more. Nope! Nope!
Mou suki wo fuyasenai Non Non
It's as if the world inside my dream is a completely different one
Yume no naka wa maru de betsu sekai
where I can even tell you how I really feel.
Sutoreeto ni omoi mo ieru no ni
I wear my favorite clothes every day
Okiniiri no fuku wo mainichi kichau no
so that person will turn his gaze towards me.
Ano hito no mesen ga kocchi ni chiratsuitekimasu you ni
"I like you!" If I could bring myself to say it out loud
I LIKE YOU no kotoba nara ieru
I would even be able to talk about love with you.
Renai soudan suru koto mo dekiru
I want to be tucked into your heart
Anata no haato ni tsutsumaretai no ni
and I will do anything to be there.
Doushitara tsutsunde kureru no
"I love you!" Those are the words I want to hear from you
I b YOU wo anata kara kikitai
and my breath will quicken when we kiss.
Kisu suru shunkan no chikai kokyuu wo
The me who is performing for you is the cutest of them all!
Anata wo mane suru atashi wa ichiban kawaiku naru hazu
Transcribed by Steve
Editing, TLC: Zalis (ReDone-Subs)
Retiming, Encoding: E_B (Soldado)
Typesetting: shani-san and E_B (Soldado)
QC: E_B
U-Um, I'm home!
What's with that!? She really  has no manners!
I'll make a bunch of rice cakes for you, then.
Which do you like better,
red beans or soybeans? But we're out of tea...
I'm home.
O-Oh... Mitsuki-chan's home.
Yes. I'll put her on.
Hello?
She finally put you on.
I thought I'd have to talk to Tanaka-san forever.
Dr. Wakaouji! Why are you calling me?
Ah, well, actually...
Apparently they've decided who's going to be your manager.
Eh!? Manager!?
Keep your voice down! Someone's listening.
Why'd you hear about my manager?
Because I've become your "guardian."
And I just talked with her a moment ago.
So, the manager said that
she was going to come visit us.
Mitsuki-chan, could you come to the hospital right now?
Yes! I'll be right there!
THE MANAGER ARRIVES
Why would you need to see Dr. Wakaouji?
Isn't he making a house call tomorrow?
Yes, but he said he wanted me
to come to the hospital immediately.
Um, I do have some shopping to do, so...
...shall I take Mitsuki-san to the hospital?
That is acceptable. Please take care of it.
Knock it off, Meroko!
No way! Mitsuki-chan's still changing!
It's okay now.
Besides, why'd she even need to change?
She can't meet the manager in that body anyway.
Ah! That's right.
Can you make me 16 after we get to the hospital?
Wait a minute.
That'll be okay for the manager...
...but isn't she going to be with her "guardian," Dr. Wakaouji?
Yeah, so what?
What will the doctor think if he sees
Mitsuki as a 16-year-old?
What do we do!?
W-What do we do? These situations call for...
The Shinigami Handbook.
Let's see, let's see...
Just as I thought...
we'll have to tell them everything!
These two are Shinigami.
Their names are Takuto and Meroko!
On card: "Manager"
Takuto turned my 12-year-old-body into that of a 16-year-old!
And when I'm like that,
I don't have any cancer in my throat!
I can sing with all my heart!
Really? That's how it is?
I'm perfectly fine with it!
Okay.
It's not okay!
If stuff like that worked,
we'd be living the easy life!
Geez! Let's see...
Meroko... Is that handbook really of any use?
I get it!
I'll give you a rare chance to see my power!
Oh? You're going to show me?
So what's your idea, then?
W-Well, I'll... tell the manager that...
Um...
It's her little sister, Mikazuki!
Or something like that...
We just have to fool them!
Won't that Wakaouji guy
suspect that something's up?
Like I said...
Mikazuki is... her modeling stage name.
That's it! Let's go with that!
Well, it's a shot in the dark,
but we'll have to try it.
Yeah.
And you'd better try as hard as you can, too!
Yes!
Reception Room
Here we are.
Yeah.
Reception Room
I wonder if I should go in with you.
Hey! If she pulls a stunt like that,
it'll be a proble-!
Um... what'll be a problem?
Eh? That's...
...I think that would be
too much of a problem for you.
Please take care of your shopping first.
I'll come pick you up later.
Please wait in the lobby, okay?
Okay!
Meroko!
No more...
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I shouldn't have been yelling
when I was in that form.
All right, let's stick to the plan.
Okay.
Really?
She's here.
Excuse me.
Hey. We've been waiting for you.
This is your manager, Ooshige-san. Introduce yourself.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Ooshige, from Village Pro.
Wow... It's a woman, huh?
And this is...
P-Pleased to meet you.
I'm Kouyama Mitsuki.
What are you saying, you idiot!?
If you don't follow the plan,
you'll mess everything up!
Ah! That's not what I mean!
I'm her little sister, Mikazuki!
Huh? Little sister?
Um, that's...
That's it. Mitsuki-chan,
tell Dr. Wakaouji to step outside.
Tell him that you're going to explain everything.
Okay. Can you come out here for a bit, Doctor?
I see. "Mikazuki" is your stage name, huh?
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Then what about the "little sister" part?
That's... Um...
I know! You...
...are going to debut as a "little sister" character to another talent in the company.
Eh... is that true?
It's not, but just tell him that anyway!
Ah. I see!
Apparently, I'm going to debut as the "little sister"
of another talent at the company.
So that's it! But...
There's still something else?
Hmm?
Oh well.
Hang in there, Mitsuki-chan.
The first impression is always the most important.
Now, you need to properly greet the manager, who's going to be taking care of you.
Shall we go back?
Man... sorry about that.
She hadn't told me the whole story yet.
It's nothing. Please don't worry about it.
Let's start over.
She's Mikazuki-chan, a little sister.
I'm looking forward to working together.
Me, too.
So then...
Um... where's the person herself?
Person herself...?
Um... l-let's see...
School! Say that she's at school!
Is that going to work?
It'll be fine!
Um... At...Attending school!
Ah. School, is it?
Yeah. She goes to school like she should.
See? That totally convinced both of them.
Well... it sure seems like it.
What do we do now? Shall we wait for her?
Wait... for whom?
Say she'll be here very soon!
She'll be here very soon, so...
Really? Then since her guardian, Dr. Wakaouji is here...
...I'll give him a general explanation of what we'll be doing.
Oh, sure.
That was too close.
Should we really let things keep going like this?
Ooshige-san, there's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
She's going to be very busy from now on, isn't she?
Her schoolwork comes first, right?
Yeah, there is that...
Let's not forget about your throat.
That won't be an issue.
We handle many girls
who are around Mitsuki's age...
... and they basically only work after school and on weekends.
I'm relieved to hear that.
That just leaves the issue of her debut event.
Since she's a fresh new artist chosen at such a major audition...
...it would be wise to have her debut
as soon as possible.
Of course, towards that end...
...we have voice training, dance lessons...
...and instruction in other fundamental skills
that she'll need to develop.
Hold on a minute.
You said something about voice training...
From that, it almost sounds as if
Mitsuki-chan were becoming a singer.
Oh man...
This would be the flaw in the plan.
Doctor! Actually, that's...
What are you going to do?
Um... Um... well...
Not this!
Hello~? Wait, what am I
supposed to do with a phone!?
Phone?
Ah, can you call her for me?
Ah... yes! You're going to do that!
Make a temporary retreat!
W-Wait!
What was that just now?
A belly roll?
Ah...
Things have taken a turn for the bizarre.
How stupid are you?
Can't you see how simple this is?
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
The manager, Ooshige-san...
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
...thinks that she's Mitsuki's little sister, Mikazuki.
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Dr. Wakaouji thinks that Mitsuki is...
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
...just using "Mikazuki" as a stage name.
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
So far, so good.
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
But, if Dr. Wakaouji finds out that I've become a singer...
...then everything we've strung together will become unraveled.
That's where we'll have to take drastic measures...
As I thought, it'd be best to tell Dr. Wakaouji the truth.
No way! If you spring something like this on him...
There's no way he'll believe it.
Yeah. You're the only human that can see Meroko and me.
That's right. How do you expect him to believe you about us Shinigami?
But unless we make him believe...
You're such a helpless kid.
Mero-Mero Change!
How's this?
There's two of me...
"How's this?"
Meroko, you...
If I'm in this form, I'll be able to do something.
I swear upon the honor of the leader of Negi Ramen,
the Shinigami Duo that silences childrens' tears, that I'll get everything squared away!
Doctor!
Mitsuki-chan!
I was worried. Where did you run off to?
Sorry! Mitsuki was... feeling a little sick!
Then, don't you think you should be lying down somewhere?
Nope! I'm totally fine now!
Really? I guess that's okay.
Her voice is kinda off...
Aw, c'mon!
Her personality's wrong, too...
No way, no way! It's just your imagination!
By the way, Mitsuki-chan...
Yes?
I don't quite understand what that Ooshige-san was talking about.
What do you mean?
From what she said, it sounded like you were going to become a singer.
That's because...
That's right! A commercial!
She was talking about a commercial!
Really?
Yep! And I'm playing the role of a girl who debuts as a singer!
Come on, come on! Hurry up.
Let's go back to where Ooshige-san is.
We still have things to discuss, don't we?
Ah... yeah... I guess so.
She's got a talent for coming up with one crazy idea after another...
It feels like she's building a house of cards.
But at least he bought it.
His face doesn't convince me that he's convinced.
I still have an ace up my sleeve!
Ah! Dr. Wakaouji, over there!
Wait, what? Whoa!
It looks like an emergency! Make a run for it!
E-Emergency? Wait!
W-Wait!
Now that the doctor is out...
Mero-Mero Change!
How's this?
Meroko... again?
For now, I'll go take care of the manager.
[ "desu wa" is a feminine sentence ending ]
I mean... I'll go take care of her.
[ "~de gozaru" is an archaic sentence ending ]
Nobody talks like that nowadays.
Well, I suppose this would be
the quick and easy path.
I wonder if... this is really okay...
Huh?
I... no, I mean...
[ Watashi is a feminine from of "I" ]
Is there something wrong with me?
[ Boku is a masculine, but boyish, form of "I" ]
No. Where is that girl?
She's feeling a little sick...
Huh?
She'll feel much better after resting, though.
Ah... is that so?
Your speech still sounds weird.
I know that.
Anyways, Ooshige-san...
Yes?
I've decided! I'm going to put my faith in you...
...and leave everything concerning Mitsuki to you.
I'm honored...
So, how are you going to explain this to the doctor?
Well...
Yes. This is Wakaouji.
Yes.
Ah. I understand.
Ooshige-san.
There seem to be visitors for you in the parking lot.
For me?
I wonder who it could be...
Again?
Once we make it through this,
everything should be resolved.
This certainly is tiring, though...
I can't just leave things up to Meroko and Takuto...
I have to go and tell the truth!
Man... Mitsuki-chan.
That business about an emergency was utter nonsense.
D-Dr. Wakaouji!
What is it this time?
Is there a fire or something?
Or did a wolf show up?
That's not it!
Something showed up, but it wasn't a wolf!
Um, they call themselves "Negi Ramen!"
Maybe you really should be lying down.
Like I said, they're Shinigami
who call themselves Negi Ramen...
What are you two doing out here?
Come in, come in.
You'll just have to trust Meroko on this one.
Dr. Wakaouji.
Yes?
Mitsuki-chan is amazing!
Ah... not that  much...
Well, anyways I think she's
a great girl who's full of talent.
R-Really?
Please! Put your faith in me!
Leave Mitsuki-chan to me!
O-Okay.
Ah... what a bother.
There weren't any visitors here to see me.
What do you mean by visitors?
But... you just told me that there were...
I did?
At any rate, Kouyama Mitsuki is depending on you from now on!
It's my pleasure.
Okay!
I really want... Mitsuki-chan to do her best.
As a doctor,
giving you check-ups is about all I can do.
But beyond being your doctor, I...
...wanted to be something of a father figure for you.
Doctor...
Work hard, okay?
Dr. Wakaouji...
Mitsuki, a moment?
Are you okay, Meroko?
This must be the first time she's
transformed so many times in one day.
'Sup...
She's already at her limit.
I'm still juuust fine.
Whom should I transform into this time?
Ooh, I wanna be Takuto!
Um... Dr. Wakaouji.
Yes?
Forgive me if I'm wrong, but...
...didn't you use to play keyboards in Route L?
Eh... yeah.
Just as I thought... you're that prince!
I was a huge fan of yours!
Oh, really?
I really was an incredible fan of yours!
We passed by each other at some studio somewhere.
I wasn't working behind the scenes back then;
I was also aiming to be an idol.
But unfortunately, I failed miserably.
Oh, that's right.
Now that I finally have this chance...
...could I get your autograph?
Does Mitsuki-chan have a cell?
Ah, Mikazuki-chan!
Huh? Yes?
Mitsuki-chan is still in high school, right?
Eh... yes.
Actually, I came to give her a cellular phone today.
She'd be hard to reach without one, right?
Yeah...
That's right. I'll be heading to
the high school to give it to her.
Great timing. Thanks for your help.
What are you going to do?
If she goes to the high school,
Mitsuki won't be there.
Takuto! Please make me sixteen!
I want to talk to her myself!
Guess I've got no choice.
If I'm the 16-year-old Kouyama Mitsuki...
...I'll be able to introduce myself to Ooshige-san properly!
Ooshige-san!
Mitsuki-chan?
Yes. I'm sorry for being late.
I heard from my little sister that you were coming here.
Really? I'm glad we got to meet.
Yes!
Pleased to meet you. I'm Kouyama Mitsuki!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Ooshige Masami from Village Pro.
You'll be very busy from now on,
so you'd better be ready!
So I say, but you're still a new artist, right?
I'll have to fully train you from the ground up.
Please take care of me!
Okay. For now, let's work hard!
Okay!
Eichi-kun, I have a manager now.
Everything's finally falling into place...
...for me to become a singer!
There's just one thing that's never gonna change...
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
the dream that I have always been drawing.
Zutto egaiteta yume
How would I, as I am right now
ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
look to those small eyes I used to have?
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
Say, won't you look up? The night sky stretches so far.
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Yes... very soon... you will understand...
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up...
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
...and find the full moon.
Full Moon wo sagashite
Let's sing a song!
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now.
itsu demo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
Day by day...
Day by day
I hold the fate dealt by the past and the hopes of tomorrow in my heart.
kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou wo kono mune ni kakae
Let's sing a song!
Together, forever! As long as I'm with you, I can overcome any pain.
itsu demo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
More and more...
More and more
More and more and more... to be closer to you,
I stand here now and give...
Motto motto motto chika zukitai ima koko ni itekurete
Many thanks for you!
PREVIEW FOR NEXT TIME
That girl's debut has finally arrived.
Her producer is the super-famous Takasu Kohei!
Hmm, that's impressive.
But you know... She said she doesn't like
Takasu's songs, and that she'd write her own.
Can an amateur like her really do something like songwriting?
It's all right. Everything will work out as long as I'm there.
No it won't! You see, songwriting is...
...something you have to put your soul into!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
The Feelings in Your Song.
THE FEELINGS IN YOUR SONG
Look forward to it!