I've never worn such light, smooth clothes before.
Tsk!
Cal...
Confrontation
So those are the details of the plot Claudia McCunnen has weaved so far.
She trapped me in order to bring me down,
persuaded Zwei, who became Phantom,
and seized Wisemel's power.
One can only say that her way of handling things is simply superb.
Lizzie Garland contacted me.
Claudia McCunnen has disappeared.
Looks like she isn't going to show up and give excuses on this matter.
lt's hard to believe, Scythe Master...
but I think we could see this as the proof of your story.
According to your suggestion,
we should keep collaborating with the Godo Family who supported Claudia?
The cocaine robbery from a year ago surely is a painful memory to Inferno.
However, the profit from the market run by the Godo Family in the Far East
is several times greater than the loss.
Hm.
On top of that, if we are to put rational arguments aside,
please give consideration to the excellent decision of Mr. Shiga...
who disciplined his own people as soon as he learned the truth.
I see. It is, indeed, a reasonable suggestion. However...
Of course, I'll have the Godo Family reduce the margin they were demanding
as the penalty for this incident.
That's okay, right?
Okay, then Mr. Shiga...
With regards to Claudia McCunnen, who enticed your brothers...
we promise she will receive the cruelest of punishments.
Thank you very much Mr. McGwire.
We're currently investigating where Claudia ran off to,
but the question is Phantom.
What will that man do?
Would it be okay Mr. McGwire...
if I send Ein to pursue him?
A confrontation between the current and the previous Phantom, huh?
Interesting.
Are you suggesting we become subordinate to the Bloodies?!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's almost like Romero was killed by Isaac himself!
The Bloodies are now being backed by...
a newer, stronger organization.
So what?!
One of these days, the era of Inferno will come without fail.
Do you want to push your way to the top that bad?
You'd even sell yourself to the one who killed your little brother?!
I'll get to where Romero couldn't.
I believe that doing so is the best thing I can do for him.
I don't want to give up now.
Please come with me, Lizzie Garland. I need you.
It's true that I'm a gangster, but I have no intention of becoming depraved.
There's a code of conduct that I can't compromise...
one more important than acting out of self interest!
If you swear that you won't cross that line...
then yeah, Clo...
I'll come with you.
I promise.
You fool! You jumped the gun.
You're a big fool!
No luck. I can't find anything.
Dammit! Contact Lizzie. Tell her that nothing turned up here.
I found the key to that car.
This car always looks so cool.
We don't often get a chance like this. I wish we could've had the owner, too.
Tell me about it.
Reiji... Good...
Seems like you're okay.
I guess you know the situation more or less, right?
Claudia, you were...
I'm not going to justify myself to you.
I've done the best I could all this time to survive in the organization. That's all.
I've paid you a reasonable compensation, too.
I'm not giving up yet.
I can still recover, Reiji...
if I'm with you...
We'll leave LA and join an organization on the east coast.
But in order to protect myself from Inferno's pursuers,
I need your help, Reiji.
I'll be waiting for you at that drive-in on route 39.
This time for real, I'm entrusting you with my life.
Cal...
Such minor scars can be removed anytime.
But I purposely did not allow such treatment. Do you know why?
Yes, Master.
What do those scars mean?
Humiliation and corruption.
That's right.
Ein, you were my masterpiece,
but you were tainted by that man twice in the past.
You're far from perfection right now. You're trash that's hard to even look at.
But even then, I kept you, wrecked, by my side...
because I thought that reformation might be possible when the time comes.
Kill Zwei.
Avenge your defeats with your own hands.
If you restore yourself on your own and take back the brilliance,
I'll have those scars removed, too.
I'll once again love you as my work.
I appreciate it, Master.
Will Ein be able to defeat Reiji Azuma?
When push comes to shove,
she'll finish off Zwei even if they end up stabbing each other...
without hesitating to sacrifice her own life.
Oh? You're going to dispose of her after all this?
By having gained Ein, an experiment...
my art is about to advance to an even higher level.
Although she's memorable as my first completed work,
I don't find much value in a monument, so...
But as it is the final stage, you could've used a more reliable method.
Sometimes an actor's acting exceeds the director's direction.
And sometimes the paintbrush moves in an unexpected way.
Surprising both, the artist and the audience...
It's mischief caused by the Muses.
Will the finale be a tragedy... or a comedy?
Entrusting the plot of the finale to fate is...
a great thrill that causes your heart to race, don't you think?
Isn't killing her too much for you, Lizzie Garland?
Don't underestimate me. Who do you think I am?
You and Claudia have known each other for a long time.
You might become emotional and hesitate to pull the trigger.
Shut up, you asshole.
Girls don't like guys who aren't on time, Reiji.
Everything... started here.
Zwei...
I... I'm...
I'm not called... Zwei.
What...
What... have I been doing?
I wanted to keep running like this...
so fast that no one can catch up, leaving everything behind...
You'll eventually fly away into the sky, you know.
That would be really wonderful. That's real freedom...
How far were you planning to go by taking such huge risks?
I don't have a set goal. I'll just go as far as I can.
That's stupid.
You'll get tired from running someday and stop.
If you're not standing on the ground then, what are you going to do?
There must've been some things that you shouldn't have left behind, right?
Yeah... But that's alright.
There were sceneries that you could see only when you run with this speed.
I just wanted to chase them.
Even until the end...
You fool...
I'm sorry.
Are you going to die like this without doing anything?
Fighting against you is useless.
That'll be a problem for me. I was ordered to fight and achieve victory...
to prove that I am the strongest one... the one and only Phantom.
l see. If that's the case, I'll go along.
You're tough...
So you're still given...
reasons that you can fiercely fight for like this...
by that Scythe?
Elen...
Why?
There's no way I can win.
Nor do I think that I want to win.
I've had... enough.
Even if I could kill you and escape from this situation, what do I do after that?
What will change?
Being lied to and manipulated, I can't even protect what I cherish.
The exit is nowhere to be found.
I can't stand this repetition any more.
So please... finish it this time for sure... with your hands.
I see.
I won't blame you. I don't think it can be helped.
I surely couldn't bear it, either.
But you're surviving and still fighting... even now...
for that Scythe.
No.
My reason for living is...
this...
You told me to survive.
I swore to fight of my own free will.
This is the mark you engraved then.
I admired your strength on that day, although it was a short period of time.
The evidence of your promise remains on my body.
So I couldn't give up on my life.
That's...
You are my other self.
Taking my place, you walked the path that I gave up on
while fighting... and resisting.
So I've lived dreaming of you...
thinking that even now, my other self is living strongly and freely somewhere.
This scar always reminded me of it.
But there's no way that I can bear such a pain forever.
If you're going to give up, no one can blame you.
So...
if you're going to break your promise from that day... first eliminate me.
End everything now.
There's no way I can do that.
It's okay. I'm Master's failure.
I'm a puppet that's just waiting to be discarded.
Elen...
The only reason this world isn't an endless hell
is because you're alive.
So, please... kill me.
I don't want to live in a world without you.
Up until today, I couldn't keep any promise.
I thought I lost everything.
Reiji...
But if my promise is still alive here,
then I want to keep at least that one.
That'll be, for sure, my last...
I'll take you away from Scythe.
Things seem to have turned out in a very disappointing manner indeed.
Well, I don't know about that.
It could also be just an intermission.
Bro...
Thank you, Reiji!
I'll take good care of it.
I'll take good care of it... always.
Cal...
Cal... I can't go to the world where you're waiting for me for a while.
I still have unfinished business to take care of.
Reiji?
Let's go.
Next episode
Promise
Liar.
You said we'd never be separated.
You said you'd stay with me.