Welcome!
Excuse me.
Y-Yes!
I'd like...
Mamedai!
What?!
I just love Mamedai here.
Well, same here...
I was thinking how you're such a nice gal, and how I'd love to be in the same class as you...
And how I loved you!
Wh-What? Th-That's not...
I was talking about mame daifuku! You know, sweet bean mochi!
Oh, those?
Yes, those!
Whether we misunderstand or make mountains out of molehills...
Whatever the reason, the blooming of the flower called love is often embarrassing.
But even those embarrassing moments can end up being fun.
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
These beans are quite delicious.
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
Hey, Dad.
What's up?
Making sweet bean mochi's all well and good,
but since this is autumn, how about putting in some grapes?
Or maybe some diced pears, or even persimmons!
Ain't happening.
Our mochi's perfectly fine with sweet beans.
Huh?!
What about last spring?
That strawberry mochi we made was the talk of the town, you know?
Yer that quick to drive us outta the family, are ya?
Huh?
Mamedai!
Fuku!
Mochi!
Okay, okay.
Huh?
Do you know that song, Dela?
How could I not? You're always humming it.
Oh, I see.
So, did you figure out what song it was?
Nope, not yet.
I do wonder.
Tamako!
Yes?
Shaddup.
Hm?
Dad?
Good morning.
Oh, morning.
What's up?
I was wondering which sweet bean mochi would be the best.
Huh? Why's that?
One of my friends said they'd be stopping by to buy some.
Oh, really?
They wanted it for a gift, apparently.
So leave a few decently shaped ones for them, okay?
Got it. How many?
Ten packs of five.
And what's their name?
H-His name's Yuzuki.
Oh?
Tamako.
Breakfast's ready.
Thanks, Choi.
In the dusk...
Episode 9
Breaking Out Into a Love Song
of the music room...
This is delicious!
I don't know how we managed without you, Choi.
It's pretty nice having a stylish breakfast like this.
Knives and forks!
It's like I'm in a different country!
Lady Choi!
Could I join you for break—
You had some beans just before, didn't you?
So you can eat after we serve everyone some tea.
Yes, ma'am!
Oh, right. Dad.
About Mochi Day...
What?
How about we pound some mochi? It's Mochi Day!
Even though it ain't New Year's?
I hear Mochizou's place will be giving out character merchandise on Mochi Day.
Character?!
Free to anyone who spends more than a thousand yen—
A mochimochi charm!
The heck's this?
Mochi pounding sounds a heck of a lot better.
Let's pound some mochi, then.
Yeah!
Wait, ain't this just a normal rain charm?
Mochi pounding? That sounds like fun.
Come eat some, okay?
Huh?
Aren't you gonna let me pound some mochi?
Hammering nails is one of my key
specialties, so I think I'd be great at it.
Oh, yeah!
You'd probably pound them into oblivion!
Hey, you two!
Get practicing!
You're setting a bad example for the freshmen!
Yes, ma'am.
Midori's pretty tough.
That's "Captain" to you!
Captain!
Hm? What is it?
With great power comes great change in personality.
Too bad you couldn't become captain, huh?
Yeah, but I'll usurp the throne by the time we graduate.
Seriously? There's a day for that?
When is it?
Mochi Day's on October 10th.
That's also my birthday!
Is it?
At least remember that!
Oh, didn't we talk about this last year too?
See you tomorrow, guys.
Later.
Hey!
Anko!
'Sup?
Oh, Mocchi.
Hey, did Tamako ask you for advice about anything recently?
Nope, nothing.
Like "What birthday present should I get Mochizou?", perhaps?
She's forgotten all about it because the only thing on her mind right now is Mochi Day.
I-I see.
Well, I guess that's to be expected.
Mochi Day and all.
Ahh, I've had enough of this!
Oh, I'm not that depressed. Don't worry about it.
You're the least of my worries right now!
I didn't end up any thinner, but
because I built up some muscle...
I can fly easily even when I'm nice and round!
Two blocks of firm tofu, please.
Sure thing, Dela.
You're looking well, Dela.
Some slices of cod, please.
Sure.
Now I need to get onions, cabbages, carrots, and chrysanthemums.
Hey, An.
We're having some fish hotpot thing tonight.
I see.
Hey, An! Wait up!
But I can't leave yet!
Er, what else was I supposed to buy again?
Onions, cabbages, carrots, and chrysanthemums.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
Oh, come on!
Here you go, Tamako.
So pretty!
Welcome back, Tamako.
Thanks.
Thanks, Dela.
This is hot!
They're good when freshly fried, huh?
I'm home!
Welcome home.
You seem to be your usual self.
Huh?
Anko looked down in the dumps.
Now that you mention it...
I'm back, Choi!
Welcome back.
I'll help!
Is that supposed to be a god?
It's an offering to my mother.
It's called a monovase.
I'm home!
W-Welcome back.
Hey, Anko.
Let's have rice omelets tonight!
You said you wanted to eat some the other day, right?
Weren't we having fish hotpot?
We could save that for tomorrow.
Nah, hotpot's fine with me.
Anko!
Yer classmate's here to pick up some sweet bean mochi!
Hey, Anko!
Got it!
That's Yuzuki, right?
Dad didn't have to be that loud!
Your face looks like mochi!
I'm heading downstairs, okay?
Grandfather humbly requests that you try some of this store's delicious mochi and hot tea.
Thank you.
You can have half, if you'd like.
Really? Don't mind if I—
Er, I don't mind if I miss out. I'll pass.
Tamaya's chicken is really talkative, isn't it?
I am no chicken!
Ten packs of five, right?
Y-Yes. Thank you very much.
No, thank you.
I wonder what Anko's up to...
Dela. Please send for her.
Right away!
An!
Your boyfriend's here!
Won't you greet him?
Stupidela!
Perhaps she's sleeping.
Sorry about that.
Don't be. Tell her I said hi.
I'll be on my way now.
Hotpots are tasty, aren't they?
This thing is so bittersweet!
Let's make some rice porridge later!
Thanks for the food.
You're done already?
Yeah. I think I'll go to bed now.
Did you catch a cold?
Maybe.
Listen up, Mochizou.
Could you do me a favor?
Anko's been acting kinda depressed.
Could something have happened at school?
I'm a bit worried.
Over.
Now that you mention it, she was acting a bit weird when I saw her on my way home today.
All right. I'll ask her tomorrow—
I'm off.
Huh?
What's up, Mocchi?
You're leaving earlier than usual today.
Well, I'm on duty.
Sis is still getting ready.
No, I didn't come here for Tamako today.
I see.
Hey! Anko, wait!
I already told you! Sis has forgotten all about your birthday!
That's fine.
Huh? It is?
More importantly, Anko.
A bad test score isn't going to ruin your entire life.
What are you talking about?
Huh? That's not it?
Then, just because you fought with your friend doesn't mean—
No, I didn't.
You got yelled at by a teacher, then.
You tripped and fell in the hallway...
No, I didn't.
You fell down the stairs?
None of the above!
What is it, then?
Yuzuki's transferring away!
Once first semester ends and autumn break begins...
On October 10th! Mochi Day!
Tamako Market
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
What's this, Gohei?
You too?!
Of course!
Today's Mochi Day, after all.
I'll be starting first!
Hell no, I am!
Mochizou!
Go get the mochi dough!
Okay, Dad!
Don't ya dare call me dad!
Why're you going into their store?!
Is the dough ready, Tamako?
Yep.
All right! I'll carry it out.
Oh yeah, Mochizou. Did you ask Anko?
Y-Yeah.
What'd she say?
She said her friend's moving today.
Anko's got her own stuff to deal with too, you know.
I see.
Let's go.
Anko.
Use this.
It's grated radish.
We've got some pork soup prepared too, okay?
Thanks.
Anko!
Hello.
We came to help.
Look, Anko.
I practiced pounding mochi just for today.
Kanna Smash!
Bam!
Kanna Crusher!
Wham!
Midori, what time is it now?
Huh?
Almost four.
One... two...
Bam!
Once more!
Here I go!
Wham!
There.
And again!
Slam!
Dela!
Mochi pounding looks similar to our prayer for the Earth's blessings.
Oh, now that you mention it,
it really does!
Kanna, what's that?
A snake.
Lady Choi?! That's—
Those hand movements call forth the rain!
Swinging your hips like that quickens crop growth!
This is indeed our island's Earth Dance!
Lady Choi's...
Lady Choi's enjoying herself!
Choi's so cute!
That looks like the mochi pounding pose Kanna was making earlier.
All right! I'll pound some mochi next!
I, Makino Kanna, will form the bridge between mallet and millstone for the sake of mochi's bright future!
Here I go.
Bam!
Go for it!
Now.
Kanna's swinging for the fences, isn't she?
Wham!
Slam!
Anko.
What is it, Mocchi?
Anko, you should go see Yuzuki and say your goodbyes.
You can still make it, right?
He said they're leaving by car in the evening.
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
Then go right now!
I can't go!
Even if I did, I wouldn't know what to say to him!
How about...
"I love you," maybe?
That is so stupid!
"Best of luck," then?
Anybody could say that!
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
Just tell him you love him.
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
That's impossible!
Anko.
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
Here.
What's this?
What about An?
I'm asking Anko to run an errand for me.
Oh.
Please do this for me, okay?
Go take this to Yuzuki.
Huh?
I want him to eat this mochi.
I know he'll just love it.
I mean, it's freshly pounded mochi!
It obviously tastes better when eaten right away.
Yeah.
Is freshly pounded mochi tasty?
Yep.
Would he be happy if he got some?
Of course!
Okay, I'll go, then!
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
Dela.
What is it?
Take care of Anko.
Roger that. Leave her to me.
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
Thanks, Mochizou.
October 10th
is Mochi Day!
Oh no, it got dirty!
An!
Run, An!
Dela!
As for me, I'll fly!
And I'll go on ahead!
Hey!
That's kinda unfair!
Anko?
What's wrong?
Well, uh...
Anko! Are your knees okay?
Y-Yeah.
Hold on a sec. I'll get some bandaids—
Hey, wait!
Come on, An! This is it!
Uh, here!
Eat up.
Uh...
Dela!
My apologies.
Um... here. It's freshly pounded mochi.
Mochi?
Y-Yeah!
Today's Mochi Day, so we were
pounding mochi over at our place!
And this is freshly pounded mochi!
Freshly pounded mochi's delicious!
There's Anko inside—
No, wait! I meant the red bean paste kind!
But I fell on my way here, so they might be a bit disfigured...
And so...
Thanks, Anko.
We always get Tamaya's mochi for New Year's decorations.
So we'll be coming over to your place around that time to place our orders and pick them up.
I can see you then, right?
Don't hold back. Eat as much as you want.
Delicious!
And you're eating a bit too much.
See? Your cheeks are all squishy!
I'm next! Let me touch them too!
There!
Squishy-squishy!
I know it's kind of an idiotic thing
But I'll make you happy forever
I love you
I love you so much it hurts
Dad! That song!
Come with me for a bit!
Tamako!
What's happening?
Where are you going?
Hey, wait! Hold on!
Stop making a fuss.
What's all this about?
Dunno. But you come too, Anko.
Oh, so that was the song you were talking about?
Its melody's a lot different from what you made it sound like, though.
Well, she was tone deaf!
"She"?
That was the song Dai wrote for Hinako.
Mom?
You wrote it?!
Kunio! Don't tell her what she doesn't need to know!
Dai and me used to be in a band when we were students.
In the dusk
of the music room,
you play the piano
I see your
gentle face
in profile
It's Dad.
I'm drawn to it
That's Dad?!
So you're saying this is the song you've been talking about?
I can't look away
It sounds nothing like it.
I write down your
It's a love song?
telephone number,
over and over to memorize it
What's all this? Did something happen?
I pick up
They looked so cool!
Both the record guy and Tamako's dad!
the receiver
Dad once fell in love with someone too, didn't he?
and keep turning the dial
Yeah, and that someone happens to be our mom!
without calling you
Oh, I see.
I can't muster up
the courage to do it
I will sing this song for you, if nothing else
I know it's kind of an idiotic thing
Thanks a lot for today, Mocchi.
No problem. See you tomorrow.
Oh, right. Hold on a sec, Mochizou.
But I'll make you happy forever
Mochizou.
Happy birthday!
I love you
Happy Birthday, Mochizou!
"Everybody loves somebody."
That's what they say.
Everyone falls in love someday.
I love you so much it hurts
Just like I did with you.
I can't muster up
My songs
the courage to tell you
I will sing this song for you, if nothing else
I want only you to listen to it
I saw the tape, Dad!
Dad!
You know, Dad.
I love you even more now!
Shaddup!
Everybody loves somebody.
Tamako Market
Autumn and chestnuts go hand in glove, don't they?
Tamako here.
Chestnuts are so tough on the outside, but they're so sweet and tasty on in the inside.
Aren't they adorable?
Eat some chestnut mochi and you'll feel right as rain!
Episode 10      A Flower Blooms on Her Baton
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?