Question 11
Yuuji, Shouko, and their Childhood Memories
Where did I go wrong?
When did I set my heart on him?
If I had the chance to start over...
To go back to that time, that place...
From the moment I laid my eyes on him...
...I'd want to set her free.
It's my fault for so carelessly capturing her heart.
No.
That wasn't it.
I realized what was beyond that.
I found something more important.
That's why...
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
"There's a child prodigy in Minazuki Elementary School."
That rumor started a few years back,
and indeed, that child was a faster thinker than those around him.
Furthermore, he was a diligent, hardworking boy.
Adults praised him highly,
and expected many great things of him.
Yet he...
You're really amazing, Yuuji.
How so?
The teacher praised your last mock exam scores.
"That's our prodigy," he said.
It's nothing really.
But you scored higher than even middle-schoolers.
I guess.
You really are amazing.
The sixth graders who took the exam with us were vexed.
I messed up a social studies question.
I would've been number one if it weren't for that.
I was always aiming for the top back then.
"He'll definitely receive a recommendation for Shimozuki Middle!"
That's what everyone said!
It's a piece of cake if I want to.
Well, too bad for the others though.
However, convinced that I'm smarter than my peers, I naturally looked down upon them.
Hurry up, Shouko.
We'll go home after you're done with that.
But I want to talk with you.
No way. I wanna go home.
Let's talk.
No.
I wanna.
You know, Yuuji...
My breasts have grown recently.
Are you all right, Yuuji?
Where the hell did that come from?!
You were ignoring me, so I changed the topic to something that might interest a guy.
Th-That doesn't interest me at all!
Well, I definitely was interested.
Cut the chatter and finish your work!
I know that.
But I still want to talk with you.
You can just chat with your friends.
Yeah.
That's why I'm chatting with you right now.
Jeez.
Shouko stood out in class.
With a well-to-do family, good grades, athletic talent,
and of course, her good looks—
you could say she was overly blessed in every aspect.
Kirishima Shouko
I'm... Kirishima Shouko.
She's so cute!
Totally!
Hey, try talking to her!
Why don't you go?
You like her, don't you?
I don't!
Don't you think she's acting too cutesy?
Her family's loaded, right?
So she's one of those rich girls?
It's kinda hard to talk to her.
I know.
I guess it's only natural that Shouko got attached to me.
I treated everyone equally, after all.
It's already been two years since you transferred here.
Yeah.
I've made a few more friends I can chat with, too.
So school's become more fun for me recently.
Eh? School is fun?
No one plays with me at home.
There's no one to talk with.
My home's so large that I feel lonely.
School is a lot more fun.
How spoiled you are!
I'd love to have a huge house like that.
Why don't you come to my place next time?
No thanks. Reading is a hundred times
more fun than playing with you.
Meanie.
Whatever.
Cheapskate.
What about it?
Blockhead.
I'm fine with that.
You...
You really like me.
That's why you're too embarrassed to come over.
Man, why do you want me to come over so badly?
Um...
Why is it? Just spit it out!
Grandpa's been talking about Seiryuu Girls' Academy often.
That prestigious girls' school?
Are you going to transfer again?
Probably.
My family always asks if I'm bullied at school.
I see.
So you wanted to show them
you have friends to stop them, right?
I don't want to transfer.
I finally made some friends aside from you.
Why don't you bring them over then?
I'm still not that close to them.
Well, it's nothing to do with me.
I treated everyone equally.
That was because,
I couldn't give a damn about anyone.
You're so mean, Yuuji.
I'm not.
You are.
Are.
Not.
Yuuji.
My breasts are the largest in the class.
Class Duty
Still, it was enough to make a lonely young girl,
I said I wasn't interested in them, didn't I?!
find hope in him.
Hey, Sakamoto!
Don't ignore us!
Don't think you can run away!
Don't be so big-headed!
This is why I wanted to get home quick.
What did you say?
What do you guys want?
I don't have time to waste on guys like you.
You've got some mouth to talk to your seniors that way.
You're so cocky for a fifth grader!
You guys have been waiting here to get me day after day since I beat you on the mock exam.
Don't you have anything better to do?
Too lonely since you don't have friends?
You're the one who's got no friends!
Getting all cocky just because you're smart!
We're sixth graders!
Show some respect!
Respect?
You guys are dumbasses.
Do you even know what "respect" means?
Why should I show respect to dumbasses like you?
You—
We're your seniors!
And even with an extra year of studying,
you guys still lost to me...
And now you want me to show you some respect? Don't make me laugh.
You should show me some respect.
What did you say?!
You sure you wanna do this?
The teachers will know if anything happens to me.
Unlike you, I'm special.
Got it? Then get lost.
Don't let me see you around here again.
That guy's pissing me off.
I'll get him back one day.
How do we do that?
We'll just trash his locker or shoe box if we can't get him directly.
Good one! No one will know who did it!
All right. Let's teach him some manners.
Let's do that.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Yuuji.
You're late today.
I was doing class rep duties.
Oh, really?
I thought you were playing with Shouko-chan.
Why would I be playing with her?
How stupid.
You're friends, aren't you?
You're wrong.
There you go again.
She'll be a real beauty by the time she's grown up.
If you keep rejecting her, it'll be too late to say, "My god! She's as hot as Mom!"
I won't.
And you're not hot, Mom.
You're so mean!
I'm gonna be late tomorrow as well.
Oh, more class duties?
Nah.
I have to teach those seniors of mine a lesson.
Your seniors?
Stuff happened.
By the way, you're wearing an apron. Don't tell me you—
I'm gonna make your favorite, meat and potato stew!
I just finished peeling the sweet pot—
Why are there sweet potatoes in the stew?!
Well, potatoes crumble too easily.
So I used the tougher sweet pot—
You'll have the definition of meat and potato stew,
crumbling before them!
Ugh, never mind.
At least that sounds edible.
Oh yeah, I forgot to get the meat, so how 'bout some meatless meat and potato stew—
That'd just be steamed sweet potatoes!
Library
As they couldn't touch me,
they were gonna go after my stuff.
Knowing that, I provoked them on purpose.
This is going to be fun.
I've already got everything valuable they might go after.
My plan was to kill time until
the three sixth graders got on the move,
and go call a teacher once they start
messing with my belongings.
All right.
I'll continue that book I was reading the other day.
Being intellectually superior to others, I began to think of myself as some sort of hero.
Huh?
Oh right...
Shouko didn't come and pester me today.
Wednesday
Day Duty
Kirishima
Absentees
Ryuu
Latecomers
Ooshima
Early leavers
Things done
Call
Class Duty
Kirishima
Question 11
Read the following
passage and answer
the questions given.
"Where did Sadakichi go?" asked Jihei.
Daisuke shrugged and answered,
"He's at Okiku's place.
He said he was going to use his skills to
write a poem that expresses the feelings
he's harbored for 10 years."
Upon hearing that, Jihei raised an
eyebrow and said,
"So he's gonna read poetry to her, huh?
We both know how that's gonna end."
"Totally. He's untalented (                ).
Question 1
Fill in the blank in the common phrase and
state its meaning.
Question 2
What sort of ending does the underlined "end"
refer to? Describe the ending that Jihei and Daisuke anticipate.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Question 1
He's untalented
(but earnest).
This means that despite
being enthusiastic about
his poetry, he lacks ability.
Question 2
They are expecting him to
fail due to his amateurish
writing.
Teacher's Comment
Correct. There are many other ways the sentence could be completed, such as
"He's untalented (and unoriginal)". Both phrases mean the person is inept in
some way. From that, it's obvious that Jihei and Daisuke are expecting
Sadakichi to fail.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
Question 1
He's untalented
(but determined).
This means he's trying
his best although he's
not very good.
Question 2
They expect Okiku to be
touched by how hard
Sadakichi worked to write
his poetry, even though
he's bad at it.
Teacher's Comment
This is far from correct, but I still quite
like your answer.
I was always following Yuuji around back then.
Even if he was cold towards me,
Yuuji was the only one who treated me fairly.
I wonder if he's still at school.
That's why I liked being around him.
Damn, nothing here either! That guy's sly!
Maybe someone already took his shoes?
They just might have!
Someone must've had the exact same idea!
Fine, let's do something else.
Sakamoto
So what should we write here? How about "I cheated on all my tests!"?
Good one!
Excuse me!
Um...
Th-That's...
Who are you?
Those are Yuuji's.
Please, don't do that!
What? It's none of your business!
Get out.
But... Yuuji is my friend.
It might have bothered Yuuji if he had heard me say that.
That was what I thought.
But...
It is my business!
He actually has friends?
And a girl, too!
Forget about her. Let's just do it.
Okay.
Let's make this a big one.
Stop!
What— Get off me!
"We ain't friends" is what Yuuji would've said, I thought.
No!
Cut it out!
Hey you!
Get off!
You're in the way!
No!
Get lost, I said!
Even so, I...
No!
Are you all right?
What have you done to my clothes?!
You're pissing me off!
Stop!
Too late for that now.
Those guys should've fallen right into my trap.
They're at it!
Wh-What is this?!
Why is Shouko caught up with—
Could she be...
It was immediately apparent why she'd gotten involved.
I-I gotta save her...
Yes, just like the hero that I wanted to be.
After all, they were just a bunch of idiots,
and I was a smart, unique individual.
There shouldn't have been anything to fear.
It's gonna be fine.
Calm down.
Those guys are nothing!
There were three of them; the outcome was obvious.
Oh right, I can call a teacher...
What will happen to Shouko then?!
If news of her getting bullied reaches her parents...
She'll be transferred!
That's got nothing to do with me!
What other choice do I have?!
Don't you know the answer already?
I just wanted to teach them a lesson.
So you're gonna pretend you never saw anything.
Like I can do that!
Friendship
Hard work
Hope
Dreams
Guts
Talent
Courage
No matter what you choose, you're gonna be hurt.
You're sure to be hurt in one way or another.
Even so, there's only one thing for you to do, isn't there?
But they're older than me!
And three of them, too! There's no way I can win!
Whose fault is this?
But...
Oh, you're afraid of getting hurt, aren't you?
Of course I am!
Aren't you a hero?!
A hero wouldn't back away.
He's gotta save people, even if he knows he's gonna lose—
Shut up! That only happens in manga and anime!
Weren't you making fun of them until now?
That's only with studies—
Smart guys have it tough, eh?
You're just scrambling for excuses,
to save your own ass.
So you're telling me it's better to be an idiot?
I guess so.
An idiot who jumps into the fray without thinking is way cooler than you are right now.
Why?
How did this happen?!
Why do I need to be so troubled over this?
I'm not the one at fault.
It's those three!
And Shouko too, for not thinking!
So...
Why, damn it?! Why?!
Oh yeah, Shouko could just shout for help.
That's right! She could just shout for help.
Then even if the teacher finds out about this, and she gets transferred,
it'll be her own doing.
It won't be my fault!
This is the right choice.
Shout out, Shouko! Shout for help!
It's better to be transferred than bullied, isn't it?!
Go on! Shout out!
Call for help!
Go on!
Shout for help now!
Shout! Shout! Shout!
Shout!
No! I don't want to transfer!
Why?
Why?!
Y-You guys!
What the hell are you doing?!
Yuu...ji...
You should know your limits!
Get lost, you guys!
Sakamoto!
And the main dude shows up.
We're going home, Shouko.
Hey!
Hold it right there, Sakamoto.
You're chickening out?
Yuuji...
Just let her go.
But—
I'm fine!
I'll call the teach—
Idiot!
I told you to go home first!
You're gonna get in my way!
Okay, I will.
I'll go home first.
I realized then, for the first time, how weak I was.
I was absolutely pitiful.
It was embarrassing.
And I,
seeing his trembling shoulders as he told me to run,
hated myself for being unable to help him.
The one who had dragged Shouko into this mess,
was none other than me.
And I had to pay for my wrongs.
No.
You're wrong, Yuuji.
That's not all.
I...
Welcome home, Yuuji.
I received a call from the school.
What happened?
Nothing.
Nothing happened.
That can't be true.
You're in such a sorry state.
I couldn't stand those guys, so I hit them.
Yuuji, is that all it was?
You're so noisy!
They pissed me off so I hit them!
There's no other reason!
They were annoying you, right?
Aunty...
I'm sorry.
He was protecting me and ended up like that.
Don't worry. You told me what really happened, so it's fine.
But if this isn't cleared up,
everyone else will think Yuuji was the bad guy!
And his recommendation for Shimozuki Middle will—
It's all right, Shouko-chan.
I don't want him to only excel in his studies.
I'm so happy that he could stand up for someone else!
You know, Aunty...
Yes, Shouko-chan?
When I grow up,
I will be his bride!
My my, how impatient you are!
I will make him happy!
That's supposed to be his line!
I got it wrong...
I'll cheer you on until the day he says those words to you!
Really?
Yes, really!
As long as you don't end up hating him someday.
Okay?
Don't worry.
I'm sure...
I will love him, always.
Hi-Ho! Let's Go!
itsudatta ka ima mo ieru
いつだったか今も言える
I feel like I can tell you now
wasureteta wake ja nai oboeteru
忘れてたわけじゃない覚えてる
I haven't forget; I still remember them
tsuyogatte shikato kimekonda
強がってシカト決め込んだ
I tried to ignore you before
sonna kao de minaide wakatteru
そんな顔で見ないでわかってる
Please, don't look at me with such a face
tsurai ze!
つらいぜ！
It's painful for me, do you know?
ikanakya ikenai kyou dake wa
行かなきゃ行けない今日だけは
Today, I must go
omae nya miserenu makeikusa
お前にゃ見せれぬ負け戦
I can't show you this losing battle
"Guddo jobu" oya yubi tate nagara
「グッドジョブ」親指立てながら
I put up my thumb and said "Good Job"
makenai ze itsudatte tsuyoki da ze!
負けないぜいつだって強気だぜ
I won't lose! I'll stand strong!
Hi-Ho! Let's Go!
omae ga iru kara
お前がいるから
As long as you're by my side
Hi-Ho! Let's Go!
ikeru
行ける
I can go on
Hi-Ho! Let's Go!
omae ga iru kara
お前がいるから
As long as you're beside me
Hi-Ho! Let's Go!
moeru
燃える
I can fire up
mainichi ore no senaka wo
毎日俺の背中を
You were patting me in the back every day
tataite kurete itsudemo
叩いてくれていつでも
I hope it'll go on forever
maitoshi tsunoru kimochi wo
毎年募る気持ちを
I can't tell you these feelings, which piles up every year
ienai amanojaku da yo
言えない天邪鬼だよ
How contradictory, isn't it?
rekishi ni nokoranai ga
歴史に残らないが
They won't be recorded in history,
omae no mune ni wa nokoru
お前の胸には残る
but they'll be recorded in your heart
sugee kotoba wa ore kara
スゲー言葉は俺から
I can only describe them with flashy words
tanomu kara ore kara iwasete kure
頼むから俺から言わせてくれ
Please, let me say them out to you
Question 12
Answer the following question.
What would be a phrase for a
group of suspicious individuals
who do as they please?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
A horde of demons.
Teacher's Comment
Correct as usual, Himeji.
In ancient times, this idiom was used to
refer to groups of actual demons and
spirits. Nowadays, this phrase is used to
refer to demons of a far more human
variety.
Sugawa Ryou's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 12: What would be a phrase for a group of suspicious individuals who do as they please?
Death to popular guys!
"Death to popular guys!"
That only applies to you
That only applies to you people.
people.
Next episode: Idiots, a Fool, and Requiem!
Idiots, a Fool, and Requiem
This will be on your test.