I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a little incident changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
We've crossed paths many times, and yet...
we still don't really know anything about each other.
Because I want to hear your answer,
and because I want to know you...
I've decided to confront you directly.
I could shake off my hesitation because I believe in the magic within my heart.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
I trembled with anxiety
Afraid of knowing the truth,
I shut the door to it
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
and found shelter in my dreams
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
that was dyed a deep blue
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
I ended up hurting your heart
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
and the truth behind my smile,
I will deliver my gentle love to you
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
Let us always walk together,
free from the shadows of loneliness
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
You three... return to the ship.
Understood...
And also, as for Nanoha
and Yuuno...
you two will be getting a lecture
from me on your actions.
Episode 10
Everyone's Separate Heartfelt Vows
Everyone's Separate Heartfelt Vows.
Orders aren't just for protecting the
individual, they affect the group as a whole.
What I mean is that your selfish actions
could have affected not only yourselves,
but also the people around you.
I trust that you understand?
Yes...
If this were a normal case, you both
could expect severe punishment, but...
taking your impressive results into account,
I will overlook your actions this time.
However...
this will not happen a second time.
Understood?
Yes.
We're sorry.
Now then... the real
problem starts now, huh?
Chrono, have you learned anything about
the incident, any data at all?
Yes. Amy, put it on the monitor.
Yes, yes!
Oh, my!
Right. A mage from our home world,
Midchilda, Presea Testarossa.
A researcher of new energy sources for interdimensional travel.
Despite being a great mage,
she conducted illegal research that
caused an accident, leading to her exile.
The data we have confirms the earlier attacks were from her.
And... that girl named Fate is most likely...
Fate... Back then, she said "Mother..."
M-Mother?!
Mother and daughter, huh?
U-Um... rather than surprised...
she looked more frightened.
Amy!
Are you able to pull up any more
information about this Presea woman?
Where she went after being exiled?
Any family members?
Anything at all?
Yes, yes. I'll look into it right away.
This woman... is Fate's mother...
Having that opportunity right in front of your face,
and then squandering it,
just mindlessly ignoring them...!
I'm... sorry...
You're too cruel, Fate.
Are you so intent on filling me with grief?
I want us to be friends.
Presea Testarossa...
according to Midchildan records,
she was the Central Technology Development
Bureau's third director 26 years ago.
At the time, she was working on new energy sources for interdimensional travel,
developing the "Hydra" reactor.
She conducted an experiment with
illegal materials... and it failed.
The results included a mid-scale
dimensional distortion at first...
which opened a wide fissure,
eventually engulfing the surrounding areas.
Apparently, it was a controversial incident.
She claimed that only the result was a failure,
and that no illegal materials were used.
She moved many times after that,
continuing her research in secret.
But at some point, she fell off the grid.
And that's about all I can find.
What about her family ties and her actions
up to the point when she went missing?
That data was completely erased.
Right now, the main office is
compiling that data for me.
How long will that take?
They said about a day or two.
With Presea and Fate
having used so much mana,
I doubt they'll act anytime soon.
And we still have to repair
the Arthra's shields, as well.
I think you two should take some time to rest.
Huh? But...
Especially you, Nanoha. It's not good
for you to miss school for so long.
I'll approve a return trip for now.
It'd be a good idea to see your family and
make an appearance at school again.
Yes...
Fate! Fate!
Fate! Fate...
Only nine...
It's enough for a dimensional distortion,
but I won't be able to reach Al-Hazard.
We don't have much time...
neither me nor Alicia...
You're her mother,
and she's your daughter, isn't she!?
She's working so hard for you...
She's doing everything she can for you...
How can you keep doing
such cruel things to her!?
That girl is certainly inept at creating familiars...
I can see she allowed this one
too many unnecessary emotions.
Fate is your daughter!
All she wants is to see you smile,
to return to your old,
kind self... that's why...!
You're a nuisance.
Disappear!
It doesn't matter where...
but I have to teleport...
I'm sorry, Fate... just wait a little while...
Fate. Wake up, Fate.
Yes... Mother.
These nine Jewel Seeds you've
managed to collect for me...
they're not enough.
In the worst case scenario,
I need at least five more.
More, if possible, but hurry and
get them, for your mother's sake.
Yes...
Arf...?
Oh?
That girl ran away.
She was afraid and wanted
nothing more to do with this.
If you need another, I can prepare
you an even better familiar.
Never forget... that the person who is
always truly on your side is your mother.
Do you understand, Fate?
Yes... Mother.
And the ten days I spent with her went by so quickly!
My. Is that so?
Lindy... I'm not sure whether
to call that a wonderful cover-up
or a complete lie...
It's pretty impressive.
Well, I obviously can't tell them the truth.
It's so your family doesn't worry, so please
call this my "consideration and concern."
But Nanoha is quite a good little girl.
I'd almost like my son to learn from her example.
My, my... there you go, saying things like that again!
My Chrono just has no social skills whatsoever!
Oh, that can't be!
Nanoha!
You came home so suddenly,
can you stay for a while?
Yeah.
Arisa and Suzuka have also
been really worried about you.
Have you gotten in touch with them yet?
Yeah. I sent them both a message earlier.
And, send!
Miss Arisa, did you receive
a nice message or something?
Not really. Just a normal text message.
Samejima! Stop the car for a second!
As I thought, it's a big dog...
It's injured... quite badly!
But it's still alive.
Samejima.
I understand, allow me to take care of it.
Fate...
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha.
Ah! You're finally awake.
Huh? I've seen this girl somewhere before...
You sure are a strong dog, aren't you?
You were hurt pretty badly,
but you survived.
Until you're fully recovered,
I'll take good care of you here at my house.
You can relax here.
Ah...
She's that girl's friend...
Go on. I warmed up some
dog food... can you eat?
If you can eat that much,
I guess that means you'll be okay.
After you finish eating, go to sleep so you
can hurry up and get better, okay?
Nanoha!
Thank goodness, you look well!
I am. Thanks, Suzuka.
Arisa... sorry for
making you worry, too.
Well... I guess it's nice...
to see that you're doing well...
I see... so you'll have to leave again...
Yeah...
It must be tough.
Yeah... but everything will be okay!
What about after school?
Can you hang out?
Yeah, no problem!
Then... how about my house?
I just got a new video game...
Really?
Oh, now that I think of it,
I also took in an injured dog last night.
A dog?
Yeah. It's really big,
and its fur is kind of orange...
There's also a red gem on its
forehead shaped like this.
So it really is you, Arf.
You, huh?
What's with those injuries?
And... where's Fate?
Oh, my... it looks sad now.
What's wrong? Are you feeling all right?
It might be in pain...
Should we just let her rest?
Yeah...
Yuuno! Hey now, that's dangerous.
I'm sure Yuuno will be fine.
Nanoha, I'll hear the story from her myself,
so you go with Arisa and Suzuka.
Okay.
Well then, how about some tea?
I happen to have some
really good tea inside.
Yeah!
I can't wait!
Right?
Yeah, yeah!
So what happened?
What happened between you two?
If you're here, then I guess the
Administrative Bureau is also watching, huh?
Yeah...
I'm Chrono Harlaown of the
Time-Space Administrative Bureau.
It would appear that your
circumstances are quite complex.
If you could explain them to me truthfully,
I promise nothing bad will happen to you.
Nothing will happen to either you
or your master, Fate Testarossa.
I'll tell you... everything.
But promise me...
promise me that you'll save Fate.
That girl hasn't done anything wrong.
I promise. Amy, start recording.
I already am.
Fate's mother... Presea Testarossa...
is where everything begins.
The hero takes 28 points of damage.
Remember the item you just got?
Use it here.
Which one? Which one?
Nanoha... did you hear?
Yeah... I heard everything...
Looking at your story, the current situation,
and her familiar's testimony and status...
it would appear that her story
is truthful and consistent.
What's gonna happen now?
We will arrest Presea Testarossa.
The fact that she attacked the Arthra
is enough to warrant an arrest.
So now that we have an order from the captain,
our mission will shift to Presea's arrest.
What will you do now, Nanoha Takamachi?
I...
I want to save Fate.
Because of Arf's feelings...
and also, because I want to.
Whenever I see Fate's sad face,
I somehow also feel a little sad.
So I want to save her...
from all the sad things in her life.
And I told her I wanted to be friends...
I haven't heard her
answer to that yet, either!
I understand.
We're also grateful that you're
lending us your magical power.
We'll leave everything regarding
Fate Testarossa to you, Nanoha.
Is that all right with you?
Yes...
Nanoha... right?
I don't have the right to
ask you... but... please...
Save Fate...
Right now... that girl really is all alone.
Yeah... it'll be fine. Just leave it to me.
You're late, Nanoha!
See? We were waiting for you so
we could enter this new dungeon.
Sorry, sorry!
Ah! It looks so cool!
As planned, you'll return to the Arthra tomorrow morning.
Isn't it though?
Yeah! It's really amazing!
Use the time before then to
do what you can about Fate.
Alright!
Yeah. I'm sure everything will turn out fine.
He died...
Ah... that really got me going.
Really, it's so much more fun
when you're here, Nanoha.
Thanks...
I'm pretty sure I'll be done with things soon,
so I'll be able to hang out all the time again.
Nanoha...
Did you... get over it, just a little?
Ah? Um... I wonder?
I've been worried about you...
Well, I wasn't angry because you were hiding things from us,
or because it felt like
you were ignoring us,
but because you seemed
so troubled and lost...
It got so bad that I thought you
might leave us and never come back.
I won't go anywhere...
I'm your friend, right?
Of course I won't go anywhere.
Really?
Yeah.
That's right...
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll come right back here.
All I'll be doing... is spending my time
a little differently than usual.
It's all so I can continue to be honest
with my feelings from now on.
It's a small journey I have to take
so that I don't regret anything.
You definitely look much better.
Have your worries finally faded away?
Dad...
You knew I was worried about something?
Well, of course I did.
I'm your father, after all.
You have to leave again early tomorrow morning, right?
Yeah... I'm sorry to make you worry again...
Well, I know you're a strong girl,
so I won't worry too much about you.
Do your best, and stay strong.
Yeah!
Uminari City suburbs
Takamachi residence
Nanoha!
Uminari Seaside Park
This place should be fine, right?
Please show yourself... Fate!
Scythe Form.
Fate... let's end this once and for all.
You can't listen to what that
woman has to say anymore.
Fate... if you keep going like this,
things will just get worse and worse...
So, Fate...
But... even so, I'm still her daughter...
You can't just throw away
everything you've done so far, right?
You can't even consider running away now.
And I'm pretty sure the Jewel Seeds
are behind everything you've done.
So, let's bet them.
Each of us will put our Jewel Seeds on the line!
Put Out.
This is where it starts...
Where it all starts.
Everything about us has yet to begin...
So... in order to truly start things between us...
Let's begin...
our first and final true battle!
Make a little wish!
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
weaving through the forests,
and passing through the silver wind,
I was looking for something neither of us had
Ah, within a diorama of the city
I was just crying alone
until the day your warm hand
reached out to me
I felt your strong gaze
during those swaying days,
and then, at long last
I finally found the secret key
Make a little wish!
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
and shine their light
down upon on your path
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
If you say you can't do anything,
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
I resolved to have a
decisive battle with Fate.
And deep within it lies the connection
between our pasts and presents.
The Garden of Time which
has been set in motion...
Just what is this Al-Hazard
that Presea wishes for?
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 11
Memories That Lie Beyond Time
Episode Eleven:
Memories That Lie Beyond Time.
Lyrical Magical,
full power, full throttle!