You'll make any wish come true, right?
Don't fret, I can do yours without a doubt.
So, you're ready?
Yeah. Do it.
Now take hold of it.
That is your fate.
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll walk upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 5  There's no way I regret anything
res novae
man, that face is scary
Excuse me.
That wasn't very ladylike of me.
What's wrong, Hitomi?
Not enough sleep?
Yes. I was at the hospital and had to deal with the police until late.
What? Did something happen?
I guess I was sleepwalking, or something?
There were a lot of people with the same symptoms,
and when I came to, they were all lying around me.
Huh? What's up with that?
The doctors said it was called a collective hallucination or something.
I have to have a complete physical after school today too.
What a bother...
You shouldn't have come to school then!
No, I couldn't do that! Then it'd be like I was actually sick.
People at home would get even more worried about me.
I guess honor students are like that!
You're pretty tough!
It's been a while since I've felt this great.
I feel wonderful!
Sayaka-chan, aren't you scared?
Hmm? Well, yeah, I am a bit scared.
But I took care of that witch from yesterday pretty easily.
When I think about the fact that I might have lost two of my friends, both you and Hitomi,
I find that's much scarier.
So it's kinda like I have more self-confidence?
I feel more at ease?
It's like I want to congratulate myself for everything so far.
I guess I'm flying high.
Magical Girl Sayaka-chan will do everything she can to protect Mitakihara City!
So you don't regret anything at all?
I guess if I had to pick something...
It'd be the fact that I hesitated to begin with.
If I was going to become a magical girl anyway, I should have decided sooner.
If Mami and I fought that witch together, she might not have died.
I...
You're thinking of something weird, aren't you?
I... I should have...
I can say all of that because I'm already a magical girl.
The idea is that I became a magical girl anyway, so why shouldn't I have done it sooner?
It's like I was destined to become a magical girl from the start.
Sayaka-chan...
I found my wish.
I had something worth risking my life for this whole time.
I'm just a little frustrated it took me so long to realize that.
That's why you shouldn't feel inferior to me for not becoming a magical girl.
That's all.
Yeah...
Anyway, I have to get going.
Huh? Do you have something to do?
Yeah, just a little something.
I see. So you're not getting released yet.
I still haven't completed the rehabilitation for my legs yet.
I need to be able to walk completely first.
They say they don't know why my hand healed all of a sudden,
so they need to look at it more thoroughly.
How are you feeling, though?
Is there anything strange with your body?
No. There's so much that isn't wrong, it's scary.
It's even starting to make me think being in the accident was all just a bad dream—
like I'm not even sure why I'm in this bed anymore.
This is a miracle just like you said.
What's wrong?
I said a lot of mean things to you.
It doesn't matter how depressed I was, I...
Don't worry yourself thinking about anything weird that happened.
You should be really happy right now!
Don't make that face.
Right.
All of this just doesn't feel real.
Well, that makes sense.
I guess it's about time.
Kyousuke, let's get a breath of fresh air.
Why are we going to the roof?
It'll be fine.
Everybody!
The real celebration will be when you get out of the hospital,
but since your hand healed faster than your legs...
I-Is that...
You told me to get rid of it, but I just couldn't.
I...
Now try it. Don't be afraid.
Mami-san,
my wish came true.
There's no way I regret anything.
I'm the happiest I could possibly be right now!
That's the new magical girl in this town, huh?
Do you really want to start fighting with her?
I mean, it looks too easy.
I'd kill someone like her in an instant.
Or what?
You gotta problem with all this?
It may not be as easy as you think.
There's another magical girl in this city, after all.
What's she like?
I don't know either, really.
Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
She became a magical girl after forming a contract with you, right?
You could say that, and you also could not.
She's an extremely rare irregularity.
Even I can't predict what move she'll make.
Sounds good to me.
Being bored all day isn't good after all.
I need to have some excitement.
What did you want to talk about?
Um, about Sayaka-chan...
It's easy for her to believe what she wants to, and she gets really stubborn.
She's quick to fight...
But she's a really nice person!
She's kind and courageous.
And she'll go to any length to help someone.
That's fatal for a magical girl.
Really...?
Excessive kindness leads to weakness.
Reckless courage becomes inattention to detail.
And there's no reward for dedication of any kind.
You can't be a magical girl unless you understand that.
That's why Tomoe Mami lost her life.
Stop talking like that!
Sayaka-chan might be saying she's fine,
but when I think of something happening to her like what happened to Mami-san,
I don't know what to do.
You're worried about Miki Sayaka, aren't you?
I can't do anything for her anymore,
so I want to ask you.
Could you be friends with Sayaka-chan?
Don't fight her like you did with Mami-san.
It should be much safer if you all fight together to kill the witches, right?
I don't want to lie,
and I don't want to make any promises I can't keep.
So give up on Miki Sayaka.
Why...
She shouldn't have made a contract.
Honestly, it's my fault as well.
I should have watched her actions properly, not just yours.
Then you...
But now that I've taken responsibility, I must tell you that it's a mistake I can do nothing about.
It'd be like trying to bring someone back from the grave.
She's become a magical girl already.
There's no hope for salvation.
That contract forces you to give up on everything in exchange for a single desire.
So you've given up too?
You've given up on yourself and the other girls? On everything?
That's right.
I won't make excuses and say I'll try to atone.
I must continue my fight, no matter what sin I must commit to do so.
It seems I wasted your time.
I'm sorry.
Are you nervous?
Well, yeah.
One mistake and I'll be dead.
Madoka.
Sayaka-chan, are you going to...
That's right. I'm going on patrol to search for bad witches!
It's part of the job when you fight for justice.
Will you be fine by yourself?
I will!
Mami-san did this too.
I should be able to do this since we learned under her.
I can't do anything,
and I know I'll just get in the way,
but could you take me with you—at least until it would cause a problem?
Aren't you trying too hard?
I'm sorry...
I shouldn't. I know I'd get in your way.
No, I'm really happy.
Hey, can't you tell?
My hands started shaking, and they haven't stopped.
Pathetic, huh?
I'm a magical girl now, but I kinda feel helpless by myself.
Sayaka-chan...
You're not a nuisance. I'm really happy.
I feel a lot better just because someone would stay with me.
Like that alone gives me the power of one hundred people.
I...
I'll protect you.
So relax and just follow behind me.
Let's go get those witches together like we always have.
Right!
You know it's dangerous, right?
I'm stupid, so if I'm by myself I might do something reckless.
If I keep in mind that Madoka is here with me, I think I can be careful.
I see.
Well, it's fine as long as you have a plan.
Kyubey...
You have a plan too, right Madoka?
I know how you want to protect Sayaka.
Just by staying with her, you're able to keep an ace up your sleeve if the worst happens.
I...
You don't have to say anything right now.
I'm sure Sayaka will be against it too.
But if there comes a time when you have to make up your mind, I'll be ready.
Okay...
It's here.
This barrier is probably a familiar's, not a witch's.
The easier the better.
I don't have a lot of experience.
You can't let your guard down.
I know.
Is that...
It's going to get away!
Leave it to me!
Wait a minute. What are you two doing?
It's going to get away!
Can't you tell? That's not a witch, it's a familiar.
It's not gonna have a Grief Seed.
If you just leave it be, someone's going to get killed!
You just have to wait until it eats around 4 or 5 people and becomes a witch.
That way it'll form a Grief Seed.
Why are you trying to strangle a chicken before it lays eggs?
Are you saying that we should let the witch kill everyone it attacks?
I think you're thinking about this wrong.
You know about the food chain, right?
I'm sure you learned about it in school.
The witches eat the weak humans.
And we eat those witches.
That's the way stuff works, right?
The stronger you are, the higher up you are.
That's...
You...
I hope I'm wrong here, but you didn't form a contract with him just to make people watch you play out some ridiculous joke,
like pretending to be a superhero and wanting to rescue people, or something else that stupid, right?
And what if I did?!
Could you, like, stop?
It really pisses me off when someone messes with my work just because it seems kinda fun.
Sayaka-chan!
Hmph. Stupid rookie.
Cool your head a bit.
That's weird.
I should have hurt you enough to put you in the hospital for three months.
Sayaka-chan's okay?
That's because she became a magical girl using a wish for healing.
Her ability to heal damage is far greater than anyone else's.
Who'd lose to you?
It's because people like you are around that Mami-san...!
You're annoying.
So freaking annoying!
Actually, you shouldn't even be talking to me that way.
I've been doing this far longer than you.
Shut up!
Stop moving around. You freaking slowass.
Sayaka-chan!
Madoka, it's too dangerous to get closer!
If you're so dumb you don't get it when I try to tell you...
And you don't get it when I beat you down...
I'll just have to kill you!
I won't lose...
I won't lose!
Why...
Why... do two people on the same side have to fight when a witch isn't even here?
It's hopeless.
Neither of them feels like backing down.
Please, Kyubey, make them stop!
This shouldn't be happening!
I can't do anything.
But if you want to stop them by force...
It's not like there aren't any options on the table.
Only another magical girl can come between their fighting.
But you have the capacity to do that, if that's what you really wish.
That's right...
If I form a contract too...
It's over!
I...
There's no need for that.
Someday the light of love you hold within your eyes will transcend time
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光がときを超えて
and destroy the dream of a world racing towards destruction.
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ壊すだろう
Now that you've drank every ounce of your hesitation, what do you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干した君が望むものは何？
Will there be a fleeting tomorrow for this greedy admiration?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
I want to see you, smiling with the power to destroy even God,
子供の頃夢に見せた古の魔法のように
like the ancient magic you showed me in my dreams when I was young.
神さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Everything depends on these feelings of courage from the flower that was plucked
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
that now lays in my frightened hands.
思いだけで頼るすべて
This wish will awaken that light.
光を呼び覚ます願い
Illustrator Yuupon (nitro+)
Sayaka-chan, you became a magical girl to fight witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch; she's a magical girl like you!
Episode 6   There's definitely something wrong with this
There's definitely something wrong with this.
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Aya & Chika
Editor: limitbreakingcat
Timer: euronymous
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Encoder: Miku
Quality Check: kozu
rune
thedarkhaze
King_Arthur
Robo210