I'm sleepy...
Good grief.
Speaking of which, you left tissues in your skirt pockets when you threw them into the laundry basket.
It was troublesome for me.
Yeah, yeah.
Also, remember to separate clothes that are coloured differently.
The dark coloured ones in the orange laundry basket...
Okay, okay! Shut up, shut up!
Why do you have to be so particular about such minor stuff?
If you're a man, stop finding faults in these minor details.
Take this, home run! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Home run, yeah!
Don't mind!
Okay! It's my turn next.
Captain, fight!
Thanks for everyone's encouragement.
Kushieda...
Okay! Give me all you've got!
That refreshing smile.
Yeah!
Kushieda.
Those glittering droplets of perspiration.
First base, yeah! Second base, yeah!
Go around the third base, and home run!
And that song which is out of tune.
Home... in!
Ah, Kushieda.
In the morning, you too...
You're looking too perverted, disgusting dog.
Kushieda, regarding the weekend boy-girls combined training...
Ah, Kitamura-kun. I was also about to say...
Hey! Do you understand, you stupid dog?
Hey, stop it!
Hey, stop right there! Hey!
Yeah. Even if they're in the go-home club,
they still have intensive exercise this morning too.
After all, health is our greatest concern.
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono tanjun de katte ni kakedasu shiromono
Love is sweet and bitter, an amazing thing that's simple and bolts out
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
otoko to issho no ECCENTRIC na anata
You are together with an eccentric guy
tsuyogari soburi wo zenshin matomete tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PRE PARADE
A naive pre-parade
atama no naka wa junjou PRE PARADE
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
Your Song
Mobile phone stylist... Minori, you've got a skilful hand.
Well...
I've got quite skilful hands even if I don't look like it.
Kushieda... What is she doing?
Great! I've finished one!
Okay, next up is...
What are you doing, making that sound as if you're being strangled to death?
Ah, no...
That's right! Do you want me to do this for yours, Takasu-kun?
I've got a job as a mobile phone stylist!
S-Stylist?
Shall I put up the word "Ryuuji" using purple beads for you?
Kushieda... For my sake?
No! I...
Kushieda.
We'll leave ours to you too.
Whoa, an order, huh?
Then, write down your name, the colour and image that you want, on this sheet.
Um, I want it in pink.
I want a big heart shape,
one that gives others a feeling of immense cuteness.
That would be really cool.
Her occupation is a mobile phone stylist, huh?
Kushieda who's beaming with such radiance, and the glittering mobile phones.
A really wonderful combination, huh?
Hey. Ya-chan won't be eating dinner here because she's going to have it with her clients, right?
So, let me have her share...
And she called me "Ryuuji"...
She even remembered my name?
That's because I'm always calling you that.
Anyway, about Ya-chan's portion...
Ah, I talked to her so much today.
Hey, Taiga. I didn't appear weird when I was talking... did I?
Listen when others are talking.
I'll tell you this too.
You acted really weird then!
Hey, is dinner still not ready?
That hurts! Geez, it'll be ready soon!
We're having rice bowls today.
Huh?
What's wrong?
The rice cooker... is broken.
Welcome! Good evening!
What should I order...
There's no need to come to a family restaurant.
Although the rice couldn't be eaten, there was still bread.
Nag as much as you want now, mongrel.
You'll be grateful enough to bow to me soon.
Huh?
Here it is! Two servings!
We haven't ordered anything...
Keep it a secret, but this is Taiga's special treat, the extra large ice cream.
Eat it without letting the other customers see you.
Thank you as always, Minori.
Always?
Huh? You don't like sweet stuff, Takasu-kun?
Then shall I change it into potatoes for you?
I'll give you more, much much more!
N-No... I...
Minori, you're still working at the convenience store and the karaoke box, right?
That's right! And the steamboat store since last week too!
That many?
I still have some free time, even at this pace.
After all, I'm the manager of the female softball club so I can't have absences.
Seeing you working this much, do you have something that you're hoping to buy?
I have the time, so I should to go to work.
Go to work?
That's right. The Labour Revolution Files.
She's referring to the Labour Revolution Files from Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei.
Yes, the revival of labour revolution.
And speaking of which, you two have a good relationship, don't you?
Miss, the menu please.
Well then, enjoy yourselves.
You...
Just today, my eyesight really seems to have deteriorated a lot.
You're merely a mongrel...
You actually drooled at the sight of Minori in that family restaurant uniform.
I'm just...
I just thought about how beautiful she was when she smiled.
Don't! Don't stab my eyes!
If I stab anymore, it will dirty my fingers.
Damn.
However, why is she taking up so many jobs?
Didn't she tell you that it was the Labour Revolution File?
Could there be some reason that made her need money urgently? Like family matters for example.
Or things like raising funds for her sickly mother?
Didn't she say that it's just labour?
But...
It would be best if you stop thinking like that.
Things like "There's only me who can understand her true self".
I'd be overcome with disgust.
Ah, I hate it. Stay further away, you're disgusting.
Hey!
Taiga, what's with that tone?
Why are you being so cold?
Didn't I tell you not to come near me?
Moreover, was there a time when I wasn't cold towards you?
Now that you mention it...
Here! Inko-chan, sorry for the wait!
This is your dinner.
I'll give you more, much much more!
N... Ko...
Whoa, you're talking, Inko-chan? Are you going to say your name?
Nn... Ko... Nnn... Ko... UNKO!
unko - It means "shit" in Japanese.
We've gone out for breakfast.
There are sandwiches in the refrigerator.
The morning of a day off is really refreshing.
Right, Taiga?
I shouldn't have told you after all.
Did you say something?
In order to see Minori, you're going to the family restaurant by not making breakfast.
The rice cooker is still broken, it can't be helped.
Then we should've gone to the appliances repair shop.
Moreover, didn't you say that you hate eating bread?
It's not a problem if it's just for breakfast.
What are you being lively for?
Those clothes don't suit you.
Ah, I forgot something...
You're really troublesome.
I beg you, let me go!
It won't change no matter what you wear anyway.
Huh, Niichan?
Aren't you Mirano-chan's son?
Ah, Uncle Inage.
Mirano?
Ah, Yasuko's stage name.
She uses it at work.
Mirano-chan
Hi~
Go past the North-west gate, and keep walking straight for another 200 metres.
I'm Mirano from Vaisravans' Heaven.
How old do you think I am?
23? You're right!
How lucky this early in the morning!
Mirano-chan's DNA Touch!
Not bad, not bad! The muscles are pretty tight.
It's good to be young!
Let's go.
This old man is somehow making me angry.
Oh, it's the two of you.
If you haven't had your breakfast,
I recommend this fish sausage which is rich in DHA and calcium.
Ah.
Huh?
To
ra
do
!
www.aerosubs.net
Kushieda...
Minori?
Here, carry these.
W-Why...
Here.
One more!
Let me move those.
It's okay. Let's have some tea, Mirano's son.
Why do I have to do something like this?
Although it's only limited to her days off, I begged her to come.
Kushieda! Work hard!
Yeah~ Understood!
We're really busy recently.
There's not enough manpower.
Manpower...
That's right, Miss.
Since you're Kushieda's friend, would you like to work here too?
I'll be generous with the pay.
Okay!
I'll do it.
Huh?
Together with her.
I've had enough!
Hey, don't start a fight.
It'll bring trouble for Kushieda.
Then go help her by yourself!
Little one, I have a delivery for you to make.
Get three cartons of beer from the storehouse over there.
Yes, with pleasure!
Okay! This will do.
Be careful during the delivery.
What's wrong, Taiga?
Huh?
You...
Could it be that you don't know how to ride a bicycle?
Shut up!
So what if I don't know how to ride a bicycle?
It'll be okay as long as I deliver the goods, right?
You're wrong! You've gotten it wrong!
Heat's gushing out from you, Taiga!
That was terrible...
Well, by pushing it, it should be safe, right?
Ah, that's right. We have to stock up on those shouchuu.
shouchuu - low quality distilled alcohol drink.
Ah, I'll also...
I'll help too.
Look, it's not nice doing nothing at all.
I'll be counting on you then!
Yeah!
Um, where's that potato shouchuu...
It's so hard to see in this darkness.
Yeah, that's because this place isn't used often.
It's opened about once every week.
It'll be bad if we're locked up here.
Well, that'd be a pretty relaxing and happy atmosphere for a mishap.
That small girl ran away without locking the door, really.
Hey! There's still someone inside!
SOS! SOS!
Calm down, Takasu-kun.
Kushieda.
Singing is most effective in this kind of situation.
Eh?
Effective?
I'm an idiot.
There's no need for me to work so hard at all.
I'm sick of it.
What are you referring to?
Ki-Kitamura-kun.
W-Why are you h-h-h-here?
I'm doing some self-training.
Speaking of which, is that yours?
Yeah... You could say so...
You know how to ride a bicycle already?
What an amazing improvement.
Um, about "knowing how to ride"... Um...
How did you know that I don't know how to ride a bicycle?
Ah, I did observe you often last year.
A bicycle's really good. It can widen your world.
See you then, Aisaka. See you tomorrow.
Last year he...
Me...
Damn.
Ouch...
Damn it!
If it's a world where Kitamura-kun won't see me...
Even if it's widened, there's no meaning to it!
Damn it!
You took quite a while...
What happened to you?
Nothing much.
Anyway, where's the other two?
Speaking of which, where did Kushieda go?
I don't mind if it's Ryuuji-kun but...
That mongrel dared to slack-off while I was working so hard?!
What are you saying?
Ah, that's right, next up is three blocks away...
Ryuuji! What are you doing?!
Ah, ah~ The bridge leading towards the future~
That's the great bridge, the great bridge!
My throat became dry.
We've sung so loudly, and no one noticed.
Ah, around this time, Uncle is obsessed with his horse racing.
Is that so?
It's getting a little cold.
Ah, if you don't mind, my coat...
Okay! Let's warm up!
The pitcher is scared! Hey, hey, hey!
You say I'm scared but...
Aren't you the pitcher?
The pitcher is scared! Hey, hey, hey!
Could it be that you're... really scared?
Look at your hand, it's trembling hard.
Oh no, this is due to excitement.
Look, here I come!
Okay.
Strike!
Come, change.
Batter change.
Because there's no need to be scared.
That's why I'll blow away my weakness!
Kushieda.
Could it be that...
Hey, Takasu-kun. Can we get out through that?
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he!
Where is he?!
Look, Takasu-kun.
Over there, huh?
The reason why Kushieda seems to be so sparkling,
might not be only because she's lively and energetic.
Watch out!
Kushieda, sorry! Are you alright?
Your nose is bleeding!
That's nothing.
Nothing...?
A nosebleed is the perspiration of the heart.
Come on, there's only a little more to go.
Stack it, stack it up, Takasu.
Yes!
That's right. Blowing away weakness, huh?
Good, we'll get out of here for sure!
Yeah, of course. Fight!
Eh?
Come on, when I say fight you should say...
Eh... Ippatsu...?
faito ippatsu - A popular catch phrase of an energy drink in Japan.
That's right, that's it.
Fight!
I-Ippatsu!
That's right.
Kushieda has always been beaming with such radiance ever since the beginning.
The time when I met her too.
Fight!
Now too.
Ippatsu!
And now, she's still radiant.
I have found you.
Taiga! How did you end up here?
How, you say? I used the ladder...
Yay, Takasu-kun!
We can now get out with this.
But...
Thank you, Taiga.
This is truly the ladder leading to the future.
Well, Minori...
Come on, get up quickly, Takasu-kun.
Y-Yeah...
Um, like I've said...
I dropped the ladder just before...
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru monotowa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
It will be good if you are a little more honest, but you are always rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
That Moment's Face
Sealed quietly in the depths of the heart.
Something I couldn't tell, and it's shared only by the two of us.
Oh, I've told Takasu.
Ki-Kitamura!