So Ra No Wo To
That noise would wake the dead.
A Day with the Squad -
Rio Runs
Let's eat!
How is it?
It's pretty good.
Yeah. This is yummy.
Well, it's not bad.
Great!
It's a dish native to my village.
Is this "miso" the stuff that's
made the same way as soy?
Yes.
I brought a bit of miso
my mom made.
There's plenty more,
so eat up!
To Treize?
Yeah.
We finally received notification
about more supplies.
I'm taking Kureha-chan
to pick them up.
We're running low on ammunition, medicine,
and a lot of everyday supplies, right?
We'll be all right now!
And Noël?
Carl-san's studio, right?
Got it.
Kanata!
We're spending the whole
afternoon practicing!
Really?
Grub's ready.
What horrible manners...
Your dad would cry
if he saw that.
Like I care.
Here, have a snack.
Fortune cookies?
You don't like them, huh?
It isn't the kids at the
church's fault.
Demanding money to spread
their useless superstitions...
It's the same as everywhere else.
Oh, that's not true at all.
These are good cookies!
Oh, my!
Good Luck
She seems like she's
really fitting in.
It's cute how hard
she always tries.
You think?
I'll admit she's serious
and fired-up.
But things out here aren't easy enough
to get by on those qualities alone.
What does that look mean?
It's a secret!
What?
That's annoying.
Horrible Luck
All right, see you guys.
I'll be back late.
OK. Be careful.
Don't cause trouble
for Rio-sempai.
Setting sail...
Bye-bye!
I don't expect you to
be able to do this,
but you should be able to control the
sound using only the mouthpiece.
Try it!
O-OK!
How are you finding
life at the base?
It's fun!
You're so easygoing
about everything.
I'm a bit jealous.
Come to think of it,
why did you join the army?
You see...
I... I heard I could learn to
play an instrument for free...
But I understand that p-protecting
the country is important!
I don't care whether it was
for money or whatever...
Those with a distinct goal in mind last longer
than those who just kind of joined up.
Um... Thank you.
Then, why did you join, Rio-sempai?
I...
Yeah...
I guess for the opposite
of your reason.
But that's rare these days.
You almost never hear brass instruments
outside of the military.
I heard it a long time ago...
A sound like yours, Sempai.
Kanata?
A sound of the sky...
What's wrong?
Wake up!
Wake up, Kanata!
Answer me!
No!
Just stay still.
It's hot. It's hot, Mom...
Are you hot?
OK... It's OK.
You're OK.
Mom... Mom...
What's wrong, Kanata?
Kanata!
I want some snow to eat...
OK. Just wait!
Snow... Where's the snow...
Why the hell would we
have any snow?!
Calm down.
Calm down...
Medicine!
No. That's a last resort!
Medicine, medicine...
Medicine! Medicine...
Found it!
...running low on a
lot of stuff, right?
Damn those idiots in
the Supply Corps!
Damn.
What should I do...
Damn it all!
Um... Did you need something?
Did the children cause
problems again?
Please forgive me for my rudeness
up until this point.
So, um...
Save her!
Drink this.
Good girl.
She's got a bit of high fever,
but this should do it.
Is it something really bad?
I think it's malaria.
Malaria? Only kids get that.
Even adults can get it
if they're very tired.
A lot of kids get it right
after we take them in.
The more they appear to be fine,
the worse it is when it hits.
She was fighting it off the whole time, I bet.
Th-Then... Will she get better?
She won't stay like this forever, right?
I think she'll be fine.
I'm so glad.
Thank you...
Uh...
My name is Yumina.
This is infused with herbs.
Give it to her a little later.
Uh, thank you for everything.
Don't worry about it.
Serving the people of this town
is our joy and our duty.
May all blessings be upon you.
Thank you for your cooperation!
Ow.
I-I'm sorry!
You OK?
I'm sorry.
I'm an omiso.
The stuff we had this morning?
No.
Miso dregs...
When you make miso soup,
you strain the miso...
The leftover beans,
and stuff from it.
Good-for-nothing, useless,
like that...
I've always been like that,
ever since I was a kid.
So I thought that this time, I'd work
really hard and not trouble anyone.
But...
You were a lot more fragile
than you looked.
And a selfish, spoiled kid...
Did... Did I say something?
A lot of stuff!
Oh, sempai!
What?
That song you were singing...
What are you talking about?
This song.
Amazing.
She only heard it one time.
It wasn't the first
time I'd heard it.
I heard it a long time ago.
I always wanted to play it myself.
That's why I...
That song sounded like it was
coming down from the sky!
But I guess once an omiso,
always an omiso.
Kanata.
We can't just rely on the
church for everything.
The Takemikazuchi is a
relic from a past era.
And a lot of things are
sleeping inside it.
A lot of things?
Yeah. Ask Noël for the details.
OK, this is it.
Here goes!
This is it!
This song!
This is probably what that song
sounds like complete.
Lots of instruments, all playing in harmony,
becoming one piece of music.
It's the same as a tank crew.
Commander, gunner, driver,
and communications...
Everyone works together
to operate one tank.
Every part is important.
Every sound is important.
Don't look at me like that.
It's just something I heard
from the person I respect and
admire more than anyone.
To borrow her words...
Kanata, why do you think superior officers exist?
So their juniors can cause
problems for them.
It's fine if you can't do it now.
Just remember how much it hurt,
how powerless it felt,
and how happy you were
to be protected.
And someday, when you're in the position
to protect someone, it will help you.
So cause as much trouble
for me as you'd like.
I did the same.
Of course, if you screw up,
you'll be scolded and punished.
But... If it hurts, say so.
When you're suffering, tell me.
OK?
Understood!
I'll make sure to cause lots and
lots of trouble for you!
N-Not that...
Go easy on me, OK?
Jeez... I should've stayed.
Kanata got Rio-sempai
to nurse her.
What? It was no big deal.
Looks like she was just tired.
She'll be fine if she sleeps.
The Takemikazuchi's lights were on.
Sorry. I used it a bit.
Was there a problem?
You listened to that
song, didn't you?
Yeah.
You said you never would again.
I just really wanted to hear it.
So?
It's a secret.
Rainy Season Sky
- Quartz Rainbow
Next time:
Rainy Season Sky,
Quartz Rainbow.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.