I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but then a small incident happened.
What I received was a courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
We've crossed paths many times, yet... we still
don't really know anything about each other.
Because I want to hear your answer,
and because I want to know you...
...I've decided that I'll confront you directly
and shake off my hesitation...
...and just believe in the magic within my heart.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
You three... return to the ship.
Understood...
And also, for Nanoha-san and Yuuno-kun...
...you both will be getting a lecture from
me personally on your actions.
Everybody's Separate Heart-felt Vows.
Following orders doesn't affect a single
person, but an entire group of people.
What I mean is that the selfish actions you took
could have affected not only yourselves...
...but it could have also affected the people around you.
I trust you understand?
Yes...
If this were a normal case, you both could
expect severe punishments, but...
...taking your magnificent results into account,
we'll overlook your actions this time.
However...
I will not do this a second time. Do you understand?
Yes.
We're sorry.
Now then... the big problem starts now, huh?
Chrono, have you learned anything about
the incident, even superficial data?
Yes. Amy, please transmit it to the monitor.
Yes, yes!
Oh, my!
Yes. The mage hailing from the same place
as us, Midchilda, Precia Testarossa.
Her field of study is in the development of energy
sources allowing one to traverse dimensional space.
Despite being a great mage...
...she was involved in an accident while doing
illegal research, and was thus exiled.
The data we already have about her and the data
from the magical assault earlier both match.
And... that girl named Fate is most likely...
Fate-chan. Back then, she said "Mother"...
M-Mother?!
Mother and daughter, huh?
U-Umm... rather than being surprised...
she seemed to be more frightened.
Amy! Are you able to pull up any more
details about this Precia woman?
Like where she went after being exiled?
Or anything about her familial relationships?
Anything at all?
Yes, yes. I'll look into it right away.
This woman... is Fate-chan's mother...
Having that opportunity right in front of your face
and squandering it, mindlessly ignoring them...!
I'm... sorry...
You're too cruel, Fate.
Do you really want to fill me with grief?
I want us to be friends.
Precia Testarossa... according to Midchildian records...
...she was the third director of the Central Science
& Development Bureau twenty-six years ago, but...
She was also privately working on a thesis involving
energy sources allowing the traversal of dimensions.
Then, the concepts of this "Hydra" thesis were tested.
She conducted her experiment with illegal
materials... and the experiment failed.
The results included a mid-scale dimensional
disturbance at the beginning...
...which caused the fissuring of the entire central
area, eventually engulfing the surrounding areas.
Apparently, there was a large
dispute about the incident...
...saying that the failure didn't
exceed her expectations...
...and that there was nothing illegal
about the materials used.
She moved many times after that, continuing
to perform her secret projects.
But at some point, the records
lost track of her whereabouts.
And that's about all I can find.
What about her family ties and her actions
up to the point when she went missing?
That data was completely erased.
Right now, the main office is putting
together a file on that data for me...
How long will that take to prepare?
They said about a day or two...
If that Precia woman and Fate-chan are able
to release that much magical power...
...we can't afford to act hastily.
And we still have to repair Asura's
shielding system, as well.
I think you two should take some time to rest.
Huh? But...
Especially you, Nanoha-san. It's not good
for you to miss school all this time.
I'll approve a return trip for now.
It'd be a good idea to see your family and
make an appearance at school again.
Yes...
Fate! Fate!
Fate! Fate...
Only nine...
I can cause a dimensional disturbance with these,
but I won't be able to reach Alhazred...
We have no more time... neither me nor Alicia...
You're her mother, and she's your daughter, isn't she?!
She's working so hard for you...
She's doing everything she can for you...
How can you keep doing those cruel things to her?!
That girl is certainly inept at creating familiars...
I can see she imbued this one with far
too many unnecessary emotions.
Fate is your daughter!
All she wants is to see you smile,
to return to your old, kind self... that's why...!
You... who are nothing but an intrusion...
Disappear!
It doesn't matter where... but I have
to transport myself somewhere...
I'm sorry, Fate... just wait a little while...
Fate. Wake up, Fate.
Yes... Mother.
These are the nine Jewel Seeds you've
managed to collect for me.
However, this is not enough.
In the worst case scenario, I need at least five more.
If it's at all possible, hurry... and get
some more for me, your mother.
Yes...
Arf...?
Oh?
That girl fled.
She was scared and wanted nothing
more to do with this.
If you need another, I can prepare
you an even better familiar.
Never forget... that the person who's always
truly on your side is your mother.
Do you understand, Fate?
Yes... Mother.
And the ten days I spent with her went by so quickly!
My. Is that so?
Lindy-san... I'm not sure whether to call what you're
doing a wonderful cover-up or a complete lie...
It's pretty impressive.
Well, I obviously can't tell them the truth.
It's so your family doesn't worry, so please
call this my "consideration and concern."
But Nanoha-san is quite a good little girl.
I'd almost like my son to learn from her example.
My, my... there you go, saying things like that again!
My Chrono just has no social skills whatsoever!
Oh, I'm sure that's not the case!
Nanoha!
Since you came home today unexpectedly,
you'll be able to stick around for a little, right?
Yeah.
Alisa-chan and Suzuka-chan have also
been really worried about you.
Have you gotten in touch with them yet?
Yeah. I sent them both a message earlier.
And, send...
Miss Alisa, did you receive a nice
message or something?
Not really. Just a normal text message.
Samejima! Stop the car a second!
As I thought, it was a big dog...
It's injured... seriously injured!
But it's still alive.
Samejima.
I understand, allow me to take care of it.
Fate...
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha.
Ah! You're finally awake.
Huh? I've seen this girl somewhere before...
You sure are a strong dog, aren't you?
You were hurt pretty badly, but you survived.
Until you're fully recovered, I'll take
good care of you here at my house.
You can relax here.
Ah...
She's a friend of that girl...
Go on. It's warm dog food... will you be able to eat it?
If you're that hungry, I guess there's
nothing to worry about.
After you finish eating, go to sleep so you
can hurry up and get better, okay?
Nanoha-chan! Thank goodness, you seem fine!
Yeah. Thanks, Suzuka-chan.
I'm sorry to you too, Alisa-chan...
making you worry about me while I was gone.
Well... I guess it's nice... to see that you're doing well...
I see... so you'll have to leave again...
Yeah...
It must be rough, huh?
Yeah... but, everything will be okay!
Do you have time after school? Do you think
we'll be able to play for a little bit?
Yeah, that's fine with me.
Then... do you wanna come over to my house?
I have a new video game...
Really?
Oh, now that I think of it, I also
found a hurt dog last night.
A dog?
Yeah. It's really big, and its fur is kind of orange...
There's also a red jewel on its
forehead shaped like this.
So it really is you, Arf-san.
You, eh?
What's with those injuries?
And also... where's Fate-chan?
Oh, my... it looks like she's lost her spirit.
What's wrong? Are you feeling all right?
It might be in pain...
Should we just let her rest?
Yeah...
Yuuno! Hey now. That's dangerous.
I'm sure Yuuno-kun will be fine.
Nanoha, I'll hear the story from her myself,
so you go with Alisa-chan and Suzuka-chan.
Okay.
Well then, do you wanna have some tea?
I happened to have some really good tea inside.
Yeah!
I can't wait!
Yeah, yeah!
So what happened?
What happened between you two?
If you're here, then I guess the Administration
Bureau is also watching, huh?
Yeah...
I'm Chrono Hallaoun of the Time-Space
Administration Bureau.
It would appear that your circumstances
are quite complex.
If you could explain them to me truthfully,
I promise nothing bad will happen to you.
Nothing will happen to either you
or your master, Fate Testarossa.
I'll tell you... everything.
But promise me... promise me that you'll save Fate.
That girl's done nothing wrong...
I promise. Amy, start logging.
I already am.
Fate's mother... Precia Testarossa...
is where everything begins.
Use the item you just got here.
Which one? Which one?
Nanoha... did you hear?
Yeah... I heard everything...
Looking at your story, the current situation,
and Arf's testimony and status...
...it would appear that her story
was truthful and consistent.
I wonder what's gonna happen now...?
We will arrest Precia Testarossa.
The fact that she attacked the Asura
is enough to warrant an arrest.
So now that we have an order from the captain,
our mission will shift to focus on Precia's arrest.
What will you do now, Takamachi Nanoha?
I...
I want to save Fate-chan.
Because of Arf-san's feelings...
and also, because I want to.
Whenever I see Fate with a sad look on her face,
I somehow also become a little sad.
So I want to save her...
from all the sad things in her life.
And I told her I wanted to be friends...
and I haven't heard her answer to that yet, either!
I understand.
We're also grateful that you're letting us
continue to use your magical power.
We'll leave everything regarding
Fate Testarossa to you, Nanoha.
Is that all right with you?
Yes...
Your name was... Nanoha, right?
I don't want to be in your debt, but... but... please...
Save Fate...
Right now... that girl really is all alone.
Yeah... it'll be fine. Just leave it to me.
You're late, Nanoha!
See? We were waiting for you so
we could enter this new dungeon.
Sorry, sorry!
Ah! It looks so cool!
As planned, you'll return to Asura tomorrow morning.
Isn't it though?
Yeah! It's really amazing!
Use the time before then to
do what you can about Fate.
Yeah. I'm sure everything will turn out fine.
He died...
Ah... that really fired me up.
Really, it's so much more fun
with you here, Nanoha-chan.
Thanks...
I'm pretty sure I'll be done with things soon,
so I'll be able to hang out all the time again.
Nanoha...
Did you finally release that stress you had?
Ah? Umm... I wonder?
I've been worried about you...
Well, the reason I was so angry at you wasn't because...
...you were holding secrets, or because I couldn't
understand what you were thinking, but rather...
...because you seemed so uneasy and lost...
It got so bad that I thought you might not return to us...
I won't go anywhere...
I'm your friend, right?
Of course I won't go anywhere.
Really?
Yeah.
That's right... I'm not going anywhere.
I'll come right back here.
All I'll be doing... is spending my time
a little differently than usual.
It's all so I can continue to be direct with
myself about my feelings from now on.
It's a small journey I must take
so I don't regret anything.
You definitely look much better.
Has your indecision finally faded away?
Dad...
You knew I was worried about something?
Well of course I did. I'm your father, after all.
You have to leave again early tomorrow morning, right?
Yeah... I'm sorry to make you worry again...
Well, I know you're a strong girl,
so I won't worry too much about you.
Do your best, and stay strong.
Yeah!
Nanoha!
This place should be fine, right?
Please show yourself... Fate-chan!
Scythe Form.
Fate... let's stop this once and for all.
You can't listen to what that
woman has to say anymore.
Fate... if you keep going like this,
things will just get worse and worse...
So, Fate...
But... even so, I'm still her daughter...
You can't just throw away everything
you've done so far, right?
You can't even consider running away now.
And I'm pretty sure the Jewel Seeds are
behind everything you've done.
So, let's bet them.
Each of us will put our Jewel Seeds on the line!
Put Out.
After this... we can settle everything after this.
Everything about us has yet to begin...
So... in order to truly start things between us...
Let's begin...
...our true first and final match!
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
I resolved to have a
decisive battle with Fate.
And deep within it lies the
connection between our pasts and presents.
The Garden of Time which
has been set in motion...
Just what is this Alhazred
Precia wishes for?
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Eleven:
Memories That Lie Beyond Time
Lyrical Magical,
full strength, going all out!