A scrub who does nothing.
Man, that really pisses me off!
I only joined as an assistant under the
condition that I wouldn't have to work.
In the first place, it's not like I joined because I wanted to!
Hey, Maki...
Riko!
I simply can't lose my focus now that I know Mizushima's after my head.
Well, you've certainly lost your mind.
Did she say something to you yesterday?
N-Not really, no.
Huh?
Her eyes are red.
Did she stay up late working again?
A vice president who does everything.
Shut the fuck up!
N-No!
Not you!
My bad.
I'll take the day off from student council stuff today.
Wh-Why?
I've got my reasons.
Besides, we can't get any love practice done until Mizushima gives up.
No point in me being there then, right?
Riko...
Hey...
Wait—
Let go of me!
Oh, hel—
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Sayo and Eno the Aggressors
What is wrong with you?
I...
I wanna do it too!
We'd been doing it every day, so now I miss it!
I've been really frustrated recently!
Calm down!
Calm down and be a bit more specific!
So I'm gonna do it right here and now!
You've got it all wrong!
She's talking about running the marathon!
Jeez, why'd you have to go and declare war?
Well, I just went with the Boom the Baron flow.
What the hell kinda flow is that?!
Actually, who the hell is that?!
They knew I was the one behind the harassment, though.
What? Really?
I'm sure I was a hot topic of conversation too, th—
Try cold.
That's pretty harsh!
How about "didn't cross their minds"?
That's even worse!
"Forgot you existed"?
Please, just stop!
Damn that Maki!
How much does she have to
ignore me until she's satisfied?
Why'd it end up like this?
That's what I wanna know.
I'll make it so you can't ignore me anymore.
Where've you been hiding that this whole time?
Maki Natsuo!
Your daddy is lingerie!
What just happened?
How could she bring that up?
Unbelievable!
Sorry, but can I ask you to tell me about your father?
The sunlight's making it hard to see who it is.
Name yourself, coward!
She still hasn't realized?
Just how far under her radar am I?!
As his daughter, you're lingerie too!
Seriously, why are you doing that?!
Oh, it's working!
Here, Sayo. Let her have it.
All right.
Your big bro's a leech!
But I don't have one.
Well, I do have a younger brother.
My older brother has a job.
You've got it wrong!
My big brother's only trying to find himself!
I just picked something random to say. It had nothing to do with your family.
Really?
That's okay, then.
Let's go.
Where?
What's up with that lingerie thing?
N-No comment.
A retro lewd old man?
The word "lingerie" sounds so mature and adult-like!
Ahhhh, I can't hear you!
We're gonna check out the student council office while those guys're out there.
Say.
Don't you think finding a job is more important than finding yourself?
So you were talking about my family after all!
I'm just speaking generally.
Not about your family.
The key to the student council office?
Faculty Lounge
Maki pretty strongly insisted that I not hand it over to anyone but the current members, though.
Miss...
Forget president. Am I not even
recognized as a member anymore?
Y-You can have it!
Stop crying!
How was that?
Oscar-worthy, right?
Yeah, it was amazing.
So stop crying already.
What is that?
Boom the Baron.
If I'm not mistaken, Maki used to keep
all the important papers in this cabinet.
Huh?
What's with this file?
It doesn't have a label—
Love Lab Results?
Love Lab Results
The next day
Off to the student council now?
Yeah, I guess.
It's really a huge pain!
You say that, but I know you're enjoying it!
Huh?
You used to look so bored all the time,
but you've stopped doing that ever
since you joined the student council.
I never knew you were such a workaholic.
Work, eh?
She's right. I'm not bored anymore.
I basically got forced into becoming an assistant,
but I could just not go if I really didn't want to.
Hey, Maki!
M-Maki!
President!
Overwork and a lack of sleep.
The student council at this school is quite busy.
She's very responsible and tends to take everything upon herself,
so keep a look out for her, will you?
You're her assistant.
I knew.
I knew that she'd been pushing herself lately.
I knew all along,
yet I did nothing about it!
Kurahashi?
I've finally gotten my hands on some decisive evidence!
Those guys are practicing how to attract guys,
make the perfect first impression, and stuff like that!
I see you read quite a bit of this.
Neck exposure
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Hand-
kerchief
sticking
out
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
Toast
on
standby
in her
bag
A-Anyway, we'll slip this into the materials
needed for the class rep meeting tomorrow,
and when they all read it and create an uproar, I'll make my entrance!
No longer will Maki be able to igno—
You know...
Isn't it a good thing that they didn't think
you were the one behind the harassment?
It means they think you wouldn't do something that mean.
I do get the feeling they've simply forgotten about you, but we've gotta think positive.
I just lost all motivation to think.
I think that plan of yours is underhanded.
Does that really sit right with you?
Of course it does!
I'm gonna go photocopy this thing.
Found you!
Hey, cheapskate!
Is that really the first thing you
should say after finding someone?
Though you aren't wrong.
So, what do you want?
Mizushima.
Did they find out we sneaked into the office?
I don't think we left any traces behind, though.
Could you please come back as treasurer?
Oh?
Are you okay with letting this
"cheapskate" manage the books?
This cheapskate right here?
S-Sorry about that.
What's this all about?
Maki fell sick.
She said you were a really fast worker.
Please...
Please help her out!
Ah, dammit!
Yeah, yeah, I'm useless. And yeah, this's all my fault!
You're yelling at the wrong person. Stop it.
Shaddup! This's just my prickly exterior!
What part of you isn't prickly?
Search me!
Sure.
I'll do it.
What? Really?
On one condition, though.
What is it?
Eno...
Could you reinstate her as president?
What?
Reinstate Eno as president?!
Yep.
Wait, who's Eno?
I need to start all the way over there?
You're talking about Enomoto, the former president, right?
Right.
What?!
You were in cahoots with the ex-president?!
Yeah.
We've been friends for ages.
I thought you just wanted to be the treasurer again!
That's part of it, yeah, but this all began because Eno wanted to be president.
What the hell?! Stop making one
shocking revelation after the other!
I've got more than enough on
my plate with Maki falling sick!
Uh... I'm sorry.
Dammit, Maki!
"I can't think of anyone," my ass!
An ex-president who's friends with this girl is way too fishy!
Well? Will you accept my terms?
I want you to help President Maki out.
I'll just go back on my request if it means she won't get to be that anymore.
That isn't a balanced trade at all, you shi—
I'm working hard every day!
You see?
Oh, you figured it out?
You're smarter than I expected.
She's making me livid.
But you know, Maki being the president is just weird.
Blame the ex-president for not doing her job!
You're saying Maki bears no responsibility for stealing all of Eno's work?
Maki can do everything by herself.
I'll admit that she's talented and capable, but she doesn't trust people enough.
Eno's not like that.
Well, she's got a screw loose,
is childish, selfish, has a bad temper,
snaps and takes it out on others,
jumps to conclusions,
is a crybaby...
You've got more cons than pros there, you know?
Is somebody talking about me?
She compiled this like it's a normal report.
And this doesn't name anyone. Just "president" and "assistant,"
nobody would notice the difference at a glance.
Sayo's right. This probably is pretty underhanded.
It's like putting someone's diary up for all
the world to see without their permission.
"Agenda: Dropping your handkerchief"?
W-We need this for tomorrow's meeting!
What? Handkerchief dropping?
Indeed!
We're going to have a heated discussion about it!
I-I see...
This is also additional material for the meeting.
Could you make some copies for me?
O-Okay.
Leave them on top of that table over there when you're done.
I'll come get them later.
Okay, all done.
Now I just need to slip them in.
I wonder what's keeping Sayo.
She's hopeless. Guess I'll go pick her up.
Sure, she might have a lot more flaws than strengths,
but Eno gets mad at me when I act irresponsibly,
yet she'll place her trust in me once more and let me handle things.
Uh... what's going on here?
I'd much prefer Eno over Maki as president.
S-Sayo...
The problem with her is that she
overcompensates for that with her defects.
Stick with the praise until the end, will you?!
Who?
Oh, just Eno.
H-Hello.
Hello.
I'm not sure what's going on, but you were talking about how I was more fit to be president, right?
You quit that job to save what little pride you had left!
I'll admit Maki's partly to blame,
but she would never abandon her post!
You're not the one I see fit to be president!
Amazing, Wine!
So gallant, Wine!
Wine?
I feel the same way!
Wine
The Wild
One
Riko
Wine? Are you high?
Maki? Fit to be president?
I know that better than anyone!
I just wanted to trouble her a bit,
so that when she turned to me for help,
I could say, "Oh well," and assist her anyway.
But you just had to go and become her assistant, didn't you?!
What?
I'm the bad guy here?
So basically, you wanted her to rely on you,
but she totally ignored you,
and to top it all off, made me her assistant, so that got you all pissed off?
See? Childish, right?
Sayo!
You! Quit being the assistant right this very minute!
If you do that, I'll stop doing these mean things!
No can do.
What are you, a toddler?!
Takes one to know one.
You idiot! Fool! Birdbrain!
Negotiations have broken down.
Suzu.
Let's team up and make sure that
Maki doesn't push herself anymore.
I'm willing to do some work too, so teach me the ropes.
Sure, Kurahashi!
That was the first time you called me Suzu. I'm so happy!
You can call me what you want too.
Wine it is, then!
Why?
You're so selfish, Eno.
First you say you want to be the president,
then you tell her to quit being the assistant.
Shut up!
I like it when you act hilariously dumb.
I'd rather not see you acting just plain stupid.
The heck? What a selfish thing to say!
Not as selfish as you can be.
I'm going to quit plotting all this nonsense.
In tomorrow's meeting, I'll hold my head up high and say I want to be president again.
If I don't get the backing, I'll graciously accept my defeat.
Are you giving up on getting Maki to acknowledge you?
Yeah, I'm good!
I'd much prefer Eno over Maki as president.
I managed to hear something that made me even happier.
I'm gonna try to be vice president if I fail with this!
I don't think you can call that "gracious."
So yeah, we're not going to get any extra help.
Don't worry, though. We'll do our best!
You don't have to...
Also, Riko only joined because I said she wouldn't have to do any work—
Shut yer trap
and rely on people more!
Okay!
Th-Then could we each come up with ten subjects to research?
Actually, you rely on people too much for that stuff.
I'm so glad, though.
I was afraid you'd stop coming if the harassment continued.
This was first time I've ever kicked up a fuss with other people.
It was just so much fun that I really didn't want to lose it.
I've always been doing this by myself, you see.
Oh, it's not that she refuses to rely on people.
The problem is she just doesn't know how to.
Seriously, I'm too talented for my own good!
Then there's your personality.
Oh yeah, why didn't you say
anything about the ex-president?
She was clearly suspicious!
You knew that Mizushima and her were good friends, didn't you?
But she...
Just be the president then!
Nobody's gonna follow you if you
keep doing things your way, though,
so I'm sure that you'll come
crying to me for help someday!
Nobody had ever said something like that to me before.
If Enomoto was involved in the harassment,
that'd mean she still hasn't acknowledged me.
I didn't want to admit that.
Try telling her that next time.
What?
Why can't they see they make such good rivals?
So dumb.
Looks like I don't have to worry about the rain today.
Well, then...
Oops.
Crap. Did I mix them all up?
Must be stuff for tomorrow's meeting.
Whatever. They'll be fine.
I should get rid of this so nobody ever sees it.
Oh, Enomoto. That—
A second look revealed a mistake in this report,
so I'll be getting rid of it.
The copies you asked for are on the table!
Don't worry about picking those up!
Enomoto's a real hard worker,
but she's a bit too restless, isn't she?
The next day
The student meeting will now begin.
First, take a look at the papers on your desks.
It has reports on each committee's achievements, goals and issues,
along with proposals from the suggestion boxes placed around school.
We, the student council, included our comments in those reports while we compiled them.
We'll take questions and suggestions in a bit.
Objection!
Enomoto?
This meeting doesn't concern you, so please leave!
Oh, but it does!
I'm still officially the president,
and you're my assistant, the vice president.
The reason I'm here today—
Um...
What's this "love lab research" supposed to be?
Huh?
This is what you've been doing, Maki?
Did they do this?
Disgusting.
You've got it all wrong.
The "president" written here refers to her over there!
What?
You said it yourself!
You're still the president, and Maki is your assistant!
Love research at the student council?
What the heck is this?
We aren't allowed to be in relationships, either.
Hey...
This is what they've been hard at work with?
Well, the contents look completely serious.
Yeah, but I wouldn't put it past Enomoto to do this.
She does seem rather opinionated.
She seems like she'd be difficult to work under.
Was she really doing this?
No way!
I feel so sorry for Maki.
Poor thing.
Maki...
But you know, this is kinda embarrassing.
How disappointing.
Enough yapping!
Don't you sneer at someone who's been working hard for all of you!
I dare you to find me someone who's never
daydreamed about having a perfect boyfriend,
or having a guy find them cute!
Right here!
Whose side do you think you're on?!
It embarrasses me to admit it, but I have.
Isn't it the normal thing to do?
Doesn't matter if you're a student council member or extremely talented,
we're all the same in that regard.
That's why...
That's why you looked into it, right?
Because a student who wishes to remain anonymous asked you to.
There was a letter from someone who said
they wanted to know more about this stuff.
Suggestion Box
Right in here.
Yeah!
We looked into it to help her out!
Oh, so that's what this was all about.
So nice of you!
The two of them are quite good at helping others out.
I want to take back everything I said.
Seriously.
That saved us big time!
You could've spoken up sooner, though.
Hey, I only just thought of it.
That sounds so fake.
Sorry about all these issues.
Let's wrap things up here and finish this some other day.
Also, take the feelings of that student into
account and keep this under wraps, please!
Okay!
We managed to pull through, somehow.
Come on, I know you're shocked by all this, but...
Thank you, Riko!
I didn't do anything.
Seeing you get mad like that made me really happy!
I'm so very glad you saw me that day!
I hope you'll continue to be my friend!
Of course I will, idiot!
Thank goodness!
I'm really sorry.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I'm sorry for pinning the blame on you too.
As a token of my apology,
I'll work for you as your vice president!
I'll take treasurer, then.
What the hell?!
This means we'll all be able to research love!
Things will be getting quite lively.
I haven't said anything about doing that!
You seemed pretty up for it, though.
For real?!
Really?
What're you talking about?!
Did you hit your head or something?!
Suggestion Box
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
I'm Fuji Girls' student council
vice president, Enomoto Yuiko.
I was so worried about my juniors that I came back for them.
And I'm the treasurer, Mizushima Sayori.
I was so worried about the student council's budget that I came back for it.
W-Well, we can trust you to handle the money.
Leave it all to me. I'm keeping a close watch on the student council's budget and your allowance, Eno.
Wait, why my allowance?!
You've been wasting money recently.
Or so your parents said as they asked me for help.
Have some more faith in your daughter!
Love Lab Research Resumes ! Or so we thought...