Ruth, I think it's just about done.
Let's skim off the scum.
Koutarou, you read the script, right?
Time for practice!
Wake up, Koutarou!
Koutarou!
I can't get used to this, no
matter how many times I see it.
Why do you have to
sleep all weird, Sanae?
Good morning, Your Highness.
Please wake Yurika-san up first.
Sure.
Yurika, wake up.
It's morning.
I can't eat anymore...
Stop talking in your sleep.
I told you, I'm full.
You won't wake up, huh?
How's this, then?
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
I can't...
I can't eat that much...
Wake up!
I can just pick out the meat...
Theia-chan, we'll help!
You need to use shock treatment!
Wake up!
It's morning!
Potatoes are attacking me!
She's still not up!
We need something more stimulating!
She's must be a pretty heavy
sleeper if that didn't wake her...
It's so warm...
And just like that, I'd spent three
whole seasons together with these guys.
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Um, what's Christmas?
Invasion Going Well?!
Hm?
Why do you ask, Ruth?
Well, several members of our class
have been talking about it,
ever since December started.
I thought you would know, Kiriha-sama.
Indeed.
I don't know the specifics,
but from what I've heard—
I'll tell you!
Christmas is when you get to eat
all the chicken and cake you want!
That's not right.
It's when Santa gives you presents.
Santa?
Do you know this man?
No, not really...
You receive presents from
someone you don't even know?
What if it's something dangerous?
It's not like that!
Why not?
Huh?
Why...
I heard that Christmas was
a formal religious event.
Got the wrong info...
That's a problem.
That's not really wrong, either.
It's only recently that couples
get all lovey-dovey instead.
Lovey-dovey?
That's right.
It's a day as sweet as cake!
Everyone's talking about Christmas.
So, what are you doing, Kou?
Hm? What about me?
Christmas. What are your plans?
You're not seriously going to
tell me you don't have any?
You're in high school, come on.
Well, if I had to say—
It doesn't have to be couples!
You can get together with friends or family,
and eat good food.
Yeah!
You have a party with everyone!
A party?
N-No, we can't!
We have to practice for the play, instead!
What? Really?
Of course!
We're going to really
start practicing tomorrow.
So much for getting worked
up about Christmas.
Wait, you're practicing with
Theia-chan, aren't you?
No.
Hm? You have something else?
Yeah.
I do have plans for Christmas!
Hey, Kou!
The Silver Princess
and the Blue Knight
Part 2
We're going to start practicing again.
I'll be with Satomi-kun.
How about some Christmas cake?
Here you go.
Only three days until Christmas Eve.
The Harukaze Pastry Studio
is taking orders for cakes!
Sakuraba-senpai.
Hey, there.
Hello, Santa.
You working here?
Ho, ho, ho.
I started today.
Please have this present, young lady.
I think I've been a pretty good girl.
You're only going to give me this flier?
Hm... This is a problem...
I'll take this, then, Santa.
Does it look good on me?
Very cute.
You look like a little kid.
You're such a tease, Satomi-kun.
I'm only telling the truth.
Hm? Here you go.
We're accepting orders for cakes!
Sorry for bugging you.
Oh, I'll help you out to make it up to you.
You can't.
I wouldn't be working for myself.
Actually...
There is something I'd like
for you to help me with.
I wanted to ask when I had
more time tomorrow, but...
What is it?
Koutarou's started a new job?
Yeah, according to Makkenji, he suddenly
decided at lunch today to get one.
I've been telling him since this morning
we need to start practice, too.
I can't believe him...
Perfect!
It's a etheric stove!
He didn't say anything
until this morning, either.
Why suddenly want a job?
Yeah.
Supposedly, Satomi-kun didn't
tell Makkenji-kun why, either.
I bet there's a reason why
he wants to keep it secret.
I just hope he found himself a girl.
A girl?
Satomi-san did?!
Yeah, he's going to go on a wonderful
Christmas date with his girlfriend,
so he's working hard at his job.
How nice. Someone's growing up.
He promised that he'd practice
as soon as the script was done...
Her Highness is working so hard, and yet...
He's all lovey-dovey...
with a girlfriend...
Um, Ruth-san...
I'm back.
Welcome back, Koutarou.
It must be cold out.
It was so cold.
Oh, we're having stew today?
I'm happy.
I'm back.
Oh, Ruth-san.
Satomi-sama, could you
explain yourself this instant?
Huh?
No, I'm trying to tell you...
It's only a three day part-time job.
I'll keep lunches open for practice.
It's not like there's some special reason
I didn't talk about the job I was taking.
Why did you have to get a new job, anyway?
Yeah. It's weird.
Well, I kind of needed some
money for New Year's...
Is that really the only reason?
I don't believe it.
Huh?
Well...
It's time to stop hiding it, Koutarou.
Huh?
Everyone already knows, so there's no point.
Right?
Actually, Koutarou and I have promised
to go on a date for Christmas.
Koutarou's working so he can pay for me.
You're so cruel...
You have Sakuraba-senpai, too!
No, you know...
Satomi-sama...
Her Highness has stayed up so many
nights for the play, and yet, you...
What a ridiculous act.
It's obviously a lie.
I don't sense anything sneaky from you two.
You two feel like nothing but
friends since the amusement park.
Oh well, everyone's gotten a lot sharper.
Well, who cares about the job?
We'll study hard during winter break.
Got it?
Y-Yeah, leave it to me!
Anyway, let's eat.
O-Oh, we don't have a ladle.
I'll go—
Thank you, Kiriha-san.
You helped me out.
No problem.
I wish you would have told me first, though.
Huh?
Anyway, let's eat.
It looks great!
Let's eat!
All my power's being sucked out...
Brother!
Stew really is the best in the winter!
Meat! Where's the meat?!
Come on, Koutarou. Let's eat!
Koutarou, I got you some.
Thanks!
Hey, Koutarou. Don't get it everywhere.
Your Highness...
Brother, switch with me...
N-No thanks.
All right.
That's a great tree.
Oh, Sakuraba-senpai.
I was able to get it with
my pay from yesterday.
A little bit more expensive
than I was hoping, though.
I see.
I brought these from home,
feel free to use them.
Thank you. That helps!
I want to see the smiles on everyone's faces.
Yeah.
Please keep it secret until then, though.
Of course.
It's a surprise party, after all.
Everyone, make sure you keep yourselves
in line during the the holiday season...
And then it was the day of the
closing ceremony, Christmas Eve.
See you when third semester starts!
Have a good New Year.
Merry Christmas.
What? A surprise Christmas party?
Yeah.
I was thinking of holding it
in the Knitting Club room.
I'm having Sakuraba-senpai
help me out, but...
You're not going to ask me
to help out, too, are you?
You could have asked earlier!
I need more people.
Please!
All you have to do is get everyone to come.
Please?
I have a lot of complaints,
but I'll accept out of the
kindness of my heart.
I owe you!
Okay, see you at the club room at 3 PM!
Huh?
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Sanae
Huh? Who's Sanae?
Looks like your guess was wrong.
Guess it wasn't for a girlfriend, after all.
I guess I was just hoping things were
finally going somewhere for him.
To think it was something like this...
Yeah.
So, what are you planning?
Well, I'll help, of course.
I'll make sure it turns out interesting.
That took a while.
I need to pick up the cake, too.
Satomi-kun!
Oh, Senpai!
Are you done setting up the room?
It's terrible.
Come quickly!
Huh?
Sumo!
Knitting Society
Kamibasami attack!
Fullback!
What's going on?!
Um, I don't really know, either...
Knitting Society
Did they get the wrong room?
Well, it seems like they got
permission to use this room.
What? Why?!
Anyway, let's prepare
another room, Satomi-kun.
Yeah, but we don't have much time...
How about your apartment?
Huh?
I see.
Apartment 106, huh?
Sorry, Senpai, I'll be going ahead.
Please come later!
Okay, I will!
Yeah, I shouldn't have tried to act cool,
and just had this party at
my apartment from the start.
That's where I met all of them.
I think I ran into Sanae first.
She's like my little sister now.
I've gotten used to her clinging
to me, and going into my body.
Theia's grown up quite a bit.
She's a lot kinder and more straightforward
than she was when I first met her.
I wouldn't mind serving under her now.
Ruth-san is very dedicated.
I'm glad she's around.
If Ruth-san wasn't here, I don't think things
would have have gone well with Theia.
I thought that Yurika was
completely unreliable at first,
but she's surprisingly committed.
I don't get bored with her around.
I feel like I can really talk to Kiriha-san
since that amusement park was invaded.
Kiriha-san said that we're best friends now.
I wanted to show them how I felt.
There wasn't really any reason
to keep it a surprise.
It would have been enough to
just have fun with everyone.
Merry Christmas!
Huh?
Koutarou's surprised!
We got him!
It went better than expected.
Our plan wins!
You're so easy, Satomi-san.
You still have a long way to go, Koutarou.
Sorry for surprising you, Satomi-sama.
This is...
Kurano-san and the others figured
out what you were planning!
Makkenji!
You betrayed me!
No, they asked me first.
I didn't betray anyone!
No, you're the one who called
all those athletes right?!
That was me.
I had Sakuraba-senpai help, too.
I-I'm sorry, Satomi-kun.
They convinced me it'd be more fun this way.
N-No fair...
Actually, you guys...
Come on!
Don't get so mad, Koutarou.
You were trying to do the
same thing, you know?
Yeah. Hoisted by your own leotard.
It's "petard"!
Sigh. What was the point of me working?
Koutarou.
We brought the tree you
got with your earnings.
The Harukaze Pastry Studio
Christmas cake is here, too!
Cheers!
What would you like, Harumi-senpai?
Thank you very much.
Everything looks great.
I don't know what to pick.
Thank you.
These are really good.
Did you make all of this by yourselves?
Yeah.
Jeez, you guys got me good.
Koutarou, I want some chicken!
Hm? Sure.
Yay!
That looks great.
Koutarou, what are you thinking?
Nothing.
I'm going to eat some!
I think these invaders may have
invaded my heart, instead.
We had fun today.
Yeah, it sure was fun being surprised.
Come on, Satomi-kun.
I apologized for that.
No, I'm going to remember that forever.
Harukaze
Park
But, Santa isn't like that.
Ho, ho, ho.
Oh, Santa.
We meet again.
Yes, and I have a present
for a good girl this time.
Thank you.
Can I open it now?
Ho, ho, ho.
Of course.
It's nothing special, but
you can use it right now.
Was this the piece you
knitted at the beginning?
You're right.
So it might be a bit rough here, but...
I wanted you to have my first project.
Sorry for giving you this as my present.
No, I'm really happy.
This will bring back lots
of memories for me.
Does it suit me?
It doesn't.
You should have gotten a better muffler.
That's enough.
Why are you talking back to your princess?
Princess Alaia, forgive me.
As long as you understand.
Allow me to give this to you.
Lord Veltorion, this sword will protect you,
from any enemy you may face,
or from any hardship.
Then I shall protect you
with my life and this sword,
Princess Alaia.
Koutarou.
You still haven't remembered, have you?
But that's all right.
You still have places you need to be,
and people you need to meet.
After countless years and
distance, someday, again...
Harukaze Shopping District
The Silver Princess and the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess
and the Blue Knight
Part 2
Performance Today
E-Everyone, are you all ready?
Yes, Your Highness.
Everything's perfect.
The dragon's great, too.
You can relax a bit more, Theia.
It'll be fine.
R-Right.
If you forget a line, I'll help you out.
All right, everyone,
we're going to make this play happen!
It's the last episode of
Mahou Shoujo Love Love Heart.
Too bad!
I'm sad.
I loved everyone.
I know. It's sad.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
The End?!
See you again.