My Silky Love
nijuu yojikan zutto
Every hour of the day
My Silky Love
kimi no koto omoutabi
whenever I think about you
My Silky Love
modokashii kono kimochi
these impatient feelings
My Silky Love
tada afurekaetteku
just overflow
suki to ieba kantan nanoni
It would be easier if I just tell you that I love you
kimi ga mae ni kichauto
but when you appear in front of me
kyara ga sobie watashi no koto wo jamashiteru
my personality stands up and interferes
itsumo naraba tsuyoki de ikeru
I can usually pull through with my assertiveness
sonna seikaku nanoni
That's just the way I am
donna ganbattemitemo kabe wa kuzusenai
But no matter how hard I try, I can't break the wall that's between us
sasshite hoshii kono kimochi wo
I want you to realize my feelings
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimi ni
That's why I always gaze at you with the message of
daisuki da yo to okuru shisen
"I love you"
saidai no yuuki de
with all of my courage!
yaburesouna SILK no HEART
My heart made of silk feels like it's about to rip apart
kimi ni atte kizuita yatto
After meeting you, I finally realized
ai ni wa bukiyou dattandatte
that I'm really clumsy when it comes to love
wasurekaketa koi no kizuato
My scars from love that I've almost forgotten
kyuu ni uzukidashitano kyun to
have started to ache all of a sudden
itsuka wa watashirashiku suki to
Someday, like how I normally would...
iwanakya ima yori yowaku nacchau yo
I must tell you that I love you, or else I'll become even weaker