Shine!
I dream of stars (Let's find them)
I'm over the limit
I know I'll keep surpassing myself
I won't lose to anyone
Purple is the land and blue the sky
Wow!
You wouldn't expect anything less from 5pb, Leanbox's diva, would you?
(Green leaves are in the air)
Indeed!
I want to gaze at it with you once more
(Forevermore)
Your tenderness, your warmth (I want to feel it)
You might be far away now, but we will meet again
Shine!
I dream of stars (Let's find them)
I'm over the limit
My love will not waver (Gracie☆Star)
Comets circle the world (They are bifrost)
I know I can cross the barrier they are
I won't lose to anyone
I don't care if it's a concert or whatever,
but you're being way too noisy!
Put yourself in the shoes of those who have to work in this racket.
First things first, I'd like to know why a mouse has to go underwater.
"Sea mouse" means something else entirely! It refers to a worm!
Found it!
Thank you all!
Next up:
Dimension tripper!!!!
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
#03 A weekend (girls' night out) at Leanbox
It's all well and good that she invited us to the concert,
but what's with Vert not showing up herself?
I'm sure she has her reasons.
Well?
Which one is Vert's room?
Hey, it's unlocked!
Porno
Superstar
What...
...happened here?
It almost looks like this room was broken into.
I think it's more likely that it just hasn't been cleaned up.
Oh, this is a game that can only be bought by those over eighteen years of age!
Hey, stop that!
We've got little girls here!
What are the rear guard doing?!
I'll back them up.
You all carry on without me.
Jeez!
Oh, here she is!
That was quick! You could've said something!
What are you doing, Vert?
Hey!
Not there!
She's clearly playing an online game.
Four Goddesses Online?
Hey! Sorry to see you couldn't make it!
Oh my.
Welcome, ladies.
Sorry, I'm a little tied up right now.
Hold it! Why'd you ditch us to play games?!
I thought I'd just play for an hour before leaving,
but my faction ended up laying siege to the enemy.
I couldn't just up and leave like that.
I thought you were going to throw a party for us here after the concert.
We're right about to topple their castle, so if you could wait just a little bit longer...
I never knew she was like this.
Well, hobbies vary from person to person.
Wow, what a goddess-for-nothing!
She might be even worse than me!
Not a chance.
Zoinks!
They're in perfect sync!
What now?
Looks like we'll be waiting a bit longer.
Let's see...
All right!
Let's get everything ready!
What?
Why do we have to?
Quit whining.
We've come all the way to Leanbox,
so let's make it a party worth the trip.
First off: Nepgear, IF, and Compa,
go shopping for ingredients!
O-Okay!
Everyone else can help clean up the room.
Begin at once!
There she goes again.
She just turns into a total bossypants sometimes.
It's like some weird switch in her brain.
Quiet!
Get to work!
Leanbox Live
Looks like Ge-Ge and Iffy aren't here yet.
I'd better hurry, or the old hag will yell at me 'til the mice come home.
That hurt!
Wh-What?
Is it that amusing to see a mouse trip and fall?
I'm so glad you're okay!
You look a little bruised, though.
I'll put this on for you, 'kay?
There! All better!
Be careful, okay, Mister Mouse?
O-Okay.
I'll take my leave, then.
W-Wait!
What is it?
Um...
Could I have your name, please?
It's Compa!
C-Compa...
Such a sweet name.
Ge-Ge?
Get your hands off that thing!
What's wrong, Ge-Ge?
I don't know.
It's like all my strength just left me.
Could it be anemia?
But I've never heard of a goddess suffering from anemia.
That was close.
Never thought I'd run into one of the CPU Candidates.
That aside,
Compa's an angel.
A total angel!
Hnng!
Ladies,
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Welcome to my party!
Actually, Vert,
you didn't do shit.
Let's not do this.
You're wasting your breath.
I heard you had a dizzy spell earlier.
Yes, but I'm all right now.
Come now, ladies.
Let us eat, drink, and make merry!
I've prepared an extraordinary game for us today!
What is it? Tell me!
I'm sure showing it to you would be quicker than explaining.
Neptune and Noire,
could you step back for a bit, please?
Roger!
Huh? What's going on?
Give us a splendid fight, you two.
Wow!
Oh no! Nep-Nep!
Zoinks!
I've turned into a Dogoo!
I-Is this supposed to be me?
This special camera captures your movements
and projects them out in 3D.
Pretty amazing technology, don't you think?
So, you want me to fight Noire like this?
Hey, you stinking Noigoo!
I'll send you flying all the way to Planeptune!
Wh-What the heck's a Noigoo?
Yay! I scored some points!
Now I'm mad!
You'd better prepare yourself,
Nepgoone!
Look at you, you sucky Noigoo!
By the way, there's also a more realistic combat simulation mode
which you can use for combat training.
Amazing!
That sounds fun.
I wanna play too!
Of course!
Please, enjoy yourselves!
You're late!
Do you mean to ruin our entire plan?!
I rushed here as fast as I could, you know.
It's your fault for making such a tight schedule, hag!
How many times must I tell you to cease addressing me, your superior, in such a way?
W-Well, whatever.
I can't allow mere mice to perturb me.
Hand you-know-what over already!
Gotcha.
Now we have four.
Tonight,
the rules of this game they call their world
will be turned upside down.
Over my dead body!
What is it?
We're in the middle of a party here.
Vert, actually...
Yikes.
We're done already?
What's wrong, Vert?
Well, there's a waste disposal plant in the Zune district.
I hear a large amount of monsters showed up there.
The Zune district...
It's a small island, isn't it?
They say it adjoins land during ebb tide, and only then.
Why are monsters such a big deal? They show up all over, right?
It's an area under this nation's rule,
so this shouldn't be happening.
But it would appear that it is.
I'll be going there now.
Let me tag along!
This is a problem for my own country to deal with.
C'mon, fate must have brought us here today!
Let us help.
Doing the whole "we're all friends because we signed a treaty" thing again, are we?
You got that right!
I'll help too.
I owe you one after you helped us during the kidnapping incident, after all.
Okay, then! The three of us—
I-I'm coming too!
Who knows how long you three would keep us waiting otherwise.
Ladies...
Very well.
Let the four of us go—
Um!
I'll come too!
M-Me too!
Me three!
Me four!
You girls should stay back.
This isn't a game.
What?
You need to stay here and keep watch, Uni.
You can't even transform yet, after all.
Nepgear!
Leave this to your trusty ol' sis.
I gotta show off once in a while!
Okay.
So, on that note,
it's morphin' time!
Let's be on our way, ladies.
I'm amazed you were able to scrape so much trash together.
I had to.
Otherwise, we wouldn't be able to lure all the CPUs here at once.
Get over here already.
Are you okay, Nepgear?
Y-Yeah...
I'm fine,
but I'm kinda worried about Sis.
Is your sister not that strong?
Nah, it's not like that.
She's really strong when she gets serious.
I'm so weak, but she always keeps me safe.
But...
I don't know why,
but I have a bad feeling about tonight.
A bad feeling?
Okay, I got it.
Thanks, Otome.
Seems like I was right all along.
Did you figure something out?
The mouse at the shopping mall looked familiar,
so I asked a friend in the intelligence bureau to look into it for me.
And unsurprisingly, he was on every country's blacklist.
He's on the list of most wanted people—
Or should I say, most wanted mice.
Huh? Mister Mouse is a bad guy?
That makes me sad.
That's not all.
I also found out that he was spotted boarding a boat for the Zune district a few hours ago.
Doesn't that mean...
It's just guesswork at this point,
but somebody probably arranged for those monsters to appear at the waste processing plant.
If I leave now, I can still make it by ebb tide.
I'm gonna go check things out.
Me too.
Take me with you!
No way.
I can't put you in danger too.
But I'm really worried!
Please, IF!
Land ahoy.
Ugh, look at 'em swarming over it like flies.
There's lots of them, but they look easy enough to handle.
But it'd spell big trouble if they somehow managed to make it to the city.
We should hurry up and—
These fatasses are the big hitters, eh?
Can't complain about our enemies here, can we?
Let's take down one each!
Race you for it!
I ain't gonna let you one-up me!
Wait, you three!
Basic battle theory says we should team up and take down one at a time!
More like basic cowards' theory.
Good heavens.
They always get so headstrong when they've activated HDD.
Well,
I'm no exception!
Listen up, Nepgear.
Whatever happens, don't try the impossible.
We'll retreat the moment we sense any danger.
Okay.
Thank you, IF.
Lace Ribbon Dance!
I win.
Tanzerin Trombe!
Damn, I'm second?
Looks like those two aren't done yet.
Rainy Ratnapura!
Cross Combo!
I suppose those two are tied?
That also means they both finished dead last.
I was just a little bit faster.
If you say so.
I was last—
Noire! Blanc!
Wh-What is this?!
Don't fuck with me!
Makes my skin crawl!
I should just...
I guess it's about time.
Is that the one behind this?
Goddesses,
fall into my sanctuary!
Th-This light...
I'm losing strength. How?
It's that rock.
We just need to destroy it!
Anything that depends on Share Energy as the source of its power
cannot come into contact with that rock.
Be it a weapon,
or even a goddess.
What is that supposed to mean?
That rock is called an Anti-Crystal.
It's a stone that severs the link between you and your Share Crystals,
robbing you of your powers and abilities.
Anti-Crystal?
Oh, these are some real Kodak moments.
These pictures are gonna cause quite the commotion around the world.
Goddammit!
You're not gonna get away with this!
I'll beat you black and blue!
I do wonder how you'll manage that.
Goddesses inside an Anti-Crystal field will continue to lose their strength and energy.
Just hang around and watch your chances of victory go down the drain!
Sure is quiet here.
Maybe they're done exterminating the monsters already?
Nope, they're still around.
Where are Neptune and the rest?
IF!
Look at that!
Sis...
I wish  /  I will be here where we met
I would go fight  /  Until my life bears fruit
I won't forget  /  I will start on an endless journey
My promise to you  /  Only one vow will accompany me
The sad things, too, let us forge a closer bond
The goddesses taught me that
Everybody now, remember the sky we saw
Happiness? Lucky? Your smile?
I won't lose, I want to be happy
I won't give up, everyone
Happiness? Lucky? Your smile?
Let us find our future
Love & Peace
This program was filmed before the CPUs were captured.
Nep Station!
Today, we're comin' at you straight from the studio!
Here's today's special guest!
I'm 5pb.
Please buy a copy of my new single, Dimension tripper!!!!
This isn't stealth marketing!
The Sisters' Resolve (Turn)
Just blatant old-fashioned marketing!