World War III.
By 2036,
it will have resulted in 5.7 billion casualties worldwide.
And this is what starts it.
Huh? What is it?
It's only a model.
Maybe it transforms or something?
A time machine.
Seriously?
I knew you'd recognize it, Uncle.
Then that makes this easy.
Come with me.
I refuse.
Okarin?
I came here from the alpha world line.
Over the past three weeks,
I changed the world line again and again,
sacrificing Kurisu to return to the beta world line.
I won't let it all be for naught!
Kurisu?
Wasn't that the name of the scientist
who was stabbed at the radio building?
Okabe Rintarou,
what if I told you that the way to avoid World War III
is, on July 28th, 2010,
to prevent Makise Kurisu's death?
What do you mean?
I don't know the details,
but I have one mission:
To save Makise Kurisu
and to go to the one world line unaffected by the attractor field,
the Steins Gate!
To you, insisting on life's merits and meaningless proofs
is pathetic and unfit to relieve your boredom
The conceited fools who act like they are the leaders
are proof of a basic theorem
A love that believed in infinity and the far side of the sky
were shown me by the freedom of my imagination
Finity mercilessly recorded the passage of time
leading to a choice that puts my future at stake
Hacking to the Gate
I mustn't pretend that I never made a promise
with my friends back in the day
So now I try to beat time itself with the gadgets I am left with,
and I observe alone in my solitude, but never doubt myself
Open the
Steins Gate
Steins Gate?
The architects of this plan were
my father and your future self.
None of it is anything more than a hypothesis.
It's possible the theory is wrong,
and there is no Steins Gate world line,
but I'm going anyway.
I'll bet on the chance that a bright future's waiting for me.
If you're coming with me,
then take my hand.
Um,
Mayushii didn't really understand any of that,
but if this person,
this Kurisu, is important to you,
shouldn't you try to help her?
World War III sounds like one of your crazy fantasies.
No one else could handle it.
I don't care about the 5.7 billion people in the future...
but...
Thank you.
Let's go.
Two people can get in it?
Of course!
This is my father's masterpiece.
Okarin!
Leave your phone.
It might interfere with your phone in the past.
I'll be back.
Good luck.
This is a time machine.
Yeah,
I stopped in 1975 and 2000.
It's working fine,
but it's running out of fuel.
Wait. It can go from past to future?
Of course it can.
It's a time machine.
I see.
Is that because we're in a different world line now?
Sit down.
We'll head to just before noon on July 28th.
We can't change location,
so if we arrive too early, it'll spread panic at the radio building,
possibly affecting Makise Kurisu's actions.
Your first time, the Gs are pretty tough.
Get ready.
Okarin...
What is this?
These always show up.
I guess they're like fragments of time.
Pretty, huh?
Let's go!
W-Wait.
I think I'm going to throw up.
What a wimp.
Hurry!
Don't let your other self see you.
It'll cause a serious time paradox.
How long until her stabbing?
Twenty minutes or so, I guess.
I'll prepare the time machine.
You protect her, Uncle.
Stop calling me that.
July 28th.
On the day I saw Kurisu lying in a pool of blood,
I came with Mayuri to see
Professor Nakabachi's press conference.
I heard a noise on the roof.
That's right. After that, Mayuri went to the seventh-floor Upa machines.
Oh, no!
You called me here for this?
There aren't many left of this series, and Mayushii's...
Oh well.
I'll take the back stairs to the eighth floor.
It's a metal... a metal Upa!
Is it rare?
Really!
Now that I'm here...
I'm sorry.
K-Kurisu?
H-How do you know my name?
Kurisu is alive.
Have we met somewhere?
Kurisu...
Are you listening—
What's wrong?
Answer me.
I...
I... You...
Wait!
In the handouts, you can read about the time machine's basic design.
I will use this conference as an opportunity to discuss the fundamental theory behind it.
Professor Nakabachi
The operation notes said that you'd be able to identify Makise Kurisu.
Can you?
Yeah.
Also, it's dangerous to take her outside.
If we don't figure out who stabbed her,
we can't change her fate.
Just like Mayuri?
Doctor!
What is it?
You know exactly what!
What is this "time machine theory" of yours?
Kerr Black Holes?
World lines?
You stole all of this from John Titor!
Kurisu will be stabbed right here soon.
Is she really going to be here?
Wait! Maybe she was stabbed elsewhere and brought here.
Yeah... That's possible!
Kurisu?
So it does happen here.
What's she reading?
A time machine?
Is that why she's the key to changing world lines?
What do you want?
Daddy, I wanted you to read this.
Daddy?
Professor Nakabachi?
You contacted me for the first time in seven years.
You asked me to come to your press conference, right?
That was my inspiration.
Wait. So Kurisu's dad is...
So I thought I could use it to theorize a time machine.
I wanted to hear your ideas.
If this is accepted, you can use it
as revenge for everyone who kicked you out—
I wasn't kicked out!
I got sick of them and left.
Sorry.
It's not bad.
Really?
If you're okay with it,
I thought we could put both our names on the paper
because you inspired me—
Don't be stupid.
Leave!
I'll publish this paper under my name.
Wait!
You wouldn't steal it, right, Daddy?
I never thought you'd resort to tha—
Shut up!
How dare you call it stealing?!
Why are you so smart?
A girl shouldn't be smarter than her father!
If it weren't for you, I would've been smart too!
If it weren't for you...
You're that kid from earlier.
So that's it?
You were plotting to ruin my conference together, huh?
I see.
So that's it.
Daddy!
I'll protect her!
How dare you insult me?
Why, you...
Stop it, Daddy!
Please!
Don't even speak to me!
Oh, shit!
What do you know?
You don't know how I feel.
You don't know how I've been humiliated
and the shit I've been through!
If it weren't for you...
Don't...
Don't do it!
Kurisu...
K-Kurisu!
Fools.
This is the perfect end for you.
I'm sorry for getting you involved.
Why?
Because he's my dad,
I wanted him to accept me.
That's all.
Kurisu...
I'm scared...
I... I don't want to die.
I don't want to die.
I don't...
Kurisu...
Kurisu!
They're back already!
Okarin!
Okarin, that blood...
It's all right.
It's not his.
I was the one who killed Kurisu.
Okarin?
I know it hurts, but you can't give up yet.
We have enough fuel to go back one more time.
Shut up!
Nothing will change!
The attractor field convergence will kill her all over again.
It's your phone.
A message?
Open it.
But...
Just do it.
Turn on the TV.
Turn on the TV?
The TV?
Mysterious Fire in Cargo Bay
Professor Nakabachi Defects to Russia
The plane carrying Professor Nakabachi
made it to Russia,
despite a mysterious cargo bay fire.
We were very fortunate.
If this hadn't triggered the metal detector,
Mayushii
the paper would've gone up.
That's Mayushii's metal Upa!
Look. It has Mayushii's name on it!
She's right.
But what's it doing in Russia?
That paper is the start of everything.
Next comes the international time machine arms race.
To rule time is to rule the world.
And that begins a world war.
5.7 billion lives are at stake.
Save Makise Kurisu and change this world line!
It's impossible.
It's just like with Mayuri.
No matter what I do, it'll end up the same.
Kurisu will die.
How can you say that after only one time?
One time?!
It's more than that.
How many times...
How many times do you think I've failed?!
I already know
how insane this time loop is
and what a cruel fate it has in store.
I knew this...
I knew this would happen.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
You're not the kind of person to quit halfway.
Mayushii knows this!
You're not the kind of person to ever give up.
Even when Mayushii couldn't say goodbye to her grandmother,
you never stopped going to her grave.
That's why I could say goodbye.
That's why I got better!
So don't give up.
You should've received a video file on July 28th.
July 28th...
You should be able to watch it
now that you've failed once to rescue Makise Kurisu.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry I lied to you.
The plan called for you to fail once.
So that you would see this.
What is this?
Nice to meet you, me from 15 years ago.
It's Okarin!
If you've opened this message,
then you've failed to rescue Kurisu.
It must've been painful,
but that pain gave rise to my obsession,
so it had to happen.
You could say it was a part of the preparation.
Now we can begin the plan in earnest,
the plan to save Makise Kurisu
and enter Steins Gate.
We have two objectives.
First, we must destroy the paper on time machines,
which Professor Nakabachi took to Russia.
Second, we must save Makise Kurisu.
If I could do that...
But avoiding her death and changing the past are impossible
because of the attractor field convergence.
Isn't that right?
I'll do my best to explain.
Saving Makise Kurisu is possible.
You're just approaching it the wrong way.
Listen well.
You must not change the past once it's been established.
You must not undo what you saw that day.
If you do either, the past will change, and all will be lost.
Remember your experiences in the alpha world line.
It was only three weeks,
but you should have memories of your time with Makise Kurisu,
everyone's sacrifices to save Mayuri,
and everything that's happened.
You must not waste those three weeks.
You must not undo them.
The only reason you wish so desperately to save her
is because of the world lines you experienced.
And it's the sole reason
I devoted my life to developing a time machine.
The reason you've managed to get
as far as you have is that we both want to save Kurisu.
Thus, you must deceive your other self.
Save her without changing the past where she died.
Make your past self
mistake a living Kurisu for a dead one.
If you do, the past won't change.
I get it.
What does he mean?
Okarin, do you know?
I know you'll understand me.
By the way, the time machine's ID is C204.
I'm sure you know what that stands for.
Christina...
And I was the one who named the target world line Steins Gate.
You know why I named it that.
It doesn't really mean anything.
Isn't that right?
I will now explain the parameters
of the final mission, Operation Skuld.
Change the result without changing the established past.
The past consists of Makise Kurisu lying in a pool of blood,
and Okabe Rintarou seeing her there.
Change the past without changing that.
Deceive your other self.
Deceive the world.
That is what you must do to reach Steins Gate.
Good luck.
El Psy Congroo.
What was that?
Was that you, 15 years from now?
The voice was so deep!
Operation Skuld?
El Psy Congroo?
I still talk like that when I'm 33 years old?
I sound like a rabid fangirl.
Okarin?
I'll do it,
if that is the choice of Steins Gate.
I am the mad scientist, Hououin Kyouma!
Deceiving the world is nothing to me!
He's back to the usual Okarin.
Still, Mayushii likes Okarin better when he's like this.
I'll say it once more.
I am...
the mad scientist...
Hououin Kyouma...
and the world is in the palm of my hand!
Sore wa oroka yue no guuzen manekarezaru kiseki
It tells us that these are foolish notions and unwanted miracles
Tozasaretekita gate "kisei" wa owatta
The gate that once was shut is supervised no more
Open the eyes
Kousoku he to te wo nobashita omoide no parusu ga
My mind wished to reach the speed of light
Tobikomu fukashigi na logic
and fell into an eldritch logic
Open the eyes
Uchuu ga mada kakushimotta chitsujo no nai riron
The lawless rules of the universe remain hidden from us
Mugen to yobareta ten to ten ga fusei na chikara wo karite
What we call eternity is but dots connected, empowering each other
"Saisei" wo suru
and resurrecting us time and time again