[ED] Huh? That's strange...
I... I don't understand...
I-I thought it was this way.
Maybe... that way?
[ROY]
Are you lost, Fullmetal?
[ED SHOCKED]
Hey, give it a rest...!
If I hadn't had to come back
to keep a certain
moron out of trouble,
I wouldn't've
gotten turned around!
I don't recall anyone
asking you to come back.
You have got
to be kidding!
You'd prob'ly be halfway
to psycho town right now
if me and Scar hadn't
stopped you when we did!
[ROY]
Don't patronize me...
Please. The lieutenant had
already talked me down
by the time you even showed up.
[ED]
What?!
You two should keep quiet...
before the enemy hears us.
Listen... Even if he won't,
I'd like to say thank you...
I couldn't have snapped
him out of it by myself.
I don't know if that
means anything to you--
I'm sure the last thing any
Ishvalan wants to hear
is that they've done a
kindness for someone like me...
[HAWKEYE]
...but you did...
[HAWKEYE] It was you
who brought him back...
Back to himself.
So, thank you.
[SCAR] Your gratitude
is unnecessary.
[GUN BURST]
Right... right...!
Copy that...!
Hey, that's enough,
we can stop shooting...!
Cease fire!
[SOLDIERS COUGHING]
[CARLY] Attention
Central soldiers!
Attention Central soldiers...!
Briggs forces have taken
the Operations Center.
Damn those traitorous
Briggs cowards!
[CARLY] We have
thirteen men in our custody,
including General Cremin...
Repeat... Briggs forces have
taken the Operations Center.
Central soldiers, cease all
hostility immediately...!
I repeat: we have
your General in custody.
You were using the tank
as a distraction to hide
your true purpose--
using your alchemy
to dig that tunnel.
Ha ha!
Now you're catching on.
What was that...?
I didn't copy--
Repeat...!
What?...!
Are you sure?!
What is it?
The Operations Center!
It's been overrun
by Briggs forces,
and they've captured
General Cremin!
[OLIVIER] Operations...
is Buccaneer there?
Sir!
It's getting bad out here.
We have a large number of pale,
humanoid monsters on the loose!
[OLIVIER]
They're hard to kill, and,
worse... they're man-eaters!
No matter what happens,
do not open any gates!
You hear me?
[OLIVIER] We can't allow a
single one out into the city!
We need to destroy them
right here, right now!
Yes, General!
Cremin's making all
the wrong decisions...
What is he thinking?!
[FRANK] From now on,
I'm in command.
[FRANK] As of now,
this is Operations.
[FRANK THINKS] The Fuhrer's
chair-- a veritable throne...
If we win this battle,
it just might be mine.
[DUMMIES ROAR]
[ARMSTRONG] More?
Will they never stop coming?
Uh... sorry, General...
but what in the hell
are these damn things?
The Immortal Legion...
as promised.
[OLIVIER] Created by placing
human souls inside of
mannequin bodies...
Soldiers with no fear of death.
Just think...
this is what your
masters wanted
for all of you men.
That monster can still move?!
How many times do
we have to kill that thing?
As many times as it takes!
[SLOTH BELLOWS]
He really is a
tenacious one, isn't he.
No!
[BLAST]
[ARMSTRONG AND OLIVIER BELLOW]
Major! No!
General Armstrong! Sir!
[ARMSTRONG]
Stay back!
She and I are the
ones he's after...
Keep your distance!
Must kill her...
Such a stubborn woman...
that General.
[SLOTH ROARS]
Now, PULL!
[SLOTH STRAINS AND GRUNTS]
Dig into it, men!
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 6] Both of
you...! Run now, while you can!
What...?
This way, please, quickly!
Major! Go! Now!
You would have me
run away from this?
The mere thought of fleeing...
of leaving the
battlefield in disgrace...
I swear on my life,
such a thing will
never happen again!
[ARMSTRONG GROANS
AND STRUGGLES TO GET UP]
[SLOTH GRIMACES]
[CHAINS BREAK]
[SOLDIER SCREAMS]
[IZUNI]
You refuse to run...
That's impressive.
[IZUMI]
You're a fine man...
[IZUMI CHUCKLES]
But then, I've already got a man
a hundred times finer than you.
And who are you?
[IZUMI] Hmm...
A female officer?
You must be the indomitable
General Armstrong, then...
That subordinate of yours--
the one who has the Mohawk--
he asked me to
come and help you.
That man...! Who asked him?
Such a pain...
[SLOTH ROARS]
[OLIVIER AND ARMSTRONG
GASP IN DISBELIEF]
[SLOTH BELLOWS]
Honey...! Coming at you!
[SIG]
Right!
[SIG ROARS]
Extraordinary!
Who is he?!
He's my husband.
[SIG GRUNTS]
[ARMSTRONG GRUNTS]
[ARMSTRONG]
Incredible valor...!
Respectable muscles!
[SLOTH ROARS]
[SIZZLING ELECTRICAL ENERGY]
Ow... Hurt.
[SLOTH GROANS]
Will that monster
never stay down?!
Am I... dying now...?
For real...?
[SLOTH]
What is dying like?
[SLOTH] Such a pain...
to think about it.
But such a pain...
living... too...
[ARMSTRONG GRIMACES IN PAIN]
Major!
All that's left are
scrawny mannequins...
Get a move on
and eliminate them!
Right!
I think I'm going
to need a moment.
Right... We can handle
the rest from here, sir.
[OLIVIER] I don't
know who you are...
but I am grateful
for the help.
It was my pleasure.
With skills like yours,
I'm surprised I haven't
heard of you.
My skills...?
I'm a housewife and an
alchemist, nothing more...
You have met the
Elric brothers, haven't you...?
They're like family to me.
Wait, does that mean
that you're Izumi Curtis?
[IZUMI]
That's me.
So I assume the
Elrics are here, too?
Yeah...
I imagine they are.
Well now... perhaps we should
take care of the rest
of these dummies...
Tell me the truth...
Can you stand?
[OLIVIER] Don't
ask stupid questions.
Hold on a second...
You're severely injured...
You should take it easy.
Now that's rich!
We adults can't very well
be caught lounging about
while the youngsters
do our fighting for us.
[OLIVIER] We carry the
burden of this world now...
But none of us is going
to be around here forever...
We have to show the
next generation how it's done.
You make a good point.
We'd like to help.
We'd appreciate it...
Together, the two of you
seem almost invincible.
Yes, well... I wouldn't try to
build us up too much...
Apparently, I'm one of the ones
they've marked as a 'sacrifice.'
I'll lend you all
a quick hand...
then I'm gonna get
the hell outta here.
[IZUMI] I won't give him
a chance to catch me.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[HOHENHEIM] This is
quite the reunion,
and yet you're stone-faced.
Too bad... you're so much
less fun than you used to be.
[HOHENHEIM]
Long ago...
you were full
of life and spirit...
a vibrant being.
[HOHENHEIM]
Lust... greed... sloth...
gluttony... envy...
wrath... pride...
Those are the
seven deadly sins of man.
[HOHENHEIM] In excess, any one
of those will ruin a person...
Even so, you must understand
them all to understand humanity.
Otherwise... your knowledge
remains incomplete.
[HOHENHEIM] Why would you
sever them from yourself?
[HOHENHEIM YELPS]
Careful...
You nearly killed me.
[MASSIVE EXPLOSIONS]
For once, listen to me!
[HOHENHEIM]
Stop this!
Please be more careful...
Fighting has never been
a particular specialty of mine.
[HOHENHEIM GASPS]
[BLAST]
[MASSIVE COLLISION]
Answer me this!
Why would you create
the Homunculi--
treat them as children--
have them call you "Father"?!
Back when you were an
arrogant speck in a flask...
you used to scoff at the
very notions of
community and family...
[HOHENHEIM]
But actually...
a family is what you wanted
more than anything, wasn't it?
You wanted what the humans have.
[HOHENHEIM THINKS]
Where did he go...?
Is he holding back until
the transmutation
circle is activated?
[HOHENHEIM GRIMACES IN PAIN]
[FATHER] There
is no part of me
that wishes to lower
myself to their level...
Instead, I shall become
a far more perfect being.
There is a Philosopher's
Stone buried within you...
[FATHER]
I intend to take it.
[HOHENHEIM GRUNTS IN RELIEF]
[FATHER]
Hmmph.
So I've finally elicited
a reaction from you.
What have you done?
You might say that I've
simply done what you wouldn't.
You don't realize...
You have cast aside
something every bit as
important as your emotions.
And what could
be so important?
Don't expect to
win this battle easily...
Not when you're fighting us.
[YOKI STRAINING]
[MARCOH]
Give up; it's no use...
The tire is definitely stuck.
[HEINKEL]
What are you doing, idiot?...!
If we don't hurry,
the eclipse is going to start!
Shut your mouth...!
C'mon-- Just take care
of the car, already!
Well, since you asked nicely...
[AL] Dr. Marcoh,
please stand back...
Mr. Heinkel and I can
handle this on our own.
[MARCOH] Well, I'm sure
you can, but still--
[HEINKEL] We're fine...
Let us take care of it.
Right. Here we go.
[AL AND HEINKEL]
One... two... three...!
[DUMMIES ROAR]
Get yourselves to
the Operations center...
And I mean now!
Oh... Right!
Thank you so much!
[BUCCANEER] You know, these
mannequins are taking out so
many Central soldiers, they're
doing most of our job for us.
[BUCCANEER]
Let's keep moving...
We'll take the main gate!
[FALMAN]
Yes, sir!
[SOLDIERS GASP]
No fair...
at least give us a chance.
[EDISON]
Stop this! You beasts...!
How dare you?
How can you attack me?
You were supposedly created
to obey every order we gave you
no matter what...
This must mean the
good gentleman lied!
He lied to us about you!
[DUMMIES ROAR and GROWL]
Get back!
St-Stay away from me...!
I'm not one of the targets.
It's the others
ones you're after.
I'm not supposed to die!
[EDISON WHIMPERS]
[EDISON LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
I don't know who you are,
but you have
my sincere thanks...
Please!
Join my security detail...
I... I'll see to it that
you're taken care of---
[EDISON IN AGONY]
This "good gentleman" you
were speaking of earlier...
I wonder if you'd be so kind as
to tell me a bit more about him.
[OLIVIER]
This place is a mess.
Will you be taking over
the command here, sir?
I don't know why anyone
would sit there and make
themselves such
an easy target...
Let's go.
Uh... right!
Olivier! Look!
[OLIVIER]
Where does this lead?
[BRIBIE] Looks like it goes
quite a ways down.
Is that where the mannequin
soldiers came from?
If that's the case,
the passageway might
link up underground.
Yes... Right... Copy that...
General...! Buccaneer's squad
has just taken the main gate.
[BLISS] There was
little resistance, and
few were injured.
We also control
the main entrance...
They've secured tanks,
and are currently
taking up positions.
[CARLY] Buccaneer Squad...
maintain your position.
And be absolutely sure
not to open the gates
until every last
one of those
mannequin soldiers
has been done away with.
[BUCCANEER]
Copy that.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
This is the west gate...
Briggs' White squad
has taken control.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 2] North
Gate... Black Squad in control.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 3]
Blue Squad has the east gate.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 4] Yellow
Squad has taken the armory.
[CARLY] General Armstrong...
you know what this means.
[CARLY]
We are now in control
of most of the
Central Command Center.
We've done it...
We've beaten them!
[BUCCANEER YELLS OUT IN JOY]
[SOLDIERS CHEER VICTORIOUSLY]
[FALMAN LAUGHS]
I guess the colonel
didn't make it here in time.
[SOLDIERS IN UNISON] Vic-tor-yy!
Vic-tor-yy! Vic-tor-yy!
[BRADLEY]
Greetings, I'm back.
[MULTIPLE SHOCKED REACTIONS]
And judging by the mess I see,
it would appear that things
have gotten rather out of hand
in my absence, now wouldn't it.
[BRADLEY]
As of now,
I am personally
taking command...
We will get rid of the rebels.
All available Central forces...
it's time to fight.
He's back... King Bradley!
That bastard's still alive?
Where is he...?
Which side will
he attack us from?
Salute His Excellency...
Fuhrer Bradley!
[NARRATOR]
Destruction and slaughter...
violation and despair...
all wrought from
the king's blade...
He uses his power to overwhelm
and bring down his opponents,
laying waste to all
who stand in his way.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood
Episode 56:
"The Return of the Fuhrer"
Wherever he sets foot...
you will find a battlefield.