“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
I wonder if the Dollars should even exist...
I must... I must do something.
No matter what you know or see about your girl,
don't turn your eyes away.
It's just like King Ghidorah.
She was wearing a Raira uniform,
and she had big boobs...
It can't be... It can't be.
She...
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
A girl has been surrounded by the Kokinzoku.
Where?
In front of Peroche...
They're moving now. It looks like they're taking her somewhere.
What does she look like?
Her uniform is... Raira, I think?
She's wearing a Raira uniform, and glasses.
And she has big boobs.
Why is Sonohara-san...?
Everyone in Dollars! Emergency!
That's right! Let's all help her!
Do they really think that we'll allow this?
The Kokinzoku are getting too cocky.
And now...
We sit in the living room again and wait.
Breakup Announcement
Anyone who's nearby, help us out!
Gather up, everyone!
Are you one of the Dollars?
Are you the one who was with the black rider causing that uproar?
You bitch.
These people are from the Kokinzoku?
Mister policeman, this way!
Hurry, hurry!
Stop right there!
What have I done?
This way.
Just go straight. There's a door in the back.
I was desperate, thinking I had to do something.
Where'd she go?!
I found the girl. I helped her escape through the Orb Ikebukuro building.
Those guys are still here.
Is anyone near the Orb Ikebukuro building?!
However, I was just confused while I was running away.
Hurry! The exit is right here.
Giving birth is easier than worrying!
Why?
And, click!
Horada-san! That's not fair!
The Orb Ikebukuro building secretary and security guards are members of the Dollars. We let her through!
Well, she just came from the Orb Ikebukuro towards my place!
Who? Why?
Why are you helping me?
Damn it!
Are you all right, sir?!
Member of the Dollars passing by - I just helped a bit.
And here I thought I was quitting.
Don't quit!
You can't quit!
I knew you'd come back.
A dream?
Where did the girl go?
Is this a dream?
Move!
The girl just changed into a rabbit costume!
Where did she go? Damn!
Why you!
Better hurry up. You'll lose her!
Damn!
Idiots! What are you doing?!
W-What's going on?
The Dollars are trying to stop us.
Call for backup.
We'll win this with numbers, with sheer numbers!
All these people I've never met are helping me.
It's like I'm dreaming.
What are you doing? It's that way!
Bunny-chan has made it to safety.
Togusa, pull out.
Roger!
Fighting is no good, yes?
I make you into sushi toppings!
They're all ringing! So many of them!
Our allies aren't the only ones getting the messages.
It's them, too.
What's that? A rabbit costume?
Hey, what's wrong?
Yeah, a rabbit.
Where did the rabbit go? Anyone who finds her, report immediately!
That her?
Well, I can't see whether her boobs are big or not, so I can't tell.
I guess we'll have to make her take it off.
However,
my dreams were always my own lies.
Wait!
I only had dreams of my family laughing happily and carelessly.
So there's no way this was a dream.
It was reality.
It was the hand that told me it was so.
And then, I suddenly realized...
I recognize this hand.
Even though I had never felt it before...
This was...
Why is it that you never notice the important things until they're gone?
Kida-kun...
Why?
Why, you say?
You mean you think it's odd that I should stop the Kokinzoku from cornering you?
That's my cute, erotic Anri-chan.
That look suits you, too.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
What are you doing, Anri-chan?
What were you looking for so furtively?
Tell me, Anri-chan, what is your motive?
Kida-kun, I think you...
Think I what? Think I'm evil?
Think I'm an idiot for protecting you?
You do, don't you?
Don't say that.
Does Mikado know what's happening?
What were you trying to do to him?
I...
You knew...
You knew how he felt, and still...
Why can't you tell Ryugamine-kun, Kida-kun?
Was it fun?
Fooling me and sucking up to hi–
What am I saying?
I just didn't want you to get hurt or hurt other people,
and yet... I made you run away too. I...
Found you!
Here she is.
You are one of the Dollars, aren't you?
No.
Quit playing around. Why didn't you say so earlier then?
If you're not one of the Dollars, then what's your deal?!
Do you want to know what I am?
What? What are you?
What have we been dealing with?
Oh, I know. You're an ally of justice, are you?
I would have liked to show you what happened to the people who tempted you into trying to defend the peace!
We beat the living crap out of them.
What I did was...
And, seeing that you're here alone and unhurt...
How annoying! All this ring, ring, ringing is getting on my nerves!
What makes you think I can read that much?!
What the hell! Why are you telling me about little girls and rabbits?!
Shut up!
Found the girl. She's okay. That's one matter settled.
And that's because...
"And that's because..."
And that's because the Ikebukuro Fortissimo showed up!
Thank you for saving me again.
Who are you again?
I've turned my phone off for the day, so... See ya.
Celty-san...
Mission accomplished!
Long live the Dollars!
We did it! We did it!
That's why we're the Dollars!
When we all put our heads together,
nothing is ever scary!
Thanks, everybody.
They found her.
Now the most important thing is...
Mikado...
Well then. That's game and set!
Shizu-chan always shows up at the good parts.
Still, it's not over yet.
Pretty soon, I'll be able to perform a checkmate and an ote at the same time.
Celty, there it is, there it is! Grab that mushroom.
Celty, you'll never get it that way. Never.
Come on, haven't I told you to be careful at that spot?
No way!
Celty.
I-I'm sorry.
You were fast asleep, so we didn't wake you.
S-Sorry to trouble you...
It's not a bother at all. It's better for you to be here, in fact.
It's dangerous to live by yourself.
Are you sure?
If there's anything you need, I'll get it for you.
Thank you very much.
You should skip school today too!
I already contacted Mikado to let him know.
You know Ryugamine-kun?
Yeah. I do.
I...
You needn't worry about a thing, Anri-chan.
It's all right! I'm your friend, and this shady looking guy in white is trustwor–
...is on our side.
Hey, what's up?
Why did you start writing "trustworthy" and then change it?
Why? Hey!
Celty? Hey!
However, I'm quite surprised.
About what?
Well, I didn't think Celty-san would be living with a man.
The Shogun hasn't showed up since then, has he?
Who cares? We know what we gotta do.
All of us standing here knows exactly what we gotta do, right?
We gotta crush every last one of the Dollars from here on out!
I'm calling the police!
Where are you right now?
They're fighting again. Those yellow guys.
There sure are a lot of them.
They beat him down and then some... My friend said he saw them.
We can't lose. Let's all work together, just like before.
What are you thinking about right now?
The Dollars are disappearing.
What do you mean?
What? It's the founder.
Are you going to run away, leader?
You don't mean... we're disbanding?
21:34.
Ikebukuro Dollars announce their dissolution?
No! Disappearing is being colorless and clear.
In other words, being the Dollars.
What an irresponsible leader.
You're wrong! We should trust him!
Say something!
Explain yourself!
The Dollars are going away.
How terrible.
I can't access it anymore.
Seriously?
The home page is still there.
However, the forum is completely closed.
Hey, what does this mean?
In other words, he was serious.
Whatever. Let it be.
I spent a long time alone, and I had lots and lots of time to think.
When I did, two faces would come into my mind...
Two smiling faces would come to mind,
and not go away.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Of course. There's something I'd like to talk to you about, as well.
I just feel like I can tell you everything, Celty,
because you know me so well.
I see.
I know what you mean.
Then the two guys you always hang around don't know your true identity.
I've always been the one who is saved.
By Kida-kun, and by Ryugamine-kun. And yet, I...
First, we have to stop this conflict.
Yes.
We have no other choice but to talk to Mikado about it.
With Ryugamine-kun?
Anri-chan, how well do you know Mikado?
You don't know, do you?
He's just like you, Anri-chan.
Perhaps he's hiding it from you because he's so close to you and values you so much.
Anyway, you should hear it from Mikado himself.
I'll bring him here.
Don't spout awkward nonsense at her while I'm gone.
Oh, and don't interrogate her or give her any of your weird tests, either.
I got it. Trust me.
Okay, I trust you.
Anri-chan, wait here a bit.
Celty-san.
I don't want to run away anymore.
Let's go. Let's go!
If you have to blame someone, blame Kida Masaomi, the one who ordered us!
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time:
Hitches and Complications
Durarara!!
Why did I freeze up back then?
What am I waiting for?
What am I so afraid of?
Saki, I'm not afraid anymore.
I'm not running away.
Next time: Hitches and Complications