Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well. Do you know
someone among your friends
who likes to make everybody laugh?
Anna told me that her father used to
make her laugh a lot when she was little.
But the father she met after not seeing
him for a long time is completely different.
When something like this happens,
I wonder if there is anything I can do.
I wonder. I wonder.
What is it that you want to do?
Every time I was asked that
I looked up at the blue sky
The answer is only in my heart
I don't easily say the
words that are really important
I start running towards
the place the light points to
There's so much in my heart
that I want to embrace, I could cry
I'll keep painting my way,
I promise, take it someday
Beyond the horizon,
where the white clouds drift
The future is lined up and
it'll always be there by my side
Anna, you're the best!
"Anna's Not So Amazing Father."
It seems your fans are coming
to see you every day, Anna.
Anna, I think you should be a
little more sociable with your fans.
Like this?
Not good?
Unfortunately...
Your fans will cry if they see you like that.
Ouch!
I think I still have a long way to go.
Hey, Anna, why did you join Kaleido Stage?
I know you like to make people laugh.
Because I love Kaleido Stage.
But of course, I love comedy too.
I see.
So, your dream is to make the
audience laugh at Kaleido Stage.
Yep.
Well, if it's your dream, Sora's
already made it come true, right Sora?
What's the matter?
Well...
The stand-up comedian Jack Barron
will be at the Comedy Theater?
What? What?
Is he funny?
I'm not sure.
'Cause I haven't seen him in ten years.
What do you mean "haven't seen him"?
He's my father.
What?
No, stop it, Bacchus! Stop it!
Here, give it back to me!
Ribbit, ribbit!
Wait, Bacchus!
Give Anna's shoe back, ribbit!
The thing I still remember is that he used to
imitate frog or owl sounds to
make me and my friends laugh.
Anna, I need to talk to you.
Who are you?
I'm... To tell you the truth,
I'm an alien from the planet Jaga Imo.
And my name is "Jagaimo" jaga.
If you don't hurry up, you won't have dinner.
We got scolded, jaga.
But, then, one day...
Why, Jack?
Please understand, Julia.
I don't understand.
If I stay like this, I'll be ruined.
Daddy!
See you later!
Please come back soon!
But after that, he never came back.
A talent agent who specialized
in comedians told Dad
that he could get him
cast in a famous TV show.
But... He's never been on TV.
Well, you hear this kind
of story all the time.
Since then, have you seen your father?
No, not even once.
He sends a Christmas card once a while.
His address keeps changing,
so there's been no way for me to contact him.
Oh...
That's why you have been checking
performers at the Comedy Theater.
Because you never know when your
father may perform at the Comedy Theater.
Well... That's sorta the reason.
But I truly love comedy.
Hey, the Comedy Theater is close by! Right?
Well, in that case, we have to go!
When I actually have a chance to meet him,
a part of me wants to, and
another part of me is scared.
We shall accompany you, Your Highness!
What?
Don't! Don't!
Didn't you hear what I said?!
Don't put your hand in my back!
What the hell are you doing?!
Take your hand out of my back!
Anna's father...
--I wonder if he'll notice Anna.
--Hm? Did you say something?
--I'm hard of hearing nowadays.
--Since he hasn't seen her for ten years,
--The thing getting harder
is not your hearing.
--I'm sure he'll be surprised.
Isn't it also getting harder
to go back home to your wife?
Thank you, thank you.
Hey, you thank them too!
Thank you very much.
Hey, that's my voice!
Next up is a man who missed
taking the world by storm.
Jack Barron!
Everyone, please welcome him
with a warm round of applause.
That old man's been using the
same old material for the last 20 years.
All that's changed is that he got
bald and the puppet got dentures.
And the level of the audience went downhill.
What's wrong?
You guys look like you're not having fun.
So you two are dating?
Yes.
The girl you brought here
yesterday was better looking.
What?!
Hey, you, what the hell are you saying?
He's lying. Lying!
But don't worry.
You're skinnier than the
girl he brought here yesterday.
Oh, wait...
That's enough!
Thanks for the beer.
Be careful on the way home.
Anna...
Daddy... Daddy...
Look at that.
The Little Mermaid of Kaleido Stage is here.
What?
Oh... Hello...
The girl who plays the Little Mermaid
looks more like a blowfish in a fashion show.
The Little Mermaid is without
a doubt a dreamlike story.
Is it a story of a blowfish girl
who is trying to be a princess?
This is... my dad?
This is...?
Anna, you're cute!
Come on, Anna, your mom is waiting.
Daddy...
I expect Kaleido Stage to turn
into a seafood restaurant any day now.
Oh, Anna!
Anna, wait a second!
Looks like everyone's in a hurry today.
Is it the basketball finals today?
It seems like there's still a fan of
Jack Barron other than myself out there.
Come to New York with me.
Make your family proud!
Daddy... Where are you going?
Daddy...
Daddy!
He fooled me.
It was great.
A good job, Anna.
I'm glad to see that you're doing fine.
Sorry about yesterday, making you feel bad.
Don't worry.
By the way, what happened
with your father after that?
Well...
I think it's better not to see him anymore.
What! Why?
Jack Barron abandoned my mom
and me, and turned into another man.
I don't think he wants
to see his daughter now.
Anna...
She still has a long way
to go to be a comedian.
Why don't we go there one more time?
Wait!
Sora!
Please wait!
Wait!
Oh... Excuse me!
Please wait!
What did you do to Sora?!
Mr. Policeman. It's not what you think.
Is this revenge for yesterday?
No.
Because you ran away...
You came to see Anna, didn't you?
I just happened to be in the neighborhood.
Anna told me a story about her
father from when she was little.
She told me that he was a nice
father who made her laugh a lot.
"Even though he's an unpopular comedian
who keeps making the audience mad."
Isn't that what she said?
She didn't say that...
There's no point in her
meeting with a father like me.
You must be thirsty from all that running.
Well...
Excuse me,
how long will you be staying in town?
Until tomorrow.
Once I finish the evening
show, I'm leaving town.
What! That soon?
Well, anyway, I was invited onstage because
the owner of the theater felt pity for me.
It says, "Once again, a silly
person somewhere around here
is poking her nose into
something she should not."
Liar.
I remember this card meant
something better than that.
It seems like you've become a little wiser.
This is the reversed position of The Moon.
It means that one will
acknowledge his faults,
and remove a misunderstanding.
And he can correct his course and
point himself in the right direction.
It is a card for hope.
Okay.
I'll do my best so that Anna and
her dad can meet one more time.
Your father told me that tomorrow
night's show will be the last one.
Oh, no!
What?
It shrunk...
Hey, Anna,
why don't you go see your father after all?
Well, maybe, I should...
What?
I should have eggs
sunny-side-up for breakfast.
Hey,
your father said he'll be waiting
at the restaurant near the pier.
Anna...
Sora, her father is the talk of the cast.
What?!
Don't you think it'd be better
to just quietly keep an eye on how
everything turns out once in a while?
Welcome!
Mr. Barron...
Oh... Well...
I know you took the time to come here, but...
I already know.
Of course she doesn't want to see me.
Oh no.
It's my fault.
If I hadn't poked my nose into her business,
Anna might have come to see you on her own.
Anna is lucky,
having a nice friend like you.
Well... I don't know if I could
say I'm doing this for Anna.
I...
I lost my parents in a car
accident when I was young.
What?!
I thought... Since Anna
can still see her father,
she should meet him and talk
about many things like she used to do.
So...
I'm doing this not for Anna, but for myself.
Sorry... I...
Oh... What's wrong with me?
Hey, Little Mermaid, snap out of it.
Tears don't suit you.
When Anna cried,
this always cheered her up.
Please bring a large serving of chocolate
chip ice cream to this little mermaid!
Hello.
Oh... Mom?
Anna? Are you doing all right?
Yes. How about you?
Just wondering what I should do
with the window that Bacchus just broke.
What's wrong?
Something happened?
I met Dad.
What! Jack?
Yes. At the Comedy Theater in Cape Mary.
Comedy Theater...
Do you know the place?
Of course!
I met your dad at that
Comedy Theater a long time ago.
What?!
One day, an inexperienced new comedian
showed up to meet the owner, Bob.
From that evening, Jack appeared
on stage at the Comedy Theater.
He was warmhearted and funny.
And he had an original personal technique.
He became very popular
at the theater in no time.
Before I knew it, I was
also a big fan of Jack Barron.
But he's different now.
When a guy makes the audience
mad and gets a kick out of it,
I don't call him a comedian.
That is the worst!
Did you tell Jack?
What?
How you feel.
If what you said is true,
the only person who can save
the current Jack Barron is you.
Please give my best regards to Jack.
Thank you. Thank you.
Next up is Jack Barron, whose
performance here tonight will be his last.
Do your best, Jack boy.
So Anna didn't come after all.
They will have another chance to meet.
Yes.
Huh!
So, the audience is still here.
Well, it's true that you can't see
this kind of stupid ventriloquism on TV.
Hm?
You're wearing nice looking glasses.
As a matter of fact, I have some too.
Oh, this is the best.
When I wear this, I don't need
to see that girl's same old face.
Hey, what are you saying?!
Oh... This again...
Look, look, look...
You're chilling the audience.
What the hell are you doing?
Anna?!
Anna?
This is a surprise.
You and your mom are exactly alike.
Well, of course, your mom
was 30% prettier than you.
If you're such a comedian, why
don't you make the audience laugh,
Jack Barron?
Or, are you just a Junk Baron now?
Junk Baron Jack Barron.
That is a perfect stage name for me.
Didn't you say you would
make it big in New York?
Then what are you doing in
this shabby comedy house?
Ten years ago...
The agent who scouted me
said that he would help
me debut all over the U.S.
He was a very talented man.
Jack Barron abandoned his
family and followed that guy.
Thanks to that agent,
I ended up going around to all of the
comedy theaters in New York every day...
trying to find a job.
What?
What happened to that talented agent?
He was drinking every night...
with my money.
What?
I was rejected by all the
comedy theaters in New York.
In the end, I was even rejected at a
dairy shop on the New Jersey state line.
So, it was like the NYC
Marathon out of season.
A month passed by, and when
I came back to the cheap New York hotel,
the agent, my money and
my luggage were all gone.
Seems like he was more
talented in that kind of area.
Then you should have come back home!
What the hell were you doing for ten years?
I lost my hat.
I kept looking for that hat...
in back alleys and underpasses.
I also used to search in the
trash bins at the posh hotels.
Ironically,
I realized,
when I finally came back to the
stage after so many years away...
Daddy!
The one I want to make laugh...
The one I want to make
laugh one more time is...
Then, why don't you make
me laugh like you used to...
You're a comedian, aren't you?
Make your darling daughter laugh, Jack.
Mr. Jack!
Remember this?
Anna, you're cute.
Anna...
Please, Anna.
If you cry with this,
I won't know what to do.
Anna...
Daddy...
Don't you want to be my partner, Anna?
What?
My current dream is right here, so...
I see...
Where are you going now?
I'm heading to a comedy theater in
St. Louis that Bob recommended me to.
I'll revive Jack Barron one more time.
Then, so long.
Oh, Daddy!
Good luck, Daddy.
Mom said hello.
Okay. Then I'll be going now.
My father is Jack Barron.
The Jack Barron I've
loved since I was little.
When you're lonely, what do you do?
Never say you don't get any of that
Sleep, play, flip through a magazine
When you're lonely, you're lonely
Like always, invisible vibes fly
around the city today, tulututu
Anyway, the vector of my heart
is talking about so many reasons
I want to be free and fly the skies
But I don't have space to spread my wings
But I have faith
There is a future yet to be shaped
And there's a me that I want to shape
Even if I'm sad, even if it's a mistake
I'll do what I want and
fly towards the freedom
"Next Kaleido Star"
Why am I so concerned about that girl?
And so, once again, another ordeal.
This time it's ropewalking?!
Moreover, underneath the
rope is a sea of fire.
This is a big chance, with an opportunity
to co-star with Miss Layla on the line.
I'll make sure I will do it
successfully. I will. I will!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"A Hot, Amazing, New Production."
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...