Finally! The day of showing my
drawings that were reborn has come!
Finally the outcome of the show done
with Nido-san is going to be shown.
What about your self-confidence?
Of course I have it! So much!
Even if Nido-san puts
out a really good book?
Of course.
I don't think that's
going to be good for me.
Even if Hoshi-kun
doesn't buy it from you?
That's going to
set me back pretty far.
I'll be cheering you on.
You demon!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
I still can't get used
to this full train ride.
This is still the real thrill.
I'm sorry. Are you okay...
Nido-san?
Najimi-san?
Oh, Tsuyuri-san, good morning!
Good morning. I'm looking
forward to you two's battle.
It's not a battle.
I'm just going to be
selling at my own pace.
M-Me too!
Oh, I thought you stepped on
her foot because the battle started.
I wouldn't do such a cheap thing!
I-I don't really care
about such a thing.
I said it wasn't on purpose!
Please, Najimi-san.
No, thank you.
Go ahead, Nido-san.
Oh, well, I should
sell out at lunch time, and...
...I'll be able to sit down because
it will be a time when it's not crowded.
I'm young, so I'll be fine.
8th Edition
You can see everything!
Over there!
Oh, you were late, Nido-san.
Same to you, Najimi-san.
I thought you weren't participating today.
Um, excuse me.
Please don't run
within the exhibition hall.
I-I'm sorry...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Justice, we sold half of it!
Huh?
Justice?
Oh, I'm sorry, Sora.
I was just thinking of something.
Is there something
that's bothering you?
Could you tell me?
Yeah, it's about Najimi's new book.
She let you see it?
Yeah, but...
How is it? You're so astonished
you can't even say anything.
No, this is...
We don't have words
because we are fed up.
The angle of this character's
face is always the same.
On top of that,
you didn't draw any bodies at all.
Wow, you guys both were able
to figure that out right away.
It's harder to pretend
that we don't see it.
This next Comic Festival is the day
of the battle with Nido-san, right?
So I need to make
a book with higher quality.
I get it!
The only way you can draw
is from this angle, so you...
...put it all on the line for this battle.
Yes.
Good idea, right?
Yeah, you'd most likely be able
to fool maybe two or three...
Hooray!
She's fine with two or three people.
That's not good.
Then let's sell it off fast
and go cheer Najimi on.
Gosh, Justice,
you're like Najimi's dad.
Sora...
Justice!
Thank you, Sora!
Thank you very much!
It finally died down a little.
How are you over there?
Q-Quite well!
Finally on the wave!
Just the enthusiasm though...
Oh yeah, if you would like to,
want to read my new book?
Wow, looks like you
have a lot of confidence.
Ah, yeah...
Looks like you worked
really hard on the cover, but...
...the most important
thing is what's inside.
It's good!
One person out of that two
or three was right next to you.
How did you in such a
short amount of time...
I can't believe it.
Accept the truth right in front of you.
Nido-san, don't be fooled!
In this book, all the
faces are the same angle.
But it's still good.
R-Right?
No, no, it means that she can't
draw anything other than that.
I get it! You figured out what
you can draw and you drew!
How smart!
I don't think that's right either, but...
...more like, she didn't
draw any bodies in this book.
Meaning it's an erotic manga, but...
...it's not erotic.
So don't worry. You still
can't figure out the outcome.
Reverse Upper Classmen Homerun
S-So what about your new book?
May I look?
That's...
No, no! Tsuyuri-san said I should
do one for the female audience...
So it doesn't mean that
I like that kind of stuff.
When I started drawing, you could
say that the pen just kept on going...
I guess...
Tsuyuri, did you look at this?
It's the first time
I've seen the printed...
No, of course I still
think I'm really bad.
But I think it's drawn more
erotically than Najimi-san's.
Yeah, it is erotic.
R-Really?
Yes, it's too erotic
to the point it won't sell.
Don't you think
that's a little too much?
Well, like here, you forgot
to put the mosaic over it...
Due to certain circumstances,
there are no sales of new books.
Well, it's better than
finding out after you sold them...
Right?
Nido-san, I fixed
everything with a marker.
So now you can sell it!
Tsuyuri-san!
The battle is back
at the starting point!
Y-You're right...
It's been fixed, so it's all good now!
It was perverted
beyond my imagination.
You are seriously
such a perverted girl.
What are you doing?
H-Hello, Najimi-san.
Tsuyuri-san and Kaneru-san
are also here, huh?
What, you're acquaintances?
Thank you for the other day.
What about Justice-san's new book?
No...
I didn't buy it...
That's bad!
You have to go to
the person you like first!
Yes, that's why I'm here...
Oh yeah, even if he doesn't buy it,
he can get it straight from Justice-san.
Maybe I was being a little too nosey?
Hoshi-san, here.
I think my book is a
genre that you would like.
Okay...
You like it, right?
R-Regardless of if I like it or not...
...it's very well-made.
You worked hard on it.
Please sell me a copy.
Hooray! Thank you very much!
What?
Ah, no, Hoshi-kun is my fan...
Here's the new book.
Yes.
What? It's so well-drawn!
I'm looking forward to the inside too!
If you want, you want
to buy like three copies?
What happened with this?
It's good, right? I worked hard!
Usually, even though you are
inexperienced, you work hard...
Huh?
It's just like you are
totally scared of failing with this...
The manga that I like of yours is...
...not like this!
Hoshi-kun...
Really...
He actually liked Najimi's manga.
He's Najimi-san's fan,
but he only bought my book.
I was right. For people that know,
they know which book is better!
May I get a copy?
Thank you very much!
Oh, can I get a copy too?
How much is it?
May I have a copy?
Please give me one too!
Thank you very much!
Me too!
Najimi...
Um, how's it going?
Did you sell any?
I sold five copies!
Yeah!
How great! Congratulations.
Amazing!
Keep it up just like this next time.
Y-Yeah!
Cheer up. Even if it was
just one copy, you sold it.
On top of that, who cares
about winning or losing?
But that one copy I sold was
a copy bought by your fan.
Shouldn't it have the value of
five copies or more with just one copy?
One copy is one copy.
Just accept the fact that you lost!
Hey, you were the one that said
winning or losing doesn't matter...
Kaneru-chan.
Najimi.
How about the victory?
Well, to tell you the truth, it hurt that
my only fan didn't buy from me, but...
I thought I should
create something better.
Really...
What?
I was thinking what
happened to making money?
Of course that is the
number one priority!
I meant something good for money!
Is that so?
That's right!
Father, Mother, I will not be
hooked on dojin activities or anything!
I'll make it feel better for you.
What are you talking about!
Najimi, you can see everything...
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Next episode, bathing suits, after-bath...
We will have a lot of that stocked
and will be waiting for everyone.
9th Edition
There's a slip up too! Dojin meeting!