My job's going well!
And the concept for my next manga is perfect!
And now, finally, my second doujinshi event!
Haaah...  But for some reason, I'm feeling a bit unsatisfied.
Unsatisfied?
Yeah, I wonder what's missing?  Passion?  Tension?
Hmm...  Then, how about getting a rival?
That's it!
No matter what manga it is, the protagonist gets fired up by the appearance of a rival!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
oshitari? hiitari?
Pushing? Pulling?
sakusen!! doushiyou?!
Which strategy should I use?
oh! what a night! tomaranai
Oh, what a night! Don't let it end,
risou to mousou bousou BATORU
This out of control battle of dream and delusion
mekuru meku sekai jinsei kore deai
This amazing world!  For life to encounter this..
ikenai? demo mitai nee motto motto
I shouldn't, but I want to see!  It'll make me more and
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
More and more and more and more and
shichaundeshou?
More excited, won’t it?
iijan iijan iijan iijan isshoumon no yuujou
It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! Lifelong friendship!
HIIROO mitai ja nai kedo guttokichaimasu
He doesn't look like a hero, but he'll come running to
kimi boku dare? sore are kare dare de mo OK! donna basho de mo
You, Me, Who? This, that, him, whoever, OK! Wherever we are!
minna to ireba saikou no hoshi nan desu
If we’re together it’s the best planet ever!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
What's wrong?
Why are you asking me?
You've been looking like a wrung-out boxer for a while.
Wrung out, huh?
In a way, that might be true.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
It's not good to keep things bottled up.
I'm not exactly bottling anything up.
I'm just a little tired.
I'll be fine, sorry for making you worry.
I see.
Will you listen?
So you wanted to tell me, didn't you.
Like I usually do, I went to go buy doujinshi...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Those guys!
Thanks for doing this.
Its okay!
Najimi and Hoshi-kun?
Where are they...
After a while, they ended up at...
A-A hotel district?
Don't tell me!
My Najimi is...
That loose?
Wouldn't it be good to ask the actual person?
No, even if you dared me to do so.
Najimi is an adult and can decide everything for herself.
That's right.  She's a mature woman, after all.
B-But then again, whether to ask or whether to play dumb, that's the problem.
I guess you're an adult who can't decide anything for himself.
But wouldn't I be disrespecting her, violating her privacy like that?
The point is, you don't have the courage to ask.
No, wait...
I just haven't decided yet.
I guess it's stupid to get all flustered.
True.
After all, there's many things you can do at a hotel.
For example, this, or that, or this kind of thing, or that kind of...
Wow, you really saved me.
Honestly, I was wondering whether I'd be able to finish this by myself.
There's no need for thanks.
I just thought it'd be more fun to do it together.
That's right, two people doing it together is more fun than doing it alone, right?
Hey!
Though when three people do it, it starts to get a little abnormal.
I wonder, could you be quiet for a bit?
What are you talking about?
It's too soon for kids like you to know.
Ask her.
Huh? What is it?
Ah-I-Uh...
What should I...
That panel, it'd be better if you showed more of it.
Ah, thank you!
Huh, so they're going to a hotel in this scene?
Y-Yeah.
You pervert, Najimi!
It's too soon for kids like you to know.
Right, Justice?
You pervert, Najimi!
What was that about?
Who knows?
That Hoshi guy, acting so improperly towards Najimi.
I need to beat some sense into him, somehow!
That's it! Manga!
Manga will make him see!
Right, the theme will be the sinfulness of promiscuity, the greatness of pure love.
The story of the fall and rehabilitation of a young man steeped in sin.
Under these circumstances, I'll draw as much as needed no matter how many hundreds of pages it takes!
Well, what was the real place like?
Though there's a hotel in this scene,
I've never been to one so I didn't know what they were like.
So the picture gave off a hospital-ish vibe.
So the two of you went to do some research.
A hotel?
Did you take a trip somewhere?
See, they wouldn't let me in alone.
Why, why?
So you tried going by yourself as well.
Besides, inviting Justice to come with me felt like a bother.
I mean, it felt like he really misunderstood before.
Actually, he's still under the wrong impression now.
Still, I'm a little suspicious of Hoshi-kun.
It's fine!
I'll say this ahead of time, there's nothing like that going on.
I'll swear on it, even.
Got it.
After all, it's unimaginable that you would do something like that, Najimi.
Anything like what?
Well, go on and show me the fruits of your research.
After all, there's not long to go before the event.
Yeah!
Anything like what?!
This is...
Oh, Najimi.
Ah, Justice!
How are you doing?  Will you make it?
I think so.
Najimi!
Najimi-chan belongs to me!  I'll love her to pieces!
You bastard!
Justice! HELP ME!
Najimi!
NAJIMI!
A dream?  Damn, I fell asleep.
I guess it's to be expected, seeing as I haven't slept in a while.
We came to hel-
Oh, Najimi, you're okay.
No...
What about you, are you okay?
Is there something on today?
We came to help because
You called us last night, and said that you wouldn't be able to finish,
Even though you weren't getting any sleep!
Oh, that's right.  Sorry.
Wait, are you really okay?
Also, Sora's here too.
I wanted to see you, Justice!
Sora...
Now get some rest already!
But I've got to complete this masterpiece in order to rehabilitate a certain person!
What kind of nonsense are you spouting?
This is amazing.
How many pages is it going to be?
500 pages.
What an idiot.
The three of us will do as much as we can,
So why not sleep for a bit?
It'll be fine,
I've gotten a bit better at this!
I'll help too!
Okay.
So, as you said,
Just for a little...
All right! Let's do our best!
Hang on, Najimi.
Haven't you inked a bit too much?
Huh, really?
Oh, this part wasn't supposed to be inked.
Well, white-out's for times like these.
Najimi?
You should wait until the ink's dry...
Too late.
It's blurring the ink!
Don't mind, don't mind!
I should be able to just use some tissues and...
I went and spread it out further!
There's no way to fix this.
Don't worry, that's more than enough.  Thank you.
This'll do.
Oh, finally found it.
I look forward to... huh?
Same here, I look forward to working with-
Feels like she's less skilled than I am!
Here's a copy of my new book, if you'd like.
Ah, here's mine!
Did she just laugh?
No, it's just my imagination.
Was she just being polite?
With this kind of quality, there's no way she'd be laughing at other people.
Please do your best today!
What's with that composure?
I wonder why she's supporting me?
Don't tell me.
She's thinking I'm...
Less skilled than her?
The Comic Festival will now commence!
Yeah!
Um...Najimi-san's booth was...
Is all of this doujinshi?  Amazing.
Geez...
Even though running's prohibited on the show floor.
Hey, Sora.
Oh, sorry. I've got a lot of packages this time around.
I see!
Oh yeah, I heard about Najimi from Tsuyu-rin!
Tsuyu-rin?
Apparently those two were taking photos at the hotel!
What a troubled man...
Geez.
I think he hung up.
Geez, Justice is acting like he's her dad!  Worrying so much...
Sora,  you didn't give enough information.
If you don't make it clear that they were just taking photos of the hotel room...
Well, whatever.  This will be fun to watch.
W-Why did I run away?
There's no longer any reason to, is there?
I always believed you'd show up, Hoshi-kun.
H-He's going to kill me.
We've sold out!
Well, I guess this is what the mornings are like.
Yeah, this is how it usually goes.
Ahh...  I couldn't even sell one.
There's no way she'd be able to sell with quality like that.
If I can sell more than her, it'll mean that I'm better than her!
Maybe this battle...
Will be decided...
By the sale of a single copy!
And so, couples are born!
fushigi itsu no ma ni ka
It's strange
hajime no ippo fumidaseba
Before I noticed
maru de yosou gai de
After taking the first step, despite my predictions
iya mo iya mo suki ni naru
It might be icky, but I'm starting to like it,
hontou no watashi ga mezamechatta!?
Has the real me woken up?
mufufu miryoku kamo ne
Hah ha ha! It might be charming,
jinsei kake masshigura
To live life fast and free.
sora wa PINKU iro de
The sky has turned pink,
BURUMA mo BYUtto tonde iku
Even bloomers fly through the air,
mitaiken na ERIA saa susumou!!
An area I haven't experienced! Now, forward!
yume miru otome wa SUI SUI CHAO!
Girls who dream can do anything smoothly,
kewashii michi mo hiraoyogi
Swim through even the hardest path,
mizutamamoyou no ashita ni naare
Get used to a polka dot future,
dakara ganbaccha Oh!
So then, let's give it our all!
Busier than a summer festival,
More nudity on display than the beach.
If you think about it that way, doujin events are pretty good, aren't they?