And so,
in the Roman Republic, the landholding aristocracy held the major government offices,
creating a clear class division between the Patricians, or aristocrats, and the Plebians, or commoners and farmers.
This is boring.
The two consuls or the dictator and 300
senators were chosen from the aristocracy.
The Senate was the highest legislative and advisory body.
A senator's term of office was—
Is that coming from 1-A?
Omichi-sensei?
Probably.
Yeah, that's definitely 1-A.
What's going on there?
Who knows? I'll bet Omichi's lost it again.
Is that Chitanda?
Alright, alright, let's carry on then.
Where was I again?
Was I at the Senate?
The Senate was Rome's highest legislative and advisory body...
taikutsu na madobe ni
Sitting bored by the back window,
fukikomu kaze ni
A breeze blew through the room
kao wo shikameta no wa
The reason I screwed up my eyes
terekusasa no uragaeshi
Was to hide how embarrassed I was
Mazui Presents
Hyouka
aimai ni unazuku tenohira no kyou
I gave a faint nod from the edge of my palm
egaiteru jibun wa sukoshi oogesa de
The "me" I was trying to be was a bit more than I was
nani ka kawarisou na ki ga shiteiru yo
I get the feeling that something is going to change soon
kokoro ni yobikakeru kimi no sei da ne
You reached out to touch my heart; it must be because of you
kumorizora nozoita yokan
I had a feeling, looking into the clouds
te wo nobasou itsu yori mo chikaradzuyoi yuuki de
I reached out my hand, with a stronger courage than I'd ever had
hikari mo kage mo mada tookute
The light and the dark are still so far away
sore demo bokura wa
But even though they are
yasashisa no riyuu ga shiritai
We still want to know how people could be so kind
ima wa dare no namae demo nai
Now it doesn't matter whose name it may be
kagayaki no kanata he
Beyond the horizon's light,
zenbu kako ni naru mae ni
Before it all becomes the past,
mitsuke ni ikou
Let's go and find out
A Deadly Sin
You're the one who said you were going to do it!
Please calm down, Mayaka-san...
Quiet, Chii-chan.
Maybe you have a reason, but that's besides the point!
Oh right, Mayaka-san!
You could have at least called me or something!
Would you like some cookies?
This could have been avoided if you had just contacted me!
I know you had your cell phone with you!
I know! How about I go get some milk?
It'd be fine if it were just a hassle for me, but it's not!
What's with that look?
Listen to me!
Do you understand your position here?
Chitanda Eru doesn't know when to quit.
This won't be fixed just by saying sorry to me.
And I know you're aware of it,
but you don't have a shred of decency when it matters.
Don't even bother.
You didn't say anything, even though you knew what would happen.
After that, it rained, it was windy, there was lightning, and even hail fell in the end!
I spent time picking what to wear, and all of a sudden they're a wreck!
And it's all your fault!
Aren't you tired yet?
I am.
Then take a break.
Fine.
I wasn't out to help you!
You sure can get mad.
I'll bet you let out a lot of stress there.
If you had more common decency, I
wouldn't get stressed in the first place.
Maybe you should take a lesson from Chitanda-san.
I've never even seen her get angry.
But if you're going to say that, I've never seen you or Oreki-san get angry, either...
Fuku-chan totally gets angry.
He really does.
Do you?
I guess.
I don't display it as obviously as Mayaka, but I do every now and then.
I find that hard to imagine...
Well, I am only human. Of course I get angry.
You just don't show your emotions in front of others.
I see.
Though it's nothing special when you get angry.
Nothing special?
You really do look down on me...
I'm actually a bit curious now...
I can imagine Chitanda planning something to get him riled up.
That could be fun.
Do you get angry, Oreki-san?
There's no way he'd get angry.
Because he's easy going?
No, because he's a sad excuse of a human who can't even get angry.
Hey! That's just mean!
Hey look, I got angry!
Houtarou's lack of emotions aside,
I think Chitanda never getting angry is a special case.
You should try to emulate some of that calmness of hers.
It's not like I can change that part of me just by trying.
I can't be like Chii-chan.
Um... that doesn't sound like a compliment...
I think it might be, actually.
We're just making observations.
They're not inherently good or bad.
People who are unable to get angry are a different story,
but I think it's an excellent trait not to get angry.
Wrath is a serious sin, after all.
I think you should scale back on your outbursts, Mayaka.
Sin?
The seven deadly sins, right?
Yep. I figured you'd know, Chitanda-san.
I'm sure you've heard of them too, right?
Yeah, I know of them.
Wait, aren't there 108 sins?
That's Buddhism.
Whatever.
Let's see...
Wrath, pride, gluttony, greed...
Envy, lust, and sloth, right?
Ah, right!
Sloth, huh?
Why are you looking at me?
I guess that makes you perfect, Chii-chan.
You're diligent, and you don't overeat.
Well...
I can't imagine you being greedy, and you're definitely not lazy.
Um...
And you're not into... dirty things.
Yes, but...
It's hard to tell if she's envious of anyone, though.
Those two aren't even complimenting her anymore...
They're just teasing her.
Let's stop this!
Besides, when I get hungry I can eat a lot!
She doesn't seem the envious type, either.
So would anyone.
We should just call her Saint Eru.
Doesn't "Chitanda Eru" sound kind of angelic?
Uriel, Gabriel, Chitandael?
Please stop it!
She got angry.
She told us off, too.
Sorry, Chii-chan.
Whatever!
Look, now you made her mad.
You were totally playing along, too.
I don't think it's good thing to never get angry.
It's the same for the other deadly sins, right?
I think pride and greed are also important.
How?
If you can never feel pride, then that means you have no self confidence.
And someone who never feels greed wouldn't be able to support their family.
New technologies would never have been invented if people never felt envy.
Um... I didn't mean to turn this into a lecture...
I see. Interesting...
So you're saying that it's a matter of degree?
I don't think it's useful to just take the deadly sins as absolute and apply that to our lives.
So you don't think it's necessarily bad to get angry?
That's right.
If you can never get angry at anything, that probably means you have nothing that you like, either.
I do get angry. Yep.
But if that's the case, why don't you ever get angry?
Because it tires me out.
And I like to avoid getting tired.
Chitanda-san's been poisoned by Houtarou!
This is bad!
There's a ghost haunting Kamiyama High!
The ghost of energy saving!
Wake up, Chii-chan!
Chii-chan!
These guys sure run their mouths...
I'm just joking!
It was a joke.
A joke, huh?
And here I thought I'd found a soul mate.
Sorry, I was just playing around.
Of course I can get angry. And I do.
Like, for example...
I get angry when people waste food.
Each grain of rice is a drop of sweat.
That's a farmer's daughter for you.
That reminds me...
On that topic, wasn't it you who got angry in Omichi's class during fifth period?
That's right!
How could I forget?
I was hoping I could ask you about that!
Crap.
I'm curious!
I'm curious! I'm curious!
I'm curious! I'm curious! I'm curious!
I think I'll go home now.
I was hoping I could ask you about that!
Did something happen?
Yes. During fifth period in math class, I got angry.
You got angry?
But I don't know what happened to make me angry.
There was no need for me to suddenly get angry,
but something happened to make me angry,
but I don't know what it was that happened.
Say what?
I said, I'm not sure what...
Either ways, I'm curious!
Shousho
When the air of Taisho has not yet come.
Hyouka
Fifth period today was math class.
Omichi-sensei is our teacher for that.
I'm sure you already know what kind of teacher he is.
Anyway, let me explain from the beginning.
Let's see...
He arrived pretty much just as the bell chimed.
Right before he entered the classroom, he stopped for a moment and looked at the class name plate.
Everything up until that point was fairly normal.
He started off by writing down a quadratic equation on the blackboard.
The equation was simple, but he included a restriction on the domain of x.
Domain
And then he singled out Kawasaki-san and told him to draw the range of Y.
Kawasaki-san looked obviously confused.
Ah, that's right.
We hadn't learned anything about domain restrictions yet.
Kawasaki-san said he didn't know how to.
But then Omichi-sensei got mad and began to berate us.
He told Tamura-san, who's quite skilled at math, to answer next.
But he couldn't answer it either.
At this point I realized that he had mistaken how far we'd gotten in the textbook.
Others in the class began to realize too, and it started to get rowdy.
Then the teacher got even angrier and yelled at us.
Ah, yes.
He was striking the blackboard as he reprimanded us.
I think there were people in the class who could have solved it, but we had all gone silent.
Omichi-sensei once again singled out Tamura-san and yelled at him.
That's when I stood up.
I asked him to double-check where we were supposed to be in the textbook.
Ah yes, that's when I got angry.
What happened after that?
After he took a look, he muttered "Oh, right," and then apologized.
He told Tamura-san to sit down again, and then class resumed as normal.
So that's how Omichi is?
Seriously. I went through a lot of trouble after the midterms because of him.
We had teachers like him in elementary and middle school too.
It's not like he's a bad teacher or anything.
And you can't blame him for failing your tests.
You'd better make it up at the end of term.
Yeah...
So anyway, what do you think?
Was there something strange about that story?
What I wanted to ask you was,
why did he make that mistake in the first place?
He's not the type to do that...
That's true.
Omichi is pretty strict, but that's because he's strict on himself too.
So then why did he make that mistake?
That's what I don't get.
I don't get it either.
Oreki-san!
No idea.
Go look inside his head and find out yourself.
This would be simple if I could do that.
Really? Well that's too bad.
Just give up then.
I'm curious!
Please help me figure this out!
Why me?
You can figure it out if you just think about it a little!
Don't give me the "You can do it if you try!" speech.
Chii-chan, you shouldn't expect too much from him.
He was a grasshopper in his previous life.
Mayaka-san, you can see people's former incarnations?
Nice diversion, Ibara!
But right now I'm curious about our teacher.
Damn, she's persistent.
I'm curious!
After class, Omichi-sensei always writes a note in his textbook.
Do you know why?
To keep track of how far in the curriculum he went that class?
That's what I think too.
And before entering a class he always checks the name plate.
It seems like he's got all his bases covered, so where did his mistake come from?
I'm guessing his memos are like "July 1st, class A" on page 15 or something.
It has to contain at least that much in order to know how far he's gone.
Maybe he got the date wrong?
That might have made him backtrack, but it couldn't have caused him to skip ahead.
Use your brain.
I guess that's true...
Mind if I ask something?
Yes, of course.
I can understand why you'd get angry.
But I wouldn't want to talk back to a teacher like that.
So why did you?
I was angry, but not because he was yelling at us.
Then was it because there were people who could have answered but didn't?
No.
I don't think anyone wanted to stick their neck out in that situation.
Then, because other people realized his mistake but didn't say anything?
No...
Because you felt sorry for Tamura, then?
I certainly felt sorry for him, but I don't think I'd get angry over that.
After all, I can understand why he'd yell at students who
didn't seem to remember anything from the previous class.
So what was it that made me angry?
I find myself hard to understand sometimes.
I guess.
I still don't know enough about Chitanda to know what makes her angry or happy.
What do you think, Oreki-san?
I think it's safe to assume that Omichi was writing down the class' progress in his textbook.
Yet he was mistaken.
The fact that he carried on anyway means that the previous
page must have had a note saying he'd already done it.
Your class hadn't been taught domains yet, right?
Yes, that's right.
And what if you had?
What do you mean by that?
Omichi teaches math every year.
At some point, last year's 1-A learned it.
If you're saying he might have mistaken last year's notes, I'm afraid that's impossible.
What do you mean?
The teachers get new textbooks every year.
They need to have the latest revisions to stay consistent with the students, right?
Omichi is using this year's 4th edition.
I see...
You're filled with useless knowledge, as usual.
I'm a database, after all.
There's the possibility that he mixed up the notes he wrote.
But I'm sure Chitanda wouldn't accept that answer.
I really don't get domains, though.
It's already hard enough for me to just draw the x and y axes.
It would be scary to be singled out by Omichi.
Wait a second.
1-D has already learned domains?
Yeah, we have.
Satoshi's class already did domains, but my class and Chitanda's class haven't yet...
I see.
That face tells me you've thought of something.
Maybe.
Chitanda.
Yes!
You're sure that he made a note a page ahead of where you'd gotten to?
Yes, I believe so.
Additionally, the note was written this year, and shows the class' progress.
Yes.
What if the memo he wrote wasn't, in fact, for your class?
What if it was actually Satoshi's class' memo?
My class?
Omichi is in charge of classes A, B, C, and D, right?
Even if it wasn't A or B, that doesn't mean it has to be class D's.
And anyway, why class D?
Because it's quite possible he mixed the two up.
C is clearly nothing like A.
What? Are you an idiot?
A and D aren't anything alike either.
Omichi teaches math.
So what?
A math teacher has a much higher chance of mixing up A and D.
What?
Oreki Houtarou's writing
Let's say he wrote "July 1st, A" on page 10, and "July 1st, D" on page 15.
Yeah, so what?
How could he have mixed those up?
If he had mistaken the D for an A, that would explain what happened.
True, but how?
A math teacher would have written them like this.
Oh! Lower case A and D!
I get it now!
That makes sense...
I lost points on an English test because the teacher couldn't tell the difference in my handwriting.
Oh, you too?
In my case, it was "n" and "h".
Yes, that does seem likely.
Finally cleared that up.
A and D...
I can understand the mistake now.
I may have gone too far in what I said to him.
That was wrong of me.
Why would you say that?
Omichi was in the wrong!
He deserved anything you said to him!
And besides—
Now, now.
It's getting pretty late. We should head home.
But Fuku-chan!
It's fine, Mayaka.
The mystery's solved.
That's not what I mean! Fuku-chan!
The normally calm Chitanda got angry.
And so she wanted to know why.
She said it's not necessarily bad to get angry, but the truth is, she never wants to.
Houtarou, Chitanda-san. We should go.
Perhaps Chitanda wanted Omichi to have had his reasons, and
wanted to believe that she got angry because of her own mistake.
Ah, right. Let me clean up.
Maybe Chitanda Eru is just that kind of person?
No. What do I know about her?
Even if I can predict her actions sometimes, I couldn't hope to understand her heart.
That'd be a deadly sin, just like she was saying.
"Pride".
I'd better watch out.
Even just today, how many times already has Chitanda done or said something unexpected?
Oreki-san?
Aren't you going home?
Ah, yeah...
Oreki-san.
Thank you so much.
It seems all you do is help me out.
Yeah, and it's a hassle.
What are you doing?
Aren't you coming?
Yes, we're coming now.
Let's go.
I guess I'll finish tomorrow.
Oreki-san!
That might be true for you, Mayaka, but just think about it...
And so today, more of my high school life was squandered away.
Personally, I think sloth is more than enough sin for me.
konya koi ni kawaru
Tonight’s the night we fall in love
shiawase na yume de aou
Let’s meet in our sweet dreams
kitto ne mitsukete ne
Please come and find me
madoromi no yakusoku
A promise for when we sleep
mebaeteta nukumori atatakakute tomadou
I felt a growing warmth; it felt so nice that I couldn’t think
konna kimochi wo mada anata wa wakaranai no
But these feelings I have, you still don’t know they’re here
sono shisen ni wa imi nante betsu ni nai hazu
I don’t think there’s anything special in how you look at me
datte tomodachi ni shiteru no to onaji
It’s the same way you look at your friends
akegata ni kieteku chiisana negaiboshi
Fading into the dawn, my tiny wishing star
yoru no aida de no mahou
Magic that lasts only the night
konya koi ni kawaru
Tonight’s the night we fall in love
shiawase na yume de aou
Let’s meet in our sweet dreams
kitto ne mitsukete ne
Please come and find me
madoromi no yakusoku
A promise for when we sleep
Next time: The Ghost, When Examined
The Ghost, When Examined