When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
I'm Nagi Sanzenin, 13 years old.
A Sagittarius with blood type AB.
My birthstone is turquoise.
It's awful! It's awful!
Maria, my precious butler's been
kidnapped by some bad guys!
Waaah!
All right, since it's come to this,
I'll transform into Mask the Money
and I'll smack the bad guys with 150
million yen, duralumin case and all!
I'm the warrior of love,
courage, money, power...
...and also of friendship,
hard work, and victory!
In the name of money, Mask
the Money will punish you!
It will take approximately 40
years to pay that back in full.
Well, given how much it is...
That's what happens when you work
out a reasonable repayment plan.
No interest, no collateral, and
repayment contingent on your success.
No financial institution would
loan you 150 million like that.
You should be grateful. There's
no reason to resent me.
P-Please don't worry. I am grateful.
Your smile is twitching.
Hayate found himself trembling anew
at the overwhelming amount he owed.
Looks like spring is still a long way away.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Looks like spring is still a long way away.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
The Beast, the Robot, and the Butler that Shouted
or Maybe Didn't Shout Love at the Heart of the World
What? There are only 3 people
living on this estate?
Yes. Even among our secondary residences,
this one is particularly small,
so we don't need that many servants.
I see, so this place is small...
But when there are so few people,
it makes me feel even more tense.
How so?
Because, I'm going to be
living here, too, right?
No matter how vast this place is,
the situation of being under
one roof with a cute girl is...
Y-You idiot, don't say it like that!
We may be under one roof, but...
I mean, it's not as if we're
sleeping in the same room.
Well... But still, the
thought makes my heart race.
Makes his heart race?
You know, living together with
a pretty girl like Maria.
What do you mean by that?
I'm warning you,
if you ever lay a hand on Maria,
I'll do far more than just kill you.
Uh... What?
I'll use all 48 killer techniques
and 52 submission holds on you
and I'll turn you into mince
meat with the roller from hell!
What?
Uh, um, what do you mean
by "lay a hand" on her?
Thus, with the end of
the year coming up fast,
my new life began.
I guess it's already New Year's Eve.
This year sure was a terrible year.
My home was utterly cleaned out,
Eviction Notice
not even the table was spared.
And I couldn't muster the urge to
find my parents, who ran out on me,
To Hayate
A Christmas Present For You
so I accepted the Miss's kindness
and decided to work as a butler
at this Sanzenin estate.
The amount I owe is definitely huge,
but I'm just going to work
hard, so I don't get fired!
So, Maria, I have a question...
What should I do?
I still don't have a clear
picture of what my job is.
Let me think...
In a word...
I suppose you're Nagi's pet.
I-I'm her pet?
That was a little joke.
R-Right...
I'm sure you'll gradually come
to understand what your job is,
so for the time being, would
you please go wake up Nagi?
C-Certainly.
Let's keep things neat and tidy.
Floor Layout (2nd Floor)
Let's see. Study, piano room, homework
room, reading room, wardrobe room,
plus a PlayStation room, a Dreamcast
room, and an N64 room...
Is there any point in keeping these separate?
This must be it.
Good morning, Miss.
It's morning!
If you don't get up soon, your
wonderful breakfast will get cold...
Calm down. Calm down, Hayate.
It's impossible. It must be a 1:1 scale
model made by Kaiyodo or something.
No, it's got to be Sony!
It must be Sony's new model of
the AIBO or the PlayStation 5!
Man, Sony's world renowned
technology sure is amazing!
Oh? Hayate?
You came to wake me up? Thank you.
By the way, why are you just standing there?
N-Nothing, just that, behind you...
Oh, no wonder it was hot. So you
were sleeping with me, Tama.
Tama?! He's enormous and
you treat him like a cat?!
Come on, Tama, wake up.
If you don't wake up soon,
your breakfast will be gone.
Oh, don't! Such behavior will result
in you becoming his breakfast!
M-Miss, wait...
No, you idiot!
I just woke up! Don't stare at me so much!
That's not it! That might be what
our older audience is doing,
but that's not the issue right now!
You seem awfully shocked by Tama.
Pitiful! Really! You are truly
pitiful, Hayate Ayasaki!
Where the hell did you come from?!
Uh, um, who is he?
Oh, right, you still hadn't met...
My name is Klaus.
I am the head butler of
the Sanzenin household.
Head butler? In other
words, you're my superior?
Wait, now's not the time!
Miss, you're in danger!
In danger?
What are you saying? It's one measly cat.
No, no, that's...
A tiger. It's a tiger.
Oh, you!
That was my chance to make a pointed
comment after keeping quiet until now!
Listen well, boy.
If the Miss says that it
is a cat, it is a cat.
This is Tama, whose zoological
name is Whitetigerneko!
Wait, you just said it was a tiger!
A gigantic, vicious-looking beast
like this needs to be caged quickly!
It looks like that long-winded
remark has offended Tama.
What?
I'll warn you now.
Tama is a stupid cat, who is only
friendly towards the Miss and Maria!
Anyone who offends this idiot
becomes his victim immediately!
Doesn't that mean that he isn't
friendly towards you, either?
Oh...
Th-That's not true... Right, Tama?
Hey, Tama, enough with the rampage.
Honestly! What a huge commotion
first thing in the morning.
Thank you very much, Miss. You saved me.
Tama, as a cat of the Sanzenin family,
you should keep this in mind.
If you're going to play...
...take it outside!
Wh-Why you! Don't get too carried away!
Cyclamen
Don't think this is my first
time fighting a savage beast.
I may not look it,
but my parents once told me,
"We'll give you meat to eat,"
so I ended up breaking into a safari park
and stealing meat from the
lions on a regular basis!
That's my Hayate for you!
It looks like he can play
with Tama as an equal, too!
We shall see about that.
Think of how many butler candidates
have fallen in defeat before Tama...
Hayate will be able to
win, even against Tama!
Then, if he cannot, I shall
consider him a failure as a butler
and have him leave.
That's fine! You can fire
him or do whatever you want!
WHAT?!
If I can't win barehanded against
a tiger, I'll be out of work?
In the safari park, all I did
was basically run away...
Hayate!
Go for it!
Oh, well. I should've died on
that Christmas Day anyway...
I have to try my best, so
I don't disappoint her!
Here I come!
Pardon, Miss.
Something has been bothering
me for a while now, but...
The area that they are fighting in...
Now, then...
I hope the cyclamens are
flowering beautifully.
Can't show you!
I give up, I give up! I give up, Tama!
Or rather, there's no way a person
can win barehanded against a tiger!
At least, give me a
psychogun or a prog knife!
Can't show you!
Give me a knife!
Tama.
What are you doing?
M-Maria...
Honestly!
I put great care into
raising the flowers here,
so I have repeatedly told
you not to play in here...
Cycla men
Did you do this?
Uh, um...
Or were you egged on by the two upstairs,
saying if Hayate couldn't win against Tama,
he would be fired because he's
not qualified as a butler?
Busted!
I will get to you once I finish
treating Hayate's wounds,
so would you mind waiting a
little while for breakfast?
Y-Yessir.
Sure...
I'm so sorry.
I'll have a stern word with those two later.
N-No, not at all.
But why in the world does
she have a pet tiger?
A lot happened and he has nowhere else to go.
Uh, but there are lots
of places, like zoos...
Yes, well...
I'm embarrassed to say, the truth is...
Nagi took him in when he became
separated from his parents in Africa
and after that, Tama was literally
pampered like a kitten...
Matsuzaka beef, top quality fatty
tuna, massages 3 times a week...
He became so used to luxuries,
it would put humans to shame.
So never mind the wild, he couldn't
even handle life at a zoo.
But he will never harm Nagi
and he would surely risk
his life to fight for Nagi.
He has a very good understanding about that.
He knows what would've happened
if he hadn't met Nagi.
If he hadn't met her...
I see. So I guess you're the same as me.
Don't lump me together with a loser like you!
Moron!
Sheesh! Looking so damn poor!
Go get run over by a Mars rover and die!
Fool!
Also, don't tell the Miss and
the others than I can talk.
I-I see.
Pets belonging to rich folks can talk...
Having grown up surrounded with love,
Tama apparently picked up human
speech somewhere along the way.
But other than Hayate, no
one else knows of this fact.
Devil's tongue noodles.
(Itokonnyaku)
Scoundrel!
(Kusemono)
At any rate, I am against
making this person a butler!
I see.
Is this the mustache that's
making these lame jokes?!
That hurts! My mustache!
Is this the mustache, Klaus?!
That mustache is my pride and joy!
I decided to hire him in
thanks for saving my life.
I believe I promised to select
Himegami's replacement.
There is something messed up about hiring
a poor-looking boy in the first place!
Y-Yes, his face may have the
look of poverty about him,
but it can have a calming effect!
Hayate is the soothing type!
If you wish to be soothed that much,
you should get a hamster or something!
Too bad! A hamster's too soothing!
Hayate's look of poverty is
actually just about right!
This boy looks like he'll never
have money luck in his life!
Hiring him will only bring
misfortune to those around him!
Um, they both do mean well...
I know...
There's no knowing when you
might become the target
of another kidnapping like the other day.
Without the strength to protect his
mistress, even at the cost of his life,
we cannot hire him!
Protect my mistress, even
at the cost of my life...?
Strength, is it? Then there's no problem.
Pardon?
Certainly, Hayate's body is uncommonly tough.
After all, he was able to handle Tama.
That's not all.
I'll have you know, with
every transformation,
Hayate's combat abilities will
increase by leaps and bounds.
And Hayate still has two stages
of transformation left.
You understand what this means?
What?! I have no such functionality!
What?! You don't?!
Really?!
I'm not Frieza. Looking so
troubled isn't going to help...
If you have a problem with Hayate's
strength or qualifications,
why not give him an evaluation test?
Evaluation test?!
Yes, if he is truly capable
of protecting the Miss,
he should even be able to swim across
a pool of boiling hot coal tar.
What?!
Hmm, a butler should definitely be fine,
even if he's dropped from
a height of 2000 meters.
Um, hello?
All right, we accept your challenge!
Wait! Um, what about what I think?
Then please wait a moment.
I shall have the test prepared right away.
Yes! Bring it on! Do you worst!
Augh...
Or rather, I don't know
what I'm being tested on,
but is it going to be okay?
In more ways than one...
It'll be fine!
What?
Knowing you, you'll be
able to manage somehow.
Cyclamen
Um, Maria, could it be the Miss
has high expectations of me?
High... expectations?
She tends to be extremely
shy around strangers
and she doesn't openly show
her emotions very much...
What?
In particular, she's been smiling
less after Himegami left.
So it's been a while since
she was that energetic.
The fact that you saved her
must have really delighted her.
Part of me is definitely
doing it for the money,
but if she's putting her faith in me...
I decided that I wanted to
live up to her expectations.
Now, then, are you prepared for this?
This is the test that will
evaluate how qualified you are!
This is...!
Um, what is this?
Currently being developed by a company
controlled by the Sanzenin family,
this is the caregiver robot "Eight"!
I have been waiting for
you, Mr. Hayate Ayasaki.
Don't tell me you expect
me to fight this thing...?
Don't be so crass.
He is a caregiver robot.
In other words, the ultimate
butler, born to serve his master!
You will use these various
items from daily life
and you and Eight will compete to
see who is the superior butler.
Wait. Miss?
I don't know... This is
an awfully ugly robot.
Grr!
Please!
This is technically the world's
most cutting-edge caregiver robot!
Most cutting-edge?! This thing?!
If an ugly robot like this
was taking care of you,
wouldn't you actually want to die?
Please!
Well, at any rate,
this robot doesn't seem capable
of combining or transforming.
There's no way Hayate would lose. Right?
W-Well...
I-If you want to see combining
or transforming that badly...
...how about I transform you?!
Damn! I missed.
My, my, what a terribly
short-tempered cutting-edge robot.
Wait, this is no time for that!
Please hurry up and shut it down!
Once my ardent pathos is set
in motion, no one can stop me!
You shut up!
Mr. Klaus?
Um, as I recall, to stop it,
you have to open the back panel
and enter the password 1-1-9-2...
Hayate, it'll apparently
stop if you just break it!
H-Hey!
So this is going in that
direction, after all.
Hayate!
That's right! I have to protect the Miss!
For I'm... I'm to be her butler!
I am going to fight in earnest!
Miss, please step over there.
What?! Is this guy really for caregiving?!
Fire!
It must be a feature necessary
for women living alone...
You know, stalkers seem to be a big problem.
That sounds absurdly fishy.
Kid, don't think you can keep
running away from me forever!
Hayate!
That's the water pipe!
I see! Machines are weak against water!
I wonder who's going to clean up this mess...
So what?
The waterproofing on Japanese
robots is the best in the world!
Now's my chance!
Wha?!
Th-These are...!
That's right!
Pure silver knives, which conduct
electricity better than stainless steel!
Furthermore, underfoot is a
wool carpet soaked with water!
And this is 100 volts of pure domestic power!
W-Wait, if you use that
under these circumstances,
you'll be electrocuted, too!
I'm sure.
But...
It's apparently a butler's
duty to protect his mistress,
even if it costs his life.
Hayate...
Act cool all you want. You're going
to be poor for the rest of your life.
Buster Collider!
Wh-What's a Collider?!
Takaya!
And you kids out there,
don't ever do this at home.
He acquitted himself rather
brilliantly, didn't he?
Do you still find Hayate's
abilities dissatisfactory?
Very well.
We can employ him at least
until we find our next butler.
And now, with the tolling
of the New Year's Eve bells,
the new year is finally almost
upon the Japanese archipelago.
Good-bye to the last year.
Hello to the new year.
We hope that the new year
is a good year for everyone.
Ah! You're awake! I was worried!
Miss...
Oh! What happened to the butler test?!
You passed, of course.
Thank goodness...
But I made such a mess of that room...
I am sorry.
It doesn't really matter.
What?
There are plenty of other rooms
that will serve as replacements.
But there is no replacement for you...
Miss...
O-Oh! So, well, you know...
I was happy that you protected me. So, um...
I-I'll continue...
...to count on you, Hayate!
Yes, please leave it to me, Miss.
There are still a lot of problems,
but it seems he should continue
to do well at this estate.
Oh, my!
That day, I swore to myself!
That I would protect this person, the
Miss, even if it cost me my life!
Hey, you there! Are you listening?!
Eh?
That's what you get for going
on and on for 3 whole episodes.
Look! The cherry blossoms
have all scattered already!
What of it?!
Now, let us continue where we left off!
Up we go...
Starting next episode is a new development!
This showdown sequence has been put
off since the start of Episode 1,
but this will finally be the end of it!
Hayate!
New development!
And thus, the boy became a legend...
No, he became a butler.
Next time, he will fight with a giant campus!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
Preview
You're not a Hakuou student, are you?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Just who are you?!
Um, I'm...
Don't lie to me!
But I haven't said anything yet...
Could Hayate have become involved
in something troublesome again...?
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"My First Errand. This
Is Snake. No Response".
Ayasaki, if you don't try to get
what you want once in a while,
you'll miss your chance at happiness.
Have you ever felt the cosmos?!
My First Errand
~This Is Snake. No Response
SIGN: If you don't watch "Hayate the Combat
Butler" again next time, I'll get mad.