I'm relying on numbers!
We got it!
These are The Dollars?!
What is this?
They couldn't all be...
For example, you could marry me.
Are you keeping our secret about "that?"
Celty...
This is much more fun than I thought it'd be.
I'm screaming that, "I've been born right here and now!"
Give Celty back to me!
I guess I have to thank you.
If it weren't for you, my sister would've locked
her away in that cramped research facility again.
Yagiri...
Are you all right?!
Anyway, give Celty back to me.
I have to run away with her somewhere before the police arrive.
That's why you're—
I've watched her since I was a child.
I wanted to set her free...
To let her run free in a wide-open world...
And I'd live there with her.
I've always, always, always, always, always,
always been thinking nothing but those thoughts.
You can't stop the power of love, you know.
In contrast to that, what are you?
You relied only on strength in numbers both then and now.
My love won't fall apart so easily!
It won't work!
I feel pain, but I'll forget it!
There's no need for pain in the life I'll lead with Celty!
That's why I won't feel the pain you're dishing out!
That's ridiculous!
Stop it!
Please, stop!
Seiji is strict, violent, and different from
most people, but he's not a bad person!
And he has someone he likes!
That's not her.
It couldn't be...
That's why...
It couldn't be! It couldn't be! It couldn't be!
That's not her. That girl...
That's...not my head.
That girl...
Her name is...
Harima...Mika?
I'm right, aren't I?
You're Harima Mika, the girl who Seiji supposedly killed, right?
That's a lie.
Right?
He's lying, right?
I'm sorry!
Hey, you're there, aren't you, Seiji?
I'm here again!
Oh my, you forgot to leave the door unlocked again.
I can't come in if you do that.
Could you be sleeping?
Do you remember?
Seiji, I sat next to you during our entrance exams.
Since the person on my right had
the awesome name "Ryugamine Mikado..."
I wondered what kind of name the person to my left had...
And when I glanced over, I fell in love at first sight.
You even smiled when our eyes met, Seiji.
So, please show yourself, Seiji!
Pretty please?
Maybe you're not feeling well?
Is that why you're not opening the door?
Then I'll open it for you. Just wait a bit.
I'll be right there.
I looked into some things after that day.
Like your birthday, and stuff about your family...
Se-Seiji...
So, you've seen it.
Um, err, I, well...
Uhh, I won't tell anybody!
Umm, umm, it's okay!
I'll grow to like what you like,
no matter what hobbies you have!
Um, so don't—
It's okay.
Seiji...
Seiji...?
It's okay.
I'm sorry!
I didn't really die!
Then, your sister...
You want Seiji to like you?
What a good girl.
And...and there was a doctor there, too.
He said with a little cosmetic surgery and some makeup, I'd look just like that head—the head you're in love with!
He said, "You're Celty now, since that's what its name is."
So I tried to be like Celty for your sake!
But Namie said that wasn't enough.
She said you'd figure that out, so they'd use surgery
and medication to make my memory disappear.
But I didn't want to lose my memories!
Someone who knows my name.
A doctor who knows I'm a dullahan.
There's only one person like that in this city!
I just wanted to be with you!
That's why I went through all this!
This has to be a lie.
Then I...
So you couldn't distinguish the impostor from the real thing.
That must mean that's all your love amounted to.
Good work.
Seiji!
Um, I think it's amazing that you
risked your life trying to get her back.
I misunderstood you, Harima.
You've certainly got some personality
problems, but you're definitely not a stalker.
I mean, you put your life on the line for him, which
is something you probably can't do out of selfishness.
The fact that you still love the guy who almost killed you is amazing.
In many different ways.
Harima, I think you're a lot like Yagiri.
Welcome home.
You want to say, "What's the meaning of this," right?
And next, you'd say:
"So, you knew that my head was in that research facility."
"So, both you and your father were colluding with Yagiri Pharmaceuticals."
"Your father was probably the one who stole my head!"
"Yet you hid that from me and cut up a dying girl."
"I may be a monster, but chewing up and
spitting out humans makes you the real monster."
Am I right?
Oh yeah, I'll say this in advance to clear up any misunderstandings.
I neither know nor care whether my
father was the one who stole your head.
And the girl wanted us to perform that minor surgery on her.
Those Yagiri people may have guided her towards that decision.
But that's none of my business.
"Can you understand what I'm thinking?"
Yes, I can.
I've loved you for twenty years.
Of course I'd understand something like this.
Why now...?!
Why'd you keep quiet about the location of my head?!
Because I love you.
That's why I kept quiet about it.
You'd go off somewhere if you found it.
I couldn't bear that.
I won't say I'll give up so you can be happy.
Our love for each other is at stake in this fight.
I won't ever let you go.
To make sure I don't, I'll exploit others' love, their deaths,
myself, and—this may sound contradictory—but even your feelings.
Even if I get my head back, I wouldn't ever think of leaving—
But even if that's what you think, your head might not.
I've been thinking.
Why did a faerie like you appear in front of humans in this world?
Maybe you were able to manifest yourself in this world precisely because you've lost your head.
Then maybe once your head is back in your hands and your
memory returns, you'll fade from this world like a puff of smoke...
...as if everything that happened up until now was an illusion.
I'm afraid of that happening.
Will you believe what I say?
I believe in you.
Conversely, you're the only person I don't distrust.
I'm scared, too.
I'm afraid of dying.
I understand that there's no one here who can kill me.
I'm not boasting.
I accept it as a simple fact.
There's no joy or feeling in my acceptance of it.
But—or maybe because of that—I'm scared.
There's no core inside of me that controls my death.
My head itself is that nucleus.
If someone were to destroy that core...
Then, regardless of my will or situation...
Would you believe...
I have nightmares even though I don't have eyes or a brain?
Would you believe in someone who
trembles in fear at the nightmares she sees?
I've been afraid of that, so I've been
searching for my head in order to control my will.
If I said that, would you believe me?
I said it, didn't I? You're the only one I believe in.
I'm at a complete loss.
We're so stubborn that we never leave the realm of speculation.
We're idiots.
Yep.
Hey, Shinra.
What?
Let me punch you once.
Okay.
Alright, now let me punch you.
See, you're most beautiful when you're honest with yourself.
That punch was a substitute for our wedding kiss.
Right?
Are you crying?
However, that's pretty amazing.
Yo, Izaya.
Oh, Dotachin. Long time no see.
Stop calling me that.
By the way, do you know how The Dollars got its name?
Isn't it from, "Give me your dollars!" or something like that?
No, it's not.
It's because the organization basically doesn't do anything.
They're "The Dollars" because they lounge around going "dara dara."
That's how it is.
Dotachin, did you see that just now?
The black biker—
No way, was that real?
So it wasn't just some illusion...
Maybe it was some CG kind of thing.
That CG thing is in The Dollars, too, you know.
Amazing!
Is that true?
I'm honestly surprised.
I knew lots of people online claim to be in The Dollars.
However, I didn't realize so many people
would come to an impromptu gathering.
Humans truly exceed my expectations.
It seems you have some dream about escaping everyday life,
but life in Tokyo will become routine for you after six months or so.
Moreover, if you want to reach the non-everyday, you'll either have to move somewhere else or get into more "underground" things.
But once you step into that world, it'll only take about three days for that to seem normal, too.
If you truly want to continue escaping from everyday life, you've no other choice but to keep evolving.
No matter whether you're aiming higher or lower.
Enjoy everyday life!
Out of respect for you, I gave you Yagiri Namie's phone number
for free, and I won't tell anyone you're the founder of The Dollars.
It's your organization.
Use it when you want to.
IIIzaaayaaa!
It's apparently time for our meeting to end.
Good luck, Tanaka Taro!
Wait, you bastard!
IIIzaaayaaa!
Eh? No way...
Eh?!
The next day, life returned to being astonishingly normal.
For him...
And him...
As well as the boy...
Hey, Mikado.
I saw on the Net that The Dollars had a get-together!
And apparently, Simon and Shizuo are in The Dollars as well!
Plus, I heard that the black biker has no head,
she drove down a wall,
pulled out a huge scythe,
everyone was like, "Bwaah,"
and it was amazing!
I don't get any of what you're saying.
And for them as well.
I don't love you.
But I can't forget my love for her when I'm looking at you.
So, I'll accept your love for me.
Until I can get her back.
Tanaka Taro has entered the chat room.
Good evening.
Evenin'. I've been waiting.
Thanks.
I'm pretty tired today, so I'll be signing off early.
Oh, so you didn't get much sleep?
Did you pull an all-nighter or something?
Yeah, kind of.
I guess Kanra isn't here yet.
Kanra...
...will come, right?
Uh, something just came up.
Oh, I see.
Sorry, but I've got to go.
See you.
Setton has left the chat room.
Sorry to intrude on your fun.
It's an urgent job.
No problem.
And now, my everyday life is continuing on like it always has.
The fact that I bump into people I
don't want to meet hasn't changed at all.
It seems the whole thing's been dispelled.
Well, ghosts are scary because they always sneak around,
then appear out of nowhere, and you made quite the entrance.
No one will be afraid of you anymore.
Speaking of which, you didn't kill anyone, did you?
What's with that scythe?
Can it even cut?
Are you chasing that girl?
I can help out whenever you need me to.
Call me.
See you later.
I don't know where Yagiri Namie is.
But I don't care.
I am who I am, and there's nothing wrong with that.
The days continue like they always have.
They bring neither excessive desire nor despair.
Nothing's changed.
Yet I'm overwhelmed with a sense of fulfillment.
I'm right here.
You're over there.
If I'm your savior, then you're mine.
And so, the boy contemplated things.
He thought about what Orihara Izaya said.
Could the boy who yearned for an unbelievable
reality continue to seek new ones for all eternity?
And would that eternity end up becoming normal for him?
I'm sorry for everything I did.
Thanks.
Hey, that's my seat!
Oh, it says you're right behind the class rep.
Huh? What's with you?
You just come out of nowhere and sit by Kitakawa...
She would never be able to interact with
Harima Mika the same way ever again.
Whether or not that's a good thing is something only she herself knows.
But, is that true?
Maybe people don't really understand themselves.
All they can do is keep evolving.
That man's words echoed throughout the classroom.
After doing something so bold, he thought he could do anything.
He never thought for a split second...
That it would take so much courage to ask out a girl from his class.
Time remaining until he reaches the girl: thirty seconds.
Time remaining until he finds his friend hitting on the girl: thirty-five seconds.
Time remaining until he delivers a powerful kick to his friend: forty-five seconds.
Time remaining until she turns down his offer of tea: seventy-five seconds.
Time remaining until he invites her to eat lunch with him on the roof: seventy-eight seconds.
Time remaining until he falls in love with her:...
Time remaining until he confesses to her:...
But you did something idiotic, too.
You threw it all away for the sake of your brother's twisted love.
Or should I say, your twisted love for your brother?
Anyway, aren't you in trouble?
There's that merger with Nebula, right?
If word of this were to get out because of that...
The Mafia or a really skilled sniper might
shoot you right between the eyes like, "Bam!"
Checkmate.
A cleaning crew?
Yeah, the way they always pick them up.
Understood.
Hello? Things have gotten a little more complicated.
Can you leave that room right now?
You can't have a double checkmate, can you?
I'm sure your uncle was just like me.
He believed in that world less than anyone, feared death
more than anyone, and revered Heaven more than anyone.
But...
I'm sure of it.
That world does exist.
Let's leave it at that.
They say that all dullahans are female.
Do you know why that is?
No.
One of my subordinates was researching that for a while, but since I deemed it pointless...
A rationalist, I see.
Well, that aside...
There's this heaven—although it's
technically not a heaven—called Valhalla.
In Scandanavian legend there are female angels clad in armor
called valkyries who take the souls of brave soldiers to Valhalla.
Women who greet the dead...
Does that story sound familiar?
There's a theory that dullahans are the
forms of valkyries wandering the Earth.
If that's so...
She must be waiting...
For her awakening, for battles...
All to search for sacred soldiers to admit into Valhalla.
Even though it's alive, it hasn't awakened because this isn't a battlefield.
If I could, I'd like to be chosen as a soldier, too.
What should I do if Valhalla truly awaits one after death?
I doubt I could go to a war zone and prove myself there.
Then I'll have to make a war break out that only I can cause.
Right?
How lucky am I?
I don't believe in the afterlife, I live a life such that I'll
never get into Heaven, yet I meet a fallen angel because of it.
No way...
That's all just speculation on your part.
Those who believe get saved.
Moreover, didn't I say this is just an insurance policy?
As long as I exist, I don't care whether I
go to Hell or if there's only suffering there.
But, if I can, I'd rather go to Heaven.
Hey, Ms. Namie, let's all go to Heaven together.
As a member of The Dollars, I'll hold on to this.
It's difficult to see what's right in front of you.
There's no way Celty would ever guess that her head's part of the same group she belongs to.
That's right, you should join The Dollars, too.
Our boss likes to drag our new recruits into things.
Of course, I'm the one who's been doing most of the recruiting lately.
Let's make this fallen angel flap her wings.
Shall we?
Her everyday life:
Nothing happens in it.
Nothing changes.
Yet some things are born and some
things disappear in this city every day.
Next Time: Sudden Twist.