♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1,
LET'S JAM ♪
♪ MY LOVE FOR YOU ♪
♪ BURNS DEEP INSIDE ME,
SO STRONG ♪
♪ EMBERS OF TIMES WE HAD ♪
♪ AND NOW HERE I STAND ♪
♪ LOST IN A MEMORY... ♪
[BEEP]
THE ELDERS ARE
MAKING THEIR MOVE.
YOU'RE IN DANGER.
GO QUICKLY BUT QUIETLY.
[CLICK]
♪ ...AND SMILE ♪
[COCKS GUN]
[BEEPING]
WHAT A FOOLISH THING
THIS IS THAT YOU HAVE DONE.
A FORTUNETELLER WARNED US,
ON THE NIGHT OF THE RED MOON
THE SNAKE WILL SLITHER
AND STRIKE,
BARING ITS VENOMOUS FANGS.
YOU LOOK SO PITIFUL,
VICIOUS, AND YOU ARE.
WE HAVE ALREADY INFORMED
YOU OF OUR FINAL DECISION.
YOU CANNOT SUCCEED US
AS A LEADER OF THIS CLAN.
THE SYNDICATE DOESN'T NEED
CORPSES THAT CAN'T FIGHT,
WHO'VE LOST
THEIR TASTE FOR BLOOD.
NOR DOES IT
NEED CALLOW UPSTARTS.
YOUR UNBRIDLED ARROGANCE
HAS SEALED YOUR FATE.
TAKE HIM TO THE CHAMBER.
[CAWING]
KILL ME.
JUST DO IT NOW.
YOU CANNOT CHOOSE
HOW YOU WILL DIE, NOR WHEN.
YOU MUST LEARN HUMILITY.
WHEN YOUR PRIDE IS BROKEN,
THEN WE WILL SEND YOU
TO THE UNDERWORLD.
DON'T FORGET...
A SERPENT'S VENOM
POISONS SLOWLY AFTER THE BITE.
OH, MAN, NEVER
SCREWED UP THAT BAD BEFORE.
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
YOU AND I WERE DOING FINE.
THEN THEY COME ALONG
AND MESS UP EVERYTHING.
SEEMS LIKE EVERY
BOUNTY'S A PROBLEM.
"PAMPER ME.
BABY ME."
NOTHIN' BUT TROUBLE.
I UNDERSTAND NOW
WHY YOU HAVE THIS ATTITUDE
ABOUT WOMEN AND KIDS.
[GUNFIRE]
DEFINITELY TOO MUCH VERMOUTH.
WHO ARE THESE GUYS?
OH! UGH!
LINN?
I'M LINN'S BROTHER.
CHINN.
THAT'S RIGHT,
YOU WERE BOTH INSIDE.
ONCE YOU'VE
CROSSED THIS LINE,
YOU CAN NEVER GO BACK
TO THE SYNDICATE.
WHAT HAPPENED, CHINN?
VICIOUS IS GONNA BE EXECUTED.
HE TRIED TO PULL OFF
A COUP, BUT IT BACKFIRED.
THEY GOT HIM IN THE CHAMBER.
AND YOU'RE A TARGET NOW, TOO.
SO'S JULIA.
JULIA?
[CRASH]
THEY'RE IN THARSIS CITY.
I'LL COVER YOUR ESCAPE.
PLEASE, GO NOW, WHILE YOU CAN.
I OWE YOU, CHINN.
GOOD LUCK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOIN'
ON WITH THE RED DRAGONS,
BUT IT'S REALLY NOT
YOUR PROBLEM NOW, RIGHT?
VICIOUS, JULIA.
TO ME THOSE NAMES SOUND OMINOUS,
LIKE A MAGIC SPELL
THAT UNLOCKS AN OLD DOOR,
A DOOR THAT SHOULD STAY CLOSED.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA-- OH!
KEEP IT STILL, PLEASE.
[CLINK]
[GRUNTING]
YOU'RE NOT IN
THE SYNDICATE ANYMORE, SPIKE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
AND YOU, DOCTOR,
FORGET EVERYTHING YOU'VE HEARD.
IN FACT, FORGET WE WERE HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU YOWLING ABOUT?
I'M JUST FEEDING STRAY CATS
THAT WANDERED INTO THE OFFICE.
PESKY CATS
I CAN'T EVEN GET RID OF.
ARGH...
WHEN THIS IS OVER,
I'M LEAVING THE SYNDICATE.
THEY'LL KILL YOU.
YOU KNOW HOW THEY WORK.
LET THEM SAY I'M DEAD.
I'LL BE WAITING
AT THE GRAVEYARD.
BY THE GRAVES, NOT IN ONE.
SPIKE, I CAN'T COME WITH YOU.
YES, YOU CAN.
WE'LL LEAVE HERE.
WE'LL GET OUT OF THIS.
AND GO WHERE? AND DO WHAT?
LIVE. BE FREE.
IT'LL BE LIKE WATCHING A DREAM.
SO, YOU WERE
GOING TO BETRAY ME?
DID YOU REALLY THINK
YOU COULD JUST LEAVE?
VICIOUS...
KEEP DREAMING, JULIA.
IT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
ARE YOU GONNA KILL HIM?
I WON'T.
YOU'RE GOING
TO DO IF FOR ME.
EITHER YOU KILL HIM,
OR ELSE BOTH OF YOU DIE.
THOSE ARE YOUR ONLY OPTIONS.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
SO THERE'S NO PLACE
FOR ME, AFTER ALL.
WELL, I WON'T GO,
AND THAT'S THAT.
AND I DON'T CARE
WHO COMES HERE TO PICK ME UP.
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE A LIFE
WHERE I'M ALWAYS
IN SOMEONE'S WAY.
MOTHER, I'VE
BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU!
ALFREDO.
OH, I TOLD YOU TO WAIT
AT THE CURRY RESTAURANT.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S OK.
I'M JUST GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
CAN YOU REALLY
TAKE CARE OF ME NOW?
IT SOUNDS TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
YES, MOM, DON'T WORRY,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
MMM...
HAVE YOU FOUND A NEW JOB YET?
NO, BUT I WILL.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR CO-HOST,
THAT BLONDE GIRL?
HMM? OH, I THINK
SHE'S MARRYING HER AGENT.
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT GUY.
[PHONE RINGING]
WHERE ARE YOU?
HUH. WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I'M HEADING OUT TO
THE CITY OF THARSIS.
I WANT YOU TO MEET ME THERE.
WHY SHOULD I?
WELL, IT'S HARD FOR JET
TO GET AROUND BY HIMSELF
WITH HIS LEG ALL SHOT UP.
OH!
SO QUIT WASTING TIME AND GET
YOUR ASS BACK TO THE SHIP.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M COMING BACK?
YOU TAKE TOO MUCH FOR GRANTED.
I HAVE MY OWN PLACE
TO GO BACK TO.
WHAT AN ATTITUDE.
HIGH AND MIGHTY.
JET IS NOT ALONE.
HE CAN TAKE CARE OF HIM.
ED AND EIN ARE THERE, TOO.
[ENGINE RACING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
YOU SAVED ME.
AND YOU SAVED ME BACK.
YOU'RE A GOOD SHOT.
IT'S A PLUS WHEN
YOU'RE CHASING BOUNTY HEADS.
YOU'RE A BOUNTY HUNTER?
WELL, I'M TAKING
A VACATION FOR PERSONAL REASONS.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH A ROUGH TIME YOURSELF.
HMM...
IT MIGHT BE GOOD
TO WORK WITH ANOTHER WOMAN.
HOW 'BOUT IT?
YOU WANT TO PARTNER UP?
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO TAKE CARE OF.
RIGHT.
TOO BAD.
DO YOU KNOW PLACES
WHERE BOUNTY HUNTERS HANG OUT?
IF YOU WANT TO PUT A BOUNTY ON
SOMEONE, I CAN TAKE CARE OF IT.
I'M LOOKING FOR
A BOUNTY HUNTER.
I'LL DRIVE YOU BACK.
I HAVEN'T EVEN ASKED YOUR NAME.
FAYE.
FAYE?
FAYE VALENTINE.
IT'S A VERY COMMON NAME.
AND HOW 'BOUT YOU?
JULIA.
JULIA?
IT'S ALSO A VERY COMMON NAME.
I'M GLAD I MET YOU, FAYE.
SAME HERE.
UH, HAVE I MET YOU
SOMEWHERE BEFORE?
IF YOU SEE SPIKE AGAIN...
TELL HIM I'LL BE
WAITING FOR HIM THERE.
THAT'S ALL.
HE'LL KNOW WHAT IT MEANS.
TELL HIM THAT
I'LL KEEP WAITING.
BUT WHY?
SEE YOU LATER, FAYE VALENTINE.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
HOW DO YOU KNOW I KNOW SPIKE?
ARE YOU STILL IN PAIN?
HAVE YOU HEARD THIS STORY?
HUH?
A MAN INJURES
HIS LEG DURING A HUNT.
HE'S IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE SAVANNA.
NO MEANS TO TREAT THE WOUND.
THE LEG ROTS
AND DEATH APPROACHES.
LAST MINUTE HE'S
PICKED UP BY AN AIRPLANE.
HE LOOKS DOWN AND SEES
A LAND OF PURE WHITE BELOW HIM,
GLISTENING IN THE LIGHT.
IT'S THE SUMMIT OF
A SNOWCAPPED MOUNTAIN.
THE MOUNTAIN IS KILIMANJARO.
AS HE GAZES DOWN, HE FEELS
THE LIFE FLOWING OUT OF HIM,
AND HE THINKS,
"THAT'S WHERE I WAS HEADED."
AND?
I HATE STORIES LIKE THAT.
MEN ONLY THINK ABOUT THE PAST
RIGHT BEFORE THEIR DEATH,
AS IF THEY WERE
SEARCHING FRANTICALLY
FOR PROOF THAT THEY WERE ALIVE.
TURN BACK.
WHEN YOU AND I FIRST MET,
YOU TOLD ME SOMETHING.
YOU SAID THAT
YOU HAD DIED ONCE.
THAT YOU HAD SEEN DEATH.
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST LET IT GO?
FORGET THE PAST.
THERE WAS A WOMAN.
FIRST TIME I FOUND SOMEONE
THAT WAS TRULY ALIVE.
AT LEAST,
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
SHE WAS THE PART OF ME I'D
LOST SOMEWHERE ALONG THE WAY...
THE PART THAT WAS MISSING...
THAT I'D BEEN LONGING FOR.
SHE'S BACK.
HUH? WHO?
THIS IS NOT A REPAIR SHOP,
ALL RIGHT, FAYE?
DON'T JUST COME BACK HERE
WHEN YOU'VE THRASHED YOUR SHIP.
WHERE IS HE?
WHERE'S WHO?
THE GUY WITH THE FUZZY HAIR.
MMM, FUZZY HAIR, HUH?
CAN'T YOU JUST SAY
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR SPIKE?
WHERE IS HE?
DOING SOMETHING
IN THE WORKSHOP.
WAIT A MINUTE, FAYE,
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
YOU DIDN'T COME JUST TO
SEE SPIKE, THAT'S FOR SURE.
I WAS ASKED TO
RELAY A MESSAGE FROM JULIA.
HOLD ON.
[PHONE RINGS]
JET, YOU THERE?
WHAT? I DON'T HAVE
ANY NEW INFORMATION.
WE'RE NOT REALLY
IN A POSITION TO--
I'M GLAD YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
I WAS WORRIED.
IT'S GETTING
PRETTY INTENSE, YOU KNOW.
THE RED DRAGONS?
YEAH, THERE WAS
A COUP ATTEMPT TWO DAYS AGO.
NEW GUARD VERSUS OLD.
THE OLD GUARD WON,
AND NOW THEY'RE HUNTING DOWN
ANYONE WHO COULD BE
CONNECTED TO THE COUP.
THEY'LL ANNIHILATE EVERY SINGLE
TARGET DOWN TO THE LAST MAN.
AND YOUR PARTNER'S
ON THEIR LIST.
YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT WHY WOULD
THEY GO AFTER A GUY
WHO LEFT
THE SYNDICATE YEARS AGO?
IF HE WAS EVER
PART OF THE GROUP
THAT STAGED THAT COUP,
THEY'D TAKE HIM OUT.
THAT'S HOW THEY DO IT.
WHAT KIND OF LOGIC IS THAT?
JUST RUN, JET. THE POLICE
CAN'T STOP THESE GUYS.
LEAVE MARS AND DO IF FAST.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT,
BUT THANKS.
YOU GOT SOMETHING?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU
HAVE SOME INFORMATION.
IT'S GONNA COST YOU.
WELL, I DON'T
HAVE ANY CASH.
[RUMBLING]
UNH!
YOU PICKED A BAD TIME
TO COME BACK, FAYE.
YOU SURE YOU
DIDN'T CALL THEM HERE.
YEAH, RIGHT, OR MAYBE
THEY FOLLOWED YOU HERE.
UHH.
WELL, IT WAS BOUND TO
HAPPEN SOONER OR LATER, HUH?
WAIT!
HOLD ON!
I DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
SHE SAID SHE'D
BE WAITING THERE.
SHE SAID YOU'D
KNOW WHAT SHE MEANT.
WELL, I DON'T, SORRY.
HER NAME IS JULIA.
SOMEONE'S TRYING
TO KILL HER, SPIKE.
THEY'RE AFTER HER.
HEY, JET,
I'M READY TO TAKE OFF.
ONE WHO DISTURBS
THE GENERAL AFFAIRS OF OUR CLAN
MUST BE EXECUTED ACCORDING TO
THE GENERAL WILL OF OUR CLAN.
AAH!
I'M TAKING OFF, TOO.
YOU CAN'T, ONE OF YOUR
MAIN THRUSTERS IS TOTALLY SHOT.
SAME DIFFERENCE IF WE
GO DOWN WITH THE SHIP.
YOU MAY LEAVE FINAL WORDS.
OR YOU MAY
BEQUEATH YOUR POSSESSIONS.
NOTHING.
[CROW CAWING]
AND YOU WILL
SHED TEARS OF SCARLET.
AAH!
SPIKE,
CAN YOU STILL FLY?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT US,
JUST GO.
FIND WHAT YOU LOST
AND GET IT BACK.
GO.
THE LEADERSHIP OF
THE RED DRAGONS
HAS NOW CHANGED HANDS.
FROM THIS TIME FORWARD,
MY POWER IS THE ONLY POWER.
THERE HAVE BEEN MANY THINGS,
BUT THE NEXT
EPISODE IS THE LAST.
UHH, SURE WAS LONG.
NO USE DOIN' THIS.
SO, HOW WAS IT, JET?
BECAUSE OF YOU I ENDED UP
I ENDED UP RAISING EIN.
I FOUND OUT
I LIKE DOGS, AFTER ALL.
HEY, JET...
I WONDER WHERE
HE WENT OFF TO?
COME ON, YOU'RE NOT
EVEN LISTENING TO ME.
OH...WHAT'S THAT?
NEVER MIND.
NEXT EPISODE, THE REAL
FOLK BLUES, PART TWO.
WE'LL SEE YOU AGAIN. SOMEWHERE.
HUH? IT'S OVER?