Stop lazing around, transfer student!
It's clean up time.
He's a weird guy.
I don't know what he's seeing, sometimes he just spaces out.
He looks a bit clumsy.
Lucky, the rain stopped.
It's pretty, isn't it?
I was about to miss it.
Because it's a scenery of nature,
we often overlook it.
The ship will set sail on Monday midnight.
There's people that will pick us up at the hotel, so we have to stay there until the evening.
Just five more days living here.
I hope no one tries to stop us.
I wonder...
You should prepare for the worst.
I don't want to do this again...
If only we could disappear like mist...
Then...
Scythe!
What is it, Ms. Garland?
Where's Phantom?
You better not be scheming something again.
Phantom?
Wasn't she supposed to be with you today?
I lost her.
Damn, just when I took my eyes off her.
It's not like something will happen today, right?
I'm sure she will come back tonight.
The armory is almost empty.
Oh... that's a problem.
What is she planning to do?
Oh well, I know a place where she'll probably show up.
Contact McGuire and Mr. Shiga and tell them I'll go look for Phantom immediately.
So the dice have been cast.
She's just a kid.
Are you serious?
I'm over taking over where Zwei left off.
But...
Drei?
Yep. That's my name from today on.
Nice to meet you, Miss Experienced!
Can you cover my back?
Hey...
You won't run away, will you?
God, I'm not good at babysitting.
I'm sorry about what happened a few days ago.
I surprised you pretty badly, didn't I?
No.
Back then abroad, she...
Well, I never thought she'd chase me here...
and I never expected her to punch me.
But I'm glad I could meet her again.
She hit me, but I think we had a good talk.
It's over between me and her.
Okay.
I'll make up for it next time.
We could go to the cinema again.
Then...
Goodbye.
Bye.
Eh?
Why is it dark?
Ah, mom won't be home today.
Hi. It's not the first time we meet,
so don't be so wary.
Why are you here?
You are Godou's little princess, aren't you?
Eh? Godou?
Are you talking about my uncle?
Uncle?
Oh well,
I'll leave the dry explanations for later.
Um...
You might not see one every day in this country,
but yeah, it's a real gun.
Get on the bike.
I'll tell you something about your beloved...
...Reiji's secret.
I thought you'd show up, Phantom.
Wait for a bit.
Nice timing.
I need to talk to you.
Cal.
The game's on again.
No one touches Zwei and Ein.
If you can't promise that...
...I'll kill the little princess.
I won't let anyone interfere.
Don't lay a finger on my target!
How many stupid things will you do until you're satisfied?
Do you hate Zwei that much?
You bet I do.
No matter if it's a traitor or someone who harms civilians,
I can never forgive them.
There are lines you mustn't cross.
Open your eyes, Cal. Once you go past this point, you will fall into a bottomless abyss.
I've been wondering all the time...
Lizzie, why were you so nice to me?
Both Zwei and me didn't want you to become an assassin.
So I felt.
Everyone is so selfish...
I'm Phantom.
If you have a problem, just try and stop me.
Right here, right now.
Once the melody is over, I'll draw.
If you don't pull the trigger before that, you're a sentimental idiot.
You're destined to die here.
Cal.
Huh?
I don't want to kill you.
Cal!
Why couldn't you pull the trigger?
Why didn't I shoot?
Are you sure you want such a heavy gun?
Yeah, I don't want to shoot easily.
Yet, this gun... this gun...
...is getting so heavy...
...too heavy.
Clau...
You'll be here for three or four days, so ration it.
Why?
Please tell me the reason.
Why go so far as killing people?
That's mine...
This is the last of your friends you contacted, right?
This Kanji... you read it as "Reiji", don't you?
Who are you to him?
His ex-disciple...
...and his ex-lover.
You're lying.
Why do you think that?
What do you think you know about him?
You see...
I learned how to use this from Reiji.
What did you think he was doing in America?
He's an assassin... and an extraordinary one at that.
I don't think I can count the people Reiji killed.
That's...
You're being played with.
Two years ago a man called Godou Daisuke was killed in Los Angeles.
You said he was your uncle, right?
Why do you know this?
I'm well informed. Better than you.
The truth is that he was a gang member,
and the story about him being your uncle is bullshit.
In reality he was your brother from a different mother, and I know that.
That's a lie.
What? You don't like being the daughter of a mafia man?
There's even more to it.
Godou Daisuke's death wasn't an accident.
Your precious Reiji as good as killed-
Don't make up stories!
It's up to you to believe it or not.
But one day you will have to believe it, and your life will be stained with blood and death.
When that time comes, remember the stories I told you.
All I've said is the truth.
What is your goal?
To have a fight to the death...
...with Reiji.
One will kill the other.
That's awful.
The day will come.
Come, it's the beginning.
Hello.
Sorry, but this isn't Mio speaking.
What happened to Mio?
Calm down, I have no intention of hurting her.
While you're busy running away,
I thought I would take the burden of your hostage off your shoulders.
I'm doing you a favor.
Wasn't I supposed to be your only target?
Mio doesn't have anything to do with...
You wanted to go back...
...to being honest.
According to your wish...
...I'm protecting your life.
I won't let the Godou clan or Inferno get in your way.
As long as you go to school, you will be safe.
But there won't be any sudden disappearance.
I don't know where you could run away to...
But if you go somewhere out of my reach,
Mio will go meet her brother.
Remember that!
I'll always keep an eye on you.
This time...
...you won't be able to run.
I can't believe she even went as far as to disobey Inferno.
That's proof of how much she detests me.
We should take a different path.
A different path?
Oh my, oh my...
It seems Phantom has kidnapped Mio.
Just how far does your ego go?
As I thought, you're well informed.
Don't fuck with me!
This is your plotting, right?
I'm afraid not.
She is brother's memento.
She's not your toy.
Your words might affect the treaty with Inferno.
I won't let the abduction of Fujieda Mio ruin that.
I'll go ahead and search for Drei.
As per her instructions, remain still.
I will shoot Drei and free Mio.
We're being monitored, though.
If we try to save Mio by force, she'll...
If I disappear alone, I'm sure Drei won't harm Mio.
Why are you so sure?
Her target is you.
But...
We aren't cornered yet.
Conquer your emotions.
If you can't...
...you will perish.
Rest assured, Mr. Shiga.
I have already summoned my staff.
They are my ultimate soldiers, perfectly trained and controlled.
A will that crushed emotion...
...lets them finish any job they are assigned.
I will achieve the results you desire.
They cannot fail.
If you live on...
...that would be my...
...proof I ever lived.