Tomorrow is the long-awaited
Christmas Eve!
In order to confess
my love to Takuto,
I've worked hard night after night
to knit a scarf for him!
But...but...but...
Why?!
I'm not done yet!
Mitsuki!
Please! Help me so I can
finish it in time!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
What am I going to do?
We forgot about your grandmother.
We were being careless.
We were on cloud nine after
the Best New Singer Award.
And it's not like I can butt in...
Well, you at least have a passport.
It could have been worse.
That's not the problem.
We have to persuade her grandmother.
That's right.
I know!
Meroko, you transform into Mitsuki
and stay at home.
What?!
So you mean I have to
stay home alone?
You've got it.
Takuto, do you really intend to go
and leave me?!
Huh?
- You're so mean!
- Ouch! Oww!
- That's outrageous! You've gone too far!
- Ouch, I get it!
What do you wanna do, Mitsuki?
Should we ask Meroko to do that?
No.
I want to go tell Grandma about
going to America.
I once lied to Grandma and went
to a sleepover.
That time, I felt like I had lied
to Grandma's feelings as well.
That's why this time
I want to tell her properly.
Yes.
About that, I've gathered the information
so please come to the hospital.
So this is that new
treatment method?
Yes. If we continue the current treatment
and do the operation,
there's a possibility she
would lose her voice,
but with this treatment method
Dr. Lon Herberd wrote about,
there is no worry of that.
And?
I contacted that doctor,
and we came to an agreement.
Then, Dr. Wakaoji...
Yes.
Yay! Then I'm sure
your grandmother will okay it!
What do you mean?
That Dr. What's-His-Name will
examine Mitsuki's throat!
What?
If we tell her that, your grandmother will
understand and let you go to America.
Really?
Yep.
I'll come to
your house tomorrow,
and we'll talk to your grandmother
about everything, okay?
Yes!
So, I contacted the doctor and he'd like to
examine the condition of Mitsuki's illness.
Then he'll determine whether this
treatment method can be used on Mitsuki.
So...
You're saying you'd like to take
Mitsuki to America?
Yes.
It's quite sudden isn't it?
Grandma...
Doctors in Japan can't do
that medical treatment?
Unfortunately, no doctors in Japan
have attempted this treatment yet.
I thought that I'd study it on this trip
so that I can be of help in the future.
DEPARTURE FROM
CONVENTIONAL APPROACH
FOR THROAT DISEASE TREATMENT
I'm against it.
What?!
Why, Grandma?
I don't understand that medical
treatment very well yet.
No matter how many times
you explain that it's "good,"
I won't allow something I don't understand
for my beloved granddaughter.
However, if you actually
meet the doctor...
I understand what you're saying.
But to go to America
for only that reason.
Can't we wait until he has
the opportunity to come to Japan?
Well...
Mitsuki is a child with a weak body.
I can't agree to taking that child
around America.
My number one concern is
this child's body.
Is that wrong?
Mrs. Koyama, you're right
to be concerned, but...
Mitsuki, you shouldn't
just jump at new things
because you've heard
that they're good.
But Mrs. Koyama!
What would you do if something
happened while she was in America?
Would you take responsibility?
Grandma!
You be quiet.
No! Please!
Grandma, please understand.
With this medical treatment
I won't lose my voice!
I'll be able to keep doing what
I love to do... sing!
Mitsuki!
You...can't possibly still have
an interest in music, can you?!
Well?!
Mitsuki...
Mitsuki!
I'm a singer...
I mean, I want to be a singer!
Grandma!
I want you to hear
my song, Grandma!
That's why I don't want
to lose my voice!
Dr. Wakaoji,
what is this all about?
It's just like Mitsuki said.
The two of you were
making a fool of me.
That's wrong!
That's enough! I don't want
to hear anything else!
Mrs. Koyama!
Grandma, please!
Please let me go to America!
I absolutely will not allow it.
Umm... Ma'am, Mitsuki is...
How dare you!
It's disgraceful to eavesdrop!
Y-Yes! I'm sorry!
Keep your spirits up.
I'll try asking her again tomorrow.
Okay...
We'll make sure that you can go.
So don't worry.
Yes.
The operation...
Is it in there?
THINGS THAY MAY INTERRUPT FATE
THERE ARE NO NEW MESSAGES
No, it looks like it's okay.
I see.
What is it?
We're in an unfortunate business.
Yeah.
Grandma, please listen to me.
I'm coming in.
I'm sorry that I've
kept quiet about music.
Of course,
I've known that you are against it.
But I really want to be a singer.
I believe that you are concerned
that my body is weak.
But please let me go to America.
I can't do that.
Why? Why, Grandma?
Is it because I didn't tell you
about my music?
Do you hate music that much?
Even though my mother and
I like music this much?
Why? Grandma, why don't you
understand my feelings at all?
I'm sure that my mother ran away from
home because you're like that, Grandma!
Grandma...
Grandma, I hate you!
Mitsuki!
Mother, I hate you!
What are you doing?
Packing to go to America.
What? But you still...
Hey, my life goes until spring
of next year, right?
Then...
I want to at least sing until then.
And I'm going to America,
no matter what.
Didn't Wakaoji say that he's going
to talk to her again?
It won't work! Grandma won't
go back on what she said.
On top of that,
this might be my last chance.
Hey, where are you going?
To Ms. Oshige's...
Well, shouldn't you
at least tell Ms. Tanaka?
Ms. Koyama, here's your mail!
Oh...thank you.
It's addressed to Grandma...
MRS. FUZUKI KOYAMA
HIMEKI MUSIC ACADEMY
A music school?!
- Huh?
I'd love to see you.
It's been so long.
Grandma graduated
from a music school?!
I wonder if it's this way.
Hey, what's the point of doing this?
Grandma went to a music school!
The person who
sent this postcard
probably knows the reason
why she started hating music.
Have you been waiting?
I'm sorry, the lesson went
a little bit long.
I'm deeply touched that Fuzuki's
granddaughter would come all this way.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, is tea okay with you?
Oh... Yes, thank you.
Wow, it smells good.
It's rose tea.
And here are some cookies.
I just baked them.
Please have some,
if you'd like.
Thank you.
It would have been nice if this kind of
person were her grandmother.
Shh...
Is something wrong?
Oh no...
So, Fuzuki really didn't
tell you anything, did she?
No.
Fuzuki and I were childhood friends.
We really liked music.
Fuzuki would often play
the piano while I would sing.
And then we both
entered music school.
Fuzuki got engaged to someone
she met at the school.
And my, how she glowed so brightly.
Engaged?
Yes.
But then...
It's no good!
And the competition is so soon!
You'll exhaust yourself
if you practice too much like that.
You have to take
a little break.
I don't care about that.
If I can't win this competition,
I'll never make it as a pianist in this world.
But—
Shut up! It's different for you because
music is just a hobby!
Don't bother me.
As a result,
their feelings drifted apart.
And he went abroad on his own.
He left my grandmother?
Yes... He chose
music over Fuzuki.
She debated whether or not
she should go with her fiancé,
but in the end, she made up her mind
to part from her fiancé and from music.
She said that it was painful
to be exposed to music.
But Fuzuki said that
she made the right decision.
She said music is a demon that confuses
people's feeling and makes them unhappy.
No way!
And then, after a while,
she contacted me.
She said that she'd had
an arranged marriage.
And that she had been
blessed with a cute girl.
That must be my mother.
Back then, she would sometimes
come to this house to chat.
She would bring
her young Hazuki with her.
But since the young lady passed away,
she's been out of touch.
It's been a while since then, so I started
wondering how she's doing now,
and I took it upon myself to send
a postcard for the class reunion.
Oh, I see.
But to have a lovely
granddaughter like you...
I'm sure that she's
very happy now.
I'm glad.
Today, I played very well,
and my teacher complimented me!
That's great!
Yeah!
When I first met Grandma...
the cherry blossoms
were in full bloom.
When I saw Grandma's frowning face,
I thought I wasn't really welcome.
But back then,
Grandma was still suffering.
What are you going to do?
What should I do?
Can you persuade
your grandmother?
I don't think I can.
So why are you
standing around here?
When I heard Grandma's story, I...
You're going home?
But if you return now,
she might lock you in.
Is that okay with you?
Was I a bad girl for
making Grandma sad?
Mitsuki...
I cause her a lot of worry to begin with,
what with my weak body.
But then to say that I want to be
a singer on top of that...
I'm sure that she hates even
hearing the word "music."
Ma'am!
What is it?
Umm... Mitsuki is...
Mitsuki isn't here!
When I came to call her for dinner,
she was gone.
Almost all her things
are gone,
and her beloved music box is
nowhere to be found.
Could it be...
that she's run away?
If you don't accept me,
Mother, then I'll move out!
Mother, I hate you!
Hazuki!
My beloved daughter, who means
more to me than anything.
And...
Thank you for taking me in.
My name is Mitsuki.
The child that was born in
exchange for that girl's life.
The child of the man
who stole Hazuki.
What should I say?
How should I speak to her?
But this time,
I have to protect her.
You're not a bad girl.
You never stopped wanting
your grandmother to like music.
Am I wrong?
That shows that you care
about your grandmother.
But...
Well, can you tell her everything
about the length of your life?
What?
Takuto!
Why would you say that?!
If I tell her that,
Grandma will be sad.
But if you don't, your grandmother won't
understand your feelings at all.
That's true, but...
I understand why your grandmother
came to hate music.
But you have a reason why
you have to sing, don't you?
Takuto...
Why do you sing songs?
Tanaka! Contact every place
you can think of!
Yes!
Mitsuki!
Grandma...
Mitsuki! What a relief.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and come in!
Grandma.
What is it?
I'm going to America.
Even if you don't approve,
I want to go to America.
You're going to leave me too?
I'm sorry. I don't think
that you'll understand.
But Grandma, I love you.
That wasn't true
when I said I hate you.
Please just understand that.
Please listen to my songs someday!
I'm sorry!
Mitsuki! Mitsuki—
Ma'am!
Ma'am, are you injured?!
Ma'am...
It's always the same.
It's always the things I hold dear
that pull away from my hands.
We're here in America!
Hey Takuto,
where do you want to go?!
You're completely
in sightseeing mode.
Do you understand,
you and I didn't come to play.
You're so annoying!
If you wanna talk
about being excited,
I'm not all that different from
that girl in full-on love mode with Eichi!
Once again,
you're taking her side!
It's so frustrating!
Stupid! Stop it, Meroko!
It's not like that!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Across the Pacific."
- Look forward to it!