Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
It's summer! It's the ocean!
Thanks for chaperoning and driving us today, Sensei and Nee-san.
No problem!
But seriously...
Huh?
You guys must really have nothing to do.
Summer Staples
Sorry to trouble you on your holiday.
No, no, not at all.
Narumi-san, you're in the traffic safety division, right?
That's right.
Yep, leave all the traffic laws to me!
Ah!
Someone passed us.
Eh?
You bastard...
H-Hey...
What about traffic safety?
Nee-san goes crazy once she's behind the wheel.
So Kagami and Tsukasa will have to be our sacrifices.
Really~
Is that so?
Even though she's a policewoman?
Huh...?
That's odd...
I seem to have lost sight of them...
Ah!
Sensei, that's the wrong way!
Sensei, that's a one-way street!
U-Unbelievable...
I didn't expect them both to be bad choices!
That car's amazing!
Who the hell is it!?
The downhill breaking and shifting, it's perfect!
It's right behind the FD!
And it's acceleration is better, too!
It's just barely touching the guardrail!
The point of attack will be...
The five consecutive hairpin curves up ahead!
It's speeding up!
Are the brakes shot?
She passed him!
What's with this insane ****-D style driving!?
Nanako-san...
You're really good...
...at driving.
Is that so?
You see...
When I ride in a car, I usually get sick.
So, I brought some medicine just in case...
But I didn't get sick at all with your driving, Nanako-san!
Ah?
This isn't the time to be making jokes!
Sign: To keep our city clean, fireworks are banned between 10 PM and 7 AM.
Now...
How about we find ourselves an inn?
Ah!
It's really sunny, a perfect day for swimming at the beach!
Seriously...
Yesterday I had no idea what was going to happen.
I'm going to put on my swimsuit right away.
Do you always have to be so childis---
Konata-san, are you serious?
I haven't heard of anyone wearing a school swimsuit at your age.
Kagamin, you know there is a demand for it, too.
Izumi
H-How old is that swimsuit!?
By the way,
you're really athletic, so why do you have to bring an inner tube?
Just because you can swim doesn't mean you have to always freestyle laps in the ocean.
I'm in the mood for leisure right now.
L-e-i-s-u-r-e.
Besides, if I'm going to supply this "demand",
then school swimsuits and an inner tube just have to go together.
Do people with this "demand" even come to the ocean?
In manga or anime, watermelon-splitting is a really popular event.
But I guess not too many people do it when you actually go to the beach.
I've seen it done before,
but I guess they feel it's just a waste of a watermelon.
Indeed...
If you shoot a watermelon with a shotgun, you'll probably be covered in watermelon.
You watch too much anime.
Have you ever done it, Miyuki-san?
You're pretty rich.
I've never done it.
Now that I think about it,
I can't imagine rich people doing it either.
Now that you mention it...
I had a feeling it wouldn't happen...
But your eyes didn't end up like a manga character.
I'm sorry to have disappointed you.
Who would've thought at our age...
...we'd have to come to the ocean with just girls and end up babysitting.
It sucks to be single, doesn't it?
U-Um...
I'm not...
But if you're just going to bring a guy like that,
it's better off coming with just girls, don't you think?
That's why I'm...
Late marriages are in vogue lately,
so it's a good idea to take your time and choose properly.
You're mistaken!
My husband is just currently at a job assignment away from home.
I'm already married!
The ocean is supposed to be a mecca for romance.
But I guess we're just the unlucky ones.
Well, at least we don't have to put up with annoying guys.
Besides, we have this person here,
so everyone probably thinks that we're sisters on a family outing.
And a one-two!
What's the matter?
It kind of feels icky sitting down when you're still wet.
I know how you feel.
How about you settle for an air-chair then, Tsukasa?
You're pretty extreme, aren't you?
What now?
My neck's tired.
Is that so?
Oh!
Just as I expected!
What are you so happy about?
Because this looks like the textbook definition of a seaside restaurant.
Look at this curry with nothing else.
As expected from a seaside restaurant.
You wouldn't want to eat something like that normally...
But in this atmosphere, even something that isn't too good seems to taste better.
Beer at the ocean is the best!
Sometimes, having a warm one isn't bad either.
I can't agree with a hot dog costing 300 yen, though.
Yep, yep!
And they could be undercooked, but we'd eat them anyway.
I actually kind of like how this chicken is...
Something that's a little too greasy and over-spiced.
Even plain yakisoba like this tastes pretty nice.
But the thing is, you'd never try something like this at home!
Konata's touched.
Hey.
Is this food so good that you have to raise such a ruckus?
Not really.
Not enough to make you run on the beach in a loincloth.
Is that from some anime again?
Eh, I drank too much.
Guess we'll have to stay another night.
Yui-neesan, what about your work?
I took leave for tomorrow, too.
So don't worry about it!
It's freezing~!
Sensei, you're exaggerating...
Geez.
Why is your hair always so stiff after you swim in the ocean?
I dunno.
Maybe it has to do with the salt or something?
Right, Miyuki?
I believe so.
The main causes are the sodium content and UV rays.
Why's that a bad thing?
Your hair is always getting hit with UV rays.
Um...
If I try to explain this in detail,
it's going to take quite a while, but...
Sure sure.
Well then...
The reason why your hair is damaged after a trip to the beach...
...is because the ocean's salinity and the wind-blown salt particles that get stuck in your hair, causing it to lose its moisture.
And then, the UV rays damage your dried hair.
Again, if you get hit by strong UV rays outdoors, the melanin pigment...
...changes color, causing your hair to turn brown.
Still, when excess particles, such as salt and chlorine, are left in your hair...
...it causes your hair to turn dry and brown.
The UV rays and excess particles are the main reasons why your hair gets damaged in the summer.
All of the above result in damage to your cuticles.
The cysteine bonds, that keep your hair strong, break...
Look, look!
Timotei.
Timotei...
Timotei~!
What's that?
I wonder what we look like from the perspective of others.
Not sure...
Just can't keep the conversation going...
Probably like we were family or relatives or something like that, right?
I guess so.
No further response?
Nee-san, Nee-san!
Timotei.
Timotei...
Timotei~!
Oh!
How nostalgic!
I remember doing that.
There it is!
This was the response I wanted.
How old are you?
Mandom!
Enough with the old geezer jokes.
What's up, Kona-chan?
I triggered a flag on this one.
What are you talking about?
This is where the event starts!
And just so you can see both choices...
Remember to save frequently!
Leave no stone unturned!
Setup, complete.
Perfect!
Let's see it.
I don't follow at all.
You know, it's because you act like this all day.
Like what?
That's why no one tries to hit on us.
Y-You're the one that initially brought it up, you know!
I wasn't even thinking about anything like that.
Ah, so Kagami wanted to get hit on, huh?
O-Of course not.
Ah!
Darn it!
I missed it!
What is it?
Um... Uh...
I was just wondering how you took care of your hair.
Mine's pretty smooth so I don't do anything.
Hm...
How about you, Onee-chan?
M-Me?
I guess... just the usual.
To tell you the truth, it was pretty close today.
What was?
Well, you know... that.
Ah!
It was almost time.
Oh, oh, that.
That's good, then.
Tsukasa, were you all right?
Yep, I was totally all right.
Mine ended a week ago so the timing was perfect.
Isn't it troubling when it happens like this?
Yes, it is.
It would be sad if you were the only one who couldn't go into the water...
Then again, you don't really want to use one of those.
Yep, I know.
Makes you think twice.
I've never used one.
What a candid conversation you guys are having.
What about you, Konata?
Ah!
Don't tell me...
What's with that face?
Nothing.
It's been said that this is a true story...
There was a person working at an image software wholesale company...
...who was on his way home from work.
He boarded the bus really late, like he usually did.
That person's house was near the end of the route...
The passengers kept getting off along the way...
Until he became the only passenger left on the bus...
But the driver thought the bus was empty...
And then...
Began singing "DANZEN! Futari wa ***Cure" at the top of his lungs!
...or so I've heard.
Eh?
I'm so glad...
I was really scared.
To tell you the truth, I'm scared, too.
I'm Sukekiyo!
Where did you get that mask from!?
Well then, good night.
Yeah, good night.
The Inugami Family!
It's so much fun scaring you.
Why don't you sleep already?
Hey!
We're leaving!
Okay!
I can't say anything really interesting.
I'm Tsukasa...
Tsukasa...
Onee-chan!!
What is it?
I was scared!
A little girl just got one step closer to adulthood, Kagamin.
Huh!?
Comp-Matsuri is really popular.
That's because Japanese people are weak to limited edition stuff.
If that's all it takes to increase their sales,
then they should have them every month.
Then it wouldn't be very "limited" any more.
I actually listened and...
Yes?
Remember to clean up your room and things during the break.
Oh!
How nostalgic!
This textbook is from middle school.
Onee-chan, take a look at this album.
Doesn't Dad look dangerous in this picture?
Huh?
I've been wondering about Dad's thing ever since this picture.
Seems like you're having fun...
But how's the cleaning going?
Hey, do you want these clothes?
If you don't want them, I'll take them all.
Then I'll just leave it here.
Thanks.
Hey, how about this?
I guess I'll take that, too.
How about these?
This?
Hey, are you using me as a trash can?
You get delayed looking at old albums and stuff.
Yeah, I understand.
When there's an old magazine, you can't resist reading it.
I know...
Speaking of which, where's Tsukasa?
She doesn't like to throw her stuff away, so she takes a while.
She's at it today, too.
Tsukasa seems like she would keep everything she finds.
Kagami, on the other hand, you seem like you'd throw away almost everything.
Why is your image of me...
So aggressive?
You kept your textbook from middle school?
You don't have anything like that?
I leave those along with my memories at my old school...
You should take them home.
It's a nuisance to the school.
I'm finally done cleaning up.
Even though there is something I probably wouldn't use,
I then remember the times I used to use them.
So it's really hard to throw stuff away.
There are some people that just want to keep everything.
Tsukasa, you would be their saint.
You, on the other hand, would even throw away things you actually need.
Seeing how you leave your textbooks at school.
Miyuki...
You should go get your teeth looked at before school starts again.
I know I should,
but I just can't...
I would hate forcing you to go if you don't want to that much...
But if you don't want to go, we can have the dentist come here.
A house call.
W-Wait a second!
Lucky Channel!
Oha-Lucky!
It was so fast, but this is already our 6th Lucky Channel!
I hope you've all become quite familiar with this corner by now.
I'm Kogami Akira!
Karuuun~
No.
Did you say something?
It seems my assistant, Shiraishi Minoru, isn't used to the job yet, and is still a nervous wreck.
I'm scared... I'm really scared!
I guess all of you guys looking at him is what making his heart race.
What should I say?
Because of Akira-sama, we went to the mountains.
I hope he gets used to the job soon.
And then we went to the beach as well.
Especially the part about "mind what you say to your superiors" or something else may happen around here...
I'm doing all I can to make this show as interesting as it can be...
And then that gum was hard...
I just hate things like that!
All 54 of them...
54 pieces, all in my mouth!
Today, I would like to introduce a key character from Lucky Star: Izumi Konata!
But I tried my best!
What else can I do?
Hey.
Stop babbling.
Not my thing!
Let's see...
Izumi Konata-san, 17 years old.
Her hobbies are games, anime, and reading.
Um...
According to our data,
she checks out every new show and book...
On weekends, she plays MMO's non-stop...
In other words, she's an otaku?
It would seem that way.
Hm...
I need to think of something quick!
By otaku, you mean those types of people, right?
Like people who enjoy House Classics.
The ones who cry when watching "A Dog of Flanders" or something, right?
What!?
From what era is your image of an "otaku"?
Have you been keeping up with the times?
Stop spouting nonsense!
U-ummm, no...
Well, I suppose "A Dog of Flanders" and cute moé characters...
Both have that soothing appeal that you desire so much.
But nowadays, people yearn for girls like me!
Pure as the driven snow and cute as can be!
You understand?
If I look to the right, they look right!
If I look to the left, they look left!
They stand in line for concerts the night before and don't even take a bath!
And while that might create some problems, still they want to see me!
With that thought alone, they stand in that blazing heat, determinedly awaiting my arrival!
Even if that bandana on their head is drenched enough to be wrung-out!
Well...
They are customers.
They won't stop talking while I'm doing my handshakes.
And at the MC, they blurt out things without even being aware of their surroundings.
Isn't it horrible?
I'm here right now only because of people like them.
I have to try hard for them.
You know?
Is that how it is?
You'll understand soon enough.
The hardships of being an idol.
Once you've been through the good as well as the bad, you'll see how it's really like.
Like having fans or clients you don't like...
Wah!
Perfect timing!
Do you have a better understanding of Konata-san's character now?
Let's meet again during next week's Lucky Channel!
Bye-bii~
Today seemed more like an introduction to otaku...
...rather than to Konata.
Akira-sama, are you okay?
Leave me alone.
Um... Uh... Understood.
At that moment...
What the correspondent saw was...
...not funny.
Ah, that felt good!
I get it, I get it.
So Tsukasa, did you put your song in?
Yeah, I did.
Tsukasa's voice is so pure.
Ehehe.
I hope I can sing it properly.
Ah, what are you singing, Miyuki?
I really don't know that many songs.
It's embarrassing.
Oh.
So this is what she came up with...
Tsukasa-san, do your best!
Ashita wa tokubetsu SPECIAL.DAY
明日は特別　スペシャル.デー
Tomorrow is a special, *special day.*
Ichinen ichido no CHANCE
一年一度の　チャンス
Once in a lifetime chance.
Oh DARLING
Oh　ダーリン
Oh darling.
L-O-V-E Lovely! Tsukasa!
L－O－V－E　Lovely！　つかさ！
Hey, hey...
Oh DARLING I Love You!
Oh　ダーリン　I　Love　You！
Oh darling, I love you.
L-O-V-E Lovely! Sayuri!
L－O－V－E　Lovely！　小百合！
Who is that?
Dare mo ga ukarete CARNIVAL
誰もが浮かれて　カーニバル
Everyone's excited, a carnival.
Kareshi no HEART wo itomete
彼氏のハートを射止めて
Steal your boyfriend's heart.
Oh Baby, Oh Baby, Love Me Do!
It's not read as Kuninama Sayuri...
Who the hell is that?
What was her club
member number again...?
Amai amai koi no CHOCOLATE
甘い甘い　恋のチョコレット
A sweet, sweet chocolate of love.
Anata ni agete mite mo
あなたにあげてみても
Even if I give it to you...
Medachi wa shinai kara
目立ちはしないから
It won't stand out.
Shut up!
Watashi, chotto, saigo no shudan de kimechau
私、ちょっと、最後の手段で決めちゃう
I think I'll finish it with my 'last resort.'
VALENTINE DAY.KISS
バレンタインデー.キッス
Valentine's Day kiss.
VALENTINE DAY.KISS
バレンタインデー.キッス
Valentine's Day kiss.
VALENTINE DAY.KISS
バレンタインデー.キッス
A Valentine's Day kiss...
RIBBON wo kakete
リボンをかけて......
Tied with a ribbon.
Sha la la la suteki...
しゃラララ　すてき...
Sha la la la a lovely...
Preview
Next week on Lucky Star:
Schedule for
Second Semester
Kagami here.
When you try to peel the skin sticking up on your finger...
But you accidentally pull it and make it worse.
Doesn't that really hurt?
And the timing to pull off a scab...
You think it's about the right time.
So you start peeling it off from the edges, thinking it's okay.
So you go for it and pull, but you start bleeding again.
The damage is pretty severe.
Next week: "Image"
「Image」
Look forward to it!