WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is the Cheif Animation Director:
谷口淳一郎 (Taniguchi Jun'ichirou).
Okay! Um, so then, we are continuing, um...
Episode 8 I'm Really An Idiot um... commentary, with the role of Madoka, I am Yuuki Aoi!
Yup!
Yup, and with the role of Homura, I'm Saitou Chiwa.
And, this time's guest—
And!ahis time's guest—
And, this time' guest!
Ah, Chief Animation Director, I'm Taniguchi.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you!
Wow, you deal with the art.
This unsettling atmosphere!
Right, seriously.
This atmosphere...
Reall—
Well, for starters, the amazing visuals sort of distracted me... um,
ga!
Chief Animation Director Taniguchi-san is someone I'd like to talk to now...
Yes.
For starters... what sort of feeling does the work you do have?
What sort of work is it?
Um, as an official description, it's making sure the series and characters hold unity overall.
Yes.
Unity.
Well, it doesn't really come out though (lol)
Aeee~
Uuuu~
(lol)
So you go to each individual animator-san, and sort of iron out the wrinkles?
That's right. Yes. Yes.
Ahh.
For the characters, ensuring the entire time that they are—
Yeah, seeing the series overall.
I see!
What an amazing sense of balance!
That's the job.
Amazing!
That's quite difficult, isn't it?
Right–Well, actually, that isn't particularly true, though.
Really, it's the people who draw the original images and who actually draw the movements that have it hard.
Right.
Yeah.
So, you look it all over, and say "fix this part up a little bit" to grab hold of a balance?
Right. That's right. Yes, yes.
Huaaaa~
By the way, about how many people are there drawing?
About... There are around 10 people who create the original pictures and movement.
Ohh.
Around there.
Then, as for people who make corrections... there are about one or two of those people.
Yes.
Then, there's me as well, who also deals with the drawing of pictures.
Then, there's a feeling of fixing things.
Hee~
Heeeee~
So it's like that!
That's right, huh?
Right.
There are a lot of people collaborating for that, huh?
Ne~?
But it's truly amazing, isn't it?
Mmm!
It's especially true for the work this time. The battle scenes, and the transformation scenes too, they're...
Ahh.
Yes.
(lol) They have so much movement, and the angles and such have a somewhat unique feeling, it's kind of like...
In normal — Well, somehow,
compared to normal mahou shoujo shows, the fighting style is yet another very different thing, right?
Ba– They really have a "shounen battle" resemblance to them.
Right. Yeah.
Is there any discrepancy in that viewpoint to you, in regards to the writing style?
Writing style...
No, um, for us too, when we see the content, we're surprised each time.
Like "What's this!?" (lol)
That's right...
Mm...
Somehow, then, um...
The scenes with movement and stillness have a large contrast... Isn't that quite intense?
Yes.
Really, we've talked about this previously, but...
Scenes where just two people talk while sitting down, scenes where they talk through their facial expressions...
Ahh.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Madoka☆Magika has quite a few of those.
They're there, ne.
Mmm.
Then, we were very cautious about that point when acting out those scenes, but...
Right, right.
Drawing facial expressions... somehow... "How do you decide on those?" was something we thought about a lot...
Ne~
Then on air—Ah, well after knowing what it is on air it's a bit like "That", but for me—
(lol)
ahahaha~
During the after recording, there were still many facial expressions I still didn't know, and when we saw them on air...
Ah, it's true for Madoka right here too, but it's like "So it's this kind of face" or "Here you can't see her eyes."
Ne~
Um, that is, a facial expression where you can't see their eyes.
Ah, that's right, ne.
Yes, yes.
Then, "Here was a close-up on the eyes?" or such.
We came to know that kind of thing.
Ne?
Do you help with achieving balance in that sort of area, too?
That's right, primarily in deciding the art for facial expressions.
Mmm!
Really, when it comes time to draw, I'll try the facial expressions and such myself.
Yes.
Ah, you do?
Yeah.
Yeah, pr–probably, um, to other people it looks like I'm making some disgusting faces.
Making those faces.
(lol)
Doing similar facial expressions would be pretty unpleasant (lol)
I was making sad faces. Yeah.
Ahh.
Having done that, when I saw them done properly on screen, I was quite happy.
Heee~
He~
Then, what is it... this atmosphere the art holds, since it's Ume-sensei, the character's faces are wide.
They have quite a sorrowful feeling to them, don't they?
Yes, yes, yes.
Especially since they're wide, that's right.
Ne? Yeah, that's right.
Somehow, when I see that kind of expression I think "Eh, amazing!" everytime.
Ah, in the beginning really, um... these characters made some kyun-style smiles.
Yes. Yes.
Ahhhhh.
Halfway through, that stops. Um... really, the conversations become quite heavy, don't they?
That's right, ne~
It results in absolutely no smiles.
Mm.
Somehow, at the very beginning of the opening, when you really want to hug Madoka, that distressful crying face...
It isn't really... what is it...
The animation is quite... seeing it in just a "4-pattern" style, I wouldn't have thought it was so moving!
I think the art is amazing. I really love that face. Somehow... I feel thankful for it.
Mhm.
When we did our acting, we put a considerable amount of feeling into it, but...
When we did that, like when you heard our acting, did that give you a hand later on?
Ah, that is, um... um, it was instructional, yes.
Well, when we drew most of the art, after recording was finished.
Ah, is that so!
Yes, yes...
(lol)
Well, you persevered to make the art!
Yeah.
But even still, to think it moves this much... you know?
So difficult...
Really, this time there are so many scenes like this one, which successfully portray "true feelings."
Yes.
It hurt so much, and there was no helping it when we were acting it out, but for the people drawing the art,
It hurts~
I believe they must have felt the same thing when drawing!
Always doing the facial expressions...
Really, somehow, this is something I've always thought up until now...
As a person who worked on this Madoka☆Magika... it's really a work that everyone made, I'd say.
Ne?
I've had this conversation with Ao-chan a number of times, though.
That's why, especially true for my acting of Homura, but...
"We entrust it to you," was said many times...
Little by little, stuff like how the tone of voice should be, or what is said where,
鶴岡陽太(Tsuruoka Yota) = Sound Director
I'd discuss that with Tsuruoka-san and would influence as much as I possibly could.
It was like that. All the way up until the final moments..
Then when she becomes a little bit more dere, and perhaps before then, too...
It was like "As for facial expressions, this time they're being entrusted to you."
Mmm.
Mm, mm, mm.
It was something like that.
That's right, um, Homura—
Lots was left to each person.
In relation to Homura, at this point she doesn't have that many facial expressions yet.
That's right, ne.
Ah, but, it's in this episode, I believe.
Ah, that's right, in just a little bit, that'll be there. It'll come, you know.
It comes. "That" does.
Well, QB is pretty simple, I think. (lol)
Ah, ah, ah.
Um, I'd say this person's face doesn't change much. You can't tell what it's thinking, but it's a living thing.
This feeling is amazing.
He just moves his tail around.
Ne?
He moves it around like this, a cute little nyan-nyan.
That's right, isn't it?
Irritates me. (lol)
(lol)
Then this face close-up.
That face close-up.
This, you know.
Right, that.
When he moves his tail around like this, is he actually trying to convey something?
No, not at all. Actually, that probably comes down to the people who draw or decide on the art for those cuts.
Ah~
Heee~ Ah, is that so.
But, right now when he says "That is interesting" and such while moving his tail,
Ne?
it's like "I wonder if it moves when tension gets a bit higher."
See, for cats, it's true for my own cat too, when they're irritated they'll "bang bang bang" their tails and such,
Mm.
Right, right, right, right, right.
or when they're like "I wonder what to do," their tail will go "fuyo!" up and such. So...
I was thinking, "Amazing, they took that sort of thing into account too," or something.
You know, for me, this kind of eye close-up is amazing.
Ne~?
Right.
Then, the editing has this sort of tawny feel to it.
Ah, that's right, isn't it.
Ah, right, right, right.
When we first began this work, we had quite a few ideas which looked different. [more CG-ish, probably]
That's different now. By now there are a lot of things that have a more "drawn" feeling.
Yes.
Those kind of touches were inserted by Kishida-san, the character designer.
Somehow, for things you'd say are in a hand-drawn style... Well, it's true here too...
Ah, right.
Somehow, the art has a feeling of being sketchy, doesn't it?
Mmm.
That's right.
That's another point of warmth.
It has a bit of a "sepia" feeling.
Mm, right.
It has that kind of feeling.
Thanks.
For that area, we asked staff of other works; it was rather difficult to obtain a unity throughout.
I see!
Yeah.
Is that right!
Then...
I see.
Depending on what episode you're overseeing, how you view who the characters are will vary greatly, won't it?
Mm!
That's right, yes, yes, yes.
Somehow, it's true for their standpoints and such as well...
Yeah.
So in that case, facial expressions also really differ between episodes.
If people who drew for episode 1 saw an episode around this part,
"Eh!? What's this? They're totally different people!" is what they would think.
It's to such an extent.
Things would be different~
The shape changes, doesn't it? Of this story.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think for that area, keeping balance must be incredibly troublesome.
Mm.
But, um, especially for people who draw, umm, an episode...
For example, working on ep1, then afterward, something like ep5...
It must feel disjointed, right? Without seeing all of it.
That's right. Yes, yes.
So, do you have to explain things regarding that, such as "This is done in this manner" or "The world has become like this"?
Well, that is a producer's job.
Ah, I see.
Yeah. Like Miyamoto-san, the Series Director's.
He'd do that instead, you know.
Taniguchi-san, do you look at the overall flow of conversations and say, "Don't do this kind of expression now,"
Yes.
"Do this with a more sorrowful feeling," or "Make this less sorrowful"?
Do you strive to reach that kind of balance?
That's right, um, deciding on various things regarding CG or facial expressions of cuts.
Ohhh.
Heee~
But those are also trial cuts, right?
I mean, for speech—
Well, one by one they become different.
Right.
I think this for our acting too, but what words were written, or how to say them, completely changed, so...
Being able to piece all of that together from those "trials" requires an amazing sense of balance.
Ne? It's amazing, truly.
Really, the facial expressions have become completely different compared to my first time seeing them.
Hee~
That's right, isn't it?
Somehow, kind of... (lol)
There are a lot of characters, aren't there?
Yeah.
Who was the hardest person?
Ahhh!
Mm.
The hardest...
That piques my interest!
Hitomi, I believe.
Oh~ Eh, so it's that.
Her eyelashes are big (lol)
(lol)
Ahhh!
As far as drawing goes, she completely changes – the person who changes the most.
The character with the largest rate of change there. Yeah.
Obtaining uniformity for that area was a little difficult.
I see.
Ne?
Then, conversely, easier characters to draw?
Ah, eh... Homura, I believe.
Ah, is that so?
That's right.
Oh, why is that?
Nah, somehow... Um...
A cool character has a lot of outside influence which help decide how to draw facial expressions.
Ah, that's right, I was told "We'll leave it to you" often.
I see!
Certainly.
Really, for such a cool character, or a character that you believe doesn't get shaken up very much,
"There will be a lot of facial expressions" is something I really thought for Homura.
Ao-chan, you've said that too, right?
Right, somehow, in episode one when Madoka is in disarray... she's actually in disarray and has a squeakiness to her, right?
I think that is amazing.
It has this kind of design, but you can still do those expressions, amazing...
Really.
Regarding the people who draw, there are a lot of them who like to draw cool facial expressions.
Ah I see!
Parts like those gloomy eyes.
Ah, but, certainly... especially for Homura-chan, whatever she does is always cool. (lol)
That's right, huh?
(lol)
Somehow, those angles when she's agitated are quite scary, huh?
And then, when she turns around, too.
Right, right, right, right.
Since her hair is so long, it turns into such an intense drawing! Like right here.
Right!
Ah! Finally, right here... in front of someone else, she said "Madoka."
Right—Right! That's right, isn't it.
This episode left a huge impression on me.
There's a lot that happens in conversation too, but...
Homura, up until now, has kept how shaken up she is a secret inside of her.
Finally - SHE GETS TOTALLY SHAKEN UP!
Right, right.
Other people see it, actually.
Totally shaken up~
I mean, there's the part coming up where the feelings she holds regarding Madoka finally come out...
Well, her feelings begin to be more at the front.
That's right, ne.
Yeah.
Gradually.
I, um, personally... well, coming this far, Ao-chan and I like Kyouko-tan...
How is it to draw a straightforward girl such as Kyouko?
Right, well, Kyouko is another character who was easy to draw.
She's somewhat of a standard character.
There's a direct connection, right? Between her feelings and facial expressions.
Ahh, right.
Mm.
Mmm.
Kyouko~♥
Kyouko, you know, when she comes, it's very calming.
Kyouko, so relieving, Kyouko~
Ah... ha~♥
She's the character who'll mostly appear at any place, right?
She's human, isn't she? Extremely.
Right.
The fact that she thinks humans can be good,
that part of Kyouko-tan is relieving.
I love what happens right after this.
This "Khan!" thing she does.
Right? This, ne~
I think it's very girly.
Ne?
Actually is.
Then, um, sort of...
This very "real" topic begins.
Right, um...
Super extravagant hosts.
It really drives me crazy.
AHHHHHHhhhhhhh! (lol)
"With pleasure" they say.
It's "With pleasure."
Right, right.
كا كا شى أماه دي ما
That's right, um... Miki Shinchirou-san and Tobita-san are both amazing.
Miki Shinchirou-san and Tobita [Nobuo]-san are the voice actors for these hosts.
Ne?
Amazing!
Really.
Tsuruoka-san went this far to put his hand into this work, it really moves me. I've said to Tsuruoka-san:
"Tsuruoka-san has such fighting spirit!"
Calling in these two to play the roles of these hosts... I think it's amazing.
Mm.
Right, right, I really think so too.
Ne~?
But somehow, since I didn't think that would be the case, somehow...
When I saw the cast list, it was like "Mm?" ... "Mm!?" (lol)
That's right, it's quite tight-knit, isn't it? The workplace had a very tight-knit feeling to it...
That's right, ne.
In the workplace there are a lot of girls, so overall everyone understands [each other]...
Ah, that's right, ne.
Yes, yes.
So it was really very tightly knit.
Ah, right, at the workplace where you draw scenes, that kind of...
Does the atmosphere and such change because of the members?
Ahhh... Well, actually, work from home is pretty common. Yeah, yeah.
Ah, that's piques my interest.
Eh? Is that so?
Is that so?
So, you have your own kind of nature around you.
Yes, yes.
Not working with other people very often... isn't very unusual.
It doesn't have that feeling at all.
Yeah.
Mm.
mm, mm.
Well, especially in this work, the manual labor parts [are done at home].
Ah, that's right, huh?
For times like that...
You have to gradually track the people down, don't you?
That would certainly be true for the current sekaikan.
"No! No! I don't want to come out!"
(lol)
Yeah. But, the atmosphere at the actual workplace is...
Hmm.
I'd have to say there's a lot of guys.
Ehhh.
I feel like guys draw girls cuter than girls do.
That's right, ne.
Yeah.
They're surely able to recognize the cute parts of girls, aren't they?
Mm, mm.
They really get that sort of thing.
Somehow (lol)
Really, starting from this point, he really sticks to his agenda...
ヽ(`Д´)ﾉ Q—BUAIIIIIIIII~
Somehow, just like this, there's a lot of scenes where they just stop, aren't there?
Where a character or situation stops, and they just think for a bit.
For times like this, are you cautious about...
Well, I always think "Ah, the visuals are moving about," like different objects are moving, but...
Do you put a lot of thought into balance for those "other items" on screen too?
Right, that is lumped together in content, with CG.
Yeah.
Well, if everything just stopped, that'd be weird.
Mmm.
Then, for example, right now this water fountain - the color keeps shifting about.
Somehow doesn't that display her - Madoka's - emotions?
Emotions.
Right, right. Yeah.
I think that this is just such a complete work of art.
Ne~?
I can really feel that, you know.
Mm, somehow, for us there is a lot to think about, since we hear a lot of things...
We think about many things with a "doing the drama ourselves"-style feeling...
This art of drama is truly amazing, I feel very fortunate for being able to do this work.
Mmm!
Mmm.
So just like here... When humans think of or say things, how will they move after that?
It makes you think about every day observations.
Mmm.
Ah, that's right, um...
Well, we wanted you to observe things unintentionally in this scene.
Ah, but we might see that!
(lol)
That's right, that's right.
(Ah, shaki)
(｀・ω・´) ｼｬｷｰﾝ
(｀・ω・´) ｼｬｷｰﾝ (Shakiin)
This is a term / emote that is used when tension is rising.
I cannot give you the origin or a literal TL of "Shakiin" itself, as I do not know it. It seems that it may have originated from a Japanese TV show of the same name, or it's just a sound effect.
(｀・ω・´) ｼｬｷｰﾝ
Suddenly shakiin (lol)
Really, when it comes time to draw the drama, you can't read too much of it yourself.
Yeah.
Then, those who feel it stronger are the animators... as they are able to watch it.
Ahh, I see.
Yeah.
I see. That's right, everyone is amazing.
Right, right.
Not just humans, but even this type of animal-thing, they're able to depict it well...
That's right, isn't it.
Here it comes!
It's come!
＼GOOD SHOT!／
Yup it's come~
Tonight, she'll do a little bit of an attack, though...
The lights have become red. (lol)
Right.
Ahh!
Ne?
You know, the Homura right here, I really love her~
And Madoka's surprised face she's making here is also amazing.
Right...
(lol) I'm looking at QB.
(lol)
Despite that, Madoka can just stay sitting there. Amazing.
Right here she finally really explodes...
Mmm.
Mm.
She does, but...
I hadn't done any crying up until now, so I was very surprised...
But, what is it, when acting as her, my voice just wouldn't come out.
Mmm...
Mm.
Mm...
Somehow, ne... her emotions are too heavy. If this were real, it'd be like:
"WHAT DO I DO!?" is the kind of feeling it'd have, since it hurts so much...
Then she loses all of her strength, and is unable to stand.
Mmm.
For acting out this girl—It was even properly written in the script,
"There might be people out there that think this is because she's run out of power, but..."
"That isn't the case, instead she's this type of girl."
she tries and tries, then goes "Waaah!", then "Ahhh," and loses her strength.
Right...
When she loses her footing, the girl's weak parts come out...
This scene left a very large impression on me.
Mm. Now, she says her name for the first time.
Right. Right.
She shouts it.
That's right.
But you know, somehow, it's like it reaches her yet it doesn't reach her.
Then she screams out "MADOKAAAAAA!" when normally she wouldn't call that out...
Right.
Mmm.
This girl's weakness.
I love the facial expression right after this, too.
This you know, who was it, I wonder, during interviews...
I'm asked, "Since expression doesn't change too much, does Madoka have drama?"
I think, "No, no, no."
The biggest enemy in front of them, is the sudden "fate of a girl."
Tdhe biggest enemy in front of them, is the sudden fate of a girl."
Actually, I think it was properly done.
This strength of a girl. And, this sort of general expectation—
(lol) This.
(lol) This guy.
Frustrating me! (lol)
The way this guy moves (lol)
(lol)
So, the fact that even though this was written by guy[s], I thought it was able to achieve such portrayal of girls...
Ne~?
Ne? That's right.
Mmm.
Right.
It has a lot of that, doesn't it, Ao-chan?
It's there. It's definitely there.
That's right, somehow, Homura-chan is...
Amazing!
She's constantly straining and straining, and even though at first she kept her distance...
But when Madoka's confidence is lacking just a little bit—
It's not yet different; In this world, it's still impossible, isn't it?
Right–Right.
Ne?
Right.
Somehow, even when she's in a situation where she can't avoid balancing the importance of two different people,
Madoka is always helping another stand.
For this part right here, umm, I want to say "Sorry!"
"I'm sorry, but I have to go to Sayaka-chan."
Now, the name "Incubator" has finally been revealed.
Right! That's right, ne.
"Incubator" is—
Um, fukaki.
It means that.
Right, right, right.
It means to incubate an egg.
To incubate!
Then, that was actually also included in QB's design, wasn't it?
That's right.
The round circle on his back...
There's an egg on his back.
Um.
That's an e–egg.
Ah, r–right, that's right.
Right.
That's right.
(lol) I didn't know.
Somehow, what is it... um, a small animal, and an egg.
That's right, an incubator. When we were saying incubator once...
Ahh.
For that, Ume-sensei was like "Ah, I can't say!"
Yes.
"can't say!"
(lol)
Right.
So for the people listening to commentary now...
It's like "I'm sorry we burdened you."
It was actually that.
Well, well, when you say egg!
It's like that feeling now, isn't it?
It's like that!
It's like that~
From an egg comes:
(lol)
Ne?
This part, you know, is another thing... It's Sayaka, though...
It's moving...
No more, no more, around this episode, seriously...
No more~
It gets really sad, though.
The visuals too... Um, the scenery gets mostly dark now, doesn't it? From around here on out.
That's right, ne.
It's true for that evening scene earlier too, though...
Were the most disjointed things characters?
The world is.
D–Disjointed?
Ah, 'cause see, a lot of different people are drawing, so...
Somehow or another the background locations can be more easily dispersed among—
Ah, that was also there, yes.
Ah, that was really there?
Some number of people were working on that.
Ohh... Ah. Is that so?
They were doing that.
Eh~
That's right, this is coming now...
Ah!
Ne, that "really idiot" just now, sheesh~
(lol)
Really...
It's sad...
T–This "bang!" makes me think of her rejection,
it hurts so much that there's no helping it...
That's right~
Iya...
Ah...
Just this, it's like people start to fall into tragedy more little by little, ne?
Mm.
Ah, it's like a mermaid.
Mm!
Heh~
It's come.
Jeez, another thing may be coming with this line.
Yes~
Hah...
Mm.
This was a theme from the beginning, I think? Surely.
Ah, I wonder about that (lol)
This.
This...
Ahhh...
Right!
"Just now, you narrowed your eyes, right!?" (lol)
Ne!?
"I thought you didn't have feelings!?"
Ahh–
Finally, the secret of mahou shoujo is...
That's right, ne.
This line is quite amazing, isn't it?
Amazing.
Then, I'd like to ask Taniguchi-san a question!
That's right.
We're already at the ending...
Yes.
Taniguchi-san, for this piece of work...
In what sort of way do you see this work, or what do you take away from it?
Mm, right.
Well, personally, I've done mahou shoujo things in the past, but...
Yes.
Mm.
But this one has a completely different point of view.
And it became a work with such a huge headquarters.
That's right, ne.
Yeah.
Entering from the outset, I didn't think that'd happen.
Mm. There are a lot of voices and feelings.
Ah... It's amazing, isn't it.
Ahhh.
Yeah. Although we aren't done yet.
Ah, that's right. Even now it's receiving high praise.
Everyone is in a working state.
People are still working.
Ne, really... but somehow, all the way until the end, everyone is crafting this so throughly,
I have a ton of confidence in this work.
Because every individual really gave it their all.
Mm.
Mm!
That's what I think, ne~
Ne?
Then umm, Shaft's immediate responses.
Mm!
That's right, ne.
I know it.
That's right. Truly~
Yes (lol)
Amazing.
Okay, then we're done, volume 4 is over.
Yes.
Yup, volume 4 is over, sending you off is...
Yuuki Aoi and—Saitou Chiwa, and—Yeah. Taniguchi and—
Ah, Ta— Who else is there?
(lol)
Right, "everyone!"
Ah, yes, thank you.
Yes, thank you very much!
Yes! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
(lol)