This is a simple thing to do if you understand the method.
With this, I don't feel like I'll lose.
I'll give it to you.
That thing was your goal, right?
Oi...
Since I don't want to be indebted to you...
this makes us even. That's good.
Okay, let's go home, Madoka.
Sayaka-chan...
Ah, sorry...
I'm a bit tired.
Don't push yourself. Hold on to me.
That idiot.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it again here?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away however many times necessary as I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 8
I'm... Really an Idiot
Today's service has ended.
Sayaka-chan...
You shouldn't use that kind of fighting style.
Saying that it isn't painful is a lie.
Just watching you was painful.
You're fine getting injuries since you can't feel them...
That sort of thing is no good!
I have to do that sort of thing or else I won't win.
Since I have no natural talent, you know.
If you fight with that kind of style, then even if you win,
it won't be in your best interest, Sayaka-chan.
What is "in my best interest"?
After I've been given this kind of form, what would you say is in my best interest?
Sayaka-chan...
You know, for me right now... Killing witches. I have no purpose except just that.
I'm a stone.
I only appear to be alive by moving a dead body.
For a thing such as my best interest, what would you say someone could do?
Isn't it meaningless to even consider?
But I... want to know how I can make you happy, Sayaka-chan.
If that's the case, then you should fight.
I heard it from Kyubey.
You have more natural talent than anyone else, right?
Without any of the hardships that someone like myself goes through, you could beat witches easily, right?
I...
That's...
If you're saying you want to do something in my best interest, then start by trying to put yourself in the same position as me.
Impossible, right? Of course it is.
You wouldn't cease to be human merely out of sympathy, right?
It isn't sympathy or anything! That's...
Although you could accomplish everything, you do nothing, and in your place I have to go through this experience.
You put yourself on a pedestal and play innocent, so don't say things like "I understand."
Sayaka-chan...
Don't come with me.
I'm an idiot...
What a thing to say...
There's no way to save me now...
Akemi        Homura
I predict that Walpurgis Night will appear within this range.
What's your basis?
Statistics.
Statistics?
I haven't heard of anything like a Walpurgis coming to this city before.
Really, just what exactly is the source of your statistics?
Neither of us could be called anything like a trustworthy manga hero, but y'know...
Wouldn't it be all right to show a bit more of the cards you hold?
That is something I, too, would certainly like to ask of you.
Akemi Homura.
Why are you showing your face around here? You...
Well, well! Does that mean I'm an uninvited guest?
I came tonight to notify you of information that both of you will find important, though.
Hah?
Miki Sayaka is exhausting herself faster than expected.
It isn't just her magical power usage.
A curse has begun to form inside of her.
Whose fault do you think that is, exactly?
If it continues at this rate, it may become troublesome before Walpurgis Night arrives.
You should act in a cautious manner.
What is that? What does that mean?
Instead of me, what if you ask her?
If it's you, then you should already know, right? Akemi Homura.
Just as I thought.
Where did you obtain that information? I'm quite interested.
Are you...
I have heard what you want to ask.
Vanish.
You'll let that guy be?
Killing that thing won't result in any solution at all.
More importantly, Miki Sayaka.
Just what is the "trouble" that guy was talking about?
Her Soul Gem has accumulated too much impurity.
It must be purified quickly, or else it will result in an irrecoverable situation.
Akemi        Homura
The auxiliary verb "must" means something that you are absolutely duty-bound to do.
However, if it's "have to", then you're pushed...
When you are expressing a general duty for one person, if "must" is used, it represents an individualistic sense of responsibility...
At that time... Even if chasing her was forbidden, I should have...
But still, Shizuki-san, you return home in this direction?
Up until now, it's like I haven't seen you return home this way...
That's correct. It's actually in the completely opposite direction.
Then... why today?
Kamijou-kun,
I have something I'd like to say to you.
Eh?
She hasn't come home? Since yesterday? That's...
Yes. Um... I understand.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Sayaka-chan...
I have to search for her.
Why don't you understand?
Since you simply lack the necessary surplus, aim only for witches.
Shut up.
Thanks for the big, unnecessary help.
Your Soul Gem is already at its limit.
You must purify it immediately.
Use this.
What are you scheming this time?
I have had enough.
You're no longer in a situation where you can doubt people, are you?
Do you find it that unpleasant to be given help?
I'm going to be a different type of magical girl than all of you.
That's what I decided.
I'd find it unpleasant to befriend those who would do something like abandon and use someone.
I don't need a reimbursement or anything.
I'm the only one who'll absolutely never use magic for her own benefit.
You... are going to die.
If I were to die, it'd simply mean that my time to kill witches would be over.
In short, my use would come to an end.
That's fine, then.
This world doesn't need someone like me if I can't beat witches.
Hey, why?
I only want to save you.
Why won't you place your trust in me?
I wonder why...
Somehow, I simply understand, you know.
That you are a liar.
Your eyes look like they've given up on anything and everything.
You always speak empty words.
That's even true right now.
You say things like "It's for your benefit,"
but in truth you're thinking of something completely different, right?
You can't completely deceive me. Not like that.
Just like that, you torment Madoka more and more.
Isn't Madoka unrelated?
No. Anything and everything is for that girl's sake.
You are sharp.
Yes, you hit the mark.
I don't want to help you.
I just don't want Madoka to witness your ruined appearance.
If you decline me here, you're just going to die anyway.
If you're going to bring Madoka any further sorrow...
I would rather...
...with this hand...
...kill you right now.
Miki Sayaka.
Oi! Hurry up and escape!
Are you insane?
Weren't you going to help her?
Let go.
I get it.
So if I'm holding on to you like this, it means you can't use that unusual technique?
Wha—
Damn it.
You can't let 'em make an excuse or anything.
You need to keep close tabs on the full sum of their earned income.
Women are idiots, after all. That's why if they possess even a little bit of wealth, they'll immediately use it on something worthless.
Man, seriously. You can't treat women like humans, you know.
When you think of them as dogs or something, you have to discipline them, yeah.
She'll be delighted about that too.
If you say, "I'll punch you in the face!" then they'll almost always fall silent, man.
Pft. If you neglect them even a little bit, they'll instantly become spoiled and start saying stuff like they wanna "become family."
It's a forbidden thing to pamper 'em.
Man... In 10 years, a cabaret girl like her will be working for the same amount of money as she is now.
She needs to understand her own limits, yeah?
They're really annoying when you throw them away too, you know...
You're so skilled in that area, Shou-san, that it's enviable.
I need to follow your example too—
Hey, let me hear more about that person.
Excuse me?
About the woman you guys were talking about just now...
Let me hear more details.
Ojou-chan, are you a middle school student?
It isn't good to be out playing at night.
That person found you important, so she tried her best to please you, right?
And you even understood that, right?
Yet now she's the same as a dog?
You won't say thanks?
She's useless now, so you'll throw her away?
What's with this person? Someone you know?
N–No...
Hey... does this world have value worth protecting?
For what purpose was I fighting?
Tell me.
Right now. You tell me.
Otherwise, I'll...
Sayaka-chan, where are you...
Do you resent me too, I wonder?
If I resented you, could that return Sayaka-chan to how she originally was?
Impossible. My power is not extensive enough to do that.
Hey... that time, when you said that I "could become an amazing magical girl."
Was that... true?
Saying something like "amazing" is a humble way to put it.
You'd become a ridiculous magical girl.
Perhaps the strongest in this world.
If I had accepted the task instead of Sayaka-chan, I wonder if she would've ended up becoming a magical girl.
Sayaka achieved her own wish.
Concerning that point, Madoka, you're not related at all.
Why is someone like me...
I cannot comprehend that either.
To say it clearly, the latent power hidden within yourself
is on the scale of something that is theoretically impossible.
Even I, too, want someone to explain it.
Is that so?
If the power within you were to be unlocked, creating a miracle would be nothing,
as I believe even distorting the laws of the universe would be possible.
Why are you the one single person who possesses characteristics to that extent?
I do not yet understand the reason.
I...
thought of my lowly self as someone who had no redeeming qualities.
I'd surely go on forever without benefiting or helping anyone else.
I thought I'd simply be living for some reason or another until the end.
That was something frustrating and lonely, but... I still thought, "It can't be helped."
That's considerably different from reality, you know.
Madoka, if you desire it, you may be able to become an omnipotent god.
If it's me...
Kyubey, if it's me, I wonder if I could accomplish things that even you can't do.
So that means...?
If I formed a contract with you, could I return Sayaka-chan's body back to its original state?
I believe something of that level would surely be of no difficulty for you.
In your eyes, is that wish something worth offering your soul for?
If it's for Sayaka-chan's benefit, it's fine.
I'll become a magical girl—
A–Awful!
No matter what, you don't need to kill...
You...
Why do you always... sacrifice yourself like that?
Saying things like you've never helped, or there's no point to you...
Don't just decide you're inferior on your own...
Think about the people who consider you precious too!
I have had enough!
If you were lost, there are people who'd be sad...
Why don't you realize that!?
What will become of the people who protect you!?
Homura-chan...
Have we, somewhere...
Have we met somewhere before? With me...
That is...
Sorry...
I have to search for Sayaka-chan.
Wait...
Miki Sayaka is already...
I'm sorry.
Wait...
Madoka!
Even though you know it's futile...
You just don't learn your lesson, do you?
There are as many replacements as necessary, but meaninglessly crushing one is still troubling, you know.
Isn't it wasteful?
This makes two times that you've killed me, but...
Thanks to that, I can see the special characteristics of your attack.
That was time-manipulation magic, right? Just before.
Just as I thought.
Somehow I had a guess, but...
You're not a human being from this time axis, are you?
Your true character and your plan... I know everything.
I see.
That's the reason why you've been going so far to get in my way.
You would go that far for your desire to change Kaname Madoka's fate?
Yes.
I absolutely will not allow things to go according to your plan.
Kyubey.
No... Incubator.
Finally found you...
Hey you, how long are you going to keep being stubborn?
I'm sorry that I took away your time.
What's that?
This isn't like you, is it?
Yeah.
That's because I don't particularly care anymore, you know.
In the end, I... Just what exactly did I find precious, and what was I protecting?
Nothing at all has any reason anymore.
Oi...
"Hope and despair balance out to reach equilibrium and become zero..."
There was one time, right? That you said that.
If it's now, I understand that very well.
I certainly did save some number of people, but...
But, in proportion to that, resentment and jealousy accumulated in my heart.
I even hurt my most precious friend's feelings.
Sayaka! You couldn't be...!
To counteract a prayer for someone's happiness, someone else has to be cursed.
We magical girls are structured in that kind of way, aren't we?
I'm... really an idiot.
Sayaka!!!
In this country, women in the middle of growing to adulthood are called "girls," right?
Well then, for those of you who will become witches before long...
魔法少女(Mahou Shoujo) = Magical Girl
魔女(Majo) = Witch
You should be called "magical girls," shouldn't you?
Someday, the light of love that has lit within your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
(will pass through time)
(時を超えて)
A single dream belonging to the ruined world will certainly
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ
(be destroyed, I hope)
(壊すだろう)
Drinking every last drop of hesitation, what is the thing that you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Does such a greedy aspiration have course in an evanescent tomorrow?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
Like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was a child
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
I want to meet you, with the power to crush even darkness with a smile
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Inside these frightened hands lies the courage of a plucked flower
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
I rely only on my emotions for everything
想いだけが頼る全て
The light will awaken the wish.
光を呼び覚ます願い
I don't know if you think I'm an idiot, but...
As for me, y'know... Whether or not she can really be saved...
Until we ascertain that, I don't want to give up.
Episode 9
I Wouldn't Forgive That Sort of Thing
I wouldn't forgive that sort of thing.
Subtitle notes, runes, and extras @ http://tri4.net