Eh? How do I lose weight?
I haven't gone on a diet before.
Seriously? Even though you're so thin?
We're going.
Yeah.
My body has never been very prone to gaining weight.
So it's predisposition?
That's so nice... I'm jealous.
Kawashima is so into being the central figure among the girls, isn't she?
Yeah.
If you push yourself too hard, you'll get stressed.
I think you should eat what you want, just eat healthily.
I can't pretend that I didn't hear that!
W-What is this about?
W-What are you doing?
Wait... let me go!
What is it?
Come on, come on, come on...
Sensei! Kawashima's hiding meat in her stomach!
We're only allowed to bring 300 yen worth of meat on the field trip!
Is this 300 yen worth of meat?
Bananas can't be considered meat!
This is the meat buns' portion.
This is the high grade ice cream's.
This is the American hot dog's potion!
Take this, Convenience Store Fist of Truth!
We devote this to the diet warriors who perished with the star dust.
Yeah.
Well then.
The Convenience Store Fist of Truth is strong indeed!
No, it was a difficult opponent!
Those two...
Are you alright, Ami-chan?
They're really cruel.
I feel bad for you.
Um...
This is the calm before the storm, huh.
Oh, so if they do this, this is how Ami gets.
Doing that all of a sudden, they're so mean!
Eh?
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, yet complicated and mysterious
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
onkou tokujitsu ECCENTRIC na anata
You, who's gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PURE PARAATO
A naive preparation
atama no naka wa junjou PURE PAREEDO
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
True Self
Ah, that's refreshing.
As expected of Minorin, this was a job neatly done.
Female bonding... is pretty scary.
As a diet warrior, I can't just sit by and watch.
We must face the fat directly,
and certainly, the God of Weight Loss will smile upon us.
Surely, she as well will understand this one day.
Ah, so that's how it is.
Who's that guy?
That's right.
Ryuuji.
I'll make you salad for dinner tonight.
Y-You are making it?
I learned how when I was in elementary school.
I can make the dressing by myself too.
I have to buy lettuce, right?
Then you pull it apart, right?
Then you cut it up, right?
And then you put it on the plate, right?
Look! It's done.
The lettuce isn't washed,
and it's not rinsed off either.
Where did the dressing go?
You nag too much about minor details, sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law...
Takasu-kun!
W-What is it, Kawashima?
I beg you, can you accompany me for a while?
Huh?
That guy... just now...
Hey, Kawashi-
You...
Hey, how long are you guys sticking together?
Completely ignoring my existence,
and sticking so closely, so closely, so closely, so closely...
Hey, Taiga. Just now was...
I'm scared, Takasu-kun!
You indecent girl!
Hey, Kawashima. What was with the guy just now?
It isn't someone you know?
Y-Yeah.
As a model, things like this do happen sometimes.
Being harassed by fans.
Even when I specially transferred schools...
Hey, you guys are going home right now, aren't you?
Yeah.
Can you let me hide in your house for a while?
If I see him again, I'll be scared...
I see.
If it's this, leave it all to me.
Huh?
A drafty wooden rental home...
Or a safe high class condo with auto-lock function.
Which one do you want to choose?
High class condo!
It's decided then.
Come to my house then.
Huh? Wait a minute.
Why do I have to go to your house?
It's okay, I won't force you.
Even though I can easily trespass into Ryuuji's home, so security is obviously a problem.
Eh?
It's okay, it has nothing to do with me anyway.
W-Wait, Aisaka-san.
I told you to wait for me, you little brat!
Oh well, this is fine too.
Here you go.
Sweet!
It's the honey-pickled kumquat that Ryuuji made in bulk.
I even added a little soda.
In any case, it's too strong.
Good grief, letting me drink something like this.
And you say you're a diet warrior.
Is your brain as small as you are?
You're completely changed, aren't you?
I can't wait to let the whole class see your true self.
What true self?
I've no plans to show it to others.
I see.
So, after drinking the honey-pickled kumquat juice,
your throat should be in its best condition, right?
Huh?
Not planning to show your true self?
Then let me see the fake that you created yourself.
Thoroughly, okay?
Oh, good morning.
Good morning...
Kawashima, you looked tired.
I can't get rid of the fatigue from yesterday.
Yeah, that was scary for you, wasn't it?
It's not that...
In Aisaka Taiga's condo...
Five hours like that...
No, it's six hours...
What did Taiga do?
Jackson.
Huh?
Uganda.
Ugan... da?
Falco.
Akechi Mitsuhide.
Matsumoto Seichou.
Oda Nobunaga enthusiastically singing a French song.
Dazai Osamu carrying out an ambush attack personally.
And then, Amaterasu being completely sealed up!
Hey, are you alright, Kawashima?
That's right, I made her do it.
150 rapid-fire impressions.
It's the best when she got all fired up.
An Akechi Mitsuhide impression or something...
I've no idea how you managed to do it.
She obeyed me when I said
"If you don't listen, I'm throwing you out."
You're too harsh.
No, I'm grateful to you, Aisaka.
Kitamura?
Kitamura-kun?!
Aisaka, I have a favour to ask you.
Ami-chan, you don't look well.
Is it really okay not to go to the infirmary?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Y-Yo...
Come here, stupid Chihuahua.
It's feeding time.
Stupid Chihuahua...
I'm clearly referring to you, aren't I?
Acting cute, always barking, and to make things worse, you always seem to be in heat.
Enough already, come with me.
You've gotta be kidding.
Why do I have to be with someone like you?
I've already promised my friends...
Michael Jackson being a bus tour guide.
Mona Lisa going around a corner at 200 kilometres per hour.
A happy The Thinker.
The photographs that I took have all been copied.
They might just be leaked accidentally.
Wait, don't do that!
Okay, I got it. I'll go, okay?
Damn you!
Um, Ami-chan?
Sorry!
Um... I forgot that I promised to have lunch together with Aisaka-san today.
I'm really sorry.
Hold it there!
Itadakimasu!
Itadakimasu.
What the hell is this?
By using her fake mask to deal with things,
no matter how long it may last,
Ami will not be able to make true friends.
That's why I'm begging you guys, who know her true nature.
Even if you say that,
I'm fine with it...
But Taiga and Kawashima don't really get along...
Aisaka.
I beg you. You are one of the only few female friends who I can entrust things to.
Like I said...
Thank you, Aisaka!
That Kitamura is pushing all the troubling stuff to us,
and ran off to the Student Council meeting by himself.
Whoa, Kushieda's lunch box is wonderful.
Although it looks big, this lunch box is super low in calories.
Look, this is king trumpet mushroom.
This is konjac.
And this is strip konjac rice.
Really, why do I have to...
Here, Ami. I'll give you the kelp.
I said I don't want it.
Is that so?
That's nice.
Ah, no.
Well then, lunch box, lunch box.
Huh? Takasu-kun's lunch box...
Why are the dishes the same as that of Aisaka-san's?
Hey, why?
No, um...
This is because...
It isn't a problem now, right?
My lunch box consists of fried egg roll and stir fried vegetables.
Ryuuji's lunch box is just rice.
My side dishes!
Here, Takasu's will be a meatball lunch box with this.
Thank you.
Why are you letting Aisaka-san do as she pleases?
A-Am I?
Ryuuji was my dog in his previous life.
Serving the master, is a dog's happiness.
That's right, they're destined for each other.
It's not, it's not.
Geez, Minorin, you're at it again.
Sorry. This is just a joke, a joke.
Geez.
Hey, can I have your attention please?
Today is the monthly voluntary Neighbourhood Clean-up organized by the Student Council.
But not many people signed up...
Are there any brave heroes who'd like to participate?
Sorry, Kitamura.
There's a special sale at the Kanoya Supermarket today.
Takasu, you're willing to help?
Well then, get to the school yard after you've changed.
Really, why do I have to go?
Like I said, I'll be responsible and participate with you.
Even when you're saying that,
you're just thinking of being together with Kitamura a little more, aren't you?
You're right.
You're really honest, huh?
Takasu-kun, I'll come too.
Having just transferred, I want to get used to this school.
Minorin.
As a diet warrior,
I've got to be a girl exercising her body with all her might in order to slim down,
and I just can't sit this out.
I said I didn't come to slim down, didn't I?
Let's do our best, Takasu-kun.
Y-Yeah.
Alright, you punks.
Time to raise your spirits!
You better not slack off, scoundrels!
Hey, hey, calm down.
Have you gotten your working gloves on?
Have you brought the trash bags?
Have you confirmed your cleaning areas?
Yes!
Don't underestimate this city.
If you go out there like that, you'll get thrown off this ship, you punks!
Show me your fighting spirit!
Yes!
As expected of the President after all.
Okay, then let me brief you on the arrangement. First is...
In the end, Kitamura went along with the people from the Student Council.
Sorry, the officers are wanting to go on a different route.
Then why did I...
Hey, isn't this piece of trash just like Aisaka-san?
Especially on the trait of being so helplessly small.
Then, this trash is just like Kawashima-san.
With its sodden, depraved, flabby qualities.
Let's go, Minorin.
Eloping? I don't mind that.
Let's go, let's go.
The trash is waiting for us.
There they go.
As partners who were both abandoned, let's pick up litter together.
Eh? Um...
Picking litter is pretty fun, isn't it?
Ah, I wonder if it's because I'm together with Takasu-kun?
Kawashima, well...
Hey, let's go over there this time.
Be careful!
Hey, are you alrigh-
Ugh, disgusting.
What's this?
What the hell is this?
Kawashima?
Ah, it gave me a fright.
Geez, now my shoe is all wet.
Kawashima, don't move.
No, no, no, no!
Get away!
It climbed on!
Don't kick my face!
Damn. Okay, salvage!
It's alright now.
Look, the frog went home too. Okay?
I don't want to do this anymore!
Eh?
Ka-Kawashima?
Just kidding.
Did you believe it?
It's raining.
Ah, no. We're going to get wet.
We've got to take shelter, right, Takasu-
Look here.
Isn't it enough already?
Eh?
What are you saying? I don't get what you mean.
I get it even less.
Why would you force yourself to participate in such an annoying chore?
You don't get it?
So this approach is useless against Takasu-kun...
Trying to smooth over your fake mask,
I've seen through it long ago.
You have to be more... how do I put it...
That's right, show your true self.
I can't be without this mask.
You don't understand my feelings, right?
Yeah, honestly speaking...
It's fine like that.
Look, I'm a natural airhead.
Kawashima?
What's wrong?
Hey, Kawashima!
Hey, what's wrong with you?
If you want to take shelter from the rain...
Hey, what are you doing?
That guy was yesterday's...
Why?
If I say it bluntly, that guy...
...is a stalker.
S...
Why didn't you tell me?
Because...
It's frustrating...
Frustrating?
I don't want to admit it.
Having my life messed up by that kind of person.
It's his fault that I had to move.
I didn't want to bring my parents trouble.
So I came here alone, and imposed on my relatives.
I also decided to take a break from modelling.
But, being chased by that scum even when I came here...
Takasu-kun! Kawashima-san!
Hey!
That's weird. We definitely heard that they came to this area.
Let's forget it and go home, Minorin.
I found a cute mini-sized ghost!
Super cute. Lucky!
Ghost, you say?
Taiga!
Watch out!
I don't want to be called a ghost by someone as suspicious as you.
No way, what is she trying to do?
Her opponent is a stalker.
In the first place, who gave you the permission to take the photographs?
You're disgusting me.
It doesn't matter, right? It's not a big deal.
Of course it matters.
I'm going to destroy that camera together with its owner!
What are you running for?
Hold it there!
Wait a minute, Taiga!
That idiot...
Why...
Why isn't she scared?
That guy is obviously a pervert.
Kawashima?
Unlike me, being forced to stop work by that scum,
moving over here and even transferring schools.
Getting so irritated and stressed...
Buying junk food to gorge myself on...
This means...
Ami-chan lost to both that good-for-nothing punk and Aisaka Taiga, isn't it?
Takasu-kun.
You said it just now, right?
You told me to stop pretending, right?
Y-Yeah. I think so.
I got it.
I won't pretend being Ami-chan anymore.
I won't pretend, I won't pretend, I won't pretend...
Kawashima?
After this, I'll live on with this dark personality.
I'm not one who's easily wavered!
Hey!
Kawashima...
Kawashima, after that, was amazing.
Not watching her step at all, she ran through the town in a magnificent form.
And she recklessly crushed the cowardly stalker's camera into pieces.
Facing this sudden change,
the stalker was frightened to the bones.
And then...
Liar. Being just like a demon...
You aren't the Ami-chan that I know!
You're not an angel! Your personality is too dark!
So what about that?
Ami-chan's just so cute.
Who cares about personality?
Kawashima. Hey, are you alright?
Hey, Kawashima.
I did it, Takasu-kun.
Is that so?
But... I was scared.
Here, warm yourself up.
This is honey-pickled kumquat...
You know it well, huh?
Taiga likes it.
Taiga... you're calling Aisaka-san's name directly, huh?
Are you still suspecting it?
That girl's lucky, right?
Stubborn. A mess.
But, she doesn't put up a pretence.
Even so, she has friends by her side.
And Takasu-kun by her side too.
If I show you my true self, what would you do?
Will you fall in love with me?
Ka-Ka-Ka-Kawashima...
Hey...
W-Wait a minute, I...
Taiga! Are they inside?
Taiga?
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru mono to wa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
Unable to be honest, I'm just rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
Pool Opening
Waterproof, and made to repel water.
In subtle gradation,
it can be set up with just one touch too.
How's this, Taiga?
For the Ginyu Forces!