I'm gonna kill this Kida Masaomi,
who ordered this!
Those are the eyes of someone
who's ready to die.
Horada? Which Horada?
I wanted to tell you what he's thinking.
I'm ready to kill.
And I won't let anyone deny me that!
No matter what ugly thing you may see,
are you prepared to accept it?
Kida-kun!
Why?
Masaomi!
Mikado...
Ryuugamine-kun, why?
You were right.
This is worse than I'd imagined!
Selfless
Devotion
There you are, black biker.
Everyone, get 'em!
Now!
Betray him!
Hey, what the hell is going on?
Yo.
K-K-Ka-Kadota!
Wh-Why, you...
So this disguise was enough to fool you, huh?
I guess just grabbing anyone you can,
to join, isn't a good idea.
Kadota-san, what's happening here...
Togusa reminded me.
When Izumii was arrested,
a guy named Horada
managed to avoid getting charged.
So I gathered thirty or so of my best friends,
and we all put on some yellow scarves.
Yumasaki and Karisawa stood out
too much, so I left them behind.
Aren't we gonna get to do anything?
Sometimes standing out too much is bad.
I didn't even want to remember you.
It makes me sick.
Were you the one who broke her legs?
Um, well, I...
Was it you who made her cry?
Damn it. M-My gun...
Where's my damned gun?
It was you, wasn't it?
I was gonna use that wrench
to bust your head open.
But Anri and Mikado aren't like us.
They don't need to see a body.
That's all...
Masaomi!
Masaomi! Masaomi!
Wake up!
Kida-kun!
Celty-san told me all about
you and Sonohara-san.
I'm sorry...
I didn't know anything...
Ryuugamine-kun, I...
You don't have to say anything.
I think I understand what's going on,
so don't force yourself...
If only I'd told you what I was
suffering and worrying over,
this never would've happened.
I felt like you were drifting away
from me, so I got scared.
Masaomi.
It's my fault!
I didn't tell either of you what
was happening with me.
Sonohara-san.
I'm sorry.
The two of you are very important to me.
You were with me the whole time.
You two are great together.
Masaomi...
If you're taking me to a hospital,
can I ask a favor?
What is it?
Take me to Raira General Hospital.
There's a girl waiting for me...
M-Masaomi?
Masaomi! Masaomi!
What a mess.
Kadota-san.
I told him not to run,
but this wasn't what I meant.
He should hold back some.
Are those people...
Yeah. They're all Dollars.
There are some things you can do
if you don't have a color.
You know, even if you tell them to disappear,
they were invisible to start with. So they can't.
Hey! Horada's running!
Horada-san, this way.
That bastard...
I'll follow him.
Take Kida-kun to the hospital.
Got it.
There's a van outside.
Togusa, get on it.
Right!
I've got some cleanup to do.
Take care of Kida.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Horada-san, Higa's not here!
Leave him!
It's h-h-here!
The black bike!
Shut up!
Horada-san, what do we do now?
We need to hide somewhere
till stuff cools off.
Once Izumii gets out of jail,
everything'll be fine.
Horada-san, look! Ahead!
Ahead?
I-It's him...
Shizuo! Heiwajima Shizuo!
He's alive?
But why is there a sign post there?
Why is he alive...
Why-
Horada-san!
Don't try running away!
Horada-san, get a hold of yourself!
The black bike?
You've got guts, pulling next to a
cop bike, before he turns on his lights.
Don't screw with the traffic cops, kiddos.
Horada and his gang were arrested.
They tried to complain that Heiwajima
Shizuo destroyed their car,
but supposedly, the police
weren't interested.
Take care.
Thank you.
Where's Sonohara-san?
Yup, this is it.
Thanks.
Now I can collect the Awakusu-Kai reward.
Cool.
Couldn't get the bullets, though.
Oh, it's fine.
Fine.
Would've been great if he'd been
able to kill Shizu-chan, too.
So you used me to pass information
about Shizuo to Horada, right?
He could have died if he'd been
hit in the head or the heart.
It's a real shame...
That's how it is, Mother.
Thank you.
Go home and live your life like normal.
Um, you're Orihara Izaya-san, right?
Sonohara Anri-chan?
Or should I call you Saika?
What do you want, at this hour?
I'm going to cut you!
Why...
Why did you do this?
I didn't do a thing.
Let me see...
If I had to give a reason,
I'd say that I love humans!
So perhaps I love to see them in
all kinds of different ways.
Now, here's the question!
Was that answer the truth or a lie?
Once I control you, I'll understand.
By the way, what about you?
If you really want a peaceful everyday life,
then use that sword to cut
everyone you know.
That... That would be wrong!
Oh, my. Then your refusal to clarify things
with Mikado-kun and Masaomi-kun,
when you know they both like you...
Is that the right answer?
You've convinced yourself that
you can't love anyone,
and you're using that as an excuse to
be complacent with yourself now.
Saika will love people for you?
How stupid...
Please shut up!
You shouldn't underestimate me,
you know that?
There's a reason I can go
one-on-one with Shizu-chan, right?
And if nothing else,
you shouldn't have given me this.
Don't worry. I won't shoot you.
Who will it be?
That couple over there?
You can't love anyone,
so it won't bother you.
I knew all along that Higa-kun was
one of the Slasher victims.
Why do you think I asked him
to get me the gun?
You.
I wanted to declare war on you.
I love people deeply, too.
I'm not handing them over
to a stupid sword!
Humans...
are mine, after all.
Oh! But I don't need Shizu-chan,
so you can have him.
Slice him to pieces as soon as you can.
Good luck.
Bye!
You're late.
What's with that face?
I got hit with a hard punch.
Hey.
Simon?
Want to hear kind of a bad story?
You're such a cowardly ass, it's funny.
I'd agree with that, Simon.
But I like that quality of mine.
You know Masaomi's girlfriend, right?
She gave me a call.
Told me about you,
about everything happening.
All of it.
Saki?
Why would Saki...
She's seriously in love with Masaomi.
And she's done with you.
I see...
She is, huh?
Hey, Izaya...
Don't wreck the town too much.
Simon, I really do
love people. That's all.
Don't try to fool me.
You just don't want to lose to Shizuo, right?
You have some kind of complex about him.
You're more transparent than you think.
Simon, you know...
You're way too different when you
speak Russian, not Japanese.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Was it you who told Horada
about Mikado-kun?
I dunno.
Scary...
You're still upset about that, huh?
Man... Some people act just as I expect.
And some, like Simon and
Shizu-chan, never do.
That's why I love, love, love humans!
Yeah, that's right.
That's why I can keep at this damned job.
It's so fun, it sickens me.
I've said it before, but I'm pretty sure
humanity hates your guts.
I don't know about that...
Sa-
I know.
After all, you didn't come, Masaomi.
You spent the whole time calling Izaya-san.
Again and again...
He laughed when he showed
me his call history.
But don't worry about it.
Even if you'd come after that, it wouldn't
have made a big difference to me.
Stop it...
So I think it was for the best that
you didn't come and weren't hurt-
I understand!
I understand...
I'm an awful person...
I wonder what she saw in me.
The way you're strangely honest.
How long have you been here?
A while.
I heard from Karisawa-san and the others.
About everything.
You're an idiot.
You really are.
I've always known that.
I have to apologize for something.
I let them catch me.
Izaya-san said that it would end it all.
So I... I went there myself that night.
And then he spread the information that-
I knew.
Izaya told you to, right?
To pretend you couldn't walk,
to keep me distant.
He wanted me to be his pawn.
Masaomi.
I'm an esper, after all.
For the first time, I disobeyed him!
I think I can finally say it.
I couldn't save you.
I'm sorry.
But I do love you.
So please...
Don't leave me!
Hey!
You're such an idiot.
You really are.
Sure I am.
Let me have at least one flaw.
If you think it's a flaw, fix it.
Let's fix it together...
Several days later, Masaomi and
Mikajima Saki disappeared together.
He submitted a letter to the school,
saying he was leaving, and then vanished.
The everyday life that had been
the three of us changed.
But the town is the same as always.
Russian Sushi!
He is...
And they...
And he...
It's peaceful.
Yeah. Seems there's a bunch of internal
problems among the Blue Square survivors.
And the Yellow Scarves have calmed down.
I see. So there's no danger of Mikado
and Anri-chan being attacked.
What's with that sexy outfit?
If you're going to seduce me like that,
I'm taking a shower and changing the bed sheets...
What's wrong?
Nothing... Normally, you'd be jabbing me
in the ribs or grabbing my face.
Actually, I'm seducing you.
And they...
Will our lost everyday life never return to us?
Maybe I liked Kida-kun.
And that's why I'm so lonely.
But I don't know.
I don't really understand things like that...
But there's one thing I learned.
The Dollars are the town, itself.
A lot of people arrive,
and a lot of people leave,
never in the same colors.
Something is always happening.
People are hating each other,
loving each other,
becoming friends, and drifting apart.
Title: To Everyone
The Dollars are here.
They'll stay here.
In the same way a town exists,
so long as there are people,
the Dollars will continue to exist.
Hello.
Hello!
Hi.
Oh! There's someone new here.
Hi!
I'm Bakyura.
Kanra-san invited me!
I met him over the net. Did you?
No, I know him IRL.
He's someone I know from work.
At least on the surface.
Kyaa!
When are you going to die, Kanra-san?
That was harsher than expected!
That's awful.
I'm sorry!
Kanra-san's just such an ass,
I had to!
Private message from Tanaka Tarou-san
Um, Bakyura-san.
Sorry if I'm mistaken.
Masaomi?
Is it you, Masaomi?
If you'd say... If you'd say something,
I'd appreciate it.
We know each other in person.
Tell them what a great guy I am!
Square root of 3.
Eh?
If you were to give him a number,
it'd be the square root of three.
Do you mean I'm so beautiful,
no mere number can express me?
It means, "Still too difficult for elementary schoolers,
so you shouldn't show it to them."
Oh, I'm sorry.
I've gotta go.
Bye!
Later!
Goodnight!
Um, Bakyura-san.
Please come again.
You're welcome here!
I will! Bye!
Night!
Goodnight!
<Bakyura-san has left the channel>
A place to go home to...
A lost everyday...
They existed on the net.
He'll come back.
Masaomi will come back.
So when he does, let's get mad at him.
Let's laugh and get really mad at him!
The two of us together.
Looking back, I don't quite get it.
Anyway, it would change my life.
But in a way, nothing changed at all.
It was, at the same time, very, very strange,
but also the sort of thing that could happen to anyone.
Here in Ikebukuro...
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.