When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
My name is Seishiro Kurausu.
I have retired as a butler
and now live as a plantation owner in Brazil.
Wait! I have yet to retire!
I will be a Sanzenin butler to the very end!
There's nothing left for you to do.
And a replacement for Himegami's
been found already,
so I'm sure you've got no regrets left.
What could a beast know of my feelings?!
Doesn't it bother you more
that the beast is talking?
It looks like even that
poverty-stricken butler
will be able to manage
the spoiled little miss.
Hah! As if I could leave it in
the hands of that greenhorn!
I'm going back to Japan!
Oh, no, you aren't.
You're going to enjoy the rest of
your days here in Brazil with me!
What?!
No, not that!
Not that!
Tama! So it was you?!
So it's a dream punch line
right off the bat this week?
Well, then, good-bye, everyone.
There's no way a tiger would talk.
I must be tired.
Brazil Overseas Trips for Seniors
What's this?
"Coffee plantation owner wanted in Brazil"?
How did this get into my room?
Whosoever commands the
butlers, commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
"Klaus" is written as "kura"
as in "kurashiki (warehouse)"
and "usu" as in "usu-kine
(mortar and pounder)"
I am 100% Japanese!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Klaus is Japanese Because His
Name Is Written "Kurausu"
A good temperature.
Ironing out the morning paper.
This is the butler's first
duty of the morning.
As expected, the delayed
release of "Dragon Quest"
is affecting the price of the stock.
Goodness!
To think I had become a coffee
plantation owner, comfortably retired.
What a strange dream I had.
Go ahead.
Huh?
If you want to retire, why don't you?
What?!
Heavens, no!
I intend to spend the rest of my
days at the Sanzenin household!
I was merely speaking
of what I had dreamed...
According to Freud, dreams embody
your unconscious desires.
In the depths of your heart,
you are thinking you are tired
already and want to retire.
I-I am not!
Besides, if I were to leave,
the Sanzenin household would...
...have no problem whatsoever.
What?!
Hayate and Maria will take
care of the day-to-day things.
Oh, no need to worry about
asset management and such.
Especially with the recent IT-related stocks,
it's probably beyond your abilities already.
Anyway, I'll be fine.
I must not run. I must not run.
Um, Mr. Klaus?
An AT Field! An emotional barrier, I see.
Oh, Maria.
Oh, I don't know anymore.
What could have gotten into Mr.
Klaus? He seems so depressed.
Yes, something must have come
as a great shock to him...
Oh!
Huh?
Aim for a Space Legacy?!
Mahal
No idea. Though, I did tell
him that he could quit.
You didn't have to take
his dream seriously...
Normally, if you have a butler who
has served you for many years...
You give them a room of
their own at the residence
and treat them like family...
It must have come as a
shock to be told to quit.
There's no way he'd quit
over something like that!
Deep inside, you must adore
Mr. Klaus very much, Miss.
H-He's just an easy character to mess with.
Then please don't tell him to quit.
He may be getting swallowed up
in Dirac's sea right about now.
Indeed.
Then go do an involuntary
salvage operation or something!
Understood.
What was that laugh for?!
I'm coming in.
Head Butler.
Oh, Maria, the Miss has
given me some time off.
I will spend the rest of my life in Brazil.
P-Please! There's no way the Miss
seriously wants you to quit, right?
But! But!
If you've made up your mind,
then it cannot be helped.
What?
I shall inform the Miss.
Wait! There may be some sense
to what the Miss says, too!
Dreaming of retirement...
It seems I have become less than
dedicated without realizing it!
I am thinking of going back to my days
when I was a footman aspiring
to become a butler!
A footman?
Footmen are people who work under butlers.
Incidentally, there are no footmen
in the Sanzenin household.
As a footman, I challenge Hayate
Ayasaki to a serving-the-Miss match!
What a way to stack the
odds against yourself.
Damn! Butting in needlessly!
I was almost on my way to
Brazil, just as I'd planned!
A-A serving-the-Miss match?
I don't recall asking you to
do anything so bothersome.
It was Mr. Klaus who suggested it, so...
You have certainly grown a lot
in a short amount of time, boy.
However, you have one fatal flaw!
Wh-What about me is...
Maybe it's how you look too
good when you cross-dress.
Now, now.
Boy, a butler is ultimately
his mistress's shadow.
You are too aware of
yourself as a protagonist!
But he is actually the protagonist,
so it can't be helped.
In fact, he is rather unassuming
for a protagonist...
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
A-At any rate, for the next 24 hours,
we will wield our skills as butlers
to the utmost to serve Miss Nagi!
In the unlikely event that my service
is less satisfactory than the boy's,
I will leave the estate!
What?!
Y-Yes, sir!
I will compete with all my might,
so as not to insult the Head Butler!
And thus, the serve-the-Miss match began.
Boy, do you know what the most essential
skill is for a butler to have?
Well, like starting out hated,
but being thought of as a nice
person by the final episode?
Or swapping places with
one's mistress by chance
and ending up solving the case?
No!
To be inspired enough to
anticipate what's to come!
You need the ability to
read multiple steps ahead
to anticipate what your mistress desires!
For the nobility, the morning
begins with tea upon waking up!
Oh, if it's that, I already prepared it.
What?
Ah!
What?!
It is ready, Miss.
Thank you, Hayate.
Y-You fool!
In England, the land of butlers,
this is a duty that is so important
that there is a role specially
dedicated to making tea!
If you do not even know how to
properly make tea, you are no butler!
These are technically tea bags made for
the British Royal Household, though...
What?!
Ah! That sounds good!
Lemon or cream? Which would you like?
Listen here! Back in England, there
is no such thing as lemon tea!
Only milk tea exquisitely
prepared by the butler
serves to bolster the start of every day!
Then I'll go with lemon.
The lemon tea you made is good, Hayate.
Thank you very much.
Th-This can't be...
Nagi, please try to go a little easy on him.
It's wrong...
It's just wrong. Just wrong...
So you are going to school today, Miss?
Yes, because it would be mean
to mess with Klaus too much.
I see. But why?
It may not look it, but
Klaus and I go way back.
The fact that we know each other well
is precisely what makes
it worth messing with him.
Ah! Right now, I can get two
extra pieces with the bucket!
And it comes with nuggets to boot!
I-I wonder if they ran out of chicken...
It looks like he didn't
follow us all the way here.
So it appears.
You there!
Keep it down!
Miss!
Th-That's a piece of finely
polished silverware!
That is the symbol of a first-rate butler!
Zvaaaaam!!
Boy! I have quit being a human being!
Mr. Klaus!
Y-You're a Sanzenin household butler!
The word "butler" comes from one
who oversees the wine collection,
a permutation of "bouteillier"!
Wine! Vintage wine!
Violet Overdrive!
Damn!
Bordeaux! Burgundy!
I have no wine for a drunkard!
Kraaaash!
Stop right there!
They're both gone...
Yeah...
On sunny days like this,
playing hooky is the best!
It's even more relaxing when I think
of how everyone else is studying.
Now, if only we had a butler to make
us some tea, it would be perfect.
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
Switching places?!
Negoro Butler Ninja Skill, the
Switching Places Technique.
That was an unexpected nuisance.
Now, then...
M-My chronic back problem...
Oh! That's Nagi's head butler!
I'm looking for a perch.
(Tomari-gi o sagashite imasu.)
A bittersweet memory.
(Suppai omoide daze.)
What the?! Holy cow!
This is super first rate cake and tea!
Much appreciated!
I owe you my life, so I
wanted you to enjoy it.
Thank you! Let's dig in!
"Thank you," huh?
A butler is his mistress's shadow,
but deep inside, he is always waiting
for that one word of thanks.
This is better than the ones from
the shop by the train station!
And this tea has been poured exquisitely.
Just lovely!
I've found you!
Katsy!
Yukiji!
We have a really good reason for this!
I don't care about any of that!
Treat me, too!
Huh?
What on Earth are you going on about?
Play dumb, will you?!
You've got vintage stuff, don't you?!
Yukiji, you seem to be out for blood.
Sis! What are you doing being
so violent towards the elderly?!
The elderly?!
After all, he came falling
out of the sky just earlier.
He's a grandpa, and who knows when
something might happen to him.
RIP.
Well, sure, but...
M-Mr. Klaus?
Just how far could they have gone?
Well, Klaus has probably recovered by now.
Mr. Klaus!
Oh? Here I was wondering who you might be,
but if it isn't the renowned
Mr. Klaus of the butler world.
Judging by your appearance, you are
a butler of the Ohkouchi household.
My name is Himuro Saeki.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
And this is Little Master Taiga.
I will pretend I did not hear that last part.
What?
Butlers have long considered it an honor
to be called by their master's name.
You are an Ohkouchi butler and
you do not even know that?!
Wow, I had no idea, Himuro.
Little Master! Petals!
Oh! R-Right!
To think you would cite an Edwardian
custom in our Heisei Era!
It is so difficult to see.
The sight of a formerly great
butler in his declining years.
Wha?!
It is sad that even as you
have grown feeble with age,
you still cling to your position.
Th-That was awesome, Himuro!
With reflexes like that,
you will not be able to protect your
mistress in her time of need, you know.
Perhaps you should retire and
think about living your own life.
You are young, Ohkouchi butler.
What?
I am my mistress's shadow.
Shadows never have their own
private lives to begin with!
If I see that I can no longer
be of use to my mistress,
all that is left is for me
to merely disappear quietly.
Don't tell me...
...he just found his resolve to step down?!
No way!
Is he serious?
Is there no way for us
to keep Mr. Klaus here?
We do have a trump card for that.
Really?!
Yes.
However, it will require
you to lend a helping body.
Oh, please. That would
be "lend a helping hand".
I-I have a bad feeling about this.
Ah, I have such fond memories of everything.
My life's purpose was to be
with the Sanzenin household
and to live out my days here.
But what the young Ohkouchi
butler said had some merit, too.
Perhaps it is high time I ended this...
Mr. Klaus.
I-I have met you somewhere before!
You are the sweet lady I saw in the garden!
This was a good idea, if I do say so myself!
Hayate's unique allure when dressed
in women's clothes would be effective
even in the gay town of Ni-chome, Shinjuku.
Even Mr. Klaus will surely
find comfort in this.
Wh-What is your name?
Ayasaki...
Ayasaki?
Oh! It's H-H-H-Hermione!
Ah! Hermione!
What a fantastic name! Like the
name of someone who can use magic!
Y-Yes.
The truth is, I am a goddess, who
lives in the estate's Yashagaike Pond.
Ah! I knew that you could
not be an ordinary lady!
Mr. Klaus,
I have been watching you all this
time from the bottom of the pond.
H-Have you really?!
You must not quit being the head butler.
You are still far too young for that.
What is the matter?
I have grown weak with old age and
even my hair is completely white.
That is not true.
You are a fine gentleman with graying hair!
I-I am, aren't I?!
I get that a lot at the adult
social club in Ikebukuro!
So you will no longer say
you will retire, right?!
But lately, I can barely lift my
arms because of my old shoulders...
Y-You're just a little
stiff, that's all. See?
Look at how stiff you are!
Stiff!
Please do my upper and lower back as well.
Certainly!
Oh, there. Right there. That's the spot.
Please hurry up and get convinced!
You difficult bow-tied old man!
Who the hell is Klaus talking to?
Further that way!
No, we cannot go there.
T-Time for a tasty treat!
Hermione, th-the truth is...
Honey!
To think I have grown senile
enough to be seeing things...
It backfired...
This tiger again!
Brazil Overseas Trips for Seniors
What's this?
Forgive me, man!
Tama, don't tell me you did
this for a female tiger?!
I've fallen in love with that female tiger!
But I'm a tiger, so I can't
get to Brazil all on my own!
And so you used Mr. Klaus?
You want to go to the plantation in Brazil.
You want to go. You want to go!
I just whispered that to him!
I'll tell you one thing.
Huh?!
There are no tigers in Brazil!
What?!
I know!
If I tell Mr. Klaus that
his dream about Brazil
wasn't the product of his subconscious,
but that it was Tama's underhanded plot...!
No, I can't say that.
I'd forgotten that no one
knows that Tama can talk...
Klaus!
What's the flower language for this flower?
Miss, it is loyalty to you.
Really?!
Yes, I just made it so.
This is for you!
Miss Nagi!
Mr. Klaus.
It no longer matters, boy.
There is nothing that I can do
that you are not capable of.
Hey, Hayate!
Miss Nagi!
This morning's Butler
Economy Marketing Journal
is soaked from the morning dew!
I can't read the stock market news!
Head Butler.
You have yet to teach me
how to iron the newspaper.
Boy!
If you can't even iron the newspaper,
the winner of the match is Klaus.
Miss!
Come on, Klaus!
It seems I have no choice.
A good temperature!
It seems Mr. Klaus has completely recovered.
Yes.
We owe it all to you, Miss.
He may not be much, but he is a
part of the Sanzenin household.
I would not wake up feeling
good if I had driven him away!
Shall we go make some lemon tea?
That is a good idea.
Next time, they will not fight,
but instead, aim to coexist
with small animals.
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
Wataru & Saki's
Wataru and...
Saki's...
Butler Report
Butler Report!
With the sunny smile and the boyish charm,
I'm the manager of Rental Video
Tachibana, Wataru Tachibana!
And I help take care of him.
I'm the maid, Saki Kijima.
Now that the image song is ready to go,
maybe we should make some
promotional merchandise!
What do you think would sell well?
How about a rare glimpse
at Rental Video Tachibana's
clutzy maid in a pleasingly
embarassing situation?
What do you think? You have been
attracting more customers, lately.
Young sir, would you please stop it?!
Tachibana!
Preview
Hayate, what kind of girl
would you say is your type?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Uh, good question...
I think I like normal girls the best.
"Normal"?
I'm not sure you'd understand, miss...
How dare you?! Do you think I
can't become your ideal girl!?
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"I Want to Go Back to Being an Ordinary Girl,
But Buy My Character Songs, Okay?"
I Want to Go Back to Being an Ordinary Girl,
But Buy My Character Songs, Okay?
I see! So, Hayate likes normal girls...
Did you know the lion statues in
front of certain apartment buildings
are called "shiisa" in Okinawa?