Please forgive me, Asuna-san; my powers aren’t good enough…
No, you tried hard, Aniki!
Yep, you did, Negi-kun!
You’ve done a very good job; persisting that much against the school council.
It’s obvious that selling products provided by students in school is impossible from the start.
Man, I thought that it would be sold out if I sold them to the public…
Chupa Tee!
What’s this? The lights are on.
You…!
ROSE!
Afternoon tea with a green wind. Hailing from the Country of Mist - Love and bravery’s Ambassador of Friendship.
They call me… The Black Rose Baron!
Back again... huh, you masked man!
Why you… How did you get in here!?
Did you prepare this full course all by yourself?
Wait, before you do anything, it’s stuck on my head! It’s stuck!
We’re gonna get him, Negi!
Alright!
LISTEN TO ME!!
Did you know that...
It was always thought that hippos are herbivorous.
But in reality, they consume meat.
Farewell!
Dang it!
Chupa Tee…
In order not to dirty the table, he laid this out, huh…
Unforgivable! I’ll never forgive you, stupid Black Rose Baron!
Chupa Tees are not shower caps!
Asuna, for this occasion, it’s “lunch mat”!
Amazing… You weren’t even close.
But, it’s more amazing that you actually understood that, Jou-chan!
As expected from Ojou-sama!
Oy, I thought I was gonna die for a second…
by Haruna
All of Negi-chan’s partners have gathered, mya!
The numbers have gone up while we were going about things carelessly.
What’s that?
Let’s see… a fascinating figure, de gozaru...
The Black Rose Baron is a messenger of the devil! We must bring him down!
So that drawing was the Black Rose Baron…
Well, that’s Asuna for ya. Her drawing sucks!
Don’t say it sucks!
“Bring him down!” sounds so adult-like!
It’s an adult’s decision, desu!
How did we get to this point so suddenly?
Something happened last night, that's all...
The Black Rose Baron shall never be forgiven! BRING HIM DOWN!
YEAH!
She’s talking about bringing him down… but he could still be Negi-kun’s dad, ya know…
She’s forgotten about it completely…
Come with me, and we shall look for this masked man!
OKAY!
Forward MARCH!
Question, Leader!
What do you want, Oniwaban?
Can we… remove the shirts now?
What kind of question is that!?
If we take off the shirts, we’ll look like a suspicious group!
We will move as the Chupa Team till the end!
If we do that, we won’t look suspicious at all!
It’s strongly suspicious.
Just you watch, you Black Rose Baron, you!
You’re about to meet the Fist of Justice!
Negi-bouzu, Asuna-dono is being a little wild; is that okay with you, de gozaru?
Eh, I guess. For the time being, I believe we should investigate.
Once again, forward MARCH!
Question, Leader!
Konoka!
It’s an important question!
Ask it later!!
You’ll regret it if I put it off.
Eh?
You will. No joke.
We’re listening.
Regret?
What is it, Ojou-sama?
You see…
Gulp
This is a research group; don’t you think it’s weird to have a leader!?
Eh?
Say what?
Alright! Good luck with your search!
Okay!
Ah! The Chupa Team! Count me in, guys!
Ha-Haruna!
O-Oh, crap!
Eh? What did you say “Oh, crap!” for?
No, well, uh…
Haruna, right now Samohan Kinpou is having an autograph session in the library!
Eh!? No way!
I gotta go, fast!
That was a close one!
Ojousama, I think you’re misinterpreting it.
There's no Samohan Kinpou, de gozaru.
Who’s that? An adult?
Come to think of it, Haruna-san has shown up every now and then for the Chupa Team.
And the design for the shirts did come from Nee-san after all.
Umm… I’m starting to think that the Chupa Team isn’t really a secret identity.
Can we… take off the shirts now?
Ah, ow ow ow ow, my chronic disease’s relapsing…
Hey you, no faking.
The Black Rose Baron, eh…?
Negi and the others left to search for him, but so far, they've had no luck.
Well, of course they can’t find him.
Eva, is he really…?
Yes, without a doubt.
There is some leftover spirit within the Baron.
Is that so? Then that means that the series of incidents with the illusions are…
Yes.
The Star Crystal - it's a legendary magic item that can amplify an infinite amount of magic power.
Inform the Dean, and start planning an urgent intervention
No, I think it’s best not to make our move just yet.
Eh?
If we rush things, we won’t be able to avoid the bigger troubles.
We must observe, just for a while.
Still, Evangeline!
Have you forgotten?
Even he cannot handle the Star Crystal.
At any rate, our path shall be shown in due time.
Master, sorry to have kept you waiting.
Thanks. Takamichi, you take part in this, too.
No thanks, my manners are…
Forget manners; just eat it.
“Eat it”!?
Here you go – Niboshi dashi.
Ramen!
Come on, hurry up and eat it.
They’ll get soggy.
Eh? Ah, okay.
Truly elegant.
Yes. It’s the heart of Japan.
That’s definitely wrong.
It may not be necessary to mention this, but the search has ended with no success.
Don’t say that!
Ah, I’m so tired…
Yeah, I’m all tired.
The investigation planning was no good.
We were just going in circles, de gozaru.
Having Ane-san make any sort of plans is like saying "Do a Hindu Squat to an Aruana"!
What did you say!?
She was listening! ANIMAL ABUSE!
No more snacks!
Desu!
Eh? Really?
That’s not good; that was all we had!
There’s plenty in my dorm room, so I’ll go get them.
Oh, Nodoka-dono, I am grateful.
I’m grateful!
Nodoka, so you eat this sort of stuff, too?
No, it’s just that Haruna bought it cheap, but got too much. So just wait a bit!
Ah, then let me accompany you!
Carrying it all yourself might be a burden and all.
Negi-sensei…
Konoka is so mean!
There’s a limit to how much you can joke around!
Well, if it were me, I wouldn’t be dashing off.
Aside from that, Kuu Fei-san sure is late…
She went to go borrow a can opener from Satsuki-san, but how long does that sort of thing take?
I wanna open this up and see what’s inside so badly!
Onigiri Topping-filled meat buns are so yummy, aru!
Chao, you’re a meat bun genius, aru!
Really, Kuu Fei?
Lingshen, what if we ate some with small fish inside?
Ooh, good idea!
Kuu Fei!
Yes!
I’m gonna check up on her.
Wow, there’s so many of them!
Eh? That voice belongs to…
Negi-sensei.
I think we’ll be fine with this amount.
Wow, it’s organized so well!
As expected, Nodoka-san!
Oh no… The books are all left sloppily…
Please, don’t look around that much!
Ah, I’m sorry, I just-
No need to…
I just got complimented!
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
Are you okay?
Yeah… thank you.
Magic…
Good night!
Yue-Yue, I’m back!
Welcome back.
So Haruna came to visit!
How’s the toy can?
Aside from that,
we saw what happened earlier, Nodoka.
EEEEEHHHHH!?
Next day, mya-!
It’s Sunday, Motsu.
Eh?
What, Motsu?
You have a weird sentence ender, mya.
It’s something to express my originality.
That a bad thing, Motsu?
Hello, mya.
Death!
Desu?
OOOOOWWWWW, yeah...
What do we do…?
Hey, Asuna…
Shh!
What’s that over there?
It’s Asuna-san’s operational plan, de gozaru.
It’s my latest trap for capturing the Chupacabra!
“Latest,” eh?
What was that?
Nothing!
Hey, will that really...
catch the Black Rose Baron?
Leave it to me!
Where does she get all that confidence?
So, what is the reason for that bait, de gozaru?
It seems that the Black Rose Baron is a foreigner.
And when it comes to foreigners, of course, they think of geishas and Mt. Fuji!!
Oh geez.
Nodoka-san?
Y-Y-Yes?
Is something wrong?
N-no! I-it’s nothing!
Asuna-dono!
Here it is!
Someone really did show up!
Desu!
I can’t believe it!
And this is the result of my hard work!
Let’s lift it up!
Alright! Kaede-san, give me a hand here!
Gotcha!
Is that really…?
1, 2…!
Black Rose Baron, we finally meet!
Hello. I am Zazie Rainyday.
See, look! A foreigner!
Hey you there! Don’t fake it right away!
Aww, that's it?
Ah, for Zazie-dono to fall into this trap isn't so swell to hear, de gozaru.
Not so swell... my stomach isn't so swell as well.
75 points!
How very kind of you…
Not at all!
Yes?
Um, can I have a word with you?
Eh? Nodoka-san, you want me to activate the contract?
Yes. Please activate it.
Why again?
Um, well…
I understand. It’s okay!
Negi-sensei…
Well then, here I go.
O-okay!
What? Negi-sensei is a mage!?
Ooh! Negi-kun’s a true-to-life mage!
That’s so cool!
I gotta tell everyone!
No! You can’t!
You can not tell anyone!!
Why?
If people find out that he’s a mage, not only will they take away his magic certification, but they’ll turn him into an animal, too!
So please, keep it quiet!
Wow, that’s some amazing stuff there.
So then, why do you know about the whole mage thing?
What kind of relationship do you have with Negi-sensei?
R-relationship?
Um, well, uh… er…
Um?
Well?
I’m… I’m… I’m Negi-sensei’s partner…
“Partner”!?
You’re engaged to Negi-sensei!?
N-no, you got it all wrong!
I’m not talking about that kind of partner!
Partner: Miyazaki Nodoka. Show me the power within you!
Contract, activate!
Applause!?
Ah, sorry, we just suddenly…
Yeah…
Haruna-san! Yue-san!
Why are you guys here!?
Could it be that…?
You two feel so warm and comfy that you’re getting sleepy, de gozaru!
Oh? Come to think of it, Konoka-dono and Setsuna-dono are no longer here, de gozaru!
They realized they had something to do, so they left.
Basically, they ran away, de gozaru?
Negi-sensei and Nodoka-chan left not too long ago, too, desu.
Oh! Indeed!
Hey, Asuna-dono, why don’t we just call it a day and take a nap, eh?
I didn't even have to suggest, de gozaru?
Wait, you chupacabra…
Oh boy, even in your own sleep, you talk about chupacabras, de gozaru.
Give me back my earlobe…
“Earlobe”!?
I see.
If Nodoka-jou-chan showed you Aniki’s magic, you wouldn’t tell anyone about it!
Eheh, that’s what we promised!
We were so impressed that we just had to applaud, though unintentionally.
Negi-sensei, I’m so sorry!
No, it’s alright, Nodoka-san.
It’s because I thoughtlessly used my magic.
And on top of that, I’m really happy.
For you to be trying so hard to keep my magic a secret from the others…
Thank you.
Negi-sensei…
Yup, now things are settled!
No it’s not!
What are you gonna do, Aniki?
We can’t just leave it like this!
You’ll never know when Motsu and Shichimi will find out!
We don’t tell anyone.
Well, I wonder about that. I might slip up, you know…
Eh, no, don’t do that!
Basically, you have…
no choice but to make a provisional contract, Negi-kun!
Haruna!
Is that how you approach something like this?
Ah, Nee-san! Quick to talk; I like that!
You told them about the provisional contracts, too?
I-I’m so sorry!
Well, let’s exchange a contract!
If we do, we’ll be able to use magic too, right?
Exactly!
Well then! First up is Haruna-nee-san!
Pactio!
It’s pretty warm here!
Well? What do I do now?
Eh? Nee-san, you don’t know about exchanging a provisional contract?
Well, Nodoka didn’t exactly tell me how to exchange one.
For some reason she was embarrassed…
I see. Well, that’s Jou-chan for ya.
So what do I do?
You kiss Aniki, Nee-san.
Eh!?
Kiss him?
I’m sorry. That’s just how it goes…
That’s it? Okay, okay!
Well, let’s kiss!
Eh!?
Ah… okay…
Haruna! You can’t just easily-!
What are you talking about? It’s just a plain ol’ kiss!
Right, Negi-kun?
Um… I guess…
Here’s the kiss!
Contract complete!
Yay! It’s complete!
I’ll be able to use magic now!
Yaaaaaaay!
Oh, geez, Haruna!
Now, after Yue-jouchan exchanged the contract, it’s all safe!
Wha?
Ah. She’s gone.
Yue-san…
Yue-Yue?
This isn’t good, Aniki! We gotta hurry and find her!
What’s “not good,” mya?
Did something bad just happen?
In a good way!
No! Nothing!
Yeah, that’s right!
It’s not like Yue-jouchan, who learned about Aniki’s secret, has disappeared, leaving us clueless!
Chamo-kun!
Ah, dang it!
Retard.
Not good!
We heard something interesting, then.
Yeah, mya!
Now, we shall ask and check for ourselves, mya.
And if that’s the truth…
Ah! Wait!
Ch-Chamo-kun…
Negi-sensei…
My secret as a mage will be revealed…
What do I do?
When that happens, I’ll be…!
There’s no way I’d kiss him!
Hello, Ojousama.
Won’t you kiss me?
WHAT’D YOU SAY!?
What an unfortunate twist! What’ll happen next? Watch carefully and wait till next time!
Mandragora. This plant will shriek upon being uprooted.
Next Time: “Well, Out of All Those Theories Mixed Together, it All Comes Down to Your Feelings, But…”
By Yue.
Well then, let’s try uprooting it.
It’s sleeping.
Ookochi Akira from Swimming Club is taking care of an Aruana. His name? Yamamoto.
At first, she obtained him as a research subject to learn to swim…
Yamamoto!
…but he became a family member.
Yamamoto, you’ve gotten a bit bigger, haven’t you?
It should be because it’s in growing phase, huh, Yamamoto?
Hey, I know Yamamoto’s great and everything…
Can’t you do anything about your guys’ get-up?
Hey, look who’s talking!
They’re all weird. Right, Yamamoto?
You also, no?
No~