You're finished!
Homura!?
You...
What the hell are you doing!?
Oh, I see. You're that irregular.
You and that technique...
Stay out of my way!
Sayaka!
Don't worry, she's just unconscious.
What's with you? Whose side are you on?
I'm an ally to the calm, and an enemy to those who fight for no reason.
Which one are you, Kyoko Sakura?
Have we met somewhere?
Perhaps.
Well, it's certainly not like I'm wearing a nametag.
I'll be leaving for today.
A wise decision.
You... Saved us?
How many times have I warned you?
How foolish can you be?
There's no need for you to be involved in this. I've told you that repeatedly.
I...
If I'm fighting a fool, I'll use any means necessary.
Homura... Why...
Still, it's obvious she's planning something.
Be careful!
Homura Akemi... Could you be...!?
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 6 This just isn't right
Miki
Okay, you're fine for a while.
Wow, it's so dark...
You're cutting it close. If it gets any more corrupted, the witches might speed up.
Don't worry, though. Let me see that.
Now you're okay.
You ate it?
That's just another duty of mine.
But you need to hurry up and find another Grief Seed to purify your Soul Gem with next time.
Is it that important to keep it clean?
Kyoko Sakura was a fierce foe, wasn't she?
With a pure Soul Gem, you can do whatever you want, without worrying about using too much magic.
That's Kyoko's strong point.
That's the problem!
She sacrifices people in order to farm Grief Seeds!
As you use magic, the Soul Gem is dirtied.
Sayaka, you should realize that without collecting Grief Seeds, there's no way you'll beat Kyoko in a fight.
I guess...
Mami didn't have enough Grief Seeds either, did she.
But she still fought.
Was she just more talented than me?
That's certainly true.
That's no fair!
It's unavoidable. Kyoko's talented and a veteran.
On the other other hand, there is a prodigy who could surpass Kyoko
on raw talent alone, even without any experience.
Huh? Who?
Madoka Kaname.
Madoka?
Really?
Yeah! So if you're that desperate for the power to stand up to Kyoko...
It's better if you just ask Madoka to do it.
Once she contracts with me...
No way!
This is my fight.
I won't let her get caught up in it.
Hey! What is it now?
You can have this city.
And what caused this change of heart?
Girls like you are the most suited to become magical girls.
Sayaka Miki can't handle it.
Tell me something I didn't know.
And what about Sayaka? If I ignore her she'll just come after me again.
If possible, I'd like to settle that peaceably.
Stay out of it.
I'll deal with her.
Anyway, that's beside the point.
Who are you, really?
What are you after?
In one week's time, Walpurgisnacht will arrive.
How do you know?
That's a secret.
In any case, if you win then, I'll leave this city.
I don't care what you do after that.
Walpurgisnacht, huh.
I guess it will be tough alone. Maybe I can win with a helping hand.
Want some?
It's no good. You've taken too long.
The familiar's tracks have faded overnight.
I see.
Hey, Sayaka...
If you keep hunting witches, you're probably going to run into the girl from yesterday again.
Yeah, that's pretty obvious.
I think you should find her before that and try to talk things over.
If you don't, you might get in an argument again...
Argument, huh.
Madoka, do you think what happened yesterday was just an argument?
No. That was a real duel to the death.
We only started sniping at each other.
As we kept going, we both were trying to put an end to the other.
That's even worse!
That's why talking things over is crazy!
She uses human beings as bait to hunt Grief Seeds!
We could never compromise!
Sayaka, didn't you become a magical girl to hunt witches?
She's not a witch, she's a magical girl just like you!
If you just find a reason to get along, I'm sure you could!
Even if you do things different ways, you both want to hunt witches!
There's Homura, too!
Even Mami didn't have a serious problem with Homura, so...
That's absurd!
You saw it with your own eyes!
She just waited for Mami to get killed, then took the witch for herself!
She let Mami die so she could have a Grief Seed!
No... That's wrong...
That transfer student is just as bad as Kyoko!
They don't think of anyone but themselves!
I understand what's going on now.
Mami was special.
The other magical girls are all like those two.
No...
The familiar that escaped yesterday may be small, but it can still kill!
Maybe its next target is your mom or dad!
Maybe even little Tatsuya!
Are you really okay with that!?
I won't forgive anyone who lets one escape.
I didn't want this power just to fight witches. I wanted it to protect the ones I love.
So if I find a human more evil than a witch...
I'll fight her.
Even if she's a magical girl.
Sayaka...
Kyubey, say something!
All I can say is that that's too reckless.
In her current state, it's impossible for her to defeat Homura Akemi or Kyoko Sakura.
But...
Sayaka would never listen to that.
Good work today.
I left some potato salad in the fridge.
- Tomo
Can't sleep, huh?
Can we talk?
One of my friends is in trouble.
She hasn't really said or done anything wrong,
but for some reason, the more she tries to do the right thing, the worse her life gets.
That's not that unusual.
It's not fair, but just doing the right thing over and over doesn't guarantee you a happy ending.
If anything, if everyone's convinced they're doing the right thing,
it just drives happiness away.
She's not doing anything wrong, but she still won't be happy...
That's so unfair...
What should I do?
You can't just smoothly solve the problems of people like that
by butting in and telling them what to do.
But if you want to try, there's a messy way you can do it.
It's just to get things wrong.
If she tries too hard to do everything right, someone needs to make her mistakes for her.
Mistakes?
Tell white lies. Run away from scary things.
Things you can look back on and realize they were the right decision.
Sometimes, when you've got no other choice, your best chance is to just take the fall.
And she'll understand it's for her sake?
Sometimes she won't.
Especially not right away.
I told you, it'll be messy.
Sometimes you'll have regrets or just want to give up on her.
I've raised you well, Madoka.
You don't like, you're a good girl. You always try your hardest to do the right thing.
You're a wonderful child.
But you need to learn how to mess up before you grow up.
Learn how to mess up?
Your wounds heal faster when you're young.
If you learn how to fall now, it'll be useful later on.
Once you grow up.
Messing up will get a lot tougher, you know.
The more you're responsible for, the less you can afford to make mistakes.
Isn't that tough?
It's tough for all adults.
That's what makes drinking so great.
I want to be able to have a drink with you, Mama.
Hurry and grow up, then!
Being a grownup is only as fun as it is tough.
Oh, if you're looking for Kamijo, he was discharged yesterday.
His rehab was going so well that they moved it up.
I... I see...
So you're just gonna go home?
After spending all day trying to catch up with him?
You...
I know all about the kid that lives here.
He's why you contracted with Kyubey.
What a waste. You blew your one chance at a miracle on him?
You'd never understand!
You're the moron who doesn't understand.
Magic is there for fulfilling your own wishes.
If you use it for someone else's sake, it never works right.
Didn't Mami Tomoe tell you that?
If you're so caught up on making him yours, I've got an even better idea.
Take that magic you just got, and...
What!?
March right in, and smash his hand and his legs until he can never use them again.
Make him completely helpless.
Then he'll be completely yours.
His heart and his body.
If you're too shy to do it, I'd be happy to take your place.
Just as a favor to my new colleague.
It'll be so easy.
I... I'll never, ever forgive you!
This time, I'll...
Why don't we go somewhere else?
Wouldn't want to attract attention.
If she tries too hard to do everything right, someone needs to make her mistakes for her.
Even if you tell me to do that...
Madoka.
Madoka!
Hurry! Sayaka's in trouble!
Follow me!
We won't have to hold back up here.
Let's go all-out.
Wait! Sayaka!
Madoka!?
Stay out of this! It's none of your business!
No! This just isn't right!
Birds of a feather bug me together, huh.
Then what would that make your friends?
This isn't what we agreed upon. I told you not to lay a finger on Sayaka Miki.
You're too damn lax!
Plus, it doesn't matter. She's after me too.
Then I'll take you on.
I won't hold back.
Fine, as soon as I'm done eating.
Very well.
Hey, I'm right here, you know!
Sorry, Sayaka!
Madoka, why did you just--
If I didn't, you'd--
Sayaka?
You shouldn't have done that, Madoka.
What are you doing throwing away your friend, of all things?
What...
What!?
Stop it!
What's going on!? She's dead!
Sayaka?
Hey, Sayaka!
Wake up!
Hey, what's wrong!? Come on!
This can't be happening! Sayaka!
What the hell just happened?
You!
At best, you magical girls can only control your bodies within a hundred-meter range.
A hundred meters!?
What are you talking about!?
What's that supposed to mean!?
You normally stay extremely close to it, so this doesn't happen very often.
What are you talking about, Kyubey!? Help her!
Don't let Sayaka die!
That isn't Sayaka, Madoka. It's just an empty hust.
Sayaka is what you just threw away.
What!?
I'd never be able to ask you to wight witches with a weak, damage-prone human body.
For you magical girls, your "body" is nothing but hardware.
In order to make it easier to use magic,
I simply grant your soul--that which is you--this safe, compact new form.
When you seal that contract to become a magical girl, my job...
Is to rip out your soul and turn it into a Soul Gem.
You son of a...
Give me a break! You've turned us into zombies!
But isn't it convenient?
Even if their heart is crushed, even if they bleed their last drop...
Their body can be repaired with magic, and be used again.
As long as the Soul Gem isn't broken, you're invincible.
It's much better for fighting than the fragile human form.
That's terrible! I can't take it!
Magical girls are always like this.
You have the same reactions when you learn the truth.
I don't get it.
Why do humans all have such a problem with where their souls end up?
Huh?
What happened?
One day, perhaps the light of love shining in your eyes will
(Go beyond the time)
There is but one dream, of a world rushing toward its doom
(Will it be destroyed?)
Swallow your hesitation! What do you desire?
Chasing these greedy desires, will the future fade away?
When I was a girl, I dreamed of you
Wielding something like unto ancient magic
I want to be by your side as you smile,
filled with the strength to smash even the darkness
In my trembling hand, I grasp
the courage of a plucked laurel
Relying only on my emotions,
my prayer awakens the light
Illustration: Hajime Ueda
When you took on your fate of battle, you each had a wish, right?
They've been fulfilled, haven't they?
Episode 7 Can you face your true feelings
Can you face your true feelings?