It appears we've landed in the subway.
Yeah.
Where are Mitsu and the guys?
Nowhere to be found.
But right now, we need to do
something about the corporal.
There should be a temporary base
if we go above ground.
He can be treated there.
Hey, dumbass!
You there?
Are you guys all right?
Obviously!
Like hell we'd die in a place like this, shithead.
Can you guys get out?
No problem!
Then you go ahead!
We're going to stop by somewhere.
We'll meet you at the defense line!
Um, but...
Don't be late!
Well, shit.
I couldn't kill the commander.
Oh, deary me.
That blow wiped out several troops.
It seems the humans are fighting with their best as well.
Their best?
The vampire extermination unit's elite of the elite:
the Moon Demon Company.
Well, then...
Shall we?
Let's crush these wretched humans.
Hey, jackasses.
Did you enjoy your meal?
You better savor it, because that was your Last Supper.
Lend me your strength, Demon Blade Mahiru-no-Yo.
This is it, guys.
If we stand our ground, this war is as good as ours.
We will exterminate them.
Every last one.
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
Choices and
Consequences
Is everyone ready?
Yes!
Mika, Yuu, we're off!
Yeah.
Take care.
See you later.
See you later!
Lunch time! It's lunch time!
Yay, food!
I'm gonna eat a lot!
Now, now, you'll trip over if you rush.
Hey, Yuu.
Not now.
Hey, hey, Yuu!
Will you shut it?
What do you want, Mika?
If you could escape, what would you want to do, Yuu?
Huh?
What's there to do?
The virus is everywhere outside,
and the human race is practically extinct.
I'm just saying, if we could escape to the outside with our family,
to a world without vampires...
Doesn't it sound exciting?
Just us?
Yup, just us family.
Sure, it sounds exciting enough, but...
Really?
I guess.
Looks like my work's cut out for me, then.
What?
Nope, it's nothing.
Well, I have some errands to run.
Errands? What are you up to?
Like I said, it's nothing.
Weirdo.
But his idle daydream never became reality.
The outside world is no paradise either, Mika.
Shall we go, Yuu?
What about the corporal?
I've been told he'll live to see another day.
I see. That's good.
Moreover, Lieutenant Colonel Guren has issued our squad an order.
Guren's here?
Yes.
Messages were relayed to each post.
He's at the main intersection
of West Shinjuku's fifth district,
holding off the vampires' main force.
Our backup is immediately required.
Their main force...
So we'll win if we defeat them, right?
I'm sure the vampires think the same:
defeat the Lieutenant Colonel, and they'll win.
Let's hurry and regroup
with the others at the defense line.
Then we'll head to the fifth district.
I said that's impossible!
We have orders to send all men to the defense line.
If they manage to break through,
Shinjuku will be no more!
Our own troops are at breaking point as well!
We have the extermination unit there, don't we?
Only three members, all of whom are young kids!
On the other hand, the enemy has a partisan platoon!
Yuu!
It's only a matter of time until we're defeated.
Fine. We'll send our own platoon.
What's the—
Excuse me!
By "extermination unit," did you mean the Moon Demon Company?
Um, I'm not sure.
Who are you guys?
We're from the Moon Demon—
The three you mentioned.
Was it a girl with two other guys?
Y-Yes, that's right.
Where are they fighting?
Shinjuku Central Park.
We'll handle it.
Send the squads to the defense line, got it?
Wait, Yuu!
Think properly for a second!
We don't know for certain that it's them.
We mustn't act on brash assumptions.
Backing up Lieutenant Colonel Guren
is our top priority!
Even he would have trouble
against the enemy's main force.
Shinjuku's defense line is crumbling.
Right now, we're the only ones who can support him!
Shit, they just keep on coming.
Mito and I will cover you.
You go after the commander.
Sounds like a plan.
I'm counting on you!
This is most intriguing.
If only Thirteenth Progenitor Crowley had made it,
things would have started looking up.
Oh, well.
Lacus, Rene.
Round up the others and fend off the humans,
minus that impetuous monster.
Yes, sir.
Leave it to us.
So, Mika.
Perhaps I'll finally be able to see you,
Third Progenitor Krul Tepes' favorite, in action.
You and I will kill that disdainful man.
Understood?
I can handle him myself.
Ah, most heroic.
He'll regret ever drawing his blade against me.
Come, my sword.
My, how scary indeed.
We're close, Yuu!
Yeah.
Thanks.
For coming.
The Lieutenant Colonel did say that we were a family.
And to put our life on the line for this family.
Dumbass.
What?
He said that as well, remember?
Can't say I do.
There it is.
Shinjuku Central Park!
Yoichi, behind you!
Damn it!
Of course everything goes to shit
without the dumbass and the midget.
It's because we can't assemble into a formation.
Here they come!
Don't write me off yet!
Kimizuki, behind you!
Die!
Yuu!
Yuu?
Eyes on the enemy, Mitsu.
Where are the enemy troops?
Dead on the ground.
The one you just killed was the last.
What?
Holy shit, you guys! Nice work!
Not really. I'm just better than you.
So? What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I heard you guys were in knee-deep, so I came to the rescue.
Like we needed it.
Hell, the mission was to regroup at the defense line.
You said that.
I know.
I know, but...
But what?
Don't tell me you thought we'd die that easily.
Have some faith in us, will you?
Yeah, I got it.
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry, then don't do it again.
Let's go.
But if the same thing happens tomorrow, I'm coming.
What?
Were you listening to me?
Don't get me wrong, I trust you guys.
But I'm still coming.
Tomorrow, the day after,
and forever.
My bad. I forgot you were a serious case of braindead.
Save your breath, Kimizuki.
You just can't fix stupid.
Actually, the more you say it, the more stupid he gets.
C'mon, guys!
Now, now.
Well, then.
Since the rain has let up, shall we go?
Yeah.
Now that all five of us are here.
Yuu.
All right, let's do this!
I'm gonna slaughter all those damn vampires!
Oh, what do we have here?
You're a vicious one, aren't you?
Am I?
I wish I could say the same for you.
Detonate: Fudou Myou-Ou Spell.
Tsk, you can dodge that? Give me a break.
The explosion was far too slow.
Besides, did you really expect such
old spellcraft to work against vampires?
Never a disappointment, Mika.
Overwhelming power and arrogance.
But if you don't watch your step,
that arrogance will be your downfall.
Shall I assist you?
What are you playing at?
How could I possibly lose?
Like I said: watch your step.
They never intended to fight you one-on-one.
They've caught on, Shigure.
Kill them.
Sir.
Goshi, you're up.
Way ahead of you.
Checkmate, vampire!
There we go, Mika.
Now you're in my debt.
Damn, looks like we're in deep shit now.
That silver-haired vampire is incredibly strong.
Listen, Mika.
Don't underestimate humans.
They're greedy, cunning, and tenacious.
Although saying that to a former human feels somewhat odd.
Shut up.
Well, shall we take this seriously now?
If we both work together—
I don't need you.
I know what their tactics are.
My sword, drink more of my blood.
See, what did I tell you?
Does that arrogance come from your status as someone previously human?
Looks like I'll need a second pill for these guys.
You mustn't, Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
And you mustn't look away.
Take your own damn advice.
Oh? Not bad at all.
Please don't, Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
You could die if you take more than one pill!
And if I don't, I'll be dead for sure!
Either way, we have to take them out
before the effect wears off.
Are you done talking?
Because I'm coming for you.
Well, aren't you polite?
Sorry, but could you give us a little more time?
How much more?
We need to take our medication,
so if you could shut up for twenty seconds, I'd—
Yeah, I thought as much.
Not to mention, you're even faster than before.
I'm not holding back anymore.
Holding back on the battlefield?
Very childish, don't you think?
Not when that very same child is about to kill you.
Oh, man.
Looks like it's the end of the line.
Oh?
Enemy backup spotted.
Mika, you'd better wrap things up quickly.
Shit! Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
Everyone, please take a pill!
We'll rescue the Lieutenant Colonel and retreat!
Let's go!
Yeah!
This is it, human.
You shitter.
Guren!
Get...
Get the fuck away from Guren!
Yet another human...
This is such a chore.
Y-Yuu?
Huh?
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Childhood
Reunion
"Childhood Reunion."