Mitsuki returned to work
for the first time
since the cancelled
commercial audition.
But Full Moon was everyone's topic
of gossip at the television station.
Furthermore, someone had cut her
costume to shreds
and she was in a big pinch
very early in her comeback!
But they overcame the problem
with Mitsuki's idea and
the TV recording finished
without a hitch.
This girl has gotten really tough!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
My first solo performance?
I thought it might be
a little soon, but...
There have been so many
requests from fans.
So we decided to just pluck up
the courage and do it!
Are you serious?
It's like a dream.
You won't be saying cute things
like that for long.
Starting now you'll be very busy.
Your summer vacation is completely lost,
so prepare for it.
I will!
And so as an experiment for
this first live show,
won't you take part in the planning?
What?! Me...take part?
Yes.
We want you to put
your present feelings
into this as much as possible, Full Moon.
My present feelings?
Isn't there something?
An image or a keyword,
anything is fine, just say it.
Maybe I'm asking too much, after all.
No, I'll do it.
Please let me do it!
W-What's going on?!
Today I will explain the importance of
concepts for live shows.
Huh?
She's messed up.
Darn it!
I give up on these!
Anyway! For a good live show,
something like an image,
or a theme is important!
Oh, about that, I...
After all, when you wrote lyrics,
you were so distressed,
it was difficult, right?
That's why Meroko will help this time.
Like she said, that's...
It's like, Meroko is too thoughtful
and like, the number one candidate
for the wife of a Death Spirit!
This is no good.
I know that everyone thinks so.
Um... Meroko?
Listen to what people say!
Mitsuki already knows that.
You know?
Well, what do you intend to do?
It's Full Moon's first live show!
Yeah, the theme is the moon and stars.
The moon and stars?
Yes, I've decided that Full Moon's
live performance's theme
is going to be the moon and stars.
You decided?!
Takuto! If you'd decided,
couldn't you have said something?!
I kept trying to say something
but you weren't listening, were you?
No way!
Meroko's disappointed.
Thank you, Meroko,
for worrying about me.
Actually, this live concert
will be distributed
throughout the world
through the internet.
That's why, surely...
I realized you were always next to me.
Why do I like you so much?
Your voice echoes and
it sounds almost sad.
Up to now who was supporting me?
I realize, now that I'm far away.
What was supporting me?
The moon and stars.
I'll put all of my thoughts for Eichi
in the moon and stars
and sing with all my might.
Watch it, okay, Eichi?
I...I can't...I can't breathe!
We've decided on Bayside Hall
for Full Moon's first live performance!
We've confirmed that doors
will open at 5 and we start at 6, right?
Yes, furthermore we already
put the order in yesterday
for sets and lighting.
How about musicians?
We've already gathered the best people!
We're right on the mark
for a background chorus.
Good. Have you assembled
the dancers?
Yes, we've gathered foreign dancers
with great experience.
Good.
That's perfect.
They're really excited.
Yep!
Everyone is working so hard
for my live show!
The posters are hot off the presses.
- Hmm...
- Looks great!
Wow, it's beautiful!
Yes, it's well done.
Okay! This is finally the start
of Moon and Stars!
Let's work hard!
Yes!
Moon and Stars...
It's the first live concert!
And so you're in the middle
of preparations?
Yes, I think it's going to be
a really good show.
Please come everyone.
- Yay!
- Go for it, Full Moon!
Yes, I'll work hard!
Yep, leave it to me.
I'll advertise it perfectly.
Thank you.
Actually, my children are
big fans of Full Moon.
I'll go see the show with my kids.
Do your best.
I will!
Here, take this.
I definitely want you to come, Mr. Akiba.
This is the best!
To be able to see your first live show
in seats this good...
As your fan, this is really exciting!
Put these posters all over
the inside of the store!
Okay, I've got it.
Big Sister Full Moon.
I'm cheering you on, so be
sure to make your concert cool!
I know, leave it to me.
I'm going to work my hardest!
Takuto, you cheer her on, too.
Yeah!
Promise!
Yep, I promise!
Yeah!
Thanks for everything today!
Hey, do well at your live show.
I'm rooting for you.
I will.
Ms. Komaki...
Thank you very much!
Oh, so it's her first
live performance, huh?
Everyone, come to my first show, okay!
- Yay!
This will be the site of
your live concert.
Wow, it's big!
This is a starter before you
go out on bigger and bigger stages.
If you're surprised by this much,
we're in trouble.
Um... Can I try standing on it?
Of course you can.
It's your stage.
I'm gonna do my best!
I-I'm home.
Hey!
You're late!
Sorry.
Whoa there.
She should at least change her clothes.
That's right, and you have
to care for your skin.
Hey you little brat! Wake up!
Yes!
My first live performance,
Moon and Stars,
please come and see it.
Wow, she's really groggy
with sleep.
Jeez. She's helpless.
Do your best.
Good night.
Come in.
I wonder if it's done.
Yes!
How is it?
It's good,
but doesn't it lack impact?
You're right.
I feel like something's missing.
Shall we try making it showier
with accessories?
And...
- Huh?
Change her make up
so it's more colorful.
What? What? What?
How about like this?
Well...
Since it's come to this,
I'll take more of a risk!
Oh, I'm sorry! It will come off
in no time at all.
Let's see...
Where did I put it?
This is...
What are you doing, Mitsuki?
Full Moon?
Done!
It's the moon and stars!
Yep, it's cute!
Okay, with this as the starting point,
let's take a fresh look at the costume!
Lovely!
We put a bit of effort into it.
Thank you, Machi!
Since that's done,
next are accessories.
Yes, that's right, the theme is...
- Moon and Stars!
Okay, let's work this thoroughly!
Yes!
Um... After that one is this!
Oh... I wonder if this one
is better than that.
Don't sleep!
But I'm so sleepy!
Meroko, weren't you ready
and willing to help?
The too thoughtful number one
candidate for a wife, right?!
Eichi.
It's pretty, isn't it?
Yep.
I'm sure the time will come
when you'll sparkle just like the
moon and stars in the sky, Mitsuki.
I made a wish upon
the moon and stars.
That's why I named it
Moon and Stars, Eichi.
I want to sparkle.
For Eichi, so he can find me.
so it will reach everyone
who supports me.
It's done!
Is that all?
No.
Next I'll try doing it in this color.
At this rate, she intends to do it
until the break of dawn.
This will work.
I'll get this right over
to the accessory studio.
Yes.
Th-There's a problem!
What happened?
The event site has been cancelled!
What?!
What's going on here?!
The live performance is tomorrow!
They said that someone claiming
to be from Village Pro
called in to say that Full Moon's
concert has been cancelled!
No way!
That's complete bull!
Explain the circumstances and
book it again!
However...
They said just after that
another event took the spot.
The posters, tickets, and
everything are done, you know?!
Anyway, everyone split up
and make phone calls!
Anywhere is fine,
just pin down something that's open.
- Yes!
Yes, it's tomorrow.
I understand, excuse me.
I see, then it's no good?
It's tomorrow.
I wonder if we can find
an event site or not.
Um... What's going to happen?
Yeah, if we don't find it...
All we can do is cancel
the live performance.
What?
No way...
I don't believe it!
Serves you right.
Please do something for me.
I'm sorry, but...
Please!
Could you please go home?
The place is already taken. Sorry.
Please!
Email? I wonder who it's from.
"I'm looking forward to Full Moon's
first live concert."
The high school girls I met that day!
But...
I'm sorry.
The live concert... Now I can't do it.
It's too bad that it has to be cancelled!
It doesn't matter where you do it,
I just want to hear your live singing voice.
It's "Moon and Stars."
How chic and cool would it be
if were under the real starry night's sky.
Moon and Stars...
Under the real starry night's sky.
Yes, that's it.
I can sing songs anywhere!
Lighting over there.
- Do it quickly.
- Yes!
If you don't hurry, we'll miss the
start time for the concert!
Right!
There's been a change in the
event site of Full Moon's live concert.
It's over here.
This is the event site?
Where's Full Moon?
Okay, please start.
Okay.
Okay everyone!
Thank you for waiting.
On the last night of summer vacation.
Let's all make it exciting!
Full Moon's first live concert,
Moon and Stars, starts now!
Oh, Full Moon!
Wow, pretty!
Looks like the real moon and stars!
Using your Death Spirit powers again.
Thank you! I'll do my best!
Well, I guess its okay.
Everyone, thank you for coming
to my live concert today.
Please enjoy yourselves to the end!
So romantic.
Yeah. The best so far.
Eichi, are you watching?
Somewhere in the world!
Hey Meroko. It looks like the manager is
moving into the neighborhood.
What?! Is that okay?
Why? She said it's to support her work.
But the fact that Mitsuki is Full Moon
is absolutely a secret from her family.
See! Now she's been discovered by
Ms. Tanaka the helper!
Oh no.
Next time on Full Moon:
"Moving Panic"
- Look forward to it!