Street No. 08
"Fully-Automatic Band Music"
And Yet the Town Moves
Lost technologies.
The towering pyramids, the Nazca Lines,
the floating city of Machu Picchu.
How these were made in such ancient times
is still a mystery to this date.
And when time passes and they fulfill their purpose,
MARUKO SHOPPING DISTRICT
the monuments, which have now
lost their sense of existence,
are one day destined to disappear
without anyone's notice.
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
Kaze wa nandaka suzushige
Doyoubi no yoru wa nigiyaka
Kurai kimochi sae
Suguni harete
Minna uki uki
Uki uki
Downtown e kuridasou
Coin Laundry
Automatic
Now on Sale
It's raining hard.
We're stopped in our tracks in a place like this.
I wonder if it'll stop if we wait it out.
It was so nice out during lunchtime.
Coin Laundry
The weather is so irregular.
This is what you call a gang rain, right?
You mean guerilla rain.
Automatic
Now on Sale
We're stopped in our tracks and can't move,
so wouldn't you consider it the same as a gang?
What kind of interpretation is that?
Aw, man.
Coin Laundry
The weather forecast said it wouldn't rain.
The forecast I saw said it was going to rain.
Eh?! Why?!
Depending on the meteorologist the forecast can differ.
Automatic
Now on Sale
Who is the meteorologist that got this right?
I don't know!
Coin Laundry
I wonder if there's such a thing
as a winning percentage of meteorologists.
Like, this person is better during the summer season,
or is bad about predicting snow.
Then I'd watch the one whose forecast
is right before I leave the house.
That reminds me of those people who sell
predictions and information for a horse race.
Automatic
Now on Sale
By the way, Senpai.
What is it?
You knew it was going to rain,
but why didn't you bring an umbrella?
I left it at school.
Eeek!
Coin Laundry
I thought it was only a drizzle...
It's starting to rain big time now.
It doesn't look like it will stop anytime soon.
Automatic
Now on Sale
Coin Laundry
I'm starting to get cold.
We are here with wet clothes...
The rain during this season is cold.
Automatic
Now on Sale
I know!
Coin Laundry
We're already at a coin laundry,
so let's dry our clothes in the dryer!
If we stay like this, we'll catch a cold.
Hold on a minute.
What are you intending to wear while we dry our clothes?
Oh.
Really, you don't think about anything.
Coin Laundry
It's no problem!
In this heavy rain, no one is going to come.
Tattsun, let's dry your clothes, too.
What, no! Impossible, impossible!
It's okay, come on! Before we catch a cold!
No! I told you it's impossible!
Coin Laundry
If someone comes, you be our shield and hide us!
What? Isn't it more effective if Tattsun used
her nice figure to be our decoy?
I refuse! You have nothing to lose by
being seen, so you should be the shield!
Then size-wise, Kon-senpai has nothing to lose.
That was a great hit!
He had it captured in his core.
Well sorry that I have nothing to lose!
Oh, and here we change pitchers. Is this their last straw?
It is the last one.
My underwear is wet and it doesn't feel good...
It's the last one, huh. There's still a while to go.
Do you want to borrow that? It looks dry.
I'm sure they'd want another one at this point.
I see, then let's see if they can hang in there with this one.
No way! I don't even know whose it is.
They've been pushed to the point of being naked!
We should've dried our underwear, too.
What are you going to do if someone comes in?
A pinch, what are they going to do?
...and he hits! Will it go in? Will it go in?
Ohhh, it's a foul ball. That was close.
What are you doing, Senpai?!
Their life was spared. Their pinch still continues...
Isn't it great and liberating?
It's still damp.
It's not as bad as earlier.
It's slightly warm, too.
Ohh... It's cold.
It was warm for only one moment.
Damp clothes draw out body heat.
If you knew this, you should've said so earlier.
It looks warm on the inside of a clothes dryer...
I won't stop you, so do as you like.
You can be the dead body who died a mysterious death.
That's great. You like mysteries like that, right?
I don't want to be the victim.
I'm at my limit. Let's get something warm to drink.
Cold            Cold             Cold             Cold             Cold           Cold
They're all cold!
They must not have switched them out yet.
UDON
Hey, don't slack off and do some work!
Give us some warm coffee!
It's not something an employee playing hooky would say.
UDON
There's a vending machine for udon.
I'll buy it! I'll take anything that's warm!
UDON
What comes out of an udon vending machine?
Udon noodles in a cup?
UDON
But there's no place for this vending
machine to produce hot water.
Oh.
I don't see a hot water thermos either.
UDON
My 300 yen! Give it back!
What a demanding customer.
aera dnev eht ni tcudorp a si ereht fI
.tnemyap yna tresni ton od esaelP
ROOD GNIDNEV
AERA DNEV
On top of that, nothing's coming out. My 300 yen!
Oh, it seems like something is moving.
aera dnev eht ni tcudorp a si ereht fI
.tnemyap yna tresni ton od esaelP
ROOD GNIDNEV
AERA DNEV
Is it stuck inside?
Oh!
What is it?
It's moving! It's making the udon on the inside!
If there is a product in the vend area
Please do not insert any payment.
VENDING DOOR
VEND AREA
UDON
It came out!
What is this?!
Looks like a kitsune udon...
UDON
Hot!
Thith is fifing hot kitthune udon.
It's not a cup noodle... On top of that,
it's faster than a cup noodle!
Could this be...
Its appearance is old, but it's actually
an alien machine from the future?!
I wanna do it again!
UDON
How many bowls are you intending to eat?
I want to get a good look at how it moves!
It's not a game, you know.
I got this one, since I'll eat it too. I want something warm.
Change Return    Change Slot
Cooking in Progress
Cooking Completion in:
seconds
Oh, here it comes.
It's pouring the hot water.
And it's properly draining it.
It's putting hot water in again.
Wow, it puts the noodles through the hot water twice!
In goes the broth...
...and it's done!
Huh, that's so interesting...
UDON
Hot! The taste is not so bad either.
Hey, what about the hamburger?
How do you think that works?
UDON
If the lamp is on,
We cannot sell.
Amount inserted
Coin inserted
I'll buy it.
Hamburger    Hamburger
Let me see, let me see!
Microwave heating
HEATING                        While the light is flickering,
the item is being heated,
so please wait.
How is it? Are they making it inside?
I can't see.
Vend area
PUSH
Man... it came in a box.
They must've just heated something that was pre-made.
Hamburger
Hot! The box, I'd burn my hands on it!
Vend area
PUSH
Hamburger
These future people don't know
how to do things in moderation.
I thought they came from outer space?
Hamburger
UDON
It's a... sorta... shabby-looking box...
I'm sure it's what's inside that counts!
Hamburger
The inside looks kind of pathetic, don't you think?
Who are you calling a Pathetic Burger?!
Note: Hotori is still upset about being scolded by the policeman
for riding her (illegal) scooter in Episode 2
What are you getting angry for?!
I'm sure they're using the best ingredients.
Ingredients:
Meat product (beef, pork, chicken, mutton,
horse, rabbit & etc)
Added ingredients (Yeast food, emulsifier, Artificial
flavoring, Spices, Caramel Color)
Ingredients. Meat product (beef, pork,
chicken, mutton, horse, rabbit, & etc).
UDON
See? They use so many different types. It's so luxurious.
What about the stores that boast 100% beef?
In any case, they went as far as listing "rabbit,"
so I wonder what other meats are not listed.
I'm sure it's this...
A part-time worker at a burger shop
opens the refrigerator at night and sees...
I know. A meow burger, right?
You're like a cat, Kon-senpai,
so won't this be cannibalism?
That's an urban legend.
Butchering a cat is a bigger hassle and more expensive.
It may be edible worms.
UDON
Edible worms are high-quality food.
What kind of high-quality gourmet is that?
UDON
Coins Accepted
Change Release
Okay. I'm going to try the
ham and cheese on toast as well.
Toasting
Whoa! Hot, hot, hot, hot!
UDON
Aren't they all too hot?
Aliens don't know how to do things in moderation.
=Caution=
Contents are HOT
See, it says “Contents are hot. Please be careful.”
Please be careful
UDON
It's not written in Esperanto?
What is that?
It's the common language of Earth.
That was yummy.
We're all warm now.
After all, food tastes better
when there's a playfulness like this.
I don't think the person who designed this
was playing; they were serious.
I know!
What Seaside is missing is this playfulness!
If we have a playful heart,
coffee that's a little bad will taste better, I'm sure!
We need to prioritize learning how to make good
coffee before playfulness, don't you think?
Oh, it looks like it's about to stop raining.
Mmm. I love the smell of freshly dried laundry.
Arashiyama
I'm a bit hungry.
Coin Laundry
I went through the trouble of finding this oasis
in the city, so I have to utilize it at times like this.
Hm?
UDON
Lost technology of ancient culture.
Time will pass, and one day, these monuments
are fated to disappear without anyone's notice.
Coin Laundry
However, until then they will continue
to live amongst people.
It's making poko-poko noises
as the water boils, poko.
I-it won't open.
S-Sanada?
Sorry to trouble you, but can you open this for me?
Sure.
I'm sorry, Sanada. You're a customer...
Thank you!
After all, a task that requires strength
has to be done by a man.
What's wrong?
A jar! Please find a jar!
One with a really tight lid!
I'm going to have Sanada open it for me!
Found it!
Sudachi
Jam
Grrr... Jar...!
Seaside
Tattsun is a widow!
Don't make me out to be some sort of troubled person!
That can't be...!
Stop slacking off.
Yes ma'am.
Head Maid, your stocking has a run in it.
Oh.
Hey, what are you doing?
Pervert, don't tell me you...!
N-no I didn't...!
That can't be...!
Sanada, did you do something to the Head Maid...?!
FRESH FISH SANADA
It's a nightmare that won't leave my mind.
I saw something that I didn't want to,
and so it's a Sanada Memorial.
Osaka specialty Pokopoko Heddoya! Poko.
Not as if someone initiates it, but gradually the days
start changing and people become distracted.
The seasons come around again... a season for festivals.
It's still a month early, but I see preparation
for the school festival here and there...
There are people who wait all year just to
participate in the school festival. So stupid.
You think so?
Not really...
Why isn't our class doing anything?
Let's participate in the school festival, too!
There are lots of people who pulled out
because of their club activities.
Maybe there isn't enough manpower?
Next year, let's do something with everyone in the class!
A high school festival can only
be done during high school!
Even though it’s you Hotori,
you’re saying something that’s valid.
What about a play?!
I'll write the script!
I have an idea I've had kicking around!
Jelly Island Murder!
That's the one where I get killed, isn't it?
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Seaside
I got rights to get on stage!
But first, curry and coffee.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey! Not "yeah!" but "yes!"
Don't let your guard down
no matter who the other person is.
Yeah, yeah.
And? What did you get?
Are you planning to sleep over in some mountain lodge?
Not a cottage, a stage, you moron!
I'm surprised that Kon-senpai could return Hotori's joke.
Even I didn't understand.
They held a lottery for the right to play
the outdoor stage on the third day of the festival.
I got one.
Let's put together a band!
We're not sure about singing in front of people...
Who said you would be the vocals?
That's right. You're tone-deaf.
What?! You've never heard me sing!
I don't have to hear it!
Your face looks like you're tone-deaf!
Actually, she is below average.
How does he know?! Has he gone to
karaoke with Hotori or something?
I'll do the vocals and bass!
You do the instruments.
A guitar, or keyboard... You can play something, right?
Normally, people won't be able to do something like that.
That's right.
Hotori...
When you were in elementary school
I taught you something. What about that?
Oh! I can do something that's not unlike a keyboard.
Come to think of it, I have dabbled
in something that's not unlike a guitar.
For real?!
Ho ho, to think I could get my members together
so quickly and conveniently!
I know where to go for drums, too.
Light
Music
Club
It's just like you to do this, Kon-senpai!
Haribara. You have too much movement in your feet
so you get tired later in the game,
and your movements become sluggish.
For someone like you,
I thought up a training regimen that would put
you in the habit of planting the lower body
and handling everything with your upper body.
Senpai!
Light
Music
Club
Great! I have my members!
Because there is a back side, there is no front, poko.
I do think I messed up, getting all excited
without even checking.
I'll give in... Begrudgingly give in...
and agree that the accordion is not unlike a keyboard.
Okay.
ORCHESTRAL CLUB
Is that a guitar? Huh?!
There are strings.
If any instrument with strings is considered a guitar,
then a harp, or a Taisho Koto, or even a
right triangle would become a guitar!
The right triangle has no strings, but a hypotenuse.
That's right, a hypotenuse.
You don't even know and
you're just playing along, aren't you?
Oh well...
I should be thankful that you're even doing this with me.
It's not like there aren't bands like this.
Kon-senpai's selfish requests have got me in trouble.
You say that, but you seem to be
enjoying this an awful lot.
When I think that this will continue until after
the school festival ends, I get a headache.
But it's a good thing to have
worked on something so hard.
Hey, hey, what kind of cafe
has this place turned into this time?
A singing cafe! Go and sing something!
—The day of the School Festival—
59TH ANNUAL SCHOOL FESTIVAL
FLEA
MARKET
GRILLED CHICKEN
Masters
80 yen
Special
SAUCE
SALT
Pork Miso Soup
Badminton
Pork
It's delicious
Uh-huh.
Parental Devotion
Sample
Who drew this manga?
Oh, the person here...
It's good!
Ah... Th-thanks.
CRAM
What about this 4-panel manga?
Oh, that's me.
Manga
Research
Society
It's interesting!
Thank you!
Manga
Research
Society
Oh, I was in the middle of shopping
for takoyaki and Korean pancakes.
Takoyaki, pancakes...
...on three!
You're not going to buy?!
Takoyaki, pancakes...
Friendship
Bazaar
Let's see, the fresh spring rolls are in the
north building, 3rd floor, Gymnastics Club...
Oya High School Festival
Guide Book
Tatsuno, the yakitori is at the tent in the school field.
Let's gather all these quickly and eat.
What else do I need to get...
Um...
Just for a little bit... I want to walk around
the school festival with you, Sanada.
Huh?
I didn't become fat! I grew, poko.
I'm the kind of person, and I understand this
myself, who's really self-centered,
or should I say self-conscious sometimes...
But at the more important parts,
I'm very shy... And so... um...
But tomorrow, I'll play the violin the best I can, and so...
Of course, you don't even have to ask.
I'll come and watch.
What should I do? This is no different
from me confessing my feelings!
Tatsuno joined the band to overcome her shyness.
Good for her! I'd like to see it through.
What are those two doing?
Can they not even go shopping properly?
The takoyaki and okonomiyaki I went to
the trouble of buying is going to get cold!
Note: Again, Hotori messed up what she was assigned to get.
She was supposed to get Korean pancakes, not okonomiyaki
DEAR HOTORI,
THAT'S TAKOYAKI
AND KOREAN
PANCAKES,
GOT IT?!!
—Last Day—
59TH ANNUAL SCHOOL FESTIVAL
Full volume lullaby...
Today is the last day!
Potato Man                 Judo Club         200 yen
Traditional Boiled Potatoes
What was 200 yen is now 50 yen!
Take it home for 50 yen!
Gymnastics Club
Fresh     Spring Rolls
LEGS
We've sold out.
Gymnastics Club has sold out!
Outdoor stage
Performers
Green Room
Person in Charge:
3-D Watanabe
Of course, you don't even have to ask.
I'll come and watch.
Ohhh, why such a thing...
Tatsuno, are you nervous?
It's okay! Just take what you have practiced
and throw it out there as it is!
Then the results will come naturally!
B-but I'm not nervous.
Why don't you shut up, blowfish face!
B...?!
B-blowfish face?!
I've never been so mortified in my life!
This one I can't forgive,
you high-and-mighty Glasses-face!
Stop it, I was fooled into learning the drums!
It's a training scam!
Right now, that's irrelevant!
Stop this internal fighting!
What are you doing, shaking things up
so close to the performance?!
Kon-senpai...
I-
I lost!
Oh? Deja vu!
Then, please get ready.
Before I go to bed, I practice throwing shuriken, poko.
Now, the final act on the outdoor stage,
the 4-girl rock band "Maids"!
"Maids" is a play on words from
how much all of this was a maze
and how their costume is a maid outfit.
Well then, your performance please!
Don't believe what I say
If you go the opposite way as me, you won't go wrong
A cloud flew over the southern sky
We say good-bye to a groggy day
Who is on vocals?
It's Kon.
No way?!
Maids!
It wasn't supposed to happen this way
Hoi!
I didn't intend it to be this way
This is not rock
Hoihoi!
This is not rock!
Hoihoihoi!
Don't believe my tears
There's something appealling about it.
It feels like rock in a way.
What does it say on that girl's apron? Seaside...?
The back of my words have thorns
Kon-senpai!
In the east sky came a UFO
Isn't just the bass awfully good?
We say good-bye to a confusing day
Her singing is kind of like SION.
You're going to make SION mad.
You may say that but there is someone
Waiting at the edge of the world
It may not go as you think
But this is a season for plentiful harvest
We are super precocious maids
Chaos, cosmos entropy-hyara don don
Here, let's hit it one time
Vamos, mammoth, Setsuna Meio, bye-bye
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oioioi!
It's not "hoi!" I told you, it's "oi!"
Bye-bye
And so...
After a clean-up day, school resumes.
There, the remains of the festival
have gone away without a trace.
Hi, Fu, Hi, Fu, Mi, Yo!
Taikutsuya rock damashi tazusaete
Hitorigurashi no bakuon jinsei
Tennen no chouchin fugu na hoppeta de
Machi wo kaosu ni kyo mo makikomu
Tsundere wa intelligence no akashi nari
Kyou mo kareni wa naze ka kokurezu
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatako
Konna band mo yarase ja ne
Konna member rock ja ne
Mezashite iruno wa ondo ja ne
Tadori tsuku no wa nehan ja ne
Warera wa Meido "Yeah!"
Meido sugata de
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kokora wa meido "Yeah!"
Jiken genba wa
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ahhhh..."
Muteki no meido "Yeah!"
Benpi wa nanzan
Kancho kancho!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kiyoku tadashiku isagiyoku
Seaside wa zessan! Eigyouchu!!
"Meido arigatou gozaimasu!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
Hey, listen!
When I bought a red-bean ball at the
snack store, I got a winner for the first time!
I got another ball!
Where would it say the red-bean ball is a winner?
When you bite into it, there's a ball
inside of the shell instead of red bean,
and when you turn that in, you get another one!
But doesn't that mean you've
only gotten the extra shell for free?
Oh?! That's true!
I was so excited about winning,
I couldn't see through its true nature!
Cafe Seaside
Next episode, Street Number Nine,
"Smash! Adult Shopping Plan."
Cafe Seaside
STREET NO. 09 "SMASH! ADULT SHOPPING PLAN"
We'll turn softly around and around, poko.
Cafe Seaside