When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Hayate has been rather low on sleep lately.
The reason for that... is a bit like this.
I love you, Brenda.
Why are you here?! Why did you
wake me?! Why try to seduce me?!
Wh-What the?!
Don't look at me like I look delicious!
I'm going to be eaten!
Stop! Don't eat me!
I'm an afro.
I won't taste good!
I'm bland!
I'm an afro.
Wait, it's a dream!
It seems kind of afro-ish...
Afro...
Wait, what?!
An afro?!
Pardon me for interrupting your nifty scene,
but who are you showing off for
and what are you showing off?
Oh, this way!
More like, who?
Nabeshin! He looks good in an afro.
Nabeshin! He apparently
owns four red jackets.
Nabeshin! An immature director,
who was invited by Kawaguchi
and shamelessly came on the show.
Nabeshin! Creates
opportunities for tons of jabs!
The number of women he's done is...
Or rather, this is an awfully old intro.
That's news to me!
This is our current intro.
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Huh, so this is the current intro.
I want a redo using this.
It's a lot of work to reanimate, you know!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Devil Hunter Welcome Yoko Isumi,
and Nabeshin
Um, the episode title screen is over...
What? Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay...
Then I guess I'll do this.
And ignore the script.
It's hard to tell
if he's motivated or not...
I'll be turning 43 this year.
So what about it?!
Mystery Woman
The machine clinging to my legs
cries out! It's a Walther P38!
C-Could it possibly be...?!
Hayate Ayasaki...
Was that right, Mikako?
Something like that, Director.
It seems sort of fated
that everything's going to vanish.
Time for you to go!
That's from Ame-Yoko, isn't it?
What? H-How did you know that?
There's a Nakata and
Company's label on the grip.
What? F-For real?
Wait, you're right. Looks so cheap!
Nakata and Company is...
But I'm still shooting you!
This Week's Butler Battle
Listen to the narration!
So what if I can't handle hot food?!
A-Are you serious?!
He's fast! Or actually, he's crazy!
Escape
Um, what are you doing?
Oh, sorry, storyboard deadline.
And we're cutting it next week.
Storyboards for anime?
Basically.
Oh, I never introduced myself.
Director Shinichi Watanabe
Address: 29-29 Nerima Town,
Nerima City, Nerima Prefecture
It's supposedly a pretty rare business card.
"Shinichi Watanabe". "Nabeshin" for short...
Yup, yup. Directing anime and voice
performances is my main occupation.
Being a butler's a part-time job,
so don't disturb me.
Disturb you? But you're
the one who started...
And he falls asleep now?!
Mr. Nabeshin, please wake up!
Don't sleep like a log on the show!
Oh, sorry. I didn't get
any sleep again last night.
An all-nighter?
Last night, on a park swing...
Why is it Kawaguchi?!
The thing that's wrong
with Kawaguchi is that...
Ecstasy
I never asked to hear about Mr. Kawaguchi.
Topple
Mr. Nabeshin, what is it now?!
I-I'm hungry.
Working night after night in the park?
Apparently.
And an afro for no purpose...
It really is for no purpose.
In this day and age,
he's like a protected species.
Uh-huh...
I must safeguard him.
What?! That's where this is going?!
Seconds!
Yes, yes, don't worry about weight gain
and eat as much as you like.
Don't trouble yourself on my account!
May I ask for one more thing?
Once more, please.
May I invite my wife and kid, too?!
Y-Yes, you may.
They're already wolfing it down
before you even said that!
Don't trouble yourself on our account!
Thanks for the food.
You finished that food amazingly quickly.
That was yum-yum.
The dessert is yum-yum, too.
Yum-yum!
She was my kind of maid. Where did she go?
Do you mean Maria?
She's busy with a lot of things, so...
As thanks for the meal,
I was going to show her the DVD
of us on "Welcome Newly-Weds!"
We weren't newly-weds at the time, though.
You can at least watch it, Hayate.
I don't care about something like that.
What do you mean "something like that"?!
I-I'm busy with a lot
of things to do, so bye!
Hold on, Hayate!
Please explain regarding "something
like that" in the Kansai dialect.
I'm gonna getcha!
I'm sorry!
Hayate had the following thought...
I can't put up with this anymore!
I don't want this! You can't! I reject it!
And this is one of my shows.
So mean! No fair! Slow! How far?!
It brings back memories!
Shoot! I'm dancing to their tune!
Isn't this enough already?!
And this is the bucket-shaped
washing machine we won on the show.
So useless!
What is the big idea here?
Whoever gets away with it wins, Kobayashi!
I'll do it! Backwards!
It's no use. At this rate,
never mind the residence,
Lululu, Excel!
this entire anime is
going to get taken over.
Lalala, Excel!
All right, I'll say it!
I'm sorry.
What?
Please forgive my husband.
Please.
What?
Just as tuna will die
if they're not continually swimming,
my husband can't survive
unless he's continually in the spotlight.
How unfortunate...
This is not exactly by way of an apology,
Nabeshin
Desktop Calendar
but please take these.
What are these things?
These are trifling things, but...
They're my husband's Comiket goods.
Y-You're giving them to me?
Please buy them. At retail price.
I don't want them! I mean, ma'am!
I'm outta here!
I said that enough is enough
is enough is enough!
Hayate.
Look, look.
Please leave!
Tama!
Meow!
Thank you for having us!
To hell with afros... To hell with afros...
Hayate...?
Another afro?!
It's a wig, though.
Hayate! I said, Hayate!
She's been calling for you for a while now.
Thank you for your kindness!
It seems Isumi is heading over here.
What? Isumi is?
That's right. And she's coming alone!
Iz A Shopping Arcade
Alone?
That's right.
Members of Isumi's household
informed me, so there's no mistake.
Iz Headed Ur Way
Where am I?
But Isumi...
...gets so terribly lost every single time.
Where am I?
She knows she'll get lost,
so why does she always go out alone?
That's easy!
She actually thinks
of herself as a reliable person.
I shall be fine next time.
Glint
That's what she thinks.
What?!
But she always ends up
getting lost anyway.
That's why she's oddly... you know.
"You know"?
She's stubborn.
I am an oddly stubborn person.
Where am I?
She had gotten lost, as always.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
I am in trouble. I am in trouble,
but I shall be fine today!
Glint
Ta-da
Why? Because I have a cell phone with me.
If I use this, it will tell me where I am now
and what path I should take.
And the girl thought...
"There is nowhere to punch in numbers!
Stare...
"The latest and greatest cell phone!
"With a 240 megapixel camera
with shake reduction
Stare...
"and a 1seg receiver.
"And it apparently has
the ability to play music,
"but no buttons!
"Come to think of it,
it looks like it might open...
"Yes! Open! It opens! This is
something that undoubtedly opens!"
Open sesame!
Open sesame-sesame!
Open sesame and salt!
This cell phone is broken...
It's yer head that's broken!
S-Sakuya... That hurt...
Why the heck?! Why can't
ya open a cell phone?!
What are you, Kars?!
Have ya stopped thinkin'?!
Kars is...
Boom
Isumin Kick!
(Isumin kikku!)
Sniff, sniff, smoked egg smells good.
(Kun-kun kun-tama ii nioi.)
I swear! Ya play the dummy
to the hilt all day long.
So? What the heck are ya doin' here?
I am not telling someone who smacks
people's heads with paper fans.
Eh?
Incidentally, if it's Nagi's
house, it's over that way.
I-I was just about to head
that way as well...
Ah, sorry 'bout that.
But...
Will ya be able to get there?
A missy who can't even use a cell phone
and has zero sense of direction...
Well, don't ya worry.
I'll make sure ya get there.
I-I do not really need your help to...
Yeah, okay, okay. I get it, I get it.
Please help!
I get it, I get it.
Crap... Crap... This is bad!
Please, help us!
Splish-splash!
Crap! This is bad!
Hallucinatin' in the middle of town is bad!
For the sake of us
boys 'n girls' bright future,
this kinda immorality
shouldn't be permitted!
Calm down, Sakuya.
This fish is not a hallucination.
What? But ya don't see 'em at the fish shop.
He is a kind of land god.
A "land god"?
He is harmless.
But...
Truly what I would expect
of the famed Lady Isumi!
Color me surprised!
So? How may I help you?
Yes, the truth is...
We would like your help
in defeating a monster.
Defeating a monster?
Isn't he a monster?!
Goodness, no!
A monster has been ravaging our pond lately
and we are at our wits' end!
Truly, we feel as doomed
as a carp on a cutting board!
Just kidding.
Let's go Isumi.
This place'll also be swallowed
up by the Sea of Decay soon.
A god who says such worthless
things can just go 'n perish.
Oh, please!
Wait, Sakuya.
A monster formidable enough
to trouble the land...
Even if he is a "worthless god",
A worthless god?!
it still bothers me.
Even if he's mad worthless?
Even if he is mad worthless!
Thank you very much!
Some of the remarks were hurtful,
but that aside, thank you very much!
Lighthearted afro...
Wonderful afro...
What's with that tedious afro?
Please rewatch the first half later.
Full-bodied afro...
Still, as always, Isumi is late...
Um, shall I go check on her?
I suppose... Then, I'm sorry,
but I'll be counting on you.
Isumi is delicate,
so I'm worried that she may be
getting hassled by some weirdo.
Ya sure got hassled by a weirdo...
Though, I kinda knew ya
had a strange power...
Is it 'cause these monsters're always
hasslin' ya that yer always gettin' lost?
I suppose... I think I get
hassled maybe 2-3 times a year.
Then that's not it!
But he is not a monster, you know.
What?
He is a land god. A fairy born
out of nature, if you will.
Callin' somethin' like this a "fairy"
totally ruins the image
for the like of Tinker Bell.
Then what're monsters?
Monsters are beings that have
attained supernatural powers.
Beings that've attained supernatural powers?
For example, they say that if a cat
licks lamp oil every night for 20 years,
it attains supernatural powers
and becomes a goblin cat.
I see...
And people, too.
If they attain supernatural powers
somehow, they become ogres.
Beings who have thus attained
such powers are called "monsters".
Then, the monster that's
troublin' him is also...?
Yes.
Considering he is a carp,
it is probably the koi herpes virus,
which has been rampant lately,
attaining supernatural powers
to become a monster...
We will call it...
...the Koi Herpes Monster!
What the hell's up with that?!
Hey, you!
Carp?
What did the Koi Herpes Monster do to ya?!
What did he do? Well...
Blush
H-He turned me into live sashimi.
Is that somethin' to blush
about?! Live sashimi?!
It was when I was doing
synchronized swimming in the pond...
And yer just gonna start
narratin' the flashback?!
Carpassion synchro-, love-nized...
What are you doing?! No! Nooo!
Stop! Don't be so rough!
Don't force my skin off!
What did I just say?!
Whoops, I forgot the wasabi.
Wasabi. Wasabi.
This is my chance!
Now's my chance to run!
Right now, I can get away!
Though I'm not quite full-fleshed!
So the Koi Herpes Monster bastard
tried to eat ya with wasabi?
De-fin-itely.
What a bastard.
If it were me, I'd definitely
do carp cooked in miso soup.
Nooo! Don't!
Anything but that!
Please have mercy...
Quit doin' synchronized
swimmin' in the carp miso soup!
More like, ya like synchronized
swimmin' that much?!
Ya in love with it?! Ya just can't stop?!
A bit...
Even so, he is technically a land god,
so the paper fan is a bit...
Visually, it evokes domestic violence, too,
so you may suffer divine retribution...
But don't ya think she'd like it?
What?
If ya tell Nagi 'bout this,
she could use it as material for her manga.
I cannot do that.
Huh? Why not? It's funny.
Ya don't come across
stories like this every day.
Nagi is excessively terrified of the dark.
I could never tell her this.
Come to think of it, when did she
become so scared of the dark?
I didn't think she was so bad
with it way back when.
So, something did happen, huh?
I never intended...
...to make her cry like that.
I'm scared!
That is why I will never hurt
a friend of mine ever again.
That's quite a grand
resolution, little girl!
Th-That voice!
So he's...
That's right! I'm the Koi Herpes Monster,
who became a monster
by attaining supernatural powers.
And my name is the Great Koi Herpes Monster!
He's got the same exact
namin' sensibility as you.
No, he tacked on a "Great".
He is the one! He tried
to turn me into live sashimi!
Or actually, he didn't try, he did!
You think he can win against me,
now that you brought
this person to help you?!
Shuddup, Anpanman's enemy!
I am not Anpanman's enemy!
I am the Great Koi Herpes...
Bye-bycteria!
I am busy, so I will make this brief.
Switching on work mode.
Yer merciless when ya get like this.
Crap!
We can't have you underestimating us!
Herpes!
I see. He's a virus, so he multiplies.
This is a large undertaking.
Yeah.
Then, I am going to use an enormous power,
so you draw the attention of the enemy
while I do that, Sakuya.
Huh?!
Not to worry. Humans cannot
contract the koi herpes virus!
Twinkle
"Twinkle"?! This isn't an issue
of if I can contract it or not, is it?!
Or actually, ya just said
it all cool and stuff!
I will never hurt a friend
of mine ever again.
Ya said so!
You are full of energy, so you will be fine.
Ya moron! I'm pretty frail, too, ya know!
Wait, where'd the Carp God go?
Oh...
Mr. Great Monster, Mr. Great Monster,
they were just talking about you guys,
saying, "Aren't they a rip-off
of the Black Devil on 'The Funnies'?"
Ya fool! What're ya saying'?!
And I mean that in all kinds of ways!
We aren't a rip-off! We were inspired by it!
Like it matters!
We're not letting you live,
no matter what it takes!
And I get cornered in 4 scenes?!
Die in another 2 scenes!
Watch out!
Butler-in-debt...
Are you all right, Sakuya?
Just what I would expect of my dear Hayate.
He appears like a sudden gale
when there is someone in trouble.
A new player, huh?
But one additional kid won't matter...
Huh?
Who are these people, who look like
they're a rip-off of underling suits?
We're not rip-offs! We're...
So who are these weird people?!
They're not people! They're monsters!
The carp miso soup asked
Isumi to defeat 'em!
Eat this!
Super Letter M Straddle Combining!
I also got cornered easily!
We're in big trouble!
Eight Leaves, Sixth Form...
Isu...mi?
...Crush and Destroy.
Th-This can't be...
Then, was that strange incident also...
...Isumi's doing?
Please keep this a secret from Nagi.
Now, shall we go to Nagi's place?
Yes! Wait, Isumi, it's this way.
Sheesh, ya can never be too sure with ya.
No live sashimi! No carp miso soup, either!
Wait, it's over.
Woohoo! Now I can go
synchronized swimming again!
Do whatever you want.
Ah! So you're finally here, Isumi.
And Hayate, good work.
What?!
Yes, well...
Bring everyone tea then.
Yes, please leave it to me.
Say, mind if I ask ya one thing?
Ya know that thing ya did?
With that power of yers,
I think ya could've won
without me drawin' the enemy away.
How 'bout it?
Oh...
I cannot tell someone who smacks
people's heads with paper fans.
Wha?! Ya were still holdin'
that against me?!
You give me far too much credit, Sakuya.
Liar!
Arg! The way ya said
that totally pisses me off!
Those two get along well, don't they?
Well, of course, they're friends.
Why? Why?!
I'm dissolvin' our friendship!
This is good-bye!
I'm positively denyin' ya!
Arg!!!
Friends, huh?
You are good, afro!
You, too, Mr. Carp.
Friends!
That's right, you have to take good
care of your friends and afro hair.
Next time, they will fight
against another familiar-looking
super pretty-boy butler.
Carp cooked in miso soup
with the sashimi I found!
Thanks for the meal!
I am Nabeshin, da-da-da!
I look good in an afro, da-da-da!
Whoever gets away with it wins.
I hate tedious afros!
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate...
Ayumu Nishizawa's
Lettering by Mikako Takahashi
and Ayumu Nishizawa's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Ooh, Yah, Tah! I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I am Ayumu Nishizawa.
Miss Nishizawa, you have
appeared in every single episode,
but we rarely get to
meet in the show, do we?
I know! I envy you, Sanzenin.
Even the poor hamster apparently has fans,
so we've prepared a fan service scene today.
It's a scene that really pushes the limit!
What?! This is news to me!
Hayate, you're not allowed to look!
What?! That's easy for you to say, but...
But we have no time,
so it'll have to wait until next time.
Bye-bye!
Preview
When it comes to autumn,
it's the season of culture. Right?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
So, next time will be the Hakuou
Academy culture fest episode.
As members of the student council,
we'll work hard to liven up
the culture fest, too!
So, Hayata, we'll leave the rest to you!
R-Right...
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Why?! Academy Culture Fest – Part 1".
Next Hayate the Combat Butler
Why?! Academy Culture Fest – Part 1
Did you know?
In the old days, the saury was a fish
that was used only for oil extraction.