Ôkeanos.
But what's with this change of heart?
We're heading out to town?
Nothing. I just want a change of pace.
Weren't you constantly whining
about wanting to visit the busy areas?
The joy of visiting markets in foreign lands is every bit as great as the joy of battle.
I feel really bad for the nations that got invaded for a reason like that.
What's up, boy? You say it like you actually saw it happen.
Don't worry about it.
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
And link them on to tomorrow
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Crying and embracing the night
Screaming its grief out loud
The distant ideals gently heal
These legs that've stepped forward
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
No matter where I go
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
This is horrible...
It's too much!
We worked so hard to create all this art...
How could they?!
How...
How could anyone do this and still call themselves human?!
Ryuunosuke.
Only a very select few can
comprehend true beauty and harmony.
To the vast majority of philistines,
beauty is simply something to destroy.
That is why we mustn't become
excessively attached to our creations.
All things that are given form are fated to break one day.
Instead, we creators should find
joy in the process of creation itself.
So we create just as much as they break?
Precisely!
As always, Ryuunosuke, your frank understanding is your virtue.
Maybe we had too much fun...
...so God punished us.
I'll tell you this, Ryuunosuke.
God never punishes humans!
He simply toys with them.
M-Mister?
I once committed greater atrocities and
blasphemies than had ever been done on this Earth.
But no matter how much I murdered
and defiled, no divine punishment came!
Next thing I knew, my quest for evil
had been ignored for eight whole years.
In the end, it was not God who destroyed me, but the self-interests of humans just like me.
The church and the king convicted and executed me simply because they coveted my wealth and land!
What brought an end to my evil deeds wasn't judgment or anything like it.
It was simply theft!
But, Mister...
God still exists, right?
You are faithless and never witnessed a miracle. Why would you think that?
Because the world appears to be boring...
But you just have to look to find all kinds of crazy stuff!
I've always thought this.
A world filled with so many wonderful things could never have come about by chance.
Once you decide to enjoy it for real, you'll
find no better entertainment in this world!
There's got to be an entertainer out there
who's writing a saga about five billion people.
If you wanted to describe somebody like that...
God is the only thing you could call him!
Then, Ryuunosuke, do you think God loves humans?
He's head over heels!
He couldn't possibly write the saga of this world continuously and restlessly without love!
I'm sure he has loads of fun writing it, enjoying his own work all the while.
God loves human virtues like courage and hope,
but he loves screams, blood, and despair just as much!
If he didn't, there's no way fresh intestines could be so colorful!
That's why I'm sure the world is filled with God's love!
In an era where people no longer believe
and the state has abandoned God's will...
I had no idea a faith as new and
invigorating as yours could result!
You have my admiration, Ryuunosuke, my Master!
Come on, don't make me blush!
But wouldn't my blasphemies simply be a
farce according to your religious viewpoint?
Nah.
It takes the best entertainers to get
smiles out of playing the villain, right?
If you ask me, I bet God just loves playing along with your antics!
So you're saying that both blasphemy
and praise are forms of worship to you?!
Ryuunosuke!
You truly are the bearer of a
deep and profound philosophy!
A God who makes puppets of all men for
his sport and is just another clown himself...
I see.
Then his vicious ways make sense.
Very well.
Then we'll have to stain the garden of God
with the brilliant colors of despair and terror.
We'll have to show the director in heaven that he's
not the only one who knows what entertainment is!
Are we gonna do something awesome again, Mister?
Cool! Cool!
All right, I'll be in this bookstore for a while.
You can do anything you want except leave this arcade.
In the event I'm attacked, it's all over for you too, got it?
No conquering.
No plundering.
Huh?
"Huh"? What do you mean, "huh"?!
No shoplifting, and no eating without paying!
If you want something, pay for it with money!
Or do I have to use a Command Spell to make you listen?
No need to be rude.
Macedonian etiquette passed
for civility in palaces everywhere.
Well, I'll see you later, boy.
The king gave dominion and the power to tax to
the local nobles and took his armies further east.
Just like what I saw in my dream.
He just wanted to reach the sea at the world's edge...
Did he continue his campaign so he could see Ôkeanos?
Hey, boy! Where are you?
There you are.
You're so small that it's impossible to see you in between the bookshelves.
Finding you was tough.
People are normally smaller than bookshelves, idiot.
So what did you buy?
Check this out.
Admirable War Tactics came out today!
And I got the first press limited edition!
My Luck must be pretty high!
You know, there's no point in buying the game if you don't have the console for it.
No problems there.
Come on, boy.
We're playing VS mode when we get back.
I even bought two controllers!
I'm not interested in low-class entertainment like that.
Man, why do you keep restricting your own view of the world?
Don't you ever want to try anything fun?
Shut up.
If I have time to waste, I'd rather spend it on a search for Truth.
So, what were you looking for here, then?
This book?
Whoa there, this is a book about me!
You're a weird guy.
I'm right here. You could've just asked me if you wanted to know something.
Sure, I'll ask!
I'll ask you, then!
History says you were really short.
So why have you materialized with such a huge body?
It says I'm short?
Looks like you really can't trust books written by someone you don't know.
You're not mad that it's wrong?
It doesn't really bother me, no.
Is that strange?
Aren't people in power, no matter the era, desperate to leave their name in history?
I suppose having your name recorded in
the history books is a form of immortality.
But if it's just my name and nothing else that got passed down
for two thousand years, I'd rather have even a hundredth of that...
...added to my life.
Then is it true that you died in your early thirties?
Yes, that's right.
Mister!
Show us something that'll shock even God!
Look forward to it, Ryuunosuke!
I'll give you the greatest "Cool!" you've ever seen!
Seriously?
I can't wait!
Ph'nglui mglw'nafh wgah'nagl fhtagn.
Something awesome's gonna happen!
Why are you so quiet?
Nothing.
I was just thinking about how boring you are.
What?
So you were bored after all.
Then stop whining and play this game with me.
That's not it!
Even if I get the Grail for a Servant like
you who's practically guaranteed to win...
I couldn't take pride in that at all.
It would've been way more rewarding if I'd contracted with Assassin!
I don't know if that would've worked.
I think you'd be dead.
That's fine!
I have no problems with dying in my own battle!
That's why I joined the Grail War!
Yet...
I don't know what to tell you.
If your wish for the Grail was something that impressed me, I wouldn't mind obeying you.
But since you just want to use it to get taller...
Don't just assume things!
You don't need to be in such a hurry.
It's not like the Grail War'll be the
most important event of your life—
What?!
When you ever find a way of life that you can be truly proud of,
you'll be forced into your own battle whether you like it or not.
You can search for your battlefield then.
I can't be the only one who's
not satisfied with this contract.
I'm sure you don't like it either!
Having a Master as pathetic as me.
You'd be able to win a lot easier if you made a
contract with a more competent Master, right?
I wonder about that.
Look at this, boy.
This is the enemy I'm fighting.
Try to draw the two of us next to the enemy.
So that we can compare you and me.
That's...
...impossible, right?
Against the enemy we're about to fight, you and I are the same.
Just tiny little dots.
What point is there in comparing how big we are?
But that's exactly why I am excited!
It doesn't matter how weak or small you are.
With a body not even the size of a dot, I will someday surpass the world.
The excitement in my chest is what causes the King of Conquerors' heart to beat!
So you're basically saying your Master doesn't matter, right?
No matter how weak I am,
it won't pose you any problems.
Where'd that come from?
The inferiority you feel is actually the quality of a king.
You may grumble a lot, but you know how small you are.
And yet, you'll still struggle to reach
heights greater than you can imagine.
That's not a compliment.
You're making fun of me.
That's right, boy.
You're a hopeless idiot.
Your desires lie beyond yourself.
"Glory lies beyond the horizon", after all.
In the world I lived in, that was the most basic rule of life.
Is that why you kept heading east like an idiot?
Yes. That's right.
I wanted to see Ôkeanos with my own eyes.
But my dream didn't come true.
He didn't see that sea?
Ôkeanos remains the place I strive for.
It's an endless dream.
That sea is an imagined scenery Rider holds in his heart.
Laugh if you want.
I'm just another idiot who dreams the same dream even after two thousand years.
So, boy.
A contract with an idiot like you is totally fine with me.
The river.
Can you see what is happening, Lancer?
It's Caster, all right.
He has taken position on the river
and appears to be doing something.
I cannot make out the details, however.
This would be the perfect opportunity to defeat him.
Indeed.
If we defeat Caster,
I can regain one of the bonds with Lancer that I had lost.
I will go engage him.
Sola-Ui-sama, please stay here and bear witness to my deeds.
What?!
I'm your Master now! I'll assist you by your side.
You mustn't.
You don't understand matters
of battle like Lord Kayneth did.
That river will become a land of death.
Please understand.
But...
Sola-Ui-sama, do you suspect that the
tip of my spear is still shrouded in doubt?
That I would selfishly fool around in battle?
Lancer, I leave all field decisions to you.
May you fight freely with no regrets.
I am in your debt.
Should you return victorious...
Lancer, please show me your smile.
Caster...
It's clear from this incredible outpouring of mana
that Caster is performing magic of an enormous scale.
Welcome, Holy Virgin.
I am overjoyed that we can meet again.
You never learn, fiend!
What are you trying to do tonight?!
I'm terribly sorry, Jeanne.
You're not the guest of honor tonight.
But if you would like to join us as well, I could have no greater happiness.
At this banquet of death and decadence that I, the humble
Gilles de Rais, have prepared, everyone may eat their fill!
Now let us once again raise the flag of salvation!
Caster is being absorbed?!
Gather here, O abandoned ones.
I shall lead you! I shall command you!
The deep resentment that we, the oppressed, hold
shall reach God himself!
O God in heaven, with words of
condemnation I praise your holy name!
That's...
Arrogant God!
Cruel God!
We shall pull you down from your throne.
Hey, King of Knights.
King of Conquerors...
Don't even start.
It's a truce tonight.
We can't fight each other in peace
unless we deal with that big thing first.
I've been going around and telling everyone.
Lancer agreed. He should be here soon.
Understood. We agree to fighting with you as well.
King of Conquerors, it will be a short alliance, but I swear loyalty to our common cause.
Einzbern, you guys got a plan?
Lancer told me this isn't your first time fighting Caster.
We need to defeat him as soon as we can.
That monster is still maintaining itself in this world with Caster's mana.
But it'll be too late once it gets its own
food source and becomes self-sufficient.
We need to stop Caster before that.
I see.
So we need to settle this before it
reaches the coast and starts eating.
But Caster himself is deep
inside those thick walls of flesh.
What do we do?
Drag him out.
That's the only way.
If we can expose his Noble Phantasm, then my Gae Dearg can destroy the spell in one strike.
Lancer, will you be able to hurl your spear
and hit his Noble Phantasm from the coast?
It'll be no trouble if I can just see it.
Rider and I will take the vanguard, then.
Is that fine, King of Conquerors?
I don't mind, but while my chariot needs no roads...
Saber, how will you attack the enemy in the river?
I am under the protection of the Lady of the Lake.
No body of water can stop me, no matter how wide or deep.
That's another rare skill to have.
I want you for my army even more now.
You'll pay for that remark later.
For now, it's imperative that we drag Caster out from inside that monster.
Indeed!
Then I shall be the first to strike!
Good luck, Saber.
Let's finish this, Caster!
Episode 13
The Forbidden Banquet
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
If I can find peace in my recollections
While reminiscing about you
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
Proof of the time I spent with you
Is right here with me
You've shown me what it means
To have overflowing feelings
Even if this world were to end
I'll be right by your side
Get 'em, Mister Bluebeard!
A failure of these proportions is unprecedented.
You want me to draw my greatest treasure, Ea, here?!
Saber!
King of Heroes, please wait!
He's unbelievable.
Kill all of them! Every last one!
Season
Begins April 2012