Welcome back. And how was it?
- They were just thugs!
- Nothing to do with the syndicate.
- Just a salaried employee.
- They just wanted money...
They went to the cops penniless!
Then, what?
All of you caught the criminals, but no
clue about the bounty we're really after?
They still use paper
just for all the complaints.
Damn it, they're just harassing us.
It's a waste
of valuable resources!
The e-mail server is down
from the sheer number of complaints.
There is a movement out there
to sue our company for damages.
What the hell
are the bounty hunters doing?
We already have a huge bounty on him!
Yes, however...
Amigo!
All you bounty hunters in the
Sol system, how are y'all doing?
Once again, it's time for Big Shot!
We'll start with today's hot news!
They apprehended the culprit
in the series of recent Gate assaults!
Really? The bounty on him
was 12 million Woolongs, right?
But the weird thing is that
20 culprits were apprehended!
What do you mean?
Apparently, they were all caught in
the act, but none were the mastermind.
Then you don't get the reward
unless you find that mastermind?
But of course!
Oh, my. I feel sorry for all the guys
who caught the culprits!
Why the hell do these
thugs that normally
just rob convenience stores
attack at the Gates?
Maybe there are fads in crimes?
Like, "Hyperspace Gates are the in thing
among today's fashion-conscious kids!"
You assault at least
one Gate or something?
Hey, guys.
Why don't we trade the information
that we each have?
And split the bounty three ways.
What do you mean?
You're the one that started all this,
saying we should research
this case on our own.
You also said that the occasional rivalry
between comrades would be good for us.
Come on, did the reward amount
make you lose your memory?
What? You guys were really
keen on the idea, too!
After all, we all wanted
the bounty to ourselves, right?
In this case, all 20 cases
were done the same way,
All of them infiltrated
the tollbooth...
deftly attached the hacking unit...
and in the exact moment that passing
ships access the tollbooth
to pay the toll,
they steal the entire
balance from the credit card.
Furthermore, the unit automatically
sent the money data that it just stole.
It immediately launders all the funds
in a bank on Europa,
making it impossible
to track where it went.
All the culprits that were caught
in the act have nothing in common.
Age, gender, nationality,
religion, criminal record...
And on top of it, nobody has any
of the money that they supposedly stole.
Well, that's about all I know.
How about you?
The guy that I nabbed said
that he was just following instructions
from a manual he got through mail-order.
Perhaps the other culprits are
reading the same manual that he was.
Manual?
This.
"A new criminal support software.
Right now, it's a real bargain.
For the low introductory price
of 30,000 Woolongs,
you too can be rich!"
What the hell?
It's not easy to be a thief nowadays.
I'm sure there are people
who want manuals to help them.
And where is this mail-order company?
It's a store that's only on the net,
so I don't know where it was.
Besides, the store has already closed.
Spike, how about you?
The hacking unit that was placed
on the Gates was something
that couldn't be made unless you knew
the system really well.
The mastermind's likely someone who has
some connection to the Gate Corporation.
That was my hunch,
and I investigated that front.
The programmers would be fishy.
But the guys from the Gate Corporation
suddenly became uncooperative.
It was as if they knew something,
but didn't want us to find out.
Are you dead?
Where were we?
Well, I guess those are the only clues
we have for now.
Give me that.
Give me.
Yeah.
This is a memory cartridge
for playing chess over the net.
This piece has one match in its memory.
And when you push it,
it connects to the net.
See?
And this has something
to do with this incident?
Nothing at all.
Maybe all of this is a game.
For now, continue playing
that game with the opponent.
Yup.
I'll go talk to the corporation once more.
Lesse.
Eenie, meenie, miny, moe.
Play ball!
Another bounty hunter?
I don't care, send him back.
But he's asking about
a chess-loving programmer.
What?
Jet!
What, Jonathan,
were you another one
that went through all the trouble
to get nothing?
This thing isn't that easy.
I believe we have given
out all the information.
What more are you saying
you would like to know?
Sorry, but there is no smoking
allowed in this building.
I'm so sorry.
Actually I had something
that I wanted you to see.
What is it?
This is a planned game.
You guys at the Gate Corporation
should know what this means.
I mean, to put a bounty on a mastermind
that we aren't even sure exists
suggests that it's someone you don't
want the police to know about, no?
Bounty hunters should just look
for their bounties.
I don't know who you are,
and whether you used to work for
the ISSP, but it's better for you
to not make inquiries.
He's going home.
Make sure he is kindly escorted
out of here.
Damn this old piece of shit!
I believe our risk is too great.
If that gets out to
the general public...
I am fully aware of our risk.
If we don't catch him,
the situation will just get worse.
But why is a ghost from 50 years ago
coming back now?
To think that he gave
everyone a chess piece...
Chessmaster Hex.
So, it is a game that he set up.
No good. This doesn't have anything
other than chess data in it.
I wonder what they were going
to do with this.
If there is no meaning to the content,
maybe the pieces are the message.
Great, great!
Spike, I have a name.
Can you investigate the guy?
He might be the mastermind
behind this whole thing.
Hey, Ed.
Ed's really busy right now.
Here, here!
Checkmate!
Or so you thought!
I'll fork the king and the rook!
Indeed! This is either
an idiot or a genius!
I like this chap!
Chessmaster Hex.
Estimated to be 98 years old.
A programmer that had been
dubbed a genius from his teens.
In the Cosmo-net chess tournaments, he
dominated the champion's seat for decades.
He began work on the Hyperspace Gate
control program when he was 30
and created the central control
system that all Gates use to this day.
However, that was his fatal error.
He doubted the safety
of the Gates he helped create
and was against putting
them to practical use.
He was banned
from the Gate Corporation.
His whereabouts
have been unknown for 50 years.
So, he's the mastermind behind
our current string of crimes.
What do you mean?
I mean, why is he seeking revenge
50 years after the fact?
If we figure out where he is,
we'll know for sure.
Hey, Ed.
Ed's really busy right now.
Hey, you, quit playing games
and help out a little.
Ed, we want to figure out
where a guy named Hex is.
Hex... Hex... The Chessmaster?
That's who I'm playing
chess against right now!
We're almost at the location we got from
the trace we did on Ed's chess opponent.
You guys standing by?
I really don't like this.
I mean, he's basically giving
us his exact location.
Can we even trust that trace
in the first place?
- You think he'd be in a dump like this?
- No, I think it was... that.
I heard there was a place
where all the scrapped remains of
obsolete Gates were gathered along with
scrap metal and abandoned spaceships
and that there were people
that started living there.
Why the hell do they want
to live here of all places?
That area has no nationality,
nor a government.
You don't have to pay taxes,
and there are no cops.
I see. It's the perfect
place to hide yourself.
It might be a trap...
This might be the continuation
of the game.
Whatever happens, happens.
Looks like we have air.
Then there is someone here.
Yo, Jet.
Jonathan!
How the hell did you get here?
Thanks for leading the way.
You were following us
the whole time?
Tough luck for you, but I have
important business with that guy.
So, I'll be going ahead.
What the...?
How the hell...?
What is this?
Hi!
Peace to the world.
And love to my bank account!
You want one?
Wow! Amazing!
Chessmaster Hex?
All right, give up!
You guys.
Can you be a little quieter?
Old man!
Don't joke with me!
Hey, wait a minute.
You won't get away with pretending
to be senile!
Who are you?
If you don't hand over
the money you stole,
you'll get a nice hole in your brain!
That's a big tube you got there.
Hey, what are you doing, Hex?
You gotta hear this. It's my first
formidable opponent in quite a while!
Must be some player
if you have trouble winning!
But before that, where's lunch?
What are you saying?
You just ate a while back!
Oh, is that so?
- Really, you've lost so much of your mind
- Who are these guys?
- that all you do is play!
- Don't know. But this old fogey...
- Have you lost it?
- Like you can speak...
To think my life savings
are never coming back.
Damn... Goddamn it.
Anyone and everyone,
you and that guy over there.
The world is all a mistake!
What are we gonna do?
This old man doesn't seem
to remember anything about
yesterday, let alone 50 years ago!
That's right.
Hex is no longer here.
Here we merely have an old man
that loves games.
Back then, Hex was riled up
for revenge, and planned this all out.
He made it so that this incident
would happen 50 years later
during the one moment that the Gate
program gets automatically updated.
Even making those that
physically commit the crime
hold chess pieces to hint
that it was his doing.
However, to that old-timer,
50 years was too long.
He went senile,
and completely forgot about
the traps that he himself had set.
Well, it works out better
for you this way.
Because now you don't
have to worry about
the fundamental defect
in the Gates leaking out.
Although the price you paid was
that we learned about that defect.
What do you want? Money?
Or are you planning to leak
this information to the press?
Just leave that old guy alone.
That's all I want.
It's a good deal, isn't it?
Ed would get lonely
if she lost her chess partner.
You're playing that thing again?
Not again. Still.
Still?
You've been playing that thing all week?!
Yeah.
I see.
Well, good luck.
Yo, newcomer. You seem happy today.
Hi!
He's a really easygoing fellow, isn't he?
That he is.
Checkmate.
I lost.
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
Love. It is to believe everything.
Hey, now, are you serious?
Love. It is the heart
that provides for all.
Come on, was that what
the story was about?
Love. It is the heart
that accepts everything.
- You know, this is getting fishy.
- Whitney. You loved me that much.
You really can't trust
the previews on this show.
A romantic love story
for all you lovers.
Next episode: "My Funny Valentine."
I'm sure it's a lie.
Yeah, a lie. A lie.