"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
S'up!
Oh, Sis.
How were the exams?
It was just like usual.
Tattered and torn, like I've always been.
During the exam period, you
have more free time than usual.
But before you know it, time
always happens to pass by,
and you end up cramming
the night before, right?
I think you need to keep this
year's entrance exams in mind.
"Base of the Sun"
From the suspect's room, authorities seized
several thousand items of
various manga and games...
This broadcast again?
Amazing.
There was another person like
you in the news again, Konata.
Every time I hear it, I
think it's really unfair.
They always lash out at manga
and stuff so quickly...
There are so many good
manga titles out there too,
but they never focus on them.
That's true... I kinda feel bad about it now.
Kagami, you really are
a good person after all!
Even when I complain like that, a
normal person would just mock me
and say "Otaku are so desperate!"
When I look at the people around
me, when there are two sisters,
one absorbs something from the other.
I mean, like Yu-chan and Sis
Yui, or Kagami and Tsukasa.
Yup, yup!
...and that's what Sis and I
were talking about this morning.
You're rather attached
to Miyuki-chan, Minami.
You guys get along so well,
you look like you're sisters.
I see... Absorbing...
Kona-chan, happy birthday!
Oh!
I'd have forgotten if Tsukasa
hadn't mentioned it, though.
Happy birthday.
Thanks, everyone!
It makes you happy to have people celebrate,
but when you get to our age,
you don't feel happy about
getting a year older anymore.
No, I'm really happy about it.
Oh, why?
Do you want to get a driver's
license or something?
I mean, now I can play
mature games and stuff.
Haven't you been playing them openly already?
No...
You just got a year older, but you
haven't changed a bit, inside or out.
Lemme go!
Miyuki, don't people think you're
older than you actually are?
Yuki-chan looks so mature.
Yes. When I step out in my normal clothes,
I am sometimes mistaken for an office lady.
I see... You skip over college altogether.
In your case, when you
go out in street clothes,
you go back to grade school.
No matter what you say, from
this day forth, I am an adult.
What are you talking about?
In the first place, if
you've become a good adult,
maybe you wouldn't be so
hot-headed over games and manga?
It's important to have a childish
heart full of dreams and passion!
So exactly which side are you on?
Oh, this?
While Sis is at her job,
we're going to secretly prepare
for her birthday party.
I'm sorry I'm late!
All right! Let's get on
with the preparations!
Yes!
"Happy Birthday, Sis"
"Happy Birthday"
Oh, good timing. It's Konata.
Maybe she'll be back soon?
Konata?
I'm sorry, I forgot to tell you.
Everyone at work is celebrating my birthday,
so I don't need dinner tonight,
because I'll be coming home late.
Yutaka, this is tasty.
Yeah, I did my best...
Yui-chan, you can take that off.
Our hopes after graduating, huh...
I have dreams and stuff,
but it's really hard when
you actually think about it.
That's true.
If you're going to college,
what you will do afterward
may depend on the department you major in.
First pick: Nutrition...
Second pick: Clothing design...
Third pick: Marketing.
Yeah. I like to cook and sew and stuff...
I see... You wrote your
dreams out, huh, Tsukasa?
What about you, Miyuki-san?
I want to become a doctor,
so all three choices are pre-med,
though I chose different colleges.
Nothing less from you, Miyuki-san.
Your objectives are so clear.
Then what about you, Kagami?
Me?
My first choice is pre-law,
second choice is economics, and
third choice is literature.
Oh, that's not all that interesting.
Does it have to be interesting?
So, what about you?
"First pick: Brigade leader"
"Second pick: Master of the Divine Fist of the South Star"
"Third pick: Anime storyboard artist"
Yeah, yeah, they're out there. The type
that tries to get a laugh like this.
Or rather, don't you have a special
talent other than staring at games?
Special talents?
I can recite the names
of every single Pok_mon.
That's amazing in its own way,
though it has nothing to
do with your future plans.
Here it is, here it is!
I'll go buy this.
You always pick from the bottom
when you buy magazines and manga.
I feel like people have
picked up the copies up top.
I mean, you want one that's
as clean as possible, right?
Oh, I understand how that feels.
It's just like going to one of
those revolving sushi restaurants,
and putting your orders in instead
of picking up the ready-made plates.
You know, the fish on the orders on
the belt tends to get dried up...
Kagami, you really do that?!
You're such a horrible customer!
You're kidding! You don't do it?!
That's kinda cheap!
I always think about how you
read such wordy books, Kagami.
Don't you get sleepy?
But this is a light novel.
It's just like manga, feeling-wise.
What? Is it the same?
It's got illustrations all over the
book, and they use simple expressions.
Why don't you try reading one?
Well, that one has been turned into an anime,
so I'll catch up on that front...
When we're talking about a
manga, you check both out,
saying how the original
work has its own goodness.
I'm telling you to try reading it.
I'm afraid I must decline.
But Kagami, you read a lot of books
in general, not just light novels.
How should I put it...
When you stock up on knowledge,
you feel like it enriches
your heart, don't you?
Well, I guess it's nutrition for my soul.
Uh-huh. I see.
Something wrong?
Going along those lines,
you stock up on sweets,
so you become physically enriched as well.
Shut up.
Magazines like the one you're reading now...
Don't they have text serials
too, and not just comics?
I always stare at the
illustrations they put in.
So despite everything you're always saying,
your love really doesn't add up to much.
You read past all of them?
Fine, all right, I'll read it!
No, no, don't bother. You
don't have to force yourself.
There's just so many other things
to read that I passed over them!
And I'm telling you it's all
right! I didn't say anything!
Oh, no!
I forgot my world history textbook.
I left it on my desk at home after
going over what we learned in class.
Konata, lend me your world history textbook.
You leave your books at school, right?
Sure. Did you forget?
Yeah.
That's unusual.
Here.
"Impossible! [laugh]" "Haruka!"
"I won't give Haruka to you!"
Oh, Hiiragi, you have quite
a fun-looking textbook there.
Well, um, this is, you know...
I'm not making much progress...
For now, I guess I'll go
find something to drink.
Oh, geez!
Huh?
I thought some of what I bought
the other day would still be left.
I guess it's a good way
to get my mind off things.
What, they're closed?
"We have finished business for the day."
This must be a challenge set against me!
That will be 320 yen.
Huh?
What's wrong, Sis?
You know, when you're all irritated,
you make a lot of little mistakes, and
you end up even more irritated, right?
Yeah, that happens. Nothing
you do goes right, does it?
I guess you'd call it a negative spiral.
That's right, I baked a
cake. Would you like some?
All right!
Studying for entrance exams is tough,
so we have to change gears every so often.
I know, I'll bake cookies tomorrow!
Oh, that'll be stress relief!
I'm counting on you!
"Later..."
So I end up stressed on this front now?
See? See?
You think so too, Iwasaki-san? That's true.
Those two are always so busy, they
keep passing by each other...
I know, I know!
That's right. Sis has her entrance exams,
so I shouldn't get in the way of her studies.
I'm sorry. I'll be talking a bit more softly.
Yu-chan, when you're off the phone,
let's play a game head-to-head! A match!
What?!
Lucky Star!
This is the last year I'll
be wearing this outfit.
When you think about it that way,
you get really emotional about it.
Something is inside...
My favorite handkerchief
that I thought I'd lost!
It was in the pocket of my summer uniform...
Didn't we have some octopus 'n' wasabi?
I wonder what this is?
Oyoyo...
I wonder what this was?
Everything about it has
changed, so I have no idea.
It sure rains a lot... After
all, it's the rainy season.
You're right.
Just when you think it's too
hot, it suddenly gets cold.
It's a problem because we
just switched uniforms.
Hey. You guys are still here?
Ma'am, you're lucky that you
can change outfits freely.
What are you talking about?
It's much easier to wear uniforms,
because you don't have to think
about what to wear each morning!
Ma'am, you know... You're really...
Yoo-hoo!
It's rainy season! It's all soppy!
Oh, Sis.
So much rain, it gets you depressed!
Would you like some tea?
Yes, please.
Then, a topic that will
brighten the conversation up.
Your first wedding anniversary
is coming up, right, Sis?
That's right. Time flies by.
The skies of the rainy
season pose a question.
The answer is the heart of Miss
Yui, whose husband is abroad,
even though their wedding
anniversary is fast approaching.
That reasoning...
I'm sorry, I was wrong to say that.
It's all right. I'm used to
having this much emotional pain.
Here. Drink something warm.
But it still depresses me!
So tasty!
I'm glad.
Geez! At this rate, someday my
love is going to rust as well!
Well, if you went to a car
repair shop or something,
maybe you'd get all better
in forty-five minutes?
It wouldn't kill you to comfort me a little.
I'm sorry, I couldn't help it...
Yes?
Then you can come back?!
That didn't take forty-five minutes.
It was an instant.
Yup.
Tsukasa, you still haven't gotten
that outfit back from Matsuri?
Nope.
That's not good.
If you don't tell her to
hurry up and give it back,
she'll make it her own before you know it.
That's a problem. I really like it!
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san
have two older sisters...
It makes you a little jealous, doesn't it?
Well, yeah.
Really? I'm totally jealous
of how both of you,
Konata and Miyuki, are only children.
Right?
There are times like that...
I mean, if the cast is that big,
you can do all sorts of things.
Like the story of a mother
and her four daughters
who eagerly wait for the
return of their father,
who left for the battlefield
in the old days in America,
or a female bandit ring that
only targets objects of art.
One, two!
Hey!
Wait, there's one too many.
Geez, when it comes to her,
everything turns into an anime or a game.
Wait, Kagami, did you go shopping
for dinner ingredients?
What?
Tsukasa, did you forget to tell her?
I'm sorry!
What? What? What's up?
What, you forgot? Mom and
Dad aren't here tonight.
Oh! Was their vacation starting today?
Yeah. So we were supposed to go
shopping for dinner ingredients.
I totally forgot about it.
I called your cell and left a
voicemail on it too, Kagami.
"1 new message"
Matsuri, we can just make do
with what's in the fridge.
What? I was totally set on making something!
It's all right, you can do it another day.
Aw, man.
Geez, it's all you guys'
fault, Kagami, Tsukasa!
I'm sorry.
Fine! I'll go right now!
Geez, that was because of
your attitude, Matsuri.
I mean...
Or rather, does she even
know what she needs to buy?
Geez, what's up with her? She doesn't
like to cook that much anyway!
Why's she all worked up?!
Sis!
Tsukasa...
Sis, you don't have the
shopping list on you, do you?
They're late...
If you're so worried, why
didn't you go yourself?
You're late!
What's wrong? Matsuri was
really worried about you.
The usual store didn't have any saffron,
so I said that we could probably
use curry powder instead.
But Sis said that since we came
out, we might as well look,
and went to the supermarket
that's further away.
Geez, you didn't have to go that far.
Well, excuse me!
Now, now, let's make dinner.
I'm starving already.
Here. Sorry to make you wait.
Now all we have left is
Matsuri's special dish.
It's done!
Wow! It looks really tasty!
Yeah. It's got just the right
golden-brown baked color, no?
Hey, Matsuri-oneechan, when
did you manage to learn
how to cook something like this?
Oh, we had this when I went drinking
with the other girls in
my seminar the other day.
It was so delicious that I
wanted everyone to have some,
so I asked for the recipe.
I see. I'm surprised they gave it to you.
Now, in any case, let's eat.
Yeah!
Huh?
What's wrong?
Listen to this. Your father
completely mistook the date.
What do you mean?
Apparently, the reservation
was for next week.
That sounds like a comedy routine...
You're just about to eat?
You haven't eaten yet?
No.
What, paella?
Matsuri-oneechan made it.
My, that's amazing.
Yeah, but Kagami got all
the ingredients for me.
She even went all the way
to a distant supermarket.
Then, shall we have some too?
Sure.
Hey, this is pretty good.
Oh, who took the mussels?
Mussels?
Oh, was I not supposed to?
I can't believe it! I was thinking
about eating those last!
Then write your name on it!
Geez, stop fighting!
S'up. I'll take a detour with you today.
You have something you want to buy?
The new book from Shin Yamada...
Though I don't have much time to read lately,
with all the assignments we have.
Yeah... I have a pile of unread
manga next to my pillow, too.
But I always end up reaching
out for the newest ones.
I kinda know how that feels.
Read what you already have,
instead of buying something new.
Well, when you buy it first,
you feel relieved...
Or rather, you feel like you're
missing something... right?
Don't ask me to agree!
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Yes, we'll deliver an energetic
installment again today!
Time flies by... This week's Lucky
Channel is already the 17th! Yes!
Your navigator is-- all
red roses have thorns--
the platypus of the idol
industry, Akira Kogami!
And...
Hello--
Today, we have invited
a very big-named guest!
How long are you going to make me wait?!
Oh? I'm showing on screen?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
He showed up again.
He showed up.
Well, today's guest is...
"Special Guest - Mr. Meito Anizawa"
The Anime Manager, Meito Anizawa! Yes!
This show has no tension whatsoever!
But, well, Lucky Star is an anime
show that draws out the lives
of ordinary high schoolers in a
very relaxed, peaceful atmosphere.
So this segment, Lucky Channel, is
also rather relaxed, and has a low...
That's no good!
Where is he?!
So fast!
Listen up! Do you know the
three necessary elements
for the success of an anime show?
The three elements? Let's see,
the voice actors, the animation
itself, and the script?
That's not it!
My uniform is burning red!
They are...
They are?
The love, time, and budget that the
staff and cast pour into the title!
Though it's not a matter that
we can do something about.
I see...
Listen up! Even if the
original work is wonderful,
it's meaningless if you
don't have a good script!
Even if the voice actors are gung-ho,
if there is no color to the
animation, it won't succeed!
Oh, line art is plenty for Shiraishi.
Shiro-ishi?
Everyone puts their lives on
the line for their own part!
The love and passion put towards a
work, grinding your body to dust,
is what creates a wonderful series!
Is that how it is?
You! You're Miss Akira
Kogami right now, was it?
Right now? I've always been
Akira, past to present.
Didn't you have overwhelming love
when you were playing Rou_an,
Gaor_nger, P_tato, or Mai_ai?
What are those?
If you have regrets for any of them...
No, none.
Burn yourself out as Akira Kogami!
No, I'm telling you...
Yes! I will burn out as Minoru Shiraishi!
Well said, Shiraishi!
All right, we'll start off with
how to catch a crowd at an event!
Oh, is it the end?
You were the host for a big
event the other day, right?
Bye-nee...
You were watching?
Of course, it's part of my job.
Thanks for the hard work today.
I was given such an important role.
I was nervous the entire time!
Now, excuse me...
Oh, not yet, not yet.
Oh, and Shiraishi, take care
of the rest for me, please!
First, your ad-libs are weak!
You can't lose against someone like Sugita!
"Minoru Shiraishi Theater"
Hey, missus! Are you dissatisfied
with your husband?
Hello! This is Minoru Shiraishi!
And let's get on with the song now!
♪ Vague sunshine? Does that mean
I'm at a disadvantage? Smooch! ♪
♪ The wrapping increases, hey,
is that a disadvantage? Wait! ♪
♪ Let's do it, you do it, that's
time to catch 'n' release, yo! ♪
♪ I say, I say, funny funny,
darlin' darlin' freeze! ♪
♪ Kinda lethargic, something's
kinda comin' out ♪
♪ I love you... oh wait, one
of those was different ♪
♪ Worrywarts, high metal bars, going... ♪
♪ And that's enough! ♪
♪ The heated body of that
flying you-know-who ♪
♪ It's what you call a normal girl ♪
♪ I'm the only one surprised? Seconds
on ramen with wire-hard noodles! ♪
♪ Da da da da da ♪
It was so fast!
It's totally missing!
That's not necessarily true.
You think so?
♪ Pom-poms cheer squad ♪
♪ Electric Denina ♪
♪ Careless, how is it? ♪
♪ Inheritance, how is it? ♪
♪ Yeah! Feeling of existence,
panting Sozaira ♪
♪ Haran haran furun furun horon
horon hiren haren horonturo... ♪
♪ Take it away! ♪
♪ I should be the one that
will be laughing in the end ♪
♪ Because I have the sailor suit
- > this is my conclusion ♪
♪ It's only Sunday! Already
in a bad mood? What to do? ♪
♪ I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3 ♪
♪ Yeah! Until we approach 3
pixels, no hesitations please ♪
♪ Do your best, be energetic,
my darlin', darlin' please! ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next...
That's boring, Shiraishi!
Stop with the cookie-cutter previews!
Heil Blayking, Manager!
All right! But before that, listen up!
Rule ♪1 in becoming a big-name voice actor!
Rule ♪1!
If you can't beat 'em, join 'em!
How small-hearted!
Next episode: To Each Her Own.
This is the end for Mr.
Anizawa, too. Goodbye!
Finger!