How are you, Negi? Is your training going well?
I’m doing fine, onee-chan.
I met up with Anya in London. She’s working hard in her fortune telling.
But she sounded quite lonely… She pretended to have a show of courage, but she’s probably homesick.
Are you okay, Negi? Are you feeling lonely?
I’m just fine, onee-chan. I’m having tons of fun over here! There’s no way I could be lonely.
The students here are all very good, and are doing very well!
I’ve had some trouble in the past, but everyone is getting along and working hard in their studies.
I learn something new every day, and it’s so much fun! It’s pure bliss. So don’t worry about me, onee-chan.
I’ll definitely show you that I can accomplish this assignment.
And I’ll make sure that I’ll grow up to be a respectable mage like my father!
AND CUT! That was the best, Aniki! That was an Academy-worthy act!
I wasn’t acting! It was all true, Chamo-kun!
I’m just fine, onee-chan. I’m having loads of fun here!
Alright!
Having been separated from his home town, Negi Springfield has been put on an assignment.
His tales have only just begun!
by Nodoka
Well then, class, be safe in returning home!
Okay!
Is class over now?
Yeah.
Then can we get something to eat?! I’m seriously starvin’ here!
Speaking of food, the school’s food court has a new line of seasonal desserts now.
Alright! Let’s go and get some now! Missing out on exclusive products hurts your manhood.
Negi-kun.
Takamichi
I need to borrow a bit of your power. Can you give me a hand?
Sure… but with what?
Seems like something bad is happening around here.
Let’s go.
Yes, Master.
Magic to make the person you like come to you…
”Put a four-leaf clover in your left pocket and chant his name three times to yourself.”...
If that's all, then maybe even I can do it!
Nodoka?
Yue!
I’m sorry. I don’t think I can tag along with you to the library today.
Really? Alright, it’ll just be Haruna and me instead.
“The Magic of Love,” eh?
Walking! walking! walking! walking!
Ah! This is uh…
This is just one of those books… that I think are good to read every now and then…!
Hmm now… by “one of those books”, did you mean on the subject of magic… or the subject of love?
Um… er… that's...
I see, so you’re interested in both of ‘em.
Love and magic… It’d be great if there was some kind of magic that can make Negi fall for me…
That’s right. I don’t think Haruna can make it today, either. She sounded like she was busy over there.
Over where?
A chupacabra research group.
Huh?
Walking! walki-
It appears that within the Academy grounds there is a strange phenomenon going around, according to eyewitnesses.
Upon approval, I would like to explain the mystery that is the chupacabra, and to lead this Chupacabra Research Group!
My, my, even this academy has lots of stuff going on!
We even had that vampire incident last year!
Vampire incident…?
What’s wrong Asuna? Your face is all red…
I-It’s not red!
Well, at the very least, I would like to review...
and sort all the eyewitness research that has been gathered so far on the chupacabra!
Why’d you turn red?
Height: At least 120 cm
Foot Size: 14.8 cm
When it cries, it emits a sound that goes “Ru-n’ya! Ru-n’ya!”
Why are you red?
I’m not red.
“Ru-n’ya”…what a weird cry, huh?
Probably, as his last words, he cries “Ru-n’ya”.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
Hey Haruna, what’s this?
That happens to be a frog and cat that I drew!
…frog and… cat…?
Are you sure you even drew this correctly?!
YES I’M SURE!
Guys, there’s trouble!
While we were taking a walk around, we found a strange shadow on the opposite end of the gym de gozaru!
Could it be that it’s…?!
Chupacabra?!
Chupacabra Research Group! Let's roll!
Roger!
It was right over there de gozaru!
Chupacabra! Come out wherever you are!
It really is over there!
Whoever strikes first wins!
I GOTCHA!!
Eh? What’s this?
It’s a Tanuki-san!
There seems to be five here. What about over there?
Three so far. What exactly is that darkness?
I don’t know. But I doubt it’s a phenomenon that was revived from something unfriendly.
So this is the work of a person?
Yeah. It could be-
Negi-kun!
Ah, we finally arrived-mya!
Long trips hurt your body.
Wha?! Who the hell are you chibis?!
What exactly is this?
My name is Shichimi-mya!
I’m Moutsu.
It seems like they’re the special ones from the Magic Academy.
These guys probably had their names changed, huh Aniki?
Much like you, Chamo-kun.
Well then, Shichimi-kun, Moutsu-kun; what important news do you have for us?
Yeah, mya.
We’re in a time where we’re going through immense trouble, so please keep this a secret.
It seems that someone has stolen the Star Crystal from the Magic Academy-mya!
Eh?!
Eh-?!
Why the heck are you so shocked-mya?
I just thought this is a shocking moment, really.
You two! Are you sure of this information?
Since the Star Crystal was stolen, Magic Academy executives have been in a state of panic.
And in order for us to spread the word, we came all the way from England-mya!
Star Crystal?! Is that-
Yeah.
A legendary magic item that gives you infinite magical powers.
Due to its overwhelming strength, even the Thousand Master could not control its powers.
And for someone to steal it… what does he plan on doing with it?
Could it be that those dark outbreaks in the school are…?!
I don’t want to give up hope, but there’s a possibility.
Star Crystal…
Since we took our time to come to Japan, allow us to fully live a life here in the Academy for a bit-mya!
You may think we’re just getting in your way, but don’t mind us! In a good way...
Of course! I don’t think you’re being a bother at all! Well then, it’s a pleasure to meet you.
Really-mya?
We really might be a bother!
Negi-chan, if you ever screw up, we will report you to the Magic Academy.
We are going to observe you but don’t worry about it.
In a good way...
I’m feelin’ kinda tired from the trip-mya! Please don’t wake me up-mya~
Geez, you.
If you wake us up, we might talk about you behind your back.. In a good way...
Oh no...
We are waiting in vain-!
This isn’t good, Aniki! If you let those two wander around…
It’ll be fine. It’s not like I’ll do anything wrong.
What’s wrong, Aniki?
This way!
Found it!
I’m going to get rid of it before it gets any bigger.
At this rate, my students are bound to catch me…
What’s wrong, Chamo-kun?
No-Nodoka-san?!
Ah… um… after finding a four-leaf clover…
Did you, by any chance, happen to see that?
Y-yes. Very clearly.
What do I do, Chamo-kun?
It’ll be fine, Aniki! Folks these days don’t even believe in magic; even if they did see it, they won’t think of it as much!
Negi-sensei, so you are a mage afterall!
That’s so cool!
She’s one of the few to believe it exists…
If that’s the case, use some memory-erasing magic!
I have no choice. I’m sorry, Nodoka-san!
I MESSED UP AGAIN!!!
Are you okay, Chamo-kun?!
This is serious-mya!
You have failed to keep your identity hidden.
We’ll inform the Magic Academy about this. He’s gonna get it bad-mya!
I-I will?!
What? It’s no big deal; some of your magic will be taken away and you’ll turn into an animal.
In a good way...
N-no way!
Now we should start packing so we can send you back to the Academy! Mya
For a Japanese souvenir, we’ve got a back scratcher and a few bags of  Kaki no Tane rice crackers.
What should I do…?
Now stop right there! The truth is, this chick here is Aniki’s partner!
They even exchanged a provisional contract, and he even has the pactio cards for it!
It’s only obvious that she’d know about his existence as a mage!
But she was hiding her other identity, acting as a normal school girl! She couldn't talk about magic, she wouldn't!
She was role playing, acting like she didn't know anything!
Got that, you two?!
Ba-dum, ba-dum, ba-dum, ba-dum, ba-dum...
I’m sorry for not knowing.
To show our apology… here.
Shouldn’t the chupacabra look like this?
What’s with you all of a sudden?
Well, Haruna’s artwork is questionable!
What part of it’s like that?!
Well, hello! There’s no way there’re frogs and cats like this in existence!!
There are now.
Please take good care of us; my name is Shichimi-mya!
Stare at me too long and you’ll be cursed. In a good way...
There are! And they talk, too!
So you’re a mage, Negi-sensei.
Please don’t tell anyone about this, Nodoka-san. If those two find out, I’ll get turned into an animal!
Okay, my lips are sealed!
Could this be a little secret between Negi-sensei and me…?
Jou-chan, how’s about you take into consideration in really exchanging a provisional contract?
And in doing so, you can always be of service to Aniki, and what I said back then won’t be a lie after all!
Chamo-kun!
Partner? I can be of help to Negi-sensei?
And on top of that, I can get me 50,000 Ermine Dollars from the Ermine Academy as commission! The excitement!
Chamo-kun, Nodoka-san is my student. I can’t do that.
U-um…!
If you don’t mind…
Uweh?
Now, time for the provisional contract ceremony!
What do I have to do?
Easy as pie! All you have to do is stand in the magic circle and kiss Aniki!
Kiss?!
Everything is already prepared. Now, Jou-chan, exchange away!
Kiss with Negi-sensei… Kiss with Negi-sensei… Kiss with Negi-sensei…!
Nodoka-san…
Do it! Kiss each other! Go on! Gimme 50 thousand!
Do you remember?
What the hell are you doing at a precious moment like this?!
Guys! What’s wrong? You’re all in a rush!
We spotted a chupacabra!
We’re sure it’s the real thing! We’ll catch it this time!
Could it be that… they’re talking about the dark blobs?!
Where next?
Second floor of the second building de gozaru!
I feel a magic presence this way.
Let’s all split up here and look for it. I’ll go for the stairs. You guys go that way.
Okay. Let’s go, Haruna!
Hmm? You two…
You’re up to something, aren’t ya?
I’ll be tagging along with you, okay?
Um… I want to help out, too!
Here?
My staff is responding to it.
So Asuna-san… knows that he’s a mage…
Everything looks normal to me.
What’s going on?!
What is this?!
This is… a forest in Wales!
Wales…?
This is where Aniki grew up.
Is that… a fairy?
Aww, how cute!
Back away!
That fairy is controlling them!
Negi! Let me transform!
Asuna-san…
We have no choice; we have to use the power of a partner!
Partner?
So Asuna-san exchanged a provisional contract with Negi-sensei…
Looks like we have no choice.
Partner: Kagurazaka Asuna. Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
This time it’s a Cosplay Card!
Cosplay Card?
When you activate a provisional contract, three cards are born. Out of those three, a random card will be activated!
This isn’t like last time, but… I still feel power building up!
Alright, onward march!
So then… Asuna-san must’ve already kissed Negi-sensei…
This is… a maze!
Hey! STOP RIGHT THERE!
Negi-sensei…!
What’re we going to do? At this rate, if we can’t find anyone and get help, we’ll all be skeletons.
Ehhhhhh?!
Leave it to me!
Now that I’ve transformed, there’s nothing to be afraid of!
This maze is nothing; we’ll clear this place in one shot!
Everyone, follow me!
Okay, we’re lost.
Eh~?!
Ane-san, I didn’t say this earlier, but…
any screw ups made by the person’s brain power results in no power ups!
Should’ve said that earlier!
So even if Asuna-san gets a power up, she won’t get any smarter!
You know you just indirectly called me an idiot!?
Ah, can’t take it…so hungry…can’t move!
You did a lot of thinking… you must be extremely tired.
Asuna-san and Negi-sensei already...
I have to try my best as well.
Aniki, what are we going to do? We don’t even know how to get back where we started!
We really are going to get lost and turn into skeletons...
Negi-sensei!
Please… exchange a provisional contract with me!
Nodoka-san…
Pactio!
Provisional Contract Complete!
You can stop now! It’s over.
Oh, um, I-I-I-I’m sorry!
A-Asuna-san!
So you did a provisional contract with Honya-chan.
I see.
Asuna-san… are you mad at me…?
Women are hard to figure out.
In any case, Aniki, activate the provisional contract!
Okay, here it goes, Nodoka-san.
Okay!
Partner: Miyazaki Nodoka. Show me the power within you!
Provisional Contract-
Nodoka-san!
Honya-chan!
Negi, do another provisional contract with me!
Ane-san, we can’t do it while you’re like this!
Are you okay, Honya-chan?!
Yeah…
A childish prank, I see.
Evangeline-san!
Not so fast!
You musn’t, Master!
Evangeline-san!
The darkness already took over her!
So was it you that took the Star Crystal?
And if I did?
What are you?! Why did you do this?!
How in the hell would you understand?!
Master!
It… went back to normal…
Master.
That bastard…
Is the stolen Star Crystal related to some of the mysteries that occurred tonight?
The darkness, the fairy, and the evil spirit that took over Evangeline's body; what is going to happen?
And what happened to the Chupacabra? Wait for the next episode!
Those who can eat udon chew on the noodles, and then drink some soup.
Next time: “Tokyo’s Security Deposit Sure Ain’t Cheap! More Like, Isn’t This the Meaning of a Provisional Contract?”
By Konoka.
It’s hard to eat the long noodles…
Jump Out! Chupa
I’m a chupa chupa chupacabra!
“I’m a chupa chupa chupacabra”…
Chupa chupa chupa chupa chupacabra!!
Theme song?!