Hinazuki's late?
She said, "I'll give you your present tomorrow."
It's quite possible that she stayed up making something and overslept.
Satoru?
But...
Satoru!
Y-Yes?
What's wrong? Worried about something?
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Hinazuki!
Anybody home?
Don't tell me...
Rubber boot footprints?
They're an adult male's size.
It snowed the night before last.
Which means an adult male has been here since then?
Hey... What are we gonna do about this?
Five musicians, playing flute and drums!
Today's a joyful Doll Festival!
Thursday, March 3rd, 1988
Hinazuki Kayo Disappeared
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
I came to a halt, and I came to reflect
On an endless today I had to lament
Made to realize that memories of days past
Are not eternal, they will not last
I've spent my days tearing myself apart
Crying alone in a corner of my heart
The times told me not to let go of what I'd got
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
But like water under a bridge, they were lost
I wanted to say it's a phase I regret most
But on that day I missed my shot
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
Today's another day I tear myself apart
Engraving a scar I'll always recollect
Saying it's you I want
ERASED
I took the next two days off from school.
Where's Mom?
Out shopping?
Actually, there was a similar incident in the next town over.
They caught the culprit right away, but now we have this.
We don't know who did it this time,
so we'll have to take steps to
prevent it from happening again.
Well, yeah, but let me talk to the
school about the media blackout.
I'll call you right after I do.
Got it.
I'll let the editors know.
I'm countin' on you.
He must be one of Mom's former colleagues, a TV Ishikari reporter.
We don't want kids rememberin' an incident like this.
True.
They'd already started making moves at this time?
I can understand bein' worried, but it ain't your fault.
I couldn't do a thing.
Really?
I wanted to put an end to Hinazuki being all alone.
You did that.
It wasn't enough.
I could've and should've done more.
It's conceited to blame yourself for somethin' after it happens.
There's only so much one person can do.
Be it you or me.
Go back to school tomorrow.
You'll only get depressed rattlin' 'round here on your own.
'Kay.
Now, let's eat before it goes cold.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
There's something I need to tell you.
When I told you Kayo was home with a cold, that was a lie.
She's had to move to her grandmother's place for family reasons.
It was all so sudden that she
couldn't say goodbye to you all,
but I got word that she's doing well in Sapporo.
Did she run away?
I heard her mother was beating her.
That's awful!
But this is good news.
Satoru.
Don't let it get you down.
Yeah. You'll see her again.
Satoru,
the Kayo story was something the school and the PTA decided on together.
I ask that you go along with it for now.
Sure.
Sorry.
It looks like there's a media blackout,
but I've seen a police car parked near
Hinazuki's place for the past few days.
Apparently her mother's also a suspect at this stage.
And just six days after Hinazuki's disappearance...
Missing
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
The city has issued an advisory.
You are to only leave school grounds
accompanied by a parent or guardian.
...the second victim disappeared.
It happened sooner than I expected.
Did you hear, Satoru?
About Nakanishi Aya from Izumi Grade School?
Yeah.
A friend who goes there told me she ran away and is now at her grandfather's place.
That sounds exactly like Hinazuki.
The running away thing is a lie, right?
Isn't this a serial kidnapping incident?
While there were a few minor differences,
history was definitely starting to repeat itself.
The investigation was made public,
but TV Ishikari only ran the story early morning and late night,
and city families with children were
advised not to watch other channels.
I'm home.
The police car that had been parked
all day and night near Hinazuki's place
only showed up every now and then
after Nakanishi Aya's disappearance.
The investigators must've started
seeing it as a serial kidnapping case.
Just ten days after her daughter disappeared,
Hinazuki's mother threw out a trash bag
with a pair of half-knit mittens inside.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
That's a promise.
Where am I?
Did I go back to 2006?
23-1 on Fourth.
The victim is Fujinuma Sachiko, 52 years old.
We're currently looking for Fujinuma Satoru,
age 29, as the prime suspect.
We have an eyewitness testimony. Over.
Roger.
Are you Fujinuma Satoru?
No, no!
It wasn't me!
Damn it all!
I couldn't save Hinazuki,
my mother's been murdered,
and I'm the prime suspect!
That's the reality I'm facing right now.
I have to prepare myself
and run away!
Episode 5
Escape
I could only think of hiding under a bridge.
Some imagination I've got.
It's not like it'd be on the news yet.
Anyway, I need to think.
Why was Mom murdered?
Because she'd realized who the culprit was?
Did I see her cell phone in the apartment?
What about her bag?
They were both nowhere to be found.
Which means the culprit took them?
Was it because there's a chance she'd gotten out information about him?
Damn it!
My head feels heavy.
I wish I could get some proper sleep, at least for tonight.
Well, eat up.
Thanks.
Sorry about today.
This is the first time you've ever been AWOL from work.
Katagiri was worried about you too.
Knowing you, I'm sure you had a good reason.
Anyway, eat first, talk later.
I will, thanks.
Oh, so you had a fight with your mother.
Yeah.
Old people can be pretty set in their ways.
Feel free to stay as long as you want,
but be sure to patch things up with her.
Got it.
Want a beer too?
Nah.
Dang, I'm out.
I'll go buy some more.
I was spot on. He's totally the "annoying big brother" type.
Sorry I lied to you.
When the police rushed there after receiving a tip,
they found a deceased woman,
presumed to be the mother of the apartment's resident.
The police are currently looking for the missing
male resident as a person of interest in this case.
This is the absolute worst-case scenario!
Next up, sports.
Today, the Japanese soccer team left for Germany, where the World Cup finals will be held.
How naïve can I get?!
No, don't hold it against the manager!
He always tries to do the right thing!
It's only natural he'd give me up!
You piece of shit!
What are you, stupid?
Airi...
That's the first time you've called me Airi, Satoru.
You know you can't leave your phone on.
They might track you via the GPS.
What are you doing?
Get on already.
You have to run, right?
Sorry to make you do that, Katagiri.
I think you mean Airi.
And now we're even in terms of bike rides.
Are you sure you want me in your house?
You know what happened, right?
The police came to the restaurant today and talked to the manager.
It was on the news, too.
Then why?
Isn't it obvious?
There's no way you'd kill that mother of yours.
Oh...
Thank you.
No need to thank me!
I can't believe you're being chased when
you're the one who's hurt the most by this.
A lot of incidents occur around you, huh?
Like this one.
You forgot this at work the other day.
I took the liberty of reading the part you had bookmarked.
It happened in your hometown when you were a kid, right?
The Hinazuki Kayo murder case.
I can't believe she died on the day of the Doll Festival.
Reading that made me cry.
Huh? The Doll Festival?
The Most Shocking Crimes Of The Century
Yeah. Says it happened on March 3rd.
Well, take some time to relax.
I have to go return the bike to work.
Don't take one step outside this room, okay?
Hinazuki Kayo (10 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
The details in the book have changed.
So the past's not set in stone after all.
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
If I can go back there one more time, I can still save Hinazuki!
Oh, right. I slept in Airi's room.
To Satoru,
I think I'd better go about business as usual today, so I'm off to work.
My family said they're going out at 10 AM,
and that they won't be back until after 8 PM.
You can find the house and bike keys next to the clock.
My cell phone number is...
Sasaoka
Not Katagiri?
I can't thank you enough, Mr. Nishizono!
It's fine.
Your father has always helped me out.
The pleasure's all ours, I assure you.
My dad's overjoyed.
He's amazed how much one traffic light and
pedestrian crossing has increased our footfalls.
I'm sure that's all due to your father's business acumen.
All I did was lend him a hand.
Besides, that's a school route.
It often came up in city council meetings.
I'm off! See you later.
Sure. Thanks, Airi.
What's that?
Oh, takeout pizza.
You should've told me!
I don't mind treating you once in a while.
Thank you, but that's okay.
It's for a friend.
O-Oh, a friend?
A-A girl, maybe?
Well, see you.
Such a cute girl.
Pardon me!
But she's only 17, so she's still kind of a child...
I should get going too.
Thank you!
Airi!
Boss?
You forgot this.
It comes free with the pizza right now, remember?
Oh, thank you.
Anyway, about Satoru...
I can't imagine him killing his...
I mean, doing something like that.
I agree.
If you happen to run into him, help him out.
Sure!
I'll offer my support as well, so call me if you meet him.
Thank you!
Can I really get closer to the culprit by looking this up?
A kidnapping case in the city three years ago?
Come to think of it, I do remember something like that.
The suspect was arrested three weeks later.
But he vehemently maintained his innocence.
What is this feeling?
Something's off.
Sasaoka
Why are you calling the police, Boss?
Airi!
You told me to help Satoru out!
You said you would offer your support as well!
You've got it all wrong, Airi!
I was, uh, just worried about you!
Then why didn't you just say so from the start?!
I wanted to believe in you!
I-I was worried about you...
That, I believe.
Sorry.
Boss, I beg of you...
If you really are worried about me,
then please don't call the police to the house of the family that's taking care of me.
I'm sorry, Satoru.
You have nothing to apologize for.
If anything, I should be thanking you.
You gave me a chance to rest.
We can't go back to that house anymore.
Nah, this is for the best.
Speaking of which, that's not your family home, is it?
No.
My mom's brother and his wife live there.
My family home is out in the country.
Instead of finding a boarding house so I could go to high school,
they told me to come stay with them here in Chiba.
Can I ask you one more question?
What is it?
How can you believe in me?
I'm not doing this because I can believe in you.
It's because I want to.
Back when I was in grade school,
I once went shopping with my dad.
They found some chocolate in his coat pocket.
We lived in a small town, and the owner was a friend.
He said he'd forget about it if my father admitted to stealing it and apologized.
But my dad adamantly refused.
That was the first time I heard my calm and gentle father raise his voice.
The owner was left with no choice but to call the police,
and my dad was suspended from his post at the local farming co-op for three months.
I know! I was watching the whole time!
I know you didn't do it, Dad!
My dad quit the co-op, got a divorce, and left home.
Apparently my mom thought he really did do it.
So I want to believe you for my own sake.
It's like someone wanting to be believed, but with roles reversed.
Go back home.
Tell the police I threatened you into hiding me.
What are you, stupid?!
There's no way you can escape by yourself, and I'm not gonna tell them that.
Could you stop asking me if I'm stupid?
Anyway...
I'll at least bring you a change of clothes.
The manager didn't call the police after that, huh?
Fujinuma Sachiko (Cell)
What is this?
This is Fujinuma Satoru. Stay right where you are.
What's going on?
Did Satoru find his mother's phone?
How?
No!
It's from the killer!
"Stay right where you are"?
A-Are you kidding me?!
No way...
No way!
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory