kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
Prepare to advance.
Forward!
Advancing.
Enemy spotted.
Ready main cannon.
Distance: 800.
Load an H.E. round!
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Loading complete!
Ready!
Fire!
Boom!
Direct hit!
All right. Inform the rear guard.
One enemy unit neutralized. Advance to our position.
Roger!
One enemy unit neutralized, huh?
Well done.
We still have a ways to go.
Filicia, it's Klaus.
Really? Well then, shall we have tea?
Good job everyone.
Mountain Climbing
The Edge of the World
You've completely healed, haven't you, Shuko?
Ever since its wound healed, it has been quite cheeky.
That's because it's wonderful here.
Hey!
Even though it's hot, she's so full of energy.
Really.
This is from Command. Sign here.
Right.
These are private messages.
Kana-chan?
Here! Here, here! Here!
Here's yours.
Thank you very much!
It's from Mom!
Noël-chan, you also have one. It's from the professor, as usual.
Professor?
Family name is Pro. Given name is Fessor-san.
It's a common name in the province of Sept.
Wow, Mr. Fessor-san, huh?
It's amazing that you have friends from that far away!
Sorry.
Eh?
A joke.
Oh, come on, Noël-chan. I actually believed you!
Go get Klaus a gift and bring it to him.
Okay!
Rio?
It's~the~us~u~al!
Throw it out.
Geez...
Well? What did Command say?
Excuse me!
What is it, Kureha?
Major Klaus, for you.
This year's, eh?
Yes!
U-Uh, um...
Thank you for always taking care of us!
Don't worry about it. It's my job.
Major.
Orders.
Oh?
Got it. I'll take care of the place in your absence.
Absence?
Best of luck, Private.
Y-Yes, sir.
Everyone! Tomorrow we're going on an excursion!
Yay!
An excursion?!
Noël-chan, this is great. Doesn't it sound exciting?
An excursion? Filicia...
Although I called it an excursion, that's a little boring, so shall we make it into a game?
A game?
In the aberrant land of Seize's southern river,
in other words, on the border of Nomansland,
there are several observation points from the previous age.
It's about time for a routine check on three of them.
We want you to have a look at them during your excursion.
In other words...
It's just an absurd mission, isn't it?!
It's an excursion you know. An excursion.
If they happen to be broken, there's nothing we can do.
Noctur-model observation points are perfect black boxes.
Analysis is impossible.
That's why it's an excursion.
So this is why he wished me "best of luck"?
Just walking normally isn't enough!
That's why the three of you...
...will carry those!
You've got no strength.
Look here. When it's like this, you have to firmly gather your weight and...
Wow! That's incredible!
I-I can't move.
Klutz.
Look who's talking!
You three really are good to have made it this far.
Listen!
The key to lifting a heavy pack is this:
First, lie on your back.
Then...
...with the weight of the pack on your back...
That's not very cool...
Now get to it!
Yes, ma'am!
Good!
Now then, Filicia and I will head to the goal point on the map, and wait for you.
If you think that you won't be able to make it, blow your bugle.
We'll come looking for you...
Got it?!
Also, wild animals may appear on the mountain.
If that happens, use of firearms is authorized.
Got it?
Now then, have a fun trip!
Right about face!
Forward, march!
March!
Now then...
Well, I'll leave the rest to you.
Roger.
It's so heavy...
So heavy...
It's so damn heavy!
Kureha-chan, stop it.
If you keep saying that, it'll come true.
Noël, how much longer?
Hey, Noël!
Hey, Kanata!
Found it!
Yahoo!
Wow, it's amazing!
Working. No problems.
That was nothing! It was easy to find.
Let's keep up the good work.
Yeah.
What is it?
Nothing. I was just thinking that this has always been here alone, protecting the town.
Now then, Noël, where to next?
Um...
If we are here...
That mountain.
Th-Th-That mountain...?
Someone do something about these packs!
Heavy...
I knew it. Both the Commander and Rio-senpai hate me after all!
It must be true... That's why they're...
Heavy...
Hey, say something, Kanata!
It's not like you to stay quiet!
Hey, come on!
Shut up.
What is it?!
I can hear it.
I can hear it!
H-Hey, hold on there, Kanata?
What happened to you?
Undead?
Y-Yeah...
Wow, it's beautiful!
It'll be refreshing, right? It's pretty, isn't it?
Break time!
No matter what anyone says, I'm going to take a break!
I've decided!
Number one!
That's not fair!
It's delicious!
Now you've done it!
Take that!
Since you were doing it...
Noël! Why you!
Take this!
A fish!
Hey, Kureha-chan, isn't it great? Isn't this fun?
Yeah! Wait, no!
Aren't you too laid back?!
But it's an excursion, so we should also make it fun!
Have you forgotten about those freaking heavy packs?
This is training, you know.
But Filicia-san said...
Hurry up and notice.
That person is black. Pitch black!
Huh?
But she's blonde and her skin is so light... She's just wonderful, right?
That's not what I'm talking about...
Kureha does not understand.
What?
That part of Filicia is good.
Isn't she?
No, that's wrong! You two are definitely looking at the wrong thing!
Geez! Someone do something about this airhead combination!
Now, time for lunch. Lu~n~ch.
We all got soaked, didn't we?
We'll dry off quickly, in this weather.
What is this?
The food is gone.
Could it have been a wild boar?
Eh?!
In my hometown, they'd often break into the fields.
But in the summer, there was a lot of food, so they wouldn't normally come out.
We have a bigger problem.
What?
The compass is gone.
Eh?!
I wonder if it was okay to leave the packs behind?
It's fine. Right now, our priority is to make it to the goal.
Do you have a bearing?
The first installation was here.
The river's location was here.
We were between the two when we first saw the mountain.
Therefore... for now it's fine if we just climb to the top.
Okay! Then no matter wha—
You're hungry, aren't you?
Is there anything we can eat?
There!
Bayberries!
Can those be eaten?
Yeah! It's sweet, and a little sour, but delicious.
We're in harmony, huh?
But it's impossible to climb. It's dangerous.
You think so?
We should hurry ahead.
It's said that Major Klaus crossed the desert without any food or water for three days,
and was still able to take down an enemy emplacement with his tank.
Something like this is nothing!
Is that true?
You've never heard?
They call him "The Desert Wolf."
He's simply amazing!
Ehh? That Klaus-san is?
So, let's do our best!
But the bayberries!
No crying allowed!
Found the second one!
A wild boar?!
Just where is the last one?
It's gotten quite dark, hasn't it?
Because we've had to confirm our bearings after every single turn.
Is this really the right way?
Probably.
What do you mean by "probably"?!
Without a compass, I cannot be 100% certain.
Then what? Are you saying that even though we got this far, it was pointless?
I did not say that.
My point most prevalent: if the compass was so important, why didn't you carry it on you?!
Wait.
We can't be fighting at a time like this!
My point more prevalent: who was it that wanted to play in the river for so long?
That's right!
You're too laid back.
What's with this "excursion"?
You're always spacing out!
That's why we're in this situation.
Do you understand?
There it is!
Yahoo!
Wait a second, Kanata!
Good grief. Somehow they were able to make it.
Goal!
We did it. We did it. Kureha-chan!
I get it.
I get it, so let go of me!
It hurts...
Look.
Nomansland.
This is at the edge of the world where people can live.
Good work.
Sorry, Commander!
We were unable to complete the mission.
What is this about a mission?
But...
I said it was an excursion, didn't I?
But that's...
We just wanted you to see this place.
These are the signatures of our senpai.
The maidens of the fort always come here at least once.
And they always see this scenery, at the edge of the world.
It's our history, isn't it?
That's right.
Can you walk a little more? There's one more thing that our predecessors left for us.
You're late.
Rio-senpai?
What happened?
Here.
Bayberries!
Back to life.
So, did you win?
Don't ask.
It was worth it, though.
Let’s remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let’s move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You’re just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know, you know, little happy!
let’s make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you hear my precious note?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
Kanata's Day Off
Hairdressing
Next time: Kanata's Day Off · Hairdressing