Sun Rangers
Hey...
Do you ever think that maybe,
there's no actual point to this job? They just—
Don't say that!
I'm trying not to think about it.
Sorry.
But, you know it's the truth.
I don't really care, though.
They told me we'd be protecting the people,
so I thought our jobs
would be really important.
No one's going to try to invade.
That's just how the world is.
Wh-What's going on?!
Nii-chan, fire! Fire!
No, this is...
Everyone, the enemy is here!
It's time for us to show what we're made of!
Huh?
What enemy, Professor Roppongi?
The earth people, of course!
The earth people are invading the surface!
All right!
It's time for us to shine!
It has finally come time for us, the
Earth Empire, to rule over the surface.
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
Three days ago
I have something
I'd like your opinion on.
Hero Show
What do you think?
Could I have you help with this?
The Earth Empire vs. The Sun Squad
"Harukaze Man and Kisshou Lady"?
I haven't seen them on TV.
I saw them on a poster
at the shopping district!
Yes.
They're a local hero team.
The youth organization within
the neighborhood association
put them together, and asked me to help.
The neighborhood association?
You know someone there?
I do.
Anyway, I'm helping with the hero show,
so I wanted you all to star in it.
It's this Sunday.
What?!
That's three days from now!
It was a last minute deal.
I was asked to get people together
who have acting experience.
Experience?
We only performed
during the cultural fair.
And he really sucks, too.
Well, excuse me.
I believe it's more important to entertain
the children than to be
good at acting, in this case.
Yeah, but...
But...
All right, I understand.
Leave it to us, Kiriha.
H-Hold on a second,
Theia, you can't just—
You should be overjoyed, Koutarou.
We get to train together again!
What—
No!
We have the sequel to the Blue
Knight play coming up soon, too.
Your training just got
moved up a little bit, is all.
I refuse!
Let me go!
I've already talked to Kenji.
And... Harumi, as well.
Huh? Sakuraba-senpai?
I'll be starring with her...
Guess I don't mind, then.
Harukaze
Kindergarten
Founding Day
All you good kids out there
at Harukaze Kindergarden,
Harukaze Man Hero Show
it's almost time for Harukaze Man!
Let's call him, everybody!
Harukaze Man!
Sorry, kids.
I defeated Harukaze Man!
For I am Princess Devil of the Earth Empire!
Harukaze Man wouldn't go down that easy!
He's way bigger than you!
Huh?!
Are you calling me small?!
Theia, that's not your line...
Princess Devil, please leave
this to your loyal servants,
Black Rose and Baron Demon.
Y-You're right.
Go forth, Baron Demon!
Right!
Come here, girl!
Hey, you there!
Let go of my girlfriend!
Your girlfriend, huh?
Silence, you four-eyes pretty boy!
I'm taking this cute girl for myself.
Come forth, Jet Black King!
Why am I always the horse?!
Jet Black King!
Okay!
Now, Jet Black King,
let's get to our wedding.
Married? I can't...
She looks kind of happy.
Girls like the bad boys.
Harukaze Man Hero Show
Will they get away with this?!
Has the good guy,
Harukaze Man, really died?!
He's—
Not here?
White smoke rises
Harukaze Man appears
The hero's supposed to
show up now, right?
Yeah. That's weird.
Someone save me!
No one's going to save you!
Stay away from that lady, Earth Man!
Who are you?
We won't forgive you, evildoer!
Red Shine.
The Sun Squad, Sun Rangers!
W-Who are these guys?
They've got no clue how this works.
There is justice in love!
As long as there is the sun—
Knock it off!
Ouch.
What are you doing?
That was just pathetic.
We've got another Yurika
on our hands, don't we?
Yuri...
Why are the heroes all the same color?!
Whose idea was that?!
Even someone who's never done
this couldn't mess that up!
Huh? No, um...
Oh, no!
It seems the heroes all showed
up in the same red costumes.
That's not right!
Red is supposed to be the leader's color.
It's the worst when you're dressed
the same as someone else.
We all have the same suits because
of budgeting requirements—
I don't care!
Hey, children!
Is this the best that the good guys can do?
Are these the heroes you want?!
No!
Then, who's your hero?!
Harukaze Man!
Harukaze Man Hero Show
Courage, the power of hope within a person!
Love, an indestructible
heart that supports courage!
We're the soldiers of courage and love!
Harukaze Man!
Kisshou Lady!
Harukaze Man Hero Show
There you are, Harukaze Man!
Hey, is this...
It's a hero show, yeah...
Who said this was an attack
by the earth people?!
That was a big mistake.
Let's go home.
Ah, Sir Baron Demon was so dreamy.
I want him to punish me!
Who was that?
Who knows...
Big Sis Kiriha!
Hey, Yocchan.
I was watching.
Harukaze Man was great!
Good, I'm glad you liked it.
By the way...
Did you come here alone?
My mom and dad are at the shop.
I see.
I'll take you home, then.
Really?!
Yeah, I need to head to the
shopping district anyway.
Koutarou.
Y-Yeah?
I'm going to take off for a bit.
Sorry, but tell everyone thanks for me.
Sure. No problem.
Let's go.
Yeah.
The outfit for Kisshou Lady got ripped and it
took us a second before we could head out.
Sorry, we messed that up.
No, we had some other
people run in real fast,
so everything worked out.
Were those guys from the
neighborhood association?
Weren't they Kurano-san's friends?
No, Kiriha didn't know
what was going on, either.
Yeah.
Was it the Cosplay Society?
The Cosplay Society would have
at least used different colors!
Then who were they?
Hey, Satomi-kun.
Where's Kiriha-san?
Oh, she went off to the shopping district.
She said she had something to do.
Huh?
I bet they're the volunteers
for the cleaning squad.
I told them they didn't
have to come today.
Volunteers for the cleaning squad?
They're in our events a lot.
They really help us out.
Since when?
Hm...
About half a year ago...
Half a year?
Harukaze Shopping District
I'm hungry after being that horse!
All you did was make horse sounds.
She did make a pretty good horse, though.
She's working hard.
She's really cleaning the place up.
Did you think she was lying?
Koutarou, hide!
What is it, Sanae?
Koutarou, this is bad!
We need to do something now!
This town is in trouble!
Huh?
Those are Kiriha's friends,
right? They're all earth people!
Yeah, I'd imagine so.
They're invading!
They're invading us!
Calm down, Sanae.
I thought that for a second, too, but...
They just look like they're cleaning.
No, they're not!
They look like they're cleaning,
but I'm sure they're...
Huh?
How can you invade while you clean?
Don't ask me.
Then, maybe I'm just over-thinking it...
Speaking of which... Kiriha...
You can't be all blue, either!
We've got a message from the chief!
He's asking for mission status.
I see...
Connect me.
No problem!
Converting to transmission mode.
Hi there Kiriha, sorry for contacting you so late.
It's been a while, Chief.
You don't have to call me "Chief"...
"Dad" is fine.
It's just the two of us, after all.
But, this is an official mission report.
You've started to become
more like your mother,
not just outside, but in personality, too.
Honestly.
Anyway, let's get to business.
Right.
So, your status?
Plan A, the tiered integration
plan, is moving to phrase two.
We've been participating in
neighborhood association activities,
so we're being welcomed locally.
It's going smoothly.
What about Plan B?
It's falling behind schedule.
As I discussed before,
Corona House's Apartment
106 is being targeted
by many different parties.
Right.
However, Plan A is going smoothly,
so I don't believe there is any
reason to be worried about Plan B.
I believe so, as well.
But, Kiriha, there's been some
unrest amongst the radicals as of late.
Especially Tayuma Shijima...
That short-tempered boy?
He keeps advocating that brute
force is the fastest method.
There may be a need to advance
Plan B based on their movements.
In other words, I will need to
obtain Apartment 106 by force...
Kiriha...
Why not come back and marry?
Huh?
If you get married, it'll solidify our base,
and our influence on the radicals will grow.
You'll also be a lot safer that way.
I..
can't do that.
Please, not yet.
I'm taking this cute girl for myself.
Sakuraba-senpai.
Y-Yes?
Did something good happen?
Well, I...
The hero show yesterday was fun.
Oh, that.
Yeah, the kids had a lot of fun, too!
Yeah.
They were all thanking us.
It's almost like a different type
of a feeling of success you get,
compared to the cultural fair.
Hard to put into words.
It was for the neighborhood association.
Maybe that's why.
We were able to help people out in our city.
It's like I really became part of the city.
That's how I felt.
Part of the city...
Could it be...
Huh?
Ah, nothing.
I was just thinking I wanted
to do the hero show again.
How about doing an action thing next?
Well, I have a knight to protect me,
so I won't be fighting.
I see.
Then just leave it to me, your
Blue Knight, Princess Alaia.
Or so you thought, but
I'm really Baron Demon!
Hey, Yurika!
Hurry!
I know!
I have to watch "Magical
Girl Love Love Heart" today!
Koutarou, see you there!
Right.
Be careful!
Sure!
Harukaze Meat
Here you go.
Thanks.
Hey, Kiriha-san.
Oh, Koutarou.
Pork for braising
Pork loin (for steak)
Buying dinner?
Ruth-san isn't with you?
Yeah, Theia-dono is busy
with the theater club.
She's getting really into the
continuation of "The Silver Princess
and the Blue Knight", supposedly.
Ruth's there to keep an eye on her.
I see.
So, I'm going to do the shopping myself today.
I'll help you carry everything, then.
Really?
Thanks.
Kiriha-chan, thanks for taking
my daughter back yesterday.
No problem.
You're always helping me out.
Oh, Kiriha-chan.
With your boyfriend today?
I'll leave that one to your imagination.
What?
We got some good tea.
I'll give you a sample.
Thank you so much.
Thanks for cleaning up the other day.
Have this, on the house.
Thanks.
I'll take it.
Hey, Kiriha-san.
Could I ask you something?
I'll answer you the best I can, based
on the content of your question.
Do you not really want to
invade the Earth at all?
Well, that was quite the question.
Why do you think so?
You were cleaning up yesterday, right?
That, and the hero show...
It's almost like you're trying
to become part of this town.
That's what it felt like.
I was wondering what was up, but after
thinking about it, it all made sense.
Kiriha-san,
you're too nice to invade.
I might just be trying to make you
believe that to gain your trust.
You tried to make me
uncomfortable by saying that
when I first met you.
I'm pretty stupid, so I kept
worrying about it, but...
Maybe you...
just didn't want me to trust you.
Koutarou...
Could I have some of your
time during our next day off?
There's a place I want you to go with me.
Koutarou, where's your coat?
I don't really need a coat because it's warm.
What about this jacket, then?
Sure, I'll take that.
Koutarou, you're forgetting
your handkerchief.
Oh, thanks.
You're not forgetting anything else?
Let's see...
My wallet...
You put it in your right pocket a second ago.
Oh, you're right.
Anyway, we're headed out!
Later.
Bye!
What was that about?
C-Could it be a d—
It was totally a date!
When did they get so close?
I won't permit it!
He shouldn't have chosen her!
Satomi-san should have taken me
and Sakuraba-senpai out, instead!
Kiriha has to be planning something!
Ruth, track them!
Yes, I won't allow your knight
to have any illicit relations!
They're heading towards the station.
Let's go!
Right!
Yes, Your Highness!
Yurika, fight!
Shizuka-sama, you're not coming?
No, I have work today.
Then, leave it to us!
We'll follow them!
We'll report our findings later!
Ruth, Sanae, Yurika, hurry!
Good luck!
That's weird...
The detector definitely
picked up earth people...
More specifically, the technology
that the earth people use.
Well, it could have been malfunctioning.
Are there even really earth people
trying to invade the surface?
Well, if you're staring to lose faith,
just look at how positive Megumi-chan is.
Baron Demon!
I want him to yell at me again...
I want him to take me away, and
tell me he's going to marry me.
Honestly, I don't think
I want to be like her at all.
We agree on something for once.
What's that?
Again?!
Everyone, emergency situation!
Are you sure this time?
It's a much stronger
signature than last time.
It's most likely the real thing.
The earth people are really attacking.
Whichever team pops their balloon
first without using their hands wins!
Ready, dom!
Well, that was easy.
Yay!
Why won't it break?!
You'll never be able to do it.
Give up, Theia.
Next Episode: Someday, With Them...
Why?!