It's so easy once you figure it out.
I feel invincible!
Take it.
This is what you want, isn't it?
Now I don't owe you anything.
We're even now, right?
Let's go, Madoka.
Sayaka...
Sorry...
I'm just a little tired...
Don't push yourself. Hold on to me.
That idiot.
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 8     I'm such an idiot
Sayaka...
Don't fight like that anymore...
You're lying when you say it doesn't hurt.
It hurt just to watch.
You can't just say it's fine to get hurt if you can't feel it.
If I don't do that, I can't win.
I don't have the skill.
If you win by fighting like that, it's not good for you.
What is "good for me"?
What could even be good for me now that I look like this?
Sayaka...
I'm just a rock now that's only good for killing Witches.
A dead body moving around like it's alive.
What's anyone going to do that's good for me now?
It's obvious how pointless it is.
What can I do to make you happy?
Fight.
Kyubey told me this.
You have the most talent out of anyone.
You can defeat Witches easily without pushing yourself like me.
I...
I can't...
If you want to do something for me,
try being in my position.
Of course you can't.
I don't expect you to cast off your humanity out of pity.
It's not pity...
You can do anything, but you refuse to do anything.
So I have to do this instead.
Don't talk to me like you understand when you don't.
Sayaka!
Don't follow me.
I'm such an idiot!
Why did I say that?
You can't save me!
Homura
I expect Walpurgis to begin here.
How do you figure?
It's statistics.
What statistics?
I've never heard of a Walpurgis coming here.
Where are you getting your statistics?
Look, we're not going to totally trust each other,
but you have to fill me in a bit.
I'd like to know too.
Homura Akemi.
How are you going to make us miserable this time?
You don't want me here?
But I have information that's you need to know.
Huh?
Sayaka Miki's exhaustion is proceeding even faster than expected.
Not just from magic. The curse is now coming from herself.
Who do you think's responsible?
At this rate, something bad might happen even before Walpurgis comes.
You should be careful.
What do you mean?
You should ask her, not me.
You already know, don't you, Homura Akemi?
That's what I thought.
I would love to know how you learned this.
You...
You've said what you wanted to say.
Leave.
You're letting him go?
You won't accomplish anything by killing it.
Anyway, what about Sayaka Miki?
What's the bad thing that's supposed to happen to her?
Her Soul Gem has collected too much taint.
If it's not cleaned soon, she may not be able to turn back.
Homura
The helper verb "must" means you have no choice,
while "have to" means that either way...
She said not to go after her, but...
Is this the way to your house, Shizuki?
I've never seen you take this way back before.
Yes. In fact, my house is the opposite direction.
What? Then why...
I have...
something I'd like to tell you.
What?
She hasn't come back?
Since yesterday?
Okay. I see.
Okay. Goodbye.
Sayaka...
I have to find her.
Why don't you understand?
You have no power to spare.
Focus on killing Witches.
Shut up. It's none of your business.
Your Soul Gem is at its limit.
You must purify it right now.
Use this.
What are you plotting?
Stop that.
You're in no position to be suspicious.
Are you so against being helped?
I'll be a different kind of Puella Magi from all of you.
I've decided.
I will not cooperate with anyone who abandons or uses others.
I don't need any payment.
I won't use magic just for myself.
You will die.
I'll only die when I can't kill Witches.
That'll mean I'm useless anyway.
So I don't care.
If I can't kill Witches, I have no reason to exist.
Why? I just want to help you.
Why don't you believe me?
Why, indeed?
It's because I know...
that you're a liar.
Your eyes say you've given up.
Everything you say is empty.
You just said you're doing this for me,
but I know you're thinking something else.
You can't fool me.
You are making Madoka suffer.
Madoka has nothing to do with this.
Yes, she does.
This is all for her.
You're very smart.
Yes, you're absolutely right.
I'm not doing this to help you.
I don't want Madoka to see you destroying yourself.
If you refuse me now, you will certainly die.
If you continue to cause Madoka pain,
I will personally, right here,
kill you, Sayaka Miki.
Run! Get out of here!
Are you nuts? Didn't you come to help her?
Let go.
Oh, I get it. You can't use your powers if someone grabs you right here.
Damn it!
No more excuses outta her.
Gotta get all the cash she's made out of her.
Bitches, man. You give them a little cash and they go and spend it on some stupid shit.
You just can't treat 'em like people.
You gotta train 'em like dogs.
That bitch'd probably like that.
Just say you'll smack her and she'll shut her facehole.
And then you be nice for a sec and she'll never want to leave you.
Never be too nice to them, god.
Like some cabaret girl's gonna make the same cash in ten years.
Gotta know their place.
Stupid cunt whined like a bitch when I dumped her.
I wish I was as good at this shit as you.
You gotta give me some tips-
Tell me about whoever you're talking about.
What?
The woman you were just talking bout.
Tell me more about her.
You a middle schooler?
It's not nice to gossip.
You must mean a lot to that woman. She wants to make you happy.
You know that, don't you?
But you're comparing her to a dog.
You don't thank her.
If she stops being useful, you'll abandon her.
Why, she someone you know?
I mean...
Is this world worth protecting?
Tell me why I should fight.
Tell me right now.
Or I'll...
Where are you, Sayaka?
Do you hate me too?
If I hate you, will you turn Sayaka back?
No. That's beyond my power.
You said I would be a really powerful Puella Magi. Is that true?
"Really powerful" is an understatement. You would be extraordinarily powerful.
Possibly the most powerful in the world.
If I had accepted, maybe Sayaka wouldn't have become a Puella Magi...
Sayaka made her own wish.
It had nothing to do with you.
Why me?
I don't know.
Honestly, your hidden potential is something I would never have even dreamed of.
I would like an explanation myself.
Really?
If you unleash your power, you may just cause a miracle,
or you may even change the laws of the universe.
But I can't explain why you alone have that kind of power.
I thought I didn't have any dreams.
I thought I'd just live out my life, never being able to
make anyone happy or be good for anything.
It made me sad and lonely,
but there was nothing I could do about it.
But the reality is very different.
If you wish, Madoka, I could make you into God.
Then could I do what you couldn't?
And what's that?
If I made a contract with you, could I turn Sayaka back to normal?
It would be easy for you.
Is that a wish worth trading away your soul?
For Sayaka, gladly.
Make me a Puella-
This is horrible!
Why did you kill him?
Why are you always sacrificing yourself?
You're not good for anything?
You have no meaning?
Don't put yourself down.
Think about the people who care about you.
Stop this!
There are people who would mourn if you were gone!
Why don't you understand?
What about everyone who is trying to protect you?
Homura!
Have we...
Have we met somewhere before?
I'm sorry...
I have to find Sayaka.
Wait!
Sayaka Miki is already...
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Madoka!
You know it's useless.
You just don't learn.
I have many bodies.
Destroying one won't do any good.
You're wasting your energy.
This is the second time you've killed me.
That's told me what kind of attacks you use.
That was time-manipulating magic, right?
It seems that my guess was right.
You aren't from this timeline.
I know what you are and what you're planning.
And that's why you keep interfering with me.
You think you can change Madoka Kaname's fate like this?
Yes.
I will not allow your plan to succeed.
Kyubey...
Or should I say Incubator?
I finally found you.
When are you gonna stop being stupid?
Sorry for wasting your time.
Huh? That's weird for you to say.
I don't care anymore.
What was important to me, what I wanted to protect...
I don't know what those are anymore.
Hey...
Hope and despair always balance out to zero.
That's what you said, right?
I understand what that means now.
I did save a few people,
but with each one, the hate in me grew.
I even hurt my best friend.
Sayaka, did you...?
Whenever I wish for someone to be happy, someone else has to suffer as much.
That's what it means to be a Puella Magi.
I'm such an idiot.
SAYAKA!
"Puella" is an old word that refers to girls who haven't grown up.
Since you grow into Witches, it only makes sense to call you Puella Magi.
Itsuka Kimi ga Hitomi ni Tomosu
Love will ignite a light
Ai no Hikari ga
in your eyes
Toki wo Koete
It will transcend time
Horobi Isogu Sekai no Yume wo
The world dreams
Tashika ni Hitotsu
as it hurries to death
Kowasudarou
One dream will be destroyed
Tamerai mo Nomihoshite
For what do you seek,
Kimi ga Nozomu Mono wa Nani
upon ridding all hesitation?
Konna Okubukai Akogare no
Do ephemeral tomorrows verily await
Yukue ni Hakanai Ashita wa Aruno
past this profound admiration?
Kodomo no Koro ni Yume ni Miteta
If I could replicate the ancient spells
Inishie no Mahou no You ni
I dreamt of in my youth,
Yamisae Kudaku Chikara de
I would go see your smile,
Hohoemu Kimi ni Aitai
harnessing the power to obliterate the darkness
Obieru Kono Te no Naka ni wa
The funeral wreath I hold
Tomuraeta Hana no Yuuki
gives courage to my trembling hands
Omoidake ga Tayoru Subete
My heart is my only support
Hikari wo Yobisamasu Negai
I will light the darkness
Artist Takuya Fujima
With help from Kentaro Tanaka
You can call me stupid.
But until we know if she can be saved or not...
I will not give up.
Episode 9     I won't allow that
I won't allow that