Look out!
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10, xXxTrIsTxXx
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
"Nanen Apartments"
Yes?
Cabbage?!
--You moved?!
--Yeah!
--Where?
--Next door.
Next Door?!
Wait, you don’t mean…?
Yep!  Room 203, right next to yours!
Now we can eat New Year’s Eve noodles together!
Are you serious…?
Hey, Mario! Let’s celebrate your move! Let’s drink!
Oh! Cabbage is here too?!
That’s perfect.
Wow! So Joe sang?
Yeah!
It was a last-minute thing, so he only sang two songs, though.
But he had the crowd on its feet!
The chicks were going crazy over him!
That’s great!
At this rate, we might become best friends to a big star!
I know! Maybe I can be Joe’s manger next year!
He’s helpless by himself!
No, wait.  I could start an entire talent agency!
Yes, yes…
What’re you grinning at?!
You get really happy every time you talk about Joe.
D-Don’t be stupid! Why would I be happy?!
Tell me, Joe… Why music?
There must be more to it than simply enjoying singing.
I have a younger sister.
A sister?
Our parents abandoned us when we were little
and we grew up together in an orphanage.
But my sister was eventually adopted.
I don’t even know where she is or how she’s doing now.
That’s why I want to become famous as quickly as I can!
If I become famous enough to catch my sister’s attention.
I might get to see her again…
That’s perfect.
Huh?
A young man who sings in the hopes
of reuniting with his long lost sister.
That’s a real tear-jerker.
So, what did you do before you joined the Five Lemons?
“Jazz Club”
♪May our destination shine♪
Joe sang his heart out. Under Kawamata’s guidance,
he trained as hard as he possibly could…
…in the hope of becoming a "big star" as quickly as possible.
“New Year’s Day, 1958”
My fortune says I’ll have great luck this year!
Oh! That’s great!
It’s the New Year’s holiday.  Guess I can’t expect any business.
Ah, well.  It’s a little early, but I guess I’ll head to Mario’s place…
Oh! Joe!
What’ve you been up to?
Are you visiting a shrine?
You at least have New Year’s off, right?
She a friend of yours?
Well, whatever.
If you’re free later, you should come with me to Mario’s place!
We’re gonna get everyone there and have a big New Year’s party!
Joe?
Turtle…
Stay away from me from now on.
I want to be left alone.
Joe…
That asshole! Screw him!
“I want to be left alone”?!
Like I’d wanna see that bastard again anyway!
Sheesh. Didn’t expect to hear
Turtle’s grumbling first thing in the New Year.
What?!
We’re not together often.  Let us enjoy our drinks!
Hmph!
I’m never talking to that blockhead again!
Gimme some more!
That’s enough, Turtle.
Joe’s at an important stage in his career.
He can’t help it.
He’s an ex-reformatory inmate who’s struggling to make a big debut.
That woman was probably his manger
And she told him to cut off all ties with us.
Still….!
Turtle.  You know what this is really about.
Basically, you’re sulking because Joe can’t hang out with you anymore.
D-Don’t be stupid!  I am not sulking!
It’s okay! I’ll play with you, Turtle Wurtle!
Cabbage! Damn you…!
There, there. Don’t worry. We’ll take turns looking after you.
--Screw you! Don’t touch me!
--There, there.
♪It’s an impossible trail♪
Stop! Stop!
You’re not sounding right at all!
I’m sorry…
Whatever.
Let’s take a five-minute break.
By the way, Joe.
You cut off all ties with those reformatory boys, I hope.
Yes…
Joe.
Mario…
It’s been a while.
Can we talk?
Sorry… I’m busy right now.
It won’t take long…
--What is this about?
--Just sit down.
I take it Turtle told you?
Yeah.
He got piss-drunk and wouldn’t stop grumbling.
It’s exactly like you heard.
I don’t want anything to do with you guys anymore.
No one’s gonna hold you back.
We all understand that you’re fighting alone.
So don’t worry about us Just do the very best you can.
Mario…
This is my new address.
Contact me if you need to.
If there’s anything we can do for you, we’ll do it.
And, when you finally do stand on a big stage,
Be sure to give ol’ Turtle a front row seat.
All right?
Just don’t forget about him before then.
Pay attention when you’re working!
--I’ll help you see your sister.
--Huh?
I won’t forget…
I’d never forget…
I refuse to forget…
♪It’s an impossible trail♪
♪But if we grab ahold of bad dreams♪
♪May our destination shine♪
Why are you guys still so nice to me
after the self-centered things I said?
Let Meg hear this!
Let Anchan hear this!
I’m going to sing with every ounce of feeling I have!
Your popularity is truly amazing!
No, you’re being too kind!
--Oh! Shigeo!
--Dad!
You were really cool today, Dad!
Was I? Thanks, Shigeo!
--Hey, Joe?!
--What’s that?
You were pretty cool, too!
Not as cool as Dad, though!
Thanks.
Big news, Joe!
The Western Festival!
That’s always great…
What about it, though!
Look closely at the list of performers.
“Joe Yokosuka, the rising star”
Th-This is…
It’s finally come.  The day you take your first step toward stardom.
Really?!  I get to perform at the Western Festival?!
I told you you could count on me.
--Congratulations!
--Way to go, Joe!
Thank you!
There isn’t much time until the show!
Time to practice!
I did it, Meg…!
“Cabaret – Closed”
Hey did you hear?
This really cool guy’s going to be at the Western Festival!
Yeah, I heard!
The one who sings at King, right?
Hey, want to get tickets and see him?
Definitely!
How about you, Meg?
Oh…
I’m not interested…
Joe’s long-lost sister Meg, now a beautiful girl,
Worked as a hostess in a cabaret club in a seedy section of town.
This was where she arrived after much struggle.
Damn that Joe!
Now he’s gone and done it!
What now, Mickey?
He promised he would never
sing again, but he went back on his word.
We’ll just have to quiet him for good.
No, he’s still of use to us.
What do you mean, Mr. Tsubouchi?!
It will be the Five Lemons who perform at the Western Festival…
You want the Five Lemons to play
back-up for us at the Western Festival?
“Akira Tsubouchi, Manager”
Yes.  Joe’s repertoire is probably still
small, so we can make up for the rest.
Then we can call it even for taking
Joe away from us without permission.
What do you say?
It would be a good deal for you, too.
You want me to let your third-rate band play back-up for Joe?
Wh-What did you say?!
I admit, it’s entertaining to see
the people who used to boss Joe around.
Now wagging their tail at him.
Unfortunately, he already has a band.
Please leave if you have nothing else to discuss.  We’re busy here.
You can’t treat us like that, Ms. Yamauchi.
I could easily ruin the Western Festival if I wanted to.
If you’d like, I can even.
Put away that toy in your coat!
I guess third-rate bands go
hand-in-hand with third-rate managers.
I have the Fukomoto gang’s backing.
Do you really have the balls to shoot me?
The Fukomoto gang?
If you don’t, then get the hell out, half-face!
A fool who’s half gangster
and half ordinary citizen is a “half-face.”
Almost like hyenas, they harass and prey on regular people.
The fact they’re absolutely acquiescent to real gangsters
while also crafty and vicious with regular
people makes them troublesome.
What the hell was that?!
You let that old hag scare you!
If you’re too much of a wimp, we’ll go take care of Joe ourselves!
Could you be quiet for a moment?
Fuck you! Shitty manager!
It’s your fault--!
Do you not know the meaning of “shut up”?!
M-Mr. Tsubouchi…!
I’m going to settle this, once and for all…
“Western Festival”
Huh? Why Me?
It arrived in the mail this morning.
One ticket was probably all he could get.
I guess Joe would want you to go.
Hah!  Why would I wanna go?!
He gave it to you, didn’t he?  You go!
I can’t skip work.
N-Neither can I.
How are we supposed to tell Anchan about Joe’s proud moment
If no one’s there to see it.
Tell him?
“January 27th”
The next day is the anniversary of Anchan’s death…
Exactly, so we’re counting on you, Turtle.
Tell Anchan about it yourself.
Fine! I’ll go!  I’ll go alright!
“Joe Yokosuka”
You did it, Joe…
Oh, come on, Meg.
I can pay! Come on!
That's him! The boy with blue eyes!
They say he’s a good singer!
Oh? His name’s Joe Yokosuka?
"Joe Yokosuka, the rising star”
What is it, Meg?
B-Brother…?
“Day of the festival”
What are you doing, Joe?
Hurry up.  All the band members are already there.
What’s the matter Joe.
You’re about to sing in front of 2,000 people;
You can’t have a glum look like that!
I’m sorry, Mr. Kawamata!
You’ve done so much for me,
yet I’m the only one going on stage…
Don’t be silly, Joe!
Don’t worry about it!
Yeah, Joe!
Besides, Dad would be so cool on stage
That you wouldn’t get any attention!
That’s a good one!
Joe!  You’re going to become a star overnight.
A star needs to stand tall and proud!
--Go sing with everything you got!
--I Will!
What’s going on here!
Why are you here?
Isn’t it obvious?!
We’re here to settle the score!
Settle the score…!
Joe!  You need to get out of here.
I can’t!  This is the only door--!
Stop that, you thugs!
Shut up!
All right, Joe!  We know you’re in there!
Come out this instant!
Dad!
It’s okay, Shigeo!  I’m here with you!
Okay…
You hear me, Joe?!  I’ll kill this hag first if you don’t come out!
Shigeo!
I have a favor to ask!
If he insists on staying in there, then…
Hey, Charlie!  Hold the old hag still!
Right!
Mario Minakami…
A man named Mario Minakami lives at this address.
Tell him what’s happening
I’m counting on you, Shigeo.
Mario… Mario Minakami.
Say your prayers, Joe…
“Western Festival”
Brother…
Is this really you?
“Is this Joe Yokosuka really my brother?”
Meg knew that her despair
would be great if she got her hopes up,
but she still couldn’t keep her heart from beating faster.
What could I keep watching over
same ta manazashi
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it itsnow
a far off distance
The road to superstardom begins.
A sister waits alone.
The captured Joe entrusts everything to Mario…