The sports duel's programme,
as suggested by Kawashima-san,
will be a 50 metre freestyle one-game match!
Lucky!
What did you write?
Freestyle Battle
If I win, we'll hold an autograph session of your impression photographs.
If I win, Takasu-kun will have to spend his summer at my family's villa.
You'll be alone for the whole summer.
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, yet complicated and mysterious
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
onkou tokujitsu ECCENTRIC na anata
You, who's gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PURE PARAATO
A naive preparation
atama no naka wa junjou PURE PAREEDO
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
For Whose Sake
All right, whoever understands it, come and write on the board.
Yes.
As expected of the class chairperson.
Hey.
Idiot.
First round, the battle for Takasu cup begins.
Ami-tan versus Palmtop Tiger.
One bet, 500 chiroru.
Chiroru: A type of Japanese candy.
What's this?
Can this be considered a duel?
If it's a swimming duel, Ami-tan will win for sure.
Tiger sinks, you know.
I want to be fought for too, what should I do?
Damn, these guys...
Ami's mine, so sorry, arl.
Could it be that you're trying to write "all"?
You bribed your way into school, didn't you? > Haruta
Isn't it bad that he can't even write "all"?
Haruta, you...
Not that!
Everyone's writing whatever they want.
What...
3000 chiroru!
Takasu Ryuuji
W-What's wrong, Aisaka?
If you understand the problem, please go up and explain it.
A-Aisaka-san?
Don't be afraid, Taiga.
It's the same as washing your face.
Come on, once more!
Even if you put it that way...
She can't even put her face in the water?
Isn't that too low of a level?
Like this, the victor's already obvious.
Don't listen to what the others say.
I got it already.
Well, you can only give it your all if it's for Takasu.
Who...
Something wrong with "Who"?
Kitamura...
Just like this, do your best with Takasu's support.
Eh? What? Support...
Hey, Taiga!
I won't train during lessons ever again.
It'll be enough to depend on image training.
These will have to wait till you are able to submerge your face into the water.
What are the dishes today?
Snow peas with egg, tofu steak, and miso soup.
There's also spinach and fried tofu...
Don't just have beans, I want meat!
Don't be so extravagant, beans are meat of the crop fields, you know.
Stingy.
By the way, you've got to train properly during pool lessons.
You have to adjust your attitude first.
I can't adjust my attitude. It's because Kitamura's watching.
That's why you have to try harder, right?
You...
In the first place, whose fault was it that I was misunderstood and had to try so hard.
Whose...
That's why, in order to not let Kitamura go to Kawashima's villa...
Ouch!
Enough already. Just make dinner for me.
Really, what's with you...?
Come on, get on with making it quickly.
I’m going to start training hard after replenishing necessary nutrients.
The rain's not stopping, huh?
Today's pool lessons will be cancelled again.
Even though I'm finally able to submerge my face in the water...
Why can't the pool be used?
Don't ask me that.
Admission tickets to the town pool.
Use them. I bet on Aisaka too.
On the paper that came around before.
Because Takasu bet on Aisaka with so much confidence.
So I thought "All right, I'll bet for you to win too!"
Me?
Yeah.
W-W-Why? I obviously can't swim.
Because Aisaka's the type who goes all out when things get heated.
We still don't know who will be the victor.
This... shouldn't it be like this?
W-What are you doing?
Shut, shut, s-shut up!
Give it your best training then.
Idiot.
Hey, do you want to go shopping somewhere on our way back?
Sudoh-Bucks?
That's not bad.
Why are you squeezing yourself in such a place? Such a gloomy person.
This narrowness is able to calm one down.
Heave-ho.
No way, Takasu's in exhausted mode?
I have been, because of a certain someone's fault lately.
Eh? Who was it? Ami-chan has no idea.
You...
Isn't the jealous tiger cute?
Huh?
How is she jealous? That girl's just seeing you as an eyesore.
Is Takasu-kun stupid?
You're the stupid one, aren't you?
In any case, don't pick on Taiga too much.
You have no intentions of inviting anyone to begin with.
I'm serious about it.
I’m serious about winning, and making plans to spend the summer with Takasu-kun.
I'm thinking seriously about things to do after winning.
I think it will be fun.
Look, aren't we getting along well?
No we're not.
You're angry, you're angry.
You...
Good grief.
There must be a limit to teasing others.
Okay.
See you.
I know about it.
W-What? What do you know?
The one who made Taiga's swimsuit's striking large portion,
is Takasu-kun.
Eh... ah... that is...
There's no need to hide it. It's a simple deduction, Akechi-kun.
Akechi Kogorou: A very famous fictional detective in Japan.
In the past, Taiga told me.
"Ryuuji will always come to my aid".
Cleaning too, buttoning up too, ironing clothes too.
What, minor things like that...
Those minor things are the most amazing ones.
Hey, Kushie-
I believe in you.
I'll leave Taiga to you.
Y-Yeah.
That's because I'm a judge, hence unable to help.
But my feelings are the same.
Leave it to me!
All right!
I'll count on you for tomorrow, I'll count on you for tomorrow...
Thank you, teruterubouzu-san.
Teruterubouzu: A hand-made doll hung outside a window to bring good weather.
The sky's finally clear.
Look, Ryuuji.
It's as if I'm swimming, isn't it?
It's about time that you train seriously.
Eh, no way. What's with this?
The duel's tomorrow, how can you practice freestyle now?
You can only use whatever can be used, right?
How uncool.
All right, not bad.
Try paddling in the water like this.
I got it already.
Hey...
T-Taiga?
That's awesome, Taiga!
Your kicking power is abnormal after all.
You might be able to win this way.
Win? Me?
I'm just paddling the water normally though.
Well, of course, we can't be complacent.
But...
I see.
I can win. I see.
Taiga?
Yeah. I must win.
Y-Yeah. Keep this mindset.
Looks like it won't stop for a while.
Although you were starting to get motivated.
What should we do? Want to go back?
Do you still want to train?
I see.
That’s right.  We can’t let the admission tickets that Kitamura gave us go to waste.
It's not about that.
It's not that. I'm trying my best...
I know. You want to surprise that Kawashima too, right?
Enough already. Saying anything's useless.
What is it?
Could it be because of me?
I see. There will be no food without me.
Like I said, it's not that...
But you don't have to force yourself.
Even if you lose, it's fine for me to go to Kawashima's villa alone.
I'll beg her to not let Kitamura go.
I'll prepare you food and freeze it beforehand.
So, don't think about unnecessary things.
You've finally shown your true colours, huh.
You wanted to go to Ami-chan's villa from the start, right?
Huh? What's with that?
To me, wherever you are and whatever you are doing doesn’t bother me at all.
What did you say? To think that I was thinking so much for you.
Who told you to do such a thing?
You're acting strange lately. During that incident with Kawashima earlier too...
Do you still want to bring up that incident?
What exactly are you not satisfied with?
What I'm not satisfied with?
When others imagine my feelings on their own,
and act like they know it all.
I hate it. It makes me angry!
Why can't you understand?
Do you want me to understand or not, which one is it?
I don't know!
Huh?
No one should know what I'm thinking.
Because... because...
I don't know myself either.
What did you say just now...
Hey!
As you wished for, I'm not participating in the duel anymore.
Itchy.
I didn't do anything wrong, did I...
Huh? Ryuu-chan?
Why is my Ryuu-chan still awake?
I'm back!
Taiga-chan didn't come over?
Why? Did you guys quarrel?
Taiga said that she doesn't care about me anymore, and got angry.
I think that's the case.
Ah, I see.
But, you understand it, right?
Taiga-chan doesn't always mean what she says.
How can it not matter?
If she really hates Ryuu-chan,
she won't be coming here to eat from the same plate no matter how hungry she gets, right?
Really, not even removing her make-up.
Come on, pull yourself together.
You didn't eat anything, right?
I actually wanted it to be sunny.
Also, I hope that you can give it your all in the duel.
That... in other words...
No matter how you think, I...
I want you to win...
Win... I...
The lunch box is sin-free. I'll accept just this.
But.
Ah.
Because it's always raining,
the swimsuit that I usually wear wasn't dry.
But isn't this against the school rules?
I'm so worried.
That beautiful Ami-tan will be swimming in this pool?
That's for bringing Takasu to her villa.
Why is it always Takasu? Why? Why? Why?
Ouch!
Why? Why? Why? Why is it always Takasu?
Stop it, you guys!
It's not decided that I have to go to the villa, right?
How will Taiga be able to win...
Why not let her try?
Unless she tries...
We won't know, right?
That idiot. It's all meat this time.
Hey, hey. How much longer are we going to wait?
It's hot.
Why isn't the Palmtop Tiger coming?
Isn't it good? Let's treat it as if we've come to see the bikini today.
Hey, if everyone is kept waiting while it's so hot...
That's right too.
What are you barking for?
Let's settle it fair and square.
Stupid Chihuahua and an addition of a stupid bikini.
What's that?
Seriously?
Taiga!
Are you swimming with those?
For an instant, I thought she was fully armed.
Doesn't she look cool somehow?
Well then, 50 metre freestyle, one-game match!
Take your positions!
Ready.
Oh, hair.
Eh?
Crap...
Unbelievable, unbelievable, unbelievable!
The Palmtop Tiger using the Ganryujima skill, this is a really exciting battle of the brains!
Ganryujima: An island famous for a duel between Miyamoto Musashi and Sasaki Kojiro.
Damn you, midget tiger!
Taiga!
Did Taiga have an accident?
This is a chance for Ami-chan!
Go!
Damn!
Are you all right? Did your leg cramp up?
Idiot, let me go! I can still...
You can't do it anymore, right?
I want to go!
But you...
Aren't you happy?
What...
It's not "what"!
Your master's working hard for your sake, so be happier!
You retarded dog!
Awesome, Ami-tan!
Things have finally changed!
All right. If that's the case, go!
I'll wag anything, tail or not!
Therefore...
Ami-tan!
Don't push me!
Idiot, it's dangerous!
Ryuuji!
Huh?
Taiga...
Takasu!
Hey, Takasu! Are you all right?
Good, he's still breathing.
Aisaka, we'll take him to the infirmary quickly.
Don't touch him!
Taiga?
But, Aisaka...
Shut up. You guys are all idiots.
Why didn't you notice it?
Why didn't you save him?
You were all blinded by that stupid bikini.
No one went to save... Ryuuji...
Ryuuji is mine!
No one is to touch him!
You see.
I want to go to your resort too.
Huh?
I lost, didn't I? Ryuuji's going, isn't he?
Wouldn't there be no one to look after me?
Therefore I'll go too...
Wait a moment.
This decision is way too one-sided, so I'm confused.
Isn't it okay? It's much more interesting if everyone goes together.
Ah, I see.
Could it be that Aisaka-san would feel uneasy if separated from Takasu-kun?
In any case, "Ryuuji is mine", you know.
That's right. I admit it.
Because, you see...
That... in other words...
That's because this guy is my dog.
As the master,
I'm given the duty of watching over my own dog, to ensure that it doesn't "pant" outside.
What is it? Did you have any expectations?
I don't have any. Nothing at all.
All right. Then let's decide on the schedule.
Let me see, let me see...
I've always been working recently.
The recent club activities have also been tiring...
Isn't it a pity that we aren't able to be alone?
But there's still a good chance.
Just like this, Takasu Ryuuji's first semester of the 11th grade came to an end.
And summer break, which is filled with much excitement, is about to begin.
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru mono to wa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
Unable to be honest, I'm just rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
To the Beach with You.
I'm actually going to the villa with Kushieda...
I'm so fortunate, I hope I won't get retribution, Taiga.
Kitamura-kun...
Has a little black seaweed.
Huh?