♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
ALL RIGHT!
YOU DO ALL THAT BY YOURSELF?
NOT BAD, AMIGO.
HEY, COME ON.
LET'S BE FRIENDS NOW.
NO REASON TO WASTE WHAT OUR
WHIMSICAL GOD HAS GIVEN US.
OUR GOD?
WELL, FOR THESE GUYS,
IT'S MORE LIKE THE DEVIL.
WANT A HIT?
IT'S DOM PERIGNON.
[POURS CHAMPAGNE]
CHEERS.
TO THE SHIP THAT
CHARMED THE DEVIL.
[LAUGHS QUIETLY]
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON WITH
THE SHOWERS IN THIS PLACE?!
THIS IS THE FOURTH TIME.
THE FOURTH TIME!
EVEN BUDDHA GETS UPSET
AFTER 3 TIMES.
HEY, I'M TALKING TO YOU!
THE SHOWER'S BROKEN.
WE'VE ONLY GOT COLD WATER.
AND THE FAUCET FELL OFF.
WELL, IF YOU KNOW ABOUT IT,
THEN WHY DON'T YOU FIX IT?
I'M BUSY RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN DO THAT ANY TIME.
[COMMUNICATOR BEEPING]
HMM?
HE'S BUSY RIGHT NOW.
'BYE.
DON'T JUST HANG UP.
WHAT IF IT'S AN EMERGENCY?
[BEEPING]
[LAUGHS]
I GET IT, FAYE.
I PROMISE I'LL FIX THE SHOWER.
HI.
YEAH. HE'LL CALL YOU BACK.
WHO IS IT?
OK, FAT.
I'LL TELL HIM.
[BEEP]
WHAT'S THAT?
DID YOU SAY "FAT"?
DON'T YOU FEEL THAT?
HUH?
UH...
IT NEEDS TO BE REPAIRED.
FAYE, I TOLD YOU I'D FIX IT.
I MEAN YOUR ARM
RECONSTRUCTIVE SURGERY.
IT DOESN'T COST THAT MUCH
THESE DAYS, YOU KNOW.
THIS SHIP IS MY SHIP,
AND THIS ARM IS MY ARM.
I DON'T NEED INSTRUCTIONS.
ATTENTION ALL
DEATH ROW INMATES.
I'M SORRY TO ANNOUNCE
THAT THE CRUISE
TO THE PRISON ON PLUTO
HAS BEEN CANCELED.
[ALL LAUGHING]
THE SHIP WILL NOW EMBARK ON
A HIGHLY MYSTERIOUS TOUR...
AND WHERE WILL YOU GO?
DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN GET
AWAY IN A SHIP LIKE THIS?
I WASN'T TALKING
TO YOU, WAS I?
YOU'LL NEVER PULL IT OFF.
YOU KNOW THAT.
IF YOU TURN YOURSELVES IN,
YOU CAN MAKE IT.
[GUNSHOTS]
UNH!
MAN, I TOLD YOU TO SHUT UP.
HEY, DON'T GET SO HOTHEADED.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU JUST BLEW AWAY
OUR ONLY HOSTAGE.
THE GUY WAS VALUABLE.
YOU TRYING TO
TELL ME WHAT TO DO?
IF YOU GOT A PROBLEM,
THEN STEP RIGHT UP!
HUH?
YOU!
UNH!
[GASPS]
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
YEAH, I HEARD ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE THAT ASSASSIN
FROM THE SYNDICATE... UDAI.
CAUGHT YOU
REDHANDED... LITTERING.
THAT'S A 2,000-WOOLONG
FINE, MY FRIEND.
THEN I'LL NEED TO COLLECT
ON THAT LOAN I GAVE YOU
WITH 7 YEARS' WORTH OF
INTEREST... AND PENALTY FEES.
WHEN DID YOU BUY ME
THAT CUP OF COFFEE?
IT'S WAY PAST THE STATUTE
OF LIMITATIONS.
SO YOU STILL THINK
YOU'RE A SHOOTER,
WITH AN OLD GUN LIKE THAT.
ISSP SURE CAN WASTE TAX MONEY.
ON THE GUN?
NO, ON YOUR SALARY.
OH, YEAH. RIGHT.
WANT ONE?
NAH.
I GAVE IT UP.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
TENTH DAY.
THIS IS NOT A WORLD FOR
SMOKERS ANYMORE, YOU KNOW.
HMM.
NEVER THOUGHT YOU'D QUIT.
SO... WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO TELL ME?
THERE WAS A RIOT ON
A PRISON TRANSPORT SHIP
THAT WAS ON ITS WAY TO
PLUTO, ABOUT 6 HOURS AGO.
APPARENTLY, THERE WAS
AN ELECTRICAL MALFUNCTION.
THE PRISONERS SAW THEIR
OPPORTUNITY AND TOOK IT.
I DON'T KNOW ALL THE DETAILS.
AND?
UDAI IS ON THE SHIP.
THEY GOT THROUGH
THE GANYMEDE GATE.
AFTER THAT, WE DON'T
KNOW WHERE THEY WENT.
ISSP IS GOING BALLISTIC.
HOLD ON. YOU'RE NOT GETTING
ANY STUPID IDEAS, ARE YOU?
THIS IS NOT YOUR BEAT.
ARE YOU SURE IT'S
A STUPID IDEA, JET?
THAT'S THE REASON YOU QUIT
THE POLICE FORCE, ISN'T IT...
BECAUSE OF THAT?
PAST THE STATUTE
OF LIMITATIONS .
IF HE GETS FREE
AFTER WHAT HE DID,
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO FEEL ABOUT
THAT MISSING ARM, PARTNER?
IT'S JUST OLD NEWS.
IT DOESN'T INTEREST ME ANYMORE.
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
JET!
I'LL GO AROUND THE BACK!
ALL RIGHT. DO IT!
[CRASH]
UNH!
UDAI TAXIM,
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST!
A SETUP!
[GUNSHOT]
SO WHAT DO WE DO?
YOU KNOW THE BOYS FROM ISSP ARE
GOING TO BE HERE ANY MINUTE,
AND OUR DEAR PILOTS
ARE VERY DEAD.
WE'RE GOING TO BREAK
THROUGH THEIR LINE.
EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
WE'VE GOT JUST ENOUGH
FIREPOWER FOR DEFENSE,
SO HOW DO WE HANDLE THAT?
I'M SURE THEY'VE
SET UP A BARRICADE,
AND THE BEST DEFENSE
IS A GOOD OFFENSE.
WE FIND THEIR WEAKEST POINT,
AND HIT IT HARD.
YOU MEAN... YOU CAN
PILOT THIS THING?
I USED TO BE
A POLICE CAPTAIN ON VENUS.
AN EX-COP, AND THEY
GAVE YOU LIFE IN PRISON?
COPS ARE HUMAN, TOO.
WE MAKE MISTAKES.
YOU CAME BACK.
HMM?
I'M LEAVING AGAIN.
AND DON'T STAY THERE.
YOU'RE IN THE WAY.
AAH. OOH!
BRING EDWARD SOME
SOUVENIRS THIS TIME.
EDWARD, IF I DON'T COME BACK,
WATER THE BONSAI FOR ME, OK?
ALL RIGHT.
♪ BONSAI, BOK CHOY
WISE GUY, WATER BOY ♪
♪ LIGHTS SHINE BRIGHT
IN THE OLD TOWN TONIGHT ♪
TEAM LEADER, DO YOU COPY?
THIS IS GROUP D7.
WE HAVE LOCATED
THE PRISON TRANSPORT SHIP.
THEY'RE SENDING
A DISTRESS SIGNAL.
APPARENTLY, THEY'RE EXPERIENCING
SOME DIRE MECHANICAL FAILURE.
WE'RE RELEASING
ONE EMERGENCY SHUTTLE.
ON IT ARE 4 OFFICERS
AND 12 INMATES.
WE'RE REQUESTING
AN IMMEDIATE PICKUP.
[EXPLOSION]
VEHICLES 12 AND 13.
NO RESPONSE.
REQUEST EMERGENCY BACKUP.
[TRANSMISSION GARBLED]
WE HAVE LOST SIGHT
OF THE TRANSPORT.
CURRENT LOCATION AT 745...
INITIATE CODE 108.
REPEATWE REQUEST
EMERGENCY BACKUP!
NO LUCK.
APPARENTLY, THE POLICE
DON'T HAVE A CLUE
WHERE THEIR SHIP WENT, EITHER.
AND WHERE DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE HEADING FOR?
WELL, THEY COULD TRY
TO HIJACK ANOTHER SHIP...
MAYBE FIND A GOOD HIDING PLACE
NEAR THEIR ORIGINAL ROUTE.
I DON'T THINK SO.
WELL, THEN WHAT?
EUROPA.
EUROPA? REALLY?
WHY GO THERE?
IF I WAS UDAI,
THAT'D BE MY MOVE.
YEAH, BUT UDAI HAS
BEEN OUT OF THE...
WELL, IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE HE WORKED FOR
THE EUROPEAN SYNDICATE.
HE'S OLD-FASHIONED,
VERY OLD-FASHIONED
THE KIND OF GUY WHO DOESN'T
REALLY BELONG IN
THIS DAY AND AGE.
HE'LL GO STRAIGHT BACK THERE.
I'M CERTAIN OF IT.
THE BLACK DOG WHO BITES ONCE,
AND THEN NEVER LETS GO.
OK.
EUROPA IT IS.
IF YOU'RE WRONG,
YOU'RE PAYING FOR THE FUEL.
WHAT THE-- UHAAAH!
HOW'D THIS THING GET FIXED?
[YELPING]
YEAH!
[LAUGHING]
OH...
HMM.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
JET'S GOING TO HAVE
A FIT, EDWARD.
HE ASKED ED.
- HUH?
- JET'S NEVER COMING BACK HERE.
[SIGHS]
NEVER MIND THAT.
JUST GET A MOP OR SOMETHING.
ALL RIGHT!
WHAT'S UP WITH JET, LEAVING
HIS PRECIOUS BONSAI TREES TO ED?
HEY, JET, WHAT IS GOING ON?
[BEEPING]
IT'S ME.
YOU'VE GONE WAY OVER THE LINE.
WE NEED A NEW SHIP.
THERE IS NO FURTHER RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN OURSELVES
AND UDAI TAXIM.
A BETRAYAL?
IF YOU WANT TO
THINK OF IT LIKE THAT.
I HAVE INFORMATION.
THAT, FRIEND,
DOESN'T WORK ANYMORE.
WHILE YOU WERE IN PRISON,
THINGS CHANGED.
NEW RULES.
[BEEPING]
YOU WERE RIGHT.
HE'S THERE.
OK. LET'S SPLIT UP.
I'LL COME AROUND
FROM THE OTHER SIDE.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
COME ON.
THE WEAPONS ON THAT
SHIP ARE WORTHLESS.
THIS IS THE WAY I WORK.
YOU KNOW THAT BETTER
THAN ANYONE, RIGHT?
HMM.
OH, JET.
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE UP
THIS BOUNTY HUNTER THING
AND TEAM UP WITH ME
AGAIN AT ISSP?
I'LL THINK IT OVER
IF WE MAKE IT BACK HOME.
[BEEPING]
IT'S A HEAT SOURCE.
THEY'RE AFTER US.
ISSP WOULDN'T SEND ONE SHIP.
THEY'D SEND A SQUADRON.
CHECK THIS OUT.
I FOUND SOME NEW TOYS,
AND WE'VE GOT THE PERFECT
TARGET TO TRY THEM OUT ON.
ALL RIGHT, JET.
WE'LL USE THIS
ICE FIELD FOR COVER.
DON'T TAKE OFF UNTIL
I GIVE YOU THE SIGNAL.
[BEEP]
UH... AH!
JET!
HELLO THERE, MY FRIEND.
WELCOME TO HELL.
UNH!
ARRGH!
AAAH!
AARGH!
[GASPS]
BINGO!
HUH?
AAAH!
THIS GUY'S GOT GUTS,
COMING IN HERE BY HIMSELF.
HMM?
[CHUCKLES]
WHO THE DEVIL IS HE?
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
THIS ONE'S MINE, UNDERSTAND?
[OXYGEN HISSING]
HE'S INSANE.
I'M NOT STICKING
AROUND FOR THIS.
[GRUNTING]
[AIR LOCK HISSES]
HUH?
[GASPS]
[HATCH SLAMS SHUT]
[GUNSHOT]
[PANTING]
HUH?
UNH!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[COCKS GUN]
[GUNSHOT]
YOU CAME ALL THE WAY
HERE TO SEE ME?
I WASN'T REALLY
LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
UNH!
AAH!
DON'T SAY THAT.
I CAME ALL THE WAY HERE
JUST TO SAY HELLO.
UH... UNH!
I DIDN'T WANT TO COME HERE,
BUT SOMETHING ELSE INSISTED.
WHAT?
THE ARM I LOST
BECAUSE OF YOU.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
OHH!
[PANTING]
WHAT A CLUELESS
CHUMP YOU ARE.
YOU NEVER FIGURED IT OUT
IN ALL THIS TIME.
[GRUNTING]
FIGURED WHAT OUT?
I'M NOT THE ONE WHO
FIRED THE GUN THAT DAY.
IT WAS YOUR OWN PARTNER.
[GASPS]
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
JET!
I'LL GO AROUND THE BACK.
ALL RIGHT. DO IT!
IT WAS ALL PLANNED OUT
FROM THE BEGINNING...
TO GET RID OF YOU...
BECAUSE YOU WERE A THREAT
TO THE SYNDICATE...
AND YOUR PARTNER
WAS ON OUR PAYROLL.
UDAI TAXIM,
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST!
HE LED YOU LIKE
A LAMB TO SLAUGHTER.
YOU WERE USED.
A SETUP!
UNH!
[GASPS]
WHY'D YOU BLAST HIM?
BECAUSE HE WAS
TELLING THE TRUTH?
YOU CAME HERE TO SHUT HIM UP
FOR GOOD, DIDN'T YOU?
WELL? NO ANSWER?
HOW ABOUT IT, PARTNER?!
YOU BROUGHT IT
ON YOURSELF, PARTNER.
YOU JUST COULDN'T PLAY THE GAME
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
BUT PEOPLE WHO GO AGAINST
THE SYNDICATE LOSE, JET.
THEY LOSE BIG.
EITHER THEY GIVE UP LIKE
YOU DID, OR THEY DIE YOUNG.
THIS IS THE REAL WORLD.
THERE'S NO PLACE
FOR PRETTY IDEALS.
AND THAT'S WHY
YOU BETRAYED ME?
THAT'S WHY YOU LIED
AND TOOK ME OUT HERE?
YOU WERE THE BEST MAN.
I WANTED TO TEAM UP,
LIKE BACK IN THE OLD DAYS.
SAYONARA, PARTNER.
UH... UNH!
[GUNSHOT]
FAT!
[GRUNTING IN PAIN]
HEY, JET.
HUH?
ONE BULLET?
YOU KNEW I'D TAKE YOU OUT
WITH YOUR GUN LIKE THIS.
CAN YOU HAND ME A CIGARETTE?
I GUESS I... COULDN'T QUIT
SMOKING AFTER ALL.
LET'S KICK THE BEAT.
THIS TIME, THE 3 OF US
WILL DO THE PREVIEWS
FOR THE NEXT EPISODE.
GEE, UH, DO YOU
THINK WE CAN DO IT?
WE ONLY HAVE 30 SECONDS.
IF YOU'RE TOO SLOW,
IT WILL BE ALL OVER.
YOU SURE ARE ANTSY,
OLD BUDDY.
AAH!
WHAT KIND OF STORY IS IT
NEXT TIME, ANYWAY?
HELL, I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT?! WE'RE ALREADY
RUNNING OUT OF TIME!
TITLE!
AT LEAST TELL THEM THE TITLE!
NEXT EPISODE...
UH, WHAT WAS IT?
I FORGOT.
CAN WE TRY THIS AGAIN?