- Fukuhara: MIZUKI HIMEJI
IS DILIGENT IN EVERY SUBJECT
SHE CHOOSES TO STUDY.
FOR EXAMPLE, TODAY, SHE'S
STUDYING A SUBJECT
THAT'S NOT EVEN
COVERED IN SCHOOL.
- HOW TO DELIVER A LOVE LETTER.
- THERE ARE MANY WAYS BUT IT'S
BEST TO GIVE IT IN PERSON.
THIS WAY THE PERSON KNOWS HOW
SERIOUS YOU ARE AND IT HELPS...
- HEY, HIMEJI. YOU STUDYING?
- ( exclaims ) YOSHII.
- YEAH, JUST A LITTLE
EXTRACURRICULAR RESEARCH.
HOLD ON.
THE BOOK SAID IT WAS BEST TO
GIVE IT TO HIM IN PERSON.
WELL... ACTUALLY...
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
PLEASE... NO MATTER WHAT YOU
THINK JUST DON'T LAUGH AT ME.
- ( glass shatters )
- Mizuki: ( screams )
WRONG ENVELOPE.
- HOW IS THIS FUNNY?
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: AKIHISA IS A YEAR 2,
CLASS F STUDENT.
THIS IS A NORMAL
MORNING FOR HIM.
- WAKE UP LITTLE BROTHER.
IT'S ANOTHER BEAUTIFUL DAY.
- ( snarls ) JUST TEN
MORE MINUTES.
- THEN THERE'S NO
OTHER WAY TO DO THIS.
I'LL HAVE TO GIVE YOU A
LITTLE GOOD MORNING KISS
TO GET YOUR BLOOD MOVING.
- ( gasps ) I'M UP. I'M UP.
LOOK AT ME, I'M UP.
- YES YOU ARE.
BUT WHY STOP NOW.
I'M HERE. DON'T I DESERVE
A GOOD MORNING KISS, AKI?
- GET AWAY. I DON'T EVER
NEED MY SISTER'S KISSES.
- WELL, THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
I'M ONLY TRYING TO KEEP
OUR FAMILY CLOSE.
HURRY AND GET DRESSED.
I'VE GOT YOUR BREAKFAST READY.
- YOU MADE BREAKFAST? OKAY,
I MUST BE DREAMING THEN.
- NOW I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU MEANT.
- MEAL REPLACEMENT DRINKS
ARE VERY GOOD FOR YOU.
I THOUGHT I'D BUY YOU THESE
BECAUSE THERE'S NEVER ENOUGH
TIME TO COOK IN THE MORNING.
- IT'S NO BACON, EGGS AND TOAST
BUT IT SURE BEATS THE HECK
OUT OF SALTWATER, RIGHT?
- HAVING ENOUGH CALORIES
IN YOUR BODY IS VITAL.
ESPECIALLY FIRST THING
IN THE MORNING.
HOWEVER, WHEN THE EVENING
BEGINS TO APPROACH,
EATING SOMETHING LIGHT
IS SMART BECAUSE...
- IT'S GOOD FOR YOUR HEALTH.
- THE AVERAGE MALE IS
SUPPOSED TO EAT
ABOUT 25 HUNDRED
CALORIES PER DAY.
I'VE COME TO THE DECISION
THAT IT WOULD BE BEST
TO GIVE YOU A THOUSAND
CALORIES FOR BREAKFAST,
A THOUSAND CALORIES FOR LUNCH
AND THE LAST FIVE
HUNDRED FOR DINNER.
EACH ONE OF THESE CANS
IS ONLY TWO HUNDRED CALORIES.
SO, I EXPECT YOU TO DRINK
FIVE FULL CANS FOR BREAKFAST.
- THAT'S LIKE WAY TOO MUCH.
- YOU GET THIRTEEN CANS A DAY.
IT'S REALLY JUST
A MATTER OF SIMPLE MATH.
YOU NEED TO STAY HEALTHY.
- THERE'S NO WAY I'LL BE
ABLE TO DRINK ALL THOSE.
- KNEW YOU'D SAY THAT.
SO, I BOUGHT ALL
THE FLAVORS THEY HAD
TO KEEP YOU FROM
GETTING BORED, AKI.
YOU'LL HAVE THE NORMAL ENTREE
WITH A SIDE OF CORN SOUP.
YOUR DRINK IS COFFEE AND YOU
CAN CHOOSE BETWEEN CAFE AU LAIT
OR CHOCOLATE FOR DESSERT.
- THINK YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT HERE, SIS.
- I'M SORRY. SILLY OLD ME.
I FORGOT, YOU'RE GROWING.
THEREFORE YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED MORE
THAN THE AVERAGE
MALE'S DAILY INTAKE.
- PLEASE DON'T.
CAN'T DRINK, ANYMORE.
- Fukuhara: A GOOD MORNING
IS STILL IN THE FAR DISTANCE.
- SHE COULD AT LEAST HAVE THROWN
A COUPLE OF GRANOLA BARS
INTO THE MIX.
- WHATCHA DOING MAN?
BIRD WATCHING?
- I'M TAKING MEASUREMENTS.
- MEASUREMENTS?
- I'M RECORDING THE STATS
ON BUST SIZES IN THIS ACADEMY.
A STANDARD A CUP IS TEN
CENTIMETERS FROM SUMMIT TO BASE.
ADD 2.5 CENTIMETERS
AND YOU'RE A, B, C OR D.
B, C, A.
A, B, D, B, B, C. B, A.
YES, A G. D, A, B, A.
- I THOUGHT THOSE
LAST TWO WERE D'S.
- SILICONE DOESN'T COUNT,
OF COURSE.
- WOW, THAT'S A GOOD EYE, MAN.
OH, LOOK AT THOSE
POOR LITTLE FELLAS.
DO YOU
STOP AT 'A' CUP?
- NOT AT ALL. AS WE GO FROM
SMALL TO NEARLY CONCAVE
BY TWO POINT FIVE CENTIMETERS
YOU GET YOUR DOUBLE A, TRIPLE A.
- I SEE. SO, IF IT'S COMPLETELY
FLAT LIKE THE ONE WE JUST SAW
IT COULD BE RATED
AS LOW AS FIVE A'S
OR EVEN GET A-BROKEN SPINE
AND CRUSHED PELVIS
WHICH DON'T GET ANY RATINGS.
( screams )
- FLAT CHESTED WOMEN OF THE
WORLD UNITE AND TAKE OVER.
- I'M SORRY, YUUJI, BUT
YOU CANNOT WATCH THAT.
- A LITTLE MORE.
THERE YOU GO.
( gasps )
- ( screams )
I GIVE UP.
- ( screaming )
- NOT THE MERRY-GO-ROUND.
- YOU GUYS ARE LIVELY, AS USUAL.
- ( groaning )
-WHY THE NURSE'S CLOTHES?
I GET IT.
YOU'RE HERE TO TAKE
CARE OF ME, AREN'T YOU?
- IT'S MY COSTUME
FOR THE DRAMA CLUB.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
FOR A MALE NURSE.
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
IT LOOKS LIKE IT WAS MADE
FOR A WOMAN WHEN I PUT IT ON.
- HOLD ON, THAT SHOULD
READ NURSE, NOT MALE NURSE.
- YOU SURE? I GUESS IT'S
POSSIBLE I MISREAD THE SCRIPT.
AND THAT WOULD EXPLAIN WHY
THE UNDERWEAR THEY
PROVIDED HAD LACE.
- WHAT?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY THE
TOP UNSNAPS IN THE FRONT.
- PATHETIC. THIS IS JUST SAD.
- YEAH, HOW EMBARRASSING.
- HUH?
- HMM?
- Hideyoshi: IT'S MY SISTER.
- PULL IT TOGETHER, HIDEYOSHI.
IF YOU ACT LIKE A TOTAL FREAK,
PEOPLE CAN'T HELP THINKING YOUR
SISTER IS ONE TOO.
- HEY, I'M NOT ACTING
LIKE A FREAK.
- DID I SAY FREAK?
WHAT I MEANT TO SAY
WAS MY STUPID BROTHER
IS A CLASS F DORK.
WHICH IS FINE, SINCE YOU
ACTUALLY LIKE THESE GUYS.
- HOW CAN YOU LIVE
WITH YOURSELVES?
YOU'RE AN EMBARRASSMENT.
- YOU SHOULD REALLY
WATCH WHAT YOU SAY.
- WHAT? YOU CAN'T
HANDLE THE TRUTH?
OR DID YOU GUYS
ALL GROW BRAINS OVERNIGHT?
- ( all gasp )
- Yuuko: THIS IS A SCHOOL.
STOP WASTING ALL YOUR TIME
FIGHTING AND PLAYING DRESS UP.
LET'S GO, REP.
- Fukuhara: MEANWHILE,
MIZUKI CONTINUED HER IMPORTANT
EXTRA-CURRICULAR RESEARCH.
- HOW TO DELIVER A LOVE LETTER.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE THE COURAGE
TO GIVE IT IN PERSON,
SIMPLY ASK
A CLOSE FRIEND TO HELP .
CLOSE FRIEND...
I GET IT. I THINK.
- HEY, MINAMI.
- WHAT IS IT, MIZUKI?
- I WAS HOPING YOU COULD
HELP ME WITH YOSHII.
- NO WAY. DON'T TELL ME
YOU ARE TOO?
- ( gasps ) YES WAY.
WHAT'D YOU WRITE?
- I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU
HAVE MY MISSING ONES?
- MAYBE IT'D WORK BETTER
IF I ASKED ONE OF YOSHII'S
CLOSE FRIENDS
INSTEAD OF ONE OF MINE.
- HEY, YUUJI.
- WHAT'S UP, HIMEJI?
- I WONDERED IF YOU
WOULD DO ME A FAVOR.
- FAVOR?
- I HAVE... A LOVE LETTER.
- WA... WAIT, SHOUKO.
HOW IS ANY OF THIS MY FAULT?
- LOOK AT THIS. YOU'RE MINE.
- ( yells ) A MARRIAGE
REGISTRATION?
NO, GET IT AWAY FROM ME.
I'LL NEVER SIGN IT.
YOU CAN'T MAKE ME.
( screams )
- IF YOU FIND IT HARD TO GIVE
THE LOVE LETTER ALL BY ITSELF,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO SPICE
IT UP WITH A GIFT.
HEY, YOSHII.
- WHAT IS IT, HIMEJI?
- IT'S NOTHING.
I REALLY WANTED TO GIVE
YOU A PRESENT
SO I BAKED SOMETHING
THIS MORNING.
IT'S COOKIES.
THEY'RE CHOCOLATE CHIP
WITH RAI...
OH, DEAR. WHERE'D HE GO?
YOSHII. WHERE ARE YOU?
YOSHII, I BAKED THESE COOKIES
ESPECIALLY FOR YOU.
- THIS IS MY HIDING PLACE.
- SHH.
- DON'T MAKE A SOUND. IF SHE
FINDS US, WE'RE BOTH DEAD.
- HAVING FUN PLAYING
YOUR STUPID GAMES, YOSHII?
- Both: IRON MAN.
- GOOD TIMING. NOW, YOU
CAN MOVE STUFF FOR ME.
- ( yells ) WHAT?
- IT'S ALSO OKAY TO SECRETLY
HIDE IT IN THEIR BAG
OR SLIP IT IN THEIR LOCKER.
IT WILL MAKE YOU
APPEAR SHY
AND THAT CAN INCREASE THE
ATTRACTION HE HAS TO YOU.
WHY DIDN'T I JUST DO THIS
AT THE VERY BEGINNING?
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING, MIZUKI?
- NOTHING.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- Both: IT'S PORN!
- YUUJI, WHERE ARE YOU?
- CLOSE ONE. IF SHE EVER MAKES
ME SIGN HER DEMON CONTRACT,
ALL WILL BE LOST.
- Kouta: MY WORK HERE
IS FINISHED.
THE COMPLETE GUIDE TO FUMIZUKI
BOOBS. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
- ( sighs ) NOT FAIR.
I DIDN'T EVEN GET A CHANCE
TO PUT IT IN HIS STUPID LOCKER.
WHAT SHOULD I DO NOW?
THIS ISN'T MY LETTER.
ALTHOUGH THESE
ARE KINDA PRETTY.
WAIT A MINUTE...
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY LOVE LETTER?
DID I DROP IT
SOMEWHERE EARLIER?
- ( grunting )
- THIS BLOWS, MAN. WHY AM I THE
ONLY ONE WHO HAS TO DO THIS?
- (screams )
AVATAR. OW.
- WHAT'S THIS?
IT LOOKS LIKE...
WAIT, THESE ARE THE QUESTIONS
FOR THE NEXT EXAM.
HEY, IF I STUDY THESE...
AND MEMORIZE ALL
THE QUESTIONS HERE,
EVEN I COULD GET A GOOD GRADE.
JUST KIDDING.
THAT WOULD BE CHEATING.
PEOPLE WILL TOTALLY KNOW
SOMETHING'S UP
IF I START GETTING GOOD
GRADES SUDDENLY.
( sighs )
- THE BOXES ARE
ALL JACKED UP.
CRAP, I'M BUSTED.
MAYBE I CAN SWAP THEM OUT WITH
THE BOXES FROM THE CLASSROOM.
I'M FINISHED WITH THE STUFF.
- SAY GOODBYE TO THOSE FOR NOW
BUT I'D START GETTING
READY TO SEE
THEM AGAIN ON THE UPCOMING
PREP TEST.
- Akihisa: YAY, TESTS.
- THERE IT IS.
THOUGHT I'D LOST IT.
THANK GOODNESS.
A DELIVERY SLIP?
HUH?
( screams )
- Announcer: BAKA AND TEST.
- WHAT'S WRONG, HIMEJI?
YOU LOOK REALLY BUMMED OUT.
- OH, IT'S NOTHING. I...
WELL... I...
- WHAT IS IT? IF YOU NEED ME
TO HELP YOU WITH SOMETHING
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ASK.
- YOSHII?
HELP ME.
- All: IT'S GONE.
- WHERE'S THAT STUPID MARRIAGE
PAPER? I LEFT IT RIGHT HERE.
- MY FUMIZUKI BOOBIES LIST THAT
I BUSTED MY BUTT ON, IS GONE.
- THAT COLLECTION OF PICTURES
TOOK ME YEARS TO BUILD UP.
- MY NURSE COSTUME, WHERE IS IT?
- HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN TO ME?
I LOCKED IT. I HAD SO MANY
SECURITY MEASURES.
WHOEVER DID THIS
MUST BE A PROFESSIONAL.
- SAW IRON MAN EARLIER.
PRETTY SURE HE TOOK SOME BOXES
DOWN TO THE SAFE.
- All: HOLY CRAP.
AND WHAT?
- YOU LOST
AN IMPORTANT ENVELOPE?
WAIT, DO YOU REMEMBER
WHERE YOU DROPPED IT?
- I THOUGHT I DID, BUT WHEN
I CHECKED I ONLY FOUND THIS.
- IT'S A SLIP FROM
THE BOX OF PREP TESTS.
THAT MUST MEAN WHEN
I DROPPED THE EXAM PAPERS...
IT MUST HAVE GOTTEN MIXED
IN WITH THEM.
NOW, THEY'RE
ALL LOCKED IN THE SAFE
AND I'M PRETTY SURE THEY
DO THAT TO KEEP US OUT.
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
- CALL FOR BACK-UP.
- WE'RE HERE TO HELP.
- THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS ARE HERE
FOR, YOU JUST GOTTA ASK.
- GOOD SUPPORT SYSTEMS
ARE FUNDAMENTAL.
- YUUJI, YOU GUYS.
- YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WITH SOMETHING IMPORTANT
TRAPPED BEHIND
SIX INCHES OF COLD STEEL.
- THIS MAY SEEM A TAD OVER
DRAMATIC FOR A COSTUME.
- MY BOOBY LIST
IS LIKE MY FAMILY.
- WE'RE GOING TO GET THEM
ALL BACK NO MATTER WHAT.
- YEAH, WE ARE.
- YOU GUYS, THANK YOU.
- WHEN WE HAVE ONE GOAL,
- All: NOTHING CAN STOP US.
- Fukuhara: THEIR GOALS WERE
ACTUALLY VERY DIFFERENT.
- WHO KNEW, THEY REALLY
DO HAVE BIG ROUND DOORS.
- Akihisa: A KEY AND A SECRET
CODE ARE NEEDED TO OPEN IT.
- I WISH IT WOULD OPEN WITH JUST
A KEY OR JUST A SECRET CODE.
- THAT'S LIKE TWO THINGS
AT THE SAME TIME.
- I SAY, WE GET AKI'S AVATAR
TO RIP THAT BIG ROUND DOOR OFF.
- I'LL BE THE ONLY ONE WHO GETS
KICKED OUT IF WE DO THAT.
- HOLD PLEASE. I HAVE
AN IDEA FORMING.
- All: WHAT DO WE DO?
- IN THE DRAMA CLUB'S
PRODUCTION OF TOP HAT BAT THIEF,
A THIEF DEVISED
THIS CLEVER DECEPTION
TO GAIN ACCESS TO A VAULT.
- All: WHOA.
- HOW DID HE DO IT?
- Hideyoshi: HE TOOK THE TIME
TO PREPARE A DECOY TREASURE.
THEN HE SHOWED THE
FAKE TO THE OWNER
AND TOLD THEM THAT HE STOLE IT.
THE OWNER COMPLETELY FREAKED OUT
AND OPENED THE SAFE TO CHECK IT.
WHEN HE OPENED THE SAFE,
HE STOLE THE TREASURE FOR REAL.
- THAT'S AMAZING.
- YOUR THIEF WAS SO SMART.
- CAN I BE THE ONE
WITH THE TOP HAT?
- OKAY. LET'S USE THE PLAN
FROM THE DRAMA CLUB.
- All: YEAH.
- ( laughs ) IRON MAN, WOULD
YOU LOOK AT THIS RIGHT HERE?
IT'S THE PREP TEST
FROM THE SAFE.
- WHY DON'T YOU GIVE ME THAT?
- WHAT?
- HMM.
- HOLD ON.
DON'T YOU WANT TO
GO OPEN THE SAFE
AND DOUBLE CHECK TO MAKE SURE?
- WHY SHOULD I HAVE TO DO THAT
WHEN YOU'RE STANDING RIGHT IN
FRONT OF ME, GENIUS?
- OH, YEAH. RIGHT...
WELL, CRAP.
IT DIDN'T WORK.
- WE DIDN'T HAVE ANY
PROBLEMS IN THE PLAY.
- I WONDER WHAT WAS DIFFERENT.
- COSTUMES?
- GUESS WE'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE
TO CRACK THIS BABY OURSELVES.
- I DON'T KNOW, MAN. A SECRET
CODE AND A STUPID KEY?
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- PERHAPS, I SHOULD OFFER
YOU MY ASSISTANCE.
- All: WHAT?
- WHO ARE YOU?
- Fukuhara: KYOUJI NEMOTO. HE
IS THE REP FOR YEAR 2, CLASS B.
- ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
OPEN A LITTLE SAFE.
I THINK WE CAN HANDLE THAT.
- YOU THINK?
- YOU'LL NOTICE THAT I SAID
"WE" THERE.
YOU GUYS GET THE KEY,
I'LL HANDLE THE CODE.
IT'LL BE A PIECE OF CAKE.
- All: REALLY?
- YEAH, I PROMISE.
WE HAVE TO COUNT ON OUR FRIENDS
IN TIMES OF NEED, RIGHT?
- NEMOTO IS TOTALLY AWESOME.
- WHERE IS IT?
- THAT'S THE ONE.
- THE KEY TO THE SAFE
IS OVER THERE?
- NO WAY. IT'S RIGHT
BEHIND IRON MAN?
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- THIS IS HOPELESS.
- OKAY, SOMEONE HAS TO
CREATE A DIVERSION FOR US.
- BY DOING WHAT?
- A REALLY HOT CHICK WOULD BE
THE PERFECT DISTRACTION FOR HIM.
WE'D HAVE NO PROBLEM
SNAGGING THE KEYS.
- HIDEYOSHI IS
THE PERFECT HOT CHICK.
- WHY MAKE ME DO IT?
- WE COULDN'T LET HIMEJI RISK
GOING IN THERE BY HERSELF
AND MINAMI DOESN'T HAVE
THE HOTNESS OF A BROKEN SPINE.
- ( screams )
- WHO DOESN'T HAVE
ANY HOTNESS?
- WHAT'S GOING ON OUT HERE?
- THIS IS OUR NEW ROUTINE
FOR DANCE CLASS.
IT'S CALLED ANGRY TROLL,
SHE CRACKS MY SPINE.
- ( screams )
- I COULD FEEL HIS
FINGERS IN MY BRAIN.
- YOUR SIGHT SHOULD
COME BACK SOON.
- BECAUSE OF YOUR PAIN,
I GOT THE KEY.
- GOOD JOB. IT WENT EXACTLY
AS WE PLANNED, KOUTA.
- SO, I WAS THE DECOY?
- ( beeps )
- OKAY. IT'S UNLOCKED.
- NOW, ALL WE NEED
IS THE SECRET CODE.
- TRY NOT TO TOUCH ANYTHING.
THESE ALARMS ARE VERY SENSITIVE
AND COULD STILL GO OFF.
- OKAY, SUPER THIEF.
- IT'S ALL YOU THEN.
- CHECK THIS OUT.
- All: NO WAY.
- A SWEET CAMERA.
- I RECORDED IRON
MAN OPENING IT.
- WE CAN SEE ALL THE NUMBERS
HE PRESSED.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT THE SECRET CODE THAT'S
JUST FOR TODAY.
- ( all gasp )
- Kouta: I FOUND IT.
- THEY'RE ALL HERE.
I'VE GOT MY PICTURES.
- YOU CAN'T GET ME NOW.
I BETTER FIND SOME
PLACE TO BURY THIS.
- HERE'S MY LETTER.
- I TOLD YOU WE'D
FIND IT, HIMEJI.
- YEAH. AND IT'S ALL
THANKS TO YOU.
THANK YOU. YOU SAVED ME, YOSHII.
- ( laughs )
- YES. MY NURSE
COSTUME'S INTACT.
- AND A BRA.
- FRONT HOOK.
IT WOULD POP RIGHT OPEN.
- ( both exclaim )
-I ALWAYS WONDERED
WHAT THOSE LOOKED LIKE.
- YOU SERIOUS?
MIZUKI, YOU'VE NEVER SEEN
A FRONT HOOK BRA BEFORE?
- STORES DON'T HAVE IT
IN MY SIZE.
APPARENTLY, CLASPS AREN'T
STRONG ENOUGH FOR ME.
- ( screams )
- THAT'S SO NOT TRUE. THOSE
THINGS ARE LIKE STEEL TRAPS.
FRONT HOOKS AREN'T JUST MADE
FOR THOSE FLAT CHESTS.
WHO SAID THAT?
- Both: STRONG ENOUGH?
- JACKPOT.
-WHAT'RE YOU DOING, NEMOTO?
- NOTHING. JUST
A LITTLE RESEARCH.
- DOESN'T LOOK LIKE RESEARCH.
- YOU'RE JUST A CHEATER.
- DON'T TRY TO GET RIGHTEOUS
WITH ME.
WE'RE IN THIS
TOGETHER NOW.
YOU HELPED BREAK
INTO THE SAFE
WHERE THE EXAMS WERE BEING
KEPT, REMEMBER?
IF THEY WERE TO
EVER FIND THAT OUT,
YOU'D BE IN AS MUCH
TROUBLE AS ME.
- BUT WE... DIDN'T WANT THIS.
WE JUST TRYING TO GET
OUR STUFF BACK.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK ANY
TEACHER'S GOING TO BELIEVE THAT?
HONESTLY, A COUPLE
OF MONTHS IN CLASS F
AND ALL READY YOU'RE NEARLY
AS STUPID AS THEM.
THIS WORLD ONLY CARES
ABOUT WINNING. THAT'S ALL.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW YOU GET THERE.
- YOU CAN'T... NO.
-THE ONLY THING I HAVE
TO DO IS ANSWER THESE
QUESTIONS CORRECTLY
THE DAY OF THE TEST.
IF I CAN DO THAT, THEN
I PROVE I'M SMART.
I STILL HAVE TO MEMORIZE
ALL THE RIGHT ANSWERS
EVEN IF I KNOW THE QUESTIONS.
- YOU'RE KIND OF A JERK.
- ONLY A MORON WOULD SKIP
THIS PERFECT OPPORTUNITY.
BUT THAT'S WHY
YOU GUYS ARE IDIOTS.
- ( all gasp )
- AM I REALLY HURTING ANYONE
BY IMPROVING MY SCORES
A LITTLE BIT?
AND WHO GETS ANYTHING
FROM A POINTLESS ACT OF
HONESTY, REALLY?
ANSWER THOSE QUESTIONS
CORRECTLY
AND MAYBE YOU COULD MAKE IT
OUT OF CLASS F.
I CAN SEE NOW THAT IT'S NOT ONLY
YOUR ACADEMIC PERFORMANCE
THAT'S DEFECTIVE BUT MOST LIKELY
YOUR VERY BRAINS THEMSELVES,
YOU WORTHLESS CLASS OF NITWITS.
- YOU'RE A NITWIT.
- HIMEJI...
- TRUE, CLASS F'S ACADEMIC
PERFORMANCE MAY NOT BE GOOD,
BUT...
BUT THEY'VE ALL
GOT KIND HEARTS.
THEY'RE CONSIDERATE. SO, I
GUESS MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
THEY'LL NEVER BE LIKE YOU.
- WOW, HIMEJI...
- YOU BETTER THINK TWICE BEFORE
YOU TALK ABOUT MY CLASS
THAT WAY AGAIN.
- ( chuckles ) HOW TOUCHING.
ANYWAY, DON'T FORGET
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER...
IF I'M CAUGHT THEN SO ARE YOU.
CALL IT THE ONE THING
WE HAVE IN COMMON, GET IT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU WERE DOING
IN HERE AND TO BE QUITE FRANK,
I DON'T CARE.
LET'S JUST PRETEND THIS WHOLE
THING NEVER EVEN HAPPENED.
WE WERE NEVER HERE.
TIME TO WISE UP,
SIMPLETONS.
HOPE YOU ALL HAVE
A WONDERFUL DAY.
- ( laughs )
- YUUJI, DO YOU REALLY THINK
WE'RE STUPID LIKE HE SAID?
- DUDE, WITHOUT A DOUBT.
WE'RE ALL EXTRA CRISPY
SUNDRIED BONEHEADS.
- YEAH, I GUESS.
- YOU'RE JUST MAD.
HE GOT US GOOD.
- I DON'T CARE IF SOMEONE
MAKES A FOOL OF ME. BUT...
TALKS SMACK ABOUT MY FRIENDS
AND THAT'S GOING TO PISS ME OFF.
- HIMEJI SHOULD TOTALLY BE
STUDYING WITH CLASS A RIGHT NOW
BUT SHE GOT STUCK
IN F BECAUSE OF LUCK.
IT ISN'T HER FAULT
SHE WAS THROWN IN
WITH THE LOSERS AND
REJECTS OF THE ACADEMY.
SO, THERE'S NO REASON
FOR HIM TO BE SUCH JERK.
WHY TRY TO MAKE HER
FEEL ASHAMED OF IT?
- IF YOU'RE THAT UPSET, GUESS
TWO OF US SHOULD DO SOMETHING.
- WHAT?
- IT'S ALMOST BEEN THREE
MONTHS SINCE OUR LOSS.
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO DECLARE WAR
AGAIN, SOUND GOOD?
WE GOT OUR BUTTS HANDED
TO US LAST TIME WE TRIED.
IT WAS ALL BECAUSE I DIDN'T
THINK THINGS THROUGH.
- I'M SORRY.
- YUUJI...
- BUT IT'S BECAUSE WE GOT SO
CLOSE THAT I KNOW WE CAN DO IT.
I'M NOT GOING TO SCREW UP
LIKE THAT EVER AGAIN.
I KNOW WE'RE READY THIS TIME.
LET'S GIVE IT ANOTHER SHOT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, MAN?
- ( chuckles ) IT'S PRETTY
OBVIOUS. I SAY WE DO IT.
THIS TIME WE'LL WIN.
THEN WE'LL SHOW THEM
THAT WE'RE NO ORDINARY IDIOTS.
LET'S GO. IT'S SUMMONER
TEST WAR TIME.
- YEAH. I SAY WE GO
AND EVEN THE SCORE.
- FIRST THING'S FIRST.
- I SHOULD GO GET
HIMEJI'S COOKIES.
- GOOD IDEA.
WHY SHOULD WE BE THE ONLY ONES
WHO RISK OUR LIVES ON HER FOOD?
- AWAKEN.
I'M SUMMONING
MY AVATAR... SUMMON.
- ( both laugh )
- Minami: WHAT'S THIS?
- IT LOOKS LIKE THE PREP TEST
FROM THE SAFE. THAT'S WEIRD.
- ( all gasps )
- ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
MEMORIZE THE QUESTIONS
AND I'LL GET A PERFECT SCORE.
- ( girls cheering )
- WOW, LOOK AT ALL
THOSE BRAINLESS GEEKS.
- THEY'LL NEVER PUT ANY OF THESE
QUESTIONS ON THE TEST NOW.
- SOMETHING TELLS ME WE MIGHT
KNOW THE GUYS BEHIND THIS.
- THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
- YOSHII!. YUUJI! WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- WE'RE SORRY.
- EXPLAIN RIGHT NOW.
WHY'D YOU TWO DO THIS?
- IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A PRANK.
- I GUESS WE WENT TOO FAR.
- DON'T GIVE ME THAT.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- Both: LOOK, SERIOUSLY.
WE'RE REALLY SORRY.
- HMM. YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO TELL ME THE TRUTH, HUH?
- WE DID. IT WAS A PRANK.
- OH, C'MON.
THE TWO OF YOU HAVE NEVER
APOLOGIZED LIKE THIS BEFORE.
OKAY THEN. YOU'RE BOTH GETTING
THE DEMON'S REMEDIAL CLASS.
- ( both screams )
- SUCK IT UP. I'M REWORKING
ALL MY LESSONS FOR YOU TWO.
THIS PRANK IS GONNA HURT.
- ( both chuckle )
- Both: YES, SIR.
- ( theme song playing )
- OH, WHAT'S THIS?
SOME GIRL GAVE ME COOKIES.
QUITE THE CHICK
MAGNET, AREN'T I?
THINK I BETTER EAT THEM BEFORE
YUUKA FINDS OUT I HAVE THESE.
- Fukuhara: THAT'S THE SOUND
OF HIS SOUL BEING TAKEN AWAY.
- QUESTION 11.
WHAT TACTIC DID THE GERMANS USE
DURING WORLD WAR II
THAT WAS A COMBINATION OF
BOMBING AND ARMORED DIVISIONS?
- LET'S GO FULL BLAST.
- PLEASE VALUE YOUR LIFE.
- NEXT TIME. RIVALS,
LOVE LETTERS, AND BLITZ TACTICS.
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.