When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
My name is Sanzenin Nagi.
Thirteen years old.
Sagittarius. Blood type: AB.
My birthstone is turquoise.
Oh no! Maria! My dear butler got taken away by bad people!
Okay then! I'll transform into Mask the Money and crush them with a duralumin case with 150 million yen in it!
I'm the soldier of love, courage, money, justice, and friendship, fortitude, and victory,
Mask the Money!
In the name of money, I will punish you!
It'll be about forty years until you pay everything back.
Well, the debt is  pretty large.
With a reasonable repayment plan,
I knew it would turn out to be something like this.
You can't find a loan company that lends
150 million yen without interest or mortgage,
and allows you to pay them back as you make money.
You should be grateful and not hold a grudge against us.
Oh please, I am grateful to you.
Your smile is twitching.
Hayate fears on account of the amount of money he borrowed.
His spring is still far away.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
My spring is still far away...
What? Only three people live in this mansion?
Yeah, since this is one of the smallest secondary houses we own,
so we don't need many attendants around.
Really? This is small?
But, if there aren't people around at all, it makes me nervous.
Over what?
Well, I'll be living here from now, right?
Even though it's so large, to be living under the same roof with a beautiful girl is...
I-Idiot! Don't put it that way.
Although it's "under the same roof",
it's not like we'll be sleeping in the same room.
But still, it makes me nervous.
Nervous?
You know how beautiful Maria-san is, right?
What do you mean by that?
Just so you know, if you touch Maria, I won't just kill you.
I'll put you under forty-eight murderous attacks and fifty-two submissions,
followed by turning you into minced meat through a roller.
Um... "touch her"?
With the new year approaching, this is how my new life began.
It's New Years Eve already.
This really was a hectic year.
The house I was supposed to have lived in was completely empty.
Didn't even feel like going out to search for my parents,
so I accepted Milady's kindness and decided to be a butler at this Sanzenin's mansion.
True, the amount of debt is large, but I must work hard not to get fired from this job!
So Maria-san, what exactly am I supposed to do?
I still don't have a clear image of the job description.
Let's see, simply put...
...be Nagi's pet.
P-Pet?
I'm only joking.
I think you'll gradually understand it,
so for the time being, could you go wake Nagi up?
Y-Yes!
So we have the study, piano room,
study hall, reading room, wardrobe,
Playstation room, Dreamcast room, N64 room.
Is there a reason to separate these?
It's here.
Good morning, Milady.
It's morning.
If you don't wake up, your breakfast is going to get cold.
Calm down. Calm down Hayate.
It can't be.
It has to be a 1/1 scale figure made by ******.
No, it's ***y! It has to be ***y!
It's must be their new **** for Playstation 5!
Man, ***y's technology sure is the best in the world. It's amazing.
Ah, Hayate?
You came to wake me up? Thank you.
By the way, why are you paralyzed?
Well, ah... behind you.
Oh, no wonder it was hot; Tama was sleeping with me.
Tama? You treat it like a cat with that huge body?
Hey, wake up Tama. Otherwise your breakfast is going to get away.
Stop, or else you'll become the breakfast.
M-Milady, hold on a second.
Idiot, I'm just getting up, so don't stare at me.
No! Well that's the correct reaction for the older audiences, but that's not what I'm concerned about right now!
Looks like you're really panicking over Tama.
Pathetic.
Utterly pathetic, Ayasaki Hayate!
Where are you coming out from?
Um, this person is?
Right, you haven't met him yet, have you?
My name is Klaus.
I am the head butler of this Sanzenin family.
Head butler? So you're my superior.
Wait, it's not the time for that!
Milady, it's dangerous!
Dangerous? What are you saying? It's only a cat.
No, that's a...
A tiger, I tell you. It's a tiger.
Why you... And I was about to finally comment on it!
Listen boy.
When Milady says it's a cat, it's a cat.
This is the White Tiger Cat, Tama.
You just said it's a "tiger" yourself!
You have to lock this dangerous and fearsome-looking beast inside a cage right away!
Looks like that long phrase just got on Tama's nerves.
Just to let you know, Tama is a stupid cat that hasn't taken a liking to anyone but Milady and Maria.
Anyone who bothers this stupid cat's mood will immediately become a sacrifice.
Which means, it hasn't taken a liking to you, either, has it?
Of... Of course you like me, right, Tama?
Tama, that's enough.
Geez, so noisy this early in the morning.
Thank you very much, Milady. You saved me.
Tama, if you're a Sanzenin's cat,
then you've got to understand what you're doing.
If you're going to play...
...do it outside.
Damn it, don't be so full of yourself!
Don't think this is the first time I've fought a beast.
I may not look like it, but I used to sneak into the safari park...
...to steal the lions' food to feed my parents some meat!
Now that's my Hayate.
Looks like he can play evenly with Tama, too.
I wonder about that.
How many butler candidates have lost to Tama so far?
Hayate won't lose against Tama!
Then when he loses, disqualify him as a butler and have him leave here.
Sure, fire him or whatever you want to do.
So if I can't beat a tiger barehanded, I'm back to being unemployed?
Besides, at the safari park, I was basically just running around.
Hayate!
Good luck!
Oh well. My life once ended that Christmas Day.
I have to do my best not to fall short of her expectations.
Here I go!
Um, Milady?
It's been bothering me for a while now, but...
The place where they're fighting is...
All right.
I hope the cyclamens have bloomed.
I give up! I give up, Tama!
There's no way a human can win against a tiger barehanded!
At least give me a knife!
A knife!
Tama?
What are you doing?
M-Maria-san.
I have told you many times you cannot play here since I am growing flowers here.
Did you do this?
Um...
Or, maybe the two up there set this up, saying that Hayate-kun is fired if he cannot win against Tama?
I will be up once I finish treating Hayate-kun, so could you wait with breakfast for a while?
Y-Yes, Sir.
Okay...
I am sorry; I will be sure to lecture them later.
I-It's fine.
But why do you have a tiger here?
A lot has happened.
He does not have anywhere to go.
But what about the zoo?
Yes, well... It's an embarrassing story, but...
Nagi found Tama alone, away from his mother in Africa, and nurtured him like a cat, and...
...he learned the luxurious life of eating only Matsuzaka beef or fatty tuna and receiving tri-weekly massages.
So not only the wild, but he will not even stand the life in the zoo.
But he never hurts Nagi,
and if it is for Nagi, he fights to the death.
He seems to have a good understanding of what would have happened if he had not met Nagi.
"If he had not met Nagi."
I see, so you're the same as me.
Don't treat me the same as you, you failure at life! Idiot!
What's with that impoverished look on your face?
Go get run over by a Mars trooper and die, you fool.
Oh, and don't tell the others that I can speak, got it?
I-I see, so rich people's pets can talk.
Tama was nurtured with much love,
so he learned how to speak the human language.
But Hayate is the only person to know that fact.
Thin konnyaku.
Intruder!
Anyway, I'm against taking him in as butler!
I see.
Is it this mustache that's speaking nonsense?
Is it this mustache, Klaus?
I decided to hire him to thank him for saving me.
I promised that I would choose a replacement for Himegami.
Besides, you're out of your mind to want to hire a poor-looking guy like him!
Y-Yes, he has a poor man's face,
but that could calm people down.
Hayate is one of those that eases your heart!
If you want a moment of ease in your heart,
get a hamster or something.
Unfortunately, hamsters are too soothing.
Hayate's poorness is what I like.
Hiring a boy who's so pathetic and looks like he'll never have any luck with money for the rest of his life...
...will only make the people around him poor, too!
They both do not mean what they are saying to be taken badly.
I know.
We don't know when you'll get involved in a kidnapping case like the other day,
so we can't hire anyone who doesn't have the will to fight for the master by risking their own life.
Fight for the master by risking their own life?
Strength, you ask? Then there's nothing to worry about.
True, Hayate-kun's body is sturdier than most others.
He was able to play with Tama, after all.
That's not all.
So you know, every time Hayate transforms, his power level increases dramatically.
And Hayate still has two more transformations left in him.
Do you understand what I mean by this?
There is no such thing as that.
There isn't?
Are you sure?
I'm not ****za.
So even if you give me that look...
If you see a problem with Hayate-kun's strength or potential, how about testing him?
A test?
Yes.
If he truly can protect Milady, then I am sure he can swim through a boiling pool of tar.
True. An applicable man should be able to fall from two thousand meters above ground and be fine.
Um, hello?
Okay, I accept that challenge.
Um, I don't have a say in this?
Then please hold on for a while.
I'll get the test ready right away.
Sure. Bring guns, arrows, or whatever you want!
I'm not really sure what this test is about, but is it safe?
In various ways.
Don't worry.
I'm sure you'll manage.
Um, Maria-san. Does Milady have high hopes for me?
High hopes?
She tends to be shy around people she doesn't know and doesn't show expressions to others often.
Especially after Himegami-kun left, she hasn't smiled much.
So it's been a while to see her so energetic.
She must have been really happy that you saved her.
I sure do have the "for the sake of money" portion in my heart,
but if she has high hopes on me,
then I want to be equal to her hopes.
Are you ready?
This is the exam to test your applicability.
This is...
Um, this is?
Nursing Robot 8, made by one of the companies under Sanzenin's authorities!
I've been expecting you, Ayasaki Hayate-san.
You're not about to tell me to fight this, are you?
Don't be ridiculous. That's a nursing robot.
In other words, the ultimate butler made to serve its master!
Using the regular household material here,
I will have you and 8 fight and see who's a better butler.
Milady?
It's a very ugly robot.
But this is the nursing robot with the world's latest technology.
Latest technology?
This?
Wouldn't you want to die if you found yourself being taken care of by an ugly robot like this?
Oh please...
Anyways, Hayate wouldn't lose a robot that won't transform or combine.
Right?
Ah...
I-If you want to see transformations or combining that badly...
...I'll transform you !
Damn, I missed.
What short-tempered latest technology.
It's no time to make that kind of comment!
Please stop it already!
Once I'm in motion, no one can stop my hot pistons.
You stay quiet!
Klaus-san?
To stop it, you need to open the panel
in the back and type in the password, 1192...
Hayate-kun! It'll stop if you break it!
Hey!
So it does come to that.
Hayate!
That's right; I have to protect Milady.
Since I'm going to become her butler.
I'm going to get serious now.
Stay behind, please, Milady.
Is he really made for nursing?
Launch!
I'm sure it's necessary equipment for women living alone.
Like a countermeasure against stalkers.
Sounds really fishy.
Brat, don't think you can keep running away from me.
Hayate!
What?
Hey, that's the water pipe!
I see. Machines are weak against water.
And who's doing the clean-up?
Who cares about water.
Japan's waterproofing treatment is the best in the world!
Now!
Th-This is...
You got it right. Pure silver knives that are more susceptible to conductive electricity than stainless steel.
And right below you is soaked wool carpetting.
And here's the 100V electricity!
Stop, if you use that in this situation, you'll get electrocuted, too.
I'm sure I would.
But apparently, protecting the master even at the cost of your own is a butler's job.
Hayate.
No matter how much you act cool,
you'll be poor for the rest of your life.
Buster Cholerae!!
W-Why Cholerae?
And it's done!
But nobody copy this move, okay?
That was surprisingly fast.
You still have problems with Hayate?
Fine. We'll hire him until we find a better one.
With the sound of the bell,
the new year is about to come to Japan.
Goodbye, last year. Hello, new year.
I hope the best New Year to you all.
You're awake! I was worried about you.
Milady.
What happened with my test?
Of course, you passed.
Thank goodness.
But I turned that room into a mess.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
There are enough rooms here.
But there isn't a replacement for you.
Milady.
Well, so, you know... I was happy that you protected me.
So, um...
K-Keep-
Keep up the good work, Hayate!
Yes. You can count on me, Milady.
There are still many problems ahead, but looks like he will do fine here.
And that day, I made a promise.
That I would protect Milady even at the cost of my life.
Hey, you, are you listening?
What?
It's your fault for talking for three episodes.
Look, even the sakura petals are starting to fall.
So what?!
Let's pick up where we left off!
Up I go.
Prepare yourself!
This long battle sequence that started in episode one will finally come to an end!
Hayate!
Die!
And this is how the boy became a legend. No, I mean a butler.
Next week, he'll fight against school!
You're not a student of Hakuou, are you?
Who are you?
Um, I'm...
Don't lie to me!
I haven't said anything, yet.
Did Hayate-kun get caught up in another mess?
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
First Mission. This is Snake. No One's Responding.
Ayasaki-kun, if you don't become a little bit more selfish,
you won't catch your happiness.
Have you ever felt the cosmos around you?