Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Now, it's time to begin.
Let's go!
Ngaah~
Hurry up and start already!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
nayaminbou koutetsubou
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
BON-BON ouendan
Let's get! cheriipai
RAN-RAN kangeikai
Look up! senseishon
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
motteike!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
getsuyoubi na no ni!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
It's been a while since I last wore my uniform.
Ah, it's Kona-chan.
Kona-chan, good morning!
Ah, Kagami-san, Tsukasa-san.
A very good morning to you.
Oh my, Tsukasa-san...
Your ribbon is not quite straight.
Thank you.
Ew.
Kona-chan, what happened to you all of a sudden?
Well...
I've been addicted to Marimite lately.
Marimite?
Are you a kid?
Image
You know,
don't go around dressing like them, too.
Um, is that cosplay?
Even I wouldn't go that far.
You'd better not.
I do enough of that at my part-time job.
Oh yeah, you work at a place that does that.
But if Kona-chan dressed up like a proper lady...
It's so weird that I can't even imagine it.
Lately, baseball games going to extra innings have really gotten out of hand.
Why do the late-night anime viewers have to be the ones that get shafted?
If you want to watch anime that much,
why don't you just get cable?
Don't they have dedicated channels for that stuff?
Believe me, if I could have,
I already would have...
But the cable TV guy said that...
...he couldn't run a cable to my house...
Yuki-chan, good morning.
Good morning, Tsukasa-san.
You look bummed-out... Did something happen?
Well, I went to get my tooth looked at, but...
Oh, you went to the dentist?
Good for you!
Why is it that when you go to the dentist once, you have to keep coming back for so many follow-ups?
Ah, I totally understand!
I've never gone to a dentist fewer than two times per occasion!
Miyuki-san, how do you do?
Ah, Konata-san, how are you?
Have you been doing well?
Splendid, thank you.
I'm glad to see you are doing well yourself, Konata-san.
Whoa, that's Yuki-chan for you.
Honorific dialogue doesn't seem to perturb Miyuki-chan at all.
Or rather, she doesn't find Kona-chan's words odd at all.
I've never seen anyone greet people with "how do you do".
Eh?
Is that so?
At the all-girls high school to which my friend goes,
they greet each other like this on a regular basis.
A high school for true upper-class ladies is quite different, wouldn't you say?
How genteel of them.
Kuroi told me to collect all the summer vacation homework.
Hand it in.
How genteel of you, Sebastian.
S-Sebastian?
A butler just has to be called "Sebastian".
Yeah, I have that image, too.
Say something funny, Sebastian.
N-No way!
I know summer vacation has just ended, but you don't have time to space out!
You should think about your future and focus on your studies.
Schedule for Second Semester
Our future... Like what we'll be doing...
I guess high school is just one stop along the way.
You haven't really thought about the future, have you?
Huh!?
How rude!
Well, you even chose humanities just so you could be in the same class as us.
Tsu-Tsukasa!
You told them!
Ah, sowwy.
And to her, of all the people!
C'mon, just be honest with yourself.
You just don't want to be alone, right?
There, there.
S-Shut up!
Yahoo!
I came over again!
Ah, Nee-san.
I did my summer homework like you told me to...
And filled in all the blanks with what looked like the answers...
And now, she's making me redo it all!
Help me!
U-Uh, sure.
But...
If you ask me, you might have to turn it in again...
You weaseled out of it...
My summer vacation doesn't get extended, but my homework does...
Maybe I should ask Kagami for her notes.
The cicadas sound soothing, just like a lullaby.
I see... Extra innings pushed it back.
Well, I guess that's helpful sometimes.
The recording times are off, too!
Huh?
Yuki-chan, where are your glasses?
I accidentally broke them this morning.
I forgot I put them on my chair...
And then I accidentally...
I apologize but, do you think I can copy your notes for today?
Sure.
You have that "klutzy" look down pat.
Konata's Notes
Konata-san, your writing is interesting.
Bad Handwriting
that can't be read
Tsukasa's Notes
Tsukasa-san, fighting!
So detailed that
she didn't get
everything down
Those guys really are useless.
Here.
Thank you very much.
It's a good thing we had the same teacher.
Yes, but...
Can you keep this a secret?
I wouldn't want to hurt their feelings.
I'm starving!
Yuki-chan, let's have lunch!
Ah, Tsukasa-san, Konata-san, thank you for your notes.
No need to thank me.
I never thought I would ever loan Yuki-chan my notes.
Well, I doubt you ever will again.
U-Um, is there something on my face?
In games, when the "glasses" character comes to school without them...
They suddenly become popular.
I guess that doesn't actually happen.
I-I don't think it does, unfortunately.
Choco cornets look kind of like drills.
Drills?
S-Speaking of which,
didn't we have a discussion about which side of a choco cornet is the head?
The skinny side kind of looked like the bottom.
Hmm...
Now that I look at it, the fat side looks like the butt.
Butt?
Whoa...
That's some junk in the trunk.
Not to mention the layered fat rolls on the stomach.
When you gain weight on the lower half,
isn't it troubling when you try to buy skirts and stuff?
Yep, yep.
If you try to get one that fits your waist, then your hips don't fit.
But if you get one that fits your hips, it fits loosely around your waist.
Having no other choice, you buy the one with the loose-fitting waist.
And when you're walking around, it spins around and around.
Yeah, yeah.
A body with a layered stomach, cornet-type.
If you turn it on this side,
it becomes a lazily sleeping body, gorone-type.
When you turn it back up, cornet-type.
I don't even know where I'm supposed to laugh.
Onee-chan, didn't you go on a diet to lose the weight you gained during summer?
Ah, I lost weight but my waist and hips are still the same.
But Kagami, I can clearly see the progress of your diet.
Really?
Yep, so clearly that I could grab it.
When you go on a diet, you tend to first lose weight in the areas you really don't want to...
That's enough!
Say no more!
When you read a sentence, always keep in mind what the overall message is,
and what the author is trying to convey to his audience.
I see how it is...
You know, I heard that people with poor vision tend to glare a lot and scare other people.
But, I think that depends on the person.
Hey, you!
When you said "depends on the person",
you looked my way, didn't you?
I've also heard that you look prettier when you make your eyes thinner.
It makes your eyes look more luscious...
Hey, we don't have to do it!
Late!
What the heck is Konata doing!?
Ah, she's here!
Sorry, I'm late.
Way late!
You're always complaining about how extra innings are too long, and now you're late?
Well, you know, there have been so many games going to extra innings that...
...I think I caught it.
It's not contagious.
So why are you late?
Overslept?
No, no, I'm not a kid.
Then, give me an adult reason why you're late.
Well, you see...
After I readied-up, I had quite a bit of spare time.
So to kill time, I played some games,
but then I couldn't find a good saving point...
You're the worst...
Worse than a kid.
Speaking of which,
there are a lot of festivals like the culture and sports festivals in the second semester.
Not to mention that we have tests as well.
Kona-chan, you're so athletic that you can do well in the sports festival.
I don't like sports festivals because they tire me.
I've never seen someone athletic who hates manual labor this much.
I wonder what our class is doing for the culture festival...
Well, it's not like there is really anything to do.
It's pretty hard to decide these things unless someone is really motivated to do something.
And the one that comes up with suggestions is responsible for most of the work, so no one steps up.
You have to stay after class and prepare.
You won't make it home in time to watch evening anime.
I knew you were going to say that.
I'm in charge of dinner tonight,
so I have to go shopping on the way home.
What are you going to make?
Everyone's favorite chicken curry!
My family loves chicken.
Curry, huh...
That sounds good.
You know, they say curry tastes better when you let it sit overnight.
I've heard that, too.
Maybe I'll make a little extra and bring some to class for lunch tomorrow.
I know I'll have leftovers, anyway.
Hi, this is the Hiiragi residence.
Ah, Tsukasa?
Ah, Kona-chan!
What is it this early in the morning?
You know that curry...
The curry?
The curry I made yesterday...
I let it sit overnight and now it's spoiled.
Really?
No way.
Really.
Why?
Curry shouldn't go bad overnight.
You'd think so...
Did you put something weird in it?
I didn't, but...
There was mold all over it this morning.
A cornet again today?
They taste good so I don't really mind.
If that's okay with you...
You know, I just realized this,
but there are times when Tsukasa and Kagami's lunches are really elaborate.
Made Properly
〇 Mini Hamburger Patties
〇 Fried Eggs
〇 Bacon Sauté with
broad beans and onions
〇 Salted Asparagus and Carrots
And other times, they can be rather simple.
Made Frugally
〇 Grilled Salmon
〇 Okra
(Just boiled and sliced)
〇 Pickled Vegetables
And nothing else...
There's a clear distinction.
W-Well, Tsukasa and I take turns in making lunch,
and I'm not that good with household chores,
so my lunch ends up being simple.
Well, sorry for that being the case!
Oh boy
Kagami, are you the type that blows pots up when you try to cook?
I don't think people like that exist.
Yuki-chan, like always, your lunches look really good.
Not really...
I just stuffed in yesterday's leftovers.
Miyuki-san's dinner is...
This extravagant?
These are "leftovers"?
Um, what's inside these eggs?
Ah, I had some leftover eel last night, so I tried putting it in.
Do you ever have leftover eel?
The only leftovers ever in our house are moldy curry.
I never considered your house to be "normal".
Good morning.
Morning.
Yo!
Look, look!
My parents got me a cell phone!
Good for you.
I happened to score highly on the standardized tests.
Give me your number and I'll give you mine in return.
What was my number again?
Give me a second, okay?
Konata, you had a cell phone?
Yep, but I usually forget it at home.
That's because the only person who calls me is my dad.
Then what's the point of you having a cell phone?
Really?
Keroro!
Whoa.
Isn't it cute?
They bought it along with my cell phone.
Speaking of which, there's a girl in our class who has a bunch of straps.
When she weighed them, the straps alone came to a total of 800 grams.
That much?
That sounds heavy.
When she took her straps off, her pain in the shoulder went away.
That sounds like too much of a workout just to talk to someone on the phone.
Don't cell phones excite you because you never know when someone will call you?
Really?
I hope someone calls me soon.
Why would you get so excited over a cell phone, nowadays?
By the way, did you figure out your number?
U-Um, not yet!
In England, there was a great civil war between the Lancastrians and Yorkists.
The two houses wore red and white roses, respectively, when they fought.
Thus, people refer to this war as the "War of Roses".
It lasted from 1455 to 1485.
This...
Ah!
Me?
That's my cell phone!
I finally got a call!
Who is this?
Okay, I'm taking this.
Come get it in my office after school.
I'm so glad that she gave it back to me.
Who would've thought you'd get spam this early?
Ah, Dad?
Yeah, I'm still at school.
I'm late because I was talking to Miyuki and Konata.
Yep, I'm fine.
I'll be going home soon.
See you.
This is what happens when I'm a little late.
Ah.
Yes?
Ah, Dad?
Yep, still at school.
I'm with Kona-chan and everyone right now.
Yep.
Shouldn't you only have to call one daughter?
It's natural for dads to be worried about their daughters.
Don't you get a lot of spam mail lately?
If you make your address something unusual, you can avoid that.
That's what I did.
Something unusual?
Like how?
My address is in romaji...
And it's superglassesgurlzlove@~
At first I wanted to pick maids or shrine maidens, but those are too popular so-
W-Wait a sec!
I get it, so please don't say stuff like that out in public.
This conversation is even more disturbing than all the spam mail.
Morning.
Yo!
What's the matter, Tsukasa?
My cell phone... My cell phone...
She left it in her pocket and...
It's gone to a better place, huh?
I wonder if they'll buy me another one?
So this guy was okay?
What a tough little dude...
So that text message last night...
The one that said, "Kagami said you didn't give her notebook back yet."
Was that the last one you sent?
Yeah, it was.
Did you happen to respond?
Um, well...
You probably don't respond to mails you get right away, do you?
Well, I usually don't reply to people I see everyday.
You should return text messages with text messages.
I see you guys everyday so I thought it was unnecessary.
You're going to lose your friends.
Now, now...
It's not that big of a deal...
Don't decide that on your own!
Ah, she never returned my notes.
Tsukasa, I'm coming in.
Ah, Onee-chan!
W-What happened to you?
I was so moved by the manga I borrowed from Kona-chan that I started crying.
Good morning!
Kona-chan, thanks for the manga.
It was really interesting.
It was so ridiculous that it made you want to laugh, huh?
Eh?
I-I cried because I was so touched.
I can't believe they're talking about the same manga with such wildly different response.
If you cry you're, like, Tsukasa and if you laugh you're, like, me.
I'm not going to read it.
I don't want to be categorized like that.
I want to see your reaction, Onee-chan.
Is it such a crime to want to know more about your friends?
Then, did you cry or laugh during Attack No.1?
Cried.
Laughed.
Then, what's your favorite manga?
Keroro Gunso!
These two...
I'm not sure if they're similar or not.
Kona-chan, aren't you going to join the manga research club?
You like manga and the ilk.
Well, I wouldn't mind joining...
And I hear the meeting times are flexible as well.
*draw draw* *draw draw*
Were you even trying when you drew this?
Yep.
What exactly did you try to draw, Konata-san?
This is Tsukasa.
This is me?
This is Miyuki-san.
Well, giving you a huge margin of error, I guess I can see it.
This is Kagami.
Oh... So I breathe fire now, huh?
Oh my...
Kagami-san, you're just the person I imagined you to be.
How terrifying.
I said stop that already!
Ah, there's a new volume of Full Metal.
Oh yeah, it's coming out.
I'm stopping by Gamers, do you want to come?
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna go to the local bookstore.
And there are some things of which I have to take care.
This is the part where you and I are supposed to go together and deepen our friendship.
What's up with you today?
I don't get you at all.
Besides, the word "friendship" doesn't fit you.
As a symbol of our friendship, I wanted your purchase points.
So this is your "friendship", huh?
I can almost
get the item I want
Wait for me just a little more...
How cheap.
It's so quiet...
Is she mad at me for mixing up my twintail ribbons with sunflowers?
Me?
Yes?
What, me!?
To Akira-sama?
Is that okay?
Understood.
Um...
Um, it's already started...
Crap, I have to do something before the channel changes!
O-Oha-lucky!
Or, I tried saying that, but...
Lucky Channel has started once again this week!
Shiraishi Minoru here.
Since Akira-sama is in a foul mood...
Saying your name before that of Kogami Akira...
You don't understand anything about the hierarchy, do you?
T-That's not what I...
You've been using those twintails quite a bit lately, haven't you?
U-Using them?
Don't get too full of yourself!
I'm terribly sorry!
Besides, in the "Let's make Akira look prettier" plan, everyone was hoping to see my twintails, right?
So what is this?
It's as you say.
I'm going with twin drills now.
T-Twin drills?
Don't underestimate the Getter's speed.
Number two. The age of twintails is over.
The next fad is: twin drills!
Konata said so in episode 2,
"Drills are every man's ultimate fantasy."
Fantasy, is it?
Well then everyone, we'll continue on with the radio and homepage.
L-Look forward to next time.
Bye-bii.
You know...
Yes?
Those twintails.
Oh, the ones I have?
Yes.
The ones you did in real life.
They had sunflowers on them, right?
Indeed, they did.
I think I've seen that somewhere.
Y-You don't mean...
How many years back was that?
It was one of my...
Ew! Disgusting!
Wow, I was so nervous.
It was really cute, I enjoyed it.
Don't you get nervous singing your first song of the day?
You don't know if you can sing it right.
Next is Miyuki's turn.
I want her to sing something sentimental.
Why?
Ah, may I have the mic?
Yep, good luck.
Um, I'm not really used to this sort of thing...
So please bear with me.
Don't worry about it.
Good luck!
Oh!
How macho.
I see.
Tying in with the other Miyuki...
Kaze no naka no subaru
風の中のすばる
In the winds of the Pleiades.
Even her singing is macho.
Suna no naka no ginga
砂の中の銀河
In the dust of the Milky Way.
A new form of moé.
Yuki-chan, you're so cool
Minna doko e itta miokurareru koto mo naku
みんな何処へ行った　見送られることもなく
Where did everyone go,
with no one to say goodbye?
Sougen no PEGASUS
草原のペガサス
In the savannah of Pegasus.
Machikado no VENUS
街角のヴィーナス
On the street corner of Venus.
Minna doko e itta mimamorareru koto mo naku
みんな何処へ行った　見守られることもなく
Where did everyone go, without being watched over?
Chijou ni aru hoshi wo dare mo oboeteinai
地上にある星を誰も覚えていない
No one remembered the stars of Earth.
Hito wa sora bakari miteru
人は空ばかり見てる
People see nothing but the sky.
Preview
And next week on Lucky Star:
Tsukasa here. Wait, I'm out of time?!
Next week: "Even without me, you can have a blast"
「Even without me,
you can have a blast」
Look forward to it!