We'll catch everyone's hearts!
Wh-What is this light?!
All the Heart Seeds we've gathered are glowing!
So that must mean...
Something amazing is going to happen!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Professor Sabark, King Dune
has gotten in contact with us.
What?
His patience has finally run out, then...
King Dune, how may I help you?
Sa...rk?
Is that... Sabark?
Yes, sir.
It seems we have a pretty poor signal.
Worry not, I can hear your voice.
Though I loathe to be blunt,
what progress has been made with the desertification of Earth and humanity?
Well, on that front, due to the appearance of new Precure...
we have fallen surprisingly behind schedule.
Sabark!
Did you think I was going to strip you of your command?
Please don't joke, Your Highness.
As the fairies who protect the Great Heart Tree managed to escape, it was an inevitable turn of events.
I'm not blaming you.
I actually have some useful information for you.
The reason that I, Dune, was defeated by Cure Flower
may indeed have been partially due to her own strength.
However, I am certain that she managed to
obtain something which fortified her powers.
I believe that was the major factor in my downfall.
What was it she obtained, then?
If I knew, it would not have caused such problems.
Regardless, we must obtain it, no matter the cost.
If we can destroy it or make it our own, we have little to fear from the Precure.
I am certain there must be a lead at the Great Heart Tree.
So I ask you to investigate for me.
Of course, sir.
The Third Fairy!
Potpourri's an Adorable Little Baby!
Y-Y-You want me to be a model?!
What's going on, Momo?
Well, the thing is, the model who always plays the role of my little sister when I do shoots for this magazine
had to pull out suddenly,
and if we don't do the shoot tomorrow,
we won't make it in time for publication.
So please fill in for her!
B-But, there's no way I'd...
Hey, wait! If you want someone to play the little sister role, why not just ask, you know, your actual little sister!
If I was going to ask you, I
would've done so from the start.
But Tsubomi's physique is pretty much exactly the same as that model's.
Well, if that's the reason, then fine...
Come on, Tsubomi. I'll tag along, so just help her out, okay?
I-I can't do it! There's no way I could model...
Tsubomi, didn't you say you wanted to change yourself?!
This'd be a really good chance!
B-B-But...
Okay, it's settled! A round of applause, everyone!
Huh? You want me to get inshide?
The Great Heart Tree...
Seek it out, Dark Precure.
If King Dune learns of this, we shall not get off lightly.
Fear not, Professor Sabark.
The Great Heart Tree is still nearby.
You mushtn't hurt the Great Heart Tree!
I didn't expect another fairy...
Tsubomi! You're really stiff.
Can't you try and loosen up a little?
I-It's not something I can do just because you ask me to.
Tsubomi!
That's nice!
This looks great.
Tsubomi, give us a smile! A smile!
Tsubomi, once we've finished shooting, let's go to a sweets buffet, okay?
Huh? Really?!
Nice!
That's what we're after, Tsubomi!
Right, okay!
Let's go to the next set!
Karin!
Karin, please wait!
Momo?
Karin? Is she...
Yeah.
I was supposed to model with her today.
I did not imagine the Great Heart
Tree would give rise to a new fairy.
Could that fairy be the lead that King Dune was referring to?
Perhaps. Capture it.
Shtop it! I can't shtop their attacks anymore!
Huh? "Run while you shtill can?"
If you shay sho!
It vanished...
Wait.
It most likely fled to join the other fairies.
Let's leave Sasorina and the others to hunt them down.
For now, focus on finding the Great Heart Tree.
Where is Sasorina?
She went to torment the Precure.
Acting on her own again...
Well, it matters not. A third fairy has appeared.
What did you say?!
I imagine it will attempt to rendezvous with the other fairies and the Precure.
So I entrust you two with capturing it and bringing it back to me alive.
Yes, sir.
That crying sounds like...
Could it be...
What's the matter?
We'll be back soon, okay?
What's with her? What's with her?!
Just going ahead and replacing me like that!
Kurumi Momoka's been planning this from the start!
What's with this "charismatic model" crap?!
Stop, stop!
Huh?
Karin, we're trying to get a natural-looking scene of two sisters just out having fun.
Can you stop staring right at the camera?
Huh? But 45 degrees to the right helps capture my best side.
Can't we change the positioning around?
You really need to start listening to what you're told, Karin.
Momoka's meant to be the star of this shoot, after all.
Sorry, but I'm feeling a little tired. Do you mind if we take a break?
S-Sure...
Karin, come with me.
Take a seat, Karin.
I've been meaning to tell you this for a while, but you really do try to draw too much attention to yourself.
Huh? Really?
What's important for us models is to attempt to convey the intent of the designers
and to place ourselves in the mindset of the readers who'll want the clothes we model.
Karin?
Your father's a really famous photographer,
and your mother's a former charismatic model!
Someone like you who's only famous because of her parents would never understand how I feel!
I'm going home!
Karin!
I see. So that's why Karin pulled out...
She's totally wrong! You didn't get where
you were because of who your parents are!
You were scouted in the first place,
and it's because you've worked so hard that you've gotten to where you are now, right, Momo?
Thank you, Erika.
I just thought that she had real potential,
so I wanted to give her some advice to help her along.
It's not just me.
The staff want Karin to come back too.
Why was she so damn condescending?
Now, whose Flower of the Heart shall I steal for my Desertrian today?
I've found a sad little girl!
Whoa! A weirdo!
You sure are rude, calling me a weirdo.
The Flower of your Heart is wilting pretty nicely.
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
It's Sasorina!
Now then, what kind of Desertrian should I make today?
This'll be perfect...
It's your cue, Desertrian!
Mannequin!
Desertrian, run wild and lure those Precure out!
I won't forgive you, Kurumi Momoka!
Wait, what?!
Hey, where do you think you're going?!
Come back here this instant!
We have to let Erika and Tsubomi know!
Wh-What the heck is that?!
P-Please halt!
Out of my way!
Mannequin!
We've got trouble!
There's this giant monster heading straight toward us!
Erika?!
Just come over here for a sec, okay?
That's...
Karin's Flower of the Heart is the one that was stolen by Sasorina!
Tsubomi, let's go!
Right!
Go forth, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
So there you are, Momoka!
You can't run from me!
Get away from here, quickly!
So you finally decided to show up, Precures!
Desertrian, get them!
Get out of my way!
We won't!
Momo... I mean, Kurumi Momoka hasn't gotten this far as a model just because of who her parents were!
Momoka has earned her place as a
charismatic model with her own hands!
Shut up!
How can you be so dense?!
Momoka thinks really highly of you, Karin!
What do you think you're doing?!
Get up off your butt up already!
Let's defeat it while we have the chance and get the Flower of her Heart back!
All right!
Kumojacky? Kobraja? What are you guys doing here?!
Pure coincidence, I'm afraid.
We've been hunting for the new fairy.
But we saw you fighting, so we
thought we'd come lend you a hand.
Desertrian!
Mannequin!
All right! That's the way!
Let's finish them off!
Big Bang Kumojacky Special!
I won't let you hurt the Precuresh!
What?!
My beautiful face, ruined!
I won't forget this!
I've found you at lasht!
Wait, who are you?
You're so cute!
Because we gathered so many Heart Seeds and restored the Great Heart Tree, a new fairy has been born from it.
What's your name?
My name ish Potpourri!
You're so cute!
Hey, stop that!
Why are you just ignoring us?!
And you! What do you think you're doing?! Get them!
Mannequin!
You're just using Karin's vulnerable, broken heart for your own ends,
and I've had it up to here with this!
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
I'll let you off with this just this once!
Karin!
What happened?!
We found her unconscious outside!
Were you attacked by that monster?
Are you hurt?
Momoka's been worried sick about you, you know?!
What?
That's right!
Momoka was totally against replacing you for today's shoot until the very last moment!
Then what the Precures were
saying in my dream was true...
We all believed you'd come back eventually.
Momoka...
I'm...
I'm so sorry!
I know.
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
In the language of flowers, a browallia means "to be blessed with charisma."
It'd be nice if Karin could tap into her
own unique charisma more in the future.
Kinda sucks, though. You woulda
gotten to debut as a model after all.
I'm fine with just being a Precure, I think.
But I really need to thank you, Potpourri, for protecting us back there.
Potpourri has very strong protective powers, it seems.
That so?
What're you shouting for?!
If Potpourri, a third fairy, has been born...
...then that must mean that there's a third Precure too, right?!
That'sh right!
A third...
A third?!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
We're on the hunt for the third Precure!
We have a vacancy for a happy, fun-loving, and outgoing Precure, no experience needed!
There's only one qualification you need, and that's...
...having dreamt of the Great Heart Tree!
So come be the latest member of the team!
Yes, you in front of the TV! You might be my partner!
HeartCatch Precure:
A Fairy Adventure!
The Hunt for the Next Precure!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!