- THIS IS FOR REAL.
OKAY, I'LL SEE
YOU LATER, BYE.
- Mizuki: I KNEW IT.
MINAMI HAS A THING
FOR AKIHISA.
- ( screams )
- THIS IS FOR REAL.
I'LL SEE YOU IN HELL.
TAKE THE FUGITIVE AWAY.
- ( grumbling )
- SHE LIKES HIM.
SHE, LIKE,
LIKE-LIKES HIM.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: A WEEK
AFTER TRAINING CAMP,
THE YEAR-TWO BOY'S SUSPENSION
IS FINALLY OVER.
- YUUJI.
- YEAH?
WHAT IS IT?
( screams )
- YOU DODGED ME.
- YOU WERE ABOUT
TO HEAD BUTT ME.
I'M NOT JUST GONNA
SIT THERE AND TAKE IT.
- I WAS ONLY
TRYING TO KISS YOU.
- YOU WERE WHAT?
OKAY, NOW STAY RIGHT THERE.
PUT YOUR HANDS BEHIND YOUR HEAD
AND EXPLAIN SLOWLY.
- A KISS, MOUTH TO MOUTH,
LIP TO LIP.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL CONSIDERING
WE'RE ENGAGED TO BE MARRIED.
- WHAT? NO.
I KNOW WHAT A KISS IS.
WHAT I WAS TRYING TO ASK YOU
IS WHY YOU--
( groans )
- WHEN, WHERE, AND WITH WHOM
DID YOU KISS?
- I JUST KNOW WHAT IT IS.
I NEVER SAID
I ACTUALLY KISSED ANYONE.
- OH, WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
- YOU'RE KILLING ME.  WHAT'S ALL
THIS HEAD-BUTT-KISSING CRAP
ABOUT IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- THOSE TWO.
THEY WERE KISSING
A MOMENT AGO.
- SERIOUSLY?
WHAT'S HE THINKING?
HE KNEW THOSE GUYS
WOULD KILL HIM FOR THAT.
IT'S LIKE HE'S ACTUALLY
GETTING STUPIDER
BY THE FLIPPING MINUTE.
- I APOLOGIZE.
- WHAT?
- WHILE YOU WERE SLEEPING,
I MIGHT HAVE DONE SOMETHING.
- AHA!
- LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
ANOTHER HERETIC OVER HERE.
- ALL RIGHT, TAKE HIM IN.
- AH! HEY, STOP IT.
I DIDN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING!
LET ME GO!
- I'M A NAUGHTY GIRL.
ALTHOUGH, ALL I DID
WAS KISS HIM ON THE CHEEK.
- MEN, TELL THEM
WHERE WE ARE.
- THE COURT FOR PASSING
VIOLENT JUDGMENT.
- WHAT HAPPENS TO TRAITORS?
- THE DEATH PENALTY AWAITS.
- WONDERFUL! AND NOW,
LET THE INQUISITION BEGIN.
- HEY, YUUJI, WHY DID
THEY BRING YOU HERE?
- BECAUSE OF YOU, YOU JERK!
- READ THE CHARGES, PLEASE.
- THEY ARE AS FOLLOWS.
AKIHISA YOSHI
SHALL BE KNOWN AS "A."
MINAMI SHIMADA SHALL
BE KNOWN AS "FLAT CHEST."
"A" IS CHARGED WITH AN ACT OF
DISLOYALTY TO OUR DOCTRINE.
EARLIER THIS MORNING,
"A" WAS CAUGHT WITH "FLAT CHEST"
AS HE SEXUALLY ASSAULTED
HER ON THE MOUTH.
OUR FELLOW MEMBERS DUTIFULLY
CAPTURED HIM AT THAT TIME.
THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN
"A" AND "FLAT CHEST"
CALLS FOR A THOROUGH
INVESTIGATION.
"A" SHOULD SUFFER
THE CONSEQUENCES
AND "FLAT CHEST" SHOULD HAVE
A WATCHFUL EYE KEPT ON HER
IN THE FUTURE.
- JUST STATE THE CONCLUSION!
- WE'RE JEALOUS OF HIM
BECAUSE HE WAS KISSING A GIRL!
- DEATH PENALTY IT IS.
- AKI, DO YOU HAVE
ANY IDEA WHAT'S GOING ON?
- NO, I WASN'T
PAYING ATTENTION.
- DOESN'T SOMETHING SEEM WEIRD
TO YOU ABOUT ALL THIS?
- HMM.
- DO YOU REMEMBER
THE LAST TIME
YOU SAW MINAMI?
- I THINK IT WAS THAT LAST NIGHT
AT THE TRAINING CAMP.
- OKAY, WHAT HAPPENED?
- WELL, AFTER EVERYONE
FELL ASLEEP,
SHE, LIKE, RANDOMLY
CAME UP TO ME.
- SERIOUSLY? AND YOU DIDN'T
THINK THAT WAS STRANGE AT ALL?
- I FIGURED, YOU KNOW,
SHE JUST WANTED TO KILL ME.
- SO THINK.  BEFORE THAT,
DID YOU SAY ANYTHING TO HER?
- LET ME THINK.
THERE WAS THAT ONE THING.
( gasps )
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY, DUDE?
- YEAH, I'M GOOD.
- WELL, WHAT DID YOU
TALK TO HER ABOUT?
- A KIND OF
LOVE-CONFESSION THING.
- WAIT, SHE CONFESSED TO YOU?
- NO, I DID THE CONFESSING.
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- THAT DIDN'T SEEM
A LITTLE WEIRD TO YOU?
- HERETIC AKIHISA YOSHI,
WILL YOU REPENT YOUR SIN
AND ACCEPT THE RULING
PLACED AGAINST YOU?
- DEPENDS ON THE RULING.
- YOUR SENTENCE
IS A SPECIAL BUNGEE JUMP.
- CAN YOU TELL ME,
LIKE, WHAT KIND
OF SPECIAL BUNGEE JUMP?
- I DON'T WANT TO CAUSE
UNNECESSARY CONCERN,
BUT I WILL GIVE YOU A HINT.
THINK SKYDIVING
WITHOUT A PARACHUTE.
- ( screams )
THAT'S NOT A HINT.
YOU'RE TELLING ME
YOU WANT ME TO BUNGEE JUMP
WITHOUT A CHORD?!
LOOK, IT'S HIMEJI!
OVER HERE!
- I HAD A SNEAKING SUSPICION
MINAMI LIKED AKIHISA.
I GUESS I WAS RIGHT.
- WHY ARE YOU STILL
ACTING LIKE THAT?!
- THEY JUST EXCHANGED WORDS
WITH THEIR EYES!
- NOW I'LL NEVER HAVE
A CHANCE WITH "FLAT CHEST."
- JUST LIKE
HIMEJI AND HIDEYOSHI,
MINAMI HAS FALLEN
UNDER HIS SPELL.
BEWARE THE DEVIL
KNOWN AS AKI!
- HEY, AKI, HOW ARE YOU?
- OH, HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- WOULD YOU MIND--
I MEAN, IS IT OKAY IF I SIT
AT YOUR TABLE WITH YOU?
- HUH?
- MINE IS BROKEN, SO...
- OH, YEAH, THAT SUCKS.
SURE.
- YOU'RE THE BEST.
ARE YOU SICK?
'CAUSE YOU'RE SWEATING.
- NO, JUST FEELING
CLAUSTROPHOBIC.
- WELL, THE TABLE
IS KIND OF SMALL.
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
- SO, UM, I WAS JUST THINKING
THAT WE COULD MAYBE--
I DON'T KNOW.
WE COULD, YOU KNOW,
HAVE OUR LUNCH TOGETHER?
I MADE SOMETHING SPECIAL
FOR YOU TODAY.
- DARLING, WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU DOING?
- ELBOW IN MY FACE!
- YOU SHOULDN'T SIT SO CLOSE
TO THIS FILTHY TRASH.
HE'S GROSS!
- WELL MY TABLE'S BROKEN.
AND IT ISN'T LIKE
I HAVE MUCH OF A CHOICE.
- SO WHAT? THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO SIT
NEXT TO SUCH
A WASTE OF SPACE.
- MINAMI LIKES AKIHISA.
MINAMI LIKES AKIHISA.
- I DIDN'T WANT
TO BOTHER MIZUKI
BECAUSE SHE ACTUALLY STUDIES.
I MEAN, TALK ABOUT RUDE, RIGHT?
AKIHISA'S DIFFERENT.
EVERYONE KNOWS HE'S GONNA
GET BAD GRADES ANYWAY.
- I'M STARTING TO FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE NOT COMPLIMENTING ME.
- NO WAY! I CANNOT ALLOW
THIS DISGUSTING PIG TO THINK
YOU MADE LUNCH FOR HIM!
FRIED CHICKEN WITH YOUR
HOMEMADE SPECIAL SAUCE
THAT YOU MADE THIS MORNING.
AND NOT TO MENTION
THE SUPER EXPENSIVE
GROUND BEEF HAMBURGERS.
AND THEN THERE'S
THE ORGANIC POTATO SALAD.
- YOU'RE SUCH A STALKER.
HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW THAT?
- OH, GUESS WHAT'S
ON TOP OF THE RICE.
A DAMN HEART!
- MIHARU, SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
( sighs )
LISTEN TO ME.
I'VE BEEN PATIENT WITH YOU
UP UNTIL NOW,
BUT I REALLY NEED YOU
TO STOP DOING
THIS KIND OF STUFF,
BECAUSE-- WELL, BECAUSE
AKI AND I HAVE STARTED DATING.
- DEFLECTIVE MAP FLIP!
- ( growling )
- THAT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND.
- I DON'T! YOU AND I ARE
GONNA GET MARRIED
AND NAME OUR DAUGHTER MIRAI
SO THE FIRST PART
OF HER NAME
SOUNDS LIKE THE FIRST PART
OF YOURS BECAUSE
THAT'S THE WAY
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA NAME IT
IF IT'S A BOY?
- I'M THINKING STEVEN
SHOULD WORK OKAY.
- YOU'RE MISSING
SOMETHING IMPORTANT!
THE TWO OF US
CAN'T MAKE A BABY!
- CLASS IS STARTING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
GO BACK TO YOUR
CLASSROOM, SHIMIZU.
- YOU NEED TO TURN AROUND
AND WALK AWAY, NISHIMURA.
I'M DEALING WITH A MATTER
OF LIFE AND DEATH.
- LIFE AND DEATH?
- YES!
LIFE AND DEATH IN THAT
I'M GONNA ANNIHILATE
EVERY SLEAZY DIRTBAG IN HERE.
- YOU ARE FORBIDDEN
FROM ENTERING
THIS CLASSROOM AGAIN, MISSY.
- WHY I OUGHTA!
- YOU ALWAYS GET INTO
STUFF LIKE THIS.
- AT LEAST YOU GET
SOME GOOD STORIES.
- LEAVE ME ALONE.  THIS TIME
IT ISN'T EVEN MY FAULT.
- YOU CAN DENY IT ALL YOU WANT,
BUT WE'RE ABOUT
TO GET IN TROUBLE
BIG TIME BECAUSE OF YOU.
APPARENTLY, CLASS D's DECIDED
THEY NEED TO CHALLENGE SOMEONE
TO A SUMMONER TEST WAR.
- SO WHAT DO WE CARE IF THEY
WANT TO FIGHT ANOTHER CLASS?
THAT DOESN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH US.
DUDE, THERE IS NO WAY
YOU CAN PIN THAT ON ME.
- YES, I CAN, IF THE CLASS
THEY WANT TO FIGHT IS OURS.
- THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WE HAVE THE WORST EQUIPMENT
IN THE SCHOOL.
WHY WOULD THEY WANT TO FIGHT US
OVER A BUNCH OF STUFF
THAT'S CRAPPY? UNLESS...
- YOU GUESSED IT.
THIS IS ALL MIHARU.
- SHE'S TRYING TO
SWITCH OUR TABLES
BACK TO CARDBOARD BOXES,
JUST TO KEEP YOU AND MINAMI
FROM SITTING
NEXT TO EACH OTHER.
- BUT HOW COULD SHE GET
EVERYONE IN CLASS D
TO GO ALONG WITH HER?
THEY KNOW SHE'S CRAY-CRAY.
- WELL, WE ARE THE RINGLEADERS
OF THE PEEKING INCIDENT.
NO WONDER THE GIRLS
ALREADY BELIEVE OUR CLASS
IS THEIR SWORN ENEMY.
- AND THEIR CLASS REP HIRAGA
WON'T TRY TO
FIGHT THEM ON IT.
MIHARU IS
RIDICULOUSLY JEALOUS
AND THE GIRLS ARE
RIDICULOUSLY PISSED.
SO WHAT COULD HE DO?
- BALLS.
- WITH THAT DAMN SUSPENSION,
THE GUYS HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO RECOVER THEIR
SCORES YET EITHER.
EVEN HAVING
HIMEJI ON OUR TEAM
ISN'T GONNA HELP US
AT THIS POINT.
- THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY OUT, GUYS.
AVOID THE WAR.
- HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT?
- I THINK IT'S UP TO
YOU AND MINAMI NOW.
BUT BEFORE WE GET STARTED,
THERE'S ONE THING
I'M CURIOUS ABOUT.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- ARE YOU AND MINAMI DATING?
LIKE FOR REAL DATING-DATING?
- AS FAR AS I CAN REMEMBER,
WE'RE NOT,
BUT SHE MIGHT HAVE A GOOD REASON
TO THINK WE ARE
BECAUSE OF A TEXT MESSAGE
I SORT OF ACCIDENTALLY SENT HER.
- AN ACCIDENTAL TEXT?
- ( gasps )
- ( sighs )
WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE.
WHAT AKI DID WAS BAD ENOUGH,
BUT THEN YUUJI
HAD TO COME IN WITH
SOME SUPER BAD TIMING
AND MAKE THINGS EVEN WORSE.
- THAT'S WHAT WAS GOING ON.
SORRY, AKI, I KNOW IT MUST SUCK,
BUT LISTEN TO ME.
YOU HAVE REALLY
GOT TO FIX THIS.
CLEAR THINGS UP
WITH MINAMI LIKE ASAP.
MAYBE THEN MIHARU
WILL CHILL OUT.
- OKAY.
- WHAT'S THE STORY, KOUTA?
DID YOU SEE MIHARU
PLANT A WIRETAP DEVICE HERE?
- YEAH, BUT
I MADE IT LOOK LIKE
IT WAS BROKEN
AND REMOVED IT.
- WHAT DID YOU WANT
TO TALK TO ME ABOUT?
- WELL, DO YOU REMEMBER
THAT EMAIL I SENT YOU
WHILE WE WERE STILL
AT TRAINING CAMP?
I JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT YOU KIND OF
GOT THE WRONG IDEA.
- WHAT?
- YEAH, I'M AN IDIOT.
I MEANT TO SEND THAT EMAIL
TO SOMEONE ELSE.
- WHO?
- I'M PRETTY SURE IT WAS SUGAWA.
- WHAT?! ARE YOU TELLING ME
YOU WERE GONNA CONFESS
YOUR LOVE TO SUGAWA?!
- I HAD A FEELING
THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
I MEAN, I KNOW YOU NEVER GAVE ME
A REASON TO THINK OTHERWISE,
BUT I THOUGHT FOR SURE
YOU LIKED GIRLS.
- YOU WHAT?
NO, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
- THAT IS JUST WRONG
IN SO MANY WAYS.
- I KNOW.  I'M SORRY.
THE POINT IS
I SENT IT ON ACCIDENT.
- TALK ABOUT A RELIEF.
I ALWAYS SUSPECTED,
BUT I DIDN'T WANT
TO EMBARRASS YOU.
I TOTES GET IT.
- ( laughs )
YEAH, YOU JUST KIND OF
ROLLED WITH IT, HUH?
- OH, PLEASE, THIS
IS COMING FROM THE GUY
WHO SENT A SUGGESTIVE EMAIL
TO THE WRONG PERSON.
- ( all laugh )
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT MY FIRST KISS?!
YOU SCREWED THAT UP FOR ME!
- I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING BY IT,
I SWEAR.
- SORRY DOESN'T QUITE CUT IT,
YOU JERK.
- YEAH, BUT--
- WHAT?
- WELL...
IT WAS MY FIRST KISS TOO.
WE'RE EVEN.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
SHE IS SO NOT GONNA GO FOR THAT.
- I DIDN'T KNOW.
SO, YEAH, I GUESS SO.
SURE, WE CAN CALL IT EVEN.
- Yuuji: NO FREAKIN' WAY!
- HEY, SO I'M GONNA
ASK YOU SOMETHING,
BUT I DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET ALL MAD AT ME.
- WHAT IS IT?
- WELL, IT'S JUST--
YOU TOLD MIHARU
THAT WE WERE DATING,
SO DOES THAT MEAN
THAT YOU, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE YOU MIGHT HAVE--
YOU KNOW, UH...
- NO! LIKE, NO.
SHE WASN'T GONNA
GIVE UP LIKE EVER.
SO IT JUST SEEMED LIKE
THE LOGICAL THING TO SAY.
I DIDN'T, YOU KNOW, YOU KNOW.
IT WAS JUST SOME GOOD TIMING.
- DENIAL.COM.
- SHE'S LYING TO HERSELF.
- OH, I WISH YOU
WOULD HAVE TOLD ME.
I THOUGHT YOU, LIKE,
LIKE-LIKED ME.
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
- YEAH, LIKE THAT EVER
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
I COULDN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU WERE ACTING LIKE
SUCH A GIRL INSTEAD OF YOURSELF.
I FELT LIKE YOU WERE
DISLOCATING MY ARM!
- WELL, AT LEAST THE MAIN
CONFUSION HAS BEEN CLEARED UP.
- NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
TELL CRAZY FACE ABOUT ALL THIS.
AND HOPEFULLY, THAT'LL WORK.
- Fukuhara:
SO THE WAR WITH CLASS D
WAS SUCCESSFULLY AVOIDED.
HOWEVER...
- BAKA AND TEST.
- YOU GUYS REALLY
NEED TO LISTEN TO THIS.
BAD NEWS THE SITUATION
IS EVEN WORSE NOW
THAN IT WAS THIS MORNING.
- Um, is it really true
That you have pictures
of Akihisa
in a sailor school uniform?
- $100 each.
Redistribution is prohibited.
- Yes, I'll take everything!
- OOPS, THAT WASN'T IT.
- HEY, WHAT THE CRAP!
YOU'RE RIGHT!
THE SITUATION HAS GOTTEN
TOTALLY WORSE.
- CALM DOWN,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
MAKE A BIG DEAL
OUT OF EVERYTHING.
- SOMEONE IS SELLING
PICTURES OF ME
LIKE I WAS HIDE-FREAKIN'-YOSHI.
THIS IS SO NOT NOTHING!
- WHAT? SOMEONE'S SELLING
PICTURES OF ME?!
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
WHY IS MY SITUATION
GETTING WORSE?
- HERE'S THE REAL ONE.
- How are things holding up
with Class F?
- Very good, sir.
They're not aware
of our plans at all.
- Perfect, we'll recover our
scores in the mean time.
If they notice
what we're up to,
we'll declare war immediately.
- WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
I THOUGHT CLASS D SAID
THEY WEREN'T GOING
TO ATTACK US ANYMORE.
- NO, THAT ISN'T "D."
WHERE DID THIS COME FROM, KOUTA?
- I RECORDED IT
IN CLASS "B."
- DAMN, THAT NEMOTO GUY
PLAYS ALMOST AS DIRTY AS SHOUKO.
- BUT WHY THE HELL
WOULD CLASS B
WANT TO DECLARE WAR ON US?
- HE LOST A LOT OF RESPECT
AFTER THAT LAST S.T. WAR.
- ON TOP OF THAT,
HE GOT THEM TO AGREE
TO PARTICIPATE IN
THE PEEKING OPERATION,
WHICH FAILED MISERABLY.
- WITH ALL THAT DRAMA,
HE PROBABLY LOST
THE CONTROL HE HAD
OVER HIS OWN CLASSROOM.
I'M GUESSING THIS
IS ALL A PLOY
TO CALM DOWN THE CLASS,
SO HE CAN TAKE OVER AGAIN.
HE MUST BE PLANNING
TO CREATE A NEW ENEMY FOR THEM
BY DIRECTING
THEIR ANGST AT US.
MAYBE THEN, THEY WON'T
BE PISSED AT HIM
FOR BEING SUCH A FAILURE.
- IF HE CAN PULL IT OFF,
IT'LL MOST LIKELY
HELP HIM REGAIN
SOME OF THE GROUND HE LOST.
- NO.
WE HAVEN'T RECOVERED
OUR SCORES YET.
IF CLASS B
DECIDES TO ATTACK US,
THERE'S NO FRICKIN' WAY
WE CAN BEAT THEM.
- I REALIZE THAT, SO NOW WE
HAVE TO CREATE A SITUATION
WHERE CLASS B WON'T BE ABLE
TO DECLARE WAR ON US.
- SO WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
- THAT'S EASY.  ALL WE NEED
IS FOR ANOTHER CLASSROOM
TO DECLARE WAR ON US
BEFORE THEY GET A CHANCE TO.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- NO, I'M NOT.
WE NEED TO ENTER INTO
BATTLE WITH CLASS "D."
- OH MY GOD! WE JUST WENT
THROUGH ALL THAT TROUBLE
TO KEEP D FROM
STARTING A WAR WITH US.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO WE GO UP AGAINST.
IF WE'RE FIGHT AN S.T. WAR,
WE'LL BE GIVEN TIME
TO RECOUP OUR SCORES
WITH THE RECOVERY TESTS.
IT MAKES MORE SENSE
FOR US TO DO THAT
AFTER LOSING TO CLASS D
INSTEAD OF "B."
- I THINK I GET IT.
IF WE TAKE THE REMEDIAL CLASS
AND GET OUR SCORES UP,
CLASS B IS LESS LIKELY
TO WANT TO ATTACK US, RIGHT?
- BUT, YUUJI,
WITH OUR CURRENT SCORES,
WE CAN'T EVEN DEFEAT CLASS "D."
- I KNOW, BUT DON'T WORRY.
I THINK I'VE GOT
A SOLUTION FOR THAT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, THOUGH.
SOMEHOW, WE NEED
TO GET CLASS D TO DECLARE
WAR ON US LIKE PRONTO.
- OKAY, HOW?
- WE CAN USE WHAT
HAPPENED THIS MORNING.
YOU AND MINAMI
JUST GET ALL COZY
AND PISS OFF MIHARU.
- WHAT?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
NO WAY.
- Yuuji: CAN'T YOU RECONSIDER?
- NEVER IN A MILLION YEARS.
PLUS, NO ONE'S GONNA BELIEVE
I WOULD BE THE GIRLFRIEND
OF SUCH A STUPID IDIOT.
- COME ON.  YOU KNOW
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN DO THIS, MINAMI.
IF CLASS B ATTACKS US NOW,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO GO BACK
TO USING CARDBOARD BOXES.
DO YOU REALLY WANT THAT?
- YEAH, AND NOT TO MENTION
HIMEJI'S PARENTS MIGHT GET
SUPER WORRIED ABOUT HER AGAIN.
DO YOU REALLY WANT THEM TO
TRANSFER HER TO ANOTHER SCHOOL?
- OH, AND WE COULD USE
YOUR HELP TOO, HIMEJI.
- BUT WHAT CAN I DO?
- WE DON'T THINK MINAMI
ACTING THIS ALL BY HERSELF
WILL BE CONVINCING ENOUGH.
WO WE WERE HOPING
YOU COULD PRETEND
THAT YOU WERE JEALOUS
OF THEIR RELATIONSHIP.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU CAN MANAGE THAT,
CAN'T YOU?
- I, UM-- LOOK,
MINAMI AND AKIHISA,
I UNDERSTAND YOU
MAY NOT WANT TO DO THIS,
BUT YOU HAVE TO.
- MIZUKI.
- I'M SORRY.
I KNOW I'M BEING SELFISH,
BUT I CAN'T HELP IT.
I JUST REALLY DON'T
WANT MY PARENTS
TO MAKE ME CHANGE SCHOOLS.
PLEASE DO THIS.
- WELL, I GUESS SINCE
I'LL JUST BE FAKING IT,
IT'S NOT THAT
BIG OF A DEAL.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH, MINAMI.
- LOVELY, NOW
LET'S GET STARTED.
- ALL RIGHT, WHAT'S THIS?
LIKE A SCRIPT?
- "SORRY FOR ASKING YOU
TO COME SEE ME LIKE THIS,
BUT I WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU."
- "I HAVE A CONFESSION
FOR YOU TOO.
I FEEL THE SAME WA--"
OH NO, NO, NO, NO.
- I AM SO NOT
SAYING ANY OF THAT!
- I KNOW IT'S JUST PRETEND,
BUT THIS IS EMBARRASSING.
- WATCH ME DO IT.
YOU'RE NOT
GETTING INTO YOUR CHARACTERS.
- Aki: WHAT?
- Fukuhara: WOW.
- I'M SORRY FOR ASKING YOU
TO COME SEE ME LIKE THIS.
BUT I WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU.
- WHAT?
- EVER SINCE I FIRST MET YOU,
I'VE BEEN IN LOVE WITH YOU.
IT WAS REALLY HARD FOR ME
TO BE NO MORE THAN A FRIEND
TO YOU THIS WHOLE TIME.
THE TRUTH IS I CAN'T BEAR
TO BE JUST FRIENDS
WITH YOU ANY LONGER.
AKI, I KNOW THIS
MUST BE WEIRD TO HEAR
AFTER WHAT I SAID
TO YOU EARLIER,
BUT PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
I AM MADLY
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO BE MY BOYFRIEND?
SO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- WOW, THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
- MY HEART IS STILL RACING.
- HEY, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU, DUDE?
- I JUST NEED A MOMENT.
COULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR
AND LEAVE ME ALONE
FOR A LITTLE BIT?
I DON'T WANT TO WAKE UP
FROM THIS DREAM, NOT YET.
- ( sighs )
YOU'RE UP, KOUTA.
THINK YOU CAN PUT
MIHARU'S WIRETAP DEVICE
BACK UP ON THE ROOFTOP?
- I CAN DO THAT.
- I WANT THE THREE OF YOU TO
HEAD UP THERE AND PUT ON A SHOW,
SO MIHARU THAT WILL HEAR IT
THROUGH THE MICROPHONE
AND GET THE WRONG IDEA.
- THE SETUP IS THAT AKIHISA
AND MINAMI ARE MEETING SECRETLY.
OKAY, NOW LINK
YOUR ARMS TOGETHER.
- UH... HOW COME?
- OUR ARMS?
- WE GOT TO MAKE THIS
LOOK AUTHENTIC,
ESPECIALLY AFTER WHAT HAPPENED,
SO DO IT.
- I'M IN.  GIVE ME YOUR ARM.
- IF YOU TRY TO TOUCH ME
ANYWHERE ELSE, I'LL KILL YOU.
- ( students chatter )
- ( nervous laughs )
WHEN YOU GRAB AHOLD
OF ME THAT TIGHT,
IT'S HARD TO WALK.
- WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE DATING,
YOU DUMMY.
THIS IS CALLED NORMAL BEHAVIOR.
- I GET THAT, BUT
YOUR YOU-KNOW-WHATS
ARE DIGGING INTO MY ELBOW.
- ( gasps )
YOU'RE DIRTY.
- IT'S YOUR RIBS.
( screams )
OH, CRAP.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE ACTING.
UM...
- YES, DEAR?
- WHAT IS IT EXACTLY
YOU LIKE ABOUT ME?
- WHY ARE YOU ASKING?
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
EVERYTHING FROM
THE TOP OF YOUR HEAD TO--
- TO WHAT?
- YOUR EYEBROWS.
- MY FOREHEAD?
I GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE.
- I HAVE TO ASK.
WHY ARE YOUR ARMS
CROSSED LIKE THAT?
- MIZUKI?
- YOU'RE SO CLOSE TO EACH OTHER.
IT ALMOST LOOKS LIKE-- LIKE...
LIKE THE TWO OF YOU MIGHT
BE DATING OR SOMETHING.
- WAIT, WAS THAT LINE
IN THE SCRIPT?
OH, SHE'S IMPROVISING.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, MIZUKI.
AKIHISA AND I
ARE INDEED TOGETHER.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME ABOUT THIS?
- I'M SORRY, I SHOULD
HAVE SAID SOMETHING EARLIER.
- SO I WAS RIGHT.
YOU REALLY HAD A THING
FOR AKIHISA THIS WHOLE TIME.
- YES, AND I'M SORRY
FOR KEEPING THAT FROM YOU.
ESPECIALLY SINCE
I KNEW HOW YOU FELT.
I REALLY AM SORRY.
PLEASE SAY YOU'LL
BE ABLE TO FORGIVE ME.
- YOU KNOW, I SORT OF
ALREADY KNEW YOU LIKED HIM,
BUT I DO FEEL BETTER NOW
THAT YOU'VE BEEN HONEST WITH ME.
I UNDERSTAND.
YOU WERE IN
AN AWFUL POSITION.
I DON'T KNOW IF I WOULD
HAVE SAID ANYTHING EITHER.
- DOES THAT MEAN
YOU'RE GONNA FORGIVE ME?
- THIS ISN'T ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT I'LL FORGIVE YOU.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
HAVE THE FREEDOM
TO LIKE WHOMEVER
YOU WANT TO LIKE.
AND I CAN'T FAULT
YOU FOR THAT, MINAMI,
ANY MORE THAN
I COULD FAULT MYSELF.
- THANK YOU.
- SURE.
BUT STILL I--
I CAN'T FORGIVE YOU FOR
KISSING HIM THIS MORNING.
YOU WENT TOO FAR!
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
YOU STOLE THE VERY FIRST KISS
HE WILL EVER HAVE.
- BUT WE ALREADY
EXPLAINED THAT WAS
BECAUSE OF
THE EMAIL AND STUFF.
- DON'T YOU "AND STUFF" ME.
GOD, MAY BE ABLE
TO LET THAT ONE GO,
BUT I WILL NEVER FORGIVE
EITHER ONE OF YOU.
- ( gasps )
NO, IT'S A WIRETAP THINGY.
- YOU GUYS ARE STUPID.  STUPID!
- IF HIMEJI SPILLS THE BEANS
WITHOUT NOTICING IT,
MIHARU COULD FIGURE
OUT THE TRUTH.
- HIMEJI, WAIT!
- HEY, HOLD UP!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO GO AFTER HER,
UNLESS YOU'RE GONNA
PICK HER OVER ME.
- I'M SORRY, MINAMI.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF.
- NO, YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME.
AKI, PLEASE, I HAVE
SOMETHING I WANT TO TELL YOU.
I THINK I'M
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
FINALLY, I SAID IT.
- WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
THERE'S A SCRIPT, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH, DON'T WORRY.
I'M DONE ACTING.
EVERYONE KNOWS
AKI LIKES GIRLY-GIRLS.
SO THIS HAS JUST
BEEN A WASTE OF TIME.
- Aki: HIMEJI.
- OH, HI, AKIHISA.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THAT THING WAS THERE.
THANKS SO MUCH
FOR SAVING ME AGAIN.
- ARE YOU FEELING OKAY, HIMEJI?
YOU SEEM LIKE YOU MIGHT
BE A LITTLE BUMMED.
- OH, NO, DO
I LOOK THAT BAD?
- WELL, NOT BAD,
MAYBE A LITTLE LONELY.
- I WONDER WHAT
THAT LOOKS LIKE.
IF I DO LOOK LONELY,
IT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE
I'M A LITTLE SAD.
EVEN IF IT WAS
ONLY FOR SHOW,
I STILL FEEL LIKE
THE PERSON I LIKE
WAS TAKEN AWAY FROM ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN,
DON'T YOU?
- OF COURSE I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU MEAN.
YOU WERE JUST GETTING
INTO CHARACTER.
- I GUESS THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S LIKE HIDEYOSHI SAID.
- I MIGHT BE
A LITTLE JEALOUS TOO.
- WHAT?
- IF YOU AND MINAMI LIKED
THE SAME GUY,
IT WOULD BUG ME, EVEN IF
YOU WERE PRETENDING.
- JUST FOR FUNSIES,
LET'S SAY
YOU WERE IN THAT
EXACT SITUATION.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
ABOUT IT, AKIHISA?
- WELL, LET ME SEE.
I GUESS I WOULD MOST LIKELY
THINK REALLY HARD ABOUT IT.
- WAIT, YOU WOULD MOST LIKELY
THINK ABOUT IT?
- YEAH, I'D THINK REALLY HARD
ABOUT IT IN MY OWN WAY.
AND THEN BE LIKE WAY HONEST
WITH EVERYTHING.
- BUT I WANTED YOU
TO TELL ME
WHICH ONE OF US
YOU WOULD PICK.
WHAT? OH NO,
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
- I WAS PRETTY SURPRISED THOUGH.
- YOU WERE? ABOUT WHAT?
- WELL, IT'S JUST THAT THE WAY
YOU WERE TALKING EARLIER,
DIDN'T MAKE IT SEEM
LIKE YOU WERE ACTING.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT-- YOU KNOW.
DID YOU USE TO PERFORM
IN PLAYS OR SOMETHING?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- IDIOT.
- DUMMY.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION 10:
"NAME THE NUTRIENTS MISO LACKS
AS WELL AS SUITABLE INGREDIENTS
THAT COULD MAKE UP
FOR THE LACKING NUTRIENTS."
- Mizuki: VITAMIN C, ORANGE,
AND HYDROCHLORIC ACID.
- THAT IS NOT ACCURATE.
- Aki: NEXT EPISODE,
"ME, ROMANCE,
AND LOVE SKILLS."
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.