This was probably the right decision to take, compared to running away from her.
No, I might have made a mistake.
Because her body was really, almost unbelievably light.
Yes...
Senjyogahara... she doesn't seem to actually weigh anything.
It's the cultural festival, but we're already in our third year.
We don't really need to do anything,
and exams preparations are more important.
Why don't we narrow down the options first,
before we let the rest vote on what we'll do?
Sounds great, right?
It seems democratic at first glance.
You're as sarcastic as ever, Araragi-kun.
Or should I say that you're quirky?
Hanekawa Tsubasa.
Our class president.
Always prim and proper, always follows the rules, terribly serious, and well liked by the teachers.
The class president of class presidents.
As a reference, Araragi-kun, what did you do for the cultural festival the last two years?
Haunted house and café.
Right now, I'm discussing the plans for the cultural festival with Hanekawa, the president of the class.
Hey, isn't there a girl called Senjyogahara in our class?
Senjyogahara-san?
Is something wrong with her?
Well, I'm a bit curious about her.
Isn't she sickly and often absent from school?
I wonder if she'll attend the cultural festival.
Well, look, the name "Senjyogahara Hitagi" is pretty unusual and interesting, isn't it?
Isn't Senjyogahara based on the name of a place?
Uh, I wasn't talking about that.
I was talking more about her given name.
Senjyogahara-san's given name is Hitagi, right?
Is that strange?
If I remember correctly, Hitagi is a term used in civil engineering.
You know everything.
I don't know everything.
I just happen to know that.
It's rare...
What?
...for you to be curious about someone else.
No, it's nothing like that.
Boys always like sickly girls.
Oh gosh, how disgusting, how disgusting.
Sickly...
But... was that really caused by an illness?
Anyway, what kind of person is she?
You probably know more about her than I do.
Wasn't she in your class for three consecutive years?
That's true, now that you remind me about it.
Well, she's the perfect model student.
Her grades are good, too.
True.
But I've only been in the same class as her for a month.
I guess I don't really know her that well.
That month included Golden Week, too.
Golden Week, eh?
Oh? Did something happen during Golden Week?
It's nothing. Please continue.
Well, let's see.
She doesn't talk much.
She doesn't seem to have any friends either.
I guess it's probably because of an illness.
She was a much more active and cheerful girl back in junior high.
You were in the same school as her during junior high?
Yes.
Senjyogahara-san was really pretty, and she was good at sports, too.
She was the star of the athletics club.
That's why I've heard a lot of rumors about her.
Rumors?
Rumors saying that she's very sociable and a nice person.
There are also rumors that she's not at all snobby,
even though her father is a big shot in a
foreign company and lives in a mansion.
She sounds like Wonder Woman.
Well...
I shouldn't be saying this...
but Senjyogahara-san...
What's wrong?
She looks a lot prettier the way she is now, compared to the past.
Her presence is...
very ephemeral.
An ephemeral presence...
Ah, I just remembered.
Oshino is looking for me.
Oshino-San? Why?
Well, he needs some help with his work.
Hadekawa, can I leave the rest to you?
That's okay, provided you promise to make up for today.
It isn't appropriate to make Oshino-san wait.
Sorry.
Give my regards to Oshino-san.
What were you discussing with Hanekawa-san?
Don't move.
My mistake.
The correct way to say it is, "You can move, but it's very dangerous."
Things like curiosity really resemble cockroaches.
They just hang around, intruding on secrets that people want to keep private.
It's so depressing I can't stand it.
Hey...
What is it?
Is your right cheek feeling lonely?
You could have just told me.
I was careless, too.
I didn't expect that someone would...
drop a banana peel in a place like that.
You noticed, right?
Yes...
I don't have...
any weight.
Even so, it's not as if I'm completely weightless.
Someone with my height and build
should weigh a little over 45kg on average.
But my actual weight is...
5kg.
It happened after I graduated from junior high, before I entered this school.
I met a crab.
It took my weight away almost completely.
Well, you don't really need to understand.
I'm just telling you about it because you'll cause me a lot of trouble if you continue snooping around, Araragi-kun.
Araragi-kun?
Hey, Araragi Koyomi-kun?
What should I do
to ensure that you'll keep my secret to yourself?
What should I do for myself?
How should I seal your mouth so that you'll swear not to reveal my secret,
even if your mouth is ripped apart?
Anyway, all I want is for you to remain silent and seem indifferent to me.
Nod your head twice, if you're willing to promise that you'll remain silent and seem indifferent, Araragi-kun.
I'll treat any other actions you take as hostility
and attack you immediately.
I see.
Thanks.
You didn't scream.
That's splendid.
I'll let you go this time.
You...
Well then, Araragi-kun, remember to ignore me properly from tomorrow onward.
Farewell.
She's like a devil.
But it's okay.
I'll be all right despite an injury like this.
Oh?
Araragi-kun?
Hanekawa?
You're still here?
Shouldn't you be rushing over to Oshino-san's place?
Hanekawa, do you like bananas?
Oh?
I don't really hate them, because they're nutritious.
If I have to say whether I like or hate them...
Yeah, I guess I like them.
No matter how much you like them, you must not eat them in school.
H-Huh?
Just eating them is still okay,
but I absolutely won't forgive you if you toss them away carelessly on the stairs!
What are you talking about, Araragi-kun?
Hey, Araragi-kun!
Don't run in the corridor!
I'll report you to the teachers!
I'm surprised to see you.
No, I should be more honest and say that I'm shocked to see you.
You were able to rekindle your rebellious spirit so quickly, despite your ordeal.
Senjyogahara—
Okay, I understand.
I understand, Araragi-kun.
Let's commence our war.
Y-You're mistaken!
I'm not here for a war.
No war?
How disappointing.
Then what are you here for?
It's just a chance, but I think I might be able to help you.
Help me?
Stop joking.
What can you do?
Just keep quiet and seem indifferent towards me.
I'll treat kindness as hostility.
Your wound...
has vanished.
What... happened to you?
Oshino?
Oshino-san?
Yup, he's called Oshino Meme.
Thanks to Oshino,
I was able to change back from a vampire to a human.
But there are still after-effects from having an immortal body.
Oshino Meme?
Sounds like quite a moe name.
Don't expect him to be anything like that.
He's a middle-aged man well past his thirties.
I see.
But he must have had moe characteristics when he was young.
Don't look at real humans that way.
Anyway, you're familiar with terms like "moe" and "characteristics"?
They're part of a general education.
People with characteristics like mine are called tsundere, right?
People with characteristics like yours are more like tundras.
My butt hurts and feels numb.
My skirt is crumpled, too.
Not my responsibility.
Stop making excuses.
I'll cut it off.
Which part are you talking about?
Now that I think about it, where's your bag?
You're empty-handed.
I left my textbook in my school locker.
And I don't need a bag if I stuff school supplies around my body.
Ah, I see.
If I don't have both my hands free,
it's hard to fight when the moment demands it.
Leave your school supplies and stuff with me.
What?
Hand them over. I'll keep them locked up.
Well, Oshino is my savior, even though he's a weird old man.
I can't let a dangerous person see my savior,
so give me your school supplies.
Why are you saying that, after we've come all the way here?
Did you intend to deceive me?
Very well then.
Here you go.
You...
Don't be mistaken.
I haven't lowered my guard against you.
What do you mean, "you haven't lowered your guard"?
Listen.
Five thousand of my rowdy comrades will proceed forthwith to invade your home
if I fail to contact them once a minute.
It'll be okay.
Don't worry about such unnecessary details.
Are you saying you can finish me off in a minute?!
Do you think that I'm a certain boxer?!
Both your younger sisters are still in junior high, right?
This way.
What are you doing?
Don't expect me to thank you for this.
I know.
Instead, you should be thanking me.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I purposely stapled the inside of your cheek, instead of the outside,
so that the injury wouldn't be obvious.
Isn't that the same as when a mugger says, "Let's hit his stomach instead of his head so the injury won't be obvious"?
Anyway, my worries were all for naught.
Yeah.
Would you feel hurt if I said that
an immortal body is pretty convenient?
I don't feel that way now.
Oh my, is that so?
Anyway, I'm no longer immortal.
I just recover from injuries very quickly.
Other than that, I'm a normal human.
Araragi-kun, let me say one final thing.
What is it?
You probably can't tell when I'm clothed,
but it's not worth violating the law in order to possess my body.
How should I put this?
On the whole, you seem a bit excessively self-conscious,
or should I say that you have an exceedingly strong persecution complex?
Gosh.
Even if it's true, there are things that you should and shouldn't say, right?
You're aware of it?!
Putting that aside, does this Oshino fellow
actually live in such a broken-down building?
Yeah, he's quite a weird person.
But he's an expert when it comes to people like you and me.
Oh, Araragi-kun?
You're finally here?
What's up, Araragi-kun?
Today, you've brought a different girl here yet again.
Stop that.
Don't make me sound like a cheap character.
Nice to meet you, my dear.
I'm Oshino.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Senjyogahara Hitagi.
I'm Araragi-kun's classmate, and he's told me about you.
Oh, I see.
Oshino.
Two years ago, she—
Don't call me "she."
Then what should I call you?
Senjyogahara-sama.
Senjyogahara-sama!
Don't say it so monotonously.
Pronounce it properly.
Senjyogahara-chan.
Ouch!
You might've blinded me!
It's because you were rude.
What kind of equivalent exchange is that?!
40 grams of bronze, 25 grams of zinc, 15 grams of nickel, and 5 grams of embarrassment.
I added 97 kilograms of malice and transmuted them into the earlier rash remark.
Isn't most of it malice?!
By the way, I was lying about the embarrassment bit.
The most important element that shouldn't be omitted was omitted!
Anyway, first things first.
What happened to her?
Ah, ignore her.
She's without shadow or form.
She's without a name and therefore has no reason to exist.
That's what she is.
You're wrong, Araragi-kun.
I gave her a name yesterday.
After all, because of her I worked a lot during Golden Week.
Oh, she has a name now?
What did you name her?
I named her Oshino Shinobu:
Heart under blade.
The name fits her, right?
I just let her use my surname.
Isn't that great?
As I was asking earlier, what happened to her?
I already told you that nothing happened.
A ruined vampire.
The remaining scraps of a beautiful ghost.
No matter what I say, her current state was inevitable, right?
I see.
It's okay if nothing happened.
I heard that you can help me.
Help you?
That's impossible.
My dear, you are the only one who can save yourself.
Before now, five people have said the same thing to me.
All of them were charlatans.
Are you one of them, Oshino-san?
My dear, you seem to be quite energetic.
Did you see something nice?
We can't continue this conversation unless you tell me.
I'll guard your secret strictly. Don't worry.
W-Well, I'll do a simple explanation first—
It's okay, Araragi-kun.
I'll explain it to him myself.
Senjyogahara...
I can do it myself.
Note: Omoshikani literally means "weight crab."
Omoshikani.
Omoshikani?
Yeah.
It's a common folk-tale in the mountainous region of Kyushu.
Depending on the area, it's called Omoshikani, Omoishikani, Omoshigani,
and sometimes even Omoishikami.
Note: In Japanese, crab is "kani" and god is "kami."
They say that crab and gods are related.
But why does it appear in Kyushu?
The location is meaningless.
It will appear when the conditions are met.
That's all.
There are stories where it takes the form of a rabbit instead of a crab in this kind of situation.
There are even stories where it takes the form of a beautiful woman, though not as pretty as Shinobu-chan.
Sounds like the patterns on the moon.
Well, the young lady here encountered a crab, so it's a crab this time.
Why did you say all of that?
I don't care what it's called.
Names are important.
I already said earlier that it might not be a crab and might instead be a god.
An Omoshikani derived from an Omoishikami.
Well, my dear, you can be considered as the luckiest among the unlucky.
Why?
Because gods exist everywhere.
They are everywhere, yet nowhere.
My dear, I can say that it might've existed around you before you became like this,
or it might possibly never have existed around you.
That sounds like a Zen riddle.
Note: Shugendou is an ancient Japanese religion.
It's Shinto, or more accurately Shugendou.
Don't be mistaken, my dear.
You didn't end up like this because of a specific event.
It's just that your point of view deviated a little.
My point of view?
What are you saying?
My dear, it pisses me off to see you act as if you're the victim here.
Oh.
This is great.
I thought for sure that you were just a selfish young lady.
Why did you think that?
Because most people who encounter Omoshikani are like that.
You don't encounter them just because you want to.
They're gods and don't normally interfere with us.
Don't interfere...
They're just there.
My dear, they won't appear unless you desire something.
Nah, I didn't originally plan to get so involved in this.
But okay, I understand.
I'll help you if you want to get your weight back.
After all, Araragi-kun introduced you to me.
You'll help me?
I'm Karen.
I'm Tsukihi.
It's time for the preview segment quiz!
Quiz!
Does heat and beat refer to me?
Is it Karen-chan?
How should I pronounce the symbol that's used to represent "and"?
Understanding the text of the question is harder than understanding the question itself.
Next episode: Hitagi Crab Part Two.
I'll only show it to those who got it right.
No one will get to see it...