Will you dress up as a girl if I win?
Funny joke...
Nice joke.
Will you dress up as a girl?
Why did
things turn out this way . . .
Why did things turn out this way...
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
Question 4
『 Me and True Intentions and a Man's Dignity! 』
Let's go back one hour...
Yuuji, how about a game of "I Doubt It"?
Oh, you're pretty sure of yourself.
Really? Didn't you learn your lesson at that hamburger joint the last time?
Thanks for the food.
Today I'll get my revenge!
Oh, now that's interesting...
How about we lighten up that wallet of yours again?
Okay! We're playing by the usual rules, right?
Fumizuki
Academy
Class F
Fumizuki
Academy
Class F
Fumizuki
Academy
Class F
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki Academy Class F "I Doubt It" Rules...
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
Class F
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Fumizuki
Academy
"I Doubt It" Rules
Place the cards face down on the table.
It's an Ace.
The other players then consider whether or not it's the truth.
If they think that it's a lie, they call out...
Doubt!
Lie
If it really is a lie, then the person who played the card picks up the entire stack.
True
If it's the truth, however, the person who called "Doubt" picks up the stack.
The game goes on until someone runs out of cards.
Doubt!
Lie
The first person who plays all of their cards wins.
Doubt!
True
Class F Local Rules!
The winner is the first person to have only two cards remaining in their hand.
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
The game ends quicker that way!
The most important part is paying attention to each card's suit.
The most important part is paying
attention to each card's suit.
The person who picks up the stack can start with whichever card they'd like to.
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Win
ner
Class F Local Rule
Be careful which card you choose, or it may cause trouble for you later.
Be careful which card you choose,
or it may cause trouble for you later.
... (Yeah, yeah)
Alright, guess I'll start...
That's an Ace.
That makes it my turn.
A two.
Three.
Now it's my turn!
Fou-
Doubt!
I didn't even finish saying it!
It's completely obvious.
It's written all over your face.
You're not very good at this.
I never play my first few cards honestly... it makes things easier later.
None of them were honest!
Tick.
I have to be very careful here.
Three.
Four.
You're playing another four, Akihisa...
Doubt.
Idiot! Here's a present for you!
Seriously?
You've had a four all along, haven't you?
It was a trick!
Not bad!
I can't tell them that I didn't notice the four earlier...
Tick.
All right, only six cards left.
Hideyoshi has four.
This is a critical moment.
How will they play it?
A six.
Muttsurini, play a seven.
Oh, seven!
No one got to call Doubt!
He's good!
It's hard to not play the card when you're set up like that.
Then, I'll...
Huh?
Oh, what are you guys doing?
Himeji-san, you haven't gone home yet?
No, I was helping a teacher out with something.
And I got this as a thank you!
Do you want to share them with me?
Thanks, Himeji-san, but can it wait until after our game of Doubt?
We've got a little wager-
I shouldn't say that we're gambling.
N-No, we're not betting, exactly...
It's just that there's a penalty for losing!
A penalty?
That's right.
Every time you lose a hand, you have to take off a piece of clothing.
Clothing?
Hideyoshi.
D-Don't, Akihisa!
Th-That's so depraved!
Himeji, we're all guys here... you don't have to get so-
Doubt!
Why are you giving all the cards to me?
It's still wrong, even if it is just you guys!
Let's eat some chocolate...
...and talk a bit.
All right, all right.
Just one more game, okay?
Let's just finish this up, then.
Huh? Himeji-san?
An eight, then.
Nine.
That's a ten.
Jack.
Queen.
I call Doubt, Hideyoshi.
So you do have all four of them...
Oh well, then...
We're all guys here, so taking a little off isn't-
What's wrong, Hideyoshi?
Oh my, Kinoshita-kun, you really shouldn't fall asleep in a place like this!
I guess there's no other choice...
I'll have to play for Kinoshita-kun.
H-Hey, Himeji, that handkerchief...
Kinoshita-kun must have been really tired.
B-But Himeji-san, Hideyoshi was fine until...
But what about...
Muttsurini?!
Seems like Tsuchiya-kun was tired, too.
What in the world...
Something weird is going on with Himeji-san.
There must be...
Could it be...
Those are...
My goodness, I can't believe that
he'd undress in front of Akihisa-kun.
Kinoshita most certainly is  tired.
There's no two ways about it... Himeji-san
has gone mental because of the chocolate!
Is something the matter, Akihisa-kun?
We can't go on with only three people...
we should probably just end-
End?
What are you talking about?
Aren't there four  of us?!
What?
I'll do my best.
Shouko, when did you show up?!
Forcibly undressing you is one of my wifely duties.
Goddamn it! That's just wrong in so many ways!
Well then, how about we play boys against girls?
Sure, it'll all be over quicker that way.
What should we do, Yuuji?
Nothing we can  do. Let's just beat them and call it a day.
But... forcing them to undress would be...
Nah...
We can call it quits if things get that far.
Got it!
You're right!
Akihisa-kun, socks are cheating!
Yuuji, that's not very manly of you.
Himeji-san, couldn't we just end the game-
We're just getting into it!
Shouko, you've had enough of this, right?
Double raise.
Undressing in front of you girls is sort of awkward, you know?
It's okay, Akihisa-kun!
If you don't want to undress...
No!
That is definitely not  a girl's uniform that you have there...
It's your fault for not listening to me, Akihisa-kun.
Zkihisa, did you notice that?
Ekihisa, did you notice that?
Kkihisa, did you notice that?
Wkihisa, did you notice that?
Bkihisa, did you notice that?
Akihisa, did you notice that?
Ukihisa, did you notice that?
Azahisa, did you notice that?
Atuhisa, did you notice that?
Akiposa, did you notice that?
Akiresa, did you notice that?
Akihime, did you notice that?
Akihisa, did you notice that?
Akihisaka did you notice that?
Akihisage did you notice that?
This is the Emergency Code!
Akihisa, do you notice that?
Akihisa, does you notice that?
Akihisa, did she notice that?
Akihisa, did her notice that?
Akihisa, did you spot that?
Akihisa, did you see that?
Akihisa, did you notice this?
Akihisa, did you notice those?
Akihisa, did you notice that!
Akihisa, did you notice that««
Akihisa, did you notice that?
Akihisa, did you notice that?   F
Akihisa, did you notice that?       Pe
Akihisa, did you notice that?       Ro
Akihisa, did you notice that?            za
Akihisa, did you notice that?
Notice what@!
Notice what£%
Notice what&#
Notice what^^~
Notice what€$
Notice what§=
Notice what;
Notice what*+
Notice twah?
Notice hwat?
cetino what?
citnoe what?
(]   Notice what?
[}   Notice what?
8''         Notice what?
@£         Notice what?
%§               Notice what?
?               Notice what?
Notice what?
?? have to do whatever it takes now.
eW have to do whatever it takes now.
Notice what?
ca have to do whatever it takes now.
Yu have to do whatever it takes now.
Notice what?
Li have to do whatever it takes now.
Tsu have to do whatever it takes now.
Notice what?
Ga have to do whatever it takes now.
We hvea to do whatever it takes now.
We aveh to do whatever it takes now.
We have zo do whatever it takes now.
We have ?! do whatever it takes now.
We have to do whatever it takes now.
We have to ?? whatever it takes now.
We have to do wthaever it takes now.
We have to do athwever it takes now.
We have to do whateevr it takes now.
We have to do whatveer it takes now.
We have to do whatever,, it takes now.
We have to do whatever,   , it takes now.
We have to do whatever it gftakes now.
We have to do whatever it tytakes now.
We have to do whatever it ta hjgkes now.
We have to do whatever it ta bcvkes now.
We have to do whatever it ta trsfkes now.
We have to do whatever it ta trs,,kes now.
We have to do whatever it takes !@ now.
We have to do whatever it takes x£ now.
We have to do whatever it takes  now.
We have to do whatever it takes )9 now.
We have to do whatever it takes own.
We have to do whatever it takes won.
We have to do whatever it takes now.
We have to do whatever it takes now»»
We have to do whatever it takes nowº~
We have to do whatever it takes now!"
We have to do whatever it takes now.
We have to do whatever it takes now.     ??
We have to do whatever it takes now.     df
We have to do whatever it takes now.     mn
We have to do whatever it takes now.     wq
We have to do whatever it takes now.     zx
We have to do whatever it takes now.             fhbv
We have to do whatever it takes now.             %if%
We have to do whatever it takes now.             ,!
We have to do whatever it takes now.             -..
We have to do whatever it takes now.                    &@
We have to do whatever it takes now.                   /§
We have to do whatever it takes now.
Set them up??
Set them up;
We have to do whatever it takes now.
Set them uplo
Set them uph
We have to do whatever it takes now.
Set them up@
Set them up?
Set them hef?
Set thme up?
Set ehmt up?
Tes them up?
Tse them up?
Ste them up?
Set them up?
fr?      Set them up?
vs?      Set them up?
?         ?      Set them up?
n         ?      Set them up?
ma               Set them up?
po               Set them up?
jiw                              Set them up?
gso                              Set them up?
Set them up?
Sorry!
Let's keep the game going, then.
Oops.
Good! Now's my chance!
What?!
You haven't chosen your roles very wisely.
Yuuji, you should never make such a silly mistake during a game.
You really do like playing around...
Naughty little boys.
Tick.
Seven.
This'll be the turning point.
6 Cards
A mistake will kill us here.
Oh?
Kubo-kun?
She
is
lying
to
you!
Kubo-kun!
You're on my side, huh?
Thank you.
I'll do my best with the chance that you've given me.
I'll put my whole heart into it...
I call Doubt on that seven!
Too bad... it is  a seven.
Kubo-kun!
Forgive me, Yoshii-kun!
She
is
lying
She
is
lying
She
is
lying
She
is
lying
She
is
lying
She
is
lying
to
She
is
lying
to
She
is
lying
to
is
lying
to
is
lying
to
is
lying
to
you!
is
lying
to
you!
is
lying
to
you!
is
lying
to
you!
is
lying
to
you!
is
lying
to
you!
is
lying
to
you!
lying
to
you!
lying
to
you!
lying
to
you!
lying
to
you!
not
to
What in the hell are you doing, Akihisa?!
He's against us if it means that you're undressing!
Why?!
Tick.
I'm starting to have second thoughts about this game.
Himeji-san!
It feels wrong to go up against your friends in a game with penalties.
As of tomorrow you're going to become an internet idol!
Just a moment, Himeji-san!
I never gave you permission to take photos of me and upload them!
Yuuji, if you feel embarrassed about it, you can close your eyes.
Goddamn it!
I'm not gonna lose!
By the way, Akihisa-kun...
W-What is it, Himeji-san?
I wouldn't end the game early, even if I had to undress.
Shouko, you...
I'm wearing my best underwear today.
We're screwed!
They wouldn't even care about undressing!
Oh.
You're going to play a King, and I'm going to call Doubt on it.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Checkmate
D-Doubt.
Faster, Akihisa! They'll be right after us!
I don't want to be an internet idol!
Hey! No running in the halls!
Please help us!
Give us supplementary lessons... anything!
What are you two doing dressed like that?
We'll explain later!
Too late, Akihisa! They're here!
Please wait, Akihisa-kun!
You have to hurry up and put these on!
You won't escape.
How do they manage to get themselves into these situations?
【Question 4】
Answer the following question.
『What is the chemical formula for Benzene?』
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
『 C  H 』
Teacher's comment:
Maybe this was too easy.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
『Ben + zene = Benzene』
Teacher's comment:
You're not taking Chemistry seriously, are you?
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
『B-E-N-Z-E-N』
Teacher's comment:
Baka to Test!
Come to my office with Tsuchiya later.
Huh?!
A trial run of the Summoning System?
New system
Trial run of the Summoning System!
Yes, I want all of you to test it out.
But why us?
Trial run of the Summoning System!
You're the best ones to do it.
Higher scores would only make things worse if something were to go wrong.
Flashback
I gotcha.
Things did  go pretty crazy last time.
I'd rather that you hadn't reminded me...
Trial run of the Summoning System!
But that's the gist of it, yes.
So neither Class A nor Himeji will be participating.
Trial run of the Summoning System!
But I'd really like to help out.
Too bad...
In that case, I guess we're stuck.
Thank you for the offer.
Trial run of the Summoning System!
So, will you help me with this?
Man, that sounds like such a hassle.
Trial run of the Summoning System!
Annoyed
Being Punishment Inspector sucks enough as it is, and now this too?
Trial run of the Summoning System!
And who was the moron that was running around the halls in his underwear?
I'm sorry.
Anyway, I don't expect you to do it for free.
New system
Trial run of the Summoning System!
How about if I give you meal vouchers and library cards for your trouble?
New system
Fumizuki Academy Meal Voucher
Today's Special
11-8-15
12:12
¥500-
Fumizuki Academy Meal Voucher
Today's Special
11-8-15
12:12
¥500-
Fumizuki Academy Meal Voucher
Today's Special
11-8-15
12:12
¥500-
Fumizuki Academy Meal Voucher
Today's Special
11-8-15
12:12
¥500-
Wow
New system
Trial run of the Summoning System!
Wow
New system
Trial run of the Summoning System!
Wow
New system
Trial run of the Summoning System!
Wow
New system
Trial run of the Summoning System!
All right, then.  I'll set up a field that covers the whole school building for the trial.
The participants will be...
Tsuchiya,
Trial run of the Summoning System!
Kinoshita,
Shimada,
Yoshii,
and Sakamoto.
Trial run of the Summoning System!
That'll be all.
Hang on a minute, you old hag.
Trial run of the Summoning System!
My points should still be pretty high.
I really don't care what happens to you.
Hey!
New system
Trial run of the Summoning System!
Why us?
I know.
It's all right!
Let's just get on with it!
Let's see...
We just need to test them out, right?
I guess so...
Okay.
Well then...
Summon!
Since it's only a trail run, I guess that wearing our school uniforms makes sense.
I don't have my weapon.
It's so cute!
It reminds me of being a first year.
Huh?
The Summoned Beings are speaking.
The old hag did say that there'd be improvement in controllability.
But honestly,
what else could I have done this morning?
Huh? Hideyoshi?
Did something happen this morning?
I didn't say anything.
Who would've thought,
that some neighborhood boy from middle school would've confessed his love to me?
Huh?!
Kinoshita-kun, have you become so popular that boys from outside of school confess to you?!
O-Of course not! I'm a guy-
It's the third time this month.
The Being is revealing all of its Summoner's secrets.
We never get to hear him talk about things like that.
Kinoshita's got a really good poker face.
No, no... listen.
I always act like-
She complimented my acting! I'm so happy!
I really am  happy about it.
Hey, Muttsurini-kun...
What?
I've always got time to hear about sex.
I don't mind... but right now I've got something little different on my mind, okay?
I'm only interested in what's under your shorts!
Smack
It really does  say what you think!
It's so funny!
Smack
It's not!
I want to see under your shorts.
Smack
Stop hitting me on the head.
He sure is honest, huh?
Maybe I should have a little fun with this...
Wouldn't you like to know what's under my skirt?
I'm not interested in-
My desire to know about skirts never ceases...
It's the place where romance, dreams,
and hopes all come together.
Tight, mini, long, flared, and pleated skirts each hold their own charms within.
But culottes really shouldn't be
considered skirts, in my opinion.
Nope, not interested.
So they really are revealing your thoughts, huh?
Huh? I can touch Minami's Summoned Being?
Man, this is nuts.
Aki, hand her over.
No, I wanna stay with Aki!
It's even disobeying its Summoner!
They're just like children, expressing their true feelings.
I see... like children, huh?
Aki, gimme a hug!
Don't ask him to hug you!
Get off of him!
I don't wanna!
Calm down, Minami.
It's okay, I'm used to it.
Huh, what do you mean?
Kids just seem to like me for some reason.
Because you're on their level mentally.
Shut up, Yuuji.
Hey, you know what, Aki?
What is it?
I'm always mean to you...
but I really lo-
No!
What do you think you're saying to him?!
Aki, are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Listen to your master!
I'm sorry.
Let me make this clear, Aki...
I don't have anything to hide from-
Actually, a girl in our grade confessed yesterday that-
No!
T-That's low, Aki!
I can't believe that you'd try and use her to hear my secrets!
She just came out with it...
Don't try to deny it!
Summon your  being and have it reveal all of your  secrets!
There's no way that I can let my secrets get out like everyone else's.
I need to think of something.
So, they speak your true feelings...
What is it, Himeji-san?
Oh, no... nothing!
By the way, how do you pronounce this?
Kakusa Mondai
Social Inequality
Umm...
Kaku-sa mon-dai, I think.
Yep, that'll do it!
Kakusa Mondai
Huh?! Why?!
Social Inequality
Summon
Goddamn it!
I'm sorry, Akihisa-kun.
But I have to know your true feelings.
Nice job, Mizuki.
Now, out with it, Aki!
Who do you like?
I need to distract him!
Goddamnit!
I should've known that idiot would be useless.
You're one to talk!
What?!
Hey, you two...
Be... care... ful...
I usually wear shorts...
but I don't  have them on today.
What are you say-
Let me see underneath!
-ing, Kudou-san?
Yeah, don't bother trying-
Hang on! Me first!
-to taunt us!
Aki, come here for a minute.
Akihisa-kun, we need to talk.
Yuuji.
Please Stand By
Please stand by.
That's for having such dirty minds.
Now think about what you've done.
I'm not wearing shorts either.
I'm sorry!
I just felt like teasing you a little.
You're so cruel, Kudou-san!
Please try and consider the circumstances!
And just so you know, I overslept today...
so didn't have time to put a bra on...
Please just spare us, already!
What's this about your bra?!
Yuuji.
It isn't what you think, Shouko!
It's just a guy's instincts.
Squish
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Aren't you happy?
L-Like this'd make me...
...happy!
Man, what a perv.
You're so lucky, Yuuji!
I'm so jealous of you!
I'm so  jealous!
That's just my  personality.
Please Stand By
Please stand by.
We're just trying to say that there's a proper way to go about these things.
Do you understand?
Yes.
It's true, Aki.
You need to take it slowly,
so that both sides are sure of their feelings-
Aki and I love each-
Akihisa-kun...
W-What is it, Himeji-san?
I know this is a bit sudden, but...
Is there someone that you like, Akihisa-kun?
Huh? Why do you ask?
I should've known.
You're really dense when it comes to questions like these.
Huh? What?
Then let me rephrase it.
I've got a plan!
Akihisa-kun, who do you like?
I kind of like Summon from Class G.
Huh? Her name's Summon?
Now, let's keep on talking about who we like, shall we?
That's so unfair, Akihisa-kun!
Is it possible that you have a secret or two of your own, Himeji-san?
I-It's all right!
I have nothing to hide-
Actually, just now...
when you were having dirty thoughts...
I couldn't help but think of some strange things as well...
No!
How's it goin-
How do they manage...
...to get themselves into these situations?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) den (Po!) kyuu (Pa!) pikkanko (Hai)
閃いて (Pa!) 輝いて (Pi!) 電 (Po!) 球 (Pa!) ぴっかんこ （はいっ）
Flashing (Pa!) Sparkling (Pi!) light (Po!) bulb (Pa!) That's right (Yes)
shinten shinaiyo
進展しないよ
I can't move ahead,
dare ka jyama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
because someone is hindering me... No, no!
zenzen tarinai sorega mondai no koubaisuu
ぜんぜん足りない　それが問題の公倍数
Nothing that I do is enough, which is an all too common problem.
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I will come to understand it.
naniga hontou no koto... Baby?
何が本当のこと... Baby?
What is the truth of it... Baby?
mitetara kokode zukai shite yo Baby!
見てたらここで図解してよBaby！
If we were to see each other, I would draw you a schematic of it, baby!
kotobamo kazumo kimi wo arasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
I wouldn't show you words or numbers.
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to (kyuuu Paaaaaan!) N no jiryoku de
心がビリビリする  S と（きゅーっ　Paaaaaan!） N の磁力で
Our hearts are flittering about from the
magnetic force of the North and South Poles.
S, S, Super kuttsuite Number I say No.1 boy!
(S, S, Super くっついて Number I say No.1 boy!)
S, S, Super numbers close together. I say No.1 boy!
omedetou!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ima kara kimi wa my, ma, my otakara
いまから君は My, ma, my ゛お-た-か-ら゛
From now on, you're my, my, my "treasure."
tokubetsu nanda dounattemo
特別なんだどうなっても
Just for you, no matter what happens,
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I will hold you tightly, tightly and never let go.
watashi wa koishitai yume ni kenkai wa iranai
私は恋したい　夢に限界はいらない
I want to be in love, and dreams have no need for boundaries, so...
tokubetsu dayone acchattamon
特別だよね　会っちゃったもん
just for me, since we met here by chance...
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
you will forgive me, won't you?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) sei (Po!) kai (Pa!) pittanko (gyuu)
閃いた (Pa!)　輝いた (Pi!) 正　(Po!)　解　(Pa!)　ぴったんこ（ぎゅっ）
It flashed (Pa!) It sparkled (Po!) right (Po!) answer (Pa!) That's right (Embrace)
You wanted to talk to me?
Um...
I am the Class E representative, Nakabayashi.
I called you here to
tell you about my fuzzy feelings...
I called you here to tell you about my fuzzy feelings...
I called you here to
tell you about my fuzzy feelings...
No, fuzzy isn't right. Painful?
No, fuzzy isn't right.
Painful? Worrisome? No...
Setsunasa and Monmon
(=)
Samon or Summon
No, fuzzy isn't right.
Painful? Worrisome? No...
Worrisome?
No, fuzzy isn't right.
Painful? Worrisome? No...
No... I can't describe it very well...
No, fuzzy isn't right.
Painful? Worrisome? No...
I can't describe it very well,
but I have to tell you about my feelings.
Are you busy right now?
No, I'm free.
Go ahead and tell me.
Daijoubu sa and Mondai
(=)
Samon or Summon
No, I'm free.
Go ahead and tell me.
I want you to go out with me!
How is it that possible that Yoshii-kun is so innocent and adorable?
His actions, speech, and demeanor...
Are all so lovely!
Hew hew.
Nakabayashi-san...
Um, yes?
Please forgive me.
I don't want to accept such an insulting rejection!
【Question 5】
Answer the following
question.
State the correct way to
treat a burn.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
『Cool with water quickly.』
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Just as expected, Himeji.
For areas that can't be cooled
with running water, place a clean towel over the affected area and pour water over it. In the case of frostbite or extremely severe burns, cover the area with a clean towel and take the victim to the hospital.
towel over the affected area and pour water
over it. In the case of frostbite or extremely
severe burns, cover the area with a clean
towel and take the victim to the hospital.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
Teacher's comment:
Next Episode
Question #5...
State the correct way to treat a burn.
『Pay them hush money.』
Pay them hush money.
Not that kind of burn.
Next episode!
"Me and a Peeping Tom and Training Camp!"
Me and a Peeping Tom and
Training Camp!
This will be on your test.