Meet Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
The other day,
a substitute for Ms. Oshige came.
But this guy was such a clumsy person.
Everything he did was
full of mistakes!
Looks like Full Moon had a pretty
tough time
being dragged around
to all these places.
At the end,
he quit his job as a manager,
so Mitsuki had to go all the way
to the train station to bring him back.
I'm so exhausted from
being dragged around too.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Hey, Meroko.
Which sandals should I bring tomorrow?
If I were you,
I think I'd go for the pink ones.
You think so too?
But the ones with ribbons are cute too.
Aren't they?!
Well then, why don't you
take both of them?
You're right!
That's much better than
regretting it later!
Sure!
It's work, right?
Then it doesn't matter which it is!
But it's my first overnight assignment!
It's totally not the same!
You really don't get it!
Okay, okay.
Fine, I don't get it at all.
Oh yes!
Takuto, you don't get it, do you?
Girls are always dreaming
of meeting a lovely prince!
Huh? A prince?
For this prince that she might
meet at any moment,
girls always want to be
in their best attire.
Right, little Mitsuki?
"Little"?
Oh, that aside, I'm not staying home
when you're gone overnight, right?
Right, I told grandma that I'd be visiting
a summer house of my friend from school.
That's good.
After this much excitement,
- Is that how it is?
- if I were left behind,
I would cry!
Her First Kiss?
I'm taking off now.
Take care of yourself.
Okay!
Mitsuki.
Take this with you.
The letter is for your friend's parents.
Have the sweets with your friends.
Yes.
The path to love is too faraway.
I can't waste my time any longer.
- Non! Non!
In dreams it's a different world...
Wow... I'm going to be singing here.
I've seen this on TV,
but everyone in the audience
are actually in their swimsuits.
I can wear my favorite clothes every day.
Hey, when is her turn coming?
I believe it'll be soon.
- No, I'm going to drown!
- H-Hey, Meroko!
I'll be drowning in
the stream of love!
Hey! Cut it out!
Thank you so much.
That was THE SCANTY, everyone.
Next, as you all know, is Full Moon.
The song is "Myself."
- Here she is!
- Hey, what are we gonna do this year?
Why don't we see how things
go for a little longer?
How many more are performing?
Three more.
What? It's almost over?
So, let's do it when we are
done checking everyone.
That's true.
Be quiet!
What is it, Murakami?
A distant place
was where I belonged.
I found a loneliness in
your eyes that day
Hey, cut it out!
Meroko, it's her song!
Listen to it!
I'm listening!
You liar!
Good job.
Thank you, you too.
Let's work together again soon.
Oh yes, can you go ahead and
go back to the hotel first?
You know the place, yes?
Yes, it's that one, right?
Huh?
Oh, no... It's that one, right?
Since you have no sense of direction,
you most definitely have to take a taxi.
All right.
All right, I'll catch up with you very soon.
Okay.
It's not that far away,
so once in a while,
maybe I should go for a little walk.
Yeah, she was talking like it's a big deal.
We can even see the hotel from here.
Yes.
Don't get lost after saying that, okay?
No no!
If she lives like a girl kept in cotton wool,
she won't even be able to fall in love!
Love?!
Yeah! When do you think this is?!
It's summer!
Summer is a season for love, isn't it?!
Right, Mitsuki?!
Oh?!
Mitsuki! Where are you?
What a pleasant wind!
Oh, wait... There's a cute girl.
Good, good.
How about this girl then?
I'd say good, good, eh?
Where are you going?
Are you alone?
You've some time to spare, right?
Hey, play with us.
No...
What? What? What did you say?
I couldn't hear that!
Stop it.
It's all right!
Come on, come on, let's go.
No!
Mitsuki!
Come on, let's do something fun.
What? But...
It's your first time here, right?
We know a fun place to go.
Why don't we go there together?
What are you doing?!
Oww!
What are you doing, fooling around?
Do you guys want to go through
the same thing you did the last time?
Damn! Why are you here?!
Crap! I'll remember this!
Are you okay?
What?!
Y-Yes, I'm fine!
Thank you very much!
It's unsafe for a girl to be walking alone.
I'll escort you home.
What? But I'm...I'm really fine!
Really?
Huh?!
Okay.
Well then, please.
What, what?!
Hey, that is looking good!
Like a good feeling for
something to start up, eh?
So, I'll take off here.
Thank you so much for escorting me!
I'd like to return this favor somehow.
It wasn't a big deal.
I just did what anyone would do.
But...
Well, will you have
a cup of tea with me?
What?
Well...
Is it okay?
Yes...
Great! Shall we go then?
Awesome, awesome!
Isn't it, Takuto?
What?
Looks like it's gonna bud!
A love affair in a summer resort!
So wonderful.
Once she has a boyfriend,
Takuto will be entirely mine!
I will totally back up their love!
What?!
You were listening to today's show ?!
Yes, I was surprised by
how amazing the song was.
My heart is still pounding from it.
I feel a bit embarrassed.
Come on now!
Let's leave things to
the young ones here, and let's go. Yes?
Really?
So this Eichi is a really
important person to you.
Yes, I am singing to meet Eichi.
How romantic.
Just the fact that there is a girl with
such a pure heart like you, Full Moon,
makes me happy.
What?
I want to help you find Eichi too.
Thank you.
You're so late!
Takuto?
What is it with that guy?
He was all over you.
Takuto, what are you talking about?
Yeah!
Don't ever see him again.
- Huh?
Why are you making such
a demand, Takuto?
Whatever, it doesn't matter!
Mr. Murakami is my friend, okay?
Are you telling me that
I can't make friends?
Beyond what I tell you,
you trust a stranger from out of nowhere?
Why are you saying such things?!
Mr. Murakami said that
he'd help me find Eichi!
He's a really nice person!
Eichi again?
That's all you ever think about!
See! You get so mad
about me mentioning Eichi.
Mr. Murakami isn't like that!
Oh really?
Well, I can't help being mad!
I'm completely different
from that guy, Murakami!
What's that?
Why are you so mad?!
Well, seems like I am no use in here.
Takuto!
Wait, Takuto! Where are you going?
Takuto! Takuto!
Jeez! What's he so mad about?
Mitsuki!
We have today off, so you can go out
and have fun today!
Okay.
Hey, hey.
Don't you waste your day off!
You've got all my support!
Support for what?
It's okay. It's okay.
Takuto didn't come back after all.
I wanted to make up with him.
Such nice weather.
All right! Let's go look for
the guy from yesterday!
Huh? Who's yesterday's guy?
You forgot already?
It's Murakami, Murakami!
What?
Hey, nice to see you again.
Oh, Mr. Murakami...
Do you have the day off today?
Then I can give you
a little tour around this place.
Would you like to ride on a yacht?
What?! A yacht?
All right! Please take me there!
Really?!
Great! Then let's get going.
Okay.
Wow!
Over there, you can see the Whale Rock.
And over there, you can see
a hazy Gekkou Island.
I see.
It looks so clear with this nice weather.
You must have brought it
with your good deeds.
Huh?
KASAI
Takuto, they're out on the ocean now!
Finally, we are all alone!
Shall we enjoy our summer vacation?
Shall we?
What are you talking about?
We're working, aren't we?
Jeez, how boring.
What?!
THINGS TO BE WARY OF TODAY
- PORK BONE SOUP
- YACHTS
THAT IS ALL FOR TODAY
THINGS TO BE WARY OF TODAY
- PORK BONE SOUP
- YACHTS
THAT IS ALL FOR TODAY
No way!
Takuto! They were saying that
they'd be on a yacht, right?!
I forgot!
What are you talking about?
The Handbook tells us to be on the yacht!
What?!
What?
Like I said, just wait! I'm almost there!
Are you sure?
If you can't kiss her before noon today,
your yacht is ours!
I assure you that
it's going to work out!
There isn't a girl that
won't fall for me!
Don't forget to film it for proof!
I know! Talk to you later.
All right.
That Murakami always does it.
Every single year, he picks up
young idols and makes them cry.
Can't blame them for being
deceived by his looks.
Totally, he looks like
a perfectly innocent guy.
Yeah.
Wow, there are so many fish!
How is it? Are you having fun?
Yes!
I'm so happy to be spending time
with you alone.
Really? I am also happy because
it's the first time I've been on a yacht.
Great.
Anyhow, when are you leaving,
Full Moon?
Tomorrow, as soon as
I am done with work.
Oh, so I won't be able to see you again.
I'm going to be so lonely.
Oh...
Now she's mine.
Oh...I found a shell!
Oh, so pretty.
Amazing! It's shining like a rainbow!
Huh? Did something happen
to you, Mr. Murakami?
No! Nothing! I'm totally fine!
Where are you, Mitsuki?!
She won't be able to hear you!
But what else can I do?
Just search around!
I'll look for her over there,
so you go that way!
Roger!
I have to hurry, it'll be noon soon.
I don't want to let you go.
What?
Mr. Murakami?
Full Moon...
Umm... That's a problem.
So kiss me!
What?!
I won't let you go back
unless you kiss me.
N-No way!
I'm sorry. Please let me go back.
Full Moon!
Yes!
Full Moon...
What?! A kiss?
Mr. Murakami is trying to kiss me?!
Oh no. My first kiss is...
Full Moon? Are you being shy?
You're so cute.
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
Eichi!
Full Moon...
Jeez, don't make me worry like this!
Takuto!
What are you doing?!
Didn't I tell you?
Don't trust a guy like this!
I'm sorry.
Here!
Take my hand! We're going back!
Okay!
Hold on tight, all right?!
- Oh!
- Wow!
Did I just bump into...
Her face...
Takuto's lips?
There you are!
Mitsuki!
Are you okay?!
Oh?
What? You were here already, Takuto?!
Whatever. Just help me down here!
Oh right. Here!
Hey, hey...
Don't tell me we have to
row from here on.
But I couldn't think of any other way.
Oh, here he comes!
He's really sound asleep.
Just leave him alone.
Is he okay?
Won't he catch a cold?
He'll be all right.
Murakami!
Hey, wake up, Murakami!
Who's she?
Don't know.
Where is this? Who am I?
What are you talking about!
You liar!
Natsumi!
How dare you lie to me?
You said you'll never date another girl
again in your life!
That was...
Hey, you there!
Don't ever trust this guy.
What? What do you mean?
This jerk! He boasts that he can
have any idol that he lays his eyes on!
What?!
He doesn't even mind paying scumbags
to get them to bother girls!
Right?
What?! Right!
Scumbags?! So those men were...
So that was a trap!
I bet you made a bet with your friends
that you'll be able to kiss her
before the end of the day
or something, didn't you?!
Is that true, Mr. Murakami?!
What a jerk! A girl's enemy!
Mitsuki...
You're the worst jerk!
H-Hey!
Yikes!
You won't get away with it that easily!
H-Help! I can't swim!
How pathetic.
Good for him!
Girls are scary.
I believed that he was a nice person.
You trust people too easily, silly.
What do you mean "silly"?!
I'm okay with that! I don't care
even if I get tricked.
I don't want to be someone
who always doubts others.
Hey you!
Hey you! Are you listening to me?
- Come on, it's okay.
- Shut up!
Hey, you little midget!
That was an accident, right?
No! It was definitely an accident!
Oh, I can't stand it!
Who does she think she is?!
Why're you so worked up, Meroko?
Do you remember Madoka Wakamatsu?
She lost to Mitsuki
in the Seed Records audition.
She's begun a serious rivalry
and she's so awful!
Hey, aren't we with her today?
Will things be okay?
Well, don't you worry.
Meroko here will be sure
to protect Mitsuki.
That's the thing I'm most worried about.
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Rival Appears"
- Look forward to it!