A Selfish Skit.
Hey, play the idiot.
You first, idiot!
We can't have everyone play the straight man!
You're being Selfish.
You're one to talk!
Thank you very much.
What a dud.
You're the one who asked us to entertain you...
Maybe I should smack her upside the head.
Don't.
She's King Selfish's daughter.
That girl was much more entertaining...
Precure Heart Shoot!
Cure Heart...
I'll make you mine!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Regina's Fierce Attack!
Mana Belongs to Me
Work keeps you pretty busy, Makopi.
Yeah.
The movie received good reviews,
so now I'm working on...
Hi, Mana!
Regina?!
Sorry for our little spat last time.
If a "sorry" could cut it, we wouldn't need Precures!
What are you plotting now?
I just can't stop thinking about Mana.
So...
I'll let you be my friend!
Friend?
You'll let her?
Aren't you happy?
Why would she be happy?
Precure Love Link!
I will not forgive you!
You mad or something?
Of course I'm mad!
The Trump Kingdom...
my homeland was destroyed!
Do I look like I care?
Besides, I didn't do that, Daddy did.
Why you...
Stop!
Mana, move.
Look, let's just calm down. Please?
Before somebody comes...
Makoto, just go back to normal for now.
Mana.
You and I are friends.
Got it?
Sure.
Let's be friends.
Wait, Mana!
Why?
When you say you'll be friends,
you aren't serious, are you?
I am.
I think it'd be nice if we were friends.
Makopi?
I can't believe you...
She's our enemy!
Didn't you see it?
Trump Kingdom was in ruins!
Yeah.
But somehow...
I feel that Regina's different.
Different how?
She's King Selfish's daughter!
That's true, but... uh...
I can't really hate her...
Makopi!
Wait!
I have no idea what's gotten into your head.
M-Makopi...
Mana, let's just go to school.
Bye, Regina.
Bye!
Now Makopi totally hates me...
Can you blame her?
You should know how she feels.
Of course she'd be mad.
So why befriend her?
Well...
Hi!
Regina?
Something wrong?
Let's go play, Mana!
I-I can't!
I have class now...
Aw, just skip those dumb classes.
Hey, I can't just...
Morning, class.
What?
It's stuck!
Now you can't have class!
Nooooooo!
Excuse me, I have to use the bathroom!
You can't come to school!
But I did it for you.
Playing's way more fun than studying.
So I did that for you!
Aren't you happy?
No, no, no, no, no!
Look, I can't play now!
We'll talk when school is over.
Please?
Fine, if you say so.
Can we stop by the student council room?
There are some papers I'd like to get signed.
Gotcha.
Mana!
School's out!
Let's play!
We're going to the student council room, so wait a bit more.
I'm not waiting.
I'll handle it for you!
Hold on!
What do you mean by "handle?"
Erasing the school!
All the boring junk'll be gone once it's gone,
and then you could play with me right now!
No, no, no!
Absolutely not!
Why can't I?
I'm doing it for you.
Oh, is that so?
If you were really her friend, you'd respect her—
Nobody asked you.
Rikka?
Let's go!
Mana!
Geez!
Hurry up!
I'm hurrying, geez!
Are you sure?
Just go.
Where should we go?
Huh? Weren't we going where you wanted to go?
Nah, we can go somewhere you want.
O-Okay...
then I'll show you around town.
Okay!
Ain't it easy?
Well, I suppose...
Whatcha doin'?
Picking up trash.
Oh, there's more.
I'll help you!
Ta-dah!
It's all clean!
Mana and Regina are friends?
It seems quite puzzling.
Is Mana all right?
Of course she is!
Why are you here?
Regina said she was thirsty,
so I said that Alice's homemade black tea was delicious.
Now.
Make it.
Since you're a friend of Mana's, I'll pour you some delicious tea.
Please wait a moment.
Aww, but I wanna drink it now!
You can't rush flavor.
The black tea leaves need time to steam,
and the cup needs time to warm...
Who's the baby?
Her name's Ai.
So cute!
You can play with her.
Charles, if you'd please.
Okay!
Charurles!
What're you staring at?
Get back to my tea.
Huh?
Oh, certainly.
Hey, have you talked to Makopi since this morning?
She seems busy with work...
I see...
Don't start getting friendly with my Mana.
Your Mana?
She doesn't belong to you!
And I've known Mana since we were kids, which is longer than—
I'm Mana's friend here.
So...
consider yourself fired.
Huh?!
Rikka...
Let's go, Mana!
Regina, the tea will be ready...
Don't need it!
Sorry, girls!
What was that?
It seems her usual tactics won't work here.
Makopi!
If you miss Makopi that much,
shouldn't you stop trying to be friends with Regina?
I can't do that!
Why is that?
Regina said we were friends,
and I don't think she was lying...
And the thought of being her friend gave me goose bumps!
Goose bumps? How so?
You must be clear with Makoto about what you think.
Oh, how do I put it?
Either way, the fact is that she sides with the people who destroyed Trump Kingdom.
It's no surprise that Makopi won't forgive her.
So, I really can't be friends with an enemy?
I wouldn't say you can't...
But I believe it would be very difficult.
I wonder what Makopi's doing...
If you're curious, how about we go and see her?
Really?
In that case...
Here.
Can you give this to Makopi?
Okay.
Hi, Mana!
Oh, Regina.
Let's go eat something tasty!
Rikka, Alice, please—
Yummy!
Mana, this is super yummy!
I know!
This shop has the best ice cream in town!
You're my friend for a reason. You're useful!
Well, I'd rather you call me "reliable."
The other flavors are yummy, too.
Rikka likes chocolate chip,
Alice likes mint,
and Makopi likes berry flavor.
Why?
You're my friend, aren't you?
So why do you think about other people?
Well, I...
Your only friend is me!
I'm the only one you have to think about!
You don't need other people.
Wait, hold on!
That's too self—
I know!
I'll just erase what you don't need!
Regina!
Refreshing!
Okay, cut!
Good work!
Let's take a break!
No calls from Mana.
Did I ask if there were?
Makopi?
Here, a refreshment.
It's Mana's homemade omelette rice.
And why isn't the person who made it here?
Well...
She's with Regina, isn't she?
I don't get Mana.
We don't really get it either.
Mana doesn't get it herself, after all.
She just had a hunch that Regina really wanted to be friends.
Mana's hunches have never been something to sneeze at.
She tried to scold that crab Selfish when she first met it, after all.
Instead of using her head,
she prefers to trust her feelings and follow her heart.
But it's King Selfish's daughter we're talking about,
so I don't think it'll end that well.
Are you not worried about her too, Makoto?
Found ya!
Regina!
I'm the only friend Mana needs!
Refreshments from the sponsor!
I'll turn you into a splendid Selfish!
Selfreshment!
You're all in the way, so get lost.
A Selfish appeared!
The girls!
Selfish!
Let's go, girls!
Rachel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Have a refreshment!
Drink it all!
You're not gonna drink my juice?!
It's not very refreshing if you force it down our throats!
It's certainly selfish.
Really, how self-centered!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Self!
Girls!
Hey, Mana!
See, I'm willing to do so much for you!
Now it's your turn.
Quit being friends with these girls for me.
Got it?
No.
Say something?
I won't leave them!
I'll never stop being their friend!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Oh poor refreshment who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
You drink, too!
Selfish!
Girls!
Mana, that was your fault!
Those poor girls!
It wasn't Mana's fault...
We're Mana's real friends...
We're the ones who wanted to be with her!
We ourselves wished to be by Mana's side!
Hardships like this are nothing we weren't prepared for!
Diamond!
Rosetta!
So annoying.
Get lost!
Refreshments... drink up!
Regina, you're wrong!
Wanting to erase the people I hold dear...
isn't something a friend would ever do!
Why are you opposing me?
Why won't you do as I say?
We're friends!
It's because we're friends!
I truly want to be your friend, so I'm being honest,
and I'm doing everything I can to right your wrongs!
I'm not listening!
Seeelf!
Listen to her!
Friends should always listen to each other!
Sword!
Geez!
Don't you dare scold me!
Heart, let's go!
We're ready, too!
Indeed!
Diamond, Rosetta!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Love love loooooove!
Huh?
Regina, let's be real friends.
What's that?
I don't get you!
You still want to be friends with Regina?
Even I have my doubts,
but I just don't think she's rotten to the core.
When I saw her smile...
I felt that she wasn't.
But I know that you have every right to be mad!
And I'll do anything I can to help Trump Kingdom!
So... well...
I will never forgive Regina.
Even if she's your friend.
But that's just how I feel, okay?
Real friends are honest with each other, right?
So I just tried being honest.
Makopi!
Also, there was way too much omelette rice.
I can't eat that alone!
I made too much on accident...
Will you help me eat it?
I can't believe her!
She tried to scold me?
But...
Let's be real friends.
What is a real friend?
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
I'll take the whole crystal for myself!
Why, Regina?
Dokidoki Precure:
Shock!
The Stolen Crystal!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!