That's impossible...
She's dead.
I killed her.
But yet, I still...
...hope she's alive,
so that I can be forgiven.
Elen...
Tell me what's going on.
Four from the trade last time, and one from today.
Muroto, the one who was killed today,
was a man who I have known since his youth.
So what the hell happened?
Depending on the answer...
Shiga, you're allowed to fire.
Lizzie.
Please calm down and think about it, Mr. Godoh.
If we start a quarrel here,
it'll only make the murderer who killed Mr. Muroto happy.
Didn't you order it?
I don't mind if you suspect me.
But if you're going to shoot, please be prepared for the consequences.
Claudia...
You probably have another way out of this instead of us killing each other.
If we let this slip for now and you follow my instructions...
I'll find the person behind it in three days and hand him over to you.
Then let me have a look at the way Inferno compensates.
Counter-snipe?
Yes.
You're kidding.
In two days, the Godoh Group will be invited to Inferno's executive meeting.
And with that, they'll be officially affiliated.
After being affiliated, even Wisemel won't be able to lay a hand on them.
To them, this is their final chance.
As I thought, you're still suspecting Wisemel.
Regarding the attack last time and the murder of Muroto,
he's the only person that would benefit from them.
The place is the 5th floor of the Atrium Hotel.
It's a conference room with one wall of glass.
Displaying the prey on the showcase, huh?
And you'll ambush that place.
Even now, you still want to use the Godoh Group as bait?
If this succeeds, everything will be fine.
Of course, this is a dangerous gamble that won't succeed without you,
Phantom.
Oh, he's back!
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Wait a bit, I'll go warm up the soup.
Cal.
I found it when I was cleaning.
Did you disassemble it?
Sorry, I'll put it back together right away.
Are you good with machinery?
I usually have fun by disassembling whatever I have my hands on.
I just want to know how it works.
All right, done!
Put it back where you found it.
Okay.
Work?
Yeah, come and give me some ideas.
Okay! Okay!
What is it?
The target's on the 5th floor of this building.
If someone were to snipe the target from here...
You're shooting?
No, not me, it's another sniper.
I'm just predicting where that sniper will shoot from.
It can't be just anywhere.
The sniping spot must fulfill some conditions.
Conditions?
The spot must be of a certain height,
and it mustn’t attract attention.
You mean like the roof of a building?
Yeah.
Then what about here?
No, that's too close.
There's no point in sniping if they're going to get discovered.
The spot must be at least 400 yards away.
400 yards? Can you even hit at such a distance?
If you have the right equipment and skill,
you can even hit up to 800 yards.
But that makes the number of buildings too big to pick a specific one...
Yeah, there are too many places.
This is your homework before bed.
Let's have dinner first.
How's that going?
Everything's ready.
Just leave it to me.
Don't fail.
If you do, your balls will be cut off.
Yes, sir.
What's wrong?
Hey, Reiji...
Don't you think sniping from a high place is annoying?
Why?
When you shoot, it feels annoying when your angle of depression is too big.
Did I say something strange?
No, you didn't.
Sniping like that really is difficult.
That means we can kind of exclude places that are too high.
The spot must be on the same level as the target,
and hopefully with a clear shot.
If we consider that, there might be fewer spots than we thought.
Good answer.
Was I right?
What you said was correct.
Yay!
What we need to do now is to look for it tomorrow.
Come with me.
I can?
I'm going out with you?
This isn't for fun.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Muroto's body was sent back to Japan on the last flight.
At the same time, Tsuzuki and Kakinuma are bringing more men here.
What about their guns?
Giuseppe is preparing them.
They'll probably be ready tomorrow...
That German?
Gifted Scotch again?
Yeah, have a drink too.
I'll help myself.
Damn that Muroto...
How could he leave so much to drink?
Not just him. There were Hamura and Shinjou too.
Five of my men died in a foreign country...
Hundreds of millions are involved.
It's only natural that it turned into a war.
They'd understand, too.
Like I said...
I'm mad at myself because I didn't even provide Muroto with a single pistol in this situation.
I'm definitely going to make Inferno settle this.
About that, I suspect that that Claudia woman is behind it.
Tell me about that.
We know the tricks that she has been using.
When her goal is complete, she'll probably want to abandon us, right?
Shiga, regarding this event, that woman is innocent.
Do you have proof?
Proof, huh?
Shiga, what's the tattoo I have on my back?
A five-colored jewel and an ascending dragon.
The dragon on my back is roaring.
That woman has the same dragon on her back.
She lives with the same spirit as me.
Holding a jewel and ascending toward heaven.
She's that type of dragon.
Only people of the same type would understand.
Just leave it to that woman for now.
This isn't something that can be explained with words.
Shiga, I count on your intelligence a lot.
So in return, believe in my instincts.
If that's what you say...
I'll just protect you from behind.
You're finally here.
All right, so what are you going to do, Inferno?
We're going.
Sorry, I'm coming right now.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance to be going out with you.
Let's go.
That's the target building.
We'll list the possibilities based on the conditions,
and after a thorough inspection, we'll pinpoint the spot.
How?
We'll look for weather vanes.
Weather vanes?
Even a professional would make preparations for a complicated sniping like this.
Especially in an area with so many buildings.
Wind.
Correct, strong wind will ruin the shot.
When shooting, the sniper must watch the wind direction.
But you can't see wind...
Oh, I get it!
Snipers will prepare weather vanes like this at different points.
Then we just need to find a spot with these pieces of cloth and flags sticking out unnaturally...
Correct.
Cal.
Sorry, no discoveries here.
Same here.
Then let's move on.
I think this is enough for today.
Wait, Reiji.
Something's not right here...
Not right?
That.
Nice, Cal.
Bingo?
Yeah.
There's no doubt that their sniping spot is over there.
Hey, so you're going to snipe that sniper from here?
Yeah.
Could that sniper be Judy's killer?
Probably.
At the very least, they're part of the same group.
Let me witness it...
Let me witness the moment you shoot!
Death isn't something you should see.
Judy...
was killed right before my eyes.
Normally, the ideal situation is to have two people on a sniping mission.
Because in that case, the sniper will have support.
Supporting the sniper by observing the target and surroundings with a different scope.
They call one who does that an observer,
someone who witnesses everything.
Can you do it?
Yeah!
Cal, give me your hand.
Yes?
Your reward for today.
This is...
Thanks, Reiji!
I'll treat it with care.
I'll treat it with a lot of care...
...forever.
The enemy's over there and the sun is behind us.
They won't be able to see us because of the backlight.
Correct.
Clau, Wisemel's here.
I see.
But Randy Weber isn't here.
It's weird for him not to bring his right-hand man at such an important meeting.
What's he plotting?
It's the promised day.
I'm looking forward to seeing how that woman is going to settle this.
A white outfit plus a gun.
There's nothing more suitable to wear for barging into hell.
Let's go, Shiga.
All right, I'll follow you no matter where you go.
There's no one there, Reiji.
Could it be that the spot is somewhere else?
Calm down, there's still time left.
Welcome to Inferno.
There! Someone's there behind the water tower!
Target confirmed.
Can you see the person's face from where you are?
It's hidden, so I can't see...
I can't even tell if it's a man or a woman...
This is bad, Reiji!
That person is about to shoot! Hurry!
No,
it can't be her.
Reiji?
She's already dead...
I killed her...
Elen was...
Reiji?! Shoot!
Show me that face of yours!
Reiji?!
There he goes!
Reiji!
Did you get shot? Did you hit him?
No, it just scratched me.
Reiji, you idiot...
Why did you do that?
I had to see that person's face no matter what.
Idiot...
Good job, observer.
He's the one who killed Judy.
You've avenged her.
Now, the mastermind behind this is confirmed.
All that's left is...
You bastards...
What? What happened?
There's another sniper...
Don't tell me...
No way...
Mission completed.
Yes, Master.
I don't want to be separated.
I want to be together forever.
I want to help Reiji.
I want him to need me.