The blue sky stretches endlessly
As I hum a tune to keep me strong
I wonder if you can hear the voice?
Oh, it's Kenzaki Makoto!
The melody continues forever
I love this song!
Me too!
It's great, huh?
I hope the seeds that my words carry into your hearts
Makopi...
We're here!
What a splendid day to get together!
The cherry blossoms are in full bloom,
there's not a cloud in the sky,
and it's sunny and warm!
Nothing beats it!
Nothing!
Mana, don't get so worked up. It's weird.
But come on!
That very Makopi...
is right here!
Kenzaki doesn't look so thrilled herself, you know.
I suppose Mana can't help but be overjoyed at Makoto becoming her friend.
Totally!
My heart's beating out of my chest!
Hey now, settle down.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Solitaire
Here?
This is where the man who gave you the Lovies lives?
That's right.
What's his name?
Name?
What was it?
Dunno.
I'm sure that guy knows something.
About the Trump Kingdom's queen!
Good afternoon!
Mister, it's Mana!
Mister!
Hello?
It's Mana!
It seems he's not present.
The door wasn't locked.
Does he know how shops work?
Wow, look at all the Lovies!
They're pretty!
Found something neat?
This is...
Kyupirappa!
A Mysterious Baby is Born!!
It's a giant egg!
If we made omelette rice with it, we could feed ten people!
Omelette rice?
Come on, it's not an egg!
Even ostrich eggs are only this big.
Dino...
It might be a dinosaur egg!
Or maybe an alien's!
No way.
Come on out, now.
Just kidding.
A baby...
It seems it was a baby egg.
No way...
She's...
so cute!
Sure, she's cute,
but should that really be the first reaction you have?
She was born from an egg...
That's quite rare for a baby!
I think this is a step up from rare!
Aww, she's flying!
Very good!
Wait, that's a good thing?
Now, what about this shop's owner?
There, there.
I believe that baby chicks think of the first person they see as their mother.
So that's it!
Your mommy's name is Mana!
There's so much wrong with all this!
I don't even know what to say anymore!
Davi!
It's time, Makoto.
What must you do, Davi?
I'm sorry to say it, but Makoto and I will have to excuse ourselves.
We have work to do.
Makopi, you're going already?
Yes.
Goodbye.
I didn't talk much with Makopi.
Not much you can do.
She has a job.
Did you sigh because you didn't find any clues about the queen?
Huh?
We can just go again tomorrow.
True.
Then why did you sigh?
I was thinking about how close those girls were.
Those three have been friends for years.
But I'm different.
What?
You want to be their friend so much that you're overthinking it.
I'm not overthinking!
If you have something to say, just say it.
You'll be friends in a heartbeat once you do.
Look, that's not it!
Solitaire
There, there.
Hm?
What's wrong?
He must've gotten scared.
That's a...
Could it be?
A Cure Lovies!
Why does that baby have one?
She must have some connection to the Trump Kingdom!
What kinda connection's that?
Dunno.
Well, let's give this a try!
Charles!
A baby bottle!
She was simply thirsty.
She's really into it!
That's good.
You've got a full tummy, huh?
After you feed milk to a baby,
you have to burp them.
You're right, Rikka.
Your mother is a pediatrician,
so you must know much about infant care.
Like this?
That's it.
She did it!
An excellent burp indeed.
Good afternoon.
We let ourselves in.
Hi.
What brings you all here?
Well, you're one to ask!
What's with that egg?
I mean,
that baby!
This baby came out of the egg.
Hm, how should I put this...
don't you have to name her?
What should it be?
Huh?
She keeps saying "Aiai,"
so perhaps it should be Ai!
Ai, huh?
Sounds great!
What a heartwarming name!
Can you two focus?
She seems overjoyed!
It's a wonderful name!
Well, if she likes it...
Her name is Ai!
Noooooooooo!
Keep it down, Mammo...
My face, my beautiful face...
has a zit!
This is your fault!
You're always making a ruckus with your nighttime bowling,
and it keeps me up at night!
I need my beauty sleep!
You've got some nerve taking a nap after making sure nobody else can!
Bel's gone too.
Everyone's so selfish!
I'm so mad!
I've gotta make something go berserk!
Hewwo, Makopi!
I'm widdle Ai!
Naiche to meetchoo!
So?
Yeah...
Aww, what a cutie!
Naiche to meetchoo too!
Is what Makoto's thinking.
Wait, Davi!
Just speak your mind!
Ah, so Makopi fell for Ai's charm too!
You're so cute!
You're my sweetheart!
Wanna hold her?
I'll pass.
Oh, come on.
Hello there, miss.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Joe Okada.
Oh, your name's Joe?
Huh?
That's really your name?
I have to ask you something.
It's about the the Trump Kingdom's queen.
Do you know where she is?
Oh, a queen!
So you know?
Every girl in the world is a princess.
And you...
all of you are queens, in a way.
My apologies,
but I have business to attend to.
Look after Ai for me, okay?
Sure!
Wait!
He got away again.
What a nice stroll!
Stuck with all the work, again...
That's nothing out of the ordinary.
Hm?
What is it now?
Hey!
Upsy-daisy!
Too much upsy!
Wait!
Here's your milky.
Huh? That's not it?
If it's not food, try a diaper.
Huh?
There's no mess.
Wh-What do we do?
I know!
I'll sing a lullaby!
Gooooo to sleeeeeeep!
She's...
terrible!
Huh?
Why?
It's not a lullaby if it wakes the dead.
Though our diva doesn't seem to notice.
Aw, shut up...
And I was havin' such a nice nap...
Way to ruin my lunch break.
But I guess babies are born to cry.
And parks are for kids, anyway.
Aw, just sleep.
Who's there?
I'll turn your desire into a dream come true.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Selfiiiiiiish!
A Selfish!
It's okay, Ai.
I promise we'll protect you!
Now hide here.
Everyone!
Right!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor sheep who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Bedtiiiiiiime!
It multiplied!
Bedtiiiiime!
Something sprouted!
A fence?
Sheep number one,
sheep number two,
sheep number three,
sheep number four,
sheep number five...
Huh?
I'm getting tired...
This is no time for...
But it's so difficult to stay awake...
Now, finish them!
Baaaahdtime!
Run wild, Selfish!
Build Egogy for King Selfish!
Why you!
Sheep number one,
sheep number two...
Not again...
I can't move...
Don't fall asleep, don't fall...
Good night...
This is the end for the Precures.
What a noisy brat.
Selfish, shut her up!
Sheep number one,
sheep number two,
sheep number three...
Why isn't it working?
Selfish, put some effort in!
Baaaaahck off!
Shaddaaaaahp!
Baaaahdtime!
Kyupirappa!
Self!
This light!
Is it...
Ai's?
Ai!
I'm sleepy again...
Baaaahdtime!
Ai...
Wake up!
Mana, you're her mommy!
You said you'd... protect her!
Then no mahtter what,
ya can't just...
Same for you!
You know Ai's so cute you can't help yourself!
So you can't let yourself fall asleep!
I know!
If we can't protect her,
what're we good for?
We'll protect her!
By ourselves!
Yeah!
You sheep!
We won't let you...
make our baby cry!
Baaaaahdy-bye time!
This way, Ai.
Baaaahdtime!
Not again!
Sheep number one,
sheep number two,
sheep number...
Three million, two hundred eighty-five thousand, nine hundred forty-five!
Bah?
Three million, two hundred...
BAHHHH?
Hurry up!
You're stuck!
Davi!
Glitter!
Holy Sword!
Our fence!
Now!
Charles!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
Loove looove looooooove!
Welp, back to work!
What a nap...
Aaaaaah!
I'm cured!
I shall let you off for today.
Bye now!
What was she so happy about?
Beats me.
Makopi, thanks.
When you yelled at me to not to fall asleep,
I was really happy!
Ai seems to be sleepy.
Now, time for another lullaby!
Let me do it.
Go to sleep,
go to sleep,
in your mother's chest.
She's asleep!
You're the best, Makopi!
I say this as a friend, but you need lessons.
Maybe...
Makopi, did you just call me a friend?
Did I?
You totally did!
You finally said it!
Come on, one more time!
Shhh!.
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Oh no!
There's paranormal activity at Oogai First Middle School!
Mana, there are flying rags and buckets chasing people!
Really?!
The sculptures from the art room are moving!
Whoah!
There are balls flying in midair!
Unbelievable!
Could this be...
Is it possibly...
Their doing?
Dokidoki Precure:
Outrageous!
Ai Goes To School!!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!