Prepare to advance...
Forward!
Advancing.
Enemy sighted.
Prepare to fire main cannon!
Distance 800.
Load High Explosive shells.
R-Roger.
Loading complete!
Prepare!
Fire!
Ka-boom!
Target in sight.
Signal to the rear.
"One vehicle destroyed."
"We still have a long way to go."
Roger!
One vehicle crushed, huh?
Well done.
We're not there yet, though.
Filicia, it's Klaus.
My... Well, shall we have tea then?
Well done, everyone.
Shuko's looking really healthy, huh?
Her wounds are completely healed, but she's still sticking around here.
That's because it's wonderful here, right?
Hey!
How can she be so energetic when it's this hot?
Yes... indeed.
This is from headquarters.
Sign here.
Sure.
These are some personal letters.
Kana-chan.
Yes! Yes, yes... Yes!
This is for you.
Thank you very much!
It's from my mother!
Noel-chan. There's one for you from Kyou Ju San, as usual.
Professor-san?
His surname is Kyou.
His name is Ju San.
It's a common name in Sett Province.
Wow, he's Ju San-san.
It's amazing that you have a friend from so far away!
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I-I was kidding.
Oh my, Noel-chan. I believed you for a moment there.
Go get Klaus a souvenir.
Okay!
Rio.
The us-u-al.
Throw it away.
Geez...
So, what does headquarters want?
Excuse me...
What's the matter, Kureha?
M-Major Klaus, sir.
Here!
This year's, huh?
Yes!
U-Uh...
...a-as always, for everything, thank you!
Don't worry about it.
It's my job.
Major.
Here you are.
Roger.
Leave the fortress to me in your absence.
Absence?
Godspeed, Private.
Y-Yes.
Everyone. We're going on an excursion tomorrow.
Yay!
An excursion!
Isn't that great, Noel-chan?
It's so exciting, right?
An excursion... Filicia?
Even though we're going on an excursion, it'll be boring to just walk around...
So let's play a game as well.
Game?
On the south side of Seize's provincial border,
in other words, near the boundary of no-man's land,
there are observation devices from the old era.
You know about them, right?
Of those mentioned, three units are due for maintenance checkups.
I would like you to examine them during your excursion.
That's...
That's obviously a mission, isn't it?!
Oh well, it's just an excursion.
Even if they are broken, there isn't anything we could do about it.
Nocturnal-type observation devices are a complete black box.
It's impossible to disassemble.
That's why it's an excursion.
This is what he meant by 'Godspeed', huh?
It's useless to walk normally.
And so, you guys will...
...be carrying those!
You're so weak.
Listen up, with this, you'll have to use your entire body weight and...
Wow! Amazing!
I-I can't move.
Klutz.
You're one to talk!
You made it this far without defying our orders.
You're all really good children.
Listen up!
When you're carrying heavy rucksacks,
you first fall on your back.
And...
When the entire weight is on your back,
How lame...
Listen... now...
Do it!
Yes!
Alright!
Now then, Filicia and I will proceed to the goal marked on the map and wait for you.
If you think you can't handle any more,
blow your trumpet.
We will come find you...
Got it?!
And, there are wild animals in these mountains.
If you encounter them, you will not be supported.
You have permission to use firepower.
Understood, right?!
Well then. Have fun.
Right face, right!
Right face... right!
Forward! Advance!
Ad-vance!
Now then.
So, I'll leave the rest to you, all right?
Roger.
Hea-vy...
Heavy...
Heavy...  heavy!
K-Kureha-chan, don't do that.
The more you say it, the heavier it'll feel.
Noel, how much further?
Noel!
Hey, Kanata!
Found it!
Amazing!
Whoa!
Operation... no abnormalities.
What is it?
We found it easily, didn't we?
Let's keep going at this pace.
Yeah.
What's the matter?
It's like...
I was thinking of how it has been here alone for so long protecting the town.
Well then, where next, Noel?
Let's see...
We are here now, so...
That mountain.
Th-That mountain?
Someone, do something about this baggage.
Heavy...
Captain and Rio-senpai must hate me after all.
That's definitely it.
That's why they're doing this.
Heavy...
Hey, say something, Kanata.
It's not like you to stay quiet.
Hey!
How annoying...
What is it!
I can hear it...
I can hear it!
H-Hey, Kanata!
What's the matter with you?
She's breaking down?
Wow, beautiful!
How refreshing. It's beautiful, right?
Break time.
No matter what anyone says, I'm taking a break!
I've decided!
First one in!
Not fair!
It's delicious!
I'll get you for that!
Take that!
Might as well.
Noel, you...
Take that!
A fish!
Hey, hey, Kureha-chan!
It's amazing, huh? This is fun, right?
Yeah!
No, it's not!
You're too relaxed.
But this is an excursion, right?
We should enjoy it.
Have you forgotten about those heavy bags already?
This is training.
But, even Filicia-san...
Get a clue already...
That person is evil.
Pure black evil.
She's blonde and fair skinned. She's lovely.
It's not about that...
Kureha doesn't understand.
Understand what?
That's what's great about Filicia.
Right?
No, that's not it!
You guys definitely must be looking at something different!
Geez! Somebody do something about this air-head duo.
Now, time for food. Time for food!
We're completely soaked, huh?
We'll dry off in no time in this weather.
Wh-What is this?!
Our food is gone.
Could it possibly be a wild boar?
In the countryside back home, they often tore up the fields.
But when there was an abundance of food in the summer,
they didn't appear as often.
There is a bigger problem.
What?
The compass is gone.
What?!
I wonder if it was right to leave to baggage behind?
Since it's come to this, our priority is getting to the goal.
Have you figured out the direction?
The first device was here.
And the river's located here.
We're in the mountains heading towards the second device at its peak.
So, at any rate, we should head towards higher ground.
Okay! No matter what-
You're hungry, right?
Is there anything edible around here...?
Found it!
Bayberries!
Is that edible?
Yeah.
They're sweet and a little sour-ish. They're delicious!
That's a chord, right?
But, it's impossible to climb up.
It's dangerous.
Really?
We should hurry on ahead.
They say that Major Klaus crossed a desert in a tank
without food or water for three days, just to destroy an enemy fortress.
This is a piece of cake.
Is that so?
Haven't you heard?
He's called the Desert Wolf!
He's an amazing man!
Ohh... he is?
So, let's do our best.
But the bayberries...
Quit whining.
Second one, found!
Wild boar?
Where is the last one?
It's getting really dark.
That's because we had to keep confirming our direction.
Is this really the right direction?
Probably.
What do you mean probably?!
Without a compass, I cannot be one hundred percent certain.
So what is it?
Are you saying that we've come this far pointlessly?
I never said that.
You should never have let such an important compass out of your sight!
Just a minute!
Let's not fight in a place like this.
We should never have been so leisurely in the river.
That's right.
You are just too relaxed.
What's with you and your excursion?
You are always frivolous and in a daze.
That's how we got into this mess.
Do you get it?
There it is!
Hey, wait up!
Kanata!
Good grief. Guess they'll manage somehow.
Goal!
We did it!
We did it, Kureha-chan!
I get it...
I get it already, so let go of me!
I can't breathe...
Look.
No man's land.
This is the end of the inhabited world.
Well done.
I'm sorry, Captain.
We could not complete our mission.
What mission are you talking about?
But...
I told you it was an excursion, right?
No way...
I just really wanted you to see this.
These are our senpais' signatures.
All the maidens from the fortress have been here at least once.
And gazed upon this scenery... the end of the world.
This is historical, isn't it?
That's true...
Could you walk just a little more?
There is one more thing that our senpais have left behind.
You're late.
Rio... senpai?
What happened?
Here!
Bayberries!
I've revived.
So, did you win?
Don't ask.
But,
it was well worth the trouble...
Next time: Kanata's Day Off - Hair Braiding