Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Sontokkya chanto release yo
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Nan kataru nan taberu
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
It's what you call a normal girlie
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
Am I the only one surprised?
Odoroita atashi dake?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Bonbon ouendan
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Ranran kangeikai
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Take it away!
Motteike!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
n n n n n n n n
It's only Monday!
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Do your best, be energetic
Ganbatte harikitte
My darlin', darlin' please!
My darlin' darlin' please!
Morning, you two.
Yo.
Good morning.
You remembered to wear your winter uniform.
Come on...
It's not like I'm Tsukasa.
What?!
But the hot weather isn't over yet...
They could let us wear our summer uniforms a little longer.
And when we have to wear
summer uniforms, it gets cold sometimes...
They should just let us choose.
Right?
The switch is more to give students a change in pace.
Else there would be more slackers like you two.
Pandora's
Box
This doesn't happen in our family...
...but I've heard that some parents monitor...
...their daughter's cell phones and e-mail.
I've heard of that on occasion.
Is it like that for you?
Probably not.
Your dad's the type to smother...
...but I guess he wouldn't do anything you wouldn't like.
That might be part of it...
My dad also uses the computer.
Maybe it's 'cause he knows how  embarrassing it is when someone else looks at your D drive.
D...
What?
We're had all these classes and stuff this summer...
In the end...
I only got to have fun with the fireworks and Ariake.
So you still go to Comiket.
Comiket?!
Well, you know...
As a result, my wallet's feeling pretty lonely.
How much did you spend?
You never know when to draw the line.
If you assume each book is a thousand yen...
Around forty to fifty thousand yen total?
Why you...
There's a limit to how clueless a
person can be about the value of money!
Still, Kagami...
There's this thing called market price.
And it's pretty expensive to publish your own stuff.
That's not what I meant!
I'm talking about how you don't
feel anything after spending so much!
It may be September...
...but it's still hot.
That's right.
It seems especially hot this year.
And there's talk about global warming.
Yu-chan can't put up with too much heat...
...so she's been resting in an
air-conditioned room most of the time.
That's what Tsukasa's been doing the whole time.
But she's just lazy.
Well...
Dad and I join in...
...and we all lie around looking like a 小 character.
小?
Shouldn't it be 川?
Nah.
Dad's always in the middle.
Your family never changes.
And I guess Yutaka-chan's gotten used to it.
Hey, hey!
Doing good, Yutaka?
I'm here to play!
Sis!
Oh?
Who's this?
My friend...
Minami Iwasaki-chan.
So this is the Minami-chan Yutaka's always talking about.
S-Sis!
So she has a reason for hope right next to her...
I'm a little jealous.
Man...
I'd heard all the fuss...
...but you sure are pretty.
You wowed me!
Want something to drink?
Beer then!
Huh?!
Didn't you drive here?!
Just kiddin'!
Barley tea's fine!
I see.
One absorbs from the other...
Absorption, is it...
Oh...
It's the Yassai Mossai?
I always get sleepy at night.
Do you have any good ideas?
Instead of forcing yourself to stay up...
...why don't you wake up early and work on it?
You'll probably feel better.
I see!
You're right!
I'll wake up early and work hard.
Huh?
Why is it the same time I always get up?
Come to think of it...
I vaguely remember turning
something off at some point...
Even when I wake up early...
...I just roll over and go back to sleep.
You have no willpower...
Maybe I should just try harder...
...and work on it at night.
I doubt rubbing your eyes while nodding off...
...will improve the results.
Why don't you have someone wake you up?
Mom and the others wake up early.
Right, Mom?
Yes, yes.
I'll wake you up.
This can't fail.
Sis is amazing.
Mom!
I told you to wake me up!
I did.
You even answered me back.
I don't know anything about that.
You don't remember?
Big Sister forgot her lunch...
Thanks!
It feels kind of weird to walk
through the hallway of a different grade.
You can feel a little pressure...
I know what you mean.
Yu-chan probably drew everybody's attention.
Being the way she is...
Usually, it's just your imagination...
...but when you walk through a
hallway for upperclassmen or underclassmen...
...you get this feeling that everybody's looking at you, right?
I already tend to stand out 'cause I'm smaller...
...but when it's because they're
upperclassmen, the pressure is more intense.
I enjoy receiving that kind of attention.
Really...
But I don't attract much attention when I'm in the first-year's area.
They don't realize I'm an upperclassman.
Wields no pressure
as an upperclassman .
Patty-chan.
Hi!
Hello there.
Are you heading to work?
That's right.
I signed up for too many shifts this week.
Aren't you still working?
That's right.
We're pretty popular.
The A-boys are all over us.
A-boys?
It's what you call boys who look like they totally belong in Akiba.
But Narimiya-kun was a little different.
You're getting accustomed to Japan.
A little too accustomed, don't you think?
I just had a great idea!
I'll write it down once I'm done with my bath.
H-Huh?
I can't remember...
This is what happens when I don't jot it down immediately...
And it was funny...
Hilarious, even!
Another exhausting day...
That might be a funny idea.
I'll write it down when I wake up tomorrow.
Er...
That's weird...
What was it again?
I'm positive it was a good idea.
Should have just gotten out of bed and written it down.
Man!
I even got out of bed this time!
Why do you forget dreams so quickly?
I'm positive that it was hilarious!
Hotel Room
Assignments
School Trip
Kyoto - Nara
Hotel Room
Assignments
School Trip
Kyoto - Nara
So...
Make sure you all talk it over within your group.
Field Trip
Kyoto ・ Nara
Since we're going all the way to Kyoto and Nara...
...you better check up on all the hot tourist spots.
Train Seating
Arrangement
Hotel Room
Assignments
Free Time Team
School Trip
Kyoto - Nara
Trash
Monitor
Minoru Shiraishi
What to
Decide
Train Seating
Arrangement
Hotel Room
Assignments
Free Time Team
School Trip
Kyoto - Nara
Trash
Monitor
Minoru Shiraishi
What to
Decide
Aren't we going through all the hot spots by bus?
Those will just be the typical places...
...so they won't be that fun.
Well now...
That's a blunt way to put it...
So Iris came in here...
I will now guide you through the former capital of Nara.
Almost 1,300 years have passed since it became the capital in 710.
While in Nara...
...I hope you enjoy my historical Nara narration.
Nara!
Nara narration!
Were we supposed to laugh?
Sorry for the wait!
This is the main body...
So the little things around it are options!
You're gonna get hit by lightning.
No!
I'm all sticky...
And stinky...
I'm all stinky now!
Here, here, here.
Indeed.
What's that supposed to mean?
Please, please.
They probably want you to take their picture.
Um... Um...
Click. Click.
Okay?
This is when you can tell how much somebody's been studying.
Like you're one to talk.
Um...
Sis.
How do you say "cheese" in Indian?
You mean Hindi, right?
Um...
Uh...
Genius girl Kagami can't do any better.
Um...
I believe that Indians will understand English.
That's right!
"Say cheese!" should be fine, yeah?
Okay.
Say cheese!
You know how...
...couples pop out of nowhere during school trips?
Can't miss the school trip event.
Perhaps...
...being away from school...
...gives people a sense of freedom?
Kinda like a now or never thing.
I'm embarrassed to say that...
...I'm unable to sleep with a different pillow.
...I can't sleep peacefully without this nearby.
I'm embarrassed to say that...
...I can't sleep if I haven't turned
this on at least once during the day.
Everyone.
The bus will soon pass Kiyomizu Temple.
The hill leading to Kiyomizu Temple...
...is known as Three-year Hill.
Legend says that...
...if you trip and fall here, you'll die in three years.
Three-year Hill will become...
...your Boo-hoo Hill.
Does it count if you break down laughing?
Okay?
We'll be moving around in individual groups now.
Keep an eye out for traffic.
We'll regroup at 12:30 in front of Chion-in.
Don't be late.
Anybody who's late gets to write a
happy 20-page report when we get back.
Sure about that?
Let's give it a try.
The Dragon Slayer's probably about this heavy.
We're really high up.
You know how the saying goes,
"Like you're going to jump off Kiyomizu..."
...but if you really jumped, wouldn't you die?
Does it mean that you no longer care what happens?
You're so pragmatic, Kagami.
Look, look!
It says marriage.
This place seems to be famous for its god of marriage.
They really spell it out for you.
Look.
You can draw love fortunes.
Let's all give it a try.
Praying for a
Good Marriage
Let's do it!
Guess I can't tell these apart...
Isn't that obvious?
This one!
Great fortune!
Lucky you, Kona-chan.
My.
I drew good fortune.
That's fine.
Now what did I get...
Half fortune?
What's this?
I-I guess you only get half a fortune.
Which means it's half bad.
Not like I care about love fortunes.
So cute!
That looks nice.
Nah.
Kagami would want this.
RECOMMENDED
What's that supposed to mean?
I'll get one of these.
Kagami! Kagami!
You forgot this!
I'm not buying it!
Then what about this?
No!
You should be careful.
Marriage Wishes
This one says, "Konata is my waifu."
Okay.
Everyone's here, right?
We'll have lunch after we've gone in the hotel.
Let's get going.
Take us there please.
They said that Koizumi's character
song was written in an IZAM style.
Teacher!
Someone's chasing us from behind!
What?!
This is like the Hokkaido shoot all over again!
Don't ditch me!
You have to go, "***tel!"
That idiot.
He's getting assigned a 50-page report!
Driver!
Sorry, could you stop for a second?
Hotel
Honnoji
See you later.
To Hiiragi
I'd like to talk
Please meet me in front
of our hotel at 9 tonight.
From a
certain boy
Doesn't even hurt!
The Golden Pavilion Temple is golden...
...but the Silver Pavilion Temple isn't silver, huh?
They wanted to group it with the Golden Pavilion Temple...
Click.
...so they named it silver to go along with golden.
It was never silver to begin with.
Click.
I wonder if it's like Poke***...
With Sapphire and Ruby and stuff.
No comment?
Our family's shrine was on the news.
We only have one day left.
Our plan for free time is all set.
Tomorrow is the beginning of our true school trip!
Off we go to the holy land!
Right...
D-Does this count as being in front of the hotel?
Did you wait long?
So...
What did you want to talk about?
You're the only person I can talk to about this.
Please give me that doll!
Doll?
You know...
The one you bought from the Kiyomizu Temple souvenir shop!
The Yatsuhashi character.
Ya-Yatsuhashi-kun?
Yeah!
That one!
I really liked it and wanted one.
But if someone saw me buying one...
...they'd probably all make fun of me!
I'm begging you!
Thank you!
I'm eternally in your debt!
Don't tell anybody about this!
Yes, yes.
I'm reading this book about four brothers.
****** of the Dragon Kings?
I can't take it off!
That's right.
Come to think of it...
The steam within cooled off...
That could make a pretty good anime.
...and formed a vacuum.
They did an anime adaptation a while back.
If you press on the sides a little...
...that should allow air to enter and make the lid easier to remove.
Really?
I had no idea!
I think they went up to the
fourth volume of the original.
In that case...
But those books are...
I'm sorry!
So sorry!
Putting on a show till the very end.
I've already looked up the directions.
Is it really okay for us to visit?
We'll just be looking from the outside so it's okay.
There's no need to go that far just 'cause we're in Kyoto.
Tsk. Tsk. Tsk.
You don't understand the geek's idea of romance.
I don't want to.
Not much here.
It makes it easier to concentrate on their job so this works.
It's a pretty ordinary-looking building.
They limit their workload so this works.
Was it really necessary to buy these in Kyoto?
Princess
Love
That's embarrassing!
Who cares?
It's a little something for remembering this day!
Sis!
Let's take a picture together!
It's for commemorating this trip.
Since we came all the way to Kyoto.
What does this have to do with Kyoto?
Tsukasa and I made it back in one piece.
Tsukasa's already asleep though.
I figured you'd be sulking in bed.
Why would I be doing that?
Did you put up the sticker photo?
How could I put up something so embarrassing?
Something so embarrassing....
The school trip was this week...
I sure worked hard.
Okay.
Time to spend the weekend gaming online for once.
Emergency Maintenance Notice
Due to an unexplained server error at 8:30 PM,
the server is currently undergoing emergency maintenance.
Good lucky!
Here's another crazy episode of Lucky Channel!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
I'm the assistant...
Daisuke Ono.
Lucky Channel is already on the twenty-first episode!
That's right.
We're finally getting close to the end.
Well, then...
Let's get straight to this corner...
This Week's
Bend
This week's...
Bend!
This Week's
Bend
Who is it?
What?
I brought your water.
What is this?!
It's warm!
How am I supposed to drink this?!
I'd rather have something out of a vending machine.
Don't mess with me!
You...
Why, you...
What do you think I've had to put up with this whole time?!
All your damn selfish requests one after the next!
Mi-Minoru?
Well, I'm gonna speak my mind today!
Do you know how I felt when I was doing this corner?!
I'd have to work at CoCo**** every day!
That's better pay than my voice acting work!
Thanks to you, I'm working full-time now!
Before I come kiss your ass here...
...I'm over there frying cutlets!
Which means you're more suited for that work.
And what the hell?!
Why are you sitting there, Ono boy?!
That's my seat!
You were abandoned.
By the director and the producer.
What's that?!
They acted too quickly!
I'm a late bloomer!
I can go from here to Starga**r in no time!
You can?
Weally?
Sittin' there making fun of me...
Screw working with Hine**su...
Or Lo** and Be***...
I quit.
I quit this stupid show, damn it!
Take that!
Who gives a damn about Lucky Channel?!
Shiraishi Minoru-san!
What are you doing, morons?!
What are you filming there?!
What's with the Cape of Thirty Years?!
If you wanna play with that...
...I'm gonna be thirty soon!
I'm talking about you....
Welcome to Idaho!
The belt isn't long enough so she's holding it up from behind.
Hello.
Minoru Shiraishi here!
Yeah.
Okay!
Now please listen!
Don't wanna hear it.
The Dentistman Song!
What is this?
What does that even mean?
Yeah, yeah.
Stop moving.
Right.
Stop moving!
I head forth giving my all!
Wait, Akira-san!
Sheesh.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Stop moving!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can I let go?
Dentistman is...
Don't screw up your lines!
...is a cyborg.
He...
He will...
You can't be a hero like that.
...continue fighting to defeat the evil cavities!
You can't fight like that.
How was it?
No good.
Redo.
Yes, ma'am.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Akira Kogami!
I'm Daisuke Ono.
Okay.
That's it for the animal talk.
That was in animal, huh?
Next time:
「There Over Here」
There Over Here.
I can cross the goal line now, can't I?
Ramen set!