This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events are purely coincidental.
These three people have theories about the movie's unsolved murder mystery.
Hyouka
Please listen to their ideas and tell us what you think.
Okay!
So you guys
are the mystery masters?
This is Nakajou Jun'ya, the vice-director from the filming team.
This is Haba Tomohiro from the prop team.
Hello.
And this is...
Ciao!
Sawakiguchi Misaki from the marketing team.
Thanks for coming all the way here!
Nice to meetcha!
S-Sure!
Is she taking this seriously at all?
Well then, we'll leave this in your hands.
Come get us later, 'kay?
Take your time.
Sorry fer gettin' ya mixed up in this mess.
We mighta started on a whim but it'd be a shame if we couldn't finish it, y'know?
Hope ya'll help us a bit.
Yeah...
Oh, right...
Please, help yourselves.
These are whisky candies, right?
It's a sample of a new product.
They're strong!
Well, should we start?
You're on the filming team, right?
Did you have a hard time with the shooting?
The actors had a fun time improvisin'...
Murder in the Ghost Town of Furuoka
Gettin' there was a job and a half, though.
Took over an hour by bus 'n' train.
Why'd it hafta be in the middle o' nowhere?
Why was it?
It caught a few people's fancy 'cos it looked interestin'.
Narakubo is basically a ghost town, right? How'd you get in?
What's-her-face talked to the caretaker 'bout it.
Is that important?
Thank you, that's all I needed.
Please go on.
How is Hongou, the scriptwriter?
Not doin' so well.
Not that anyone blames her or anythin'.
Was she particularly frail?
Yeah. She missed school a bunch of times and didn't come to the shootings either.
I guess she was working on the script.
Did the team not like Hongou's script?
No one complained! Not a bad word was said 'bout it!
So the people in charge wanted to do it?
Whatcha gettin' at? We all approved of Hongou's work!
'Course I did too!
By the way...
Did Hongou tell you anything about who the culprit might be?
Not as far as I know...
Wait a sec.
Kounosu told us to do our best.
Anyone would say that.
And did you ask the actors?
Has anyone heard anything relevant?
Nope, no one.
Do you know if the twist was something physical? Or a trick of the mind?
What's the difference?
No more questions?
Then how 'bout listenin' to my idea?
Please.
If ya ask me, a script don't need no twist.
It's all 'bout the excitement!
You're the culprit!
Just solve the case somehow,
and watch the culprit confess, cryin' like a baby.
That oughta do it.
Fin
Kaitou's death was pretty excitin', right?
A rip-roarin' death for the proud leader o' the prop team.
Real nice, huh?
You improvised that scene?
Yeah. They're all so obsessed with that crap,
the rules of mystery or whatever. Drama's where it's at!
Plus, the title's gotta lay it bare.
"Murder in the Ghost Town of Furuoka."
Murder in the
Ghost Town
of Furuoka
...or somethin' like that, so folks come 'n' see it.
Hongou must've known that too.
So then, what's your theory?
The way he died, what was it...
A locked room murder.
Kaitou died in a room with all exits locked.
So how'd the culprit kill him? Or rather...
How'd he get out?
Yeah, how?
Piece o' cake! The window!
The window?
Yeah! The culprit escaped through the window after killin' Kaitou, clear as day!
The window? Sorry, my memory's a bit hazy.
Satoshi, got the floor plan?
Yessir!
Just a sec.
Here you go.
Kaitou died here, in the stage's left wing.
The other characters entered here, from the right corridor.
The door was locked, so someone had to go get the master key.
And when they entered the left wing, Kaitou was lying there dead.
The doors to the stage and the crossover were blocked by junk, right?
Then the only possible exits were these:
The door they came in by and the left wing's window.
But did Hongou know that as well?
Yeah, that's an important point.
What do you mean?
If Hongou wrote the script just based on the floor plan, without seeing the place for herself,
then she might've intended the murderer to take another route.
Don't worry 'bout that. Before she wrote the script, she surveyed the location once herself.
When was that?
In June... or was it the end of May?
Anyway, that window's how the culprit came and went.
And there ya have it. That's how Kaitou died.
Howzat?!
How should I know?
Wouldn't that be a pretty boring mystery?
Tell Hongou 'bout that.
Not like she knows anythin' 'bout mysteries either.
Doubt she woulda come up with some cool twist.
But then who was the murderer?
The murderer?
What if the murderer's identity is the twist? Who could it be?
And after everyone entered the room,
wasn't there a shot showing what was outside the window?
Yeah.
It was clear that no one left through the window.
If anyone had walked through that sea of grass, it'd be bent out of the way.
There was no such evidence.
There's no way they could have escaped through the window!
Hongou might've just forgotten 'bout it.
The moment you use that argument it's all over.
Besides, I heard that Hongou paid great attention to realism.
But then...
Got it!
Fresh grass!
Like I said, Hongou went there 'round the end of May!
The grass must've grown out after that!
That's why she thought the window'd work!
But then we just gotta cut the grass
and retake from the corpse scene at the next shooting, and it'll all match up!
See?! Howzat?!
All right, that settles it!
The culprit escaped through the window! It works!
Hell yeah!
Catch ya later!
Could that really be it? That's not much of a twist.
At least it's physically possible, though.
Yeah, but still...
Oreki...
Do you think Nakajou's theory was what Hongou really intended?
You don't like it?
No, I just...
I have some trouble accepting it.
So you don't like it.
You're right in that Nakajou's theory is contradictory.
What? There's a contradiction?
It's a simple resolution, but it flies in the face of common sense.
What do you mean?
That's a roundabout way to put it, Houtarou.
Fitting for the detective, I guess.
Um,
what exactly do you mean?
Put yourself in the culprit's shoes. There's no way he'd enter through the window.
If he entered through the window, he'd risk crossing someone's line of sight.
Here, or here.
If he entered from outside the building then someone would see him for sure,
especially during broad daylight.
I see.
If I were the culprit, I wouldn't have gone in that way.
That's the long and short of it.
But we don't know if Hongou thought the same way.
That's true.
However, if we can read Hongou's script, we can find that out.
By the way, have you guys read much crime fiction?
Why?
I realized while listening to Nakajou
that everyone has their own idea of what a "mystery novel" is.
His way of thinking certainly was novel.
How about you, Houtarou?
Not a lot. Read a few, that's all.
Mayaka?
The usual. Agatha Christie and such.
Good start.
And you, Chitanda?
I haven't read any.
Not a single one? At all?
I don't really enjoy mysteries...
I've tried enough to realize that.
I haven't read any for years, though.
I didn't expect that.
And what about you?
Me? Well...
I know.
Fuku is trying to be a real Sherlockian.
What's a Sherlockian?
I guess that refers to Sherlock Holmes' enthusiastic fans.
Really, really enthusiastic fans.
Right?
"Sherlockian" means something a bit different...
What did you think?
Um...
We've refuted Nakajou's theory.
I see.
Oh, and also...
What?
Can we see the script? We'd like to know how much detail Hongou put in it.
Okay. I'll go to look for it. In the meantime, please talk to Haba Tomohiro from the prop team.
Hi there.
I hear you chaps might be up for a little tête-à-tête regarding mysteries.
As the Sun's strength falters,
summer's feverish heat breaks for the first time.
Limit of Heat
Hyouka
If one considers mysteries to be a duel between the writer and the reader,
a mere dilettante such as Hongou barely counts as an opponent.
Yeah, we heard she wasn't familiar with mysteries.
Indeed.
Those books were her crash course into that enigmatic realm.
Prior to this film, she knew nothing about mystery, not even via graphic novels or cinema.
Ah, it's Nobuhara's translation! A new edition as well!
The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes
Conan Doyle / Translated by Nobuhara Ken
She tried learning about mystery through Holmes?
Precisely! What a total amateur, I say!
I wonder about that.
Oreki, Oreki!
What?
There's some weird code here! Look!
The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes
Conan Doyle
A Scandal in Bohemia
The Red-Headed League
A Case of Identity
The Boscombe Valley Mystery
The Five Orange Pips
The Man with the Twisted Lip
The Blue Carbuncle
The Speckled Band
A Case of Identity
The Copper Beeches
Look, here too!
The Case-Book of Sherlock Holmes
Conan Doyle
The Illustrious Client
The Blanched Soldier
The Mazarin Stone
The Three Gables
The Sussex Vampire
The Three Garridebs
The Problem of Thor Bridge
The Creeping Man
The Lion's Mane
The Veiled Lodger
She probably just marked off the ideas she could use.
I see.
Putting that aside,
why don't we get down to brass tacks?
Is that the floor plan?
2nd floor
Sound
control room
Senoue
Wellhole
Dimmer
room
Utility
Sugimura
Stairwell
Kounosu
West
1st floor
Right wing
Stage
Left wing
Kaitou
Storage
room
Katsuta
Toilet
Waiting
room
Yamanishi
Office
Reception
Waiting
room
Toilet
Entrance lobby
Hall
I've marked the characters as such.
Then please tell us your theory.
By my assessment, this mystery is not difficult at all.
In fact, it's really quite simple.
How so?
This murder wasn't planned in advance.
Rather, the culprit merely struck when the time was right.
Why?
Had it been planned, how would he relocate Kaitou to the left wing?
Kaitou proceeded alone to the right side of the theater after choosing that key himself.
Furthermore, this was a locked room murder.
All possible escape routes were secured and the only one left viable, the window,
showed no signs of use.
To wit: Kaitou's murderer could not escape via any normal means.
As for whether he could have simply taken and returned the master key...
A conclusion as vapid as it is fallacious.
To retrieve the master key from the office, one would need to cross the entrance lobby.
Any one of the characters could easily witness someone doing so.
Thus, not one of them could safely enter the office.
And not just the office, either.
The entire right-hand corridor that leads to the left wing was accessible by none.
Ergo, this area is vital.
And why is that?
Because it means the culprit couldn't have approached the locked room.
Well... Essentially, yes.
Likewise, the victim himself could not have locked the room.
What else is there?
Nor could he have been murdered through mechanical means, or after the door had been opened.
He was quite clearly dead, with his arm severed from his body.
Thus, the solution to Hongou's locked room mystery is something other than the obvious.
What do you think? You're Oreki, right?
How would you solve this locked room mystery?
Yeah, I dunno.
Oh please, that simply won't do!
But I can't say I'm all that surprised.
This is the key.
I'm on the prop team, as you know.
Hongou instructed us to procure a rope that wouldn't snap under a person's weight.
Do you understand its purpose?
It's like I always say,
if you can't enter via the first floor, try the second!
Kounosu was there on the second floor's right-hand corridor.
Though she may seem delicate to you, she is in fact in the Mountaineering Club.
She lowered the rope from the second floor,
slew Kaitou from where he stood in the left wing,
and used that very same means of escape.
Were I to select a title for the movie, I'd call it...
"Invisible Entrance", or something like that.
And now, your opinions please.
Did Hongou ask you for anything besides the rope?
Not really. But she didn't always order everything she required.
For instance, the volume of blood she had us prepare was not nearly enough,
so we had to go to some lengths to make more.
Anything else? If that is all...
Um...
What?
Just wondering,
have you seen what's done of the movie?
I confess that I have not.
He pisses me off!
How so?
His attitude! Were you okay with that?
He even made fun of Holmes!
Not really.
Why?!
Well, Holmes is aimed at beginners.
And it does seem like Hongou is a beginner.
Well...
So what do you think of Haba's theory?
I guess it sort of works.
It's not a very interesting twist, but Hongou ordering that rope is pretty decisive.
I don't have a problem with it either.
I...
I can't accept that theory.
Like with Nakajou's, something just feels off about it.
I don't really know why, but I doubt Hongou was planning something like that.
Haven't you had enough of those?
Huh? When did I have that many?
They tasted so interesting, I couldn't stop thinking about it.
Chi, are you all right?
I'm all right! All right!
Oreki, do you think his theory is correct?
I don't.
Why?
If we were talking about a real murder, it might work,
The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes
Conan Doyle / Translated by Nobuhara Ken
but it can't have been used in this movie.
Meaning?
It's at odds with the video.
Oh, I see. The window, right?
It hadn't been touched for years, and didn't fit properly.
It took Katsuta some real effort just to get it open.
It creaked quite badly, not to mention it opens upward.
It'd be almost impossible to quietly open a window like that while hanging on a rope.
And would Kaitou just stand by and watch while she rattled away at the window?
He wouldn't be that stupid.
So that's why you asked him if he'd seen the movie?
Hongou surveyed the theater.
If the window was a key part of the plot, she would've checked that as well.
But this wasn't reflected in the video,
so we can conclude that Hongou didn't care about the window.
I shouldn't have just said yes without thinking!
How was it?
No good.
I see.
I've brought you the script.
Thank you.
Mystery
Gimme, gimme!
I wanna see it!
Mystery
You're drunk.
I'm fine!
Show us too, Oreki.
I see, it's quite well written.
Yeah, rather detailed.
"Be sure not to disturb the tall grass outside the window."
So she did consider it after all.
Oh, what about the last person, Sawakiguchi?
Sorry to keep you!
Ciao!
Good afternoon, Sawakiguchi!
Ciao to you too!
Oh man, at marketing we're in like, such a bind without the title.
We can't even finish the posters, you know?
I wanna just see that script over and done with already.
Did Hongou volunteer to write the script?
Nope. Majority vote.
Who decided that it'd be a mystery?
That was a vote, too.
And who decided to make a movie?
Aren't we getting a bit off-topic?
But I can't stop thinking about it!
Here's the minutes of our meeting.
Check it out if you think it'll help.
Thank you.
All right!
Listen to my theory, 'kay?
I want you guys to think of the word "mystery" and tell me what you see!
Let's start with... you!
The Orient Express.
That's a detective novel! Pretty hardcore.
If you asked for "mystery" in a video rental shop,
you'd usually get stuff like Friday the 13th or Nightmare on Elm Street.
But aren't those horror fi—
I see, that's right!
Think about it like someone who isn't interested in the genre.
No 31. What should the murder weapon be?
Knife (stabbing) - 10
Rope (strangulation) - 8
Hammer (beating) - 3
Others:
cover with oil and set on fire - 1
push off a high place - 2
Knife suggested (Hongou has final say)
No 32. How many murderers should there be?
1 - 6
2 - 10
3 - 3
More: 4 - 1
Invalid ballot: 1
Everyone dies: 2
About 100: 1
Two persons suggested (Hongou has final say)
For them, mystery and horror are the same.
And nobody like, entered the room that Kaitou died in, right?
So there's gotta be a seventh person! It's obvious!
A seventh person?
Hongou was looking for a seventh person besides the six actors.
As the characters start to distrust each other more and more,
they start seeing a slasher around every corner! And then a real one appears!
A slasher?
I dunno how many of them would end up dying.
Probably all of them except one couple.
Then that couple would fend off the killer,
Care
and it'd all be over with a kiss lit by the rising sun!
The title could be like,
"Bloody Beast" or something.
Dunno, I guess that'd be kinda lame?
But that's something you guys could believe, right?
B-But what about the room of the murder?
It was locked, after all!
Who cares about a lock or two?
Horror movie slashers never have any trouble with that stuff.
Otherwise... Oh, right! How about a vengeful spirit!
That'd work too!
No way! Not a chance!
Sawakiguchi's theory definitely isn't what Hongou had in mind!
That's right...
I'm still not sure if this is a joke or not.
But can you refute it? Using logic only.
But it's wrong!
That's why I said "using logic".
But wrong is wrong!
Chi?
It's like a kaleidoscope.
Kaleidoscope?
Hey, Chi!
Chi?
She's asleep.
I did like how daring Sawakiguchi's theory was.
Me too, actually.
I thought so.
But unfortunately, it's not possible.
What?
You saw how elaborate the script was, right?
If Hongou wanted it to turn into a horror film halfway through,
she would've at least listed the necessary props.
And what does a horror film need most?
What does it need most?
Come on.
Haba mentioned it too.
Hongou only asked for a little bit of blood.
As he tried to awaken
Kaitou, Sugimura
realized his hands
were covered in blood.
The script is also written under that assumption.
Which means Hongou wasn't planning some kind of bloodbath.
That's right. It wouldn't be much of a horror movie with only one death.
Everything has a reason, huh?
How was it?
Not possible.
Chi, get a hold of yourself!
In the end, we refuted all their theories.
What'll happen to the movie now?
I guess it'll remain incomplete.
That's a shame.
"That's all that remains of warriors' dreams", huh?
Later!
Yeah...
Enthusiasm is no substitute for skill, as you can see here.
Would you join me for tea?
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
This sprouting warmth confuses us
Don't you understand this feeling yet?
Normally such random glances hold no meaning
Isn't it the same when making friends?
The little shooting stars we wish upon, vanishing into the dawn
are a magic that only unfolds in the night
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
Next time: In Everyone's Blind Spot.
In Everyone's Blind Spot