Huh? Where am I?
Class 1 River
River Styx
(Underworld)
Class 1 River
River Styx
(Underworld)
Class 1 River
River Styx
(Underworld)
Scum
Back to the living
Am I...
at the River Styx?
Come here! Come here!
It's great over here!
You can have so much fun!
No need to be afraid, Akihisa.
This place is packed with fun!
Yuuji? Why are you over there?
Relax, Akihisa.
As you can see, I'm doing just fine.
You don't have to worry.
So just...
come over here!
daimondai hitori to futari
大問題、ひとりとふたり
The big question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
karafuru mawaridasu watashi no shourai
カラフル回り出す 私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
a sou ookina sekai wa kibun ga hirogaru
あ、そう 大きな世界は 気分が広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日も大好き
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当に大好き!
I really do love you
watashi no baka
私のバカ
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
星の数よりもバカだ!
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaete kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えて 君＋謎＋私は
Answer me. What does you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Question 2
Me, Yukatas, and Festival Fun!
Wh-Where...
I can't really remember much,
but I feel like I've been to Hell and back.
We really thought you guys were goners
when you started murmuring in your sleep.
I'm amazed we're alive.
Akihisa and Yuuji tried to vindicate themselves by picking up chicks.
The girls found out about it and punished them.
Really though, they sure went to town on you two.
I can't believe the all the things they did to you.
I'm not surprised.
Yeah, we were pretty out of line.
It's pretty rude to flirt with other girls
when you're already with a bunch of them.
I still think we got off pretty easy, right?
Most people wouldn't call having
a near-death experience "easy".
I doubt that's all they had planned;
there might be more coming.
What should we do, Yuuji? Run?
Run from what?
Tada!
Oh, you've all changed into your yukatas!
Yes, it's for the festival!
What do you think, Akihisa?
Y-Yeah, it looks good on you.
I think this is my first time wearing a yukata.
Oh yeah, you did grow up overseas after all!
Wh-What?
Oh, uhh... it's nothing.
Were you enamored with Minami just now?
She's especially cute in a yukata, isn't she?
What are you—
Kimonos are great because they flatter even a modest bust.
I don't really get what you mean.
Jeez, if you don't understand; then let me teach you.
Watch this.
Flap.
You see that? His reaction was much quicker than usual!
What's wrong?! Pull yourself together, Voyeur!
This isn't at all bad.
Yuuji.
How does my yukata look?
Pretty good, I guess.
Then... will you... marry me?
No way.
Then, would you like to get engaged?
Not in the least.
Then, Yuuji—
No thanks!
—want to stay alive?
Shouko, you're so damn cute!
Yuuji, you really should be honest like that more often.
I was threatened!
Mother said that all was fair in love and war.
What's going on with the girls?
I thought they'd all be angry.
Well then, everyone;
let's head out to the festival!
Let's go, Akira!
We don't want to be late.
This is only my second ever Japanese festival. I'm so excited!
It'd be bad if we're late.
Let's get going!
S-Sure.
It's pretty lively!
It all looks so fun!
Oh, they have doner kebabs.
They look delicious!
Don't they? Let's try one.
As part of your punishment, they're your treat!
I shouldn't have said anything.
Do you want one, Aki?
I'll go get it.
Sure, I don't min—
What?! You're treating me?
Is something the matter?
No! Not really...
But why?
Doner Kebab
I don't think she's forgiven me yet.
Why don't you just split it with me?
I'd like to try some other stuff as well.
Sure, you go ahead first.
Oh, you don't mind? All right then—
It seems the Japanese ones don't use lamb.
Here, Aki, you try it!
Man it's good!
Oh, Aki?
You've got sauce on your cheek.
Th-Thanks, Sis.
Akihisa, I bought some takoyaki. Would you like one?
Thanks, Himeji. I'll take one.
Here!
Open up!
Is something wrong, Akihisa?
No, it's nothing.
Then, open up!
The hot, sticky filling and chewy octopus is just—
This isn't what you think, Sis!
I'm not doing anything improper!
Improper
What's the matter, Aki?
It didn't taste good?
Are you being an idiot again, Aki?
Don't get too worked up just because it's a festival.
You're such a child!
You say that, but you're pretty
excited as well, Minami!
Th-They gave me these as a bonus!
You've been in Germany for a long time. It's okay to get carried away!
Oh, right! Want to try some cotton candy? It's delicious!
S-Sure...
Here, open up!
Is it good?
Yeah, it's great.
I'm glad to hear it.
Yuuji.
Would you like some yakisoba?
S-Sure, that'd be great.
I have okonomiyaki too.
That's very nice of you.
Here's some ramune.
Th-Thanks!
I'm glad to see Yuuji's been forgiven too.
It is a festival after all! We just want to get along and enjoy ourselves!
Akihisa!
There are dyed chicklets over there!
I thought they'd become extinct!
No, the colors are just painted on.
Oh, they aren't a separate breed?
Of course not! Right, Voyeur?
Color the chick
I'll stain you with my color!
I'll stain you
with my color!!
Th-That's common sense.
Aki, are you enjoying the festival?
Yep!
Yuuji, is it fun?
Y-Yeah.
The First Annual Miss
Yukata Beauty Pageant
Oh, Akihisa, this looks like a fun event!
The First Annual Miss
Yukata Beauty Pageant
The First Annual Miss Yukata Beauty Pageant, huh?
The First Annual Miss
Yukata Beauty Pageant
Let's find the hottest
summer beauty in town!!
A beauty contest?
That looks fun!
A photo op.
Why don't we all go?
Yeah, how about everyone participates?
Oh! I'm not trying to force anyone.
I just thought we could make
some lasting summer memories.
Sounds good.
Really?
We should participate!
I'm sure it'll be memorable.
Sure, let's participate!
All of us, that is.
Run!
Where are you going, Aki?
We're all going to participate in the contest.
I-I don't understand what you're talking about!
Yeah, we don't get it!
You were hitting on girls.
Don't tell me you thought...
...we'd let you off the hook that easy!
It's all right! I brought a makeup kit with me!
Hold on! I don't have the figure for cross-dressing!
Please, just make-do with Akihisa!
You're only trying to save yourself! You traitor!
It's time for the both of you to give up.
Look at Tsuchiya, he's taking it like a real man!
You're so cruel, Hideyoshi!
Sorry, I couldn't do it half-heartedly.
Makeup is a useful skill in theater after all.
Yoshii Akiko
Even still, you didn't have to go all out.
Tsuchiya Koumi
Shame.
I'm Tsuchiya Koumi? This is just...
Hong Shuu Ri
Voyeur, you're still doing better than me;
I'm supposed to be a girl and a foreigner!
A foreign athlete certainly could have a body like Yuuji's.
All three of you look really nice!
Yeah, you guys look super cute!
Aki, I'm so happy you've become such a beautiful child!
That's not something you say to your little brother.
Yuuji, you need more sex appeal.
You dressed me like this! So don't complain!
By the way,
why am I participating as well?
That's just standard practice.
Question 2
Translate the following English
sentence into Japanese.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Although John tried to take the airplane for Japan
with his wife's homemade lunch,
he noticed that he forgot the passport on the way.
Teacher's Comment
Correct.
It's John.
Tsuchiya Kouta's Answer
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
John took his homemade passpart
and boarded the flight to Japan.
Jane -
Please carefully consider what
"homemade passport" means.
The First Annual Miss Yukata
Beauty Pageant will now begin!
The First Annual Miss Yukata Beauty Pageant
M.C.
Obata
Our sponsor, Mr Obata, will the the judge for tonight!
Please say a few words about tonight's event.
I'm looking forward to seeing this summer's new beauties.
Yoshii Akiko
Do your best out there!
Don't worry! They'll never know!
Yuuji, you can win if you believe in yourself.
Like hell I could!
I'll be making a full record of your cuteness!
Dammit!
What should we do, Yuuji?
Let's just lose quickly and get out of these clothes!
Wait, why don't we just reveal ourselves?
That won't work.
There might be someone in the audience who knows us.
Yeah, if we try that we'll not only be cross-dressing freaks;
but ones that are bold enough to
take part in a contest like this!
I'll lose all my credibility if that happens!
You lost that long ago.
Listen, the only way out of this predicament is to lose this contest fair and square!
Our manhood's on the line here!
Thank you for your support.
Part 1 - Fin
Please support us~
New Serialization
Part 2 starts now!
All right, entry no. 1, please step on to the stage!
Inner voice
Contest
Points
Inner voice
Hmm... What should I do?
What now?
Inner voice
Hmm... What should I do?
Please tell us your name.
I'll hide my face
and answer timidly.
I'll hide my face and answer timidly.
My name is.... Yoshii Akiko.
Oh, you're quite the shy one.
That elegant look of hers is quite adorable.
She'll score well.
Why?!
I'll hide my face
and answer timidly.
WHY!?
What kind of things are you good at?
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here, I might get called
out when the audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I just lie flat out here,
I might get called out when the
audience asks me questions.
If I use half-truths,
it might sound more believable.
I'm good at cooking things such as: carbonara and paella.
If I use half-truths,
it might sound more believable.
Do you cook at home?
If I use half-truths,
it might sound more believable.
I just can't leave
the cooking to my Sis.
Yes, I do. Everyday.
I just can't leave
the cooking to my Sis.
That's quite rare for a girl nowadays.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I just can't leave
the cooking to my Sis.
I'm a guy, damn it!
I don't!
I don't have one!
The First Annual Miss Yukata Beauty Pageant
Looking for a guy
I don't have one!
That's a good news for the guys out here.
Any comments, Mr. Obata?
I'll give you some "pocket money" if
you give me your cell phone number!
If you weren't the sponsor, I'm quite sure you'd have been dealt with by now.
So, what precautions do you take when putting on your yukata?
Inner voice
Contest
Points
I'm a guy, damn it!
I try not to show off my curves.
If I don't want to
blow my cover that is.
I see, any comments on that, Mr. Obata?
I would like to know if you're wearing any underwear!
Underwear?! Like panties and bras?!
Of course I'm not!
Contest
Points
Thank you for that shocking answer.
Contest
Points
Nice high score.
Damn it!
Inner voice
I'll blow my score by
giving dull answers.
Please tell us your name.
I am Tsuchiya Koumi.
Did you swim today?
Yes.
Inner voice
I'll blow my score by
giving dull answers.
Inner voice
I'll blow my score by
giving dull answers.
Inner voice
I'll blow my score by
giving dull answers.
Inner voice
I'll blow my score by
giving dull answers.
Inner voice
I'll blow my score by
giving dull answers.
Inner voice
Do you always wear a yukata?
No.
Did you come here with your friends?
Yes.
Are they here?
No.
Other than yukatas, what sort of clothes do you like?
Contest
Points
China dress', kimonos, leotards, lady suits, sailor suits,
school uniforms, sports wear, race queen, cheerleader,
nurse, stewardess, waitress, policewoman, shrine maiden,
maid outfits, and similar clothes— I'm sorry, forget that.
A shocking revelation by Koumi indeed.
Allthough she looks collected on the
outside, she's quite the avid cosplayer.
P-Please forget what I said!
The First Annual Miss Yukata Beauty Pageant
Koumi
O-Oh no...
Take a look at this huge response!
She might just win the contest!
Ugh.. it'd bother me...
The First Annual Miss Yukata Beauty Pageant
Nice own-goal!
Why did I blurt that out?
Hong Shuu Ri here, nice to meet ya!
Inner voice
Heh, looking like this, I'll lose this
contest easily. Sorry Akihisa, but I'll
be getting out of this way before you.
Inner voice
Heh, looking like this, I'll lose this
contest easily. Sorry Akihisa, but I'll
be getting out of this way before you.
Inner voice
Heh, looking like this, I'll lose this
contest easily. Sorry Akihisa, but I'll
be getting out of this way before you.
Inner voice
Heh, looking like this, I'll lose this
contest easily. Sorry Akihisa, but I'll
be getting out of this way before you.
Inner voice
Heh, looking like this, I'll lose this
contest easily. Sorry Akihisa, but I'll
be getting out of this way before you.
Inner voice
Heh, looking like this, I'll lose this
contest easily. Sorry Akihisa, but I'll
be getting out of this way before you.
Hmm, another tall contestant?
What do you think, Mr. Obata?
Wonderful, I love tall girls!
Heh, looking like this, I'll lose this
contest easily. Sorry Akihisa, but I'll
be getting out of this way before you.
WHAT?!
Heh, looking like this, I'll lose this
contest easily. Sorry Akihisa, but I'll
be getting out of this way before you.
WHAT?!
The judge has given high praise for this contestant!
Inner voice
WHAT?!
Are further questions—
Huh?
Why don't we go for a honeymoon in Cambodia?
My nationality would cause trouble!
It'll be fine as long as there's love, "my honey".
I ain't your honey!
You'll come to love me!
I totally hate you!
I don't mind starting out as friends!
I'll treasure you forever!
Shut up man or I'll pound you!
I'll gladly accept anything!
I won't forgive two-timing.
Shouko?!
How did it turn out like this?!
That was a scarring experience.
This is an unforgettable summer in so many ways.
Now I can never marry.
Good thing the contest was forced to stop.
Too bad for the contestants though.
We went a little overboard.
Should we leave it at that?
Considering what they went through.
It seems they've reflected on their
mistakes; so let's forgive them.
I wonder who would've won if the contest had gone on.
Hmm, Hideyoshi would've made a fine winner.
Do you really think it would be "fine" for a man to win?
Voyeur was pretty cute in that yukata.
What do you think, Ms. Akihisa?
Let me see,
I'm used to Aki's crossdressing; so seeing the others do it is quite refreshing.
Stop right there!
I don't crossdress!
What do you mean, Aki?
You were sleeping with a skirt on yesterday.
Wait! What have you been doing to me in my sleep?!
Don't worry, half of it was a lie.
Lie
Lie?
How can half of it be a lie?!
Lie
Because you only wore it up to your knees.
So I was half-dressed?!
No, in doujin terms, you were half-naked.
Half naked
Half-naked?!
Ok guys, it's done!
Let's eat!
It's delicious!
Sakamoto's really good at this.
I'm so proud of my husband.
I wanted to help out, but Akihisa wouldn't let me even
though I told him I wouldn't hurt anybody with the knives.
That's not it Himeji. The problem is your ability to kill without them.
Her food is lethal.
Killer food indeed.
We can't let her make something so deadly.
Why don't us girls have a cooking competition?
The guys can be the judges.
Don't give her a chance!
How would the competition be decided?
By techinical knockout.
That was quite a feast.
I'm not quite full yet though.
We ran out of food already.
Oh well, we'll just need to get something fresh.
Something fresh?
The sea is right in front of you!
Fresh clams taste great grilled.
You're right!
Now that you mention it...
I made a madeleine cake at home.
Let's go get those clams, Yuuji!
Yeah, let's get enough to last us the whole night!
The night sea looks quite enticing, right Voyeur?
Clams are my favorite!
What's up with them?
God only knows.
So, what happened to the madeleine?
Well I made it, but I left it on
the table and forgot to bring it.
That's too bad.
I'm too young to die!
kirameite kagayaite
煌めいて 輝いて
Sparkle and shine
denkyuu pikkanko
電球ぴっかんこ
Light bulb goes off!
(hai)
(はいっ)
Yes
shinten shinai yo
進展しないよ
I'm not making progress
dareka jama shiteru no no
誰か邪魔してる no no
Oh no, someone's in the way
zenzen tarinai
全然足りない
It's totally not enough
sore ga mondai no koubaisuu
それが問題の公倍数
That's the common multiple of the problem
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I kind of get it
nani ga hontou no koto beibee
何が本当のことベイベー
What is it really, baby
mitetara koko de
見てたらここで
If you're watching
tsukai shite yo beibee
使いしてよベイベー
This is our cue, baby
kotoba mo kazu mo kimi wo arawasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
Words and numbers can't express you
(chu chu chu chu)
(ちゅちゅちゅちゅっ)
(kiss kiss kiss kiss)
kokoro ga biribiri suru tesuto
心がビリビリするテスト
It's a mind-zapping test
(tesuto)
(テスト)
Test
onore no chiryoku de
己の知力で
To solve using my own knowledge
(yes and supaaku tsuite nanbaa)
(yes and スパークついてナンバー)
(Yes and with a spark, I call a number)
(I say number wa one)
(I say numberはone)
(I say it's number one)
omedetou ima kara
おめでとう 今から
Congratulations, from now on
kimi wa mai mai mai otakara
君はマイマイマイお宝
You're my treasure
tokubetsu nanda dou natte mo
特別なんだ どうなっても
You're special
gyuttori gyuttori hanasanai
ぎゅっとりぎゅっとり離さない
I won't let you go, no matter what
watashi wa koi shitai
私は恋したい
I want to love
yume ni genkai wa iranai
夢に限界はいらない
Dreams need no bounds
tokubetsu dayo ne acchate mo
特別だよね 会っちゃっても
It's special. Even if we meet
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
Please forgive me as is
kirameite kagayaite
煌めいた 輝いた
It sparkled and shined
seikai pittanko
正解ぴっかんこ
Now I have the answer!
(gyu)
(ぎゅっ)
Jeez, they're sleeping like kids as soon as we hit the road.
Guys will always be children at heart.
Look at those innocent sleeping faces.
How cute!
They must be exhausted from fooling around like that.
I'm glad they had a lot of fun.
I'm still surprised they fell asleep so quickly.
They were staggering before they got in the van.
They ate so much for breakfast; it must've made them sleepy.
They must've been starving.
You don't say! They didn't even leave anything for us!
It's really a shame, Mizuki.
Yeah,
I didn't get to ask them if they liked the breakfast I made.
Class 1 River
River Styx
(Underworld)
Scum
Back to the living
Come, join us!
It's great over here!
Question 3
Answer the following question.
Give some examples of items that are forbidden in school.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Manga, game consoles, and such
Teacher's Comment
Correct, as always, Himeji.
Academic institutions are not only a place of study,
but also a place to learn society's etiquettes.
Academic studies are important,
but learning to obey established rules is equally important.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 3: Give some examples of items that are forbidden in school.
Do snacks count as bananas?
Are you bananas?
Next episode, "Me, That Girl, and the Stuffed Doll!"
Me, That Girl, and the Stuffed Doll!
and
This will be on your test.