It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps god's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Ushio!
Don't let 'em grab us!
Piece of cake!
I'm back...
and better than ever!
Return
Gil.
My armor won't return.
It was blasted off me.
She eliminated the strays in an instant, hacking them with a touch of her hair.
So it appears you've grown, Irregular.
Ya snuck up behind me last time.
But this time, I won't lose!
Wait!
My hacking can destroy the armor!
Shide is just a human inside.
If I can break his armor, I'll finish him this time!
That's what ya think.
These events are slightly unexpected.
They just transferred her memories to revive her.
I should've killed her when I had the chance.
No point in looking back. Let's focus on the present.
We avoided the worst-case scenario of fighting two Ushios.
Yes.
Ushio, yer growth shall be yer downfall.
Now we can just kill ya here.
Her blade is certainly threatening.
But if I use my echo, I only risk losing my armor.
However, my blade can take yer life!
Stop.
What?
Wh-Why?
Mio? That ya?
What?! Hey!
Why are ya getting in my way?!
Calm down, Sis.
No, lemme punch him!
S-Seriously? That's yer strategy?
Wow, Shinpei.
Welcome back.
I'm glad you're well.
Shinpei, yer leg...
I jumped as hard as I could just now.
It's nothing.
Just a leg.
Take care of Sis, Shin.
Sure.
Shide!
Yes?
Where do you think I came from?
What did ya say?
He really can't detect the handprint when I hide inside Gil.
Later.
Don't let him shoot!
No way.
Gil is usually in the form of this pacifier.
Throw it for him to appear.
Can I try?
Feel free.
Here.
S-Sorry!
Are you okay, Sou?
Is he dead?
Nope.
What's it like inside?
It's creepy and pitch black,
but I could hear sounds from outside.
It's pitch black because Gil has no eyes.
He has keen hearing, so you can leave the fighting to him.
With Ryuunosuke's two-second foresight, Gil might give me a chance against Shide.
If Gil takes any damage when in sync, you'll feel it inside.
You need to be really careful.
We just need to confirm if we can disable the handprint signal inside Gil.
Right.
Haine will know as soon as the signal is gone.
I don't wanna give her too much time.
I want at least two hours.
Won't they notice Gil?
Gil's presence is just like any other stray, so they won't spot him among others.
Hide leaves in a forest, right?
What if they find out?
Is there a Plan B or C?
We'll play it by ear.
What?
Let's be ready for any outcome.
I like it!
I'll bring her back.
I'm back.
Shinpei, yer back.
Really? Shinpei?
How'd it go? Where's Ushio?
Shinpei?
I thought Shinpei was hiding in a
stray to search for and find Ushio.
Then he'd take two Ushios with him to attack Hiruko's grotto.
But that's not it.
So ya looped, Haine.
What did ya see?
He found his answer.
Ushio!
Hi, everyone!
Welcome back.
Where do you think I came from?
It's Hiruko's grotto.
He set the restart point there.
He was in the stray fer two hours to hide that.
He used the loop to bring Ushio back and go fer my throat.
Let's hurry and destroy Hiruko's true form.
July 24th
(10th loop)
Summer Time Rendering
Mr. Karikiri.
The portable shrine is almost ready.
Ah! Wait a second!
Huh?
Ow, this hurts!
Kogaito, I have one heck of a stomachache!
Are ya okay?
No, I can't do this! I got the runs! I need to be in the bathroom!
Oh my.
Ya want some medication fer that?
Take care of the rest.
What a mess.
It's flat outside but normal inside.
It feels weird.
I wonder if they found out our plans.
Yes, that's what we want.
They'll prioritize dealing with us now.
They can't start a massacre up there until they kill us.
Gil feels the presence of a shadow.
At two o'clock, 20 meters ahead.
They did figure it out.
Something shot at us!
Something like needles.
Teeth?
It's trying to pin the shadow!
Toki, I'll go out and fight!
It's fine.
I'll stop it.
You guys keep on going.
I can handle this.
What?! We can't just leave ya here!
I told ya to get yer ass moving!
We ain't got time to just be sitting around!
Gotcha.
Thanks.
No, I should thank you.
Thank you, Shinpei.
You even forgave me.
Tokiko.
Don't die.
You too. Don't slow everyone down.
Help...
Haine forced ya to wake up and fight.
Let's go, Gil.
We'll let this baby rest in peace.
A dead end!
No, Hiruko's burrow was on the other side.
Yeah, this wall is new.
This ain't just some dark wall.
I can't sense anything through it.
It's made of mud!
They're coming extremely quickly from the sea and shrine grounds.
Move.
There's blood!
It heals itself.
I'll give it a try.
Don't touch it!
What?
Ouch!
Ushio, yer hand...
That was close.
It almost hacked me back.
This wall is made of Hiruko's flesh.
Damn it!
We've come so far!
Hiruko is right there too!
We'll blast it with a bomb.
A bomb? We don't have one!
Yeah, we do.
Mio!
I had Mio steal something before we left.
Those...
Those are...
Fireworks!
Where is Shinpei?
At the wall.
He just touched it.
He chose such a sweet spot.
If his restart point were too far,
his attack wouldn't be a surprise.
But if he were too close, he knew ya would sense him.
Let's hurry.
My long life has taught me something.
A wall can't stand up forever.
They all come down in the end.
Did it work?
Yeah.
Let's go.
It smells like gunpowder and grilled steak.
Don't say that. I'll never be able to eat steak again.
I also smell raspberry and rum.
No way does it smell that good!
Get down, Nezu!
Wait fer me!
Don't mind me!
Go before the hole closes!
Ya wanna die, old man?!
When in doubt, do what yer future self would do.
Then ya won't have any regrets.
Please hold him here.
Ya got it.
Say hi to Ryuunosuke.
Yer so pathetic.
Masahito? Or is it Iwao?
Doesn't matter which, Ginny boy.
Move aside. I don't want my childhood friend to die.
I'd rather not hear ya scream.
Don't underestimate me.
If ya wanna go further, yer gonna have to kill me first!
Shinpei?
M-My head's gonna split in half.
It's Hiruko's presence.
Oh yeah, ya can feel shadows now.
Mother continuously emits a signal to control the shadows.
Once Sis modded me, it couldn't control me anymore.
Ever since, Mother's comforting sound became an unbearable screech.
We shadows can ignore that creepy feeling, but Shin can't.
No way.
Let's make this quick.
U-Ushio, are ya okay?
I'm fine.
Just focus on my presence.
The ringing stopped.
Mother's signal is becoming subdued.
It stopped.
Right?
Thanks.
Sis emitted the same frequency to neutralize it.
How can she do that?
Ushio.
Yes. Let's finish this.
We used up the fireworks.
No problem.
We've got my fists.
I'll punch my way straight through that wall, no matter how many tries it takes.
Sounds good.
But there's one thing.
Ryuunosuke can see two seconds ahead.
Follow my line of sight.
Shide! We'll finish this now!
She moved her hair at high speed to form a barrier.
Too shallow.
He can detect Ushio's movements.
Haine's back from the shrine.
He really is two seconds ahead.
When Shinpei has his left eye closed, I can sense Ryuunosuke.
That's how he dodged Shide's attacks in the last loop.
Just like with Hizuru, he could strengthen his body as well.
Shinpei gained the power to fight us.
That's what he learned.
Ya really did it this time, Hizuru.
As long as Haine is watching me,
Ryuunosuke's foresight isn't an advantage.
If I foresee and tell Ushio, Haine can observe that and Shide will dodge her attack.
That's fine, though.
He experienced how powerful Ushio is last time.
Shide knows that her blow would be fatal.
That's why they must focus on her.
That's when we lure Haine...
to the kill zone!
I can almost smell yer bloodlust, Mio.
I can detect the exact position of all shadows from this distance.
Fer instance, there's a nail gun copy behind the rocks.
Which means someone is hiding there.
Sou!
What?
This is the kill zone!
Yes!
I can't move.
Sou?
I didn't sense him.
But I wouldn't.
He's just a human.
His nail gun must be Nezu's original.
The gun I sensed was Ushio's copy.
A decoy.
No, this ain't the time to analyze things.
Oh, it hurts.
Take a bird's-eye view.
What was my mistake?
No! This isn't right!
What's important is...
What's important is what's happening in two seconds.
What they're doing two seconds from now.
I need to warn Shide...
I told ya.
Quit acting so cocky all the time.
Ya pathetic human.
This is so much fun!
I can sense it all.
Haine's pain.
Her thirst.
Her sadness.
Her loneliness.
Ya wanna go home, to a place where time doesn't exist, nor does death.
You'll be with yer family, the people ya love, forever.
It'd be so nice.
But unfortunately, we'll never understand ya.
No!
These hands of yers aren't made to hurt people.
I want ya to use 'em to hold hands,
to stroke someone's head, or to hug.
We...
It's disappearing.
The mud.
The armor Haine gave me.
They got Haine.
Haine!
I'll disappear when Mother dies.
Bye, Shin.
Ushio!
I don't get it, Shinpei.
Huh?
I killed the bad guy.
It's all over.
But I can't stop crying.
Ushio, yer eye...
Shinpei!
Wait.
Neither me nor Sis have disappeared.
Mother is still alive.
What?!
Ya went easy on her, Sis.
My right eye feels like it's on fire...
Shinpei!
I can sense a presence coming from my right eye and Ushio's right eye.
But what is it?
How wonderful.
Shide.
N-No way.
How is he still moving?
We definitely killed both of him.
Is he immortal?
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time
Endless Night