Oreki residence.
Hello, this is Chitanda. I'm sorry
to bother you on a day off.
Mm-hm.
I realize this is sudden,
but do you have any plans
for the day after tomorrow?
Nope.
Thank goodness. Um, Oreki-san,
I am keenly aware
that it is putting you out
to ask this out of the blue,
but would you please carry my parasol?
Carry a parasol?
Yes.
I'm not sure what you mean by that.
I-I'm sorry, I didn't
explain myself very well.
Um... In essence, the shrine near
my home is holding a Dolls' Festival.
Dolls' Festival?
But it's already April.
They go by the old calendar. As it happens,
one of the dolls' parasol-bearers
unexpectedly got hurt,
and no one else can fit his costume.
But, Oreki-san, you appear
to be the same size.
Hold on... a person holds the parasol?
Yes. Please, can I ask
you to help us out?
Hm...
All right. I'll be there.
Do you really mean it?!
Thank you very much!
I just have to stand next to them, right?
No, we'll have you walk alongside.
Walk? With the dolls?
Yes, that's right.
So the dolls walk?
Yes.
How does a doll...
Oreki-san! Please stop
saying "dolls" so much.
I'm a little bit embarrassed by it myself.
Don't tell me the dolls are...
Yes. In Mizunashi Shrine's
"Live Doll Festival,"
girls act the part of live dolls.
Oh...
For the past few years,
I have been charged with
playing the part of a doll.
"Head upstream along the brook,
and take Chokyu Bridge
past the cherry tree."
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
The Doll That Took the Long Way Around
Oh, that must be it... a cherry tree
in bloom out of season.
Chokyu Bridge
Road Closed
Did Chitanda not know
about the construction?
Excuse me! Is it okay for me to cross here?
Yeah, you're fine.
We're about to start working, though,
so you won't be able to cross back.
Okay.
Assembly Hall
Excuse me!
Hanai-san, I brought them.
Ah, in the hall, please.
You bet.
Excuse me...
Who are you?
My name is Oreki. I was
asked to carry a parasol.
Hm...
Did you not hear about it from Chitanda?
I'm the substitute for the parasol-bearer.
Oh, you're here to take Hazawa's place?
Ah, sorry about that. Come right on in.
Hanai-san, who's in charge of the saké?
I assigned the saké to Nakatake-san.
Nakatake-san, are we okay?
Yeah, it's been ordered.
Never mind that, what about
that business this afternoon?
I asked the maid to handle it.
Are you sure?
Hey, do we have any spare banners?
In the hall.
Oh. I'll go check.
Oreki-san...
Yes?
You'll be carrying the parasol for
Chitanda-san's daughter, right?
That is what I understood.
Hanai-san! Telephone. It's the newspaper.
Ugh, for the love of...
I just can't get comfortable.
Nakatake!
How are you doing with the saké?!
It will be here by 1:00.
Stupid idiot!
The parade gets back at 12:30!
You think 1:00 will be in time?!
Have them move it up!
Right away, sir.
For crying out loud...
Oh...
Y-Yes?
Are you the one that
Chitanda-san requested?
Oh, yes. My name is Oreki.
Thanks for coming all this way.
We're just so shorthanded,
and it's a crying shame that we
have to trouble an outsider.
We appreciate all your help today.
On the contrary, I'm sorry that
a stranger like me is intruding.
I will try to keep out
of everyone's way.
If I step out of line in any way,
please let me know.
Hm... A stalwart young man.
First time in my life
anyone's called me that.
Oreki-san, wasn't it?
You just take it easy until it's time.
Fukiya-san, what about the
parishioner representatives?
Taken care of.
And the children?
And the live dolls?
A little longer.
All right. Tanimoto,
is Chokyu Bridge good to go?
I've put Murai-sensei in charge of that.
So, they've knocked off the
construction work, right?
Road Closed
Yes. He said he would take care of it.
Actually, they have begun
construction work on Chokyu Bridge.
What did you say?
Tanimoto! You checked
this out, didn't you?!
I-I reminded Murai-sensei about it!
Oreki-san...
are you certain about this?
Yes.
Sono-kun!
Yes, sir?
I hate to do this, but hop in
the truck, and go make sure.
Yes, sir.
Tanimoto-kun...
Yes, sir?
Call Murai-kun... no, put in a call
to Nakagawa Construction.
Yes, sir.
Will that cover it, Hanai-kun?
Yes.
Is there something wrong going on?
The procession crosses Chokyu Bridge.
Oh.
I hope you're simply mistaken about this.
Why is he glaring at me?
It's true! They've started construction!
Tanimoto! This is on you!
N-No, something's not right here!
I know that Murai-sensei put in
a call to the construction office.
He told them not to
start construction today.
Then why did they?
However, the day before yesterday,
they said they got a call
to go ahead as scheduled.
From who?!
Well, I guess they didn't get a name...
The workers told me the same thing.
Hm...
Never mind the reasons,
we have to deal with this now.
Isn't there any way we can
get them to halt construction?
It's too late for that.
The TV crew is already here,
and what do we do if there's an
accident and someone gets hurt?
We'd better think of a way to go around it.
What if they took the same
route and doubled back?
Like, go down the east side
of the river, then returned?
That may be fine for the east side,
but what about the west?
No dolls for them?
Good point.
Then what if they go as far as
Chokyu Bridge, then back,
and then take the western route?
Walking twice the procession
route is out of the question.
Then what if they go halfway to the bridge,
turn around, and then
go down the west side?
You want to do something
that ridiculous on TV?
So what do you want us to do?!
We could have them go down to Toji Bridge.
Hm?
If they cross at Toji Bridge,
and come back via Kaya Bridge,
it works out to just be a little
longer than the original route.
Toji Bridge, huh?
That would be, you know...
Excuse me, is there someone
here named Oreki-san?
Yes, what is it?
Chitanda-san's daughter
is asking for you.
What does she want?
Who knows?
Live Doll Makeup and Dressing Room
Is that you, Oreki-san?
Y-Yeah.
Forgive me for speaking to you like this.
I'm in the middle of
getting dressed, you see.
That is Chitanda, right?
I called you here for one reason alone...
Some kind of trouble
has arisen, hasn't it?
Yeah...
Is it something serious?
Sounds like it.
I see.
Then please tell me what has happened.
There is little time left.
Some bridge named
Chokyu Bridge has been...
so it's been proposed that we
take a route including Toji Bridge.
But when the others heard that, they...
Are you listening?
Yes, I am.
When the others heard that, for some
reason, they all made a sour face.
And that's it.
That was a very well-constructed retelling.
Thanks.
Oreki-san, can I ask you
to relay a message?
Yeah.
I will speak to the other shrine's priest.
I will ask my father to call
the parishioner representative.
Please tell them that.
That's all you want me to say?
They should know what it means.
That's what she said.
Okay, let's do that, then.
All right, everyone, our route
will detour across Toji Bridge.
What are you waiting for?!
Start getting things ready!
Shunbun ('Middle of Spring')
When the sun crosseth the center of
the heavens, and day and night are equal
Hyouka
Yes, Toji Bridge! Toji Bridge!
We already contacted Takahashi-san
in the traffic division!
Hanai-san! The cameraman is asking
where he should shoot from.
Um, weren't you able
to take over this part?
I'm not the right size for the costume.
Okay, true enough.
Besides, it's a rare sight to
see this kind of a procession,
which is why I came
back home just for this.
If I'm in the parade, I can't watch it.
'Zat so?
That should do it.
Well, what do you think?
Doesn't really suit you, huh?
I concur.
26th Annual Kamiyama Live Dolls Festival
I'm freezing.
Is that...
Irisu-senpai?
Ah...
Aw, crap.
Not good.
This is not good.
I'm thinking that I probably
shouldn't have come, for any reason.
Toji Bridge
My energy-saving ways
are coming under deadly threat.
I can't see Chitanda.
I have to know... I have to know...
If only I could see
Chitanda now, from the front,
all rouged up and gazing downward,
how would that be...?
Hotaro!
Man, that was fantastic.
Nothing could match Chitanda-san
and Irisu-senpai's elegance.
They really were pretty, weren't they?
So where are Chitanda-san
and the others now?
The main building. They said
they were purging their impurity.
Hm.
By the way, Hotaro, that outfit
did not suit you in the least.
Leave me alone.
Really. What a waste.
Just keep running your mouths.
I'm going to go buy another one of these.
Oreki, thanks.
For what?
That Valentine matter. I haven't really
had a chance to say it before.
Sure.
How's it been ever since?
Well, not half-bad.
Okay.
I snapped at him, too.
It's not often I lay into him.
Mm-hm, I heard.
Oh, Irisu-senpai...
Hey, Oreki-kun.
You were the emperor doll, huh?
It's a long story. Speaking of which,
I heard about Chokyu Bridge.
A lot of it doesn't add up
for me. What do you think?
Huh... Oh, that's a good
question. I'm not too sure.
I see. Knowing you, I thought you'd
be able to unravel the mystery.
Please stop that.
Oreki-kun...
Hm?
Back then I had a role to fulfill.
But today, I'm just the emperor.
As carefree as I am,
I'm not going to mislead you.
Uh-huh...
Oreki-san...
Oreki-san!
W-What?
Today was awful! I've been holding
it in this whole, whole time!
Yeah, being a live doll?
You're a trouper.
Not that! I mean Chokyu Bridge!
I mean Nakagawa Construction!
Oh, that?
I've been thinking it through.
But since I was playing my part,
I had to just grin and bear it.
Though I kept wanting and wanting
to ask about it, by which I mean...
"I am curious."
That's right! Oreki-san, you have
to be aware of much of it, right?
Well, there is one person I had in mind.
Ah, so do I. What do you say
we both write it down,
and then show each other
at the same time?
Fine with me, but write on what?
Here.
Good to go? Okay, ready, set...
Konari's son
Brown hair
Konari-san's son has brown hair.
We're both talking about the same guy?
Yes. Why did you think so?
Hm...
First, there doesn't seem to be
any question they got a call
telling them they were free
to work today, right?
Yes, I believe so.
Then, who would have made that phone call?
Everyone was all helter-skelter today,
but there was a single person
acting on the assumption
that we wouldn't be going
across Chokyu Bridge.
And you're saying that that
was Konari-san's son?
Yeah. I spoke to him while
getting dressed up.
Brown-hair told me that he
"came back home just for this,"
because "it's a rare sight to
see this kind of a procession."
He did?
But it's strange, right?
They hold this festival every year.
For someone who's from here,
it wouldn't be "a rare sight to see."
You're right, that is a little odd.
However, "a rare sight"
did come up this year.
What do you think it was?
They altered the route, right?
Which took us around Toji Bridge...
Ah! The cherry tree!
Yes, the cherry tree,
blooming out of season.
And only by taking today's
route would you see it.
The spectacle of a living doll
passing under cherry blossoms
is indeed a procession that's
"a rare sight to see."
For something as frivolous as that?
I wouldn't say that.
Oreki-san?
But never mind me,
why did you think it was him?
Well, you see...
Konari-san's son is the only
person I could think of
who wouldn't even care about doing
something so shameful to so many.
I see.
But after hearing what you said,
Oreki-san, I'm convinced.
Meaning what?
Apparently, it was Konari-san's son's
dream to become a photographer.
He's going to a vocational
school in Osaka to learn how.
Ah, so that's why...
I'm sure he wanted to take
a photo of a rare sight.
Could be.
Oreki-san, back in that room,
I mentioned contacting the other
shrine's priest, remember?
Yeah. That settled all the
commotion on the spot.
It may seem like a trivial
matter, but please listen.
Okay.
Road Closed
Long ago, this area was divided
into north and south halves.
The north half was our village,
and the south half was another village,
and I understand they had disputes
over territory and water.
This was all a long time ago,
but for a shrine ritual like this,
crossing over without permission
is even now a source of contention.
Ah, so that's why.
They wanted to inform them ahead of time,
but there aren't many people who
have the channels to make that call.
And that's where you stepped in.
Once I contacted the other side,
we could cross to the south
with peace of mind.
Indeed. No wonder Satoshi
calls yours a prestigious family.
I'm not so sure.
It's a small world, isn't it?
All I did was act as liaison
between the north and south sides
of a small community north of Kamiyama.
Of course, I don't consider it
to be of much importance,
but I also don't think of it
as being insignificant.
You may... have a point, there.
If I manage to make it to college,
I'm still going to come back here.
No matter what route I might take,
my final destination will be
this place. This place, right here.
Oreki-san, what did you choose
for your 2nd-year science and lit?
Oh, I chose lit.
I chose science.
You did?
I'm not put off or despondent
about coming back here.
As the Chitanda family's daughter,
I wish to fulfill the role that befits me.
I have long thought about the
means by which I will do that.
The means, huh?
I believe there to be two of them.
One of the ways is to have us all prosper
by developing a highly
marketable commodity.
The other way, from a managerially
strategic perspective,
is to make our production more efficient,
so we don't all grow poor.
Ultimately, I chose to pursue the former.
Which is why you chose the sciences.
Yes.
Yeah, I definitely don't think you're
cut out for the latter option.
That's something I found out
during the culture festival,
when I went around making
trouble for everyone.
I probably have no aptitude
for managing a company.
You're right. I think so, too.
Hm?
Please look around, Oreki-san.
This is where I belong.
There is nothing here but water and earth.
The people are all gradually
growing old and tired.
I don't think that this is the most
beautiful place in the world.
I don't think that it's full
of potential, either. Still...
Oreki-san, I wanted you to see it.
By the way...
As far as that managerial
perspective you gave up on...
What if I were to pursue that?
By the way... what?
Oh, nothing.
I...
I wonder if this is the way
Satoshi felt back then.
It's starting to get chilly, huh?
No, it's spring, already.
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?