I ran away.
My legs froze and I couldn't move.
The past will be only too happy to chase you.
What happened?
The Slasher kind of...
And so...banzai!
Hurry!
You're not thinking of joining the Dollars, are you?
No way.
You can't run from the past, Masaomi.
Don't!
Some great person once said,
"The world is a construct of the mind."
I think.
Even if he didn't say it, I'm sure someone said something like it.
Hey, welcome!
Long time no see. Thanks for coming.
It's cheap.
I'll give you a discount, boss Kadota.
Who here's a boss?
Oh yeah, five plates of your cheapest sushi.
Alright.
So, what does the head of the Gold Bandannas want with us?
For us, the world of fiction is a playground
that's just as important as reality.
Fiction and reality are equally valuable, so it's not like we hate reality.
You'd understand if he said that he wants to talk with the Dollars, right?
Fine, then.
I'll say this in advance, but we don't know much and the Slasher's attacked our members, too.
It'd be a great help to us if you
could clear up that misunderstanding, Kida.
Well, I...
Drink tea?
Catechin is good.
Hot!
It's okay, boss.
If you clear your mind of all worldly thoughts, even flames feel cool.
Don't angry.
It's WEEEALLY hot.
I bet you really do know how to speak Japanese.
Anyway, it's crazy that you can hold on to those hot tea mugs.
You might be the only ones thinking that.
Huh?
The Dollars have neither a vertical nor horizontal hierarchy, right?
So there might be a secret faction that you don't know about.
And if they slash their own members, no one will suspect them.
I see.
Well, I guess that makes sense.
And? What's their motive?
What's the point in destroying the Gold Bandannas by posing as the
Slasher if they aren't motivated by greed or making a name for themselves.
If I knew that, then there wouldn't be any
problem and we could assume it's just a grudge.
A grudge?
I haven't heard of any fights between
the Gold Bandannas and the Dollars.
Not with the Dollars.
The Blue Squares...
Kida...
I haven't forgotten what they did to us, and
even though that incident was basically settled,
that doesn't mean my hatred for them has vanished.
That's what I think.
So that's why you've come to us?
Hey, you understand, don't you, Kadota?
I want you to tell me the name of the Dollars' boss.
If possible, I'd get some of your old friends—guys from the Blue Squares who're in the Dollars—
Don't, Kida.
Don't go mixing fantasy with reality like that.
Huh?
The Blue Squares never existed.
Let's leave it at that.
You're—You're saying that Saki was attacked by
a group that never existed, leaving her hospitalized—
That's right.
Your ex-girlfriend was attacked by a group that didn't exist.
That's good enough.
Karisawa, you're about to make me angry!
You already are angry, aren't you?
Besides, Yuma-chi got angry before you did.
So you're even.
Just like how you're angry about what happened to your girlfriend,
some people are angry that others say
the Slasher is colluding with the Dollars.
If you don't think we're all even based on that,
then you shouldn't have brought up this topic.
It's true that we have some debts to pay.
If you, who ran away—unlike Dotachin,
who saved Saki—want to bring up the past again,
we're going to dispel that past form this world
by saying it was a product of our imaginations.
If reality is as equally valuable as fiction, then you should just
chalk up the parts of the past you don't need to your imagination.
That's how we do things.
You're wrong, Karisawa.
What? I am?
Assuming that the Blue squares did exist,
they're the ones who were attacked first.
And yet, they were just protesting against
being unfairly labeled as the bad guys.
Oh, yeah!
I'm so embarrassed!
I'm so totally embarrassed!
I'm...sorry.
No, we're also to blame.
We truly regret the whole Saki incident.
No, I should be thanking you for what you did back there.
We'd understand even if you did hate us...
...since we did all that to a mere middle schooler.
But you didn't do anything wrong, Kadota...
No matter how much you want to,
you can't erase the fact that you had a part in it.
Anyway, I'll be up-front about this: I don't know who our boss is, nor do I have any intentions of finding that out.
Also, I'll say it again.
The Slasher has nothing to do with the Dollars, and we
have no reason to start a fight with the Gold Bandannas.
I understand.
Come to think of it, there is one guy who knows our boss.
Who is it?!
Hold on!
What's the point of asking him?
Supposing that you find out our boss's name from that guy, do you plan on having a leisurely talk over some tea?
Or maybe you'll have some Gold Bandanna members kidnap him?
I'm just after the Slasher.
Is that the consensus of all the Gold Bandannas?
Huh?
I'll cooperate as long as I know that you can keep your subordinates in line like in the old days.
However, they've changed in your absence.
You can't say that you haven't noticed.
I...still view them—the members of the Gold Bandannas—as my friends.
You don't even know what to do, do you?
Assuming it was the work of the Dollars, does that even concern you now?
It's because of these gang wars that you...
...ran away.
But the reality you thought you dispelled
tends to come back in different forms.
However, this time it's not only my friends in the Gold Bandannas.
Huh?
This time, someone important to me who had nothing to do with either the Gold Bandannas or my past was attacked.
I can't forgive that.
Isn't that your—
Yes, it's my own problem.
I'm just using the Gold Bandannas as an
excuse to solve my own personal problem.
I won't say anything, since you realize all that.
All we can do now is leave it up to the discretion of our boss and the guy who knows him.
Eh?
However!
If, after that, you still view us as your one-and-only enemy...
If I still view you as that... What?
We'll take you up on your offer to fight.
You're prepared for that, right?
You understand that as long as you wave the flag of vengeance,
this will be different from some sandlot
scuffle kids your age engage in, don't you?
I...
You're scaring the other customers.
Take that kind of talk outside.
Here you are.
Five orders of Kremlin hand-rolled sushi, boss.
You fight?
That's because you're hungry.
Eat sushi and fill your stomachs.
Fulfill your dreams.
The human stomach is a dream factory.
Thanks, Simon.
Th-Th-Thanks for the food.
That owner's insane!
Hey, isn't this usually called attempted murder?
Well, I guess knives can cut that deep.
Bluurghhh!
See you, Kida.
Make sure you don't half-ass anything from here on out.
That owner really is crazy, huh?
If that had missed by even a bit, I would've been done for.
Sorry, but I thought he was kind of cool.
Me, too.
He made me think of a protagonist in a food manga who does Sambo and tells people not to play with knives.
Maybe he's a former martial arts instructor for the Russian military who
fought with the mafia and is now hiding under the guise of a sushi chef!
If that were true, he'd never open such a conspicuous store like Russia Sushi.
Horada, Horada...
What's that, Kadota?
Are you chanting some kind of curse?
And so Dotachin sang out, "Horada, Horada!"
Is it a binding spell, or maybe a summoning one?
It might be an electrical attack one.
Kida told you already!
Well, even after what happened before, investigating the Dollars won't lead to anything about the Slasher.
I... No, we think differently.
What?
There's a rumor that the black biker is in the Dollars.
Huh?
What's the black biker have to do with this?
Last night, we saw something unbelievable.
I see.
You're saying that the black biker is the
Slasher's accomplice because she helped it escape?
Moreover, the black biker attacked Horada.
Horada?
Horada...
Ah, so that's why you were saying, "Horada, Hora."
What's wrong? Why are you lost in thought all of a sudden?
It's no big deal, but... That's right, I might be wrong...
Wrong about what?
No, I just feel like I knew a guy with that name...
It all makes sense if there's a faction that's friends with
the black biker and they're targeting the Gold Bandannas.
Hey, Yuma-chi, isn't there something wrong with this conversation?
What about it?
Didn't the black biker take care of the Slasher earlier?
Togusa also ran it over.
In the end, Shizu-chan finished it off.
But then, there was that night when fifty people got slashed...
Maybe it's those victims?
Whichever it is, the Slasher won't come around ever again.
They wanted to fight with Heiwajima Shizuo.
You know how that ended, right?
But...
This is the number of the guy who knows our boss.
Do with it what you wish.
Cheer up.
I'll lose customers if you leave all depressed. Eat up, and leave with a cheerful expression.
Thank you very much.
Fights aren't good.
You're happy enough, so don't take away the happiness of others.
You should share it.
Hey, I just learned this:
"Parity is a good invention."
What does it mean?
You mean, "Charity is a good investment."
Are you an invention, Kida?
Are you? Are you?
This is really good.
I'm bored.
Having nothing to do certainly is boring.
Can I punch you?
That's fine by me. I'm paying you, aren't I?
Why'd you send chocolate to the Awakusu Association?
It was a gun, but so what?
C'mon, you knew that guy ran off with some handguns
from the Asakusu Association six months ago, didn't you?
Oh, the guy who that detestable dullahan was chasing.
Celty found and returned most of them without
any problems, but one still hasn't been recovered.
That's why...
I figured you'd be calling me sometime soon.
A scam?
Yeah, of course.
Okay. I'll be right there.
In the end, he was the only one who couldn't run from his past.
Some great person once said, "The world is a symbol."
I think.
Even if he didn't say it, I'm sure someone said something like it.
What a nostalgic expression.
It's the same as that face you made before.
Even though you were only a middle schooler, that expression was maturity incarnate.
While waxing nostalgic about those times, why don't I greet you like this?
Welcome back.
I know what you're going to ask.
Well, I could've just answered over the phone, but...
I doubt the gravity of the matter was appropriate.
I hear your friend was slashed?
Her name's Sonohara Anri, isn't it?
It seems like this girl is much more important to you than your buddies in the Gold Bandannas.
Long, long ago, a boy influenced by manga and TV
dramas decided to start a group called the Gold Bandannas.
The Gold Bandannas fought with another group that used blue as their distinguishing color, and got into trouble.
Let's fight!
Come at me if you want.
And then a brilliant military strategist came on the scene.
Why are they all pretty girls?
However, it wasn't Zhuge Liang, but actually Cao Cao.
Meanwhile, the gang they were hunting down captured his princess, and although the boy tried to save her, he got scared and—
Suppose the girl you liked were caught up
in the Gold Bandannas' fight and injured...
I see, I see.
It'd be exactly like that incident with Saki.
Is this what you're thinking:
"I was supposed to be in love with Saki, but I got scared and couldn't save her."
"Maybe my love for her wasn't real?"
"Maybe I just liked her for her body."
"Maybe I don't like her as much as I thought I did."
He sure can fire that stuff off.
Or maybe you actually want it to be that way now.
If that's so, then you should be able to
risk your life for the girl you love and fight.
Sonohara Anri's your touchstone for that, right?
If that's what you want to believe, go ahead.
Huh?
I just want to see this through.
Your revenge on the Slasher?
Or the annihilation of the Dollars?
Depending on your answer, it could be both.
I like how you've made up your mind.
I get it.
This is all so you can move on.
That's why I'll gladly tell you the facts about the truth, and the reality you can't do anything about.
This is an example of how three separate entities can coalesce into one, according to the times.
By the way, how's Mikado doing?
Huh?
C'mon, you introduced me to him this spring.
Your friend, Ryugamine Mikado.
What does he have to do with this?
Well, I figured he'd be really concerned about your situation.
He's got nothing to do with this!
I've never told him about my involvement with the Gold
Bandannas, and he's as immature but super-energetic as always.
He lives every day like he enjoys it.
Ooh, maybe you're jealous of the peaceful life he's leading.
That's why I'm telling you he has nothing to do with this!
And what if he does?
Huh?
Oh, I see. So Mikado's doing well, huh?
So, he's enjoying life that much even
though he's the reason his friend is suffering?
Wait a minute! What you mean by that, Izaya?!
You know what I mean.
Your BFF Ryugamine Mikado is the leader of the Dollars.
Although you may be the only one who thinks you're friends.
Reality is such a pain.
Those of us who were fed up with that kind of reality decided to remake it.
We'd set up a partition,
separate what's important to us from what was trash,
put only the things we loved on our side,
and got rid of the rest.
It wasn't that bad once we started!
We found that we could make a world
completely out of moe, tsundere, and boy's love!
It was an incredible discovery!
That's the only way to do a good job of separating fiction from reality.
Did you hear?
Apparently, the Gold Bandannas and the Dollars got in another fight.
Again...?
How scary.
It was just the kind of scuffle they always have, wasn't it?
I heard that this time they attacked the Gold Bandannas' hideout directly.
How bold of them.
You know,
there's also the headless rider.
What if she's partnered up with the Slasher
and attacked the Gold Bandannas' secret base?
Uh...
What's wrong, Setton?
This again...
There's no way even you'd believe that, Kanra.
That's just nonsense.
Saika has entered the chat room.
What are you all talking about?
We're talking about anime. (lol)
Saika has entered the chat room.
No we're not, Setton.
Saika, we're talking about what's happening with the new special effects movie.
Oh, I see.
You too, Tanaka Taro...?
It's really interesting.
They've changed producers twice so far this year, and all the scriptwriters have been replaced!
I'll make sure to check it out.
By the way...
This is just gossip, but...
What is it?
I've heard that the Gold Bandannas' shogun wants to meet with the boss of the Dollars!
Really?!
Masaomi!
What's up? You didn't stop by my classroom before leaving.
Well, I've got stuff to do...
Also, you were absent yesterday, so...
You look all better.
Um, Kida...
Ah, there you are!
Takeguchi?
Ryugamine, did you tell anyone that I'm in the Dollars?!
How about you, Kida?!
What are you talking about?
Oh, you don't know?
The Dollars are fighting with the Gold Bandannas again.
Some guy was asking people about me today.
I haven't told anybody.
Me neither.
Okay, then.
See you!
Uh, okay.
Bye.
I've got to go, too.
What? Let's go home together...
Something just came up.
My ardent female fans just won't leave me alone.
Guess.
See you!
Masaomi...
Got it? No more fighting!
Even if you're provoked, bear with it.
But, Shogun...
Don't give them a reason to take advantage of you.
If you think the Slasher is part of the Dollars, then go get some evidence!
Shogun!
You said you'd meet with the Dollars' boss;
did you learn anything from that?
No.
There are some here who say they can't tolerate being
looked down on anymore after that incident two days ago.
If they go out of control...
If that happens, I'll prepare for the worst.
Why don't I tell you how you got into this mess?
It's because you don't have a color.
You'd be naïve to think that you're safe just because...
...you don't have a color!
In reality, no one will help you if you don't have a color.
An organization where no one's bound by anyone...
As if!
After all, it's nothing more than some people playing around on the Internet!
I'll remove that crap from reality!
We're the Gold Bandannas.
Sometimes, reality employs plot developments befitting a poorly constructed 2-D production.
Masaomi?
Takeguchi...
Eh?
...was attacked by the Gold Bandannas.
Takeguchi was?!
I'm going to visit him in the hospital.
Why couldn't I stop back then?
What do I know about the Dollars?
At this rate, nothing about everyday life will change.
But...
Next Time: At A Loss