Sunshine Dynamite!
So long has time flown, and with it countless Precure have risen to stand in my way.
But today's shall be the last.
The Flowers of all Hearts have withered,
and the Great Heart Tree has all but perished.
The Earth belongs to I, Dune!
Tsubomi...
Tsubomi!
Grandma?
Grandma?!
Huh?
What's the matter?
Did you have a nightmare or something?
Don't worry yourself.
Seeing your face made me forget what it was about.
To think, my little Tsubomi's grown this big.
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Ah, Lord Coupe...
Lord Coupe...
What's the matter, dears?
You all seem rather exhausted.
We are!
The thing is, when we fought that new Desertrian the other day...
We did kinda win, but things were looking bad for a second there.
After that, we kind of talked things over,
and we realized we had to get stronger too.
And then I remembered that I'd heard about you getting this amazing power before, Cure Flower!
That you had this amazing object that'd raise
someone's strength and potential to infinite levels!
If you had shomething that good, you should've told us earlier!
So, where is it?!
It's still far too soon for you to use it.
The HeartCatch Mirage.
A Showdown With the Hottie?
We Weren't Expecting This!
The HeartCatch Mirage...
It's a most mysterious item that grants a Precure infinite power.
Fifty years ago, I confronted Dune, the Desert King, as Cure Flower.
With the last of my power,
I used the HeartCatch Mirage.
Somehow I managed to hold Dune to a stalemate,
but because I exceeded the limit of my powers,
I lost the ability to become Cure Flower.
I want to help you all grow, but only at your own pace.
Please, just forget about it.
That's not like you at all, Grandma!
Huh?
"If you give up without even trying, it's all over."
You always said that to encourage me!
I don't mean to sound out of line,
but we're really serious about this!
If we do fall in battle to a Desertrian, then we won't be able to protect everyone's hearts.
We'll take on any challenge!
We won't learn anything if we don't even try, right?!
Grandma,
how can we find the HeartCatch Mirage?
It's in the Precure Palace.
Once she lost her powers,
Cure Flower placed the HeartCatch Mirage in the Precures' castle, the Precure Palace.
Is that not correct, Kaoruko?
The Precure Palace?
Yuri...
The Desert Apostles grow ever stronger.
I think it would be best if they at least had
the HeartCatch Mirage in their possession.
The Precure Palace?! So we just need to go there, right?!
Where is it, exactly?
You can't just walk in and take it!
An arduous trial awaits you.
We're ready to take on whatever trial we have to!
Bring it on!
Grandma, I'm not your little Tsubomi anymore.
I understand.
I'll take you to the Precure Palace.
There was a place like this here in the botanical gardens?!
Yuri, won't you come with us?
What?
I'd like you to be there to watch us, Yuri.
Potpourri.
Yesh?
You have a Seed with you, right?
You mean thish?
That's the key that'll open the door to the Precure Palace.
Place the Seed in that opening.
Shure!
See you later.
The Desert King Dune's castle draws ever closer.
Fifty years ago...
It's because I didn't defeat the
Desert King that they must fight.
Where are we?
Look!
That is the Precure Palace.
Now, prepare yourselves!
Right!
Seeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Right then, let's go hunt some treasure!
Eek!
W-We're way too high up!
Don't look down! If you don't look then it's not scary!
Just relax. We're here with you.
Okay.
It's just like before.
The Great Heart Tree has come to watch over the HeartCatch Mirage's trial.
Dark Precure!
I was defeated by Dark Precure.
Before I could even undertake my trial.
Let's go.
Potpourri?
Wait for me, pleashe!
Incredible.
What is this place?
Someone's there!
Huh?! Grandma?!
I am Cure Flower, Precure of a bygone age.
In accordance with the ancient laws,
I guard the legendary HeartCatch Mirage.
Have you the heart and strength to obtain it?
I shall be your judge!
Now step forth and show you are capable of defeating me!
The HeartCatch Mirage is a mysterious item that boasts great power.
If you are to receive it, you must bear a strong heart.
Now, show me your strong hearts!
Is this...
Defeating the previous generation's Precure.
That is the trial one must undergo to obtain the HeartCatch Mirage.
Long ago, I came here and
defeated the Precure before me,
and obtained the HeartCatch Mirage.
No way.
I can't fight you, Grandma!
Even if it is your trial, I can't fight you either, Tsubomi.
So he shall fight in my place!
You're...
Why are you...
Hey! It's that mysterious hunk!
Who's he?
He looks just like your grandma's husband.
He's this guy who always saves us when we're in trouble!
Why's he here?
Your fight against the Desert
Apostles will grow ever tougher.
You need to have the resolve to
persevere, no matter what befalls you.
If you lack that resolve, you
should abandon being Precures!
I've always had a bit of a secret crush on you,
but...
there are things that we have to protect!
If defeating you is the trial we have to overcome,
th-then I will surpass you!
Yuri, take the fairies and get back!
All right!
Now, show me!
Show me the strength of your hearts!
Blossom Shower!
Marine Shoot!
Blossom! Marine!
Sunflower Aegis!
She's good at protecting her front,
but not her sides!
You're all still far too inexperienced.
I knew it was too early for you to undergo this trial.
You can do it!
Blossom, fight!
Marine, show some guts!
Sunshine, don't loshe!
Give it everything you've got!
You can do it!
Give it your all!
We are giving it our all!
They've kinda brightened me up a bit, though.
Yeah, guess so!
It's true that we might be inexperienced...
...but...
...as long as we work together, nothing is impossible!
Let's do it!
Right!
Marine!
Sunshine!
Sunflower Aegis!
Now!
Nice teamwork!
They actually managed to predict his moves!
We'll show you the strength of our hearts, pretty boy!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Precure Shining Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
You've really grown.
Huh?
Seriously?!
Lord Coupe?!
That mysterious hottie was
Lord Coupe this whole time?!
Lord Coupe!
I can't believe it was you, Lord Coupe.
I totally didn't realize!
Lord Coupe, you really are amazing!
But why was he in that form?
He wanted to be by Kaoruko's side in
the form of the person she most loved.
I'm sure that was Lord Coupe's way of showing his affection.
After all, a fairy wishes for nothing more than to give their partner strength.
I had a crush on him, and now my heart's been broken again!
Come on, cheer up!
I'm sure you'll find someone!
Potpourri, can you lend me that Seed again?
Shure!
Everyone, place your hands together.
Right.
You too, Yuri.
Huh?
The Seed changed shape!
It's proof that you have passed your trial.
Now place the Seed here.
Okay.
Brave new Precures, you have
done well to complete your trial.
Um, who are you?
It's the spirit of all the previous Precures speaking to you.
Precures...
Protect everything that lives in this world.
Protect the Flowers within all their Hearts.
This is the HeartCatch Mirage.
We grant it to you.
Thank you very much!
Now we'll be able to become stronger, right?
Maybe Yuri can become a Precure again!
Huh?
When I heard the Mirage can make your potential grow to infinite levels, we did some thinking.
If we obtained it, maybe you
could become a Precure again!
Coupe...
Fifty years ago, it was just you and me.
But things are different now.
They'll be all right.
As long as they work together, I'm sure of it.
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
An unbelievable miracle has happened!
With passion and justice burning quietly in her heart...
...and an elegant and stylish outfit!
Sleek, swaying long hair...
...and a firm, gallant silhouette!
It can only be her!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
The strongest Precure is about to make her entrance!
HeartCatch Precure:
Cure Moonlight
is Finally Revived!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!