Okay, we'll stop here for now.
Good idea.
Eh?
What's wrong, Akihisa-kun?
It feels like since midterms, it's been really glitchy.
Oh, it's gone.
Do you know how to use it?
You read the instruction manual, right?
Let's see...
Do not touch with wet hands.
Do not touch with wet hands
Do not put pressure on it.
Do not put pressure on it
Do not use it as a still ring.
Do not use it as a still ring
Do not give it to your girlfriend.
Do not give it to your girlfriend
Do not pawn it.
Do not pawn it
Do not leave within reach of children.
Do not leave within reach of
children
It doesn't say anything useful.
Wait...
For ages 13 and up.
For ages
and up
That's it!
I'm older than that!
Maybe physically.
No way.
I have books for ages 18 and up!
Please, explain further...
Based on what you say...
This is where they get the saying "Out of the mouth comes trouble."
Question 12
"Love, Courage, and Our Battle Has Only Begun! (Temporary)"
Rise and shine, Aki-kun.
Good morning, Nee-san.
Breakfast is ready.
Since you're having an Exam War with Class A,
I made you something so that you'd do well today.
Sign - Good Luck
Since it sounds like "beat the enemy," I made steak and pork—
TL Note: The kanji is written as "teki," meaning enemy, and the katakana is written as "teki," meaning beef steak.
Really?
—pictures and placed them under your pillow.
Eh? Only pictures?
So? Are you filled with confidence now?
This joke is so twisted that I'm not sure if you want me to win.
Really? Well, you are at that age where you've got a huge appetite,
so I guess just pictures can't satisfy you.
I thought that might be the case, so I made—
Really?
a video of me eating real food.
Why a video?!
And you went and eat steak by yourself?!
It was rather difficult.
I was completely full, but I still had to keep on eating.
Then why didn't you just let me have them?!
Oh, Aki-kun, you're so bold.
You're mistaken!
I don't want to eat that!
Sign - Akira
But this!
Sign - Meat
Rather than that, Aki-kun,
why aren't you giving me your thoughts on my swimsuit?
I have too many thoughts already.
There's no room for any about the swimsuit!
While we're on the subject, why are you eating in your swimsuit?
Because the video director said that you'd be happier if I did.
Video director?
Director       :      Ninja Pervert
Editing      :      Ninja Pervert
Production      :      Silver Link
Ah.
". . . Ah"
Fumizuki Academy is a school based around results.
Victory!
Any academic skills you have don't matter if you don't show them on the test.
Sign - Academic Skills
Sign - Test
That's why Mizuki is in Class F, right?
They said that personal health was part of the testing—he even lectured me about it.
Then we'll focus on results, too.
Sign - Pragmatism
What do you mean?
Beat  Them!!
I mean that the battle will start before the bell even rings.
Hideyoshi.
These are Sister's private belongings.
Her uniforms and books and the like.
If we want to find her weakness...
These should be enough.
I'll come up with something.
As expected of Class A.
How do you do these math questions?
Can I see?
I'm good at math.
Shinji
Yuuichi
Th-Th-This is....
There isn't an answer to this one!
I can't do this kind of multiplication!
A question that neither Mizuki-san and Minami can solve, huh?
She really is amazing.
There's more, too.
Why are these things so expensive when they're so thin?
I'm confiscating all of these. Confiscating!
It's still too soon for Akihisa-kun.
Akihisa, take these and go declare war on Class A.
What? I'm tired of this life of abuse.
It'll be fine this time.
Just pretend you found her beloved belongings and were kind enough to return them to her.
Oh.
That way, she'll be extremely thankful and politely listen to me.
Kinoshita-san!
You dropped this!
No!
I'm never trusting anyone again.
Don't trust them
Are you guys heartless?
Sister?
Barged in
I can't believe you!
You aren't getting away with this!
So you came to check out your future tables?
Com
posed
You kidding me? How could Class A lose to Class F?
Please don't get upset
You idiots should take a rest.
Idi... ot.
That's not what she means.
Idiots should realize they're idiots and stay in their crappy Class F.
Dumping fuel
on fire
Stop trying to cause trouble.
That's not it.
Even if Class F's scores are bad, we still aren't trash!
But you're still Class F.
Himeji-san.
You wouldn't have normally been placed in Class F, right?
Or maybe you do belong here.
You've been in Class F for so long that you've become a real idiot, too, haven't you?
What kind of bull are you spouting?
How is Himeji-san suited to be in Class F?
Akihisa.
You're admitting that Class F is the worst.
After the Exam War, I'll personally give you our fruit boxes.
Please treasure them.
You'll regret this by the end of school.
Be ready.
The first phase is complete.
But how do we fight Class A?
We can't win if we go head on against them.
We've already used Kirishima's weakness already.
It won't work this time.
Yeah, there's no way she'd make the same mistake twice.
Why do you guys think that I refused to exchange setups after our other victories?
The seeds I planted have finished growing.
It's time to begin the harvest.
A Mock Summoned Being Exam War?
I do want to declare a real war,
but there's the three-month restriction on the ability to declare war after a loss.
So why don't we just do a practice war for now?
We need to fight Class F this afternoon.
We don't have the time.
Didn't you guys attack Class F while they were recovering from the war they had just won?
I guess this is how Class A really is.
But saying that you lost because you were fatigued from your fight with us is a rather unsightly excuse, too.
Are you saying that we'll lose to Class F?
Fine. We'll take you on as a warm-up.
Any objections, Class rep?
I don't care.
Warm-up? Seems like they're underestimating us.
Really? How can we lose to some cross-dressing idiot?
Wh—
We will now being Class A and Class B's Mock Summoned Being Exam War!
Start!
Wipe them out in a flash!
Summon!
Seems like it's begun.
Hideyoshi, you're up.
Got it.
So? Do I look like a girl?
So quick...
I thought that a girl's enemy was only other girls.
What are these complicated feelings?
Amazing, Hideyoshi.
So you really were a true, beautiful girl after all!
I'm a boy!
I already said I'm a boy!
He's changed already...
I learned how to change quickly in theater.
I'm a boy!
This kind of insignificant change—I can do it in a blink of an eye.
What are you doing, Ninja Pervert?
You should have told me that this was the plan!
Seems like he's angry because he didn't get the shot.
Well, time for the final preparation.
I am Kinoshita. I am Kino—
I am Kinoshita. Kinoshita by me.
My Kinoshita.
I am Kinoshita Yuuko.
You worthless pigs!
Huh? Wh-What? Why are you suddenly—
Don't talk to me.
Your foul stench is spreading over here.
I am Class A's Kinoshita Yuuko.
I'm here to talk to you piles of trash.
Trash?
Class A's room being in the same building as you lot, I just can't handle it!
A pigsty should be good enough for you guys!
Out of all the things to say, you're saying we're the same as Class F?
We're not trash of that degree.
What did you say?
Anyway, today we will be fighting with Class F,
so we don't have time to battle you guys.
But we'll be coming for you eventually.
Be prepared!
Wh-What arrogance?!
That's it.
Finally over?
That was a drag. Let's go.
You guys started it.
Class C Rep, Koyama Yuuka.
I request to have a Mock Summoned Being Exam War with Class A.
I'll shove those words back at you.
Y-Yuuka!
Why are you here?
S-So you had this kind of fetish...
N-No, Yuuka. Th-This is... Yuuka!
And so, their relationship reached a point beyond salvation.
Everybody, go!
Fight with all you've got!
Are they crazy? Aren't they afraid of dying?
All members, sortie!
Charge!
Onee-sama, please enjoy my gallant figure in battle!
We'll repay our debt to Class F!
Sign - Yeah!
Class A is beginning to suffer from fatigue due to these constant battles.
Class E will fight too!
Even we of Class E can deal them significant blows if we attack now!
If we don't want to owe Class F a favor, we'll need to do as much as we can!
Don't underestimate Class A.
Class E Rep, Nakabayashi Hiromi, requests a Mock Summoned Being Exam War.
You won't reject, right?
Awesome! Class E is holding its own against Class A!
Exam Wars are physically draining.
Class E has a lot of athletic students, while Class A has students who spend all their time studying and none of it working out.
When they start getting tired, they'll lose their focus.
And because it's a mock war, there's no benefit of being able to take Recovery Exams to replenish scores.
So this was why we didn't swap classroom equipment!
Make the other classes indebted to us.
Sign - Small
Smalls things can stack up and make a difference.
Sign - Victory
We aren't going for a quick victory,
but rather the creation of an alliance that we can use as battle strength.
Sign - Advantage
This is how you conduct a real war!
How dare you use these kinds of dirty tricks.
What are you talking about?
You tried to use the other classes to wear us out,
but I'll tell you right now, those level of attacks don't even tickle us!
Don't think we're that easy.
I didn't think you'd still be able to stand.
I should have expected that from Class A.
Talk big while you can.
Prepare to pay!
There's... something else you should be ready for, too.
Show me some enthusiasm!
Let's show those Class F idiots how pitiful they really are.
Everyone, this next war is for real.
Class Rep?
Fight with all you've got to defeat Class F.
Good luck, everyone.
What's our plan?
The stairs are right behind Class F's room.
The main force will charge directly at them while the secondary forces will surround them using the stairs.
Attack!
Nobody's here.
Where'd they go?
Did they run away?
Hey! We're right here!
There they are!
You'll start growing mold if you don't get some sunlight every once in a while.
Damn it. Those bastards!
When did they...?
All members, get to the school yards!
They're coming, Akihisa.
Okay.
All right, let's go out!
What's with this?
Damn it!
Everyone go!
Don't let them...
get away...
Welcome.
Supplementary lessons!
Go to supplementary classes if you're dead!
It's just like Class A to actually change shoes. How sophisticated.
We've forced our enemies to gather all at one spot.
If all our members focus their attack power on one person,
we can still win, even if the opponent is from Class A.
Very good. Continue to the next phase, Akihisa.
Okay!
All members, retreat!
Don't run away!
Why did you take off your pants?
No....
Now! Strike while they're worried about their pants!
As expected of Akihisa's Summoned Being.
It's the fastest one around!
All right! I have something to ask of you.
What is it, Ninja Pervert?
Next time... Next time, please go grab the girls' bras.
I'd knew you'd say that.
You guys are pretty good.
This time I'll be your opponent.
Okay! Ninja Pervert, watch this!
You're just wasting your energy.
I'm not wearing a bra today.
Not yet...
It's finally time for us to settle our fight once and for all, Ninja Pervert-kun.
Fight it out once and for all...
uses the characters for male and female...
Ninja Pervert!
I-I'm fine!
I'll get rid of her by myself!
Yoshii-kun, Your opponent is me.
Kubo-kun?
All right! Let's settle this!
You're too naive, Yoshii-kun.
If you so desire,
Sign - Love
I won't feel shameful no matter what I wear!
Come! Prepare yourself for my heart-throbbing-love-blow!
I will treat your attacks as signs of love...
Hey, Yoshii-kun! Let's also have a battle of life and death—
Use this chance!
What are you guys up to?
We've played long enough. Where's Class Rep Sakamoto-kun?
Your opponent is us!
The enemy is thinning out.
Hey guys!
Akihisa-kun!
Aki?
Looks like it's going well.
Our disruptive tactics seem to be particularly effective against these nerds!
So there you are.
Those tricks were a waste of time.
Impressed?
But this is as far as you'll go.
Yuuji, I will defeat you.
That's my line!
Let's finish this!
Permission granted!
Summoned Being, Summon!
Summon!
I'm not hitting them?
We've trained like crazy!
With the Black Golden Bracelet, we can summon without a teacher's supervision.
So we were able to undergo Summoned Being training!
Not only do you guys rarely use your Summoned Beings,
but you're also still worn out from all the mock wars!
It's too easy to dodge you guys!
Don't you get all cocky!
One hit and you're history!
Only if you manage to land one!
And...
Even if my battle strength is weak, I can still inflict damage if I hit!
Why? You guys are just Class F!
We're also properly learning!
But we're still a wee bit far from Class A.
How...
There!
Class rep!
It's people from Class A.
They came faster than I planned.
Akihisa!
Okay, Awaken!
This path is cut off until we're done.
Damn it! Everyone, push!
Your reinforcements can't reach you.
It's fine. I alone will be enough to handle you guys.
You sure talk big!
I'm going!
Yuuji!
Prepare yourself!
Come!
Actually being matched by these guys...
Why?
We're dealing with practice, not concept!
Great!
This last move will end it all!
What's wrong?
The bracelet is...
Damn it, it can't last any longer?
It was fine even when it went out of control!
What do you mean?!
Because you properly studied, it's hit its limit!
Then—
That thing can only be used by idiots!
Kinoshita-san!
Shouko!
Himeji-san!
Yuuji...
Shouko.
Akihisa-kun.
Himeji-san.
Aki!
What's happening?
Akihisa!
Are you okay, Yoshii-kun?!
Himeji-san!
Yoshii-kun!
We're saved.
Thank goodness. I was afraid that...
That was scary, Akihisa-kun!
Really... Really scary!
Akihisa-kun! Akihisa-kun! Akihisa-kun!
I was pretty scared, too.
Me too, I was scared to death!
That's great.
Seriously, you scared me.
U-Um... I saved you because...
Wh-Wh-What?!
I did it!
Eh, what?
Winner: Class A.
Eh?!
The thirteenth question.
What is the name of the wars that utilize exams at Fumizuki Academy?
Competitive entrance exams!
Please do not forget the premise of this story.
Next week:  Idiots, Tests, and Summoned Beings
This will be on the test.