It’s here!
These are pretty cool!
I know, huh!?
You think that’s cool…?
This is so cool!
Yes; I concur!
Hey now, you guys.
Asuna-san, um… we don’t have to wear these clothes as Chupa Team members, do we?
Eh? What’re you talking about? That’s why I made them in the first place! We gotta wear it everyday!
I will not wear it.
And I refuse to see Ojou-sama wear it, either!
Aww, this is awesome! Secchan, try one on!
O-Ojou-sama…
In any case, Ane-san…
Why the heck did you make so many?
Well, the more stuff we make, the cheaper our tankers will be!
I wonder ‘bout that, mya.
Well, there are people who stay in their pond and never know of the ocean. In a good way.
What are you talking about? You saying you got a problem with that?!
Ane-san, even if those tankers end up being cheaper, would you be able to compensate them even if you can’t sell all this?
You don’t have to be freaked out, mya.
Nah, it’s one of those moments where you gotta be shocked.
Shut the hell up!
Always busy, eh? This is the lodging house of Mahora Academy’s middle school division, Grade 9, Class A!
Ah! I showed up on the screen!
I’m sorry!
No problem at all!
by Sayo
I’ll take attendance now!
Let’s see…
Akashi Yuuna-san!
Here!
It looks like I got skipped again!
Asakura Kazumi-san!
…Asakura-san?
Eh? Oh, yeah, here!
Still tired?
Eh? Oh, I guess…
Um… next is… Ayase Yue-san!
I’m here.
Izumi Ako-san!
Here!
Ookouchi Akira-san.
Kakizaki Misa-san.
It gets pretty lonely, but you can’t do much about it when no one can see you.
Negi-sensei...
But you can see me, can’t you?
Of course!
Sensei!
Yes? What is it, Asakura-san?
It’s been on my mind since I was in the 7th grade, but…
Why is the seat next to me always empty?
Oh, about that…
Could it be that…!
I’m sorry, but give me a bit more time.
Eh?
I think I’ll be able to talk to you properly about it then.
A deep fog, I seek…
The shadow seen only by closed eyes,
the voice heard only by closed ears…
Cut through the fog
and appear before me.
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
I can see them! I can see them!
Takamichi, look! Spirits!
You can see ‘em? Good job, Negi-kun!
You finally got the result of studying half a year.
It’s all thanks to you, Takamichi-sensei. Thanks a lot!
Good for you, boy.
Thank you very much, Eva-san! I gotta go now!
Imbecile. I wasn’t complimenting you.
Master is glad that she can finally return to her peaceful living.
Geez. Every evening, there's an intrusion.
Sorry about that. We cannot afford to train magic in public after all.
Why me, anyway?
This place makes me calm, that’s why.
This is why you’re such a pain.
Please do not scare my master’s character.
If you are to say, say “this place fails to make me calm…”
That’s also a pain.
Then, say “This place is disgusting…”
You really want to be dismantled, don’t you?
Cut through the fog
and appear before me.
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
Sayo-san? You’re Aisaka Sayo-san, right!?
Eh? Ah… um…
I can see you! I’m finally able to see you!
It’s a pleasure to meet you. I’m the homeroom teacher, Negi Springfield.
Though… It’s probably weird that I’m saying “pleasure to meet you” and all…
Can you… can you really see me, Negi-sensei?
Yes, I can.
It’s a pleasure to meet you, too!
Uwaaah…
Aww, what a bad hobby!
You guys are so mean…
So anyway, you want us to buy this..?
I made a bit too much. Since we’re friends and all… I beg of you, please!
I see. Well, in regards to stuff like this, I don’t need anything, so… Natsumi, you buy something!
Eh?
W-wait a second, Chizu-nee! Why am I the only one buying something here!?
Natsumi, the structure of society is not as easy as you think.
Someday, you’ll understand…
Ehhhhh!?
Eh? Why am I a ghost, you ask?
Yes. People seem to think that one becomes a ghost only when one has any regrets.
That’s why, if we can solve your leftover memories, you’ll be able to rest in peace…
I see. Good idea, Negi-sensei!
I learned that stuff in the Magic Academy.
Leftover memories…
Remainder of thought, called a Spirit. That’s what my teacher said when I was still in school.
I was also told that spirits tend to have leftover feelings that are more on the emotional and painful side.
I know you may not want to share the details, but I want to help you! I want you to rest in peace!
Negi-sensei, I’m happy and all, but I’m afraid I’m unable to tell you anything.
Sayo-san…
I’m sorry.
Were your memories that painful…?
Actually, no!
It’s just that I don’t remember anything from when I was living!
It seems that I forgot my memories during the 40 years I’ve spent being a ghost!
Unit of Hell, we have come to greet! Compassion is futile!
FIRE!
Nipaa!
Yuuna, this is awesome! Well made!
I know, huh!?
This whole thing took me a week to make!
A bitter hobby, isn’t it..?
Asuna, your Oolong tea’s done!
Ah, thank you~
…the heck is this?
This is Ako’s hobby.
Lab instruments are so cool!
What another bitter hobby this is…
Speaking of which, Ako; buy a T-shirt!
Sorry, I don’t need one!
I’ll pass on that offer, too!
Eh!? But aren’t you a member!?
I was free on those days, so I just decided to take a peek.
Won’t you buy one? I’ll make a special discount, soo please~
I told you they wouldn’t sell.
What’d you say you little…!
ANIMAL ABUSE!
You can sense something in the Girls’ Dorm, right?
Yeah. More or less.
If that’s the case, there may be something in there that’ll help you regain your memories.
Let’s take a look!
Okay! I’ll do my best!
Ah, wait, Sayo-san!
Wait for me!
Hotline?
Yes. Hold this between your door, please.
Whenever something happens, you can contact me ASAP.
Basically, it’s a string phone, de gozaru.
I thought of this when Kaede-san said something!
Since we’re in the opposite room, I figured we should take advantage of this opportunity.
I see… A hotline, eh?
With this, I can be in contact with you 24 hours a day! Yes!
Hey, Secchan.
What is it?
A string phone, right?
Hey, Kaede-san! Can you say a little something through this for me?
“A little something,” de gozaru?
Wo-tay ets-say of rog-fay roaks-cay ake-may ix-say roaks-cay.
Whoa, I can hear it! It’s perfect!
Yup, you can.
But you know…
The sound went away!
Secchan, this is the door.
If the door’s on the string, you won’t be able to hear anything!
A... A BLIND SPOT!
Secchan, you’re silly.
Ah~ Oh my gosh~
What's wrong?
I got separated from Negi-sensei!
Oh no~ What should I do~
Sayo-san! Where are you?
Negi-kun!
What are you doing? And who’s “Sayo?”
Ah… um… You see… What was it…
What was that?
Sayo-san!
Negima!?
There was a ghost in here!?
Yeah… a weird voice came out of the string phone…
String phone?
Well, um… Long story.
In any case, where’s the ghost? Did it disappear?
Seems like it, de gozaru.
I was so scared!
A ghost in the Girls’ Dorm…
If that’s the case, I’ll just have to use magic to find Sayo-san.
Rastel
Mascir…
What are you doing?
How suspicious! You’re not hiding something, are you, Negi-kun?
No! Of course I’m not…
This isn’t something the Journalism Club is gonna let slide.
This isn’t good!
I placed orders to the Yukihiro Group Merchandising Club to produce...
Customized Negi-sensei alarm clocks in which the alarm is Negi-sensei’s voice!
Negi-sensei cups so you can see Negi-sensei’s smiling face when you’re done drinking.
Negi-sensei toasters that imprint Negi-sensei’s face on the toast!
Etcetera, etcetera.
Dang, this is amazing!
Though I’m used to all of this now.
As you can see, I’ll always be with Negi-sensei everyday.
In such beautiful living, why, why would I want to include this indecent thing!?
Don’t call me “indecent!”
You’re plenty indecent!
BIGGER ANIMAL ABUSE!
Hey now, Asuna, calm down.
By the way, Maki-chan, how can you be so comfortable wearing that?
Well, if I didn’t wear this, then Iinchou-san wouldn’t acknowledge me as a fellow classmate, so…
Anyhow, Asuna-san. Try someone else. I’m never going to buy any of your stuff.
Eh!? C’mon, buy a Chupa Tee!
MAH!?
Ah, I’ve been revived! Too bad I’m dead!
T-t-t-t-t-that!
What about it?
Maybe I’m… imagining things…
Learn to get a grip, Makie-san!
Chupa Tee!
Quiet down!
This is a big scoop! Why did Aisaka Sayo, Mahora Academy’s neighborhood ghost, die!?
What exactly happened 40 years ago!?
I’m burnin’! I’m burnin’ up here! My Journalism Club spirit’s flarin’ up!
Asakura-san…
Thanks for explaining, Negi-kun!
The mystery’s been solved!
Now I know that the empty seat next to me actually seated a ghost!
That’s why there wasn’t such thing written in the students’ record book, right!?
I’ll explain this to the whole class someday, but for now, please keep it a secret!
No!
Negi-kun, that’s against freedom of the press! We have the right to know.
So when the chance comes, I’ll tell it to the class-
Is that you, ghost?
Asakura-san!
Satsuki-san! Lingshen-san!
Negi-sensei…
The ghost! Did it show up?
Ghost!?
So is it really a ghost?
What happened?
There was an accident on the meat bun!
Meat bun…?
Looks like I stole some food!
Is that good, Yamamoto?
Is Yamamoto domesticated?
A bit. Right, Yamamoto?
So this fish’s name is Yamamoto-san? How interesting!
What’s wrong, Akira?
I feel… a shiver going down my spine.
Eh? I-I’m sorry!
Misora?
I-I’m so sorry!
Akira-san! Misora-san!
Was there a ghost here?
A ghost…?
You can do it, son-in-law!
Aw man…
I’m back…
Ah, welcome back! Were you able to sell any T-shirts?
As you can see here…!
Damn this society…
What another exaggerated reaction…
Oh, by the way. Asuna, there was a ghost here earlier!
Come on, this is bad.
Ojou-sama!
The ghost showed up in another room, too, de gozaru!
Eh?
Negi-sensei is currently pursuing it.
Negi-kun is?
Then let’s get to it!
Whaddya mean, “ghost?”
I can’t think of that sort of stuff at a time like this.
How cute…
Mya~!
Nodoka, you just took a bath; you’ll catch its hairs.
I’ll be fine!
Y-Yue!
I'm so good at this!
Yue! Nodoka!?
What’s wrong, aru?
Gho...
Ghost!?
Wow, I went through!
Wintermute!
Mmm, nummy!
Does this look good on me?
Zazie’s outfit… is alive.
You suspicious intruder…!
Ah, wait a second!
Go away.
Mana-san, STOP! STOP!
I’m very sorry… I was just so happy that I started to go off and play around.
Sayo-san…
So she’s over there.
I can’t really see her, though…
I’m so scared!
Desu!
It’s alright; she’s not scary!
She was just playing around tonight; she didn’t mean to cause any harm!
Even if you say she isn’t scary…
We don’t even know what she looks like, so we can’t really understand…
For all we know, she could be a dreadful figure…
Freaky...
This isn’t good…
If only I can at least get her in a picture…
It showed up! It showed up! Look!
You’re right!
Whaddya know,
she’s just a regular girl!
You… can see me?
You’re right! I showed up!
But how…?
Eva-san…
Way to go, Master
It’s so noisy there. I’m gonna go back and go to sleep.
You slept this afternoon.
So I’ve been raised as a sleeper.
And so, all’s well that ends well for the ghost, who has even made friends with Class A.
Have you regained any of your memories?
Is that so…
I’m sorry for causing such a ruckus earlier.
Don’t be! Thanks to you, I was able to introduce you to the rest of the class.
Negi-sensei!
Sayo-san, take your time; no need to confuse yourself. You have plenty of time!
Okay! If I remember anything, I’ll report it to you, Negi-sensei!
Okay!
And until then, I’ll be in your care!
Same here!
Rise!
Bow!
Be seated!
I’ll take attendance now.
Aisaka Sayo-san!
Here!
Eh? Who’s she?
Ta-da! We’re the Narutaki Twins who always get along!
Call me Fuuka!
I’m Fumika!
Remember us, ‘kay?
Next time! “Sensei, turn us into adults, please!”
Gah! I overslept!
Everyone marched already!
Good Morning, Baka Pink!
Ah, Court Lady, good morning! I’m sorry I’m late!
I have orders for you.
Okay!
Potatoes, carrots, onions, and ah, we’re out of milk, so get some, too.
A person for errands, am I..?