Hey, Shinpei.
Close yer eyes for a sec.
Ah, hold on. Wha—
All right. Ya can open 'em now.
Wh-What did you just do?
I gave ya a present!
I-I don't get it!
Say, Shinpei, how many years has it been since ya been home?
Huh? Let's see.
Since graduating middle school, so... two years?
No kiddin'.
Y'didn't even come back fer New Year's.
S-Sorry.
Give my regards to everyone when ya get there.
What do you mean?
Ushio, aren't you...
I'm not going.
Shinpei, don't forget to find me.
Wait.
Wait, please!
Protect Mio, okay?
Ushio!
Huh?
Wha—
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I-I didn't mean to—
I-I'm very sorry!
Port Kada to Hitogashima
I almost lost my life because of that weird dream.
Chill out.
A-At times like this,
I should take a step back and settle down.
That was the first time I've ever been slapped.
All right, I've simmered down.
We will be arriving at Hitogashima momentarily.
Oh.
Wakayama City, Wakayama Prefecture.
There's an island in the Kitan Strait, Hitogashima.
It's got a population of about 700.
The local specialties are yomogi mochi and preserved squid.
It's a tiny island supported by tourism and fishing.
It's been about two years since I've last been here.
I came back for my childhood friend's...
Kofune Ushio's funeral.
July 22nd
Hey!
Welcome back, Shin!
Mio.
Are ya tired from yer long trip?!
Wh-What're ya doin'?
I was a little sweaty, so I thought I'd go fer a swim.
Well, I'm glad you seem energetic at least.
Kofune Mio is Ushio's little sister.
She just lost her older sister.
She can't possibly be fine.
"Protect Mio," huh?
Geez.
Hey.
You all right?
The sea's salty.
So how's Tokyo?
Did ya go to Shibuya? Did ya?!
Nah, I didn't go out much.
I got snot on my towel...
I didn't need to know that!
How's the shop doin'?
Yeah, that's right. I want you to bring it.
It's super busy!
I see. You make most of your money during summer break, huh?
But there's so many people I don't know now.
Though, lately, even the people I know seem like strangers sometimes.
That so?
Well, there are a lot of tourists at this time of year.
Wh-What's up?
Yer soundin' like a real Tokyo boy, Shin!
What? Me?
It really rubbed off on ya.
Huh? You're kidding!
We chatted about random stuff along the way to the funeral.
Funeral
of Kofune.
Ushio..
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Kofune Ushio
Funeral Ceremony
I lost my parents ten years ago,
so the Kofune family took me in.
Goodbye, Summer Days
So to me, not only is Ushio
my childhood friend,
she's also family.
The day before I left the island, Ushio said she wanted me to make her curry.
And I said "Maybe next time," and blew her off.
But there never was a next time.
The poor thing.
I know it must be hard for Shinpei, too.
By the way, did ya hear?
Dr. Hishigata performed an autopsy on Ushio's body!
An autopsy?
Now that's just plum outrageous!
Who did that? No photos.
A flash?
Shinpei!
Ya finally came back, huh?
Sou!
Ushio...
She tried savin' a kid from drownin', and... got swept away!
I... I was there, but she...
I'm sorry, Shinpei.
Go ahead and...
hit me until ya feel better!
What's done is done.
Plus, with everyone crying, it actually makes it easier to remain calm.
Sh-Shinpei...
Hitogashima Hall
Hey, Sou.
I heard your dad performed an autopsy on Ushio.
Ushio died in an accident at sea, right?
Take a look at her.
That's Kobayakawa Shiori, man.
Y'know, from Koba Mart?
Oh. Man, she sure grew up.
She's in third grade now.
Remember what I said earlier?
The kid Ushio saved was none other than Shiori there.
That so?
Poor girl.
She hasn't said a word since the accident due to the shock.
No way...
It's time for the procession.
Shinpei.
Could you lend a hand?
Okay.
I'll give you a call tonight.
You'll get the details then.
Got it.
Bistro Kofune
Sorry I'm back so late, Shinpei.
Welcome home, Alan.
Welcome home!
Karikiri sure loves his speeches.
Mio, y'should be lendin' a hand!
My expertise is eatin'!
I'm almost done.
Sure smells nice.
That's Ushio's favorite dish, ain't it?
Mio, could you set the table?
There's a serving for her too, huh?
It's been so long since I've had your curry, Shin.
Thanks for the food.
What's this?
Whassa matter, Mio?
Whatcha starin' at yer own house for?
Ya get in a fight or somethin'?
Summer Time Rendering
Yeah.
So, why the autopsy?
Right...
That was just the rumor mill getting out of control.
He didn't open her up.
My dad was just there for the police's inquest.
Oh, is that all?
But...
they found marks on Ushio's neck.
Marks?
Yeah.
Like someone strangled her.
In other words, it's possible this was murder!
That day, we were playing on the beach behind the elementary school since the tourists don't go there.
When Shiori was drowning and getting swept away,
Ushio was the first to notice and went to save her.
Mio and I jumped in right after.
But there wasn't anyone suspicious around.
Does everyone know about the marks?
Of course not!
Only Mio, Mr. Alan, the police...
me, and my dad know.
But judging from the situation, it couldn't have been murder.
The police labeled it an accident. And that was that.
I see.
Got it. Yeah.
Thanks.
Mio?
Here.
This is the necklace Sis was wearin' in her last moments.
You should probably hold on to it.
Ushio had this?
Hey—
Wh-What's gotten into you?
At least dry yourself off first...
Hey, Shin...
I'm never...
gonna... see her again!
I can't stand it!
I can't!
Yeah.
I can't forgive the one who killed her!
H-Hey, Mio!
Do you know something?!
Y-You little!
Sorry.
It's nothin'.
You can have the bath next.
Sis would get mad if she saw me crying like this.
Today's the last day I shed a tear!
It's pretty.
Shinpei!
Thanks! I'll treasure it!
She still had this...
Bistro Kofune
July 23rd
The best thing to distract yourself from loss is to keep your body moving.
That's probably what Alan and Mio were thinking.
And me too.
Hey, Shinpei!
Yes?
Didja find who yew were lookin' fer?
Huh? Who was I looking for?
Ya told me when we met this mornin'!
'Member? Y'said she was wearin' glasses and had huge honkers!
Huh? Was that really me?
It's too early to be drinking this much, Nakamura.
Welcome in!
Man, it is scorchin'!
I'll have the usual, please.
Man, what's with today?
This guy is Totsumura Tetsu.
He's a relative of the Kofune's, and he's the island's only police officer.
Uh... "the usual," right?
Whoa!
What the? If it ain't Shinpei!
That stuff about Ushio...
What do I even say?
Welcome, Tetsu!
Mio! Still cute as ever, I see!
The usual B Lunch Set with an order of fried shrimp and medium-sized rice, right?
Ya got it!
What happened to ya this mornin'?
Ya didn't come to eat breakfast.
I know. Get a load of this.
It's totally crazy! Y'see...
The Kobayakawas have all vanished.
Kobaya...
Kobayakawa Shiori.
The kid Ushio saved was none other than her...
Vanished?
This morning, Koba Mart wasn't open at 8 AM.
So their neighbor, Shiomi's wife, took a peek into the main house and...
it was completely vacant inside!
Well, it looks like they had quite a debt built up.
Maybe they ran off in the middle of the night.
H-Hey, Mio!
Where are ya going?!
Lunch Specials
Pork Cutlet
Fried Fish
Spaghetti Napolitan
Sorry fer the wait.
All right!
Koba Mart
Weird that they came to the funeral yesterday.
The Kobayakawas.
Yeah.
Sorry about the shop.
It's fine.
Shiori's been a bit off lately.
Yeah, she's mute from the shock, right?
No.
Huh?
Before that, maybe a week before, she said somethin' weird.
That was when she was bug hunting on Mt. Takanosu. She saw...
Saw what?
A girl who looked just like herself.
The next day, whether she was on her way to school or in school,
she constantly felt like she was being watched.
What's that mean? Like a doppelganger maybe?
'Scuse me. Ain't that the Shadow?
Who's that?
That's Nezu. He's a hunter.
They call it the shadow sickness.
Shadow?
It's like a disease endemic to this island.
Not many have seen it in recent times, but it was quite common before the war.
If y'were taken with the shadow sickness,
you'd start seein' yer "Shadow."
Those who saw their Shadow died.
They were killed by their Shadow.
And it pretends to be who it killed,
then it kills everyone it lives with.
Least accordin' to legend.
So the afflicted would go to Hiruko to be cleansed.
That's what my gramps used to say.
What was that all about?
Hey, Shin.
My grandma told me the same story when I was little.
Have you heard the Shadow story before?
No, but... it's just a superstition, right?
Yeah, it should be.
But I saw Sis' Shadow.
It was three days before she passed.
We were picking up trash at Omoto Beach with a bunch of others.
At that moment...
Look, Mio.
Huh?
You idiot!
If that's a joke, I'm not laughing!
It's the truth!
But it disappeared right before our eyes!
Th-Then, three days later, she...
I'm worried about Shiori's family...
Calm down.
Calm down. Calm down!
Mio, have you told anyone else about this?
What happened to never crying again?
Let's go to Hiruko and ask about the Shadow.
That's what the old man said, right?
The cleansing and stuff.
So...
Shin...
Hiruko is the nickname for the
Hito Shrine in the northern part of the island.
No answer.
Are they out?
Let's go check out the worship hall.
Mio?
What's up?
Wait!
D-Did you see that?!
No, not clearly...
I swear that was Shiori just now.
What?
Let's go after her!
H-Hold on!
Hurry!
Nothin'...
Could she be even deeper in?
Up ahead is the abandoned fort.
It's dangerous to go in there.
Mio, let's take a step back and think.
There it is! Shin's "take a step back"!
Assuming that was Shiori, why'd she run from us?
Yeah, why would she?
A gunshot?
She's the one from the boat.
Shin! What're you spacing out for?!
She's bleeding! Look! Look!
R-Right.
What do we do?
What do we do, Shin?
I messed up...
I'll go get someone!
Hey! Mio!
Listen closely... to me...
Sh... She...
Dad's always sayin'...
Sh-Shin...
That until you wash the dishes and clean everythin' up...
service ain't over, y'know?
Ushio!
Huh?
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Shadow