Oh, there you are!
Minami, I brought some souvenirs fr—
You're looking... kinda grim.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
The Mysterious Girls?
Successors to the Legendary Keys!
The Dress Up Keys...
Lock must have taken them during our fight...
Girls,
keep your chins up.
Gloom won't get us anywhere.
Yeah, cheer up!
But still...
Without the Keys, we can't transform into Precures.
If Dysdark were to attack at this moment...
Then I shall fight.
And I shall reclaim your Keys.
I'll help, too!
Thanks, Perf.
Where am I?
Is this...
Hope Kingdom?
Something smells nice...
What's that?
Something else smells nice, too...
It couldn't be...
Are these Dress Up Keys?
Wait!
What's this all about?
It's the scent!
The scent of the Dress Up Keys?
This dress makes my nose even stronger!
Could it be that the Keys Lock stole are sending a distress signal?
The Dress Up Keys must have appeared in Perf's dream by trying to seek out the Precures!
Let's make haste!
Right!
I promise...
I'll take you all to the Keys!
Perf, what's wrong?
I lost the scent!
Calm down and attempt to find it again!
Huh?
Haruka and the others are gone.
We got separated?!
Heeey! Perf, Aroma!
Yuiyui! Towie!
Where did they go?
What's up?
Towa?
Perf?
Aroma?
Where are you?
Where are we?
Has this place always been on campus?
It's a garden party!
It's simply splendid!
Oh?
Might you be guests?
Bonjour.
B-Bonjour.
Er, where are...
Here?
This is our garden.
It is? Our apologies for intruding.
Worry not.
In fact, why not join us for tea?
Today's scones came out scrumptious.
That sounds splendid!
Well?
We'd normally be delighted...
But right now...
We're a bit bus—
Wh-What is the meaning of this?
Three Locks and Nine Keys?!
What in the world happened while I was away?
I didn't get to steal Twilight's Keys,
but these'll be plenty, 'kay?
I-Is that...
Yep, it's special-made.
With this lock...
I can do...
This, 'kay?
That power of dreams is mine, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Wh-What are you after?
The power of dreams is sinking into despair!
Oh, it's filled!
Just as I planned, 'kay?
Now...
we're all set.
It's scrumptious!
There's plenty more!
Whoah! These scones are as good as Marble Doughnuts!
Guess we've got similar tastes.
By the by, what brings you all here?
Well...
we lost something important.
What was it?
A key.
A key? What kind?
A precious key that protects the door to our dreams...
Dreams?
Dreams...
What dreams are those?
Tell us.
What are your dreams?
My dream...
is to become a world famous top model.
My dream is to benefit society like my father and brother.
My dream...
is to become a splendid princess.
I see.
They're all excellent dreams.
I hope they come true.
I know you girls can do it.
But...
it's looking grim...
You know, we have a dream, too.
It's a grand, lofty dream.
But...
But what?
Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil.
A Dyspairvil!
How?!
No way!
Dyspear!
Hairpin style!
Dy-Dyspear?!
You're kidding!
Dyspairvil!
Oh yeah!
Our Keys!
At a time like this?!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Let's run while we can.
We're gonna bolt!
Now!
What do we do?
Without our Keys...
We can't fight.
Haruka!
Are you okay?
Dyspairvil.
What now?
It'll find us in no time here.
But we can't keep running away forever.
So we've gotta fight!
That's absurd!
Dyspairviiil.
We have to...
We have to do something!
But what?
Anything!
Even if we can't transform,
and even if we can't run away, we have to do something!
If not, then it's all over!
Not just our dreams...
but their dreams, too!
That wouldn't be right!
We have to band together and save them!
Dyspairvil!
Run!
Girls!
Thank goodness!
You're all safe!
Now's your chance!
Dyspairvil.
We're not done!
We'll never give up!
Not until our dreams come true!
That's right! We have dreams!
Dreams to protect!
Dreams we want to come true!
Our dreams will never be engulfed by despair...
They're what give us strength!
Dyspair?
Thank you, Flora, Mermaid, Twinkle.
H-H-How do you know those names?!
Use this!
A Dress Up Key!
How?!
We'll explain later.
For now, do what you must.
Please,
use these to protect our dreams!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
Let's go!
Right!
Leave those to me!
Let's make our move as well!
Gotcha!
Dyspairvil.
Dyspair!
Dyspair?!
Over here!
Dyspair... vil!
Now's our chance!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Mermaid Ripple!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
Dreaming!
Next up...
Wait, what?
Dyspear... vanished?
Thank you, girls.
Could you three be...
The previous Princess Precures?
This is the realm of our memories.
It is the Hope Kingdom in which we once lived.
The realm of your memories...
So, like, a dream?
You girls must have been drawn into our dream.
But your fears and ours...
Must have overlapped,
giving birth to that phantom of despair.
Fear?
Of the great darkness.
We're sorry we allowed our precious Dress Up Keys to be stolen!
But you were still able to drive away the phantom of despair.
What matters most in this battle...
should be clear to you now, no?
To never give in to despair!
Because our drive to protect our dreams...
is what gives us the strength to fight!
Right?
It seems I've nothing to fear.
The darkness shall soon revive once more.
This time, with far greater power.
But that battle rests upon your shoulders.
Never forget that your willpower
shall open the doors to your dreams.
W-Wait! What was your dream?
To make Hope Kingdom a land forever brimming with hope.
Are these...
Dress Up Keys?
Their powerful dream...
must lie within these Keys.
Girls!
Where on Earth were you?
We've been looking for you for hours!
Sorry!
It's a long story.
Well you better start talking, 'cause—
Wha?! Are those...
Cherry Blossom Key!
Coral Key!
Galaxy Key!
H-How did you nab those?!
It's because Perf brought us here.
To make Hope Kingdom a land
forever brimming with hope, huh?
It's a big one, all right.
We'll protect it.
Yes.
That's why we must retrieve our stolen Keys as well.
Time to finally put this toy to use, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Th-The castle...
became a Dyspairvil?!
I'm liking this, 'kay?
Now let's have some fun, 'kay?
Wh-What?
What is that?!
Now then...
this game's gonna be fun, 'kay?
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Scarlet!
With the strength to live beyond any past,
none shall extinguish my flame
If we join hands and trust in eternity
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
No way!
The whole castle's a Dyspairvil?!
It's as enormous as it is powerful—of all the times for us to be unable to transform!
Now, into the castle! We must retrieve your Keys!
Yeah! Girls, let's go!
Go! Princess Precure:
To the Future!
The Culmination of Power, Princess Palace!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Kanagawa Prefecture - Momoko (Age 6)
Osaka Prefecture - Hiyori (Age 6)