Bye-bye! See ya tomorrow. See ya!
Haruka-chan! I'll sweep over here, okay?
Right! Then I'll move the desks.
Is this where the Underwear Appreciation Society is?
Can I join?
That underwear's used for sex, right?
Amahara Kiyono-san.
The first time we met, it was pretty amazing,
but why would she want to join the Underwear Appreciation Society?
Are you thinking about Amahara-san?
Ah, yeah. She really does seem a little odd.
Yeah. She was a really pretty girl, though.
Nayu! Haruka!
Yako-chan...!
What's happened?
You're panting so hard.
I knew it... that girl's... Amahara Kiyono's...
...a confirmed ex-virgin.
Oi, look.
Huh?
A fine view.
Just a bit more...
Hmm?
Ahem.
It seems like you were concerned about something up there...
N-Not really, right?
Yeah, let's get going.
Hold it! You were peeping up that girl's skirt, right?
We didn't!
Don't lie! You cannot trick my eyes!
Hey.
Are you that concerned about what's inside here?
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's the always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Extreme Adolescence
Hold it, hold it, don't be rash!
What happened then?
A teacher came by, the guys ran for it.
A terrible situation was averted.
Bah...
My heart was pounding.
That Amahara girl... is definitely a wild one.
Yako-chan, your face is all red.
Well to have something like that happen before your eyes...
Isn't that right!
You'd be surprised too if you saw it-
She's a really mysterious girl...
Underwear
Appreciation
Society
Activities in Progress
Erm...
I'm a first year, Hayama Nayu, and...
I'm in her class, Shiraishi Haruka.
Jinguuji Yako. Good to meet you.
My introduction... was made, so I'll pass.
More importantly, to think you've been having activities here...
Y-Yes! Mizuno-sensei discussed it with the school for us.
Hmm.
I thought about this yesterday,
but why is my class representative in here?
You're in the same class as Komachi-kun?!
Which would mean that you're as old as we are...
How unexpected.
I didn't expect this either.
So the class representative is interested in this sort of thing...
"This sort of thing"?
Indeed.
For instance: this sort of thing.
Amahara-san!
Why you...! This again!
You've reddened.
Ah, K-Komachi-kun!
If he wants to see it, he should say so!
Putting on a tough show like a fool.
Right?
Hmm?
By the way, you people.
It should be obvious for people in this society,
but you're all wearing underwear fitting for it, I presume.
Fitting for it?
Correct. For instance:
N-No, these are just something my mum bought!
Wow, back-prints at this age?
Isn't that just too childish by now?
That maker's junior briefs, they're great!
J-Junior?!
Their cotton makes it so soft!
Nayu-chan, you're getting off topic!
I won't ask you to wear a thong, but can't you do better?
With that sort of underwear, no man would be satisfied.
Well, it seems there are some that prefer the opposite...
Flipping my skirt up and then insulting them...
I'll show you no mercy!
For all that talk, you're nothing extraordinary.
I'll say this now,
but I joined this society to research
underwear befitting of a true woman.
A true woman?
To me, underwear is like... a weapon.
If nobody's allowed to see it, then there's no meaning.
Hmph! With such impressive words, and you're wearing that?
Sign: Forehead-poke
What are you doing?!
That's true.
Perhaps today's was too plain.
You'll be meeting tomorrow, correct?
I'll be going home now.
I don't plan to make excuses about me being here,
but remember that everyone has their own reasons.
Even I have mine...
Amahara-san... Will she be fine with stairs and such?
Seems like it'd be refreshing...
We shall now conduct the moral exam.
Be quiet now, and stay attentive.
We'll have the teachers make their examinations now.
Your hair and uniform are both okay.
Right, next!
I was nervous.
Yeah, they snuck this on us!
We're not breaking rules, and yet this still seems vile.
Your hair, isn't it permed?!
No, it isn't.
Their checking's pretty strict.
They're looking every bit over.
I wonder if this is how cats and dogs feel in a pet show!
I kind of get it, and I kind of don't.
Go and wash that off right now!
Are you listening, Amahara-san?
I'm telling you that you're too young for make-up.
I'm not too young in the slightest.
Indeed, I've been a woman since I was born.
Moreover, it's merely foundation.
Amahara-san, this way please.
Amahara Kiyono. She's definitely a confirmed delinquent.
Amahara-san...
A difficult girl, isn't she?
Mizuno-sensei, goodbye!
Bye! Be careful on the way home!
Honestly, she will not listen to anyone.
Amahara?
Yes. How is she in class?
Her grades aren't bad at all.
But she seems a little distant from the other girls.
It looks like lots of boys are interested in her too...
It's because this is when they develop their charm, right?
Even I'm a bit interested.
Thus her wearing make-up is all the more inexcusable!
Now, now...
It's just... she is definitely too tough to handle.
Tough to handle, hmm?
Indeed, I've been a woman from the moment I was born.
Ah... she's quite something...
I suppose sunscreen and gloss are just not enough...
H-Hayama-san?!
You were late, so we came to get you.
What were you doing...?
Ah, I was... I was just fixing my hair.
I've got Mizuno-sensei!
Sorry I'm late.
Komachi-kun is still doing his best to come here.
Hmm? Oh my, a new member?
Amahara-san?! W-Why?
Should I not be here?
I also joined the Underwear Appreciation Society.
No, there's no problem, but...
Can you please start?
Look, you've kept the Class Representative waiting as well.
Although it seems like he's here despite not even
knowing whether he wants to see underwear or not.
Hey...
Uh, hey! Today I brought in something different.
Today we'll be using this.
What... is this?
What do you think it is?
Actually, it's part of a bra!
This part right here.
So bras had this many components...
Yeah!
The smallest separable parts are like these,
but the largest are made of four parts.
It often depends on the bra,
but I heard that there are bras with as many as 70-90 parts.
That's really neat!
You didn't know, Sensei?
Even though you're wearing such an enormous bra?
Amahara-san, it's normal to not know this much.
So, today we'll be assembling these?
Yup!
With these I thought, "Komachi-kun would be able to consciously handle something feminine, right?"
A single word would have been fine.
Well, with these I shouldn't be nervous, though.
Isn't this great, Representative.
Now you can proudly go about touching underwear.
N-Now, now!
Nayu-chan, what about this part?
Ah! This part is used to connect the cups.
Nayu, what's this?
This'll be...
Kind of like a plastic model.
Too plain.
I wanted to do something else.
With such long eyelashes and pale skin,
it does seem like the boys would be attracted to her.
Thus her wearing make-up is all the more inexcusable!
But that was the decision...
What is it?
U-Um, it's about this morning...
This morning? Ah...
You know, Amahara-san, I also think you don't really need make-up...
You're still young, and it'd be better to maintain that. So-
Looks like -30 points.
What?
Eh? What do you mean, -30 points?
Isn't it obvious? Her strength as a woman.
Sign: Woman Strength -30
Your eyebrows aren't adjusted,
that sloppy braid,
and that faded freebie jersey.
Well done for going outside like that.
For a woman, that's unbelievable.
For a woman... unbelievable...
Mizuno-sensei has amazingly womanly traits!
For example, the shape of the breasts and shapeliness of the hips and...
Hayama-san!
Sensei. The bra that you're wearing is the wrong size, right?
Eh-heh, lately I've been a bit busy and...
the laundry was piling up,
and I found this old bra and thought that it should be fine...
No it isn't! Bras have a lifespan.
They'll also change from the original size!
As I thought! This bra's become far too tight!
W-Wait a-
It's even coming out of the sides!
The units of area are square meters.
In other words, as the area is meters times meters,
the value is determined by multiplying length and width...
Incidentally, pi can be determined by dividing circumference by diameter.
Being an irrational number, pi holds an infinite number of digits,
and is thus generally referred to by its symbol.
Eh- oh... oh-pai?!
Excuse me.
Pai? It's pi, it's pi, it's pi...
Unbelievable.
It's unbelievable.
Amahara-san?
Even though you have such splendid breasts,
you're wearing such an unsophisticated ragged laced bra!
Unsophisticated
I thought that I could still wear it...
You're being too harsh!
Sensei, do you have a boyfriend?
Eh? That's an unexpected question...
Then I'll rephrase the question:
Do you have someone you like?
Eh? Um! Uh...
Hoho. I happen to know.
Eh? Yako-chan, you know the person Sensei likes?
I know very well.
I want to know.
Is it somebody we've met?
Indeed, you see him every-
W-Wait, what are you doing, Jinguuji-san?!
That's just admiration, or maybe... no wait-
Gracious me, Sensei, who might you be talking about?
Youko-san often said,
"Underwear and love have an entwined relationship."
Underwear and love...
Once I find someone I like,
will the way I think about underwear change, too?
I believe that as a woman,
you need to look your best for whenever the person you like may look at you.
The reason why I joined this society was to research what sort of underwear is befitting of a refined woman.
A refined woman?
Please look at this.
What's this?
A catalogue for imported products.
What!? What's with these revealing, tiny bras?
Why are you imagining me?!
But, this one's kind of cute.
This one's a bit suggestive, it's wonderful as well.
Hmm. Black lace...
Sensei, you're into some surprisingly bold things.
I didn't mean to make it sound like that...
Hey, Representative, you'd be happier with such cute underwear, right?
Like I'd care.
Regardless, study some more, Sensei.
Your make-up and underwear need work so you can look presentable.
After all, we are women.
It's true, these bras are cute, but...
they don't appear to support the bust line.
The lace ribbon on these briefs aren't of a very good material; it could hurt the skin.
Underwear should really be-
Enough with the nonsense.
But! Since underwear's something we wear against the skin,
it needs good materials and design.
Most importantly, underwear has a
crucial role in protecting the body-
Protect it, protect it!
There are underwear which are worn for your companion!
Design is first priority! Function comes next.
No way! That's reckless!
Reckless?
A little girl like yourself wouldn't understand it.
Even a child would understand comfortable underwear.
Even you have a boy you like by now, right?
That's... um... I don't really know...
For you, underwear might be something to protect you,
but for me, underwear is like a weapon.
For me, looking my best for the person I like is a priority.
If you can't show it to your companion, there's no meaning to it.
Then... Then, are you saying that there's someone you like?
T-There isn't. A person I like.
After school, you'll get hungry, right?
I brought an afternoon snack with me today!
Dorayaki!
I made some for my brothers yesterday.
It looks delicious!
I guess I'll have to treat you all to the herb tea I bought at lunch!
Yay!
All right, Nayu-chan?
Yup!
I'm in the middle of a diet, so I'd avoid sweets...
Well, today's an exception.
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
Amahara-san, can you tell me some beauty secrets sometime?
Of course, on a day off.
I'm interested too!
I'm an adult and yet I don't know much about it.
I won't teach any people with giant breasts.
Women have plenty of problems.
It seems that in Japan, brief-style underwear came into fashion in 1936 after a department store fire.
Some women who weren't wearing underwear refused to use stairs in the emergency, and couldn't escape.
It's still a sad story, huh.
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra.
A Man's Heart Wavers