"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Today is the warmest day
we've had all autumn.
School athletic festivals are
being held all over the country.
Well, I came here to
cheer my daughter on,
but to think that
it would be this exciting!
It was well worth the trip.
I got quite a few good pictures.
Dad, just where is your daughter?
"Energetic Despite
Not Being Myself"
Oh, maybe I should cut my hair
for the athletic festival.
Like, going all-out and
getting really short hair.
Sis, you're going to cut your hair?
You've been growing
it out all this time.
I just mentioned the idea.
That meaningful reaction...
It must have something
to do with a guy!
Don't relate anything
and everything to that!
Tsukasa, don't run your mouth either!
But if you were to cut
your hair, Kagami...
Isn't boxed Pocky normal and stuff?
No way! The basic tsundere
hairdo is the twin-tails!
Excuse me for having a boring face!
Come to think of it, it's almost
time for the athletic festival.
It's such a chore.
That's not a line that
a young person says.
Kona-chan's athletic, so it's all right,
but I'm just going to be
a burden on everyone!
It's all right.
Sis, which event are you
going to participate in?
Well, knowing Kagami,
it has to be, you know,
the bread-eating race!
I've been wondering for a while now,
but are you trying to
pick a fight with me?
So, in the end, what are you
going to run in, Kagami?
I was right?
So I was right?
She's irritating!
So, I've been training on my own
for the athletic festival,
since they say autumn
is the season for sports.
I see...
But are you really doing this
for the athletic festival?
Aren't you doing it for the real thing
that happens afterwards?
About what?
--You want me to actually say it?
--She's really irritating!
I see, so Miyuki is running
in the team relay.
Well, that's understandable.
In the beginning, she was going
to run in the obstacle course.
Then, there's nobody
else volunteering?
Since I've never done it before,
I'm looking forward to it.
You can't, Miyuki-san.
Miyuki-san, you have really big curves,
"Like here, and here"
so you can't run the obstacle course.
You'll get hung up on stuff.
And when I said that,
she got moved to the relay.
You know, that's something
that a middle-aged man says.
Come to think of it, did your
junior high have a scavenger hunt?
Yeah, we did.
There was a time that a guy
picked me as the thing to find.
Me?
"For what?"
But in the end, he didn't tell me
what was on his paper.
So many ideas as to what
that unspeakable element is!
Well, when I don't know
the answer, I'll ask Miyuki-san.
Don't ask stuff like that.
That's something that's
truly hard to answer.
Wait, she's really asking.
A characteristic of Izumi-san
that is a bit hard to mention,
that might be used
in a scavenger hunt?
Yup.
What about someone
with a mole on her face?
Some people are really concerned
about things like that.
Nothing less from her...
Or more like, way to dodge
a difficult situation!
But I don't think that's it.
The athletic festival is fun, but
we have exams right afterwards.
When the athletic festival is over,
we suddenly run out of things to do,
so it gets a bit lonely.
Midterms, proficiency exams, finals...
All we have left are tests, too.
Second trimester is
always full of stuff,
so you end up using all your energy
in the arts and athletic festivals.
Right.
The midterm is especially difficult, I think.
They say autumn is
the season for reading,
so I guess I'll read some books.
The season's climate is nice to
spend studying for exams too.
Hordes of new games come out
right before Christmas too!
Though we have finals before that.
Oh, come to think of it--
You two...
Why don't you stop averting
your eyes from reality?
I see... So it's almost time
for the athletic festival...
You know that pistol that signals
ready, set, go, right?
I thought that was a real pistol
until I entered junior high!
That's impossible!
I think that was the first time that
I looked up to a police officer.
No, that's completely unrelated.
Way to hang on to a misunderstanding!
By the way, Konata, when is
your school's athletic festival?
Here. It's this Sunday.
This Sunday?!
Why didn't you tell me something
so important earlier?!
I mean, we just got the flyer today.
I can't just sit here!
What's got him all worked up?
Okay, today is the real thing!
Show 'em the fruit of
your daily practice!
Ma'am, I haven't practiced that much,
but I'm really good at the actual take!
Don't be so blunt!
Anyway, show 'em what
you got in the cavalry race!
Surround your enemy from
all sides and pummel 'em!
So we should attack them where
their defense is weak, right?
But all we need to do
is take their hats off,
so punching is a little...
Don't sweat the small stuff.
That's one of those mistakes of youth.
You are only a boy, huh?
Sis, good luck!
Please do your best!
Hey, how are those red bean buns
attached to those strings?
I'm sure they're held together
by clips or something.
Then they won't come off too easily.
Be victorious!
Girls should be more elegant!
There's no such thing as
an elegant bread-eating race!
Ready...
She did it!
Nothing less from Kagamin...
That man has a really
amazing camera.
Man, he's so easy to understand...
You're going to run in the 100-meter
race coming up next, right?
For now, yeah.
How can I run fast
like you, Kona-chan?
In things like this, mental images
are important. Mental images!
On your mark...
Ready...
This is rather nostalgic
image footage we've got here.
Goal!
Just like that.
Are you serious?
3 meters 25!
Oh man... It's only till where
your hand hits the ground.
Here it comes!
That's Kagami for you. Even the sand
isn't safe from her jabs.
One, two, three.
I hear it's good to adjust the timing
to jump over the hurdles
with the number of your steps.
Number of steps?
Like... One, two, three!
I get it!
One, two, three.
--One, two, three.
--Ready...
Let's see...
Three, two, three...
One, three... huh?
Let's see, I started from
the right foot, so...
I don't get it!
Right now I'm on my left foot...
Wai--
Three two, one...
Way to plow through
every single one of them.
In a way, that's talent right there.
Ajapa...
I was no good at all.
No, I'm telling you,
I thought it was going
to be my daughter's turn.
That's a scene that you see often.
It's finally time for the last relay race.
Yuki-chan, do your best!
No, I'm telling you, my daughter...
--I'll do my best!
--Wait, I haven't done anything yet!
Yeah, way to go! Go for it!
All right! See, we're in second place!
They're doing pretty well.
Sachi, over here, over here.
Here!
Okay!
Oh no, we're going
to be in third place.
This is what you call a race!
Do your best!
--Here!
--Okay!
They're putting up a good fight.
It's getting interesting...
I wonder if Yuki-chan
will be all right...
--Here!
--Okay!
Okay!
Go, Miyuki!
All right! Yuki-chan,
you're so awesome!
Nothing less from Miyuki-san...
She doesn't forget
fan-service for the audience!
Lucky Star!
Let's see...
That must be Tsukasa.
Oh, well...
Happy Henry Likes Beer But
Could Not Obtain Food... okay.
Hey, can't you do
something about that?
I'm sorry.
In the recorder quartet for music class,
I chose the alto recorder,
but I feel like I'm going to
pull my finger muscles.
Why did you choose alto?
It's like, I thought the lower parts
would be easier.
For now, why don't you get your
fingers used to the instrument
by playing a simple song?
Yeah!
You're missing most of the notes.
Now, I'll play with you. Ready...
Wait a minute!
Tsukasa, try playing by yourself.
Something's a little different.
Why don't you relax
a bit more when playing?
If you're not tense while you play,
you might just end up playing well.
I see... Relax...
Right, right.
Yeah, I'll try it.
Is she spending more time
inhaling than playing?
I thought about eating in the
school cafeteria every so often,
but it gets pretty crowded here.
I'm getting faint...
Lines are a bother, and they
tire you out. Don't you hate them?
Aren't you used to stuff like this
from all the events you attend?
I don't like lines with no excitement
or suspense at the end.
You're so honest about your desires.
Come to think of it, when I went to
an amusement park the other day,
I had thought I was lining up
for one of the rides,
when I actually was
in line for the restroom.
It's a fundamental rule to check
what line you're lining up for.
I waited for two hours, too...
Oh, me too.
When I'm in line,
and my turn finally comes up,
the item I want always sells
out with the person before me.
"Tasty Cream Puffs!"
"Sorry, sold out"
Wow, how tragic! I don't
even want to imagine it!
Tsukasa, you're just out of luck.
Look, everyone,
what are you all having today?
I guess curry will be okay.
You can't go wrong with it.
I'm going to have ramen.
Me too. I was thinking about
eating miso ramen today.
With lots of corn, and I'd like
wakame seaweed on top too.
Kagami, you're gonna eat ramen,
flan pudding, and an éclair, right?
If I have room afterwards.
Don't you always have room?
How about you, Yuki-chan?
I'll be having a sandwich.
For now, strawberry...
That sounds like you, Miyuki-san.
Right!
By the way, isn't a strawberry
sandwich considered dessert?
Can you really call it lunch?
You're right...
You sure are picky about odd things.
Kona-chan, what about the
choco-cornets that you always eat?
Aren't sweet buns considered snacks?
It's Tsukasa who has the comeback?!
Now, that aside...
I have an unfortunate
announcement for Miyuki-san.
The line for sandwiches is over there.
That's so like her!
She's a walking example
of moe, after all.
Hey, it's your turn now, Kona-chan.
I'd like some curry,
with extra roux, please.
Sure, sure.
You're so cunning.
I'll take whatever I can get.
Okay, next!
I'd like soy sauce ramen,
with slightly hard noodles.
Okay, wait just a minute.
Thanks for waiting, here's your curry.
I'll go on ahead and save some seats.
--Please do!
--Thanks!
Let's see, next person?
Oh, yes. Miso ramen, please.
I'm sorry, the person before you
got the last of the noodles,
so we're all out of ramen.
You know, if you don't mind
soy sauce flavor,
you want to eat this?
I'll settle for the kitsune udon.
Thanks, Sis...
You know, Sis?
The order in which we came out
determined who was
the older sister, right?
Right.
I'm glad I was the younger sister!
Why?
I mean, if the older sister is asking
the younger one for tutoring,
or asks to see her homework,
that's a bit pathetic, you know?
For the time being, I don't think
things like that matter
when it comes to copying homework.
In the first place, we're twins,
so there's not really
an older or younger sister.
Don't worry about it, just hurry up
and finish your homework.
Yeah!
But if I were the older sister,
and if I were reliable just like Sis...
Sis, can you show me
your homework?
Again? I guess you can't
help it, Kagami.
--Hey, are you all right?
Get a hold of yourself!
--Wow, this is turning
into something amazing!
Ta-dah!
In Newtype...
My postcard...
Got selected!
It's the May issue!
--Konata Izumi, from
Saitama Prefecture...
--The one where Akira is
stepping on Shiraishi!
--Hey, good for you. I'm amazed
that this got on the magazine.
It's amazing! I'm so surprised!
Things like this don't
happen every day!
Well, yeah, really!
Now there's another fun aspect
in buying the magazine!
No need to praise me!
1260 yen and 567 yen?
One more book,
and I can get a point...
Then, for now,
I'll settle for something...
"Hmm..."
No, that's what they want me to do!
I can't let the wholesaler
do me in like that!
Making someone buy
something unplanned
just because I want the extra point...
That's their tactic!
I'm not so foolish as to fall for that!
I forgot that volume 5
was already out.
All right! This makes it okay!
"Yum yum"
Your total is 2587 yen.
Oh, well...
"This one is for spreading the gospel..."
--I can't get it off...
--Oh, I'm so sorry.
Maybe they don't
want to be separated.
I had thought things like that
happen only in manga and games,
but they happen in real life too.
You're right.
That means...
Those two totally tripped
their flags right now!
Konata... the Japanese word
for "fantasy" uses the kanji
for "illusion" and "belief"...
Why don't you separate
your dreams from reality?
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Today, I deliver love to you once
again with a dream-colored heart!
This is Akira Kogami,
navigator of Lucky Channel!
Likewise, I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
the assistant.
Well, time goes by so quickly
that this show is already
on its eighth episode.
You're right. We should start
thinking about new things soon,
or people will start to say
we've fallen into a rut.
What was that?
What am I gonna do?
--No, I just would like to do
all sorts of things.
--Now you've said it.
--Or that's what I thought...
--Why don't you do it?
By the way, when I was walking
around town the other day,
someone called me over!
A survey for some day spa?
Oh no, Shiraishi-san,
are you serious about that?
No, of course it was from a fan!
That's never happened to you, right?!
No, not at all!
Of course, right?!
You're just an assistant, right?!
Well, keep doing your best!
But fan letters addressed to me...
There we go, Shouichi... This many!
Why?!
Hey, Itoh!
--Aren't there any for me?!
--So amazing... I feel
like I'm a voice actor!
So there's some for me too!
What, only one?!
Your membership is about to expire...
This is junk mail from
the video rental store!
Everyone sitting in front of the TV,
please send me fan mail too!
I'm looking for lots, lots, lots of them!
Akira-sama... we should get
to the actual content soon.
Don't you get so damn conceited.
There are so many possible
replacements for you.
I'm sorry...
"Important Announcement"
Ta-dah! We have an announcement!
Believe it or not, we're going to
--make figurines of characters
from this series!
--Akira-sama... The board...
The board is upside down!
Oh, really, you knew that
the whole time!
Geez, you're so good, Akira-sama!
Actually, the plan this time around...
Don't touch me.
Oh, this is strange...
Well, the plan this time around is...
Don't touch me.
Well, this time... huh?
What the hell is wrong with this?!
Hey, Seiji!
--Akira-sama, please calm down!
--You're covering! Covering! Don't cover me!
--Hold on, that's the name of the
manager for the person inside!
--I'm telling you not to cover me!
Can it be that you did this...
Of course not!
Yes! And so, in this figurine project,
we'll have all of you vote
to see which character
will be made into figurines!
We'll be waiting for your
passionate thoughts
on which characters
to turn into figurines!
Everyone, please vote!
Okay, that's all for today!
Please look forward to
the next Lucky Channel!
Bye-nee!
If we hold a poll like this,
of course someone from
the main show will win first place.
What is this?
Am I some sideshow?
No, that hasn't been decided at all.
Oh, that's right, I'm finally
going to become a figurine...
What are you talking about?
Things like this are kind of--
Yuki-chan, that was amazing!
I'm sorry that was so unpolished.
I think I saw a new side of Miyuki.
Oh no, you're embarrassing me.
Hey, hey... Then, Yuki-chan,
let's sing together.
Oh, let's do that.
Yeah, sing, sing! A duet, then?
What can you sing?
Let's see...
Then, to pass the time, I'll go!
You're going to sing again?
Kagami, you should
sing more songs too!
What is this?
Saiyuki. Machaaki's Son Goku
was so great!
Huh? Wasn't that
played by Shingo-chan?
That was the third recreation
of the old Chinese novel.
This is the theme song
from the first series,
which was on the air
from 1978 to 1980.
Exactly how old are you?!
This is a long intro.
This is where Mr. Akutagawa
makes his wonderful narration!
I don't know who that is!
Oh, here it comes...
Another shout?!
♪ Born from an egg on a mountain... ♪
Sorry, since it's all in English,
I've had enough.
You pulled the scene this long,
and you end it like that?!
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
Miyuki here.
There are times when you use
the term "Super-D Class"
when you express the amazingly
large scale of things.
The D in this term comes from
the battleship HMS Dreadnought
that entered service in
the English navy in 1906.
In other words, "Super-D Class"
originally referred to
a class that was larger than
the HMS Dreadnought.
But that has changed over time
to have a more general meaning,
like the one I gave in the beginning.
Next episode: That Feeling
"That Feeling"
Look forward to it!