Student council president!
It's so cute.
Do you like our latest design?
I-It's okay...
Have you considered our offer to join the Fashion Club?
The Fashion Club?
I'm sorry, but I haven't. I've been rather busy as of late.
Anyway, if you'll excuse me.
President!
Could you at least come up with a design for us?
A design?
We just want you to try drawing some
clothing that you think would look cute!
You want me to design some clothing?
Please do it for us, okay?!
It's finished!
Yes?
We've finished preparations for your training, ma'am!
Understood. I shall be there shortly.
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
What?! The Student Council Prez
Wears Some Cute Clothes!
I think this'd be pretty cute. What do you think?
It does look quite cute!
You do need to get the right material for these things.
Come in!
Student council president!
H-Hello there.
Sorry to intrude.
I brought you this.
What is it?
I drew that design you wanted from me.
Huh?!
It's so cuuuuute!
It's really got that unique charm of yours, President!
Yeah! President, you have really good design sense!
I'm glad you like it!
Rather, what I mean is...
I've got an idea! Why not help
us turn this design into reality?
Huh?
That'd be great!
Well then, let's go buy some material!
Huh?!
Come on, today's your lucky day!
Let's go!
There's cotton, wool, silk, and velvet!
This is amazing! There are so many cute colors!
President!
Wh-What is it?
How about this?
It's not quite what I had in mind.
Then what about this?!
That will do nicely.
I've brought some frills that I thought would look nice!
This might work well, I suppose.
Student council president!
What colors do you want for the ribbons and tape?!
Th-They're so...
They're all very cute!
Yup!
Let's make the cutest clothes we can!
Okay!
You three take it easy now, all right?
Thank you very much!
Your mother seems like a very nice person.
Yeah, she is.
Anyway, don't be shy. Please enjoy.
Then we will!
Still, your room...
It's overly tidy and has no personality.
Erika!
Don't you have any cute things at all?
Well, the truth is...
Plushies!
I promised not to stress myself out over it,
but these things do distract me from my disciplines.
She really is overdoing it...
I've got it!
What's the next step in making the clothes?
We have to make the patterns.
Huh?
We use some pattern paper to draw out the shape, and then cut out the shape from the material.
Well then, let's start making this cute dress of yours!
Right!
bracelets
necklaces
Heave-ho...
bracelets
necklaces
All this work sure is tough...
Huh?
Erika and Tsubomi sure are late.
Isn't making the Heart Links supposed to be Erika's job?
I know!
Whoa!
You've made far too many!
It's done!
All right, now we need to cut the material!
Okay!
Grandfather!
Itsuki!
Sir!
It's time for your practice.
Yes, sir.
Father!
She finally has some friends over!
The least you could do is give her one day off.
Do as you will.
Father, listen to me!
Hanasaki, Kurumi.
Thank you for today.
I have my practice now, so you'll have to excuse me.
Good
Advice
May
Hurt
But
Will
Always
Help
Good
Advice
May
Hurt
But
Will
Always
Help
Itsuki sure does put her all into
practicing every day, doesn't she?
Itsuki decided for herself that she'd inherit the School of Myoudouin.
She did?
Did she have some reason for it?
Yes...
The role of teacher in the School of Myoudouin is always passed on to the eldest son.
But my father only had me, his
lone daughter, as his next of kin.
So my father intended to appoint
my son, Satsuki, as his successor...
But Satsuki's body was too weak, and he quickly fell ill.
And that's why she did it?
She wasn't put up to it by anyone, though.
If you please, then!
She decided to take on her brother's role as successor to the School of Myoudouin so that she could protect him.
Ever since she was five, when she started learning the martial arts.
Give me one more try, please!
That's just like her.
Yeah! My heart is aflame once more!
A-As a friend, of course!
I hope we'll be seeing a lot more of you in future.
Right!
Finally... finally, it is within my grasp!
That's quite the ruckus you're making there, Kumojacky.
Oh, Professor Sabark!
This time I'm going to pulverize them for good!
With the Big Bang Kumojacky Special!
Whaaat?!
You don't want to make the clothes anymore?
I'm sorry. I realized that I'm really not suited for that kind of thing.
"Not suited"?
Th-That's right.
Was it not fun for you?
F-Fun?
It's just that I have other things I need to be doing, so...
Well then, we'll finish it by ourselves, so you can just sit back and watch!
What?
Let's go, Tsubomi!
Hey, wait!
After making the patterns, we have to trim the material!
We only have one chance!
Focus your spirit and seize victory with one stroke!
For a moment there, the atmosphere got tense, just like in a martial arts bout.
Making clothing is just as serious a battle!
I see...
Next, we sew it all together!
I can handle that if you want!
Do you want to try?
Huh?
Here you go!
Is it really okay?
Of course!
It's finally finished!
The tunic I designed...
Hurry up and try it on!
Try it on...
What?!
Th-This is me?
Whaddya think?
You look lovely!
No way! I don't!
It really suits you.
Brother!
So that's what the real you looks like.
Stop that, will you?!
I'm just playing around, all right?!
I don't...
Itsuki...
We've got trouble!
We've got a challenger!
Itsuki!
You mustn't go!
Don't worry yourself over me!
I will protect the School of Myoudouin!
Been a while, ain't it?
I've come for yer school's nameplate, old man!
Well, if it isn't Hiroto.
Oh. So yer kind enough to remember the guy ya ostracized, huh?
The School of Myoudouin has no need of those so concerned with victory
as to abandon all decency to obtain it.
All that matters in battle is winning!
If ya disagree, then face me!
Grandfather.
I will face him in your stead.
Huh?
School of Myoudouin
Don'tcha get it, kid?
Yer sign's at stake if ya lose!
I too bear the name of Myoudouin.
I'll show you just how much your
deficiency in training will cost you.
Very well then.
I leave this to you, Itsuki.
Sir!
Bow!
Begin!
Are ya just gonna keep runnin'?!
Are you all right?
This is in the bag!
Cease!
This fight has reached its conclusion.
Th-That was cheap!
A loss is a loss, I think you'll find.
It is as Hiroto says.
Huh?!
Were this bout to the death, then you would have lost your life.
Well then, I'll be takin' yer nameplate, 'kay?
Do as you wish.
Was that really all this nameplate meant to ya, huh?
I'm sorry!
I've damaged the proud name of Myoudouin!
Itsuki.
Yes?
For a while, you will cease your training.
Huh?
I feel you have reached your limit.
The purpose behind martial arts is to
become master of your own existence.
It is not something you do for brother or family.
Do not worry yourself with the future of the School.
What is truly important is that you follow your own heart.
Follow my heart?
Grandfather!
Itsuki.
Brother...
It's just as Grandfather says, you know?
What's important is what's in your heart.
We're all very grateful that you've worked so hard, both for my sake and everyone else's.
But from now on,
you should walk your own path—the one you wish to walk—not the one you feel you must.
That's what we all wish for.
Master!
Why didn't you defeat me?!
Why didn't you tell me what it is I've been doing wrong?!
I really just want...
I am a Commander of the Desert Apostles... Kumojacky!
The Flower of your Heart yearns to wilt, so I shall steal it from you!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
You're up, Desertrian!
Nameplate! Nameplate!
This is baaaaad!
I had convinced myself that inheriting the School of Myoudouin
would've been the best way to protect my brother.
But without my martial arts,
what purpose do I really have?
I dedicated everything to learning the martial arts.
I don't have a path of my own to walk.
You have plenty!
Huh?
Yeah!
You can become a fashion
designer or whatever you want!
Become a fashion designer?
Yeah!
Just do the things you enjoy and have fun!
You just have to be honest with your heart!
Honest with my heart...
Nameplaaaaaaate!
What is that thing?
Hurry and run, you two!
Tsubomi!
Erika!
I just wanted to return to the dojo!
The truth is that I always loved the School of Myoudouin!
Is that Hiroto?!
Transform!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
It's dangerous here!
Hurry and run!
Precures...
You're so cute!
Run already!
Masteeeeeeeer!
What a baby this one is!
Wanting his Master to scold him so!
You're just abusing that dojo challenger's heart that yearned to apologize!
And I've had it up to here with this!
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
I shall not allow it!
Big Bang Kumojacky Special!
Worry not. It shall be swift.
Now, fall!
I won't let you!
Quickly!
Behind you!
Run!
Nameplate-ate-ate!
Nameplate! Plate! Plate!
Precures!
Where do you think you're looking?!
Oh? Not bad for a mere human.
I suppose I can play with you for a while.
Walking the path of the martial artist has
been filled with one hardship after another.
But at the same time, refining my skill in the arts gave me great pleasure.
School of
Myoudouin
It's not like I trained merely for my family's sake, or for my brother's,
but because I loved the martial arts too!
I can use this power to protect the ones I love!
Here I come!
How's that?!
Was that meant to do anything?
Precure!
Thank you!
But leave the rest to us Precures, okay?!
Let's finish this!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
Hmph!
So it seems you have become a little stronger after all.
Next time, you had better entertain me even more!
Now, be brave,
and be honest with your heart.
Master!
I'm sorry!
I always wanted to apologize to you for the underhanded techniques I used!
So I'm begging you! Please accept me back into the School of Myoudouin!
Hiroto.
Yes?!
Do you know the reason why I banished you?
Because I used underhanded moves.
That's not all it was.
It was because you betrayed your heart that loved the martial arts so dearly.
If you can now be earnest with your heart,
and truly wish to learn under the School of Myoudouin,
then you may do as you will.
Thank you very much, sir!
In the language of flowers, a violet means "humility."
It really is important to be honest-hearted, isn't it?
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
Oh, that's right!
I have a favor to ask of you both.
Would you allow me to join the Fashion Club?
That'd be great!
You're more than welcome!
Grandfather, Mother, and you too, Brother...
The worries that plagued me have passed,
and I can now show you the truth in my heart.
I love both martial arts and cute clothes!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The fires of youth, and the conflicts that arise from them!
The fastest embroiderer in the West...
Kurumi Erika of the Fashion Club!
And the most talented of performers...
Takagishi Azusa of the Drama Club!
Will their burning spirits be able to set their friends' hearts ablaze?!
Will these two brave club leaders live to see another dawn?!
HeartCatch Precure:
Erika is Her Rival!
A Challenge from the Drama Club!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!