Tooru!
Do you want some ice cream?
Huh?
She's not here?
Run-chan...
What are you doing down there?
Fell off while I was asleep.
Can't move. Help me.
Stop!
Wait, what are you doing?
I just had an impulse.
Saved
Another one!
Stop it already.
Nice shot!
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
There you go, Tooru.
Time to eat!
Delicious.
Tooru, have your bangs grown longer?
Well, I haven't touched them since the start of summer vacation.
Should I cut them for you?
What?
Scissors!
You're going to use those scissors...?
Exactly. Don't move!
Wait! You're cutting horizontally?
Um, you've got younger!
An elementary school backpack would suit you!
I'm not even a middle schooler?
It's over... I can't go to school anymore...
It's summer break right now.
But there'll be a school day.
Don't worry, it looks cute.
That's why I don't like it.
I know!
Let's do this like that and...
It's done!
Pair look!
Pair look...
A midsummer
night's...
Coming!
Good morning.
Good morning, Tooru-chan.
Sorry, but Run is still in bed.
Can you wake her up for me?
Sure. Excuse me.
Run-chan, it's a school day.
Run-chan, we have to go to school.
It's summer and you still wear long sleeves.
I keep telling you, it's cuter when you're cool.
Run-chan!
There you go.
I'll take it off!
I said I'll take it off!
There you go.
It's hot...
It puts me in a daze.
Run-chan, the school is the other way.
Beware of
molesters!
Oh no, perverts and molesters come out during the summer, don't they?
I hear that they sometimes call to you from cars.
Beware of
molesters!
That's dangerous! We'll have to be careful.
Hey! It sure is hot outside. Want me to take you to school?
A molester!
Ah! Somebody help! There's a pervert here!
No way...
A pervert?
Should we call the police?
It's a misunderstanding!
I'm their teacher at school!
Please don't report me!
Well, I'll give you the print-outs, so hand 'em out.
You have until the next trimester to complete the questionnaire.
All right.
Everybody, listen up!
This is a career advice questionnaire.
Think it through until the next trimester.
Don't mess around with it because you're still freshmen.
If you're not careful, exams will creep up on you in no time!
School [attendance] day
Summer homework
New term
Sept 1st
Be sure to study hard, and don't try to escape reality during the break starting tomorrow.
That is all. See you next trimester.
Kitou-sensei.
Tooru-san?
Sensei, you look pale today.
Are you okay?
Well, how nice of her! That's my students for you.
You're right, I've had a bit of a headache since this morning.
There's medicine at the infirmary.
You can overcome a headache using willpower.
You can't be like that, Kitou-sensei.
Wearing a white lab coat again.
You look like me, stop it.
That's my own decision!
And anyway, I've been wearing a lab coat since before you came here.
But the white lab coat is clearly the hallmark of the school nurse.
Never mind that, Satou-sensei. You do something about that ridiculous shirt you're wearing!
Are you telling me I have bad taste?
You're clearly not one to talk.
Then let's have Tooru-san decide!
That's fine by me.
Huh? Tooru-san?
[Note: 海栗 = sea urchin]
Uni-chan?
Tooru-san?
Kitou-sensei, did you step on Uni-chan?
What did you say? It must have been you, Satou-sensei!
No, it was definitely you, Kitou-sensei.
No, it was you, Satou-sensei.
No, it was you, Kitou-sensei.
I'm not that small.
No.
Is that... maybe... a call for help?!
It's coming from a freshmen classroom. I'm coming for you!
This way, you can get the dust off without going down to the first floor.
How did you get this dirty from a blackboard eraser, anyway?
Right?
No, not "right".
Is there a fire?
Um, Senpai, what's wrong?
This was definitely me jumping to the wrong conclusions.
Well...
I came to clean up!
Kill me.
Excuse her, Senpai, she's just an idiot.
It's all right, I just misunderstand things easily.
Now we have another thing to laugh about later, right, Tooru?
If only I'd stopped Yutaka, then you wouldn't have to endure such shame now, Yuuko-chan.
I'm sorry.
Stop it, don't apologise!
Apologising just makes it more embarrassing!
I'm sorry.
Stop it!
She's easily flustered.
Hey!
They were signalling like crazy!
Anybody would have thought there's a fire!
If there was fire, there would have been smoke.
You're just too excitable. You should calm down a little.
Nagi-chan!
Hot! Fire!
...is exactly what you shouldn't do.
But, Run!
It's summer! Why did you get a hot one?
I rushed and picked the wrong one!
It's hot!
It really is bad for people to rush, huh?
I couldn't help it! If there really was a fire, it would've been terrible!
Same goes for me, hot coffee during the summer was just too unexpected.
That's right! They should just remove hot drinks from the vending machines during summer!
No, that's really not the point.
Hot blooded
Confident in her fashion sense...
Maybe?
Ah, what do I do now?
I left the questionnaire in my desk!
I know!
It's from Yuuko.
"I left my questionnaire at school and want to go get it but I'm scared to go alone."
"Come with me."
That's why I told her not to rush things.
There you go.
"Forget about it until the next trimester."
I don't want to!
"I want to take time to write it. I'm begging you, come with me."
Really?
Nagi
To school at night?
Really?
Nagi
I'm begging you!!!!
It's too scary alone!! T_T
Yuuko
Really?
I'm begging you!!!!
It's too scary alone!! T_T
"Too scary", you say?
Oh no, I'm late. Nagi must've arrived already.
There she is.
Hey!
Huh? Why's everyone here?
I told them to come.
Is the entrance gate open?
We got in through the back gate.
The back gate is far from here.
Yuuko, run as fast as you can to us.
Yeah, here we go.
Go!
You're being impatient.
Listen, do not turn around!
Oh, stop that...
No!
That's a personal record.
Well, let's go get what you forgot.
Wait, I can't move yet.
Ah, she's dead.
It's locked, after all.
The staff entrance is locked as well?
I guess this is not going to work.
What are you trying to open it with?
Damnit.
School is really scary at night.
Well, one of the windows happened to be open.
That's kind of careless of them, but it sure helped us out.
You're right.
Yuuko, you're sticking too close!
But!
I'll get scared if I don't stick to somebody!
I understand.
I'll go and get you the anatomical model from the science lab.
No, don't!
Then let go!
No way!
They look like they're enjoying themselves.
I wonder about that.
You're a real scaredy cat, Yuuko.
Because the school looks different at night and it's creeping me out!
Oh.
What?
Since we're already in the school at night...
...let's go explore!
Sure!
Let's go!
kyoushitsu shuppatsu shinkou desu
We're setting off for the classroom,
W-Wait for me!
wasuremono wa minasan nai de shika?
忘れ物は　皆さん　ないでしか？
Ladies and gentlemen, you haven't forgotten anything, have you?
mayonaka narihibiku piano
真夜中　鳴り響くピアノ
The piano is resounding through the night.
terirorirara nazomeku nana fushigi
テリロリララ　謎めく　七不思議
Going "terirorirara," how mysterious, one of the seven wonders.
madogiwa odoridasu gaikotsu ni aisatsu
窓際　踊りだす　ガイコツに挨拶
Say hello to the skeleton dancing in the window,
hora hora ki san to esukooto shite!
ほらほら　きさんとエスコートして！
Come on, I'll be sure to escort you.
saa iza yukan omoshiroi jan ushiro wa furikaeruna
さぁ　いざゆかん　面白いじゃん　後ろは振り返るな
Now let's get going, it's really fun, but don't turn around!
maa ii jan susumu dake kowai mono nante nai sa
まぁ　いいじゃん　進むだけ　怖いものなんてないさ
Well, don't worry about it, just keep going, there's really nothing to be scared of.
dabide ya monariza mo minna issho ni tanken shiyou
ダビデや　モナリザも　みんな一緒に探検しよう
Let's all go exploring with David and Mona Lisa.
School at night sure is exciting!
Yeah.
I'm scared.
Erm...
What's up?
Bathroom.
We're going stop by the bathroom.
Sure, we'll wait!
I'm not going into the stall with you.
I understand.
Let's see, light...
Hurry it up.
I know.
Hm?
What is it?
You see that?
It came out!
Your constipation cleared up?
That's not what we mean!
Over there! Outside the gym hall, we saw a disembodied soul!
The soul comes out right after a person dies, right?
If we put it back immediately, maybe we can save them!
What are you talking about?
The soul grew feet!
Be quiet.
I want to see it!
Footsteps?
We'll be found!
A burglar?
Why?
Hm, Uni-chan?
It's just Satou-sensei.
You scared me.
What are you doing in the middle of the night?
We came to clean up.
No!
So you came because you forgot something.
That's right.
Sensei, what's with the candle?
Huh? Well, I just love candles.
This transient flame is like my life.
It's what you call affinity, I guess.
Ah, he collapsed.
He's conscientious, huh?
He's not moving.
Did he collapse for real?
He had an attack!
Oh no!
First of all, we have to get him to the infirmary!
He's face-down! You'll scratch his face!
Crap, he's too heavy.
Can we really carry him?
I know! We can just get the bed to him!
And then what do we do?
We'll take this side. Run, you take his feet. Tooru, you support him.
Got it?
Yeah.
I understand.
Here we go.
Heave ho!
He's heavy!
Hey, he's light all of a sudden.
Run, you're missing most of him!
Heave ho!
That was exhausting.
He won't wake up.
Don't do that.
Sensei, get ahold of yourself!
Don't slap him.
Serves him right.
Did he come to?
Sensei! Sensei! Get ahold of yourself!
Sensei! Can you hear me?
What is this?
Run-chan.
Satou-sensei, don't die on me!
Run-chan!
I won't die!
Is he all right?
He said he wouldn't die.
Let's go home.
You're right.
The dog isn't here anymore, right?
It's gone!
That was really tiresome.
Good night.
Yuuko-chan, see you tomorrow!
Yeah, see you tomorrow!
I'm glad those three were with me tonight.
I forgot it again!
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
In the end, it was all in vain.
Now I can't sleep at all because of all the fear.
At my age, I can't go to my parents and go, "Let me sleep with you".
I know!
It's been a while since I've slept with you.
Good night.
Preview
Mipo-rin, what is it about summer festivals that you enjoy?
No matter what you say, it's still the fireworks.
Also, the takoyaki.
And the okonomiyaki.
I also like the hiyashiame.
Oh, those are nice.
What do you enjoy about them, Yutaka?
No matter what you say, for Yutaka, it's still carts-
Wait a second!
Next time, on A-Channel:
Next Time!
Summer Festival
Summer Festival.
I like eating lots of oden from a cart vendor!
Oden in summer?