Nurse's Office
Inaban...
I thought you were a goner.
I'm not gonna die from a little dizzy spell.
Still, I was so scared.
I thought he might've been responsible.
This has nothing to do with Heartseed.
I've been feeling a little under the weather.
Nothing I would've gone to the nurse's office for.
Don't say that, Inaba.
You need to take care of yourself.
Are you actually scolding me?
I really mean it!
Yeah, whatever you say.
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
Dumb wrestling nut
What if you laugh more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Loves his little sister
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
The comic I read just now was cool.
I want to eat curry now.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi High
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry, you gotta
drink more milk
Inabaaaan
Sorry I was even born
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Cooks curry
Inaba Himeko
but I still like her
me yui
AAAAA
We should get married
I love you
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to eat a
pot of curry.
Wonder if I should.
The whole world
Let's go
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry
I can't go out with you
It'd be bad
I don't have the homework
for tomorrow
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
Time is multifaceted
Did you hear that?
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
You guys don't have to make a big deal out of this.
I can walk home by myself.
If we don't walk you home,
Kiriyama will kick our asses tomorrow.
Yep, especially since Yui and Aoki wanted to tag along but couldn't.
Screw that.
I don't need four people escorting me around.
So, Taichi...
Why don't you tell us what really happened with Yui yesterday?
What kind of question is that?
That came out of nowhere.
Who cares?
If you don't answer the question,
I'll be so upset that I'll collapse on the spot.
It's not fair to use your poor health as an excuse.
I think I'm gonna faint from the shock.
Huh?
You really have so little trust in us?
Boohoo.
Right, Inaban?
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
But there are some things I can't tell you about.
Twin Feelings
How did you come up with that brilliant idea,
you white knighting bastard?
It's not that funny.
So does it still hurt down there?
That's none of your business.
Help me out here, Nagase.
What's wrong?
I had no idea.
I knew that Yui didn't like boys,
but I never realized that she was actually scared of them.
Nagase,
I'm pretty sure that Kiriyama didn't want people to feel uncomfortable
or start tiptoeing around her.
So try to act normal around her.
Act normal?
That's all I have to do?
Yeah, that's enough.
You two would make the perfect couple
since you need each other.
Isn't that right?
I-Inaban!
That's completely different from what you said before!
The other day, you were saying how Taichi and I were all...
...wink-wink, nudge-nudge, that kind of thing!
Huh?
That's because you guys are like that.
Plus, I have a feeling that Yui's starting to fall for Taichi.
Wh-What?!
Inaban, you're too blunt.
The thing with white knights is that some girls can't resist 'em.
But never forget that kindness can hurt instead of help.
I won't.
Sorry about everything today.
Don't sweat it.
Get some rest.
Inaban, you should worry about your health
before stressing over everyone else.
I'm okay.
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot.
Iori, you should have Taichi exorcise your demons too.
Huh?
Inaban, you promised not to tell anyone.
Taichi, I have faith in you.
Help her out.
Inaban thinks she knows everything.
But she doesn't.
I mean, I know that she's trying to help...
Do you want to know more about me, Taichi?
Well...
I'm willing to talk if you promise
that nothing will change between us, no matter what I say.
Okay, I promise.
I knew you'd say that.
Well, let's get started...
Okay.
But first...
I'll tell a joke.
Huh?
Well, I always think it's a good idea
to say something funny before the mood gets serious.
Don't bother.
Why would you think that?
But when I really need to,
I can never think of anything funny!
All the more reason to not do it.
Just kidding.
The joke was that I couldn't come up with a joke when I needed one.
But I actually do have a joke.
I just chose to joke that I didn't have a joke.
Get it?
What is there to get?
You didn't need to joke that you didn't have a joke
because you didn't need to joke in the first place.
But you're actually playing along, Taichi.
That seems to happen when I'm around you.
So, I have five dads.
But I guess only three of them were official.
Do you mean that your mother keeps getting divorced and remarried?
Yep, and my second dad was trouble.
Let's just say that he could get violent.
But nothing serious happened
because I made sure it didn't.
I learned to adopt a persona.
One that fit his preferences.
What do you—
I was careful not to do anything that would make him angry.
If I behaved like this or did that, he wouldn't get mad.
He might even praise me.
I changed my tastes to match.
This was back when I was in first grade, I think.
Ever since then, I've been switching between personas.
But in spring of last year,
my fifth dad told me this on his deathbed:
"You need to start living your own life."
And after he died,
my mom said, "I'm sorry for being so selfish.
From now on, I'll work hard so you can do the things that you want,"
all while crying her eyes out.
And we lived happily ever after.
So you get along with your mom now?
But the real hell starts after that.
"Live your own life."
Those words left me stunned.
What did I like?
What did I want to do?
After spending most of my life trying to live for someone else,
I apparently forgot who I was.
My mom told me to do what I wanted,
but I didn't know what that was.
So I decided to just pick appropriate personas based on the situation.
Ironically enough, I prided myself on being able to guess what other people wanted.
But I've started to lose my touch.
I never realized that Yui had androphobia.
But that's...
And then, this personality swapping business started.
I barely had a grip on my personality as it was.
Once we began switching bodies, it only got worse.
Eventually, nobody will be able to recognize me.
I won't be able to recognize myself.
Then maybe, eventually, I'll just fade away...
That'll never happen!
Because no matter what happens,
no matter how much you change,
I'll always be able to recognize you for who you are.
That's impossible.
It's not impossible.
How can you be so sure?
That's because...
I'm in love with...
White knighting freak...
A-Anyway, I'll be able to recognize you.
You can trust me.
Really?
If you're that confident, I guess I can trust you.
Yamaboshi Academy
Morning, Taichi.
M-Morning, Nagase.
You swore that I could spill my guts
and nothing would change!
You promised me, man to man!
Who are you supposed to be?
You swore that I could spill my guts
and nothing would change!
You promised me, man to man!
Why are you repeating yourself?
And you're not a man.
So why is it that when two guys talk,
there's so much adrenaline involved?
Hell if I know.
Anyway, are you okay?
Yep, I'm fine.
But I'm not the one you should be asking.
Yamaboshi Academy
Are you me right now, Taichi?
Taichi! Are you okay, Taichi?
Just suck it up.
You're such a wimp.
I don't think I can suck it all back up.
Iori, you can go back to the classroom.
What about you guys?
I'll make sure he gets some rest.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to hurt my own body.
Student Cultural Society
I'm back.
Looks like it.
You can go back to the classroom.
I'm not going to leave you all alone while you're sick.
Sorry.
No, don't be.
You've been acting strangely lately.
I'm telling you that I'm fine.
You don't look fine to me.
Tell me what's wrong.
Keep it down.
You're giving me a headache.
Inaba!
I want to help you!
Why do you want to help me?
B-Because...
Don't say that it's because you want to help or because I'm one of you.
Well, you're always looking out for us.
You're always there for us when it counts.
So if I didn't look out for you,
you wouldn't want to help me?
Not exactly...
That was kind of a mean way to put it.
It wasn't mean.
Why do you guys have to be so nice?
Why couldn't you be a little darker?
Darker?
No, I shouldn't say that.
I'm the one who needs to change.
Uh, Inaba...
Are you sure you're okay?
What are you asking about?
My body will be fine after a little rest.
I'm not talking about your body.
I'm not okay!
Wait.
I didn't mean that. Forget what I said.
Seriously?
I meant to say that—
You once said that we were in a hopeless situation.
Aren't you the one who's hurting the most because of this swapping business?
Crap.
I'm in horrible shape today.
I must look weak in front of my enemy.
You said something similar the other day.
Am I your enemy?
No!
That's not what I meant!
You guys are
my very best friends.
Which makes you my worst enemies.
That makes no...
I'm done talking.
Go back to the classroom.
If you can't tell us why you're in so much pain,
you don't think of us as friends.
Then I'll give it to you straight.
I can't trust you guys.
If two people switch bodies,
and one commits a crime or something,
the owner of that body is the one who's responsible.
That means you can do whatever you want.
You think we would do that?
Well, it may be unfair to say you'd commit a crime.
But you could swipe some change or something.
I guess, but...
I can't help but think about the bad things you might be doing.
It's so scary that it keeps me up all night.
What's sad is that
I hate my own guts for being like this.
You, Iori, Yui, and Aoki all trust each other.
I'm the only one who's worrying about this stuff.
Inaba...
We won't think less of you for it—
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!
But this completely changes our relationship, right?
Taichi...
I don't trust anybody in this world.
That means everyone is an enemy.
And you're probably my worst enemy since, unless I'm mistaken,
you trust me more than anyone else does.
I say that I don't trust anybody,
but I still want to have fun with everyone.
That indecision is making every day pure agony for me.
I don't suffer the same way Yui and Iori do.
A lot of people end up with warped personalities
after going through some crazy life experiences.
If you ask me, they should count themselves lucky
because at least that can be cured.
But what are you supposed to do when there is no traumatic experience?
I haven't been able to trust anyone
since the day I was born.
If I try to change,
I won't be the same person anymore.
Won't be the same person anymore?
In that sense,
you're probably doomed to be the white knight forever.
Were you born that way?
Yeah, you can't help people
who don't suffer from any trauma.
But that's probably because they don't need help.
It really doesn't matter what you're born with.
Are you saying that it would be stupid to worry about that?
I didn't say that.
But maybe you're right.
Taichi!
I mean, I think you're fine the way you are.
Huh?
I'll admit that I'm sad you don't trust me,
but that doesn't mean you should force yourself to change.
I think everyone will still accept you.
Nagase, Kiriyama, Aoki,
and of course, me.
Are you retarded?!
It's not that simple!
We can't say that for sure.
So you should talk to everyone.
Tell them what you told me.
I can't take that risk!
What if they don't accept me—
In that case,
you'll still have me.
Anyway, you need to start by accepting who you are.
In my opinion, at least.
I-I can't do it.
The only consequences I can imagine are all negative.
Hey, Inaba.
When you're hiding a secret from the whole world,
you can feel the weight on your shoulders.
So I'm going to tell you a secret that I was planning to take to the grave.
What do you mean?
You spill yours, so I have to spill mine?
Yeah.
If my secret gets out,
I won't be able to survive in this school,
or in normal society, for that matter.
This is a deadly secret I'm hiding.
Are you insane or something?!
Inaba, y-you're too loud!
Whatever, just tell me this secret of yours.
I'll decide after that.
Okay, here I go...
I've...
I've masturbated to you before!
You mean that you've actually...
Yeah.
Which probably means you've also used Iori and Yui, right?
I see.
I-I want to make it clear that this isn't a regular thing!
I've hardly done it at all, actually!
Are you listening to me?
Perv!
Pervert!
Sicko! Freak! Creep!
Still...
I think you're fine the way you are.
Huh?
This is all so stupid.
It's stupid that you revealed this secret to me!
That you thought it would convince me to change my mind!
It's stupid that you thought it was acceptable to say that out loud.
And what's really stupid is that I'm actually touched.
Need a handkerchief?
What's wrong with you?
You want me to fall for you too?
That's more or less it.
So Inaban, you're saying that...
...you worry too much?
W-Worry too much?
It's a lot more than—
I know what you mean.
Whenever Aoki and I switch,
I give my body a thorough check as soon as I'm back.
What?
And I make sure that none of my stuff is missing.
That hurts!
That really hurts!
And it's only when you switch with me?!
What about Taichi?!
Um, that's all you have to say?
Well, thinking we'd go out and commit crimes is a little out there.
But don't worry.
I won't use your body to do anything bad.
Wait, Inaba.
You're saying that you don't trust any of us, right?
It's not just me, right?
That's what you're worried about?!
Anyway, let's eat.
Lunch'll be over soon.
Yeah, we can talk while we eat.
What the...
Why was I ever worried?
I made a fool out of myself for nothing.
Hey, I've never done anything bad while I was in your body, Yui.
Whatever, I know your secret now.
I can't trust you.
Inaba, could you forget what I sa—
Weren't you making creepy movies with Taichi the other day?
No way.
That's the only exception!
In return, I'll tell you my secret.
What's she talking about?! What creepy movies?!
So we're in the same boat.
I've also masturbated to you before.
What?!
A Confession and Death...
Next Time
That's a gentle way of going insane.
I fell in love with you, and that hasn't changed.
So how do you feel about Iori, Taichi?
The white knight reveals his true colors!
Is that so wrong?!
Nagase!
My daily life, gone with the flow of time
seemed like a dream beyond what my senses could appreciate
I don't understand, I don't understand
So I mumble, still little more than a child, and dream
Maybe I'm a coward
It shouldn't matter
I wish I could be stronger
Onto that sort of facade,
my weak cries,
scattered feelings,
and changing intentions
the sun shone
You were the only one that mattered to me
I knew that
Maybe
.              .
hi       to
ra        n
do      m
.               .
.              .