[CENTRAL SOLDIER 1]
Fuhrer Bradley has returned?
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 2]
With a vengeance!
He destroyed a Briggs tank!
Chew on that,
you lousy Briggs traitors!
Let's rally the
remaining troops...
We're gonna retake
Central Command!
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
[LAN FAN THINKING]
The Fuhrer is at the main gate?!
Well...
This is the first time
I've actually laid eyes on him.
So now I know what
the bastard who took
my granddaughter's
arm looks like!
[IZUMI]
Is that so...?
You sacrifice our country...
just so you officials
can gain immortality...
And enslave
the world as your own?
[EDISON WHIMPERS]
And I take it
that Fuhrer Bradley
is also aware
of these plans?
[EDISON]
He was created to lead
this country for that purpose.
[SOLDIERS WHISPER]
Why shouldn't we do it?
We're creating
a world without war!
[IZUMI]
And you'd just have to
murder the world first.
It wouldn't die,
it would be reborn.
What you alchemists
refer to as reconstruction.
We wouldn't be murdering
the population like you said...
They would be given eternal life
while dwelling inside us!
Don't you see we would bring
the world together as one?!
All as one...! And one as all!
As the few chosen
ones of Amestris,
we will bring unity
to the entire country!
[EDISON YELLS]
[EDISON WHIMPERS]
So there you have it.
You still on their side?
The only thing these
guys care about is themselves.
Will you help them?
Now wait... Listen, men...
You need to follow orders.
That's the only way I can
put in a good word for you.
[IZUMI YELLS]
[THUD]
I've spent my entire
life as a soldier
and it just feels wrong
to disobey my superiors.
But I don't even
know what to believe
after hearing
all of this.
You can't make up your own
mind after hearing their plans?
How can you follow a superior
you have no faith in?
That is not loyalty.
That's mindless self-deception.
[SOLDIERS STAMMER]
Believe in yourselves.
And choose life over death...
Otherwise you've led
a shameful existence.
[EDISON WHIMPERS]
[ERIC] I have a family
right here in Central.
[CASPER] So do I.
[GUSTAV]
Yeah... We all do.
[CASPER]
Well, sir...
Consider this
our retirement.
Come in, Operations...
What's the status?
[CARLY]
It's not exactly
favorable, sir.
The Central soldiers are
getting their second wind.
What's your current location?
[OLIVIER]
We're in the Fuhrer's office.
Any survivors?
We've been unable to contact
any of our allies near
the office, General.
I've got a bad
feeling they've been
surrounded by Central troops.
[OLIVIER] Understood...
Get out of there if
it gets too dangerous.
Get out and leave me behind.
[CARLY EXHALES HEAVILY]
Yes, sir.
[OLIVIER]
Well, this place is crawling
with the enemy again...
It won't take much time
for their soldiers
to fully regroup
and seize the building.
Then we should hurry.
[IZUMI]
We get down far enough...
I can easily dig us
an escape tunnel to the streets.
Escape, huh?
That's right...
I don't mean to sound rude,
but you look like you could use
a little breather at this point.
We're getting close.
So you can
feel it too, huh?
You mean you can sense
his presence or something?
Let's just say I've
got a bad feeling.
The best way
I can explain it is
that my old wounds
are starting to ache.
[LOUD THUD]
[ED BREATHES DEEPLY]
[ED GASPS]
[GOLD-TOOTH]
Well, now, I wasn't exactly
expecting to have an audience.
You're gonna give
me performance anxiety.
[GOLD-TOOTH LAUGHS]
Who the
hell are you?
How should I answer that?
Hmm...?
You might know me as
the man who
created King Bradley.
[EVERYONE GASPS]
That is my most
proud accomplishment.
You created the Fuhrer?
So it's safe to say...
You're obviously
working with them.
[GOLD-TOOTH]
I didn't realize
that was you...
And here I thought you
were at the radio station
when in fact you've come
here to meet me in person...
I can't tell you
how much trouble
you've saved me,
Colonel Mustang.
Why don't you boys keep
them out of my hair
for just a few minutes?
[ED GRUNTS]
Who are these guys?
[ROY]
More dummy soldiers?
No... They move
too deliberately...
It's not just on instinct.
[GOLD-TOOTH]
These men were at one time
the other candidates
to become King Bradley.
[ROY AND HAWKEYE GASP]
[ROY]
The men who were
gathered at birth...
Raised by the state...
Specifically educated...
and trained in combat
for the sole purpose
of becoming the Fuhrer.
It took eleven
unsuccessful attempts
before the creation
of King Bradley.
So that means... These men...
[GOLD-TOOTH]
You could call them
the leftovers, I guess...
But one thing's certain...
After years of training,
they're skilled warriors
in their own right.
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
They may not be as
powerful as Bradley himself...
...but they are strong.
[GUNFIRE]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[SEARGENT BREATHES HEAVILY]
Damn...
Miserable traitors.
[BUCCANEER GRUNTS]
What a stupid time
to go passing out.
Keep resting!
Forgot about this.
[BUCCANEER GRUNTS]
I better keep it in
or I'll just bleed to death.
[METAL CLANGS]
So he's still goin' strong.
[GREED YELLS]
[GREED] Oww!
What the hell, old man?!
It's not like
I meant-- incoming!
[GREED GRUNTS]
[GREED]
Cheap son of a bitch.
[METAL CLANGS]
[FU GRUNTS]
Certainly makes a
difference when you have
a weapon you're more
comfortable with.
[FU GASPS]
[FU GRUNTS]
[BRADLEY]
It's impressive how
quickly you move...
You're even older than I am.
However...
This is as old as
you're going to get.
Old man Fu! Ahh...!
Well if it isn't
the young prince.
[GREED]
Damn it, Ling!
Ask me before you take over!
I can't help but
recall the last time
we fought when
I took that girl's arm...
It seems that once again
you'd rather risk your own life
than give up
on something
that's not even
worth fighting for.
Young Lord...
Forget me...
My life isn't
worth fighting for.
Don't give me that crap!
Are you honestly telling me
that I should be like him?!
A king should fight
for his people...
...because he is
nothing without them.
This man is about to
sacrifice his own nation.
His people... I'll never
become the monster that he is!
If you truly are a man
worthy to be a king,
you must be able
to accept some loss--
You need to rest! Please!
[FU GRUNTS]
[FU LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
You're right,
Young Lord... I need rest.
Time for this
old man to find rest.
[LING AND GREED YELL]
Harden your shield, Greed!
Protect the Young Lord's body!
[LING GRUNTS]
[LING GASPS]
[FU THINKING]
Young Lord...
Become the king
you're meant to be.
But this old servant...
...has no choice but
to offer his retirement!
[EVERYONE GASPS]
[LING AND GREED]
You stubborn fool!
I'm taking you straight
to hell with me, Bradley!
You bastard!
[SLASH]
[FU GRUNTS]
[FU THINKING]
Even while sacrificing myself...
...I still couldn't lay
a single scratch on him.
Young Lord... Please forgive...
...my shameful death.
[BRADLEY GRUNTS]
[BUCCANEER]
That Philosopher's Stone
might have given you
the eyes of a god...
But even you can't
dodge an attack...
...if you can't
see it coming!
[BRADLEY GRUNTS]
Alright, old man...
Maybe you are
going to hell...
...but you
aren't goin' alone.
I'll keep you company
on the ride down.
Ohhh... You have
my gratitude...
Thank... you.
[BRADLEY GRUNTS]
[BRADLEY YELLS]
Hmm...?
[LING SCREAMS]
[THUD]
[LAN FAN GASPS]
[LAN FAN]
Grandfather!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[HISSING]
[HEINKEL]
Jeez... First a ditch and
then you run into a lamppost...
Have you ever even
driven a car before?
[YOKI]
Will you shut up?!
It's not my fault that
worthless piece of junk
was impossible to control!
[AL] Calm down,
this is no time
for us to fight!
We've just gotta hurry up
and find a way to
get underground.
Is that...?
That must be from
Colonel Mustang's men.
Let's just hope
that everyone's okay.
Brother.
Let's move!
[METAL CLANGS]
I get it...
These guys are all superhuman.
But... Come on!
This is just ridiculous!
[SCAR GROWLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[GUNFIRE]
[ROY GASPS]
You keep leaving your
back wide open, sir.
Well I've gotta give
you something to do.
[ROY YELLS]
[IZUMI]
The portal of truth...
I'm sure you're
all familiar with
the alchemist's ultimate sin...
Human transmutation,
of course...
If they commit this taboo,
they open the portal...
And they pay the
equivalent price for it.
[OLIVIER]
The equivalent price...
Hmm... I take it
you're referring to how
the Elric Brothers
lost their bodies...
Tell me, what price
was it that you paid?
I lost part
of my insides.
And then after sacrificing
a part of myself...
I learned the truth.
Human transmutation...
It can't even be performed.
God, I'm sorry...
You must find this dull...
Being a soldier and all.
[ARMSTRONG]
Quite the contrary.
The Homunculi refer to
those unfortunate enough
to have opened the portal
of truth as sacrifices.
That could very likely
be a clue as to what
the enemy has in store.
[OLIVIER]
So then... I take it there
was somebody that you lost...
and you wanted to see
them again so badly...
that you risked opening the
portal and losing your own body?
And what about you?
Don't you have someone
that you'd risk anything
to see one last time?
[OLIVIER LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
That's not really the kind of
thing we soldiers think about.
We don't see any point in
clinging to those who've died.
We only know how to fight
to keep more from dying.
I suppose that
makes sense.
However, I do have
some experience
with what
you've described.
My first encounter
with Edward Elric...
When a Homunculus
invaded Fort Briggs,
Edward blatantly
refused my orders
to tell me what
he knew about it.
At the time, I had not
yet been made aware
that the enemy
had been holding
the life of his
childhood friend hostage.
He just kept repeating:
"I can't answer that."
It was quite clear
that any further threat
from me would be wasted.
In that moment, he was
acting neither as a soldier,
nor as a "Dog of
the Military" State Alchemist.
The look in his eyes...
...was desperate.
A boy, willing
to pay any price
to protect the
things he loved.
Hmm... Ed always did have
a knack for being stubborn.
[OLIVIER LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
I'd be lying if I
were to tell you
that I wasn't moved when
I looked into his eyes.
But still...
That doesn't change the fact
that he is a naiÃ ̄ve child.
I only hope that he can
help lead us out of this fight
without his naivety burying us.
[GOLD-TOOTH]
That should do fine...
I suppose it's about
time we got started.
[HAWKEYE GRUNTS]
[GUNFIRE]
Now Number Sixteen...
Number Seventeen...
Number Twenty-one...
Number Twenty-Three...
And Number Twenty Six.
Come join me.
What's he doing?
[ED GASPS]
Now then! Here goes!
[ED]
What have you done?!
[GOLD-TOOTH]
This...? This right here
is just the beginning.
You seem like a smart boy.
Do you know how
many military operated
alchemy laboratories
there are here in Central?
The last I heard, they've only
got four labs left in the city.
No...
The 5th Laboratory...
They've got five!
It's a transmutation circle...!
The entire city!
You mean...
It's connecting all of the
laboratories into a circle?
[LOUD RUMBLING]
What's happening?!
[HEINKEL GASPS]
[AL]
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
[DOGS BARK]
[HORSES WHINNY]
Izumi.
Yeah...
That's our cue to get
the hell out of here.
We're far enough down
to dig an escape tunnel...
Stand back
a few steps.
[OLIVIER]
Then it's time to part ways.
Huh...?
We're staying.
We can't turn our
backs on this fight now.
We're on a path leading directly
to the heart of the enemy.
We didn't come all
this way just to pass up
the chance to storm in there
and pop some ventricles.
Are you sure
about this?
You saved our lives.
Thanks for your help...
Izumi Curtis.
Don't mention it...
Good luck, General Armstrong.
[GOLD-TOOTH LAUGHS]
[ED GRUNTS]
[ED GASPS]
[ED, IZUMI, AND AL]
What?!
[IZUMI SCREAMS]
[AL SCREAMS]
[ED SCREAMS]
[MARCOH]
Alphonse!
[IZUMI SCREAMS]
Izumi!
Izumi, no!
[ED SCREAMS]
No...! Fullmetal!
You... bastard!
[NARRATOR]
Anger is born from the
extreme depths of human sorrow.
And when two souls,
both shaken to their very
core with the rage of loss,
attempt to control
the same body,
they will only unleash
true annihilation.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 58: Sacrifices.
His only desire
was to continue protecting
him... even after his demise.