I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but then a small incident happened.
What I received was a courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
My feelings have become more powerful, since what
I've always believed in is resonating so strongly now.
I don't want to stop communicating, because I can't
stand it when someone is left in the dark.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
I've been thinking about her since we met...
About that girl who had such deep, beautiful eyes...
who seemed just about the same age as me.
I'm sure we'll just clash if we ever meet again, but...
But...
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?
Give me a break already!
You've been staring off into space and zoning out since
the other day, no matter what we talk about!
I-I'm sorry, Alisa-chan...
Don't apologize!
If talking to us really is that boring,
then just go ahead and zone out by yourself!
Let's go, Suzuka!
Alisa-chan...
Nanoha-chan...
It's all right, Suzuka-chan.
It really was my fault this time.
I don't think that's really true... but anyway, Alisa-chan
went completely overboard just now.
I'm going to go have a talk with her.
I'm sorry about this...
I guess I made her angry... I'm sorry, Alisa-chan...
Alisa-chan... Alisa-chan!
Alisa-chan!
What?
I can sort of understand why you're so angry,
but you can't get angry over things like that.
But it really annoys me!
It's so obvious that she's worried about something!
It's written all over her face that
she's lost and troubled!
But... no matter how many times we ask
her about it, she won't tell us a thing.
She's lying when she says she's not lost or troubled!
Everybody has something they keep secret,
even from their closest friends.
If Nanoha-chan wants to keep it a secret,
don't you think all we can do is wait for her?
That's what annoys me so much!
I'm sure we could help her, at least a little!
Anything would be fine, I'm sure...
Even if we can't do anything about whatever it is...
...at the very least, we can all worry about it together!
You really do like Nanoha-chan, don't you?
Of course I do!
Because she was there for me, I was no longer alone...
Yes...
It was the same with me...
Because Nanoha-chan was there,
we were all able to become friends...
Nanoha-chan, we're sorry.
We both have lessons today, so...
You'll be gone till late tonight, right?
Have a nice time, and do your best.
Alisa-chan...
Ah, I'm sure everything will turn
out all right, Nanoha-chan!
Yeah. Thanks, Suzuka-chan.
Now that I think about it... it's been a
while since I've walked home alone.
I guess I'll make a stop before I go home...
...because I don't want anyone
to see my face right now.
When we all first met...
...I was a lot weaker than I am now,
and I could never say what I was thinking...
No matter what anyone said or did to me,
I could never stand up to them...
And I was a terrible kid who thought only
of herself... I was selfish, and a bully.
I always made fun of our classmates
and joked about everything...
...because my heart was really weak.
Ah... that's mine...
U-Umm...
Because I was weak back then too,
I couldn't say what I wanted to say...
That it was really precious to me,
so if you could please give it back...
Even after you told me to stop, I didn't listen...
...because I thought that if I listened
to what someone else had to say...
...I'd lose for some reason.
What was it Nanoha-chan said back then...?
"Does that hurt? The hearts of people who have their
precious things taken away hurt a whole lot more!"
That's right...
After that, I got into a big fight
with Alisa-chan, didn't I?
And the one who stopped us was...
The incredibly quiet girl who decided to be brave.
Stop it!
Back then... it was because I was so desperate...
After that, we slowly began to talk more
and more to each other, didn't we?
Yeah... just the three of us.
So? What did you want from me,
after bringing up that old story?
You should know the answer to that.
I understand that she doesn't want the
two of us to worry about her, at least...
Which also means that we probably
can't help her do anything about it...
If all we can do is wait, then...
I'll just stay angry while I'm waiting!
Angry at the sadness of not being
able to understand her feelings...
...and at her, for not being able to rely
on the strength of her best friends!
You sure are stubborn.
Hmph!
I see... so you got into a fight.
That's not it. Alisa-chan just got
mad because I was zoning out.
She's one of your best friends, isn't she?
Yeah. Almost since I first started school.
Here you go.
This is your share.
I don't have cram school today...
...so I should be able to do some Jewel Seed
hunting, at least until dinnertime.
Let's do our best today.
Yeah, let's...
The food they have here... isn't all that bad!
Now then, let's see what my little princess is up to.
Oops, almost forgot this.
You haven't touched your meal again!
That's no good... you have to eat.
I had some of it... I'm fine, so don't worry.
Shall we get going, then?
I've been able to get a rough estimate of
where the next Jewel Seed should be.
And I don't want to keep Mother waiting for too long...
Well... because you're my master, Fate...
...and because I'm your familiar...
if you ask me to go, I'll go, but...
Oh, we can go after you finish eating, if you want.
T-That's not what I meant.
I'm worried about you, Fate.
Using wide area searching magic uses
up a lot of physical strength...
...yet you're hardly eating anything, and barely resting...
And your wound isn't something
you can take lightly, either.
I'm fine, because I'm strong.
Fate...
Now then, let's go. Mother's waiting for me.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha!
Hey, Kyouya... about Nanoha-chan...
Has she been worried about something recently?
That's how she looked when I saw her earlier,
and Suzuka's pretty worried about her, too...
I wonder... she has been going
out a lot at night recently...
I might be prying a bit too much...
...but do you think maybe you could
ask her to talk to me about it?
Thank you for the offer, but...
I don't really think she'll talk about it.
So I'm no good...?
Ah, that's not it! That's definitely not it.
I didn't mean that she won't talk to you specifically,
but that she probably won't talk to anyone about it.
She's always been like that, whenever
she's been worried about something.
I see...
Well, I'm sure there's nothing to worry about.
I'm sure she'll be able to solve
whatever it is on her own.
I see.
It has so many features, it'll surprise
you every time! Just look!
Ah... I might be out of time...
I'll need to get home soon.
Don't worry about it. I'll stay around
here and search a little longer.
Okay... but will you be all right by yourself, Yuuno-kun?
Yep. Go home and get some dinner, okay?
Okay.
Alisa-chan and Suzuka-chan should be on
their way home from lessons right now...
I'm pretty sure it's somewhere around here,
but I can only get a rough reading.
Yeah, I can understand... searching through
this much garbage must be a pain.
This is a bit heavy-handed...
...but I'll release a lot of magical power across the
circumference of this area and force it to activate.
Ah, wait a second. I'll do that for you.
Will you be all right? You'll be
pretty drained afterwards...
Just whose familiar do you think I am?
Then, I'm counting on you.
Well then...!
A forced activation spell in the city?!
This is really dangerous! Hope I make it in time...!
Raising Heart, please!
Found it!
But it looks like she's nearby, too.
Let's hurry and finish things, then.
Bardiche!
Sealing Form, Set up.
Nanoha, can you see the activated Jewel Seed?
Yeah. It's really close.
That other girl's really close, too.
Seal it before she does!
Got it!
Lyrical Magical!
Jewel Seed Serial XIX!
Seal!
Device Mode.
Stop it!
When I first met both Alisa-chan and
Suzuka-chan, we weren't friends...
Because we couldn't talk with each other.
Because we couldn't understand each other.
The reason Alisa-chan got angry with me this morning
was because I couldn't tell her what I was thinking...
All right! Nanoha, hurry up and secure it!
Like we'll let her!
Because we both have the same goal...
...there might be no way we
can avoid fighting like this...
But I want to know!
Last time, we couldn't properly introduce ourselves...
I'm Nanoha! Takamachi Nanoha!
A third grader who attends then
Seishou Auxiliary Elementary School.
Scythe Form.
Why does she have such lonely eyes...?
Flier Fin.
Sending an e-mail to Nanoha?
Yeah. Telling her we just finished our lessons.
Well, let's get going.
Ah, yeah! Wait a second.
I hope you solve your problem soon.
Do your best. We'll always be
cheering you on. Suzuka.
Flash Move.
Divine Shooter.
Defencer.
Fate-chan!
You said nothing would change just by talking...
...but I'm sure there are things we can't communicate
to each other without using words!
We might not be able to do anything about
competing with each other like this...
...but I can't stand fighting like this without
knowing anything about you!
Originally, I was gathering the Jewel Seeds because
Yuuno-kun was searching for them...
...because Yuuno-kun needs to gather and
return them to where they belong!
So I was here to help him!
It was just a coincidence that I ended up helping him...
...but now I'm gathering the
Jewel Seeds of my own free will!
Because I don't want to put the people
around me or my city in danger!
That's... my reason for doing this!
I...
Fate! You don't have to answer her!
You don't have to tell anything to people who are just
acting nice to you in a strange neighborhood...
...who are probably just trying to use you anyway!
Our top priority is to capture the Jewel Seeds!
Nanoha!
I'll be fine!
Suzuka, what's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing...
Geez, I'm starving. Let's hurry back home already.
Ah, yeah.
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
An explosion that large...
this is seriously dangerous!
But... Mother's waiting, so...
The true identity of the
Jewel Seeds, and a new mage!
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Seven:
The Third Mage!?
Lyrical Magical won't lose!