I can't get out because there's no door.
Because there's no door...?
Yuki!
Yuki! Yuki! Yuki!
Yuki...
No...
Say something, Yuki!
No!
Yuki!
Because there's no door?
No.
There is a door.
And that's...
my choice to select.
This
Selection
..is...
ubaware kanatte risou wa kurikaesu geemu surinuketeku
The acts of theft and granting are entwined within the endless games
nichijou wa utarete ana darake tatteiru no ga yatto kana
You finally take a stand after your quiet life was beaten to a pulp
ketsuron no nai kuuron mienai ruuru no ue de odotteru suteppu de
Dance upon the unseen rules with endless speculation
kuzurete iku kyou tsunagitomeru saishuu beru ga naridasu
The final bell rings out to bind together this crumbling world
ukabu omoi no joukei ni wa kimi ga irun da yo
Within my memories you're always there
waretterun dayo
Simply laughing
yurushitakunai no? motometenai no?
You say you can't forgive? That you have no desires?
soredemo mada
So why can't you stop?
We cry OPEN torimodoshitai mirai kowashitai sekai
We cry "Open!" to take back tomorrow and destroy the world
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
akehanashitai negai GOT IT? ima
Do you finally know your deepest wish?
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
kurosu suru I wish you don't cry
We cross and I wish you don't cry
hikari to yami no saki kasanatte mata iro ga tsuku you
Another color lies at the point where light and darkness cross
"sono saki" wo shinjitemiyou ka
And I choose to believe in it
No Trespassing
We'll be in big trouble if the
man from earlier finds us again.
But we still have to check it out.
Yuki...
Yuki!
So pretty...
Your tears, Ruu... they sparkle like jewels...
I wanted to be your LRIG.
The best Selector's LRIG.
But... what I really desired
was probably something else.
Mayu's sorrow... her darkness, her corruption, her misery...
I was born from those feelings.
But as I battled by your side,
you entered me, Ruu.
You spread within me.
I felt something... so very
beautiful and precious fill me up.
You showed me what it was that I truly desired.
Yuki...
Thank you,
Ruu.
Stop it! I don't want to hear you say that!
I hate how it sounds like you're saying farewell!
Why is she crying?
Why is it painful for her to let go?
After all, when it was me...
Man, I couldn't care less about your
deep emotions and farewells and tears.
The battle ends when one of the LRIGs disappears.
You girls lose by default.
Say, Iona—that is, Yuki-san,
can you even still fight?
Ruu and Yuki won't lose!
Shiro!
Tama!
This can't be!
How did she get out?
Tama...
Ruu...
Use Grow.
Make me and Yuki into one.
R-Ruu...
You don't need to do that.
If we really became one, Tama would be tainted!
You're pretty, Yuki.
Just like snow glimmering in the sunlight.
Me... pretty?
Tama, who dreams of the summer sun,
and Yuki, who loves the winter snow.
If Tama and Yuki come together as one,
you'll be like snow falling in summer.
Grow.
Level 5 Mayu!
Wh-Why my name?
You know, I love Tama.
And I love Yuki.
The one who created them is you, Mayu.
To be honest, I can't really say that I like you right now.
After all, you made everyone suffer a lot.
And they're still suffering right now.
Some girls have scars on their bodies and souls that will never heal.
But you had a chance to become Mayu.
The true you is next to me.
I'm sure that if things went differently,
if we hadn't had to meet like this,
I would have loved you, too.
Th-Those words...
Hearing those words doesn't make me happy at all!
I hate them! I hate how they're in past tense!
Ulith! Black Desire!
Now you're talking, Mayu.
Mayu!
Ruu, let's fight back!
Even if Selector battles themselves are twisted,
they're still the only wish Mayu was able to send to the outside world!
Okay.
What a sorrowful room...
Mayu! Summon Arc Energe!
Okay!
Attack with Laevateinn!
Mayu, are you okay?
Yes!
Why?
Why are you calling her by that name?
How's that doing?
Well, aside from the lack of appetite...
So, is that girl back?
Not that it matters to me.
Did that eat dinner already?
What is that doing?
Make that take a bath.
Not that I care.
I've never once heard my name
spoken in such a caring tone.
Look at yourself!
Aren't you supposed to be
the greatest Selector there is?!
Selector...
One who selects.
I... didn't select a thing.
Mayu?
It's not that I didn't want to make a selection.
I didn't have a selection to make!
That's right. I... I didn't take
everything away from you all.
I gave everyone an opportunity to make a selection.
Whether to cry, smile, or get angry...
At least they got to choose!
I was denied even that!
The only connection to the outside
is the sky seen through that window.
This room was Mayu's whole world.
I didn't have a chance to select—
That's not true.
Why did you seal Tama away, Mayu?
Why did you allow only Yuki to fight in battles?
That's...
Mayu hated the world outside the window,
filled by light as it was.
But in reality, she sought and longed
for that world, more than anyone else.
That's why, just when Mayu's life was coming to its end,
she made a selection.
With that, Tama awoke.
There is a world that is neither simply black nor white, filled with many colors
where Tama, carrying Mayu's inner longing for the light, was finally released.
N-No! No, no!
No... No...
I'm different... I couldn't—
Why don't you come see the
world outside together with us?
How can you say such a thing?!
Huh?
I'm already dead!
What is this? What's happening?
Mayu!
Ruuko...
Why are you trying to protect the LRIG I created?
No one ever loved me.
No one ever called me by my name.
No one ever embraced me...
No one...
If we hadn't had to meet like this,
I would have loved you, too.
If we had met differently,
would things have changed?
I was to end my existence here, unbeknownst to anyone.
I wanted others to know.
I wanted to affect someone's life with the fact that I lived here.
Even if
it had to be through hatred.
I want to know more about you, Mayu!
And not through hatred or painful feelings!
Guess what color I picked.
The color you picked?
Ulith can control all colors at level 5.
This move can only be used once.
If you can guess what I picked,
it's your win.
If you get it wrong, it's my win.
This card is my heart.
The color she picked.
Is it the color of darkness—the color of her hatred for the world outside?
Or is it the color of light she sealed away with Tama?
There is a world that is neither simply black nor white, filled with many colors.
That's right.
Get to it already!
I can't hold myself back any longer!
Now, Ruu,
what color is this card?
A world without colors.
That card is colorless.
What?
W-Wait a second!
That can't be!
You're executing me and not even giving me a chance to fight?!
No!
I have no cards to play and no Arts to use.
There's nothing I can do in the next turn.
Colorless.
The color at the end of all things, where everything is erased.
It's the color at the beginning of all things, too.
Any color can be added from here on.
You'll be the one coloring it, Mayu.
I... can begin again?
Yeah.
I...
can be embraced by someone?
Yeah.
Mayu...
Ruuko.
Let's take our oath before this world disappears.
This time, let's make your wish come true.
My wish?
It was to return the girls who became
LRIG cards to their original selves, wasn't it?
Turn the girls who became LRIGs into humans.
With that, you'll go back
to your original forms,
but Tama and Yuki might become humans too!
Ruu, you're just like a kid.
Huh?
You do understand, don't you?
Making a selection means to
pick one thing, not everything.
I did make a selection!
I'm not going to make a selection at the sacrifice of something else.
Even if it means that there'll be times when I'll want to cry from the pain and sadness,
I'll still choose everything.
That's the selection I made!
You really are just like a kid!
Look who's talking, Mayu.
I accept
the Laws of the Selector.
And now
a new Eternal Girl will be born!
Life
I walk through this endless street maze to the sound of bells
deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
Looks like they've finished
construction on that building.
And the pillar didn't make things disappear either!
I will shed the life that I was given for a brighter tomorrow
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
My, you're all dressed up.
Are you going out with the girls?
Yup! We'll be studying for our entrance exams!
What about dinner?
Ah, I won't be staying out too late today, so—
I now feel catharsis in a world that will allow neither dark nor light
hikari to yami kowasaseru sekai de mezamehajimeru catharsis
You sure know how to stomp a guy awake, Ruu...
Geez, sleep in your futon like a regular person when you stay over!
Take care, okay?
With fear in my heart I swore that I would never again lose anybody
furueteiru mune de chikatta mou dare hitori nakushitakunai
Yeah! I'm off!
Have fun.
Looks like Ruu-chan grew up a little bit, doesn't it?
You think so?
I do.
She's grown so much.
The morrow may be drenched in tears, but I will face the wind with pride
ashita namida afuretemo kaze no naka wo kakenukeyukou
It's useless! There's no more room in my brain!
It's only been an hour, you know?
She's right!
I will do what must be done for my future, I will remember my wish, and I will never give up
hanate eranda mirai he torimodosu yo kono negai wa akiramenai
If you really want to go to the same school as Hitoe, you'll have to put your back into it a bit more!
Hitoe...
share some of your brain with me!
Geez...
Hey, how about a quick breather?
A breather?
Let's play WIXOSS!
I'll trash Rhino with Tavir!
The activation ability on your new LRIG is awesome!
Kazuki told me about some different cards to try.
But I still haven't found one that matches me as well as Hanayo-san did...
The world of Selector battles has come to an end.
The girls who were sealed into cards as LRIGs were all able to return to their former selves.
Summer Update
Edition
Selector battles...
What was that game all about?
Featuring
This
Summer's
Trends
Aoi Akira's Trends
Gotta Be WIXOSS
"I don't know!"
"But I want to!"
This issue is for you!
Akira's
total
dedication
to
blue
decks!
Akira's
total
dedication
to
blue
decks!
It was a game that was born from the hatred and sorrow of a single, lonely girl.
A game of broken rules that only
brought sorrow, no matter the selection.
But...
we found something within that game.
Greetings.
Would you like to
becometh friends?
z
We made our own selections outside the rules.
If we hadn't played the game, we'd never have found them
or learned what's really dear to us.
And I finally made my selection.
So...
I will continue...
my search...
Ruu!
...for a new selection that I've yet to see.
Believing that...
is...
my selection.