Hello, Edward.. You appear
to have grown some.
I spoke with Pinako.
You tried human transmutation.
What makes you think
you can show up like this?
There's nothing left
for you here anymore!
I noticed.
Tell me, Edward.
What possessed you
to burn down my home?
After what happened,
we vowed to never turn back...
We did it as a symbol
of our resolve.
No you didn't. You were
hiding the memory.
You didn't want to be reminded
of what you've done...
And thought you could
erase the memory
by destroying the evidence.
You're wrong!
It's just like a child
who hides the sheets
after he wets the bed.
You ran away...
And you know it.
I.. You don't
know a damn thing!
You make me sick
to my stomach.
He's exactly like I was
when I was his age.
[door opens]
[laughter]
[growls]
You haven't changed
in the slightest.
All these years.. and you
look exactly the same.
Where have you
been all this time?
Why didn't you
come back sooner?
Trisha was waiting for
you until the very end...
Pinako.
Hmm?
The life form my
sons transmuted...
Are you positive
that it was Trisha?
Huh? Well I wouldn't--
It didn't even
look human to me...
so I wouldn't
think of it as--
No.. that's not
what I'm asking.
Did you notice the eye color?
Or the hair color?
What are you
trying to get at?!
Are you telling me that
that wasn't even Trisha?!
For all that those
boys sacrificed...
You're saying that
thing they created
wasn't even their mother?!
[Ling] Whoa! You don't
sleep or eat...
You don't even run
out of breath?
Uh-huh.. I just have
to make sure the seal
doesn't get harmed.
That's so cool.. So you really
are immortal then, huh?
No, I'm not.
This body... It's
like a time bomb.
Barry mentioned something...
And it made me realize that
any type of body is incompatible
with a foreign soul...
Pairing them together.. the body
will eventually reject it.
It could happen tomorrow...
or ten years from now...
but it's inevitable
that it will.
Oh, no.. Al, we've gotta get you
back in your regular body.
Well.. Hold on.. If it's
about to give out on you...
Couldn't you just transfer your
soul into some other object?
'Cuz if that's the case...
then for the time being...
Well, you're impervious to pain
and you don't have to eat!
It sounds like
a great deal to me!
No, it isn't! You don't know
what you're talking about!
Sorry.
Winry!
[knock on door]
[Al] Winry? I'm coming in.
Y'know.. you and Brother always
gotta be the first to explode...
I never get the chance
to be the one to get mad.
It's just.. well...
I guess I can't fall asleep...
I don't think this
body will let me.
Oh.
Just tell me you're gonna
get your body back... Okay?
[running footsteps]
Give it back! You have to give
my brother his body back!
He's the only family I have!
I won't let you take it!
Take it?
Do you even know
what you're saying?
You're the one who
tossed his body aside
and put him in that armor...
Aren't you, alchemist?
[Tucker] It's true.
You and I are exactly the
same. Accept it, Edward.
We make monsters.
Edward.
Why did you leave
me here like this?
[Pinako] Ed? Get out
of bed already!
Your father's about
to head out.
This one.. Do you
mind if I keep it?
It's the only photo we had
taken with all four of us.
Of course, you're
welcome to it.
Thank you.
I need to tell you
something important, Pinako.
Something terrible is going
to happen in this country soon...
You should escape
while you can.
This country's lousy
with terrible things...
And I can't leave.
I've got other people
who need me here in case
they want to come home.
I've given you my warning.
Hey Hohenheim, wait!
Try not to be such
a stranger, alright?
I wish I could, Pinako...
It's too bad I won't get
to enjoy your cooking anymore.
[thunder]
You're not really gonna
dig it up.. Are you, Ed?
Why don't we go back.
No.. My stumps are
aching from the weather.
It's about to rain...
Let's just hurry and do this.
Ed!
Don't push yourself!
Let's head on home.
No.
I'm not gonna be able to move
forward until I know for sure...
And besides...
You ran away.
I won't run
away from this.
Granny.. Mom's hair was
a light chestnut color.
This is black.
This femur...
It's much too long.
And this pelvis?
I'm pretty sure it's male.
It is?
I'm sorry... But I'm afraid
this isn't your mother, Ed.
[Ed laughs]
Then that's it...
It really is impossible to
bring the dead back to life...
The undeniable truth...
It was impossible
all along...
Edward.. Now Listen to me...
You've gotta get
a hold of yourself.
I'm okay, Granny...
It's okay.
From the moment
I made this thing,
it's been the symbol
of my despair...
But not anymore...
Now it's an emblem of hope.
Al can be returned to normal.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[phone ringing]
Curtis residence.. I didn't
expect this.. You never call.
Uh, yeah.. I need to ask
you something, Teacher.
But, well...
Well what? Spit it out.
It has to do with when you
tried to transmute your baby.
What about it, Ed?
The thing is.. What Al
and I transmuted...
It wasn't actually our mother.
What is this, Ed? What
are you trying to tell me?
I'm sorry to ask you this,
but the child you transmuted...
Are you sure that it was your
child that you brought back?
[phone is hung up]
Thank you, Ed.
It's good to know my son
and his wife helped people.
I'm proud of them.
So, Hohenheim...
Did he even bother to say
where he was going?
Of course he didn't...
And I didn't a-
Ahhh! What's wrong with me?
I can't believe I forgot
to give him the message!
A message?
Yes. A last request...
From your mother.
I'll be gone when he returns...
Can you tell him something?
I need him to know...
I couldn't keep my promise...
I died before he did...
and I'm so sorry.
A promise?
What promise?
You got me...
Sorry to ask,
but could you pass it on
if you bump into him?
Why should I have to?
I know it doesn't
seem like it...
but he does care about
you and your brother.
Teh! Yeah, I'll pass it on...
Right after I clock
him in the face.
[Pinako] Heading back to
Central already, are you?
[Ed] Yeah.. Al's
probably mad at me...
I'm gonna have plenty
of explaining to do.
What the helllll?!
I'm sorry, brother!
You..! What..! How are
you this beat up?!
Ahhh!
And you!
What the hell
are you doing here?!
Eating a delicious dinner.
Seriously.. How did
this happen to you?
[Ed] A Homunculus and
Barry the Chopper...
And just to throw
a cherry on top,
you find out your body
might reject your soul.
I'm gonna have to
extend what little
you have left of your armor.
Ed? He'll be able to get
his body back, right?
Yeah, of course he will! I
told you I'm gonna get it back.
Al.. I've gotta tell
you something...
I dug up the body that we
transmuted in Resembool.
What?! Why would
you do that?
Because, Al.. I found out
that the thing we buried
wasn't really our mother.
But.. Hold on a minute...
Then that means...
The thing we made...
I don't know what,
but it was something
completely different.
But if it wasn't, then
what happened to me...?
That's just it...
This has actually convinced me
we can return you to normal.
Ed, Are you sure?
Yeah.. But, before I
start explaining how...
Well.. Uh, Winry...
Do, um.. Uh...
Do you remember when
Al and I got in a fight
when we were kids about...
who'd marry you?
Huh? The fight we were
talking about on the roof?
Yeah, that one. Al told
me you turned him down.
Mm-hmm. Turned you both down.
Whatever, so the question's
for both of you then...
What was your reasoning?
She said...
[both] "I just don't like men
who are shorter than me."
Ahhhhh!!!
You can't judge a man
for something he can't help!
Uhhh.. I don't really see
how this has anything to do
with getting Al's body back.
I had to be sure...
Al had a memory of
something I don't recall...
And you seem to clearly remember
it the same way, Winry...
Which means that it
happened without a doubt...
So now that we know you
remembered something real...
then we also
know for a fact...
that really is Al
bonded in there.
I pulled you out, Al.
I actually did it.
I know it was only your
soul, but that's just it.
If I was able to pull
that much of you out...
then I've got a hunch...
that your body's still in
there and I can pull it out.
You think my body's
still in the portal...
existing separately
from my soul?
[Al gasps] Like Barry's body!
Right! What did you see?
Try to think back...
Can you remember what happened
when the Truth unraveled you?
[Al] I reached out...
And it was me! It was
my hand I grabbed!
I knew it!
Doesn't look like
we're done with
the Truth yet, Al.
We're gonna get in there
and pull your body out!
Brother!
After the portal.. I
remember looking at you
from inside that thing.
The thing we thought was Mom!
You were inside of it?
That thing was you?
I guess so.. But my
soul didn't bind.
It must've rejected
me right away.
So that means.. We didn't harm
anyone else's soul after all.
[knock on door]
[Bellhop] Mr. Elric?
You have a telephone
call from Izumi Curtis.
[Izumi] I did some research...
Sig and I looked up
our family lines...
And well... The child that
I transmuted.. It couldn't...
It didn't have a
single physical trait
that could've come from us.
You're on to
something, aren't you?
Yes.. I've come
to the conclusion
that death is permanent.
So not even transmutation
can change that fact.
All this time.. I thought that
I must've missed something...
but it was impossible
to do in the first place.
Ed!
Yes, ma'am?!
Thank you.
[phone is hung up]
[Al] So what did
Teacher have to say?
Well I'm not really sure why...
But she said.. thank you.
Al?
This entire time
I've been blaming
myself for what happened.
I thought it was me.
I thought I was the one
who killed Mom a second time.
And so did I.. Al.
Thanks, Brother...
Thank you...
I wasn't the one who
killed Mom after all!
Izumi.
I feel like I've been
brought back to life.
Our child wasn't made to
suffer twice because of me...
[Ed] But still... None
of this changes the fact
that I'm the one who
put you in that body...
And I don't care
what it takes...
I'm gonna make
you normal agai-
Brother... I was
right there with you
and I knew that
there were risks...
so quit trying to shoulder
all of this on your own.
I can't watch you
suffer like this.
Not on your own...
I can't just stand back
and watch other people
get hurt over what I've done.
Like what happened
to Mr. Hughes!
I felt like it was my fault
when I found out he was dead...
And I told myself that
if it meant other people
getting hurt, then I don't
even want my body back.
Brother...
I've met other people
who weren't exactly human...
but they still managed to live
their lives with a purpose.
And even in this body.. It
hasn't stopped other people
from treating me like
I'm still human.
This body could
reject me anytime...
But it's the same
with being human.
You never know when you might
get sick or die in an accident.
So I can still get
by like this...
I can live a somewhat
normal life...
And that's how I've managed
to keep going.. But now...
I can't take it anymore.
Because... I can't...
I can't take all the
nights by myself!
It's too lonely...
And that's why I have
to get back to normal.
Sure.. And you're going to.
We'll knock that Truth
jerk on his butt!
And then we're gonna pull your
body right outta that place!
[Al] Yeah!
[Winry] Huh?
That's weird. Have his
shoulders always been so broad?
[Narrator] The mere sight
of his injured friend
hastens the Colonel's
determination to uncover
the forces plaguing
the military.
While the young man is forced
to put everything he has
on the line in order
to escape from a dead end.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 21:
"Advance of the Fool."
Never wait for the
battle to come to you..
Strike the first blow!