Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
Fall is special. I eat five times as much.
Will you be getting the extra large today, too?
Futaba Odagiri!
Futaba Odagiri, you meanie!
What is this all about?
Oh, poor me!
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
It feels like fall is here.
It's a little chilly at this time of day, huh?
Grape picking.
Chestnut hunting, mushroom picking!
Maple leaf hunting!
Maple leaf hunting. I wonder
if maple leaves are tasty.
Well, they are all natural,
so maybe they taste good.
It's the autumn of eating.
You eat all year long,
spring, summer, winter, and fall.
Fall is special. I eat five times as much.
How about you two? What kind of autumn is it?
Hm... The autumn of reading?
The autumn of thriftiness!
Same as usual, then.
Yeah, I guess.
Futaba Odagiri!
Huh?
Wh-What was that?
"Ten Yen Short"
"Stuffed Hut"
What was that all about?
You do not know him?
Nope, no idea.
How impolite of him! He did not even
put a "Ms." in front of your name.
As your friend, I cannot accept such
rude behavior! He must pay the penalty.
It's fine. He's just a kid.
He was wearing East High's uniform, though.
No way, he's a high schooler? I thought
he was in seventh grade or something.
He said my first and last name, though.
How does he know my whole name?
All right, here you go!
Special Bucket o' Almond Jello!
Yay! Here I go!
Miss Yoko, your face looks like you're
looking at something disgusting.
You won't finish this one!
I ate it all! Done!
You finished...
More like you drank it all.
That was amazing, Futaba! But honestly,
it was so amazing that it put me off.
"Finished!"
"50 Jumbo Dumplings!"
"100 pcs. Fried Chicken!"
"Finished!"
"1000 pcs."
"Challenge Menu" "Extra Large Ramen"
"5000 yen penalty if you don't finish"
When did she do so many challenges? This shop
might not be able to handle her much longer.
It's okay. I do food challenges
at other shops, too.
Oh...
Take a commemorative photo for your first time
completing the Bucket o' Almond Jello challenge.
Okay.
Like this? Or maybe like this?
No matter how cute she looks, she still
finished a whole bucket of almond jello.
"Futaba Odagiri finished 300 bowls"
And these photos have her name on them.
Huh? My name?
"Futaba Odagiri finished 300 bowls"
I thought about it, and the only thing it could
be is that he saw my name on the shop photos.
But, why was he acting like that?
Right? I would understand if he looked up to me.
Normal people would be a little put off.
Futaba Odagiri!
Is this déjà vu?
But she was a girl.
Unforgivable! Not once, but twice!
No, they were two different people.
Uh... hm? They were two different people, right?
I said, the second one was a girl.
They did look exactly alike, though.
Why would he dress up as a girl?!
What is this all about?
Maybe I should get Yamaji to look
into this. They must pay the penalty.
--Oh, I do apologize.
--Hey, you wanna go karaoke after school?
--Yeah, sounds good!
--S-Sorry. I wasn't paying attention.
Oh! She must be the girl Futaba
and Hayama were talking about.
What? Sh-She's staring at me!
C-Can you meet me after school?
What?!
I wonder what Nishikawa wants to talk about.
Nishikawa is pretty, has a
great figure, and is athletic.
She's so cool!
I've never been able to approach her,
but now she wants to talk to me!
Ah, there she is.
Wow, you two really look exactly the same.
Yeah, they look like twins.
Looks like we made her mad.
Sasame Tsuji from Class 2.
Does that sound right?
I do not know the names of everyone in
my class yet. I have not talked to them yet.
Why is Futaba Odagiri here with you?!
'Cause we're friends.
What?!
Today was the first time
Nishikawa talked to me, though!
Perfect timing. Futaba Odagiri,
I have something to say to you!
Huh?
Don't get in my brother's way anymore!
Your brother?!
They must be twins!
He's a year older than me!
Really?
You look like twins, though.
Why am I in his way? I haven't done anything.
You have! I'm talking about
his big-eater challenges!
Big-eater challenges?
Ah, so he's the same type as Futaba.
He's failed the challenges
at Stuffed Hut so many times.
I see.
He's stubborn and hates to lose,
so he'll overdo it again.
Not to worry. I'll beat him so bad that
he'll never be able to overdo himself again.
Futaba Odagiri, you meanie!
I just... want to eat.
Oh, poor me!
Yeah, right.
"No more big-eater challenge.
--The Meat House"
"We reserve the right to refuse Futaba Odagiri.
--Challenge Restaurant"
"Banned! Futaba Odagiri.
--Surprise Lunch"
Maybe I overdid it. But I'm still hungry if I
order normally. And I don't have money.
"Stuffed Hut"
Welcome!
Welcome, Futaba!
Will you be getting the extra large today, too?
Mr. Stuffed!
I'll have a normal size today. I don't
want to be banned from here, too!
What, a normal size?!
Yup. I'll have a large helping of curry topped with
egg, corn, cheese, croquette, cutlet, and sausage.
That's not normal-sized!
Oh, huh?
Uh, you're one of the Tsuji's?
Mister! I'll have the same
thing as Futaba Odagiri!
I won't lose, Futaba Odagiri! You're my rival!
All right, here ya go.
Thanks!
Thank you!
"Extra Large Challenge"
Mm! Delicious!
I won't lose, Futaba Odagiri!
I won.
I won!
I beat her!
I finished it faster than you,
Futaba Odagiri! Now you're no longer a--
Hey, Mr. Stuffed. Did you
change your ingredients?
I knew you'd be able to tell.
I changed the seasonal vegetables.
I finished first!
There's no point in racing
if it's not a competition.
I want to savor it.
Wh--
Dang it!
"Stuffed Hut"
I'll remember this, Futaba Odagiri!
I won't forgive you, Futaba Odagiri!
--Oh, she's here!
--Those are delicious!
Teru!
Big Sis?
Come on, let's go home together.
Futaba Odagiri. If she's going to make a stop
to do a challenge somewhere, I have to stop her!
But if I do, then Nishikawa
might not like me anymore...
Oh, what should I do?
I see, so that boy is Futaba's rival.
It's a one-sided rivalry.
Now that I think about it,
Big Sis eats a lot, too.
Is that so?
You know how she's a little spacey.
So she eats while spaced out, too.
So it takes a while for her
to realize that she's full.
She's that spacey, huh?
Something...
...is there.
Right there!
Huh?
Apologies. Did you know I was here?
Oh my, Yamaji.
What? It was just Yamaji?
You came from behind this time, so it scared me.
Maybe I was imagining it, then.
I thought there was somebody else.
I'm pretty confident in my stealth skills.
All right, let's go.
Hm? What's that?
One, two, pull!
Ow...
Oh.
Tsuji?
Is that Futaba's rival's sister?
Oh no! How did you know?
Well...
There aren't many people who'd
fall for a trap like that these days.
I catch my brother like this!
Wait, don't put me on his level.
I needed to stop Futaba Odagiri from
doing more big-eater challenges!
But, I didn't want Nishikawa to get mad
at me, so I tried to keep undercover.
She can hear you loud and clear.
I can't believe you would set up a foul trap
in the middle of the road. How atrocious!
It's all your fault, Futaba Odagiri!
She runs away just like her brother.
She set a trap! Futaba, she's
after your life. Be careful!
My life?
Was it okay to talk to her like that?
What do you mean?
Isn't she the first person in your class
you've had a real conversation with?
She's right! Before her, you hadn't
talked to anyone in your class.
Usually, you're a loner in class who still doesn't
have any friends. Miss Yoko, she's a valuable--
Yamaji!
Well, Tsuji's brother is determined, too.
It feels like we'll be seeing
him a lot from now on.
Don't worry, I'll beat him
so bad he'll never recover.
No, you don't have to.
Maybe you can be nicer to him.
You do both like to eat a lot.
Hm... I don't know.
Can you keep it down. I'm trying to read here.
Oh, sorry. What are you reading, Nishiyama?
Hey!
"Come Forth⭐︎"
"Murder Mystery!!"
Oh.
No!
So you like these types of books?
It doesn't fit your image.
I-I borrowed this.
Oh, that's the book I lent to her.
S-See?
I buy most of them, but both of us have been huge
fans since elementary school. Especially Nishiyama.
You didn't need to say that!
It's all right. We all have our own tastes.
Why are you smirking like that?
It's fine. It's not weird or anything.
It looks like a cute... and easy to read... book...
I-I won't forget this!
I've seen this a lot recently.
Which is why you should be
nicer to Tsuji's brother.
You're telling me to be nice?
Isn't she the first person in your class
you've had a real conversation with?
That is true. But, she was so rude to Futaba!
E-Excuse me.
Er, um... I-I-m sorry!
Are you all right?
Ouch, that hurt.
Oh, my money.
Oh my!
Let's see. Oh, there's one here, too!
Nishikawa...
I'm ten yen short.
--What?!
--I wanted to buy strawberry milk...
I wonder where it went. We must find it!
Oh, I-It's okay. It's just ten yen.
Just ten yen?!
I'm sorry!
Oh, Miss Yoko. What are you doing?
Futaba Odagiri's friend. You're...
I'm Hayama from Class 3.
Tsuji dropped some coins, you see.
Did you drop them around here?
Ah! I just realized.
--It was my fault.
--I'm surrounded by Futaba Odagiri's friends!
--Oh no.
What should I do?!
What?! Was it a lot of money?
Yes, her precious ten yen.
Ten yen... ?
Here, you can have it. But if you'd rather,
you can also just borrow it.
See you.
I am very sorry!
Oh, um...
Now what? I owe one of
Futaba Odagiri's friends now.
But, I got to talk to Nishikawa a little.
And Hayama was nice.
I'm just going to return this.
Really? That sounds just like Miss Yoko.
She had that determined look
that said "every yen counts!"
But, that's what's so good about her.
She's been working for while now, too.
Nishikawa works part-time?!
Huh?
The younger one?
Is Nishikawa working part-time?
I can't believe it.
Yup, at a cake shop at the outskirts
of the Central Shopping Arcade.
They gave out fliers our school before.
Oh.
This is it, huh?
Oh, wow! There's a maid!
And someone who looks like a butler!
A shop where Nishikawa would
work really is on another level.
Tsuji?
Oh, you came already.
Oh, er...
What are you waiting for? Let's go in!
Wh... um...
Oh, this is good.
What a wonderful fragrance.
Hey, where's the new cake?
Wh-What?! How did this happen?!
What's wrong? Drink it while it's still hot.
Smells nice.
It's good!
You like it? This is one of my favorites.
Yup.
Here they are.
I've been waiting!
Huh?
We came to try the new cake.
I-Is it okay for me to try, too?
What, you don't like cake? Then, I'll have it.
Ah! I'll eat it!
You don't have to force yourself.
I'm not!
Really?
--Good for you, Miss Yoko.
--Yes. I like cake!
--Hm?
--You've made another friend.
--Then I'll feed you. Here, open wide.
--Friend?
--I can feed myself!
I guess if you think about it...
It was a miracle just to have Hayama and Odagiri.
Personally, having another high school girl
here will make things more fun for me.
You can make friends even without money!
It's a good thing that you became poor.
When you were rich and aloof...
Quiet, you mongrels!
I cannot believe that Tsuji
actually came to the shop.
Is she a friend? I wonder... I am not sure.
All right. Find a partner.
I need to find a partner... ?
N-Nishikawa!
She called out to me!
Until now, I just paired with the last person or
with the teacher. She wants to pair up with me?
U-Um...
Hm?
Are you all right?
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is
so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
"Next week."
Now, next week's Three Colors,
Three Leaves will be...
It's Sasame. Um...
Oh, next time will be these three: "The Cursed Sword,"
"Place of Death," and "Red Spider Lily."
Rock, paper, scissors!
"Next time: You've Got Them Hooked"
"Snicker"