Ahh, man, am I beat.
Being spied on for
hours will do that.
Mr. Fu and Lan Fan
were keeping eyes on him?
[Fu] Hey!
Where's the Young Lord?
He's not here.
I don't know...
Maybe he ran off again.
Good grief. I can't take my
eyes off him for a second.
Young Lord! Where have
you taken off to this time?
What if he's collapsed
somewhere again?
If so, I'd say it's
a relief... Let's go.
Coming!
Master Ling! Where are you?
Something about this
country doesn't feel right.
It's me... I'm Just checking in.
You're doing well...
Here, it's from the colonel.
Hey, it's the smokin' guy!
How's it goin'? You won
a single game yet?
Not even close... But this
game is boring anyway.
Hey, since it's night now,
I can go and cut
someone up, right?!
Of course not.
Ya gotta give me something'!
At least bring that
Hawkeye lady for a visit.
Yeah... I'll let her know
that you're interested.
He's not the only
one who's bored.
How much longer
am I stuck here
keeping watch on
this guy, anyway?
What does the colonel say?
The colonel apologizes
for having to give you
such a dangerous assignment.
He also says don't worry
about your other duties;
your absence is being
treated as sick leave.
But if anyone--
even military personnel outside
of our unit-- sees you,
he'll have you court-martialed
before you can blink...
That is all.
I don't suppose
you have any news
of a happier sort to report?
Indeed.
Oh? What is it?
Falman, I found
myself a girlfriend!
She's been really sweet,
helping me adjust to the
move here and everything.
And oh, boy is she hot!
Hey, do you think this new
girl would be fun to cut up?
Come on, what d'ya say?
Can I cut her?
Just a little, I promise.
Please, just get out of here.
Hey... are you okay?
F- food...
Collapsed by the side
of the road, huh?
Where did you come from?
What's that?
From Xing, you say?
Well, you're a long way
from home, all right.
I'll need to see your
entry visa, please.
Outta the way, everyone!
Illegal alien coming through!
Young Master!
Where are you?!
He's in trouble again!
He's collapsed, I'm sure of it!
Okay... Guess we should stop
by the military offices first.
Right.
In that case,
I think I'll head straight
to the Hughes' house
and let them know
I'm in town...
I can't wait to see Miss
Gracia and cute little Elicia!
Sounds good. We shouldn't
be all that far behind you.
'Kay, see ya later.
I wonder if Lt. Colonel Hughes
has put together
any more information
on the Philosopher's
Stone since we left.
The Fuhrer was pretty clear
with his orders regarding that.
I think it's best
if we give Hughes
the information
that we found out first.
The Homonculi.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure Hughes said
he was in the
court-martial office.
This way.
[Female Officer] Sheska? Sheska!
Yes?
You have the key for room
number three, don't you?
Yes! Oh, wait! You said
room number three, right?
It's still a total mess from
when I was using it earlier!
It's fine...
I just need it to gather
some documents, that's all.
No, really, please don't!
If you can just wait a moment,
I'll clean it right up for you!
Okay then... I can come
back later for the keys.
Please make sure
it's taken care of.
Yes, ma'am!
[Sheska] Um...
excuse me... Colonel?
Colonel Mustang?
Oh, hello Sheska...
How long was I asleep?
About ten minutes, I think.
The council meeting's
about to start.
Uh, Colonel... perhaps this is
none of my business, but...
but maybe you should try
to get a little more rest.
Mm-hmm, I'll be back.
Was that Colonel
Mustang that just left?
Oh! Captain Focker, sir!
Good morning!
Nice day, isn't it?
Good morning to you, Sheska...
Tell me... What was he
doing here? The colonel.
Ah... well... you see...
The storeroom door is open.
I'm sorry! I opened it, sir!
I'll bet the colonel twisted
your arm, didn't he?
Don't worry,
I won't tell anyone.
I really appreciate that, sir!
Although... I do wonder what
the colonel was looking into...
Do you know?
I'm not one hundred
percent certain
of all of the details, sir...
He did ask if there
were any materials
having to do with
the Fifth Laboratory...
And also... he was looking
into the Hughes case.
You know I... I got my job
here through General Hughes.
Ah, yes... I remember.
Well, I've got
tons of work to do.
Carry on, Sheska.
Yes, sir.
Good morning, Sheska.
Sir?
What the--?
Hello, sir.
Hey.
Colonel... you look like
you've lost some weight.
Maybe...
But what happened to you?
There was an... incident...
down in the south.
But, don't you worry,
it's just a scratch.
I see.
I ran into the Elric
brothers down there.
Apparently they'd gone to
Dublith to pay a visit...
an old teacher.
Major...
Sir?
Did you tell them
about Hughes' death?
No... I couldn't
bring myself to do it.
They'll find out,
eventually you know.
Yes, I know.
The Fifth Laboratory and
the Philosopher's Stone--
the Stone's key ingredients
are live humans.
Hughes always did enjoy
helping other people...
This time he stuck his nose
into the Elric brothers'
investigation...
and found out something
he would've been
better off not knowing.
Am I wrong?
If the Elric brothers found out
what really happened to him...
that he died trying
to help them...
they would blame themselves...
So, your not telling
them... was kind.
You've got it all
figured out, don't you?
I'm almost there.
Be careful, sir.
You never know who might be
listening in on you... Or where.
If you'll excuse me...
[Ed] Huh? Lieutenant Hawkeye?
Hey, guys. It's been awhile.
If the Lieutenant's here,
that means so is...
[Colonel Mustang]
Thanks for waiting.
Yep. The Colonel.
Well hello, Fullmetal.
Colonel Mustang, what are
you doing here in Central?
You didn't hear?
I was transferred
to this branch last month.
Great.
And you guys?
What brings you here?
We're just doing a little
information gathering...
And we were thinking
that we'd pay
Lieutenant Colonel Hughes
a visit a little later today.
Where is he, anyway?
Not here.
Huh?
He retired, out in
the country...
and took his wife
and daughter with him...
to take over the
family business.
So, he's not here.
I see... well, that's too bad.
We were hoping to see him.
Fullmetal...
Watch yourself...
Don't do anything crazy.
Okay...
Now you've decided to
treat them like children?
There's no need for them
to know just yet...
The fewer obstacles that stand
in their way right now...
the better.
Colonel... They are
gonna find out someday.
It's funny... I've accused
Armstrong of being soft...
But right now I'm
no better than he is.
I fail to see anything
"soft" about it.
It's cruel, Colonel.
I can't believe Hughes
is actually gone.
Oh! I almost
forgot, Brother...
We need to tell Winry
about all this...
She went straight
to the Hughes house.
Yeah, you're right.
Lieutenant Ross!
I haven't seen you
two here in awhile...
You're in a hurry.
Why the rush?
We just heard about
Lieutenant Colonel Hughes...
Yeah... It's rough news, huh?
There was still so much that
we wanted to tell him about.
We would have liked
to say goodbye.
We weren't able to reach you.
Don't worry though...
The military gave him
a proper send-off.
Wow, that was nice.
That's how it's done.
Also... If you boys
haven't heard already...
I'm sure you'll both
be glad to know...
he was promoted...
two whole ranks.
Up to Brigadier General?
He retired to the country
and they promoted him?
Lieutenant Ross?
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
And here you are, miss.
Thank you!
No! Not the Lieutenant
Colonel! Why him?!
Brother!
[Lt. Ross] Brigadier
General Hughes is dead...
He was murdered
shortly after you were
discharged from the
hospital, Edward...
I'm afraid we still haven't
found the person responsible.
It's all my fault...
I'm the one who
pulled him into this!
It's all my fault!!
[Hughes] Okay, you boys
have a safe trip...
Stop in and give me a shout
the next time you
make it to Central.
Al, how're you gonna
eat wearing that armor?
Take it off, relax!
Elrics... I understand that you
two don't have a place to stay,
which means you'll
have to come with me.
Daddy!?
What do we do?
We tell it like it is.
You go on back...
I'm the only one who has to take
the blame for what happened.
Brother...
this isn't just your problem...
It's both of ours.
Like it or not,
I'm going in with you.
Thanks, Al... but you
really don't have t--
We made up our minds...
We said we were getting our
bodies back, no matter what.
But if people are going
to die because of that...
then I don't want mine back.
Winry's already here.
Right.
Winry...
Um, Miss Gracia...
I'm sorry, but there's something
I need to talk to you about...
If I may.
About Maes?
That's right...
You too, Winry.
[Miss Gracia] So Maes learned
things about the Philosopher's
Stone that someone
didn't want him to know.
His death was a message...
A warning to you
from whoever did it...
to back off from all this.
Yeah, we basically
dragged him into it...
I'm sorry!
So sorry.
That would be just like him...
dying while trying to
help somebody else.
My husband. He always was
a busybody and a meddler,
and it got him into
trouble. A lot.
But you know... I don't
think he ever had regrets.
Not any... not even in his
dying moments, Edward.
But we...
Don't tell me you're
going to give up.
You can't let what
happened defeat you...
If you do, then that means
my husband died in vain.
Even if the Philosopher's
Stone is a dead end...
There might be some other way.
Maybe, I guess.
You boys have to keep moving
forward... any way you can.
[Elicia] Mommy...
Mommy, please don't cry.
Winry... you in there?
You haven't eaten
yet, have you?
You might want to hurry...
The dining room is closing soon.
You know you have to eat...
to keep up your strength.
Okay... I'll go back to my room.
[Ed] Apple pie?
That's right. I've practiced
making it a few times.
I know it might... sound
like... I'm bragging...
but I've gotten
pretty good at it.
I'm not nearly as good
as Miss Gracia, but someday...
I'd hoped...
That Mr. Hughes...
would get to try some too!
[Lust] So the nosy
Colonel Mustang
is snooping around
the Hughes matter?
Mm-hmm.
Do you think he
discovered anything yet?
It's a definite possibility.
So what now?
We already moved him to Central
where we'd be able to
keep a closer eye on him.
Why can't he be a good boy
and behave himself?
I'd hate to waste an
important sacrifice candidate.
Haven't been able
to learn anything
from your new boyfriend?
[Lust] Nothing.
He's either a born idiot
or a clueless hustler.
I'm off to gather some
more intelligence.
Let's go, Gluttony.
Come on, Gluttony! Don't leave
your mess lying around.
You slob.
What you said before...
about how much
nicer it would be
if the Flame Colonel
would behave himself...
Yes?
How would you feel about
us making another play?
You have something in mind?
Well, we've got a noisy mutt...
Perhaps all he needs
is a nice bone to chew on.
Second Lieutenant Maria Ross...
I'm Henry Douglas, from
the Provost Marshal's office.
Do you need me for something?
You'll have to come along
with us... Your gun?
May I ask what this is about?
You've been named
as the primary suspect
in the Brigadier General Hughes
murder case. Please come along.
That's absurd!
You can tell your side
of it later... Now let's go.
Second Lieutenant Maria Ross...
Pleading not guilty
on all charges.
Gather whatever information
you can about her...
Go now. Quickly...
but secretly.
Right.
S'cuse me, ma'am. I'd like
a bouquet of these, please.
My, my, what's this?
A hot date, lover boy?
You been waiting long, Solaris?
Oh, no... I just got here.
It's so good to
see you, Jean...
Why don't you sit down
and tell me all about your day?
[Narrator] The sacrificial lamb
is made ready to be offered
to the waiting flames...
and a young man is wracked with
animosity and deep regret.
And then... he reaches
his hand into the darkness.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 17: "Cold Flame."
All is set in motion,
tossed about by hands
unseen and unknown.