Huh? Where am I?
Class A Stream River
River Styx
(                    )
Underworld
Unde
rwor
ld
(                    )
Class A Stream River
River Styx
(                    )
Underworld
Unde
rwor
ld
(                    )
Those who are still alive
Useless People
Class A Stream River
River Styx
(                    )
Underworld
Don't tell me that this is the River Styx...
Come. Come here...
It's really nice over here... full of wonderful things.
There's nothing to be afraid of, Akihisa. This place is great.
Yuuji, why are you over there?
Don't chicken out, Akihisa! As you can see, I'm doing just fine.
Don't worry about anything...
just come over here...
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
Question 2
『 Me and Yukata and Fun Festival! 』
This is...
I don't really remember it very clearly,
but I feel like I've been to hell and back...
I thought that you two were goners once you started mumbling in your sleep...
We're alive... somehow.
Akihisa and Yuuji took up the challenge of hitting on some girls...
They were caught in the act and punished for it.
They seriously did a number on you two.
I can't believe some of the things that they did!
But I'm not really that surprised.
Yeah. I mean, we did something pretty stupid, after all.
It's not very cool to go around picking up other girls when you're already with a couple of them.
Well, we got off pretty easy in that case, huh?
I wouldn't call having a near-death experience "getting off easy"...
I just can't believe that this'll be the end of it.
They've probably something else in store for us.
What should we do, Yuuji? Run away?
What do you mean "run away"?
Oh, everyone's changed into yukatas.
Yeah, there's a festival going on.
What do you think, Akihisa-kun?
Um... yeah, it really suits you.
This is my first time wearing a yukata.
Oh yeah! Minami-chan is from overseas, right?
Wh-What is it, Aki?
Eh? Nothing.
You were just checking out Minami-chan, weren't you?
Her yukata's cute, isn't it?
What did you say?
You barely notice how small her chest is when she's wearing a yukata, right?
I don't know what you mean...
Well, if you really don't get it, then I'll show you. Take a look at this...
*Flash*
See, the reaction time is way quicker than usual.
What happened? Hold on, Muttsurini!
But somehow, this isn't all that bad...
Yuuji.
How do you like my yukata?
Well, it isn't bad, I guess...
Well then, would you like to... marry me?
Not really.
Well then, how about being engaged to me?
Not even a little bit.
So, Yuuji...
How about no?
Do you wanna live?
Shouko, you look really, really cute!
Yuuji, you really should be more honest with yourself about your feelings.
You just threatened me into saying that...
It's like my mom always said... when it comes to love, the end justifies the means.
What's wrong with them?
I thought that they were all angry...
Okay, everyone! The festival's about to start.
Yeah, Akira-san.
We don't want to be late!
This is only the second Japanese festival that I've been to, so I'm really excited about it!
It'll be bad if we're late.
Let's hurry up and go!
Um... okay...
Okonomiyaki
Wow, it's so lively!
It looks really fun!
Oh, they've got doner kebabs?!
They sure look delicious, huh?
They sure do! Let's try some!
What?
So please go and buy some to make up for earlier, Aki-kun.
I shouldn't have said anything...
Summer
Festival
Do you want some, Aki-kun? I'll buy it for you...
Yes, thank you very-
Summer
Festival
What?
Summer
Festival
You'll buy it for me, Sis?
Summer
Festival
Is something wrong with that?
No, it's nothing.
Why?
I don't think that she can have already forgiven me....
Doner Kebab
So, how about you share it with me?
There are lots of things here that I'd like to try.
Okay... you can go ahead and try it first.
Really? Okay, then.
Well, it doesn't seem like they make it with lamb here in Japan...
Here, try some, Aki-kun.
Mmm, yummy!
Um, Aki-kun...
You've got a little sauce on your lips.
Th-Thank you, Sis.
Akihisa-kun...
I bought some takoyaki... would you like to share it with me?
Thanks, Himeji-san. I'd love one!
There you go.
What's wrong, Akihisa-kun?
Nah, it's nothing.
Well then... open wide!
It's so hot and sticky... and the octopus feels so good inside-
It's not what you think, Sis! There isn't anything improper going on here!
Impurity
What's wrong, Aki-kun?
Huh?
Didn't you like it?
Eh?
Are you acting like an idiot again, Aki?
Getting so worked up because of a festival... you really are childish.
Well, what about you, Minami-san? You're pretty excited about it, too.
Th-These were given to me as gifts, so...
Minami-chan was in Germany for such a long time that it really can't be helped.
That's right.
Wanna try some cotton candy? It's really good.
Eh?
Okay, then...
Okay... open up!
Isn't it delicious?
Yep, it's delicious.
Good, I'm glad.
Yuuji, would you like some yakisoba?
Um, yes... I'll have some.
Some okonoyaki, too?
It's like you're reading my mind...
Also Ramune.
Th-Thank you.
That's good... seems like Yuuji's been forgiven as well.
It's a festival, after all! Everyone wants to forget about their anger and have a good time!
Hey Akihisa.
I just saw a bunch of different-colored chickens over there! I thought that they were extinct!
Well, those are just painted...
What? You mean that they weren't real?
Of course they weren't! Isn't that right, Muttsurini-kun?
Chicks
Painted
Let me stain you with my colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
Let
. me
.     stain
.     you
.       with
.     my
.        colors!
That's just common sense.
Aki-kun, are you having fun?
Yes.
Yuuji, having fun?
Ye-Yeah.
Oh, Akihisa-kun, this looks like it's going to be an interesting event!
The First Miss Yukata on the Beach Contest.
A beauty pageant?
That is interesting.
A chance to take pictures...
Why don't we all go?
Yeah, maybe everyone can enter...
The 1st
Miss
Yukata
on the
Beach
Contest
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
The 1st
Miss
Yukata
on the
Beach
Contest
The 1st
Miss
Yukata
on the
Beach
Contest
The 1st
Miss
Yukata
on the
Beach
Contest
The 1st
Miss
Yukata
on the
Beach
Contest
The 1st
Miss
Yukata
on the
Beach
Contest
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
The 1st
Miss
Yukata
on the
Beach
Contest
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
Oh no, I'm not trying to force you or anything!
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
The best
in town!!
Come see
the
summer's
most
beautiful
girls!!
I just thought that we could make some fun summer memories.
Sounds good.
Eh? Really?
Yeah, let's all participate.
It'll definitely be memorable...
Yes, we'll participate...
All of us.
「 Everyone here 」
Run!!!
Where do you think you're going, Aki?
We're going to enter it. All of us.
What are you saying? I don't understand at all.
I don't get it either!
You were hitting on those girls...
Don't tell me that you've forgotten...
You didn't think that we'd forgive you that easily, did you?
Don't worry, I brought my make-up kit!
What?
Wait a minute! With my figure, there's no way that I can cross-dress! Just make Akihisa do it!
Stop trying to save yourself, you traitor!!!!!
Just give it up, already.
You two should just man-up and take it like Tsuchiya.
It's so, so cruel, Hideyoshi.
Sorry, I couldn't go about it half-heartedly.
The make-up is all part of the performance.
Yoshii Akiko
Why did we let it go this far?
Tsuchiya Koumi
It's so humiliating...
Tsuchiya Koumi? Yikes.
Huang Shun Li
Muttsurini, at least you've better off than me...
I'm a cross-dressing foreigner!
If Yuuji were a foreign athlete, it'd explain his physique...
Well, don't the three of you look pretty?
Yeah, you look really cute.
Aki-kun, I'm really happy that you grew up to be so pretty.
That's really not something that you should be saying to your younger brother.
Yuuji, you're not sexy enough.
Don't complaint about it!
By the way, why do I have to participate?
That goes without saying...
【Question 2】
Translate the following into Japanese:
『Although John tried to take the airplane
for Japan with his wife's handmade lunch,
he noticed that he forgot the passport on
the way.』
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
『Although John tried to take the
airplane for Japan with his wife's
handmade lunch, he noticed that he
forgot the passport on the way.』
Teacher's comment:
Correct.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
『John-』
Teacher's comment:
is John.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
『John boarded a flight to Japan
with a handmade passport.』
Teacher's comment:
Baka to Test!
Please think again what
"handmade passport" really means.
And now, The First Miss Yukata on the Beach Contest will begin!
The 1st Miss Yukata on the Beach Contest
First of all, let's say hello to tonight's judge, Yuugata Obata-san.
M.C
Obata
I'm really looking forward to seeing all of these beauties in their yukatas.
Yoshii Akiko
Please, do your best out there.
Don't worry, they won't figure it out.
Yuuji, believe in yourself and you'll win.
Are you serious?!
I'll be sure to record every moment of cuteness.
Damn it.
What should we do, Yuuji?
We can just hurry up and lose...
Yeah, if they find out that we're guy-
That won't work.
There's a chance that someone from our school is in the crowd.
If someone were to see us not only cross-dressing...
but also being bold enough to enter a beauty pageant...
We'd never be able to show our faces again.
It'll ruin my reputation if that happens!
It wasn't that great to begin with.
Listen up, the only way out of this is to lose as quickly as we can without being found out.
This is a battle for our manhood!
Thank you for your help.
Volume 1 - End
Everyone, please cheer for us
New        Series
The Beginning of Volume 2!
So then, would the first contestant please come on stage?
The 1st Miss Yukata on the Beach Contest
Inner Thoughts
Now... What should I do?
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
So... now what?
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Pageant
Points
Inner Thoughts
Well then, please tell us your name.
Don't ruin it,
answer with a feminine voice.
I'll just hide my face and answer with a feminine voice.
Yes. I'm Yoshii Akiko.
Oh, Akiko-san, you're quite the shy person, aren't you?
Her look is so cute and put together... she'll score a lot of points.
Why?
Why!?
Do you have a special talent?
If I come up with a lie and they question me about it, the jig will be up.
If I come up with a lie and
they question me about it,
the jig will be up.
If I come up with a lie and
they question me about it,
the jig will be up.
Well, I guess it would have to be cooking things... like paella or carbonara.
If I mix in some of the truth,
it will sound more believable,
right?
If I mix in some of the truth,
it will sound more believable,
right?
Do you cook at home?
Yes, almost every day.
Leaving the cooking to my
sister is out of question.
That's pretty rare for girls these days. Do you have a boyfriend?
I am a guy for Christ's sake.
No, I don't have one!
I don't have one!
The 1st Miss Yukata on the Beach Contest
Be my
girlfriend
That's good news for all the guys in the audience.
Is there anything else, Judge Obata-san?
This old man will give you some spending money in exchange for your phone number.
If you weren't the sponsor, I'd smack you for that.
So, Akiko-san, what was your biggest concern when putting on your yukata this evening?
I wanted it to show as little skin as possible.
I am a guy for Christ's sake.
Pageant
Points
If I don't want to be
found out, that is.
I see. Obata-san, do you have any questions for Akiko-san?
I just want to know whether or not she's wearing panties!!!
Panties? Girls' panties...?
Of course I'm not wearing them!
Pageant
Points
M.C
Obata
Thank you for answering such an impolite question.
Nice going out there!
Damn you!
Inner Thoughts
My strategy will be
to give crappy answers,
so that I keep my points low.
My strategy will be
to give crappy answers,
so that I keep my points low.
Please start with your name.
Name, Tsuchiya Koumi.
Did you go to the beach today?
Yes.
Inner Thoughts
Do you always wear a yukata like that?
M.C
Obata
No.
M.C
Obata
Did your friends come here with you today?
Yes.
M.C
Obata
Are they in the crowd?
No.
M.C
Obata
Well then... other than a yukata, what kinds of clothes do you like?
Pageant
Points
Chinese dresses, kimonos, racer girl outfits, cheerleaders', nurses',
stewardess', waitress', and policewomen's uniforms, leotards,
office ladies' suits, sailor suits, blazers, shrine maidens' uniforms, maid outfits,
tennis sportswear... nothing, really.
What a shocking revelation...
You seem so cool on the outside, but you're quite the cosplayer!
Pl-Please forget about it!
Koumi! Koumi! Koumi! Koumi!
The 1st Miss Yukata on the Beach Contest
Koumi
Th-This is a problem...
With such a grand reaction from the crowd, she's sure to make it into the finals.
Um... this is really embarrassing...
The 1st Miss Yukata on the Beach Contest
Nice encore.
What just happened?
I'm Huang Shun Li. Nice to meet you.
Inner Thoughts
Hehe, with my physique, I'll
definitely be rejected by
the crowd. I'll be the only
one cut in the first round.
Don't hold it against me, guys.
Hehe, with my physique, I'll
definitely be rejected by
the crowd. I'll be the only
one cut in the first round.
Don't hold it against me, guys.
Inner Thoughts
Well, she sure is one tall drink of water...
What do you think, Obata-san?
This is amazing... I love tall girls!
What?!
What!
The judge has given very high praise to this contestant.
Inner Thoughts
Do you have another-
How about we spend our honeymoon in Cambodia?
My being foreign could cause trouble for us.
As long as we have love, we'll be fine, my honey.
I'm not your honey!
You'll learn to love me.
I seriously hate you!
I don't mind if we have to start out as friends! We'll be together forever!
Leave me alone, you senile old man!
If it's with you, I'll take whatever I can get!
I will not let you have an affair.
Shouko!
Why?
I'm scarred for life.
A whole lot of things have happened this summer that I'd rather forget.
I'll never get married now...
It's a good thing that the contest got canceled...
The 1st Miss Yukata on the Beach Contest
Not so great for the contestants, though.
Maybe we overdid it a little.
Should we just let it go?
Considering everything that we put them through...
They seem sorry for what they did...
So let's forgive them.
If the show had gone on, who do you think would've won?
Well, it'd obviously be Hideyoshi, right?
Having a man win the contest isn't exactly reassuring...
I got pretty turned on by Muttsurini in drag... what about you, Akira-san?
Well, I'm pretty used to seeing Aki-kun cross-dress, so it was nice to see the others do it as well.
Wait a minute, Sis.
I don't make a habit of cross-dressing!
What are you saying, Aki-kun?
Didn't you sleep in a skirt last night?
Wait a minute! What have you been doing to me in my sleep?!
Don't worry, I was lying about half of it.
Lie
Lying? How can something like this be only partially true?
L
ie
I only put it on up to your knees.
You made me wear it only halfway on?!
No, to be more precise, I made you wear it halfway off.
Halfway Off
Come on everybody, the meat's ready!
Let's eat!
It's really delicious.
Sakamoto is really good at this sort of thing, huh?
My future husband.
I wanted to help out with the cooking too.
But Akihisa-kun wouldn't let me anywhere near the kitchen knives.
That's not it, Himeji-san.
The problem is what you're capable of doing to people without even picking up a knife.
Her food will kill ya.
Lethal, indeed.
We could never allow her to make something so dangerous.
So... how about we girls have a cooking contest sometime, and you guys can be the judges?
Don't do it...
But how would we decide on the contest's winner and loser?
By knockout or technical knockout, I'd say.
Wow, I'm stuffed...
I'm still kinda hungry.
But we don't have any food left.
Well, in that case we'll just have to catch something.
Catch something?
We're at the seashore! Fresh clams on the grill would be awesome!
That's true!
Now that you mention it...
I made a madeleine cake back at home...
Let's go catch those clams, Yuuji!
Yeah, Akihisa! Let's catch enough to last us the whole night!
The sea is so inviting at night, isn't it, Muttsurini?
I love clams!!
What's wrong with them?
God knows...
So where is this madeleine cake?
Well I made it, but I forgot about it and left it on the table at home.
That's a shame.
I'm too young to die!
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) den (Po!) kyuu (Pa!) pikkanko (Hai)
閃いて (Pa!) 輝いて (Pi!) 電 (Po!) 球 (Pa!) ぴっかんこ （はいっ）
Flashing (Pa!) Sparkling (Pi!) light (Po!) bulb (Pa!) That's right (Yes)
shinten shinaiyo
進展しないよ
I can't move ahead,
dare ka jyama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
because someone is hindering me... No, no!
zenzen tarinai sorega mondai no koubaisuu
ぜんぜん足りない　それが問題の公倍数
Nothing that I do is enough, which is an all too common problem.
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I will come to understand it.
naniga hontou no koto... Baby?
何が本当のこと... Baby?
What is the truth of it... Baby?
mitetara kokode zukai shite yo Baby!
見てたらここで図解してよBaby！
If we were to see each other, I would draw you a schematic of it, baby!
kotobamo kazumo kimi wo arasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
I wouldn't show you words or numbers.
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to (kyuuu Paaaaaan!) N no jiryoku de
心がビリビリする  S と（きゅーっ　Paaaaaan!） N の磁力で
Our hearts are flittering about from the
magnetic force of the North and South Poles.
S, S, Super kuttsuite Number I say No.1 boy!
(S, S, Super くっついて Number I say No.1 boy!)
S, S, Super numbers close together. I say No.1 boy!
omedetou!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ima kara kimi wa my, ma, my otakara
いまから君は My, ma, my ゛お-た-か-ら゛
From now on, you're my, my, my "treasure."
tokubetsu nanda dounattemo
特別なんだどうなっても
Just for you, no matter what happens,
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I will hold you tightly, tightly and never let go.
watashi wa koishitai yume ni kenkai wa iranai
私は恋したい　夢に限界はいらない
I want to be in love, and dreams have no need for boundaries, so...
tokubetsu dayone acchattamon
特別だよね　会っちゃったもん
just for me, since we met here by chance...
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
you will forgive me, won't you?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) sei (Po!) kai (Pa!) pittanko (gyuu)
閃いた (Pa!)　輝いた (Pi!) 正　(Po!)　解　(Pa!)　ぴったんこ（ぎゅっ）
It flashed (Pa!) It sparkled (Po!) right (Po!) answer (Pa!) That's right (Embrace)
Geez, they're fast asleep, just like little kids.
Men will always be children at heart.
Look at their innocent little sleeping faces...
Cute, isn't it?
They must be worn out from running around like that.
I'm glad that they had so much fun.
I can't believe that they fell asleep so quickly.
They were staggering before they even got into the car.
Eating as much as they did for breakfast must have made them sleepy.
They must have been starving!
I know, they didn't even leave anything for us!
It's really a shame, Mizuki-san.
Yeah...
I didn't even get a chance to ask them if they liked the breakfast that I made.
Those who are still alive
Useless People
Class A Stream River
River Styx
(                    )
Underworld
Come here...
It's really nice over here...
【Question 3】
Answer the following
question.
Give examples of things
that should not be brought
to school.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
『Manga, videogames and
similar objects.』
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Well done, Himeji.
School is a place of learning, not just
lexical studies but the correct social
stance as well. It's not enough to
attend classes. One must also be able to live with regulations.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
Teacher's comment:
Next Episode
Question #3...
Give examples of things that should not be brought to school.
『Can you bring a banana as a snack?』
Can you bring a banana as a snack?
Should I say "That's bananas"?
Next episode!
Me and That Girl and A Doll!
"Me and That Girl and A Doll!"
This will be on your test.