I see the same scene every time I close my eyes.
Wait up, Yuu!
Jeez, don't you think it's a bit mean to leave your family behind?
I don't have a family, moron.
Yeah, yeah.
Everyone from the Hyakuya Orphanage is family, remember?
No two ways about it!
Hey, get off!
We're family, right?
Right, Yuu?
Of course we are.
Don't you think so, Yuu?
Man, there's just no arguing with you guys.
I see the smiling faces of my friends, my comrades, my precious family,
and then...
I see their lives claimed by a vampire.
R-Run, Yuu.
Hurry up and... go...
Yuu...
M...
Mika!
To this day, even after four years and counting,
the same scene still haunts me.
Shit, it's a Horseman of the Apocalypse!
Private Hyakuya!
What are you doing here?
You need to leave right away!
What? Leave?
Who do you think you're talking to?
I live only for revenge against those blood-sucking bastards.
If I can't even handle this trash...
what use am I going to be?!
That damned kid!
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
Humanity
after the Fall
This is just stupid.
What's the point in suspending me for violating orders when I dealt with the problem anyway?
Besides, a soldier like me at an ordinary school?
How's that supposed to work?
Hey, Hyakuya Yuuichirou!
What are you mumbling about?
Pay attention!
What's with the attitude?
Keep that up and you'll earn yourself a suspension.
What? You'll suspend me?
For real?!
All right, give it to me!
Quit messing around!
Do you take me for a fool?!
Hey, sit down!
What do you want?
Actually, do I even know you?
I'm Hiiragi Shinoa,
an army surveillance officer.
If you seem unwilling to cooperate, I will report you
to the army, and they will extend your suspension.
I'm Hiiragi Shinoa,
an army surveillance officer.
If you seem unwilling to cooperate, I will report you
to the army, and they will extend your suspension.
I'm Hiiragi Shinoa,
an army surveillance officer.
If you seem unwilling to cooperate, I will report you
to the army, and they will extend your suspension.
to the army and they will extend your suspension.
I'm Hiiragi Shinoa,
an army surveillance officer.
If you seem unwilling to cooperate, I will report you
to the army, and they will extend your suspension.
I'm Hiiragi Shinoa,
an army surveillance officer.
If you seem unwilling to cooperate, I will report you
to the army, and they will extend your suspension.
I'm Hiiragi Shinoa,
an army surveillance officer.
If you seem unwilling to cooperate, I will report you
to the army, and they will extend your suspension.
"If you seem unwilling to cooperate,
I will report you to the army,
and they will extend your suspension."
What?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Hyakuya!
If you keep disrupting my class—
Damn it!
"Damn it"?!
I'm Hiiragi Shinoa,
an army surveillance officer.
If you seem unwilling to cooperate, I will report you
to the army, and they will extend your suspension.
Cooperate.
Let's move on.
By the way, your suspension won't be lifted until you make at least one friend.
Uh... what?
Good luck. I'm sure you can make one.
What's going on?!
I thought the human race had been wiped out!
Wiped out, were we?
Is that what the vampires told you?
Well, it's true that the virus shrunk our population to a mere tenth of what it was,
and thanks to the Trumpets of the Apocalypse,
strange monsters started roaming around the earth.
But the human race isn't that weak.
The resurrection of mankind has already begun.
Resurrection?
Naturally, we intend for our organization to prevail against all the rest.
We will gather the remnants of humankind and seize control of the entire planet.
Who are you?
My name is Ichinose Guren, lieutenant colonel of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
If you come with me, you can kill those vampires.
Put this on him.
You despise vampires, do you not?
There's nothing I hate more.
Then join me.
I can give you the power you need.
Or so that idiot said, proceeding to neglect me for the next four years.
What's up with that?
Ugh, club activities...
Hey, let's get some ice cream on our way home!
"Oh, no, wait for me. I love ice cream too."
Why not catch up with them and say that?
What's your deal? Don't get all cozy with me.
Lieutenant Colonel Guren told me
that your family was killed
right before your eyes when you were younger, and so you have trouble approaching others.
You stay away from those who might be close to you in fear of losing them.
So much that you can't even make a friend or girlfriend.
Hey, don't go saying whatever you want about me!
So you can approach others.
Quit spewing nonsense,
and tell that idiot to get off his ass and enlist me into the vampire extermination unit already!
Tell him that I'm strong enough to kill them now.
He told me you'd say that, so he gave me this.
Oh, so he does get it.
"There's no place for friendless and unloved virgins like you in our army.
If you don't like it, try making a friend, and introduce them to me.
But of course, that would be entirely impossible for a guy like you."
Friend this, friend that...
You can both go to hell!
Seriously, what's with you?
Are you gonna follow me around for the entire day?
Aren't you satisfied already?
I'm afraid not.
I've been assigned to be your army surveillance officer.
Any violation of army regulations will be
reported to the Lieutenant Colonel.
P-Please stop.
What? You want me to stop?
I'm just asking you to go buy something for me,
since we're buddies and all!
Lovely.
Well, I'm going home.
If your natural reaction is to turn a blind eye,
you sure won't be making friends anytime soon.
You want to hang out with the cool kids, right?
Then get on your knees and work for it.
Like a dumb farm animal!
Hey, punk, you listenin' to me or what?
I think that's enough.
Who the hell are you?
Oh?
Contrary to intel, you're actually a rather decent human being.
Hey, now.
Who do we have here?
You his knight in shining armor or something?
Or are you gonna be our bitch instead of Yoichi?
Man, you guys sure get straight to the point. I like it.
It kinda makes me happy.
All right, you wanna fight?
How 'bout it?
What?!
Oh, I forgot to mention it earlier,
but beating up civilians will result in an extended suspension.
What?!
Me, someone's bitch...
Why me...
I-I'm sorry. It's all my fault...
Hey, Shinoa.
You gonna give us a hand?
Ha, good one.
You little...
I-I'm sorry...
And you too! Stop apologizing already!
Besides, what's your story?
Why are you letting them bully you?
I-I'm not being bullied...
Yeah, right.
That's what they all say.
It's true! I'm not being bullied.
I-I have a favor to ask Yamanaka,
so I asked him to add me into his circle of friends.
Who's Yamanaka?
Ah, I see. You have the intelligence of a monkey.
He's the one that punched you.
Oh, that guy.
So, what did you want from him?
I, um...
I really want to join the Demon Army, but I failed the entrance exam.
And Yamanaka's been promised a spot in the vampire
extermination unit known as the Moon Demon Company, so...
The Moon Demon Company? That tool?!
Hell, even I couldn't get in!
I'm gonna kick Guren's ass!
S-So I was hoping Yamanaka could put in a good word to get me another shot at the entrance exam.
I know it's weird for a wimp like me
to enlist in the army, but...
But?
I want to avenge my sister.
Avenge?
My sister sacrificed herself in order to protect me.
I wasn't able to save her, and so...
If you went to help her, you'd be dead, dummy.
You did the right thing.
But—
But nothing.
I'm saying this for your own good.
Don't join the army.
It's not what your sister would've wanted.
Little boys like you have no business slaughtering vampires.
Emergency alert!
This is a message for all students and faculty members.
A vampire from the nearby
biological research facility has escaped.
All students...
What's a vampire doing in a place like this?
There's a vampire on the loose in our school?!
Hey, shut up for a second!
A vampire's strength is fueled by human blood.
Please do not approach the vampire under any circumstances.
Please evacuate immediately!
I'll call the Moon Demon Company for—
We don't need them!
I'll kill the vampire!
What?!
I'm going to kill it and show Guren what I'm made of!
H-Hey!
Hyakuya!
That idiot...
That idiot!
Wh-What's a vampire doing here?!
I thought we were safe within the
Demon Army's main base of operations!
Hurry up and move!
Let me through!
Y-You're...
Four years have passed since then.
It's been far too long,
vampire!
I'm gonna shred you to pieces!
Pitiful human...
Yamanaka!
Take the girl and run!
Now!
You're a soldier in all but name, right?!
Hurry up and—
I-It was a lie.
Huh?
I thought everyone would fear me
if I said I'd join the army.
You meddling nuisance...
Know your place, livestock.
If you're going to interfere,
I'll drink your blood first.
Playtime's over.
You can't save anyone.
As soon as I regain my strength with her blood,
you won't stand a chance.
Stop!
Hyakuya!
Yoichi!
You little...
I owe you one, Yoichi.
W-Well, we're friends, after all...
Damn you!
Hyakuya!
A scratch like this isn't going to kill me, but nice try.
I'll drain you nice and slow before the
Moon Demon Company comes, and then,
You rang?
You... A cursed weapon?
Lights out, vampire.
You look incredibly pathetic.
What are you, a fool?
Did you really think you could kill a vampire
without an appropriate spell on your weapon?
M-Mind your own damn business.
I was this close to killing it.
Oh?
It's true!
Is that so?
But I suppose you did well for a little brat.
Thanks to you, we have fewer casualties.
You saved your school friends.
That's...
the Moon Demon Company...
I don't need friends anyway...
Whatever! You saw me!
I can fight against vampires.
Hurry up and accept me
into the Moon Demon Company!
Nope.
Besides, I hate guys who can't get along in a team.
You're the one who has the hardest time getting along.
What was that?
Nothing at all.
Anyway, it's just like I had Shinoa tell you.
If you can't make at least one friend, then—
Enough with friends already!
You don't need them to kill a vampire!
Th-Th-Thank goodness!
Hyakuya, you're okay!
I thought you'd died!
And this is?
His friend, by the looks of it.
Hey, Hyakuya.
Oh, no!
S-Someone call the ambulance!
Now you have to keep your promise,
Lieutenant Colonel.
What?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
I see the same scene every time I close my eyes.
I see the smiling faces of my friends, my comrades, my precious family,
and then...
Whew, I'm glad you were able to make a friend.
Why are you guys...
Now we can stop worrying about you.
You're far too kind for a life of vengeance, Yuu.
So...
You need to take good care of your new friend.
Well, it's time for us to go now.
H-Hey!
Wh-What do you mean?
Mika! Don't go that way!
H-Hold on!
Mika!
Hyakuya!
Thank goodness.
Shinoa, Hyakuya's awake!
Oh, he is?
As of today, you are a member of the vampire extermination unit.
Good for you, Hyakuya!
Oh, your enlistment has been
accepted as well, Saotome Yoichi.
They admired how you two placed your lives on the line in order to protect your friends.
Looks like we've become those "comrades" that you hate so much.
Welcome to the Moon Demon Company.
Hey, Hyakuya. You too.
This is stupid...
Whatever.
Hope we get along.
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
The Demon
Within
"The Demon Within."