It's the last day of the consecutive holidays today.
How's everyone doing?
I might die of boredom, that's how I am...
That's because this mongrel's completely useless...
It's not my fault that you haven't been able to see Kitamura, you know.
He did say that he'd be busy during Christmas with the student council and club activities, didn't he?
I'm saying that it should have been the dog's job to do something about it.
I bet you couldn't have talked to him anyway, even if you did see him...
Go to hell!
Oh, it's all over me!
What are you doing?
Quick, give me something to wipe it off!
Geez!
It's your fault for making fun of me, isn't it?
It's so noisy...
Oh, did we wake her up?
Here, use this to wipe it off.
So, you two were planning to eat rice omelettes whilst Ya-chan was asleep?
Your share's in the fridge, all wrapped up.
Did you write my name on it?
Did you write "Yasuko" with the ketchup?
I'll write it now, okay? So stop crying.
Sniff... okay...
I'm gonna sleep a little longer.
Ah, it's gonna leave a stain...
It'll come off if you do it right.
I'll do it for you, so in exchange...
Jonny's again?
There's no problem, right? Pretty please?
I can't go by myself, you know that.
Summer colours, simple and glamorous
Level up code for wearing clothes around
Summer accessories review
June volume, on sale tomorrow!
You should help pair me up with Kushieda.
Oh, shut up! Want me to skin you alive?
W-What is it?
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, yet complicated and mysterious
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
onkou tokujitsu ECCENTRIC na anata
You, who's gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PURE PARAATO
A naive preparation
atama no naka wa junjou PURE PAREEDO
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
Kawashima Ami
I can't believe it... Kushieda's off today...
Even that labour-girl takes a day off occasionally, you know.
I think it's a punishment for trying to be happy all by yourself.
Unlike you who have confessed and been confessed to, I still...
My eyes!
Stop saying embarrassing things, you dog-in-heat.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, this is so cute!
Huh?
Which one is it?
I think it's too long for you...
What I want is the bag. The bag, you understand?!
O-Okay...
Welcome.
I know, I know, I'm just a midget with short legs.
But I haven't troubled anyone with...
What's wron-
Ryuuji, look at this!
The bag, right?
That's not it. I'm talking about the model!
The model?
There, that person.
It's her, right?
You're right.
Her name's Kawashima Ami. She's the daughter of the actress, Kawashima Anna.
What's a girl like that doing in here?
Sorry for making you wait, Ami.
What the?!
K-k-k-k-kita-mu?!
Hey! If it isn't Takasu and Aisaka.
What a coincidence!
W-Why?!
Hey, come over here!
Even if you tell me that...
What's going on here? I see that you two are friendly as usual.
I-It's not like that!
What's the matter, Yuusaku?
Well, I was about to introduce them to you.
Yuusaku?
Her name is Kawashima Ami. She was my neighbour back when we were kids.
I guess she's what you'd call a childhood friend.
And they're Takasu Ryuuji and Aisaka Taiga.
Childhood... friend...
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too!
That is...
Ah, this? We were having a look at it just now. Then...
Oh, and here I am looking plain and dull. I should of dressed up a bit...
I don't think about it much on a day off.
It's okay, you don't have to worry about anything.
We're all here now. Why don't we share the seats?
No problem with that right, Ami?
Of course!
This place is so nostalgic.
We used to come here a lot.
That's right, together with our families.
Here, Takasu-kun.
Huh? Oh...
Would it be better if it was diet sugar?
N-No...
I mean, do you prefer to drink it black?
Hey, don't be so hasty about it.
Forgive me, I saw Yuusaku putting some in, so I...
N-No problem...
Oh, I did it again.
Everyone tells me that I'm a natural airhead and might as well be blonde.
Sorry.
N-No, really. I like sweet things anyway.
Thank you. You're really kind.
Oh my, what have I done...
Sorry...
Takasu-kun doesn't have anything to be sorry for.
Well, I'm going to the bathroom.
Um, I'm going to the bathroom too...
I give up, I can't keep things going over there...
So you came, just as I'd expected.
Aren't you going to the bathroom?
What is it?
Tell me honestly. Takasu, what do you think about Ami?
What can I say? How could you ask me that after bringing such a pretty girl without notice?
I was getting confused there.
I accept that she's pretty.
She's a really good girl. She may be a bit of an airhead but... she's kind of innocent.
Well, just have a look.
Oh boy, I'm tired.
Hey you, Ami-chan's iced tea is empty. Get some for me.
Ignoring me, huh?
Come to think of it, you've had that attitude for a while now.
Oh, I know! I'll let your boyfriend bring it for me.
I'll bet he'll do whatever I ask.
Can Ami-chan have him?
Well, I don't really need him though.
He's not my boyfriend.
Oh well. So it doesn't matter either way?
And that's how she really is.
She's spoiled, selfish and rude. She's a typical princess.
I can't imagine anything except that a demon has taken over her.
Well, I suppose that it can't be helped that you can only find men like that
in an empty town like this.
Hey, how tall are you?
I've just noticed, aren't you proportioned a bit strangely?
I can't imagine that they were selling clothes in that size!
I'm impressed that Taiga is just taking those insults...
What...
There was a mosquito on your cheek.
Oh, it was a fly.
Why you...!
Come on, Ami. We're going home now.
Yuusaku!
I get it, okay?
I'm sorry, Aisaka. We'll excuse ourselves now.
Seconds!
There aren't any. You just finished two and a half bowls of rice.
It's all her fault!
Just remembering that ill-natured woman makes me hungry!
It should make you upset, right?
Kitamura was troubled, ya know.
What should I do? What if Kitamura-kun comes to hate me because of what I did?
Well, I don't think that'll happen.
After all, Kitamura knew that...
I hate her, that woman...
Do you even need to cry?
And you, flirting with her like that!
I-I wasn't really...
In the first place, there isn't any sane person who would call themselves an airhead!
Huh?
Well, forget it. I'm never going see her again anyway.
I'll be the mature one and swallow my hatred.
Hey, that's mine!
Shut up!
I'll be studying here from now on. I'm Kawashima Ami.
Please call me Ami.
What, could it be...?
The model in Can Vi?
Oh my, she's so pretty!
An angel has descended upon us!
Thank you, God.
Everyone, be nice to our new friend, okay?
Well, I guess we need to choose your seat then.
Bingo!
I'm so glad that I'm a member of this class!
It's kind of embarrassing, being conspicuous and all...
Why? You look good in it!
Yeah, you've got great style.
Really? But I want to wear a jersey like everyone else!
Ami-chan's really pretty and she does have great style but...
My Minorin radar for pretty girls isn't working on her.
Minorin?
Are you alright, Ami-chan?
Geez, why do I have to stumble on such flat ground?
It's so uncool!
Ami-chan's got a clumsy side, huh?
I guess she's quite an airhead, right?
It's not like that!
But, people sometimes tell me that I'm an airhead...
Just as I thought.
But, it's not really like that.
Okay, okay. We got it, okay?
Geez, I'm telling you, I'm not like that!
That's amazing.
Yeah, she knows how to control her inner feelings.
Why didn't you tell me that she was transferring here?
If I did, she wouldn't have shown her true nature. And that wouldn't have been good.
What do you mean by that?
To tell you the truth, I don't hate Ami's true nature.
So, I just want everyone to find out her true nature.
And then to still like her for who she really is.
Well, that's...
Even if they don't like her after that,
I think she'll be content.
I don't want her to lie anymore.
I'm first!
I didn't know that there was a vending machine over here.
Why...?
Well, you went out right before 4th period was about to start.
I was worried, so I followed you.
No, no! I shouldn't forget how she really is...
It's against the rules to buy drinks at any time other than lunch break.
So, we're partners in crime, huh?
I'll pay for it.
Don't bother.
Take it as an apology for yesterday.
An apology?
I was really surprised. I didn't know that we were going to be in the same school.
And Aisaka-san too.
Yuusaku didn't say a word about this.
Hey, did Aisaka-san tell you anything about yesterday?
About yesterday?
Well, about yesterday... it was all my fault.
I seem to be a bit of an airhead, so I suppose that I irritated Aisaka-san.
I was just talking to her when she suddenly said that I'm impertinent and conceited...
And then...
But, Aisaka-san didn't do anything wrong!
If I were more responsible, that kind of thing wouldn't have happened.
There are times where other girls have hated me.
So, I don't mind at all. I can still go on, that's why.
I see.
So, please don't tell anyone about what happened yesterday.
I...
I understand what you mean, Kawashima.
So, let's go back to class for now.
Thank you! Let's hurry!
The sun was already high when they set forth, and the waysides were by now too crowded to admit the elegant Sanjo procession.
Basically, the sun that was already high here refers to...
Why were you together with Kawashima Ami
before the beginning of the class!?
Taiga
You're asking me why?
Really.
Takasu-kun
Minori
Takasu-kun. Minori is angry!
There's something fishy between you and the transfer student. Are you cheating? Tell me, are you?!
Remember, the moment you throw Taiga away... a punishment will be waiting for you!
Damn it! Why do I have to suffer like this?
It's a completely different matter, but I wanted to ask you what can you say about a person calling herself an airhead?
Yes? Is there any part that you don't understand?
Hm? What happened to you guys?
Hey, Takasu! Haruta's saying that he'll introduce us to a set of three girls from the track and field club.
I'm sure you'll come too, right?
Even if I go, I'll just end up scaring them.
That's not true!
It's just to make up the numbers anyway.
Besides...
Palmtop tiger...
That's how it is.
Tell me, how could this kind of thing of thing happen?
It wasn't intentional!
I stumbled, so it can't be helped!
I'll go get a cloth, you go on home.
Never mind, I'll wait at the classroom.
Ryuu-
Oh well, and why are you here? You're so irritating.
Don't come near me, you brat.
How scary! Just what you expect from someone hated by the teachers!
When I went to the teacher's office a while ago, they were all saying that I was so pretty.
They were worried that I might be bullied by Aisaka.
You're really hated by everyone, aren't you?
Let me enjoy seeing how far you can go with that split personality of yours.
It would be very easy to reveal your true nature.
But that wouldn't be fun, right?
I'll keep an eye on you.
Even if we change classes or if we graduate...
Just like a stalker would.
You're really an irritating midget, aren't you?
Maybe that's why you don't have any friends.
Oh, there was one, wasn't there?
Takasu Ryuuji. He looks like a delinquent but he's crazy for me, you know.
How disgusting! So, you really are alone now, aren't you?
I really pity you. Even that philanthropist, Yuusaku, hates you!
What did you say...?
I told him about everything you did to me at the family restaurant.
I bet he doesn't want to see your face anymore.
It's the end for you, really!
Kawashima?
Come on, out of the way.
Wow, It's Ryuu-chan's pork cutlet!
Geez.
Doesn't she know that a freshly fried one tastes the best?
If you're worried about her, go there and bring her over.
Oh, I look like a fool there!
Taiga, I'm coming in!
So you were here after all.
You could have turned the light on, you know.
Hey, Tai-
What did you come here for?
Why, you say?
Because it's... dinner-time!
T-Taiga?!
Are you alright?
Kitamura-kun... hates me now...
That woman told everything to him...
I... I...
It's okay.
What's okay about it?
Kitamura knows about everything.
About Kawashima's personality, and about what really happened at the family restaurant.
About her lies. All of it.
Really...?
Really. Besides, Kitamura isn't a guy who'd hate someone for that kind of reason.
You should know the best.
Then, why am I so small?
Huh?
Why do I have a weird name?
Well, that's...
What about it!
She does have a height of 165 cm,
and she even has the same name as one of the Sailor Scouts!
Not only that, she's also Kitamura's childhood friend!
Sorry... are you alright?
But really, you were worrying yourself with such trivial matter.
That's because I'm sensitive, unlike you!
You...
Ryuu-chan!
We're having a pork cutlet, but why don't we have any sauce?
Pork cutlet?
And it's made from black pork.
Hey, what about pudding?
Just the sauce!
Huh?
Come on, we're going home. Yasuko's going to be late for her work.
Ryuuji, look here.
Kawashima Ami-chan will be taking leave due to some educational matters.
This is...
That meant that she's having a business holiday, right?
I wonder if there's even any benefit in her taking a holiday, and attending our school.
Huh? That's...
That woman!
It really is Kawashima Ami.
What's with her outfit? And with all those stuff...
They're all sweet snacks.
Is she having a home party or something?
No, you're wrong. That's...
I've seen something interesting.
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru mono to wa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
Unable to be honest, I'm just rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
True Self
Ah, she's really annoying.
If she's gonna be anymore persistent than this...
Ami-chan will crush her!
Shut up, stupid Chihuahua!