Street No. 02
"Sexual Harassment Lawsuits are Majorly Popular"
MARUKO SHOPPING DISTRICT
Oya High School
To make the weekend a Sabbath
during which you can rest your heart,
you must work the remaining six days diligently.
That is not an exception even for God
as written in the book of Genesis.
To make the weekend a
Sabbath during which you
can rest your heart,
you must work the remaining
six days diligently.
Kirk H. Hill
Kirk H. Hill.
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
Kaze wa nandaka suzushige
Doyoubi no yoru wa nigiyaka
Kurai kimochi sae
Suguni harete
Minna uki uki
Uki uki
Downtown e kuridasou
Hollywood
Arashiyama...
You have plenty of areas in which
you don't lose to Tatsuno.
I know.
Oh, no!
My head is trying to recall Mr. Moriaki all on its own!
On top of that, it smells like a memory
that was conveniently warped!
It's a precious Sunday;
don't think about school or teachers!
I am going to concentrate and finish reading this novel.
DETECTIVE VS BOMBER
THE NARA DETECTIVE PURSUES
A MYSTERIOUS SERIAL BOMBER
AFTER RECEIVING A BOMB THREAT TO
DEMOLISH THE BIG BUDDHA STATUE!
NARA BOMBER
By Hiroto Shimabe
Stop right there!
Look closely.
What you are holding is a fish cake stuffed with mustard.
Normally, there is no way one can mistake
such a thing for dynamite...
No one, except for the culprit, which is you!
No!
NARA
For some reason the main character's face
turns into the teacher's face!
Why?
Ow!
Sis! Play with me!
I'm busy!
That's a lie. You were zoning out.
For an adult, zoning out is work, too!
Now, now, Yukiko is a good girl, so...
Let go!
Go play with... Big Brother!
Takeru!
Play with Yukiko, will you?!
Yay!
Why?!
What do you wanna do? You wanna play dolls? Come on!
Here, there's one you can play with two people, right?
It's called something and it goes beep beep, right?
What do you wanna do? You wanna play dolls? Come on!
Yay!
Play that one.
Hey!
What... are you doing...?
I didn't save yet!
Ow ow ow ow!
That hurts!
It's your fault!
Ow!
Mom! It's Big Sister!
Hotori! What are you doing?!
Oh man...
Oh man!
MAID
Cafe
SEASIDE
You two, aren't you off from work today?
Why would you bother to come here?
When I was at home, I got into trouble.
Sanada may come, so I'm here.
Sanada?
Tatsuno is so mature.
Compared to that, Hotori is...
Instead of that, listen to this, Tatsuno...
Recently, when I think about our teacher,
this area seems... kind of fuzzy.
Oh, my. Hotori, too?!
I understand!
When I think of the math test, my stomach starts to hurt.
Oh... no... not the stomach...
I say, it's not calculus, isn't it
more in the realm of forcing logic?
Seven-Eleven?
Note: Calculus (微分積分) in Japanese is pronounced "Bibun-Sekibun"
which (to Hotori's brain) sounds like Seven-Eleven: "Sebun-Erebun"
Calculus!
I can't understand you if you say difficult things.
When I was in elementary school,
I tripped on division of fractions.
Was it okay to flip the top and bottom?
I still get anxious about it...
I'm surprised that you were able to survive until now.
It seems Tatsuno isn't meant for consultation.
Although not noticing that the topic switched
from love to math is just like Hotori, as well.
Seaside
They say kids who can divide fractions smoothly
have the rest of their lives go smoothly as well.
Oh!
I saw that in a movie too!
Even if the logic doesn't agree,
if your personality lets you go along with the story,
your life will go smoothly, right?
There are formulas for life, aren't there?
Now they're talking about life!
Logic aside, there are times when you
do something a certain way, and it's okay.
Even the culprit in a detective anime...
When you can't guess, if you apply the formula
you can figure out who did it.
Really? How do you do it?!
The voice actor with the highest pay
is the role of the culprit.
Argh! I shouldn't have heard that!
Now I'm always gonna know who the culprit is!
Hotori...
If you're free, go to the vegetable market
and buy some potatoes and ball onions.
Why? I'm a customer today, you know?
Then pay for your meal and go home.
Tch. I'll go, so lend me that thing.
The one that goes vroom vroom.
Maruko Shopping District
Yahoo!
Potatoes, ball onions... Potatoes, ball onions...
Note: "Tamanegi" (たまねぎ) literally means "Ball Onion" in Japanese.
The first part of that word, "tama" (たま) "Ball," also has a coarse
slang meaning, as will be demonstrated shortly...
Potatoes...
Oh?
Hey!
Potatoes...!
Bal—
Balls!
Hey!
That was dangerous, you know?
Note: Officer Junsaku's gasps sound like the Lamaze breathing exercises
What is this? Man...
What? You stop a person and then nothing?
Really. When I see dangerous people like that,
I know that it's springtime...
You're the one who's dangerous!
I only hit you lightly!
A woman wouldn't know the gravity of the situation!
It's your fault for stepping out
in front of me all of a sudden.
You are the one at fault!
I told you before not to ride that in the streets, didn't I?!
If you don't stop now, I am going to write up
this crash as an accident with injuries!
Don't ride it on the streets?
Then are you telling me to ride it in my house?
My Mom is going to yell at me!
Wh-why you little...
Is the law on a lower level than Mom?!
Darn minors...
Do you get it? No driver's license!
No license plate!
No headlights! No turn signals!
Because of the above reasons,
it's not legal to ride in the streets!
Just like a hamburger with no patty
or cheese or lettuce or pickles...
A pathetic burger, that's what you are!
Then why don't you just eat the bread?
I can't take it anymore!
Okay, okay, I won't ride it anymore.
What the...? You're submissive today.
Because I'm here already.
More than anything, milk goes well with anpan, poko.
Oh! Are you on an errand for the old hag?
"Old hag"? I'm going to tell on you.
Onions                                              Potatoes          Sweet
Potatoes
We've got good carrots in today! Carrots, carrots!
Carrots from Kochi! We just dug them up!
So fresh there's still soil on them!
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
Hey, be quiet, I'm going to lose track
of what I'm supposed to buy!
Um...
It was something like... an ingredient for curry, I think...
Onions                                              Potatoes          Sweet
Potatoes
Yes, yes, I'm sure it was potatoes and...
Potatoes and...
Onions                                              Potatoes          Sweet
Potatoes
Carrots, please.
Thank you always for your business!
Oh yeah, Hotori-chan...
King
Milk
Take this with you.
Today is the expiration date, but I'm sure you'll drink it all.
Oh! Thank you.
If you drink milk, maybe you'll get a little bigger. Maybe.
Oh, yeah.
What are you saying is going to get bigger?!
Depending on your answer, I'm going to open up
a sexual harassment hearing, you hear?!
Policeman! Stop laughing with him and reprimand him!
Hup!
I wanna go laugh, poko...
PRODUCE   KIKU    PRODUCE                         PRODUCE   KIKU    PRODUCE
Perverted old men...
They better remember this...
Oh, don't ride it. Push it home.
MARUKO SHOPPING DISTRICT
I ask you.
Headlights and license plates, right?
And turn signals and driver's license!
Don't trivialize this! I'll take it away from you!
It's too wild. You couldn't handle it.
Note: Hotori's line here and following are direct quotes from Katsuhiro Otomo's Akira (1988)
Huh?
Let's go, Tetsuo!
There is no Tetsuo! I told you not to ride it!
Really.
Do you think that she'll move far away
to get married someday?
The town'll feel like the lights went out, I'm sure...
Right now it's as if there's a fire, it's so noisy.
I'm back.
Oh.
Sanada, you're really here.
Huh?
Aww. She's already back.
What took you so long?
It's because the police said stuff like he'd arrest me.
What did you do?
Pathetic burger.
King
Milk
Huh?
Thanks for your hard work. Do you want some coffee?
Just give me a cup. I'll drink milk.
What's up with you? Do you want to get bigger?
It's too late to start drinking now.
Because you're almost done with puberty.
Even if you're a bit small,
I don't think you should let it get to you.
It is your uniqueness, after all...
Arashiyama is Arashiyama...
Why you...!
Every last one of you! No matter who it is,
you see my face and it's always about my tits, huh?!
What?!
I am totally pissed now!
The sexual harassment trial is now in session!
N-no, I object! I was talking about your height...
That's right! Sanada is not like that!
Bystanders are not to speak without permission!
I will speak in defense of Sanada!
Objection!
Overruled!
I-I told you, it wasn't about your tits,
it was about your height...
I asked for potatoes and onions...
You have the right to remain silent!
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law!
That's not what you say at a trial!
That's what you say when you arrest someone!
Before you do anything about your tits,
do something about your brain...
Who cares about court anymore? I can arrest you!
Before you do anything about your tits,
do something about your brain...
What?! Get with the program!
This show's also called "Sore Machi," poko.
Japan
has
learned...                 Cabinet
rattled,
to disperse
next month
What about world news...
Financial Crisis!
Japan
has
learned...                 Cabinet
rattled,
to disperse
next month
Mei-do!
What is that?
It's a greeting based on a play on words
with "maido" and "meido."
Why is Mei-do a Vulcan sign?
It's not.
This is a Vulcan sign!
"Mei-do!" is like this here. It's "M" for Maid!
If we make this our store greeting,
we'll get more customers!
Blithering idiot. What proof do you have
that we'll have more customers?
Mei... Oh?
I can't do it!
In any case, this idea is rejected.
What?!
But if we don't have our own color,
customers aren't going to come, you know?
In a meeting
No one shall enter
In a meeting.
No one shall enter.
Head Maid! Look at this!
Customers aren't coming because you are an idiot!
The world is a mirror that reflects yourself.
When you are calm,
the world is filled with mercy, however...
When you are suffering in pain,
it looks as if the waves of adversity are swirling over.
Again...
There's an arrow here, too...
Here, too... Oh.
Yo, if it isn't the cleaner.
What's going on, you two?
Seems like there are arrows posted all over town.
Oh, actually I was also following those
as I was walking.
What's the deal with this?
Hey, look!
MAID
Cafe
SEASIDE
It's the old hag's place...
Yo.
My, my. Such low class...
Welcome back—
Mei-do!
This store has no sense of unity...
Seaside
Granny, what are those arrows?
Are you doing something?
What do you mean, "arrows"? I don't know.
That is indeed my invention!
So customers can follow the arrows and come...
I took two days posting these around town.
At times like a ninja...
At times like a shinobi...
Those are both the same.
No customer would come like that!
But you came.
We did come!
There isn't much we can do.
Why don't we have a meeting for the festival.
Sure. Since we're here.
Three waters, okay?
Yes sir.
Three waters, please!
Yes ma'am, three coffees, please!
Note: Katsu-curry is a Japanese dish consisting of a fried meat, usually pork,
with rice, pickled radish, and red curry sauce.
Three katsu-curries! Okay, got it!
Communication has blatantly failed, damn it!
Um...
Welco—
Welcome home—
Mei-do!
Um, the arrows...
Another one snared into the trap!
Let's rename this place Café Antlion!
No.
Just as I thought, it was you.
Oh! Hey, why did you take them down?
You four-eyed police!
Mega-poli!
Note: Hotori makes up a word, "mega-poli," which is short for
"megane" (glasses/four-eyes) and "police."
You're not supposed to post
stuff like this without permission!
I found thirty of them!
But I went to so much trouble to post these!
What do you have against me?
I don't mean for it to be that way...
When I act on what I think is for the betterment
of the town I always run into you first.
Are you a wall that stands in the way of my life?
I should be asking you that.
I'm sorry...
Our maid is an idiot.
Please, have something cold to drink...
Chew on some ice and go home
to your nest. Go home!
Go home!
I can't stand it anymore!
Don't be rude to the customer...
We told you!
MAID
Cafe
SEASIDE
You understand?
If you do it again, I don't know what'll happen, okay?
I might have to shoot, you know?
Naito
Dental Clinic
What, idiot?!
Naito
Dental Clinic
Whoa, it's an impersonation of Beat Takeshi.
Note: Takeshi Kitano is a comedian known for his confrontational humor.
Naito
Dental Clinic
Ouch...
It isn't anything like him.
What?! Say that again!
Hold it right there!
Whoa, Miss Maid is really pissed!
Run away, Taku-chan!
Uh-huh. And so you were chasing after
middle-schoolers for 30 minutes...
Head Maid, what should we do with her?
There is no allowance for extenuating circumstances.
Thirty minutes worth of her pay will be cut.
Why?! I am doing this seriously!
If you were chasing middle-schoolers seriously,
you would've caught them.
I'm talking about before that!
The original greeting and the posted bills!
To bring in a new range of customers.
Look, the never-changing uninteresting faces.
What?! Of all things, you complain about the customers?!
We're contributing to your sales to the point of
eating katsu-curry at a weird time in the evening!
That's right. I won't be able to eat dinner now.
What do you suppose you do
about my time with my family?
Oh, man...
Men with homes...
But I think I can understand what Arashiyama is saying.
Recently, my senses have numbed
and I've stopped caring...
But it isn't good that the Maid Café regulars
are always the faces from the shopping district.
There need to be lots of men who are going
to give attention to the maids to come.
Why do the customers have to be nice to the clerks?
But Arashiyama's plans are all off target!
Especially that greeting, I can't forgive that!
What?! Then let's at least make it
so the store stands out more.
That's true.
Right now, even the sign seems thrown together.
MAID
Cafe
SEASIDE
What if we order a new sign?
I agree!
I've taken care of her
like a granddaughter, Crybaby Hotori...
Now she's meddling with Granny's
way of managing a business...
Cafe
SEASIDE
Seaside
Oh. What's wrong, Hotori-chan?
Cafe
SEASIDE
Is that so, is that so.
Here, eat some curry.
After all, I couldn't give him the chocolates...
I'm such a coward...
Is that so, is that so.
Here, eat some curry.
I dropped my wallet. Let me cry!
Is that so, is that so.
Here, eat some dinner.
Granny, what's with that outfit?
What kind of revolution is this?!
It seems Maid Cafés make a lot of money.
Here...
Have some curry.
Did you eat, Hotori?
You did eat, didn't you?
I need to talk to you.
The fee for the curry you've been
eating for free for the last 10 years...
I'll let you off the hook, but...
You are going to work here, too!
What?!
I've taken care of her
like a granddaughter, Crybaby Hotori...
I'll think about the sign later, but I do agree
on making the store stand out more.
Why don't we try it?
Really?
But, how do we do it?
Let's see...
There's a huge bolt of cloth on the second floor...
So why don't I have you make a flashy banner.
Seaside
It's becoming interesting.
Hey, you have to do this seriously.
Seaside
Found it. Here it is.
There's paint, too.
Seaside
What are you going to write?
For now, "Maid Café Seaside" in big letters.
Can you spell "cafe" correctly?
Yes I can!
Cáfe
Cafè
Cafê    Cafée?    This!
Cafe
Here goes!
MAID
CAFE
SEASIDE
MAID CAFE SEASIDE
You say big things, but the result dies out at the end.
That's so like you.
Lend me some paint.
I'll write "Majorly popular" where there's space left over.
Won't JARO sue us?
Note: Japan Advertising Review Organization; protects the public from false
advertisement such as the frequently-used "Majorly Popular" (大人気)
It's okay, it's okay. These things
are first-come, first-served.
Here goes!
There!
MAID CAFE SEASIDE
MAJORLY
POPULAR
Nice, Tattsun!
*Thought to be a nickname for Tatsuno that came out of
Hotori's mouth in the heat of the moment
Sauce katsudon goes with milk, poko.
Seaside
Pull tighter on that side.
Sure thing!
MAID CAFE SEASIDE
MAJORLY
POPULAR
It's done!
Granny, Granny, come take a look!
MAID CAFE SEASIDE
MAJORLY
POPULAR
It's a masterpiece!
Is that so? That's exciting.
MAID
Cafe
SEASIDE
Ta-da!
Note: In Japanese, (大人気) can be read as "Majorly Popular" and "Maturity."
The first letters from the adjacent sign, (ない), can be read as"lack of"
and change the meaning entirely: (大人気ない) "Lack of Maturity."
LACK OF   Maturity
MAID CAFE SEASIDE
Lack of maturity...
LACK OF   Maturity
How dare that Naito Dentist!
Today, no matter what I do,
the tides of words obstruct my way!
How dare that world!
The world is a mirror that reflects yourself.
When you are calm, the world
is filled with mercy, however...
When you are suffering in pain, it looks
as if the waves of adversity are swirling over.
I am going to defeat this!
I'll cut it down and win over the world!
Arashiyama!
Do things like this at night!
As you said, like a ninja! Or a shinobi!
What about a shinobi?
What are you doing to our signage?
MAID CAFE SEASIDE
LACK OF   Maturity
I'm so sorry...
We have done something that majorly lacked maturity...
Maybe if you did comedic skits like that every day,
more customers would come?
Arashiyama
In other words, when you came back to the store,
you said the victim was already collapsed here?
Yes... I was going to return to the party right away,
so I had the taxi waiting for me.
Suspect A, a beautiful owner of a boutique.
Yes... I was going to return to the party right away,
so I had the taxi waiting for me.
Suspect B, the taxi driver who drove her there.
Yes... I was going to return to the party right away,
so I had the taxi waiting for me.
Suspect B, the taxi driver who drove her there.
I parked in front of the store and waited
when I heard a scream, so I flew in.
Suspect C, the president of an IT company
who was investing money into that boutique.
I parked in front of the store and waited
when I heard a scream, so I flew in.
The beautiful owner's voice seems
kind of cute and popular...
I parked in front of the store and waited
when I heard a scream, so I flew in.
The beautiful owner's voice seems
kind of cute and popular...
Then there she was... terrified of that dead body.
The taxi driver is a poor man, but he's
played by a voice actor with a refined voice.
Isn't it enough, Detective? Asking any more
isn't going to help you know any more.
The IT company president has to be having
an affair with the beautiful owner...
Now, we're still in the middle of a party.
The IT company president has to be having
an affair with the beautiful owner...
Let's leave the rest to the police and return to the hotel, Sachiko.
...which isn't the point here, his voice seems
like someone handsome and popular...
Wait a minute.
...which isn't the point here, his voice seems
like someone handsome and popular...
If that story is true, the only thing I can think of
Among these people, who would be paid
the highest appearance fee...?
If that story is true, the only thing I can think of
Among these people, who would be paid
the highest appearance fee...?
is that the victim's dead body walked here himself!
Surely, Detective, you don't suspect Sachiko!
The culprit is this person!
What?! How did you know?
It can't be... I can't kill a person...
This guy's only pretending to be dead.
That's right, from the hotel to here, she was with me
the whole time so she couldn't possibly have done anything.
But he didn't even speak yet, why?!
That's right, from the hotel to here, she was with me
the whole time so she couldn't possibly have done anything.
No, no, it's not that I am doubting you.
Because this is a rerun!
It's just that there is something that doesn't make
sense and that's bothering me, that's all.
Mommy! Big Sister did it!
Hotori! What are you doing?!
Oh man...
Oh, man!
Hi, Fu, Hi, Fu, Mi, Yo!
Taikutsuya rock damashi tazusaete
Hitorigurashi no bakuon jinsei
Tennen no chouchin fugu na hoppeta de
Machi wo kaosu ni kyo mo makikomu
Tsundere wa intelligence no akashi nari
Kyou mo kareni wa naze ka kokurezu
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatako
Konna band mo yarase ja ne
Konna member rock ja ne
Mezashite iruno wa ondo ja ne
Tadori tsuku no wa nehan ja ne
Warera wa Meido "Yeah!"
Meido sugata de
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kokora wa meido "Yeah!"
Jiken genba wa
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ahhhh..."
Muteki no meido "Yeah!"
Benpi wa nanzan
Kancho kancho!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kiyoku tadashiku isagiyoku
Seaside wa zessan! Eigyouchu!!
"Meido arigatou gozaimasu!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
Come to think of it, on the Chinese Zodiac,
there's no Year of the Cat, is there?
Even in the stars in the sky,
there is no Cat constellation either.
Why?! It's an animal that's so close to us!
There are Nekozuka and Nekozaki.
There's even a Tatsuno Toshiko!
If anything a Tatsu doesn't exist in real life!
Maybe it was so close that they forgot to put it in?
This smells like a conspiracy!
There must be some kind of hidden truth behind
why the Year of the Cat was omitted!
Next episode, Street Number Three.
"The Boy Who Lost His Cat."
Cafe Seaside
STREET NO. 03 "THE BOY WHO LOST HIS CAT"
Tomorrow, we'll still be turning around and around, poko.
Cafe Seaside