So, um,
Manabe, is it okay if I open it right now?
Of course. I chose it just for you, after all.
Well, aren't we confident.
I am a bit intrigued to see what you picked.
Go ahead and open it, Kotoura!
Right.
It's so cute!
A locket pendant?
Not a bad choice at all, especially for Manabe.
Indeed. I'm shocked it's something so normal.
Um...
Thank you, Manabe.
Look inside. It comes complete with the perfect picture!
Picture...?
My angelic little avatar will always be watching over you, Kotoura!
You killed him!
One morning I realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
Don't fret now
Fret,
fret,
fret
Can't you smell my feelings on me?
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Is this love?
That's a really big secret, you know?
Yeah!
That's a really big secret,
isn't it?
October
Okay, this is definitely the day we switch over to winter uniforms.
It's Not a Date
Every year, I worry that I'll embarrass myself by bringing the wrong uniform.
Oops! Almost forgot.
There we go.
Anyabeg.
Oh, good morning, Kotoura.
Morgink...
Huh? What's this?
Goomorgink.
You sound kinda weird.
And your face is red.
Could it be...?
You do have a fever!
Hgh?
Ogh, yeagh, I gesh I am feelgink a liddle owwa it.
A liddle chilly, too.
I'm ogay dough.
You're not "ogay"!
You've totally got a cold!
Hgh?
Whenj youll geddere?
Just now.
When you told us to come in.
Ogh, shyat sho?
Man, you are really tripping.
Get a grip!
Shorry, Mogidani.
Lemme shtart shome tea.
I was just kidding!
Please don't get up. Just stay in bed.
Has she been to the hospital?
I haven't had time to take her yet.
I did give her some medicine, though.
I sliced up an apple for you.
Great! This apple is great!
Hey, you're looking better already.
Still, it's no fun getting sick when you're living on your own.
Want me to keep you company for the day?
I'll be okay. I've already taken some medicine.
That's right!
And I'll look after her all day.
No worries!
Hearing you say that is terrifying, though.
Why can't you trust me?
Leaving Kotoura with you in her current condition
is like giving a wolf a gift-wrapped little lamb.
I-I do declare!
I am a gentleman, madam!
Surely you don't suspect me of harboring... ill intentions?
Noble words, but no more than words.
If words alone sufficed, the very wolves would lie down with the lambs.
Which is exactly why we need psychic powers!
Go, Kotoura! Expose the sinister truth hidden in this boy's duplicitous words!
You people just had to open your big mouths!
So we're wrong?
Well, yeah.
If you change your perspective just a tad,
and analyze this situation a bit more objectively...
So? What's the verdict, Kotoura?
Huh?
Look, I really wasn't thinking anything very weird.
Just somewhat weird.
It's okay. His mind's completely empty.
Say what?
He's being sincere. He honestly plans to take care of me.
S-Seriously?
Well, Kotoura's never been wrong before, but...
It's almost unbelievable.
You sure you're okay?
Maybe we should get going.
Crowding up the room won't help her recover.
You're right.
Okay, Manabe, she's in your hands.
And keep those hands to yourself, Mr. Wolf.
Y-You seriously don't trust me!
Sorry I couldn't be much of a host.
Don't worry about it.
More importantly...
Try not to get too flirty with Mababe, all right?
Kotoura.
She's doing better than I expected, so that's good.
Yeah.
Let's see if I'm right.
Manabe, could you wipe off this sweat?
Leave it to me. I'll get you nice and clean.
There you go. There you go now.
How's that? How's that, Kotoura?!
You like that? You like that!
It tickles!
Like it better here?
Wait, what's going on?
Th-That's not my back!
Where do you think I'm wiping? Guess!
Louder! Let me hear you!
Manabe, is something the matter?
C-Could it be?
Kotoura can't read my mind?
U-Um, you know...
What?
Wait. Hang on.
It looks like her cold is blocking her mind-reading powers, but she doesn't realize it.
But who cares about the mechanics of it? This is my chance!
The time has come.
It is the Age of Lust!
I've been a bad girl, Master. Please punish me.
You want a taste of Ms. Bunny's tight li'l fishnets?
Ohh! I messed up the exorcism, and now the Lust God is possessing me!
Eek! I've been drenched in one of those acids that dissolves armor but not skin!
This is no fun at all!
Damn it! What's the point of mentally harassing her if I can't see her get embarrassed?
Wh-Why are you crying all of a sudden?
Isn't there anything else I can do?!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance to indulge my lust!
Ugh, I'm completely drenched.
I wish I could wipe off the sweat.
Okay! Leave it to me!
What?! You must be crazy!
Manabe, you lecher!
How can you say that?
My conscience is as clean as a newborn babe's.
I merely wish to express my concern for you.
That is not the face of innocence.
But he's honestly not thinking anything perverted.
A-All right.
But just my back.
What?! For real?!
Hu! Hungry! You must be hungry, Kotoura!
I'll go get some food!
What on Earth came over me?
I'm so stupid! Stupid-stupid-stupid!
Useless moron!
I guess I fell asleep.
Manabe?
Haruka.
The porridge is ready.
Mama.
Feels like your fever is down.
Yeah.
Open wide.
Mama, can I go back to kindergarten tomorrow?
Yes.
Your fever has gone down.
I'm sure you'll be able to go.
You okay, Kotoura?
M-Manabe.
Feels like your fever is down.
Ready for dinner, then?
It's only frozen porridge, but try your best to eat some.
Here, open wide.
Oh, there's a good appetite!
Here, have some more.
Sure.
Now that I've managed to jog off all my excess lust,
I am invulnerable!
Burp.
Thanks for the food.
Okay, now rest up.
By tomorrow morning, that cold will be history.
Okay.
Right. Once I clean up, I'll head on ho—
What is it?
U-Um, Manabe...
This is only if you don't mind, but...
I'd like you to hold my hand until I fall asleep.
B-Bad idea?
Like this?
Yeah.
I beg you. Stay with me for one moment longer,
O my self-control!
Kotoura Haruka, cold defeated, reporting for duty!
We've been awaiting you, Kotoura!
Are you okay?
Manabe didn't do anything weird to you, did he?
M-Manabe kept his thoughts clean the whole time.
He took very good care of me.
So what happened to you?
I worked so very hard.
Please, won't you let me rest?
I think this calls for...
a much more thorough investigation.
Mori!
Go ahead, Kotoura.
I can't believe I trusted you!
You lecher!
This is just cruel!
After I worked so hard to overcome my desires!
But you were being all lecherous, weren't you?
Of course I was!
If you please, Moritani.
Mori!
Ow - I'm sorry - please stop hurting me.
I knew something was off,
but I never imagined she'd lose her psychic powers.
Muroto, any theories?
Well, even espers are human.
I'd guess one's physical wellbeing impacts one's psychic powers as well.
So her cold was the catalyst?
But she's recovered now.
Hey, Kotoura, have you been this sick before?
Did the same thing happen then?
I've had colds before, but I don't really remember what happened.
When I'm laid up with a fever I'm in no shape to read minds, anyway.
That only makes sense.
So, do you think your power will come back?
I don't know.
But honestly, I'd be happy to stay like this.
Naturally.
Well, enough of that.
How horrible of you, Manabe,
to toy with Kotoura's maidenly heart!
What?! Oh God, not you too!
Am I getting another crack at him?
I realize this is a tangent,
but it seems Moritani has firmly established her position in the ESP Society's hierarchy.
The sinner Manabe's penance will be:
showing Kotoura a good time!
Um, what do you mean?
Simple.
Eat her favorite foods with her.
Accompany her to her favorite places.
Do all her favorite things together!
That sounds wonderful!
I get it.
Hold on, President Mifune! Isn't that a date?
What?! A date?
That's right. Off you go.
Relax, damn you!
You wait for Kotoura like this every morning!
Manabe!
S-Sorry to keep you waiting.
What is it?
Oh, nothing at all!
What's wrong with me?
I've seen her street clothes tons of times!
W-Well then, shall we go?
S-Sure.
So where are we going?
Well, uh, let's go wherever you want to go.
Really?
Tohru, it's been so long since we've gone out on a date.
Noriko, I won't let you sleep tonight.
Oh Tohru, you playboy.
H-Hey, Kotoura.
What?
Do you think this really is a...
It's not a date! It's your penance for being awful!
It's definitely not a date!
Wait, I didn't say the word—
Aw, how cute. Their first date.
Youth is such a wonderful thing.
Mama, what's a "date?"
Sh-Shall. We. Depart. Kotoura?
Yes. We. Shall. Do. So. Manabe.
What a great little shop!
Can we take a look inside?
I'd rather check out that one.
Get a move on, Señor Lothario!
I'm sorry!
Lothario! Lothario!
Please use my actual name around other people!
Lothario!
Wow, this is so cute!
Oh, but this one is too.
How can I decide?
Well, what about this one?
What do you think, Mr. Boyfriend?
So it really does look like we're on a date?
Oh, dear! How embarrassing!
Okay, here's my opinion as her date:
This adorably slutty one is très bien!
Wh—
But this shamelessly slutty one is fantastic, too!
But! But!
That casually slutty one is also superb!
But then!
So is this gorgeously slutty one!
Why don't we just buy them all, Kotoura?
Huh?
My apologies, but your companion has sneaked off without a sound.
Kotoura!
Where are you, Kotoura?!
Don't leave me!
Idiot! He's such an idiot!
Well, I knew that. But is he trying to be obtuse?
Honestly. Why did it have to be him I...
So this is where you were, Kotoura!
Aw, she's pouting. Now what?
Manabe?
Sheesh.
Where could he have gone?
Surely he didn't go home?
I understand now.
This kind of nervousness is natural when you can't read minds.
Won't you cheer up already?
Look, I bought you some sweets.
You call taiyaki "sweets?"
It is sweet!
But really. You need to stop doing things like that.
I am sorry. I just got a little overexcited.
Actually, there's one more place I'd like to go.
This is where you wanted to go?
Yeah.
It's just not a date without a movie, right?
It's not a date! It's not a date, right?
When I go to see movies,
I always know how they're going to end before I start watching.
I see!
So I'm really excited to see one now!
Oh, I see!
Three cheers for the silver screen!
Wh—
Manabe!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
No? Then let's go in.
Yeah.
Man, this is boring.
Boring, boooring.
Then why don't you go out too?
Kotoura and Manabe are both out.
Oh yeah, I guess I could always tail them.
You were the one who pushed them into the date. Wouldn't that be a little perverse?
Well, those two can drive me nuts.
But as the club president, I should help their romance along.
Is that so.
And what were your real motives?
Well, let's see.
I simply needed to give Kotoura some sort of stimulus.
I can't achieve my objective
if her mind-reading powers don't return.
A Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
Yuri!
You'll stay for dinner, won't you?
Oh, sure, if it's not a bother.
You could never be a bother!
I wouldn't mind if you ate here every day for the rest of your life!
Mom! Don't come in without knocking.
Well it's not as if you were giving me any reason to knock, is it, Dai?
Why am I being scolded for this?
Cashier
Thanks!
Kotoura—
Kotoura!
Where should we go next?
Well...
They turned out great, Manabe.
So you like this kind of thing?
Just a sec.
I'll keep this forever.
O-Okay.
So, thank you for everything.
And, um, I,
well—
Let's hang out again sometime.
Yeah!
When something trips you up,
how do you stand again?
Can truth be found by thinking
about the days to come?
When we are born, we all come into this world alone,
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us
the flower of hope may bloom,
we start our days together here
We start our days together here
Manabe, this way! Come on!
Slow down, Kotoura!
If you run, you'll trip again!
I'm not that clumsy!
This is fun. I'm so happy.
If only I could feel like this forever!
Kotoura, what's up?
Are you all right? What happened?
Hey, she's unconscious!
Call an ambulance!
Ko—
Kotoura!
Next week, the cast of Kotoura begins its brutal battle royal!
That would make it a completely different show!
The final boss will also make a grand debut!
That is definitely not gonna happen!
But my libido will carry on its business as usual!
Episode 9
Everyone is Around Me
Way to miss the one thing we should change.