Unbelievable! What size is it?
And she's only a first year.
They're enormous.
Looks like another good crop of first years.
Yeah seriously.
Have you heard about Shiraishi?
Shiraishi?
You know, the girl with "These".
Yako-chan, I thought of a great idea!
For the Underwear Club!
Really?
Let me help you with something.
We need at least ten people to start a club.
Of course! Thank you.
I was hoping if you would come by my house after school.
Sh-She's going after Jinguji-san.
Haruka-chan, good morning.
Good morning.
What's wrong? Did you catch a cold or something?
You seem a little down.
Nothing's wrong.
I see...
There's the bell. Get to your seats.
Our Respective Forms
Welcome, you two.
Come on in.
S-Sure!
Thank you for always taking care of my sister.
Eat as much as you like.
T-Thank you.
Oh! Almost forgot the milk.
He's the guy we saw at the entrance ceremony.
Yeah.
Who would have thought he's her brother?
Itadakimasu!
These are delicious!
For a sugar-daddy, he sure knows how to cook.
Haven't we got over that misunderstanding already?!
Keigo-san, weren't you going to a meeting?
Oh, no! You're right!
Your brother has work this late?
Yes. Keigo-san is an underwear designer.
Underwear?
Yes. These are his prototypes.
That's impressive considering he's a man.
Don't you think that pattern is cute?
And that size looks perfect for you, Haruka-chan.
This size?
AA-cup?
Would this fit me?
That one has a wire. You might be better off with this one.
The back is double layered, which will help protect your sensitive chest.
I see.
I wouldn't know how to choose underwear for myself.
And they don't always feel how they look.
I-Isn't that right?!
I have a favour from you two to ask.
"Underwear Club Solicitation?"
"Fitting Plan?"
Yes. I'm sure a lot of girls our age have questions about choosing underwear.
That's why I thought we could gather interest in underwear by starting with a fitting, and then...
Hold on.
What is a fitting?
I suppose it's finding underwear that fits.
And helping people choose underwear that they can comfortably wear for a long time.
I think we've got the idea.
What do you need from us?
R-Right...
I was hoping you would model for me.
What?
W-Which means...
Stripping down to our underwear in front of everyone?
Yes, but of course, boys wouldn't be allowed.
T-That's obvious, but...
I was thinking of doing it myself at first,
but if you two help me, I'd be able to help people with large and tiny breasts.
Who are you calling "tiny?"
S-Sorry...
Why you!
If I can get people to understand the importance of fitting,
I think some people will want to join the Underwear Club.
I want everyone to know that underwear is not just cute and fluffy,
but the right underwear can also be extremely comfortable.
Well, putting "Tiny" aside, it's not a bad idea.
We get undressed to change for PE, anyway.
Then...
I'll help you.
Really?
A warrior never goes back on her words.
Thank you, Yako-chan!
Hey, get off!
You'll do it too, right?
I'm sure it won't be anything to be that scared of.
Do you think that girls like us need fitting?
Yes. It's especially important to choose the right size underwear while our bodies are developing.
I just want to do whatever I can to help.
I know I might be saying something weird again, but...
No, it's not weird.
The things that are weird are my...
Oh, darn! It's about time for my curfew!
Thank you so much.
Next time we can relax and have fun.
Keigo-san would be happy to have you over again.
Nayu, you must really look up to your brother.
Huh?
You always use "san" after his name.
For you, a person who makes underwear must be someone special.
That's also a part of it...
But I think it's because he became my brother when my mother remarried.
Both of my parents died in an accident.
Now I live together with Keigo-san.
But the two of us can talk about anything.
I'm really glad he's my brother.
I guess she's got a lot going on, too.
Yeah...
Um...
I want you to look at this.
"Big Breast Ranking?!"
What is this?
It's a paper some boys dropped this morning.
So that's why you weren't feeling well.
I've had strangers point at me, too.
It makes me wonder if it's my fault I have breasts like these.
The boys are the ones at fault.
They don't have any delicacy at all.
You're far from being a tinge at fault involving that.
That's why, you shouldn't let it bother you.
Got it?
Thank you.
Listen, the truth is, I could feel myself wavering,
after hearing what Nayu-chan said.
You mean, about her parents and Keigo-san?
Nayu-chan never says anything.
On top of that, she's always cheerful and bright.
And here I'm depressed over a simple piece of paper.
The truth is, I'm scared and embarrassed to be seen by everyone in my underwear.
But I want to do something for Nayu-chan.
Haruka...
N-Not out of pity...
I know.
But don't push yourself too hard when you're feeling down.
If there are no questions, I'd like to conclude this class representative meeting.
So she's also a class rep.
Showing off that she's the top student.
Oh, Hamachi-kun?
It's Komachi!
Memorize it already!
What are you doing here, Komachi-kun?
I'm Class E's rep.
What do you think you're doodling?
This is...
Oh, that's right!
Thank you! I've been wanting to thank you for quite some time.
Thank me?
I thought of a way to get people to join the Underwear Club thanks to you.
That's why I'm thinking of starting with an explanatory meeting first.
Don't get all friendly with me!
Sorry.
I hope everyone will come.
You've posted a notice on the meeting place, right?
I finally finished weeding the area behind the school.
Hey!
So, you're asking for permission to use an empty classroom?
Yes.
I understand.
By the way, what sort of demonstration were you planning on holding?
It's a fitting.
Eh? A fitting...?
Well, it's a little difficult to describe with words...
Hey! Where are you looking at?
She has a great figure, but she isn't taking care of it.
Why don't you use my classroom?
Yes!
What is Hayama-san up to this time?
Excuse me, Sensei.
Hayama-san?
Calm down, Tamaki!
How am I supposed to deal with a situation like this?
Stop, Hayama-san!
We are student and teacher!
Our relationship would never allow this!
This isn't good, Sensei!
Your F-cups are turning into double breasts!
Your ill-fitting bra is squeezing your breasts!
Look at how it's crushing them!
And the underwires have left marks on your bottom breast line!
Bottom breast?
It's the contour line along the bottom of your breast.
Sensei, haven't you ever thought your bra is too tight?
I guess I've thought the underside of my breasts were a little sore before.
Exactly! You need to be careful about underwires digging into your skin.
In severe cases, your ribs become deformed.
Sensei! you need to wear underwear that fits!
If you do, it will make your breasts look even better.
And most importantly, it will protect your body!
My underwear will protect my body?
Yes! You need to know more about underwear.
That's why I want to have a fitting to teach everyone about underwear.
Hayama-san...
That's great, but...
There's a boy in here!
I forgot.
Can't you be a little more careful?! Idiot!
I-I'm sorry, Sensei.
I just really love underwear, and...
Hayama-san.
Y-Yes?
I will attend your fitting.
As long as I'm there, I will allow your fitting to take place.
Sensei!
Hayama-san, you're a little unusual.
But you're a good girl pursuing your interests.
Today is the day, so...
Please change into these!
You've really stepped it up today.
Yako-chan, your breasts...
They seem bigger than usual.
Well, you know, they're growing.
Tissues?
Why would you do that?
If I strip down to my underwear in front of everyone,
they'll all know that I'm flat-chested.
But I still want to help you.
Yako-chan...
I see.
Those tissues are your courage.
Thank you, Yako-chan.
Why don't we try using a thin pad instead?
Are you alright with it?
Yes! Here.
Thank you for helping too, Haruka-chan.
It's fine. I'm doing it for you.
And it was my decision to do it.
There are already people here.
We still have another hour before the fitting.
Are you from the Underwear Club?
We're not a club yet...
Hey...
What's a push-up bra?
What size bra should I be wearing?
Even though they were calling the Underwear Club dirty,
they're interested in it after all.
Who wouldn't worry about their own body?
Aren't you going to start yet?
I have a lot of questions.
Very well. It's still a little early, but...
Let's get started!
Mizuno-Sensei still isn't here. Are you sure it's okay?
It's fine. There's no problem at all!
And for people with large breasts, the fitting of a bra is also important.
Haruka-chan, do you think you could show us?
S-Sure.
What should I do?
I'm scared.
What if they look weirdly at me again?
Haruka...
That's right.
Everyone else is confronting their hardships instead of running away.
I'm fine.
They're beautiful!
More like, awesome!
I'm so jealous!
She can wear all the womanly bras she wants.
Well, Haruka-chan...
Y-Yes.
Do you mind if I put my hands inside your bra?
Your hands?
I just want to make sure your breasts aren't being pushed towards your armpits.
S-Sure.
If your breasts are hanging out of your bra, you can push them back in with your hands.
There wasn't anything scary about that.
Nayu-chan's touch was gentle.
I guess it almost felt good.
Thank you, Haruka-chan.
W-Why is my face getting so hot?
So that's how you fit them inside the cups.
I never knew underwear was so important.
Things seem to be going really well.
At this rate, I bet some people will want to join the club.
Quit pushing! I can't see!
Idiot, keep your voice down!
What are you guys doing?!
Peeping toms?
Haruka-chan, put some clothes on.
There's still ten minutes before the fitting.
I made it with time to spare.
What are you guys doing?
I don't know. This guy just came at me-
Shut up, you peeping tom!
Let's get out of here.
Wait.
Hey! Cut it out!
Let go.
Cut it out already!
What in the world is going on here?
What were you guys doing together with the Class rep?
I-I'm sorry. I just...
I see.
You were gathering members for the Underwear Club.
And where are your prospective members?
T-They...
See? I told you no one would join.
This is proof that everyone knows the Underwear Club is just an excuse to attract the boys' attention.
No way! You've got it wrong!
Then how do you explain the peeping toms?
That's...
In any case, having caused this incident...
There's no way you'll be allowed to form an Underwear Club.
Cheer up, Nayu-chan.
I'm sure there are things we can do other than form a club.
We'll help you come up with something, okay?
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
You went through all the trouble of helping me, but because of me...
Nayu...
Check out this amazing underwear.
I'd bet you'd catch a cold wearing that.
You're right. Why is it shaped like that?
That's called an open back girdle.
It's a type of correctional underwear. It pulls your bottom together.
As expected of Nayu-chan.
T-Then... What about these?
I-I've never seen panties like this before!
A-Are you supposed to put your skin through this hole?
You mean you don't know, Nayu-chan?
You really are a bunch of virgins.
That underwear is used during sex, right?
How do you expect to form an Underwear Club when you don't even know that?
I wish I were as big as Mizuno-Sensei.
It's not easy.
Your shoulders get sore, you sweat between your breasts, and you can't wash your belly button.
I was talking about my height.
What?
Between Adults and Children
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!