I have no wishes anymore
Chaika - The Coffin Princess
My hope was hard as rock, and now it is brittle
My body is battered and broken,
and I will not last long
But I will look back on my proud life
with a mask of false courage
The reason flowers blossom
is to say goodbye and wither
This is the law of the world
All of mankind is cruel
We betray and we are betrayed
Goodnight, let us sleep now
You will hear a song
A sad, sad song
A song about you
Fill the blackness
Furom, iestrov...
Elmuto... Eril!
Natow!
Come, The Shtola!
What?
Come, tense atmosphere!
The Strays!
Jentol, winsica!
Finished already?
Do you surrender?
Not surrender!
Chaika!
A Wizard's Pride
Chaika.
Are you okay?
Okay.
Ilm, es, alas!
Schu, limic...
Come, that which bursts and scatters its mark!
The Burst!
From one to the next... Typical saboteurs.
Too bad for you!
Anything else you're still hiding?
I can still fight.
Yeah.
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
A wizard's strength is supported by experience.
What you lack is experience.
Blow away! The Blow!
Chaika!
Assa, schron, misam, winhel...
Come, The Preventer!
Chaika!
That's it for you, Mr. Hero.
Give remains!
What's wrong, Chaika?
You just got your first remains. Aren't you happy?
Why don't you celebrate a little?
Nothing to celebrate.
No?
But, damn, that thing's pretty creepy.
Rude! Father's remains, sacred!
Sorry, sorry.
I hope we can get to the next hero before the white girl and her friends do.
Yeah, while we're on a roll.
You're strong.
Both mentally and physically.
Once we're hired, we don't betray our employer.
That's the one thing we take pride in.
What's wrong?
Remembering that saboteur kid?
No! Absolute no!
Bingo, huh?
Ow!
That's dangerous! I'm driving here!
You brought it on yourself.
Gather remains, objective...
Fake white girl,
father's funeral.
Objective very clear.
But my objective, revenge. Vague.
Specific circumstances, unclear.
Won't you find that out once you gather them all?
Yeah, that's right.
So let's get as many as we can!
Rude!
Okay, okay...
What's up?
Guy...
I see you've acquired Emperor Gaz's forearm.
That's good to see.
You just show up out of nowhere...
Whatever.
We were just thinking we want to get ahead of the white girl and the saboteur siblings.
Where should we look next?
You brought information, right?
Yes, I did.
Tell where!
In a fishing village by the ocean about a day's travel from here,
there's a hero by the name of Clay Morgan.
We go, quickly!
No need to be in such a hurry.
I have one other bit of information.
Tell!
You might want to visit the island off the coast, as well.
Island?
I think you'll find something pleasing there.
You want to keep Captain Gillette's belongings here, then?
I want to leave things so that he can come back at any time.
That's why we're keeping the name of the Gillette Squad, too.
Yes, I've heard from the chief.
What's that?
We have no way to counter her...
What about the traps?
She destroyed most of them.
Damn it.
Toru... Akari...
Not surrender!
Yeah, I know.
We can't get any closer...
If we just wait here, she'll get the upper hand.
I'll be a decoy.
Decoy, dangerous!
If we stay here, we're sitting ducks.
It's do or die.
We have to make a move. Got it?
Understood.
I'll distract her as much as I can.
Akari, flank her.
Chaika, don't panic.
Just look for a good spot.
Right. Precision, important.
Okay. Let's go.
I am steel.
Steel knows no fear.
Steel knows no doubt.
When faced with my enemy, I hesitate not.
I am a weapon to destroy these.
Iron-Blood Transformation!
Trying to flank me, eh?
Alay, salama!
That's it, Chaika! Keep going!
Sabah, amasala, missah!
The Shield!
Toru!
Brother!
Toru...
Salimic, binnu, alay...
Come, to strike and crush!
The Slugger!
Ow...
Toru!
I am man.
Toru! No problem?
Yes, problem.
Relieved.
What about you? Are you okay?
Yes! Touchdown, Field Goal, Two-point conversion!
Yeah, we got her.
So you can do it when you try.
I've lost.
Yes. Because of your advice.
That's not all.
Couldn't you tell?
A moment ago, you wished to protect him with all your strength.
The stronger a wizard's emotions, the stronger the attack.
Yes...
Maybe you really are
the daughter of the emperor.
Understand, grateful.
Fredrica!
Oh... Is that your cat?
Yes!
Lady Claudia, it's time.
You're such a pest. I know that.
Yes, ma'am... I am sorry, but please return immediately.
We're falling behind schedule.
Let's have tea first.
We can spare that much time, right?
Tea time, waited!
Want grape everything!
"A sword drawn at night can never again be sheathed."
That's rather cryptic.
Yes...
But I'll take this fortune to heart and live by it.
What does yours say?
Mine says...
"It is your unchanging love that will save your loved one."
Vivi.
This is Captain Gillette's notebook. It was in the April.
Captain Nikolai and I checked the contents earlier,
and it's full of notes and theories regarding Chaika and Emperor Gaz.
Do you not think it might be full of the captain's feelings on the Chaika case?
Everything in here relates to Emperor Gaz and his castle.
I haven't yet been able to look around this library in detail.
As it says, it seems unnatural
that there are no materials left on the magic techniques used by such a wizard.
So when I looked into these documents again,
I found this.
It's a report on the force that killed Emperor Gaz.
His fortune?
Ms. Curren, is it all right if I keep these?
Of course. That's why I showed them to you.
I will continue my investigation of this library.
I would like you to continue to pursue Chaika, as you always have.
Yes. I will.
Chief Konrad.
What is it, Curren?
I just spoke with Vivi.
I see...
Now that the war is over,
I never thought I'd feel this sense of loss for one of my men again.
Yes...
Perhaps I should have listened to Albéric more than I did.
Yes.
And what of Vivi?
She is strong. She'll be fine.
Also, Chief...
You've been smoking more cigarettes lately.
It's nothing special, but please enjoy.
Grapes, exceptionally sweet!
Fresh grapes, tart, exquisite!
Bring it here.
Yes, ma'am.
As we promised.
Father's remains?
Yes.
So you weren't using them?
The remains?
Yeah.
When I heard you had established a vineyard and winery like this after the war,
I was sure you must have used the emperor's remains as magic fuel.
Well, it's not as though the idea never occurred to me.
If I had used them, I'm sure it would have kept my wine's flavor consistent.
But for whatever reason, something held me back.
You're not like the other heroes we've met.
No?
Well, the army was full of all sorts of unusual characters.
Many of them lost their way once the war ended.
I didn't want to go through that, so I found a new purpose.
And I received some of his remains as proof of my hero status,
but they aren't mine.
I had heard rumors that a girl called Chaika was gathering his remains,
so I had decided that if I met and liked her, I'd give it to her.
Better for his daughter to have them than me, right?
Grateful.
By the way, do you know where his fortune is?
Fortune? Fortune exists?!
Oh, you didn't know?
When Gaz Castle fell, one of the surviving wizards spoke of it.
He said there was a fortune left by the emperor.
Please, spare my life!
I'll give you information in return!
Speak.
I know Emperor Gaz's most guarded secrets.
What?
A wizard recently departed for a foreign island
after receiving an order from Emperor Gaz.
The emperor's fortune is hidden there.
I thank you for the information.
However, our orders are to exterminate all within Gaz Castle.
With no survivors!
The punitive force's record keeper reported a "secret island"
and "the emperor's fortune" to the allied forces.
Emperor's fortune, where now?!
I've heard that the allied forces searched for it,
but they never found anything.
Nothing?
The search was called off after that.
After the castle fell, it was also searched again,
but no experimental tools or documents were found on his magic techniques.
It was assumed that the wizard who received Emperor Gaz's order
must have taken it all
with him to that island.
Island... Father's fortune...
But I'm glad I was able to give you the remains.
Yes.
Do you still intend to continue your journey?
Then why don't I write down the locations where you're likely to find more remains?
You know?
Sure.
I know the names and birthplaces of the other heroes, at least.
There's still plenty more, so eat all you like.
My memory's a little foggy after five years,
so I couldn't say whether they're still around...
Looks like our coming here has set things in motion quite rapidly.
Yeah. No more wild goose chases for us.
Right, Chaika?
Grateful!
But why leave so late at night? You could stay until morning.
We are on the run, after all.
Couldn't you at least have some wine before you go?
I'm not a fan of alcohol.
But wine enriches your life.
Sounds like something a drunkard would say.
When you understand what it means, come visit again.
All right.
Thank you.
Many gifts, grateful!
Claudia's grapes, superb! Can never forget!
Thank you. Take care, okay?
Are you sure it was right
to give it to a girl who may not even be the real daughter?
That was like your badge of honor.
That's no badge of honor.
Just a trinket.
I'll raise the value of my own badge of honor with this year's wine.
Chaika, what is it?
What's wrong? Nightmare?
Gruesome memory... Beheading moment...
But that memory, fake. If true, would be dead.
Am I fake?
First... What am I?
Many Chaikas exist.
Some say, emperor's real daughter, dead.
My memories, turbid.
Uncertainty swirling in heart.
I can't blame you for feeling that way.
But that doesn't change your objective, does it?
Objective, gather remains.
Father, funeral.
Then all you can do is keep working toward that, right?
And all Akari and I need to do is make our master's objective a reality.
Isn't that enough?
Yes. That's what I think, too.
Well, it's morning. Should we get going?
Yes.
You're one of the eight heroes, Glen Donkervoort, right?
Yes, I suppose I am.
You lot are quite skilled.
How about you give us the emperor's remains?
About that... The remains aren't here.
Not here?
I gave them to a girl in red yesterday.
Red?
The red Chaika?
Chaika...
So they were still gathering remains?
They can't be very far.
That only leaves the viscount Alan Tramontana,
Lord Stephan Hartgen, and Clay Morgan...
I don't want the red Chaika to get ahead of us.
Chaika?
Want to look for Father's island.
If found, can learn what I am.
Wait, you...
What am I...
Want to find answer.
The sky grows dark
The bell of the beginning rings out
I live on in you
I live inside you,
twisted and tainted
The ark of our genes
rocks on the water,
sailing for the end times
All that I can offer you
is the day our curse was broken,
but one day, one day,
we will meet again,
as long as you wait for me on this Earth
What is there to be lamented?
I think on the proof we lived together
and bite into my beautiful lips
I will devote my life, my love,
and whatever time I have left
to you
Hero living in harbor town, giant spear user.
Also boss of marine shipping business!
Boss powerful, bewildered!
Want good seafood!
But first, battle inevitable!
The Harbor of Phantom Dreams Recollected
Next time: "The Harbor of Phantom Dreams Recollected".