February 28. Weather, clear.
Today, after thinking about it for a while,
I made a confession.
Kagami. Kagami?
Yawn... What is it? I'm busy.
Well, umm, actually...
Kagami... Be my friend!
Don't go to sleep! I'm being serious!
Yawn... It just sounds extremely complicated
so I'd rather not get involved.
Listen! You know I came to this school
in the middle of the semester, right?
Not only that, I'm the younger sister
of my own homeroom teacher,
which immediately gives the
impression that something's up.
On top of that my idiot brother said...
"Sasami has been a hikikomori for a long time.
I feel sorry for her."
...making it sound like I've got a terrible past.
Now everyone's keeping their distance from me!
Since then they're just watching me from afar,
acting like I'm some kind of fragile object.
And whenever they talk to me, they sound so formal.
Not only that, but they sound like
they're talking to a much older person, too.
I think you're right. I'm sorry that I didn't realize that.
You're doing it too!
Anyway, I just want to have a normal school life!
Normal and ordinary!
But I only have a little over one month left
for my first year in high school!
I still don't understand
why you'd want to be my friend now.
I figured that I should be friends with someone
like you first and establish friendship,
and eventually change others' perceptions
about me as a cheerful and smiley girl,
so that they could feel comfortable talking to me!
You know the part "someone like you"
doesn't sit well with me.
Please! I've never had a friend before,
so I have no idea what to do at a time like this...
Um, so Kagami...
...basically I want to use you as a demo!
Since you're already aware of my background
I don't have to worry too much.
I thought you'd be perfect for practice.
You know, as an "in-between" friend!
Do you realize what kind of disturbing statement
you're making as a human being?
Please, Kagami!
Yawn.
Fine. Let's do it.
Really?
First, as my friend, I want you to be
considerate of my feelings and let me sleep.
Sure! We're friends, right? Okay. Good night!
You're too loud. Please be quiet.
Okay!
And just like that, I had a new friend.
At the fingertip of God
My seasons are made
It's much longer than the starry sky
The song shakes up the sleep
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
It felt like my existence got wiped out
When I stood in the crowd covering my ears
To play what's in my heart
I'm not that mature to be able to select the noise
The flower that I found in the wilderness
It's scary yet gentle
The moment I touch it
Even the diorama could turn into reality
God drew the map for my future as a joke
Because the thousands of melodies echo
I destroy the tomorrow that's chasing me
The bond that cuddles under the starry sky
I saw the warmth
The bond that's born from the pain
That's the kind of bond I want to protect
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 5                                              Ganbaranai
"I HAVEN'T GIVEN IT ALL JUST YET"
Kagami, Kagami.
It's lunchtime. Class is over, so wake up.
What do you want, already?
Let's eat lunch together!
Why?
Why? Because we're friends!
But I can survive without eating.
That's why I want to take a nice nap during lunch,
the one time you're actually allowed to do so.
But you're sleeping even when you're NOT allowed, too!
It's going to look unnatural
if friends don't eat lunch together!
Well then, I'm going to put our desks together,
so you can go ahead and eat. I'll sleep.
That's going to look even more unnatural!
I didn't bring lunch today. Let's go to the cafeteria!
Ugh, you're annoying.
I mean, I'll go with you since we're friends.
CAFETERIA 1
Go, Tsukuyomi! You're our only hope!
D-don't lose!
Can I have some more?
Sure!
We won't lose! We won't lose!
Is that little kid teacher a monster or what?
I wonder what they're doing.
My Big Sis is in there, too...
Oh, he died.
I'm stuffed!
What are you doing, Big Sis?
As you can see we're having an eating battle.
They're supposed to pay for all my cafeteria bills if I win.
What did you wager?
A smooch on the cheek!
Sigh.
Basically, men are hopelessly simple and stupid...
Kagami!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Are you okay?
You don't need to apologize. It was an accident.
I'm sorry, Sasami, but I'm going to change.
You go ahead and have lunch alone.
Kagami...
Hey, Kagami.
What now?
Since we're friends, let's go do something
instead of just sleeping all the time.
Understood. Be friends with me all you want.
I'll take a nap in the meantime.
What am I supposed to do?
Kagami, let's go to the restroom together!
What?
Don't tell me you still can't go to the restroom alone.
That's not it! I've always wanted to go to
the restroom hand in hand with my friend!
We're girls, and that's what we do!
But I'm a robot; I have no business in there.
Don't be like that! You can wait for me outside, okay?
I'm not going in there with you!
Kagami... We're friends, aren't we?
I don't understand the point of this whatsoever.
Don't worry. At the very least,
I'm letting them know that I've got a friend.
Why did I sign up for this?
...has been finalized. Please fill out
the form with the descriptions of your
bicycle and submit to the office.
Oh?
What's the matter?
I stepped on something.
No wonder the pressure points on
the sole of my foot were being stimulated.
It doesn't hurt?
I'm okay. I'm not human, so pressure like this wouldn't-
Kagami!
-hurt me.
It seems that the rotation of the stars
isn't very smooth today.
Please go empty your bowels alone.
O-okay...
Kurari Sushi
So that's how Kagami and I became friends.
Oh, I want the salmon next.
Okay.
Kagami's always sleeping, but she's got good grades.
I want just half of that rice.
Okay.
She can memorize anything in the textbooks by sight.
She has no problem doing 7-digit math in her head.
I hate wasabi.
Okay.
She's on a high level.
Maybe I'll ask her to help me with studying.
I'll kill you if you let the rice touch the soy sauce.
Okay.
Say "ah"!
Ah...
It's delicious.
Kagami was a robot with no will at the beginning.
Tea.
Okay.
An evil organization designed her, using
a fragment of Tsurugi, but she kidnapped her.
Emotions started to grow inside her
as she spent more time with Tsurugi.
Blow on it.
I wonder if her incomplete emotions are the reason
why Kagami seems cold sometimes, or...
Sasami...
What?
Why do you talk only about Kagami?
Why don't you ever make any comment
or tweet about me?
What?
Sasami, please... please... please!
Please eat me!
I'm the one who can love you the best!
Wh-wh-what?!
Stop putting sushi on your nipple!
Don't you embarrass me in public like that!
Okay. I'll do that at home next time.
Don't you do that at home either!
I mean, don't let there be a next time!
What'll I do with you, Big Brother?!
What's the matter, Sasami?
Kagami!
Are you okay, Kagami? What happened?
Oh, it's you two... On the way home?
Stop mumbling nonsense!
You have to go to the hospital right away!
Don't worry.
Unlike you guys, I'm built tough.
I'll recover before you know it.
What happened to you?
I was just taking a nap.
You should've come talk to me! We're friends, aren't we?
It has nothing to do with you.
What?
Would you please keep that "friends" stuff only in school?
For the record, you're only using me as a demo
in order to make friends.
I don't know what kind of idea you have,
but your clinginess is annoying.
Kagami.
Kagami!
MARCH
13th
6 days left
Until the end of
the semester!
Um, Kagami... Kagami...?
Yawn... What can I do for you?
Um, I got some free movie tickets,
so do you want to come?
I'm sorry, but I already have plans for today.
When are you available?
Why don't we go hang out? It doesn't have to be a movie.
I'm sorry...
...but will you stay away from me for a while?
Am I bothering you?
No.
Your existence isn't affecting my life in any way at all.
See you tomorrow.
I don't care...
I don't care anymore!
SASAMI,
I HAVE A FACULTY MEETING TODAY,
SO I'LL BE HOME LATE.
KAMIOMI
Is that true, Kagami?
I've wanted to talk to you!
Ask me anything. We're friends.
That's great to know. Hey, what do you like to do?
I can't... I can't take this anymore...
This "normal stuff" isn't for me after all.
I can never be "ordinary"...
I never would've gone outside
if I knew this was going to happen!
Come over here, It! Follow the clapping!
Right there!
This smell must be Satchin! Thank you for the food!
Hey, it's not fair, Sato!
Eat me, too!
Me, too! Me, too!
You're not supposed to touch a place like that!
You got me!
But I'm the lowest rank of It!
Even if you could defeat me,
there would be the second and third It...
Oh? I smell Mama-lin!
Mama-lin! I'm the blindfolded It!
I'm too strong without the blindfold!
Oh? You are Mama-lin, aren't you?
Why don't you say anything to me?
Did I get the wrong person?
Let's see...
Yup, I can taste Mama-lin!
Oh? Are you crying, Mama-lin?
Let's play, Mama-lin!
It's very dangerous when you're sad.
The gods around you play it smart
and distort the world for you.
Besides, when you're sad, Tama's heart aches, too.
Tama's dumb and doesn't know what to do,
but loves it when Mama-lin smiles!
Let's play!
Okay.
See you tomorrow!
I can't do this anymore... I'm old.
That was fun, wasn't it? Let's play together again, okay?
When I feel like it.
Okay!
Hey, Tama.
How am I supposed to make friends?
Why do you ask me such a thing?
Because I don't have any.
But I thought Big Sis Kagami and you were friends.
Big Sis excitedly told me she made a new friend.
What?
She told me you practiced together during P.E.
and teamed up during English class and stuff.
I know she always has the same face,
but I could tell she was happy
when she was talking about it!
We're always worried because we're gods.
We could Alter things and make anyone our friends
just by wishing. That's why it's scary.
No matter how much I play with my friends
or hear them say that they love me,
I may be forcing them to say it.
Tama...
But Mama-lin and Big Sis Kagami are both gods,
so it's not the result of an Alteration...
You two are real friends, so I'm envious!
Mama-lin, please take care of Big Sis Kagami.
It'll be over soon. It'll be over
before the end of this semester.
What?
This is something Big Sis Kagami has to deal with.
So be patient for her.
Downloading the talisman machinegun.
Inputting the psychic missiles.
Setting Fire Emperor Kagutsuchi's Protect to Level B!
Excite Yata no Kagami!
Note: Yata no Kagami ("Eight Hands Width Mirror") is a sacred mirror
given to the grandson of Supreme God Amaterasu.
Uninstalling vulnerability factor and damaged functions.
Switching heart and emotions to Sleep mode.
Now I get it.
The Yaoyorozu cater to the Supreme God,
hoping to be liked by her.
And right now, the Supreme God is me! This foolish me!
Of all things, I wished I had friends
and chose Kagami of all people!
But the other gods became jealous
and started attacking Kagami.
Safety first
I used to be a puppet with no will...
An automated machine that achieves
the most optimal result in the best method available.
But I came to have a family and maybe friends, too...
If I become her friend,
the entire world would attack Kagami.
I don't care what's coming at me.
I don't mind getting bloody
for the sake of the normal and ordinary,
if that's what my friend wants!
The reason she told me we were friends only at school
must be because maintaining the peace
in the school was the utmost she could do!
Your gratitude wasn't what I wanted,
but I was simply happy.
So before my friend starts worrying unnecessarily...
I should take care of it while it's still a secret.
I'll send anyone who crosses me to the other world!
For the sake of my... Friend!
Kagami...
Stop making me so mad!
Year 1
Right Class
Kagami...
What's the matter? Isn't it too early to come to school?
What about you? Isn't it too late for you to stay in school?
I took a nap and overslept.
So I saw you walking with your classmates.
Are they your friends?
I don't have any such friends.
I saw them being possessed by evil gods,
so I took them away from them.
They must've been secretly living in the humans
in order to get close to you.
I know you would've been very excited
because you're immature.
But it would've been a major problem if
the evil gods talked you into Altering the world.
So you were worried about me...
Are you listening to me? Are you seriously that dumb?
Thank you, Kagami...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
You must be worried, but I'm already done
cleaning inside the school.
And even if you make new friends in the future,
it's not a result of an Alteration.
It's all you.
So just relax and try to enjoy a fun school life...
Kagami!
I'm sorry, Kagami! I was such an idiot!
Wh-what are you doing?
Your snot is going to get all over me! It's nasty!
I'll talk some sense into those gods!
And I'll make sure that they'll never ever
do anything to hurt you! So... So...
You're so annoying, you moron!
I'm sorry! I love you!
You're creeping me out, you pig!
Kagami!
Please be my friend!
Please, Kagami! I don't want you to be a demo!
Be my friend for real!
Sasami...
I used to be a puppet.
With a cold, empty heart and
no functionality to shed tears...
But I still aspired to be ordinary and normal.
I just wanted to become an ordinary girl,
who can cry and laugh.
If my wish could come true...
God... I would've wished to become human...
A foolish and weak yet warm human...
You're already warm, Kagami.
Will I be able to become a human?
Will I be able to become a friend?
Yes, you will! No, let's try to be that together!
Good night, Kagami.
Yawn... I'd like to apologize for the appearance
of the Sasami impostor in the last episode.
Staff members ate the person in question.
They ate her?!
At any rate,
it happened because your laziness made it possible
for an impostor to take over this segment.
So I want you to give it all you've got.
I'll help you out a little.
Then, let's sing together, Kagami!
I might not be able to do it alone,
but with you I'm sure I can!
Yawn... Stop being such a baby!
I'm going to cheer you on from here, so I want you to
go out there and do what you have to do.
Come on!
Akiregao kimi ga warau
You're looking fed up but still smiling
Nee issho ni kaerou
Hey, let's go home together
Kikoeru yo
I can hear it
Kimi no koe ga
Your voice
Dokomade mo hibiku symphony
That's a symphony that echoes far away
Hikari sasu koi iro
Light shines on the love color
Zutto te wo tsunagou
I want to feel the press of your hand over mine
Kasanari au shintoatsu
Kanjitainda
For a long time
Whoa, I think that was pretty fun this time.
I'm tired.
I'll never do this again.
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Ganbaranai@Quiz
It's time for Ganbaranai Quiz.
First question! What kind of question
am I going to give you now?
Hint!
It's a very hard question that
no one in the world can answer.
Tic, tic, tic, pong!
The answer is whatever you're thinking right now.
Second question!
What was the answer to the question
you just thought of?
Next time, Episode 6,
"My Parents are the Only People That I'm Troubling"
Episode 6
"My Parents Are The Only People
That I'm Troubling"