Good morning, Yuuji.
It's a beautiful day today.
Would you like to have breakfast?
Yuuji, are you still sleepy?
Shouko, get my cell for me.
Hello, is this the police?
I'd like to report a trespasser.
What grows on its own? Hmm, what is it?
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Nice to encounter you,"
that one's too easy!
There's only one answer
that I decided on at the start
My heart fluttered. Will I pass?
I won't panic whether
it's a matter of love or war
I sigh as I cram all night long
There's a genius dreamer inside of me
It'd be nice if everything I wanted came true
Pay no mind to other people's worlds
Perfect-area complete!
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area, I can hear someone wishing for it
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? We just keep missing each other
If you came to me for advice, it'd go like
"So, friends?" "Yes, friends."
That's a sad 0 points.
No! Do it again! Rewrite it!
I'm serious, one
more chance please
You know, there's a future
more wonderful than now
Make it more wonderful than
now... my life, my life, my life
Yuuji... what is this?
"Sweat"
Wh-What is that? I've never
seen that book before in my life.
It was hidden under the false
bottom in the third drawer of your desk
with a reference book cover on it.
Hello? What's the matter? Hello?
I'm sorry. I was mistaken.
Well then, just burn it and I'll forgive you.
Wait. You wouldn't punish me like
that if you were planning to forgive me.
Then, I won't forgive you even if you burn it.
So you want it burned either way?!
Ahhhhhh!
So what do you want so early in the morning?
This...
That's... a premium ticket for
Kisaragi Grand Park? Why do you have it?
--A kind person gave it to me with good intentions.
--Good luck!
--Akihisa is pretty much the only one I know who had one.
--It wasn't me!
The special event, Wedding Experience...
"Akihisa Yoshii"
"Blocking number"
Hello? Who is this?
I'm gonna kill you!
Huh?! Who is this?! What?! Hello?!
Well then, let's go, Yuuji.
I don't want to.
You lied.
I never promised anything like that.
You promised that you'd go
out with me if you lost the ST War.
I don't remember that.
Then you pick.
You swore that if you broke the
promise, you'd marry me right away.
Hey, isn't that different from what we promised?
"Episode 7"
"Me, Shouko, and Kisaragi Grand Park"
Dammit! That damn Akihisa!
He'll definitely pay for thi--
--Ow, ow, ow... Stop it, Shouko!
--All the couples are arm in arm.
No one else is using an arm lock
to keep the other from running!
Hello! Welcome to Kisaragi Grand Park!
"Yuuji Sakamoto" "Super Idiot"
"Akihisa Yoshii"
"Beep"
Hey, Akihisa. This sure is an
amusing little trick you're pulling.
Run!
You've got the wrong guy!
Why are you here?!
You too?! What's the
meaning of this, Hideyoshi?!
What're you talking about? I'm a
staff member at Kisaragi Grand Park.
I have no connection to
this acquaintance you speak of.
If you insist on playing innocent, then...
"Yuuji Sakamoto" "Hideyoshi Kinoshita"
"Hideyoshi Kinoshita"
Oops, my hand slipped.
Is it really necessary to go that far over this?
Wha...
Do you have the invitation ticket?
Here.
"Kisaragi Grand Park"
Whoa! This is a premium ticket for a special event!
Alpha calling Bravo. I've confirmed the target.
Code 70. We're moving onto Operation
Wedding. Make sure to take them down!
Hey! What's that violent communication about?!
Please pay no mind.
It has nothing to do with you.
You were clearly talking about us!
Well then, let's take a souvenir
picture, our special service.
Thank you for waiting.
Sorry, Shouko!
Looks like you can't hide your
instinctive habits, huh, Muttsulini?
Yuuji... you're naughty.
I won't do it again so forgive me.
Okay. We'll continue this in bed.
I said I won't do it again! I don't have
the slightest interest in your underwear!
I won't forgive you for that.
Ahhhh! That's so unfair! My temples are...!
Say cheese!
Cheese.
"We're getting married."
What's this picture?
It's our free service.
We added a special design to it.
This photo will be displayed in the park's
photo studio to commemorate your visit.
Are you serious?
Are you feeling shy, Yuuji?
I see nothing in this
picture for me to feel shy about.
Ah! Look! Look, Ryuuta!
Let's have them take our picture, too!
Good idea, Riko. Hey, buddy, you over there.
We'll let you take our picture, too.
I am very sorry, but this is a special
service only for premium ticket holders.
What?! What's the problem
with taking just one picture.
We're customers, you jerk!
"Tenjo"
Wouldn't it be better advertising
if you took a picture of us
instead of those boring brats? Well?!
"Tenge"
"Yuiga"
He's right. Isn't Ryuuta twice
as cool as that high school kid?
Wait.
Where're you going?
Those two bad-mouthed you.
Don't get bothered over something like that.
If you say so...
Just take the same kind of picture of us!
Okay. If you insist... Please come this way.
Okay. Please put your hand here.
Now, squeeze hard.
Ow, ow, ow...
Say cheese!
"We're getting married."
What the hell are you doing?!
You told us to take the same picture, so...
I'm gonna strangle you!
This is bad! The burger head snapped!
Are you mocking me, you brats?!
Looks like... this is gonna be a pain.
How did they sneak in here to begin with?
Are you feeling shy, Yuuji?
What man would feel shy
when his joints are being locked?!
But couples are walking arm in arm.
This position wouldn't make
us look like a couple, would it?!
Hi there, you lovey-dovey couple over there!
See? We look like a couple.
There's clearly something
wrong with her, right?!
I'm Fee the fox! I'll introduce
you to a very interesting attraction!
I saw Akihisa out on a date with
a female college student earlier.
What?! Yoshii was? Where did you see them?
Are you working here, Himeji?
I'm Fee the fox! I'll introduce
you to a very interesting attraction!
If you wanna play innocent, that's
fine by me. Tell me your recommendation.
Okay! My recommendation is the
haunted house you see over there!
I see. Shouko, we'll go
somewhere besides the haunted house.
P-Please wait! Why?
I'm sure you guys have gone
and set something up for us, right?
Please! Go to the haunted house, please!
I refuse!
Stop right there, Yuuji!
I'm Noin! I'm not going to
let you cause Fee trouble!
That getup is messed up in the head, Akihisa.
How rude! Which part is messed up?!
Yuuji, Noin is the absentminded one, so...
No fox would be so absentminded
as to have his head on backwards!
Yoshii! You're wearing the
head the other way around!
What?! Shoot! No wonder
I couldn't see the front.
Fix it quick or Sakamoto will figure it out!
They really still think that
they can keep us in the dark?
By the way, Akihisa...
is your date with that female
college student over already?
What?
Yoshii... I heard that you went on a date
while we were carrying out our important plan.
Wh-What're you talking about, Himeji?
"Sending Mail"
"Mizuki" "Minami"
"Mail Sent"
Minami's on her way here.
Let's sit down and talk.
Th-That's not good.
Amusement parks are supposed
to be places for fun, not fighting!
Hey! What's the deal, Aki?!
She's already here!
You're gonna tell us all the details.
You're gonna be honest with us.
Y-You've got it wrong!
Now, Shouko!
Let's go to an attraction
aside from the haunted house.
Hm? Shouko?
We're going to the haunted house.
What did Hideyoshi tell you?!
There, girls can jump into their
boyfriends' arms as much as they like.
"Scary Abandoned Hospital!!"
"Haunted House"
Please sign here before you enter.
Sign?
This is a written oath.
Written oaths are often prepared
for dangerous attractions just in case.
I see. Then this place is that dangerous?
That sounds fun in its own way.
Let's see... "Oath. I, Yuuji Sakamoto,
will love Shouko Kirishima as my wife
as long as I live and will share
my joys and sorrows with her.
So I swear"?!
Here is a pen.
Here's your registered seal.
Here is the vermilion inkpad.
Is it just me?! Is it just me who
thinks this situation is strange?!
Under the carbon is a second
sheet, a marriage registration form.
You're considerate.
No, they aren't!
Idiot Test
Now, please come this way.
Please hold my bag for me.
Don't hold it sideways as
what's inside will fall out.
As you wish.
Well then, enjoy this scary
experience full of thrills.
"Fire Hydrant"
An abandoned hospital
converted into a haunted house, huh?
It does have an authentic feel.
...ji
--What's that?
--...than...
Is this voice... yours?
--...ji is more... than... bigger...
--What's this? Synthesized voice? Or is it Hideyoshi imitating me?
--Either way, it's not that scary.
--...ji is more... than... bigger...
--Himeji is more my type than Shouko.
--Huh?
--She's got bigger breasts, too.
Himeji is more my type than Shouko.
She's got bigger breasts, too.
Yuuji...
Is that true?
This is a production full of thrills.
Yuuji...
Prepare yourself.
Dammit! Although the approach
is unusual, this really is scary!
I won't let you escape.
Wait! Don't jump the gun! This is a trap!
Hello there. So, how was it?
Did it make you want to get married?
What makes you think that
that would lead to marriage?!
They say that when a man and
a woman fall into a critical situation,
they'll be connected by a strong bond.
That doesn't work when one of
them is the threat to the other!
Yuuji... It's about lunchtime.
Yeah. All that running around made me hungry.
Hm?
Uhm, attention, customers.
Uhm, a special lunch show will
be held at the restaurant today.
--We've prepared a special menu
--Oh? A special menu, huh?
--for those of you with a premium ticket.
--Well then, we'll show you...
--Please be sure to come to the restaurant.
--...to the restaurant.
Hm?
What's the matter, Shouko?
I can't wait to try the special menu.
Yeah.
That was quite tasty, wasn't it?
Everything tastes good when I'm with you.
--Hm?
Everyone! Thank you very much for coming
to see our special lunch show today.
Believe it or not, we actually have a
high school student couple here today
who are dating with an eye towards marriage!
What?!
Now, we'd like to hold an
event to support those two.
It's titled "Kisaragi Grand Park's
Wedding Experience Present Quiz"!
Yaay! Boom! Boom! Honk! Honk!
Dammit! My retreat has been cut off!
If they answer all five questions correctly,
they'll be able to experience
our first-rate wedding package.
It'll be no problem if they decide
they want to get married at the time.
That'll be a big problem, won't it?!
Well then, Mr. Yuuji Sakamoto and
Miss Shouko. Please head to the stage!
Who'd go there?!
Wedding experience...
I'll do my best in the quiz.
--A dream-like wedding experience!
--Ahhh! Calm down, Shouko!
Dammit! I have to avoid this situation somehow.
Well then, let's start the quiz!
That's right! If our answers are wrong...
I'm a guy who used to be called a whiz kid.
Making mistakes on purpose is a piece of cake!
Here's question 1.
Now, bring it on! There's
no question that I can't...
When is Mr. Yuuji Sakamoto and
Miss Shouko's wedding anniversary?
"Rumble, rumble, rumble."
Strange... I can't understand the question.
Yes.
Every day is an anniversary.
"Correct"
--Correct! Every day is an anniversary! Congratulations!
--Ahh! Stop it! I'll die of embarrassment!
Here's question 2.
Dammit! Now that it's come to this,
I'll give them a wrong answer at any cost!
Where are you going hold your wedding?
Mackerel cooked in miso!
"Correct"
Correct!
What?!
It is planned that your wedding
will be held in the Phoenix Hall,
also known as "Mackerel cooked
in miso," at Kisaragi Grand Park!
Wait! You definitely named
it that just now, didn't you?!
Now, here's question 3!
Now I get your way of doing things here.
I'll give them an unmistakably
wrong answer next.
Where did you two meet the first time?
Got it!
"Eye"
Yes. Elementary school.
Correct!
Those damn jerks!
Now that it's come to this, I'll ignore
the question in the middle and answer!
Well then, here's question 4! The two of yo--
I don't kno--
Correct!
It's no use...
As things stand, I can't give them
a wrong answer no matter what I do.
"End"
Is this it for me?
Hey, isn't it unfair?
We're planning to get married, too.
Why are you treating only him special?
Yeah, let us do it, too!
"Arrival"
Burger hea-- I mean, sir.
We're still in the middle of the even--
Shut up, you idiot! I am a
cu-
st-
om-
er
too, you jerk!
I want to have the Wedding
Experience, too, you know.
You know...
Shut up, you idiot!
We're saying that we're
gonna participate! Do as we say!
Then, we'll ask a question.
If they give us the correct answer,
they'll win. If they're wrong, we'll win.
Y-You can't just...
This is my chance! If they're asking
us a question, I can definitely give them
a wrong answer and escape
from the Wedding Experience.
Ah!
Well then, here's the question. Listen good!
What's the capital city of Europe?!
Congratulations! We'll give
Mr. Yuuji Sakamoto and Miss Shouko
a gift, "Wedding Experience
at Kisaragi Grand Park"!
Well then, we'll finally start today's
main event, the Wedding Experience!
Everyone! First, please
welcome the groom with a big hand!
You bastards! I'm seriously
gonna kick your ass later!
Well then, I'll read off his profile...
This is just an experience and it's
too much work, so we'll just omit it.
Hey!
Well then, finally, the
bride is making her entrance!
How beautiful...
Yuuji...
Er?!
Do I look like a bride?
Y-Yeah, you look fine.
At least, you don't look like a broom.
Yuuji...
Wh-What?
I'm happy.
H-Hey, what's the matter?!
This was... my dream all this time, so...
Your dream?
It's been my dream since childhood...
to have a wedding with you...
to become your bride...
The dream I could never
make happen all by myself...
The dream that I've had since childhood...
So I'm really happy...
to be here with my one and only Yuuji.
Shouko... I...
Ahh... This is boring!
This is, like, really boring!
I don't care about your love life
stories. So hurry up and get going!
We've got stuff to do, you know.
Enough with the needless
stuff, get to the point already.
In any case, she said it was
her dream to become a bride.
It's like, "how old are you?"
To put it bluntly, isn't it creepy?
Could it be that you're playing a gag?
Seriously, it's funny!
What'd you say, you bastards?!
How dare you say such a thing to
Kirishima! Step outside, you jerks!
No, Yoshii!
The event will be ruined!
But...
--Calm down, Yoshii!
--...for Kirishima's sake, I can't...
Please!
Shouko...
Yoshii! Did you find Kirishima?!
I didn't see her this way!
Yuuji!
Where did Kirishima go?
I don't know.
What?!
Don't you have some idea?
We have to find her quickly.
Sorry, but I'll pass.
It's too much work.
I wanna go to the bathroom, too.
What?!
I'm in a hurry, so see you later.
That was a kinda shabby wedding.
To put it bluntly, isn't that impossible?
My dream... is to become a bride.
How's that? Do I sound like her?
Yeah, you do! That's too good.
Hey, you guys...
Hm?
What do you want?
Well, it's not really a big deal, but...
Hm?!
Let me have a word with you, will you?!
Hey.
What took you so long, Shouko?
Why are you...?
I thought you'd come here.
Yuuji...
What is it?
Is my dream... strange?
Shouko, let me take this
opportunity and tell you something.
Your feelings towards me are a mistake.
Seven years ago, I was stupid
and dragged you into things.
At that time, I was only trying
to take responsibility. That's all.
Because of me, you wasted
your years on this worthless man.
I'm really sorry.
Yuu... ji...?
I won't laugh at your dream.
You picked the wrong man to have feelings for,
but I think that continuing to care
about one person for a long time
is a wonderful thing.
So your dream is a wonderful
one that you can be proud of
and that is second to none.
That is, if you don't pick the wrong man.
Well, it was a rare experience.
It shouldn't hurt to bring a souvenir home.
Yuuji...
Oh yeah, and...
the lunch you made... was delicious.
Let's go home! If we're late,
people will get the wrong idea.
Yuuji!
What is it?
I... I knew it. I wasn't wrong in the least!
I'd have to say the first kiss
tastes like strawberry milk
As it turns to evening,
I'm pushing my bike home
So which is it, a delusion,
a simulation, or a dream?
After stumbling seven times,
I stumble an eighth time, wahahaha
Each day is different and
every day is an anniversary
Let's connect them together to that sky
My future is bright. Do I see
myself becoming someone big?
Tomorrow too, for sure...
it'll be sunny, with occasional smiles
Question 8.
What does "computer" refer
to in the Japanese language?
Super electronic brain!
That sounds pretty tough.
Next Episode! "Loss of Control, Labyrinths,
and the Avatar Instrumentality Project"
This will be on the test.
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"
"Please join us again next week!"