Romero...
If you were born and raised in a different country,
I wonder... if you would've looked calm like him, too.
Lizzie, you're still around?
You're going to Mexico tomorrow, right?
I thought I'd remind you to be on your best behavior while I'm gone.
What's that?
Don't you think he's quite handsome?
Oriental people all look the same to me.
All I can tell is that he looks carefree.
Do you think he can kill people?
You're kidding, right? He doesn't even look like he can kill a bug.
Yeah... That's what most people would think, isn't it...
Practice
Right. Keep it up.
A knife is a weapon and, at the same time, it's a shield as well.
So...
in a knife fight, the one who can deflect the opponent's knife first wins.
So you were... going easy on me then...
What's the point of putting your enemy in a full nelson while they still have a knife?
Hm?
FBI agent Theodore Brice was found dead in Tijuana, Mexico this afternoon.
When learning languages, use your eyes and ears.
The crime scene led authorities to declare it a murder and they've opened an investigation.
Mr. Brice was investigating the US-based activities of Noche de Sangre,
Nothing...
a terrorist group based in South America.
And it's believed that Noche de Sangre has something to do with this case.
She's off to kill again...
How is Zwei coming along?
Skill-wise, he's close to finishing.
I see...
This is good timing.
Ein, come over here.
Yes.
I'll bet no-one realizes...
that under this fair, soft skin lies such a dangerous weapon.
Have it at the ready.
Ein...
You're perfect.
I trained and created you. You're a perfect subject.
I want this perfection to be forever.
Complete Zwei... with your own hands... Make him perfect just like you.
Yes.
This is the last step for you to become complete.
Ein... Pass down your perfection to the next generation.
Yes, Master.
Ein, you were gone a while.
Come.
We have to get ready.
Just how long are you gonna make me wait?
You do know how important I am to your organization, don't you?
I've been taking a risk selling the military's weapons to you illegally for many years.
We do respect your service, Lieutenant Wallace.
However, your visit was sudden, you see, so..
I couldn't help it since I was caught in a murder case during my vacation.
That was unfortunate.
I heard that it was an FBI agent who was killed. Did you know him?
I have no relation with him.
I don't know why, but they suspect me.
I see...
If I'm investigated, you're as much at risk as I am.
Inferno is obligated to take care of me.
Of course.
A few hours from now, you'll be watching the sunrise in the Caribbean.
I sure hope so.
Pick the gun you think you're now the most comfortable with.
What?
Training again?
No, tonight, you'll have... a test.
A test...
Follow me.
We're supposed to be headed to the airport. What's going on?!
What the hell are you guys...
Mr. McGwire. This is Lieutenant Wallace of the US Navy.
Members of Inferno...
That's probably a large automatic gun.
She must be a guard.
I'm asking you what's going on.
This guy is...
You got too greedy.
Wha...
If you had dealt only with us, you wouldn't have been found out.
However, you sold weapons even to terrorists.
and because of that, you've been marked by the FBI.
Maintaining confidentiality is the ironclad rule of Inferno.
You guys are gonna...
Scythe!
Lieutenant Wallace, Inferno prepared a bailout measure for you.
Please run.
What?
We'll give you ten minutes.
After that, we'll send someone after you.
If you can escape, you win.
That's okay with you, right?
Yeah.
In the back of that building, there's an arsenal. Please take whatever you want.
What's the meaning of this?
We arranged a chance for you to win your life and freedom with your own hands. That's all.
Don't you feel honored and privileged to be a military officer?
So this is how you pay me back after all I've done for you?!
And you call yourselves human?!
Don't you think you shouldn't waste time?
Damn you!
You heard what's going on.
Zwei, I'll give you your first assignment.
Kill that man.
It doesn't matter how you do it. Kill him.
W-Wait. I'm still...
Your training is complete.
You did well. You were an excellent student.
I can send you into actual combat without worrying.
None other than the Phantom of Inferno thinks that highly of your ability.
Have confidence in yourself.
Confidence? Having confidence in killing someone...
Go, Zwei.
I can't.
There's no way I can!
I'll let you choose just one more time.
You either survive by accepting everything,
or die by refusing it.
Will he be okay?
His opponent is an active member of the Navy SEALs, right?
There's no problem.
The reason I troubled you to come here...
is because I'd like you to see his ability with your own eyes.
What weapons does he...
When you pursue, think as if you're running. When you run, vice versa.
Since the very first thought you have will be the same as your enemy's...
Phantom, what's your take on this?
Lieutenant Wallace is a trained pro.
He's probably also more experienced in actual combat than Zwei.
Oh?
However, as long as Zwei clears his mind,
he's better in reaction speed and ability to concentrate.
So what's your conclusion?
Fifty-fifty.
The outcome of this battle will be decided by their own potential.
Does Zwei have a chance of winning?
I don't know Lieutenant Wallace's ability.
Wait! Wait a minute!
I don't have a weapon. Listen to what I have to say.
I don't know why they're making a kid like you do this, but think carefully!
There's no reason for you and I to kill each other.
Do you have a family?
I have a brother who is a lot younger than I am.
I wanted him to live comfortably, so...
If you see one rat, there are at least thirty rats.
If one tells a lie once, it means he tells many lies.
I've been treading on dangerous ground all this time.
I finally sent him to a college.
I wanna take care of him at least until he graduates.
A craftsman has multiple tools.
Killing is the same.
Both you and I are just being used by Inferno.
The one to blame is that organization.
I thought that two bullets would be enough to settle this.
What will we do if that boy loses?
For good entertainment, certain steps have to be taken.
Just in case, may I suggest you wait in the car?
Yeah.
Play time's over.
I've seen many guys like you... cowards who can't pull the trigger.
I'll teach you...
how to kill someone!
Does it hurt, huh?
Killing people...
isn't a job that anyone can do.
Don't take it lightly.
The lesson is just starting.
Zwei...
It wasn't too bad for the first time.
Why...
Why...? This is supposed to be a dream, right?
I told you that it'd be a long dream, didn't I?
This is the continuation of the dream...
the dream that you'll never awake from... until you die or lose your sanity.
Do you want to end it?
It's up to you.
Your eyes, your ears, your heart... Abandon them all.
And become only Zwei.
You can see and hear everything with Zwei's eyes and ears.
Then you'll no longer fear anything.
You won't feel sad. You'll feel relief.
I... I...
I'm not named... Zwei.
Right... That's right.
What do you want me to do?
End it all... for me.
You're no longer you.
Get up, Zwei.
Zwei.
Where did you find such a boy?
A certain source in Japan recommended him.
I see.
So talent is buried even in such an enervated country, huh?
Yes.
You passed the test.
You're now a member of Inferno.
Assassination
Next episode
You are who I used to be.
You know this despair... as well as the pain.