A few days since coming to Tokyo,
this is what I see when I wake up.
I mean...
How many times do I have to tell you?
Good morning.
That has my name on it.
So stingy.
Come on.
Let me have half for my hangover.
No.
Yesterday, I asked you repeatedly
if you wanted one.
Well, I was drunk.
So, did you hear back at all?
Not yet.
I guess moving back
to a place you left isn't that simple.
And from your job?
Also nothing.
You know, I have to go out today.
This unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
In a world where nothing changes
We have to live through it
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
We've already started walking
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
This hopeless city of ours
But I still saw it with my own eyes
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
It looks more like a hospital
than a school.
It's a cram school after all.
Will you go every day?
No way.
I can't afford that.
I have to study while I'm here
and get into a good college.
So you want to go to college.
I mean, not particularly.
It's just that life would be hard
as a high school dropout.
Yeah, that's true.
And there are people
who'd make fun of you.
It's fine, I'm not looking
to get in your business.
As long as you can practice when you can.
What?
You're free on weeknights
and weekends, right?
We'll need to consider
part-time work, too.
Hold on.
A band?
- You said you'd do it.
- No, I didn't.
You did.
You asked me to
raise my middle fingers with you.
Please stop flipping people off
so casually.
Ow...
I didn't mean that I would sing.
I meant it as individuals.
Me with school, you with music.
Oh, that's what you meant?
I did think something wasn't adding up.
Me too. I was surprised.
It's still so crowded at this time of day.
Oh, you sound like a country bumpkin.
Zip it.
But let's say
you work hard on your studies.
How about just dabbling in music?
That's not possible.
I'm not asking you to play an instrument.
I think you'd be good on vocals.
What? Vocals?
You have a good voice and a good soul.
Me?
Yeah.
To me, a band is a group of people
who have a lot of stuff they want to say.
Like, "I want to find love!"
Or "The world pisses me off!"
Or "That was so moving!"
Or "I love myself" or "I hate myself."
I thought you were going to sing alone.
I thought so too, but there's
something nice about being in a band.
You get tense when you're together,
talking behind each other's backs,
but you keep it all inside,
and it just builds and builds.
Until you can't stand them anymore
and finally explode.
None of that sounds good.
What? Oh, right.
But it's fun.
Creating something with others
that you couldn't on your own.
What?
It's nothing.
I think this station is closer
to your place.
It doesn't feel like the city at all.
That's the draw of this area.
Your place is that way,
but there's a supermarket over here.
What? Oh, okay.
Ouch.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Consider it payment for room and board.
- But...
- It's fine.
Can you put the rest away?
Just so you know, I'm not that good.
But you still cook.
I don't hate it.
Let's see... Where's the knife?
It's kind of like writing a song.
You boil the water
while you cut the ingredients,
then make a sauce while it's stewing.
Like you do things simultaneously,
then finally bring it all together
as one thing in the end.
I see.
What a crappy knife.
Sorry, I don't have a proper knife.
It's nothing to be sorry for.
But it makes me realize how useless I am.
How am I gonna live on my own?
Did I say something weird?
No, you reminded me of myself.
You just have to
tackle these things head-on.
A cycle of trial and error.
And you'll learn from your mistakes.
Like not having any dishes.
I'm sorry.
All done.
You'll need to buy a light, too.
Is this what we're eating with?
You actually are
a girl of privilege, aren't you?
You think like a rich person.
No, I'm not.
We're very middle-class.
Just a little different.
We had family precepts.
Family precepts?
Like laws you follow at home?
Yes.
One, always eat dinner at home
as a family.
Two, no using your phone
in the living room.
Three, there will be a family meeting
every Sunday night.
Like that.
That's annoying.
My parents are proud of the fact that
they can enforce these precepts.
And word got around at school.
Yeah, I can see that happening.
But I ended up dropping out of school
after I stopped going.
Why?
What does it matter?
That?
How did you know?
It's all over your face.
The most popular
and prettiest girl in school.
She dated one hot guy after another.
So what, did she bully you?
I guess.
Why?
I don't know.
She just didn't like me.
You didn't get her back?
Girls like her make sure to have people
on their side before coming after you.
She used her friends
to ignore and harass me.
I even got taken to the hospital,
but even my family said
I shouldn't make a big deal of it.
Stop.
The hot pot will overcook.
It's okay, I like my vegetables soft.
I really think you should sing.
You could write five songs
from that experience alone.
I've always wanted to try being in a band
where I wasn't the vocalist.
I want to know what it's like
to focus on the guitar.
Are you being serious?
Yeah.
Dropping out of high school
will limit your future prospects so much.
It'll be too late if you figure out
what you want to be later.
Then...
Then I just need to
get into college, right?
I'll study and get into college then!
No, if I remain a high school dropout
who can't go to college, I'm done for.
"Done for," huh?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
It's just that I'd feel like I lost
if I don't accomplish this.
Like I lost to my bullies,
my parents, and my teachers.
Okay.
I won't ask again.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
There's more beer, right?
So heavy!
Those are books.
I'll carry the heavy ones.
You get the others.
I'm okay.
Can you do this in one trip?
Yeah, this is the last of the big stuff.
Can you check your room?
Okay!
I think that's it.
I need to study.
Here.
You'll be needing this, right?
Oh, you're right.
Either way, I can't play it.
I suppose it's better that I take it back.
Thanks.
Bye then.
Oh, you don't need me to come with you?
I'll be fine.
Okay.
Then, can I ask you one last favor?
What is it?
I didn't know this was here.
You've heard of the Tama River, right?
It's pretty spacious.
I didn't think Tokyo had places like this.
Tokyo's on the other side.
You were close.
It really is on the edge.
Do you have a request?
Anything you want.
I just want to
hear you sing one last time.
Sing whatever you want.
And also good luck with your studies.
I'm just moving back to
my old place that you've been to.
So let's grab a bite whenever you're free.
Okay.
And good luck with your music.
I'll write another song
you'll really love.
Yes.
Please flip them all off.
You too.
Wait.
If you ever want to flip someone off,
please use your pinky.
I'll be doing the same.
Okay.
Well then...
How would you move forward?
It's so blank
It's so long
The answers tend to be superficial cliches
Whether my fingers tremble or not
There's no right answer
There's no losing
I've been me all my life
That's all there is
No matter how much I fight
There's no tomorrow
Shoot.
"Jim said not to give up."
"Even in darkness,
a ray of hope will one day..."
I need to go buy one.
Girls Band Cry.
This is key.
The pronoun that fits here is...
Dodgeball was so fun!
Right? I hit two people!
- That's so impressive!
- Right?
I haven't talked to anyone.
I haven't talked to anyone all week.
Have you finished moving?
Yeah, all done. My back hurts.
Make sure to rest.
Thanks.
TOMORROW'S WEATHER FORECAST
Okay, time to study.
NEW MESSAGE FROM MOMOKA
Did you buy a light?
I got one extra if you want it.
Yes, thank you, I do!
CAN I COME PICK IT UP NOW?
Good evening!
Good evening.
Um... It should be around here.
Here it is.
Hello!
Hey! You were quick.
Excuse me.
Sorry to come so soon.
It's the one right there.
Seems like it'll work, right?
Thank you!
As long as it's bright.
You settled in yet?
That's a good question.
Wanna grab some food together?
My treat since I'm back at work.
Yes, please.
Is this Nina?
Yeah.
Awa here donated the light.
She's my new drummer.
I'm Subaru Awa!
Nice to meet ya!
I... I'm Iseri.
You'll come eat too, right?
But you pay for yourself.
What? You're so stingy!
I can't be paying for everyone!
Ready?
Actually, I should go home.
No, you should come.
Nina just got to Tokyo.
Subaru's the same age as you.
This is more like a hot pot now.
You put in too many vegetables.
Nappa cabbage gets gross
if you boil it for too long.
Here.
For you.
Thanks.
So, what kind of music do you like, Nina?
What's your favorite band or Vocaloid?
She likes old singers
because of her grandma.
Cool, I listen to them too sometimes.
Who do you like?
I mean, I wouldn't say I like them...
Isn't this Glarech?
It is.
Wait, you listen to Glarech?
I saw them live once,
and again at a music festival.
- You mean last year's festival in Chiba?
- Yeah.
It was pretty bad.
Was it?
No wonder they disappeared.
They haven't put on a show since.
I hadn't really noticed,
but you might be right.
The reviews were good though.
Do you go to live shows, Nina?
Not really.
I see.
Should we put the meat in now?
Do you not like meat?
Nina?
Excuse me, I'll be right back.
Not your type?
She's fine.
Then talk to her.
She's trying to connect with you.
What does that mean?
Is she forcing herself to talk to me?
That's how everyone is at first.
You don't know anything about each other.
It feels patronizing.
That's just your imagination.
She goes to acting school,
so that's just how she is.
She doesn't mean any harm.
How kind of her.
Really showing off how considerate she is
by dealing with a baby like me.
What's with your attitude?
I'm just fine!
You'll never be able to talk to anyone
if you keep thinking like that.
Hey!
You're right.
I don't think I'll ever make any friends.
Because of my personality.
Listen.
I'll probably be alone forever.
Thank you for dinner.
Thank you for the light.
You're welcome...
Geez, she's an idiot.
She already has what's most important.
What am I doing?
She was thoughtful and tried so hard
to make a connection with me.
I'm so stupid.
I'm so stupid!
Stupid! I'm so freaking stupid!
I'm so stupid.
Shut the hell up!
- Shut up!
- The hell did you say?!
What is that?
Shut up!
What... Hey, stop!
Shut your trap!
I can't even put up a light on my own.
I'm stuck in the dark forever.
I'll never escape the darkness.
Just darkness.
Come on, we should form a band.
Momoka.
Subaru.
You need a new hiding spot for your key.
And you already broke the light.
I told you, I like your singing voice.
Why would you say a lie like that?
I'm not lying.
You're so negative and complicated,
but it's because
you can't lie to yourself.
Even though you're so fragile,
you hate bending your views.
You're just like my songs
that I had forgotten about.
The ones I love
and want to keep holding on to.
I... I don't need your kindness...
Why are you laughing?!
What a pain!
Ow!
Just take all that negative energy
and put them into songs.
Your songs.
Here.
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
I laughed, thinking it a dream
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
I can't even say that I'm lonely
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
Is incapable of making anyone happy
But still, I feel a growing hope
Moving past all of the lies
I just want to hear
That I'm not wrong
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
I don't care if I'm still the same today
I just want to sing with you
My emotions stir so often
I've been hated
But I'm going to keep walking
Proud of myself
Who can never become anybody
Even if I'm alone
I believe in myself
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing
Next episode,
"Misaligned Questions and Answers"