Future Plans Survey
What are you guys going for?
Hina and I will probably go for liberal arts. Yumiko's still undecided.
Really? Maybe I should pick arts too.
And you, Hayato?
I've sort of decided, but I want to give it some more thought.
Which do you think is better, Hayato?
Your future's riding on this, you know.
If you don't take it seriously,
you'll regret it later.
True that.
By the way, Hayato.
Is it true you're dating Yukinoshita?
What?!
Who told you something so irresponsible?
U-Uh, there's a rumor...
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something genuine
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Did you hear about Hayama?
Apparently, someone saw them together over winter break.
Yeah. Sounds like it might be true!
Come sit over here, Yukinon!
Why do we have to move?
Happy birthday!
Th-Thank you.
So your birthday's on January 3rd, Yukinoshita?
By the way, mine's on April 16th.
I didn't ask.
What are you doing here, anyway?
There, there.
What's the problem?
I have a favor to ask of you guys, actually.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
Are you dating Hayama, Yukinoshita?
Excuse me?
Isshiki...
Y-Yes?
You know full well that I'm not.
R-Right!
Y-Yeah! I totally knew that...
We met the other day, remember?
Apparently, someone spotted you after that and misunderstood.
I see. Just like human trash to have their minds in the gutter.
Well, you know what they say about forty-nine day wonders.
You mean nine days' wonders.
If only it were that simple.
Strangely enough, there's never been a rumor linking Hayama to someone specific before.
It was like Hayama Hayato
belonged to everyone.
But ever since this rumor
started floating around,
more and more girls are
making their move on him.
How?
Straight up asking him out.
Or even if they don't go that far,
they still try some seductive recon.
Wait, they do what?
How do you seduce
someone with that?
Hey...
Are you dating anyone
right now?
N-No, not really.
See? Something like that.
Y-You're just changing how you say it!
Right, Hikki?
It's not like guys wouldn't find that appealing.
It almost gave me a heart attack.
Hikki?
Why did you clam up?
U-Uh, right.
I understand the situation Hayama's in now.
I totally get what he's going through.
Those look great on you, Yukinon!
R-Really?
Well, yeah.
I guess.
Th-Thank you.
Have you always worn glasses?
They're just blue light blockers.
Oh.
Maybe I should try wearing a pair, too.
Do you even use computers?
I do! I use 'em all the time!
Lemme see too, Yukinon.
Oh, we've got mail.
No Subject
How are you guys decidin' between liberal arts and sciences?
Got a moment?
We need to talk.
Well, I'm counting on you for the future plans consultation thing.
Huh? That's news to me.
See ya!
So, what'd you wanna talk about?
What's up with you and Hayato?
Nothing, really.
We've simply known each other for ages.
Really?
What do I stand to gain by lying to you?
Girls like you have always
been a thorn in my side.
Huh?
Who do you think you are?
Get off your high horse!
That side of you really pisses—
Yumiko!
Didn't I already explain it to you?
We all just ran into each other.
That's all it was!
Why'd Hayato get so annoyed by the rumors, then?
There's gotta be more to it.
Maybe there's nothin' right now,
but what about in the past?
Even if there was, would telling you all about it change anything?
Would you or anyone else believe it?
In the end, it'd just be a waste of time.
That side of you really...
Are you done yet?
Settle down for a sec, Yumiko.
You should calm down too.
I am calm.
I'm used to this.
So long as the people
close to me understand,
I'll be fine.
Well, duh.
That's exactly why.
I wanna be close to him.
That's exactly why I wanna know.
No Subject
How are you guys decidin' between liberal arts and sciences?
What happened in the past is not
what you really want to know, is it?
I just, well...
Like, I just thought it'd be nice if we stayed together for a while longer.
I mean, I don't want us
to drift apart like this.
And Hayato's been acting
kinda distant lately.
I know this is weird,
but I don't know
what else I can do...
No, it's not.
It's not weird at all.
Wanting to stay together is perfectly normal.
Miura wants to know about
Hayama's future plans—
what that guy wants to be in life.
She knows that they can't
stay this way forever,
and yet, she wishes to stay beside him.
But Miura...
If Hayama's not saying anything, doesn't that mean he doesn't want people to know?
He might hate you for prying.
H-Hikki!
Hikigaya...
Do you still want to know?
I do.
Even so, I want to know.
That's the only way.
Got it. I'll figure something out.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks.
So you're putting them
to good use already.
You guys can leave.
But we can't let you do all the work.
Nah, it'll probably be easier
to ask him if I were alone.
Then we'll leave you to it. Sorry.
Don't be.
Work is work.
Never thought I'd hear you say that.
My future plans?
Did someone ask you to find out?
Nah. Just asking for reference.
Mind if I ask you for
a favor as well, then?
Could you stop trying to
trap me like that?
If I objected to your behavior like that, what would you do?
I'll cross that bridge when I come to it.
I see.
As for your question,
I'll leave that to your imagination.
Future plans, huh?
I've been playing tennis for really long,
so something related to that, I guess.
Couldn't you get recruited
or something, then?
That only happens to
a handful of people.
Hayama's probably the only one
from our school that has a shot.
Pack it up, guys!
Let's continue after school!
Okay!
Doesn't suit me?
Th-That's not it.
I've never seen you act
all captain-like before,
so I was just surprised.
I'm doing a decent job, aren't I?
Though I might not seem dependable.
Nah, you're plenty dependable.
I can't say for sure yet,
but uh...
I'd probably rely on you.
Thanks.
You're late!
And thanks for coming as well, you two!
Yo, 'sup, Iroha.
What would you like us to do?
We need to rearrange the furniture.
We've also invited alumni to attend.
Alumni?
Oh, if it isn't Hikigaya!
Yo, 'sup!
Sis, I have something to ask you.
Hayato's future plans?
That's it?
Do you know anything?
Just when I thought you'd learned to stand on your own two feet, you're back to leaning on people.
I used to find that adorable when you were little, but enough is enough.
Figure it out yourself.
Yukinon...
Walk me to the station.
Pardon?
You don't get to walk home with a
bombshell like me every day, you know?
Shall we?
All right.
Have you heard anything about
which field Yukino's going to pick?
I haven't.
I guess she wouldn't come out
and say it herself.
You'd better ask her.
We'll compare answers next time.
I'm not sure you can call it that.
Don't sweat the small stuff!
By the way, did you ask Hayato directly?
Yeah.
But he didn't give me a straight answer.
I see.
So Hayato was hoping for it too.
For what?
For a certain someone to find him, perhaps?
"Everyone's Hayama Hayato," huh?
I'm not as nice a guy as you think I am.
Hello?
Hi, it's me.
Sorry for calling so late.
No problem. What is it?
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
I need your help.
Hayama! Aim for a repeat!
H-Hayato...
D-Do your best.
Okay.
While I'm at it, best of luck to you too!
Thanks.
I wasn't talking to you, Tobe.
Y-You can do it!
Best of luck.
All right.
Let's do this.
On your marks...
Get set...
Boy, am I glad I biked to school.
There's no way I'd be able to
handle this otherwise.
I'm amazed you can keep up with me.
If I forget about pacing myself,
it's not impossible.
When people reach the
halfway mark of a long ordeal,
how do they feel?
Does being only halfway there
make them despair?
Or do they feel relief at
making it halfway there?
Most people have to feel
one way or the other.
And both emotions create
an opening in their hearts.
That's why I pushed myself this far.
Was Miura a convenient way
to keep other girls away?
Well? Did she prove useful?
Shut up for a second.
Which field did you choose?
I'm not telling you.
Let me put it another way, then.
Pick the sciences.
I don't know what you picked.
I don't really care, either.
But there's still time,
so pick the sciences.
That's the only way to get what you want.
What I want?
Didn't you tell me to
quit trying to trap you?
That wasn't just directed at me.
You want to be freed from everyone's expectations.
Not many people pick the sciences.
Even fewer girls do.
You can distance yourself
from the things shackling you.
Besides, if you're following
different career paths,
people can accept that and move on.
If your group falls apart naturally,
nobody will get hurt,
and you won't have to betray
anyone's expectations.
I knew we couldn't have been friends.
I hate you.
R-Right.
I feel inferior to you,
and I can't stand that.
I want us to be equals.
That way, I can accept losing to you.
And that's why I won't do as you say.
Sorry I ruined your chances
of retaining your crown.
Nah, I'll win. That's who I am.
And I don't want to lose to you.
Damn.
Aren't you cool.
Congratulations, Hayama!
I knew you'd win for sure!
If it wasn't for your support, I wouldn't have been able to make it all the way.
Thank you.
Yumiko,
Iroha,
thank you.
A big hand for Hayama!
Nobody cares about the losers, right?
So he wasn't dating Yukinoshita, huh?
Guess there wasn't any truth to the rumors.
Infirmary
Hikigaya?
What are you doing here?
They found me taking a break
and forced me to retire.
Did you get hurt?
Yeah, a little.
Couldn't you have gotten
that looked at over there?
Nobody was around when
I crossed the finish line.
I see. You have awful timing.
Or is it awful luck?
Awful eyes?
Maybe—
My personality, my attitude... Everything about me is awful.
Looks like you can't keep
your hands to yourself, either.
Take a seat over there.
Look, I can do this myself.
Hurry up.
Uh, that stings.
Of course it does.
I'm disinfecting the wound.
It's only natural that
it'd be effective on you.
Please stop treating me like a germ.
Did you figure anything out
while running with Hayama?
Yeah.
At the very least,
he's not picking the sciences.
That's a weird way to put it.
All done.
Th-Thanks a lot.
I-It's not a big deal.
Hey.
Mind if I ask which field you're going with?
That's the first time you've ever asked me something like that.
Is it?
For what it's worth, liberal arts.
So I suppose we'll all be in it together.
In the same field, at least.
I'll be heading back to class, then.
Okay.
See you later.
Whoa!
H-Hikki.
Oh, it's Yuigahama.
Y-Yup. I just got here.
Sorry I'm late, Yukinon.
Yumiko and everyone's going to celebrate.
Wanna go?
I'm sorry.
Those weird rumors must have
caused you trouble.
I wouldn't say it was that bad.
Also,
I'm grateful to you for looking out for me.
You've changed a little.
Have I?
It's just that a lot of things
are different from back then.
Yukinon!
The food's here!
There's a whole bunch of chicken!
Totally roasted, too!
See?
She has changed a little.
It looks like she's not
chasing after Haruno anymore.
But that's all.
I don't see the problem.
Haven't you realized?
Realized what?
If you don't get it, then I guess that's fine.
Oh, right.
I forgot to tell you something.
Relationships don't turn to dust just from moving up a grade or going to college.
Uh, they totally do.
Only in your case, Hikigaya.
I'm not like you.
Why didn't you tell anyone
about your decision, then?
When you pick the only option you have to choose from,
can you really call that
your own decision?
I forgot to tell you something.
I hate you too.
Is that so?
That might be the first time
anyone's said that to my face.
Still, I refuse to pick and choose.
I believe that's the best way
to go about things.
Each and Every Time,
Hayama Hayato Lives Up to Expectations.
It's nothing but self-gratification, really.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
With the Answer He Seeks Still Out of Reach,
the Genuine Article He Craves Keeps Going Wrong.
Oh, so Hayato's going with liberal arts.
Then I guess that's what I'm goin' with too.
Shouldn't you give it some more thought?
It's not like I got any dreams or anythin'.
And while I can try another year if I fail the exams, I only get one shot to choose the right field.
I hope you know what you're getting into.
I don't need you tellin' me that, Hikio.
It may be troublesome or whatever,
but that's part of what makes this special, y'know?
I see.
So the answer was much simpler than I thought.