Ugh, what a dilemma...
Something wrong?
At work, the producer and cameraman were arguing over which kind of pudding is better.
We can't get anything done.
Maybe act like you don't care, like how you always do?
That's what I'm doing, but it's getting kind of tiring.
You'd have to be a kid to care about pudding.
Keh! Pudding for brains!
Sweets are the best medicine for irritation.
Don't you mean calcium,
Mr. Smarty Pants?
Drink milk.
Actually, you should probably drink more milk, Palm-top Tiger.
You'll grow boobs.
Really?
Really, really. Absolutely, positively.
How about it? Shall we go have some delicious pudding?
Yeah, okay.
High Purine? Or Low Purine?
Toradora SOS!
Hurray for Foodies
Sweets for Kids, aka Pudding
The pudding here is magnificent!
Delicious! Give me another!
Minorin!
We're back!
Oh, Taiga.
You've come to eat again.
Minorin!
We've come to eat again!
High Speed Bouncy Belt.
Wear this for ten minutes to get a lovely body.
That's amazing, Minorin!
Ooh, let me borrow it!
Sure thing! I'm always on the side of Diet Warriors!
Give it to me, tiny tiger!
Completely ignoring me!
So what's up today?
Oh, Takasu-kun suggested we have some delicious pudding.
The pudding here is great.
A gentle taste that reminds me of my childhood.
Blockhead!
You don't know anything about the taste of pudding!
A gentle taste!? Such balderdash!
I challenge you to a pudding throwdown!
- Ooh, what a beautiful sound...
- Really doesn't make a difference, does it?
Once it's in your stomach, it's all the same.
We'll start with my selection,
Jonny's original custard pudding!
D-Delicious!
Derpalicious! Delishilicious!
Licious! Licious!
My, that was quite scrumptious.
Despite the similarity in names, pudding barely has any purine.
Purines are found in high concentration in meat and fish.
For example, chicken liver contains 312.2mg per 100g.
Threeline grunt sperm sacs contain 305.5mg each.
Digestion of purine will lead to the production of uric acid,
so anyone suffering from gout needs to be careful or they'll aggravate their symptoms.
I should mention, gout is a form of arthritis caused by elevated levels of uric acid.
Some theories say that a cold may lead to...
I have no idea what you're talking about, you quack nutritionist.
Why does he sound so dumb for a walking encyclopedia?
Hah, we're past the age of more calories meaning better taste!
Try the masterpiece of a B-grade gourmet, the puccina pudding!
Yummy!
Yummers! Yumalicious!
Licious! Licious! Li—
My, that was quite scrumptious.
The puccina pudding channels
Mt. Fuji's appearance.
Mt. Fuji is a dormant volcano that could erupt at any time!
The last eruption came after the Genroku era of the Edo period in 1707 of Hoei!
Ash was falling on Edo a hundred kilometers away.
But there was no lava!
Ruins of Edo from that period have revealed...
So is she trying to be a long-winded scholar?
She's starting to sound dumb too.
So what do we do?
Well, I don't care who wins.
Man, it's always so hard to decide.
Shazam!
An impressive showing by both sides!
I am moved!
In the Yamagata dialect, abodondoe means: "Would you like some mochi?"
Which means that neither side wins!
Pudding! Pudding!
Pudding!
Hey, is it true that if your stomach hurts, you should eat eel and umeboshi together?
Huh? Really?
I've never tried.
Oh, I heard that it's actually good for you.
- Huh? No way...
- Gotta give it a try...
Inko Today
Po-Po-Po...
Pork!
Pork.
Po-Pork.
Po-Po-Po-Po...
Pork! Pork!
Pork bun!
Pork bun! Pork bun!
Bun-Bun-Bun...
Bunion!
To be continued