So the wish does come true.
But the one who granted it wasn't me, the Selector,
but Hanayo-san, the LRIG.
That's the Eternal Girl.
That's...
the truth behind these battles.
Hitoe!
Hitoe...
Ruuko!
We need an ambulance! Call an ambulance!
R-Right! A phone—
Hitoe has a cell phone with her! Hurry!
O-Okay!
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
Staff Station
Yes, she's fine.
The doctor said she's stable.
Staff Station
Yeah, I called them already.
And, well... I'd like to wait until Hitoe's mom gets here.
I see.
She's your friend. Of course you'd want to stay by her side.
Ruu-chan...
are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'll call if something comes up.
You were right.
I shouldn't have gone on battling.
Yuzuki... What happened?
What happened?
I won the battle, and then...
You...
will become a LRIG.
Where am I...?
Wh-What?
Nice to meet you,
Yuzuki-san.
Wh-Who are you?
I am
Mayu.
Mayu?
She told me all about Selectors, LRIGs, and Eternal Girls.
She said that all girls who become LRIGs go there.
Hanayo-san and the others had been there, too?
I don't know.
White room...
Tama, do you know anything about it?
Tama doesn't know...
Who is this Mayu?
Her name is all I know.
I see...
I guess Hanayo-san was deceiving me all this time.
I was never told that LRIGs replace their Selectors.
She's probably walking around in my body somewhere out there right now...
She kept telling me how she
would help me with my wish,
taking me for a fool all the while...
Yuzu—
Or so I thought.
But...
How cruel...
You're so cruel, Hanayo-san!
You must know
that LRIGs are not allowed to share the truth with their Selectors.
Why do you know all this?!
Who are you?! What are you?!
If a LRIG breaks this rule,
and her Selector learns the truth
and starts to decline battles as a result,
she loses her chance to ever escape from the card.
That means...
you're doing the same to Hitoe now?
After that, I...
Nice to meet you, Selector.
I couldn't believe it.
Of all people, I had to become Hitoe's LRIG.
"What do I do now?" I thought.
"Do I have to deceive Hitoe now and make her battle again?" I wondered.
"If I don't, I'll never be able to get out of here."
"Still, I..."
Let's get along, Hitoe!
Why... do you know my name?
Of course I'd know it!
We called each other friends, but we only really knew each other for a short time.
Either way, she's completely forgotten about the both of us.
I'll be your LRIG from today.
My... "LRIG"?
What is your wish?
My wish...
If you have a wish, I can make it come true.
I'm Yuzuki.
Let's make your wish come true, together.
Yu... zu... ki...
"I want to go back outside."
"Even if it takes hurting Hitoe."
"Kazuki... I want to see Kazuki!"
That's what I thought.
So, can you tell me what your wish is?
My wish...
Hitoe?
Hitoe! What's the matter?
Are you okay? Hitoe? Hitoe?!
I knew she didn't have a wish.
But...
I had to hold on to the only chance I had.
And then...
Just when I had begun to think about giving up...
Hitoe?
Hitoe? Does it hurt?
Why are you doing this to yourself?
I don't know.... but...
it must be important to me.
I...
have a wish...
Friends...
I want...  friends.
After all the horrible things she had gone through...
After all the pain she had gone through...
She asked for the same thing again.
I want... friends.
Got it.
I'll make your wish come true.
Seeing her cry sealed the deal.
They say you can't deny a girl anything when she's in tears, and they're right.
My wish... Hitoe's wish...
A wish that requires a sacrifice to come true.
I wonder if Hanayo-san had the same thoughts...
I wonder if Hanayo-san felt
just as lost and tormented as I do...
Hanayo-san...
After that, I started thinking...
Hey, Hitoe?
You want your wish to come true, right?
Let's go out and battle, then.
Battle.
I had her battle you, Ruuko.
And then I spoke the truth.
I had hoped that Hitoe would
stop battling after she heard it.
But if she does, then you'll never...!
I don't care.
Sacrificing a friend...
I can't bring myself to sacrifice Hitoe just to get back outside.
Also, if I can't live as Kurebayashi Yuzuki anymore...
If I can't love Kazuki as Kurebayashi Yuzuki...
there's no meaning to a life outside for me.
Yuzuki...
Hitoe!
E-Excuse me...
Ruuko-san!
Hitoe—Where's Hitoe?!
Sh-She's okay... right now.
She's stable now... the doctor is watching over her.
I'm sorry. It's fine.
She scares me.
Hitoe...
She was such a sweet girl, but now,
I just don't know what she's thinking anymore.
She scares me.
I don't know... I don't know anymore...
What should I do?
What should I...?
Yuzuki, you should sleep over at my house!
It's my fault...
I made her battle...
But you did it for her sake, didn't you?
Doing something for the sake of others...
I think that's amazing.
Ruuko...
Let's go! This'll be the second time you've stayed over, right?
H-Hey, listen...
Can I ask you a favor before we go?
Is this okay? Can you see clearly?
Yeah.
My, Yuzuki-chan and Kazuki-kun! You're stepping out?
Just a quick trip to the convenience store.
It looks like it's just about to snow. Be careful.
We will.
Thank you.
What's the matter, Yuzuki?
Cornerstone
Yuzuki?
I want to stay as your girlfriend, Kazuki.
This is about the only time we get to spend alone.
Dad and Mom are at home.
Everyone else is at school.
But no one would bat an eye at a brother and sister sharing an umbrella, right?
What now?
It's snowing... Kazuki, it's snowing!
You're strong, Yuzuki.
You've been strong ever since we were kids.
You always led the way for me and protected me.
I guess...
I've loved you for a long time.
That's why I'll protect you from now on.
I'm your boyfriend, after all.
My wish came true.
She made my wish come true.
Thank you...
Hanayo-san.
Yuzu... ki?
Those who do not refuse to select...
Sending Complete
So, all prepared and stuff?
Yes.
I wonder if she will come.
I'm sure she will.
We're the same, she and I.
That's true.
You and that girl both have nothing but battling on your mind.
Everything else is empty.
You really are birds of a feather.
I don't care.
Sacrificing a friend...
I can't bring myself to sacrifice Hitoe just to get back outside.
A friend...
My wish came true.
She made my wish come true.
A wish...
A wish.
Oh?
Is something the matter, Ruu-chan?
O-Oh, nothing at all.
What are you doing, Grandma?
Look, here.
It started to snow, so now
I need to wipe the potatoes dry.
I'll help!
Grandma?
Hm?
You know, I...
I don't really wish to do anything special or become some important person.
I always thought... that it didn't really matter whether I had friends or not, either.
Okay.
But then I made friends.
I was happy, and I had fun.
I wanted to be with them as long as I could.
So...
Can I...
Can I do something for my friends, too?
I'm happy, too.
I know you can.
Because you're Ruu-chan.
Grandma...
Now then...
Where should I put these?
Put them there, where the sun can find them.
Okay!
Tama?
What's wrong, Tama?
I wonder if you were a normal girl, too.
I wonder what you were like.
I wonder what your wish—
I don't know!
Tama doesn't know... I don't know anything at all!
Tama?
Tama didn't know! Really!
I didn't know at all that Selectors and LRIGs switch places!
I'm not lying! It's true, Ruu!
I just wanted to battle together with Ruu!
I understand.
Really?
Yeah, because you're my friend.
Ruu...
It's been a long day!
Time to sleep!
Good night, Tama.
Hey, did you see it?
Sure! It's some fan gathering for Iona, right?
What does she mean by "select," though?
I guess it's about choosing something?
Well, yeah, but...
Any idea where it's held?
It doesn't say anything about that here.
Oh, that? I sent her a reply,
but she never responded.
What's that about?
Ruuko.
Search it... Do a search on it!
"Iona"... "fan gathering"...
Okay...
Iona Fan Gathering
What is it, Ruu?
Urazoe Iona
Urazoe Iona Fan Gathering.
I call on those who select.
Those who are forced to select...
Those who do not refuse to select...
"Urazoe Iona Fan Gathering."
Urazoe Iona
Urazoe Iona Fan Gathering.
I call on those who select.
Those who are forced to select...
Those who do not refuse to select...
"I call on those who select."
"Those who are forced to select..."
"Those who do not refuse to select..."
"Those who select"...?
Selectors.
She's calling out to Selectors.
Urazoe Iona
That
Emotion
is
Stranded
Once you give yourself to the shadow of the clockwork
tokeijikake no kage ni unadzuitara
darkness begins to encroach from the door of the end
owari no doa ga hiraki hajimaru yami
Menacing answers lie hiding in wait
ayaui kotae soko ni miekakureru
Today's wish will become tomorrow's taboo
kyou no inori wa ashita tabuu ni naru
Lost in a labyrinth where the world is turned upside-down
ten to chi wo utsusu sakasama no meiro
the gears slowly start to turn
mawaridashita haguruma
Quietly from within the waves of people
hitogomi no naka de mimi wo sumashitara
a bell rings out, beckoning my very being
tamashii wo maneku ano suzu no ne hibiku sora e
I have no choice but to walk the endless path
mugen no hate made wo susumu shika nai
for this is the future I willingly chose
jibun de eranda mirai dakara
In the wake of the unreachable summer clouds
todokanai natsugumo yureru kagerou
lies the place of smiles I'll one day reclaim
itsuka torimodosu egao no basho
It's really close by...
What's the matter?
I have nothing to speak to you about.
It'll be all right.
Going to battle...?
I have a wish now!
That
Summer
is
Longing
That summer is longing.