And now, it's time for...
confessions!
What could you possibly mean?
Perhaps she means confessing to one's crush?
Huh? Crush?
You gotta make time for juicy confessions at a sleepover!
You do?
Sleepovers are a fearsome event.
Okay, Alice goes first!
Is that a Selfish?
No.
It's my father.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Father!
Welcome home!
Oh, Alice!
My goodness, haven't you grown big!
I don't believe I've changed that much in three months.
Nice to see you again.
Why, Mana and Rikka! Doing well, I take it?
And you two might be?
Kenzaki Makoto and Madoka Aguri.
Nice to meet you.
Glorious!
You two beauties have what it takes to be international superstars!
And father, I take it by your sudden return that...
Yes, something urgent came up.
As such, could I ask you to attend the banquet with the president in my stead?
It would make for a lovely afternoon.
Thank you.
I must fly to Switzerland posthaste.
Well girls, have a wonderful evening!
The president?
Switzerland?
Wow!
Alice's Daddy Arrives!
A Sleepover at the Yotsuba's!
I never knew your father was such a prestigious man.
Alice's daddy is the CEO of the international Yotsuba Conglomerate!
Do you know what a CEO is?
No I do not!
But Alice, isn't it tough to help your father out so much?
It may be, but it's fun as well.
Besides, it's all to make my dream come true.
Your dream?
Yes.
It's my dream to bring smiles to people around the world.
That's great!
And it was Mana who gave me that dream.
Huh?
What did I do, again?
I'd very much like to hear this story!
Then I'd be delighted to tell it.
It all began when I was still six...
I was in poorer health back then,
so I always played alone in my home's garden.
Careful!
You okay?
Yes...
Um... you are?
Shh!
You like butterflies?
Yes...
Mana!
Trespassing is wrong!
I was chasing that butterfly.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
Besides...
I'm sure it's better this way.
Hey,
I know a place you can find a buncha butterflies at.
Wanna come?
Huh? But I...
Sorry, I guess you're busy.
No...
I'd... like to go.
Then let's go!
Right!
Madam!
Leave her be.
Sebastian!
I shall take all responsibility.
You okay?
I actually know all about you.
She sees you from outside the gate.
But you never ever left your garden...
I'm... not very healthy,
so my father tells me not to leave the house.
Oh, really?
Did we do something bad?
Don't worry.
I've never had so much fun in my life!
You okay?
This is nothing.
But now I wanna go to a bunch of different places!
Really?
Then let's go!
Okay!
I'm Aida Mana!
I'm Hishikawa Rikka!
I'm Alice...
Yotsuba Alice!
And that was how we met.
I frequently snuck away from home ever since to play with Mana and Rikka.
What's this?
Something I built with Rikka.
It's our secret base!
It's not finished, though.
So let's all finish it together!
I'd love to help!
Then let's pinky swear!
Sure!
I would have loved to...
but that night, I came down with a fever.
I've just returned.
Sir.
Sebastian...
This was under your watch?
I deeply apologize.
Is Alice all right?
Father...
How could this happen?
Well...
She hasn't come out in a while.
Did something happen?
Miss Alice can no longer play with you.
She will be moving to a foreign country.
But why?
Her father decided that she needed a new environment for the sake of her health.
When's she leaving?
Today, and quite soon.
No!
Madam, it's time to go.
Okay.
Mana, Rikka...
I'm sorry.
Alice!
Why are you two here?
We heard you were moving away!
Why are you leaving?
I didn't do as my father told me.
So, you're really leaving?
He said it was for my own good.
So, we're not finishing the base?
I want to finish it!
But I can't go against my father...
Alice...
what do you want?
Huh?
I...
Alice, we're leaving.
Father!
Mana!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, but I can't!
Who's there?
Oh, you must be the one who took Alice outside!
Open the door, Alice.
Alice!
Alice...
I...
want to stay here.
I want to stay with Mana and Rikka!
Alice!
Then you leave me no choice.
Please, wait.
Excellent timing! Help us.
I cannot.
What?!
My duty is to ensure Madam's happiness.
If one should wish to steal that from her,
then I would defend her from any foe.
Oh, I see.
So you were the one who let Alice's friends in.
Well, let's see how much your duty means to you!
Forgive me, Sebastian!
Servant Fist, Third Style!
Swallowtail Dance!
Ha, well done!
But how long can you hold out?
Sebastian!
Rikka, got anything?
Is that...
The butler gave it to us.
He said it'd help us learn about your house!
Okay, I think I've got it!
Alice...
let's go outside!
Yes!
Alice!
Search for her.
She couldn't have gone far.
Madam...
I never knew we had a secret tunnel.
This house actually has a ton of them.
There they are!
What now?
Just trust me!
This way!
Hurry!
There!
Now's our chance!
Alice!
Stop right there!
Father!
Stop!
I'm sorry!
Alice!
Alice... since when could you run so fast?
Just a little more!
No...
Alice...
Please, don't take Alice with you!
I was surprised.
I didn't know you'd become so healthy.
Yes...
Ever since meeting Mana and Rikka, I've gotten much better.
Do you like these girls?
Yes.
Father, I want to stay here.
I want to stay with Mana and Rikka!
Madam has changed.
The fact that she stands with her friends before you now...
shows just how far she's come.
Sebastian...
Alice, this is the first time you've fought back against me.
But...
for some reason, I couldn't be happier.
Father...
Take good care of Alice, you two.
Sure!
But still, why would you two go so far for Alice?
Huh? Well...
if your friends are in trouble, isn't it normal to help them?
Besides...
Besides what?
It sounds like Father's leaving.
Alice!
It's a Selfish!
Hey, what the heck're you doing?
This job can suck a fat one!
I'm gonna fly where I want!
I can't believe Bel would stick such an unfashionable ring on me!
Now I need to take my anger out on something!
Mammo!
Oh, there you are.
Father's helicopter!
Lance!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor helicopter who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Go ahead and try!
Rosetta, get your father!
Right!
Father...
Sir!
Please leave him to me.
I shall.
Thank goodness he's safe.
Very well.
You...
Who are you?
A Precure.
Cure Rosetta.
Cure... Rosetta?
Selfish!
He's strong!
I hate to admit it, but this thing packs a punch!
Finish them, Selfish!
Selfish!
Self?
Rosetta!
You saved us!
I'm here now!
Selfishishishishish!
Self!
Rosetta!
Mana...
That was when you gave me that dream.
Besides, when I see other people happy...
it makes me happy, too!
I want to...
I want to be like Mana, too!
Self?!
Self...
Could you try doing something?
I want to see people smile from everything I do in life!
I want to fill the world with smiles through love!
So, come...
You and I will nurture that love!
Huh? What?!
Rosetta Balloon!
A one, two, and three!
Self!
Whatever pops out of the Rosetta Balloon is a surprise every time!
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Precure Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love looooove!
What the heck?! I still lost!
I saw your mother at the opera house in Paris.
Was she well?
Very.
She said she hopes to see you at her next performance.
Performance?
Alice's mother is a famous opera singer.
Well, I'll be off.
Goodbye.
Oh, and could you give someone a message?
Protecting smiles is all well and good, but try to stay out of harm's way.
Who might that be for?
For Cure Rosetta, of course.
Very well.
Well girls, have a wonderful evening!
Alice.
Let's go back.
We still haven't heard the end of that story.
Ah.
You're quite right.
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Ai won't stop crying!
Maybe she's hungry?
Here's your milkie!
Maybe she needs a diaper change?
I don't think that's it, either.
Girls, we have trouble!
What is it, Aguri?
Ai's having a temper tantrum, and the Selfishes have powered up!
Huh? What do we do?!
Dokidoki Precure:
Being a Mommy's Tough!
Ai's Got a Temper!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!