We aren't getting anywhere...
Ready, and...
Iinchou-san, it's morning.
Good morning, Iinchou-san!
Let's work hard today!
Good morning, Negi-sensei.
Ah... It's a good morning indeed.
Good morning, little birdie.
Little birdie?
Yes. This is the Mahora Academy Town ruined by magic.
The one that Negi and Class 3-A were transported to by some unknown force.
It looks similar to the ordinary world, but something is different;
It's a magic world!
Hu
stle!
The enemy's target is Negi!
Really. Are his pupils able to make it back safely to their own world?
Hu
stle!
"Yesterday's Enemy is Today's Friend", by Misa.
"They're so Friendly, They Quarrel", by Madoka.
"Disagreeing is also Part of Love", by Sakurako!
Ras
tel
Ma
Scir
Magister
Binders of light,
the exchangers of the oath…
What are you doing, Aniki?
I'm thinking of memorising everyone's artifacts.
In this situation, if we only search for the appropriate artifact when something happens,
then the situation would be difficult to manage.
As expected from you, Aniki!
You're getting closer to becoming a Magister Magi!
That would be great...
Alright, the next one is...
As a result of yesterday's investigation,
we now understand that the school and it's surroundings are not dangerous so far.
The problem is the outside world isn't it?
Hey, Hey! Where's Asuna?
Oh? Now that you say it, she isn't here, aru.
That's right. I think it's quieter without her around, de gozaru.
Sabotage?
You should say "Sabotenger", aru!
That's not what we wanted to say!
Nah, I don't think Asuna would do that.
Is she still resting?
Yeah, it's been a long day for her.
Even though we were transported to a magic world, she doesn't feel anxious.
Well, that's Asuna for you.
Anxiousness? If you want to cook rice, then use Binchotan.
That's impossible to grade...
No, really the stuff at Bincho is really nice to eat, de gozaru.
No, that's not what I meant.
Kaede, minus 5 points.
Survival Group, lunch please.
Oh, Asuna.
You came here too late.
Just bear it 'till noon, okay?
I can't stand it already.
Nasty!
That's because it's raw.
I’ll die!
Act yourself, hurt yourself.
Here ya go.
There's one left that we made.
Everyone ate the rest of it, so there aren't anymore left.
Sacchan is a person like a wild chrysanthemum!
I don't quite understand that, but...
Eh... Sacchan, that is...
Ah! This apron?
Iinchou gave it to us.
Iinchou did?
Our Negi Aprons!
Ugh, that Iinchou.
Expanding her influence when I'm not around!
Hey, everyone! Please wear the Chupa Tee, too!
Are you giving it to us?
Order one extra now and get a discount!
I don't want to buy it.
I'm not a rich person like Iinchou is.
Please buy it...
No!
Cheapo!
Huh?
It's gone!!
Motsu!
Thank you for your kindness.
You are most tolerant.
My rice ball was...
Asuna!
Ah, she’s here.
We found Asuna! What's she doing?
Sleeping on the floor is not really mannerly.
I’ll kill you someday.
Argh, my shoulders are stiff.
The relationship between magic and its effects are hard to understand.
I'm really tired...
But hey, if we can understand these fairy shards,
we might just be able to get out of this world!
So, let's work hard!
She's an optimist, huh?
However, her existence is pesimistic.
Eh? What did you say?
E-Err um, nothing!
Don't say things like that!
Sorry for troubling.
My, these knickerbockers are cool!
Huh?
Owh... Iinchou...
Do things seriously, please.
It’s just breathtaking, breathtaking…
Iinchou, what are knickerbockers?
They're these.
Don't you think they’d look good on, Negi-sensei?
They do look good!
Don't they?
I'm gonna get it the moment we get back to the real world.
Not again...
Everyone, how is everything going?
Ah! Negi-sensei!
As you can see, everyone under my supervision are doing their best!
It's the same mouth that said it. The same mouth.
We are merely having some small talk. Please sit down if you wish.
Oh, but I have to go to the exploration group later.
It's okay, Aniki. Just for a little while.
Please go ahead and sit down if you wish, Negi-sensei.
Alright then, I'll stay here for a while.
Negi, what are you doing?
You should be with the exploration group.
Ah, yes…
No.
Negi-sensei shall not go with the Exploration group. He is having tea time with us.
Tea time?
Really?
Erm... Well...
Then come after you're done. C'mon, let's go.
He shall not.
That’s not what you can decide, is it?
No. It's my decision. I'm the Iinchou of Class A.
I don't understand what you are saying, don't disturb us.
Who is the one disturbing?
Negi-sensei is having tea with us.
Hey, hey what are you girls fighting over?
Isn’t it quicker to ask to the one in question?
SHUT UP!
AAAH! Sorry!
Negi is going exploring!
Negi is having tea with us!
What are they doing, anyway?
Exploring!
Tea!
Please stop!
Please!
Please stop, the two of you!
Watch out! Negi-sensei!
Negi-sensei!
Right! That'll do!
Thank you very much, Ako-san
Negi-chan is alright, mya?
Yep! Just a bump!
What a relief...
Sorry for worrying you guys.
Sheesh. That happened because you came between me and the Iinchou!
I'm sorry.
Wha... What are you talking about Asuna-san!?
He was trying to stop the both of us from fighting!
You don't have to talk like that, do you?
Then, how SHOULD I talk!?
Hey, hey, Ane-sans!
Yeah. Why don't you guys just chill?
Desu.
Oh yeah, Aniki. Won't you be alright after a simple injection?
You won't feel tired after that!
Err... An injection? Err, I... Injections...
Ah! If you want, I have this!
It's... big!
Yeah, it's too big...
Let's go for it! Try giving him a shot of that!
What are you saying Asuna-san!
That's not right! That syringe looks way too horrible!
Ako-san, what's inside it?
Nutrients, I think... Maybe...
Maybe, huh...
Shoot it! Shoot it!
Alright! Just be a man while I shoot it!
Heeeeyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy!!
Go! Ako!!
Alright, here goes!
Stop it this instant!
Chamo-kun!
I am ermine Kaba-Kaba!
Chamomile Albert is my fake appearance.
And my real form is a super-robust, powerful superhero!!
He's gone, mya.
Luckily, Negi-sensei wasn't the one who got shot.
Yes.
Huh?
That's the last straw!
My patience has worn out completely!
Asuna-san, I hereby propose a duel!
Why?
Don't say "Why?"!
You have exposed Negi-sensei to danger not once, but twice already!!
You were involved in one of them too, right?
This is unforgivable.
I challenge you to a duel!
Hohoh. You're really getting into it now.
Asuna-san! Iinchou-san!
Next! The battle for pride...
...has begun.
W-What am I gonna do!?
Meanwhile, in this place...
How is it, Chachamaru?
Anything unfamiliar?
Nothing in particular.
Isn't there a hint to something that we can see?
As we thought, it looks like there’s no other way but to wait until a move.
Huh? What is it, Chachamaru?
Have you found something?
Chachamaru!
Is it the darkness?
That was a dangerous place.
That kind fool.
Go! Move it! Move it!
Show them the German spirit!!
Yuuna!
Stop playing and help us!
Ahah, sorry!
This just looked like a really nice battlefield!
Anyway, this is interesting isn't it?
Yeah, that's true.
As expected of a magical world.
If it's this easy, it won't be troublesome at all.
Viva la Magic World.
Whoa! A magic tree! Watch out!
Yuuna!
Sorry... Really...
This piece of fairy shard under analysis: There's nothing strange about it.
Chisame-san, please record that there is nothing strange about it.
Yeah, I hear you I hear you.
What!?
"Hello Hello! Is everyone alright?"
Don't read, you stupid!
Being a net idol is difficult, huh?
NO! I AM NOT A NET IDOL!
Coming this far, and yet she's still trying to fool us...
Something about Chisame, I suppose.
"Da pyonn!..."
DON'T READ IT!!
We apologize for the wait. Now, for the showdown.
This has gotten interesting eh?
This isn't interesting at all, Konoka-san.
The prize is Negi-kun!
How nice...
Stop it, Haruna-san!
I'll definitely win!
Breath-Holding Contest.
and... BEGIN!
Go for it, Asuna!
Don't lose, Iinchou!!
Negima, Negime, Negime, Negime, Negima...
Negima!?
Draw.
Clothes Peg Contest.
I apologize! Please start!
This is troublesome...
Asuna-san and Iinchou-san, why can't they get along?
Those two do get along, Negi-kun.
Huh?
They were like that ever since primary school.
What did you say!?
What?
That is unforgivable!
Shut up!
Draw due to injury.
So, shouldn't we stop?
Really, no other choice other than to stop, huh?
There's nothing we can do, mya.
I've finally gotten past the third round, but the son-in-law's nursery had a disaster.
That's too bad, myuu.
Son-in-law? Oy.
Come on, stop it already...
This time, I will not lose!
Me too!
Alright. What's the next fight?
What's wrong?
No! Nothing's wrong.
Haha... Feeling scared already?
Like hell I am!
Terror-Bearing Contest.
The first to run loses. Alright?
I will not lose!
Hey, can you guys please stop now?
This is expected of our class.
I think we are overdoing it...
Perhaps it's too dangerous?
I don't understand what kind of creature this is, but...
Is it a carnivore?
Dunno.
Asuna-san! Iinchou-san!
Stop whining and start the contest now Negi!
There's no need to think too much about this, Negi-sensei.
B-But...!
Negi!
Negi-sensei!
Uh... err okay...
Argh...
He... here it comes! Run! Quick!
What are you talking about?
You are the one who should run! It'll really enjoy it's meal if you don't!
No! I won't run!
Me neither!
B-But...
I'll... grin and bear it...
It's impossible!!
Asuna-san! Iinchou!
Oh well... I guess it was impossible after all.
It's good you guys are still alive.
You...
I'll definitely win the next round!
You guys still want to fight?
Come on...
Huh? Everyone!
The darkness!?
Negi! I'll do the fighting!
Bring everyone to a safe place while I'm at it!
Alright!
Partner, Kagurazaka Asuna.
Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
It's a Cosplay card!
Everyone! Now!
Asuna-san!
Apparently the Cosplay card isn't enough.
Asuna-san! I'm coming to save you!
Negi-sensei!
Iinchou-san!
Please let me go instead!
Please, transform me!
Alright!
Partner, Yukihiro Ayaka.
Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
It's an Armor card!
Asuna-san!
Iin... chou...
I'm coming now!
Asuna-san!
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
I found a round one!
Aww...
Silly...
Try and be a bit more gentle!
Shut up!
Here you go.
Isn't that yours?
Just take it...
Alright, let's just do it together.
Alright.
Ready, and...
Thanks, Iinchou.
We gotta be a bit more gentle right?
Iinchou...
See? They get along, right?
Yes.
Even though he is lost in a magical world filled with dangers,
Negi now feels tranquility in the wilderness.
With a novel heart, Hehe...
Wait until the next time.
Ah! It's Chizu-nee!
What??
Someone help me...
It's a secret!
If you drink vinegar, blood circulation improves and,
makes effect of beautiful skin!
Next time is, "Natsumi, A family is the king of home runs in terms of relationships, after all."
By Chizuru.
"I really don't understand, Chizu-nee!"
By Natsumi.
So, I have to drink this?
You can do it!
Believe in yourself!
I don't want to believe!
God, this is Kuu Fei-aru.
What's up?
I'm in a predicament...
Hmm? What predicament?
I have no worries!
Get outta here.