This way.
What in the world?
Get back to your posts.
It's like a giant drop of mercury.
It almost looks alive.
Must move it.
Is something wrong?
Must move it.  Must move it.
Sir?
Load it onto the truck!
Move it!
The Holy Grail War has been placed
in grave danger.
We have discovered that Caster's Master
is the criminal behind the
serial kidnappings,
which have had Fuyuki City in an uproar.
Therefore, exercising my emergency authority
as the impartial mediator,
I shall be changing the rules temporarily.
All other Masters are to suspend
their current actions,
whatever they may be,
and focus all efforts on
Caster's elimination.
Whoever eliminates
Caster and his Master
will be rewarded with extra
Command Spells.
They are Spells that went unused
by the Masters defeated
in the previous Holy Grail Wars.
I expect that they would be a priceless
commodity to all of you.
Once we have confirmed Caster's death,
we will resume the Holy Grail War proper.
If any of you have questions,
this is the time to ask.
Although I must insist that
only those of you
capable of human speech do so.
Well done, Father.
That should have all the Masters
fully engaged in this hunt.
There were five familiars in the church.
Which means...
Which means that Lord El-Melloi is alive,
despite his disappearance.
Indeed.
Promising extra Command Spells
will attract Lord El-Melloi,
who has already used one,
and the other Masters as well.
They will not want someone else to claim the extra Command Spells
when they could have them for themselves.
Yes, whoever obtains
those Command Spells
will have a considerable advantage.
Of course, we wouldn't want that.
Let those hounds sniff Caster out,
soften him up,
and Archer will be the one to finish him.
E-Excuse me...
Is this the Mackenzie household?
That is the owners' name, yes.
Right...
Is there an "Iskandar, King of Conquerors" here?
That would be me.
Oh...
Uh, pardon me.
I'll need you to sign for this.
My signature?
But of course.
There you go.
T-Thank you...
Master Strategist
Having a world map across my chest
is quite gratifying!
Where did you get that?
My package came today.
You left the house?
I tried out this so-called
"mail-order service."
I told you to stay on the second floor!
The homeowners are away,
and you were busy with your familiar.
Only I could answer the door.
I couldn't help it.
A meeting called by the Holy Church
isn't something I can ignore.
You need not worry.
I realized something when
I saw Saber last night.
There is no reason I cannot walk outside,
provided I am wearing modern attire.
Hey, wait!
If you're gonna go out,
at least put some pants on!
Of course, leggings...
Everyone in this country wears them.
Are those really necessary?
Absolutely essential!
And I'll tell you right now,
I'm not going out to buy any
mega-sized pants for you.
What?!
Boy, would you stand between
me and my world conquest?
Your pants and your quest
have nothing to do with one another, in any way, shape, or form!
You can worry about having fun
once you've defeated a Servant!
Do that, and I'll buy you any
pants you want!
Oh?
Very well.
You swear that when I present
you with an enemy's head,
you will get me a pair of pants?
You...
You really want to go outside
in modern casual wear, huh?
The King of Knights did is already doing it.
As a king, I cannot be outdone by her.
Additionally, this design pleases me.
It makes a fitting crest
for such a ruler as I!
We still have to find where
Caster's hiding...
What the heck are we doing?
Kiritsugu, should we assume the others
will now focus on Caster?
There is little doubt.
But we have an advantage
when it comes to Caster.
I don't know if he's insane,
but he is coming after Saber
because he thinks she is Jeanne d'Arc.
That gives us the advantage.
We can merely wait for an opportunity.
That won't do, Master.
His evil deeds are too heinous to overlook.
We should seek him out
before more innocents fall
to his madness.
Iri, have you learned how to use
the magical barriers in the forest?
Yes, I have.
I'm more worried about the
curse on Saber's left hand.
It's been eighteen hours since
you defeated Kayneth,
but your hand hasn't healed.
Lancer is still alive.
If we want to be completely
prepared to fight Caster,
maybe we should focus on
defeating Lancer first?
I disagree.
Just use the terrain to your advantage, and do not let Saber stay still.
Do your utmost to confuse the enemy.
You won't send her to fight Caster?
Someone will take him down eventually.
In fact, the fools who rush to fight him
will be better prey for us.
I will attack from their flank.
Master...
How long...
do you plan to continue this cowardice?!
You shame the Heroic Spirits!
Why do you not send me into battle?
Have you so little faith
in your Servant?
We're supposedly in a truce
with the others, right?
It's irrelevant.
I distrust the mediator.
He's harboring Assassin's Master,
but pretends otherwise.
He may be in league with Tohsaka.
We are safer being suspicious.
That's all.  You're dismissed.
Kiritsugu...
If...
If I...
If I decided right here to abandon
all this, and go on the run...
Would you come with me, Iri?
But what about Ilya?
What about our daughter, who's still at the castle!
I'll return for her and kill any
who stand in my way.
And after that...
I'll dedicate my life
to caring for you two!
Can we escape?
Of course we can!
It's not too late!
You're lying.
That's a lie.
I know you can't run away.
You would never forgive yourself
for abandoning the Grail...
For turning your back on the world.
You would be the first and last to judge yourself,
and it would mean the death of you.
I'm scared.
He...
Kotomine Kirei is after me.
Maiya told me.
He used Kayneth as bait
to lure me into the open.
He knew how I operate.
I've already had to sacrifice you,
and left Ilya behind.
But the most dangerous
of all is still after me.
The only one I didn't want to face!
You're not fighting alone.
I will protect you, as will Saber.
And...
Maiya-san's here, too.
Kiritsugu!
An attack?
Luckily, Maiya has not yet left.
We can meet it head-on.
Iri, get a long-range
crystal ball.
There they are.
Irisviel, the enemy is baiting us.
They must be hostages.
I'll have to go out and save them.
He knows we're watching him!
As promised the other night,
I, Gilles de Rais, have come for you.
I desire an audience with Jeanne,
my beautiful virgin angel.
Irisviel!
Please take all the time you require.
I have come fully prepared
for a lengthy wait.
Now my little lambs,
time for a game of tag!
The rules are simple.
You must run away from me.
If I catch you...
Don't!
Now, run!
You have until I count to 100!
So, Jeanne!
How long do you think it will
take me to catch them all?
Saber, you must defeat Caster!
Absolutely!
Welcome, Jeanne!
Don't you find this situation
just heart-wrenching?
Do you detest me?
Of course you do.
You would never forgive one who
turned from God's love.
Release that child, heretic!
Jeanne,
since you seem to truly care
about this boy's life...
Well, child, rejoice.
God's most pious servant has
come to your rescue!
You're in danger here.
Hurry, run away.
Just up ahead, there is a large castle.
Have you forgotten?
I warned you last time that I would
prepare more drastic measures.
Be that as it may...
This battle is longer about the Grail!
Oh, Jeanne...
What spirit, what bravery!
My holy virgin, your will would
overshadow God Himself!
Caster!
Now, I wield my sword
solely to destroy you!
If I could only use my left hand!
Even Caster can't have unlimited mana.
If Saber can just survive until he runs out,
she can defeat him.
Right, Kiritsugu?
More importantly, have any other Masters
infiltrated the forest?
Maiya...
Take Iri, and get out of the castle.
Head away from Saber's battle.
I can't stay here?
You aren't safe here,
with Saber fighting out in the forest.
I'm sure I'm not the only one
who has realized that.
Okay.
What is it, Iri?
It seems a newcomer is joining the battle.
What is this?
Is there no limit to his mana?
Wait...
Could that be the source?
Is that book your Noble Phantasm?
Indeed.
The tomes of the occult my
mentor, Prélati, left me
give me the power to command
Hell's demonic legions.
What do you think, Jeanne?
It must be nostalgic for you.
Everything is as it was
all those years ago.
Your noble comportment,
your indomitable spirit
prove undeniably that you are none
other than my Jeanne d'Arc!
So why?!
Why can you not see the truth?
Because you still have absolute
faith in God's protection?
That you will miraculously
be delivered from this evil?
How deplorable!
Have you forgotten what
happened at Compiègne?
Even after enduring such disgrace,
you would still dance on your strings,
as God's mindless puppet?
Shameful, Saber.
One expects superior swordsmanship
from the King of Knights.
Who are you?
Who permitted you to stand in my way?
That's my line, heretic.
My spear will pierce Saber's skull!
The Holy Grail granted my prayers,
to revive that woman!
She is mine.
Every piece of flesh, every drop of blood...
Her very soul belongs to me!
Look, Caster.
I have no problem with your
romantic inclinations.
If you wish to win Saber's heart,
I will not interfere.
However...
I, Diarmuid, will not allow anyone
to cut in and defeat an injured Saber
before I've finished!
Lancer, you...
Don't get the wrong idea, Saber.
I'm only here because I've been ordered
to find and eliminate Caster.
Cooperating with you is my best chance
to accomplish that, don't you agree?
For the record, Lancer...
Even one-armed,
I could kill another hundred
or so of these pests.
If only there were so few.
I will not stand for this...
Stay out of my way, you lowlife!
Fervor, Mei Sanguis.
Ninth head of the Archibald family,
Kayneth El-Melloi, at your service.
Mage of the Einzberns,
let us battle with honor and dignity,
as we wager our lives for the Holy Grail!
Relying on simple traps?
How the mighty Einzberns have fallen.
So be it.
This is no longer a duel,
but an extermination.
I see...
An automatic personnel detector.
There you are, you rat.
Sculp!
Time Alter: Double Accel!
Oh?
You created a reality-altering field
in your own body,
allowing you to manipulate
time into accelerating.
So you do have some knowledge
of magic, after all.
Your disciplined use of magic
makes your reliance on cheap traps
all the more despicable.
I will kill you to teach you your place.
Ire Sanctio!
Manipulating his body's time
must take a considerable toll.
Found him.
How far can he get in such
an exhausted state?
Time Alter: Triple Stagnate!
This thing doesn't have eyes.
If I slow my body's time by two-thirds
and quiet my heartbeat and breath
to their absolute limits...
It can't detect me.
Kayneth!
Fool, you've wasted your chance!
Episode 7
Dark Forest
Maiya-san, don't!
You disgrace of a mage!
You will know terror and hopelessness!
Pierce through, Gáe Dearg!
Who ordered you to fight?
Prepare yourself, heretic.
Next Time:
The Mage-Slayer