- Yuuji: GREAT JOB, GUYS.
HOW ABOUT WE CALL IT A DAY?
- Akihisa: YEAH, OKAY.
- ( beeps )
- HUH?
- Mizuki: SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOUR BRACELET, AKIHISA?
- EVER SINCE WE TOOK
OUR MIDTERMS
THIS THING'S BEEN ALL
KINDS OF CRAPPY.
STUPID SHODDY
CRAFTSMANSHIP!
IT DISAPPEARED.
HMM.
- I'LL BET YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW TO WORK THAT THING.
- Hideyoshi: DID YOU EVER
READ THE MANUAL?
- OKAY, LET'S SEE HERE...
"...DO NOT USE IT AS A HANDLE...
...AND ALWAYS REMEMBER
TO KEEP THIS PRODUCT
OUT OF THE REACH OF CHILDREN."
THAT'S ALL PRETTY MUCH
STANDARD STUFF.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- THAT'S IT!
- EVERYBODY KNOWS I'M OVER 13!
- YEAH, BUT YOU STILL
THINK LIKE A LITTLE KID.
- HEY THAT'S NOT TRUE! IN FACT,
MOST OF THE STUFF I READ
IS ONLY MEANT FOR PEOPLE
18 OR OLDER. ( whimpers )
- WE'D LIKE YOU TO TELL US
EXACTLY WHAT TYPE OF BOOKS
YOU'RE READING.
- BE SURE TO CHOOSE
YOUR ANSWER CAREFULLY.
- Fukuhara: THE BIRD THAT KEEPS
QUIET DOESN'T GET SMOKED.
- ( theme music playing )
- IT'S A BEAUTIFUL MORNING, AKI.
TIME TO GET UP.
- ( groans )
GOOD MORNING, AKIRA.
- GOT YOUR BREAKFAST ALL READY.
I KNOW YOU'RE FIGHTING
THE TOP CLASS
IN THE SUMMONER TEST WAR TODAY,
SO I MADE YOU A MANLY BREAKFAST
TO HELP YOUR STRENGTH.
MEAT BRINGS LUCK IN COMBAT.
AND WITH THAT BEING SAID,
I GOT YOU A STEAK
AND BREADED PORK CUTLET.
- REALLY?!
- NO, THEY WERE TOO EXPENSIVE.
BUT I MADE SURE
TO CUT OUT THE PHOTOS.
- WHAT?
JUST PICTURES?
- ISN'T THAT GREAT?
NOW YOU'LL WIN FOR SURE.
- YOU'RE NOT REALLY
MAKING ANY SENSE,
AND I'M STILL HUNGRY.
- YOU'RE SO RIGHT.
I KNOW MOST TEENAGE BOYS
HAVE BIG APPETITES
AND PICTURES ALONE
JUST WON'T SUFFICE.
I THOUGHT AS MUCH,
SO I GOT ACTUAL FOOD...
- REALLY?!
- ...AND MADE A VIDEO
OF ME EATING.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU FEED ME?!
THIS IS BEYOND CRUEL!
I FIGURED I GOT PICTURES
'CAUSE WE COULDN'T AFFORD IT.
- WE COULDN'T AFFORD
A SECOND STEAK...
AND TRUST ME, FINISHING
THAT FIRST ONE
WAS HARD ENOUGH TO DO
IN A SINGLE SITTING.
- I'M SO HUNGRY I COULD EAT
THAT PIECE OFF YOUR CHEST!
- OH, WHY DO YOU TEASE ME, AKI.
- WOULD YOU STOP IT?
I DON'T NEED ANY OF THIS CRAP
FROM YOU RIGHT NOW!
- ( moans )
- I NEED FOOD!
- YOU ARE SUCH A LITTLE MONKEY.
DON'T YOU WANT TO TELL ME
HOW MUCH YOU LIKE MY SWIMSUIT?
- THERE ARE TONS OF OTHER THINGS
I SHOULD BE SAYING RIGHT NOW,
SO YOUR SWIMSUIT, QUITE FRANKLY,
IS THE LEAST OF MY WORRIES.
WHY ARE YOU EATING STEAK
IN A BIKINI ANYWAY?
- IT WAS THE DIRECTOR
OF PHOTOGRAPHY.
HE SAID YOU'D LIKE
IT BETTER THAT WAY.
I'M THINKING HE WAS RIGHT.
- THIS THING'S GOT A D.P.?
- Yuuji: TEST SCORES ARE
THE ONLY THING THAT MATTER HERE.
NOBODY CARES ABOUT
YOUR ACADEMIC ABILITY.
SHOW THOSE SKILLS ON THE TESTS
OR YOU'LL BE DUMPED IN A CLASS
WITH THE REST OF THE IDIOTS.
- THAT'S HOW YOU ENDED UP
GETTING STUCK IN CLASS "F,"
ISN'T IT, MIZUKI?
- THEY TOLD ME THAT
STAYING HEALTHY
WAS PART OF PREPARING FOR THE
PLACEMENT TEST.
I WAS A LITTLE SICK THAT DAY.
- WE SHOULD BE ACTION-ORIENTED
LIKE THIS SCHOOL!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I MEAN, WE CAN START
THIS BATTLE
WAY BEFORE THE BELL
HAS EVEN RUNG.
HIDEYOSHI!
- THIS IS EVERYTHING
I TOOK FROM MY SISTER--
BOOKS AND A SCHOOL UNIFORM.
I DON'T KNOW IF WE CAN USE
ANY OF THIS AGAINST HER.
- WE'LL FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
LEAVE IT TO ME.
- OH, CLASS "A" BOOKS
LOOK PRETTY TOUGH.
I WONDER HOW YOU SOLVE
THIS WEIRD MATH PROBLEM HERE.
- LET ME TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
- MATH PROBLEMS ARE
A PIECE OF CAKE!
- Both: THIS...
IT'S-- UHH...
THIS MATH IS HARD!
- THE PROBLEMS EXCITE ME
BUT MAKE ME CONFUSED.
- I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT THOSE TWO MAKE TOGETHER.
- THE PROBLEM MUST BE
SUPER ADVANCED
IF IT STUMPED
THESE TWO OVER HERE.
YOUR SISTER'S REALLY SMART.
- THERE'S MORE HERE TOO.
WHY ARE THEY SO EXPENSIVE
IF THEY'RE JUST TINY
LITTLE PAMPHLETS?
- THESE AREN'T SAFE
FOR DELICATE BRAINS.
- AKIHISA CAN'T
PROCESS THOSE YET.
- ALL RIGHT, DUDE,
GRAB SOMETHING
FROM THE BOX AND THEN GO
DECLARE WAR ON CLASS "A."
- NAH. I DON'T WANT TO
GET MY BUTT KICKED AGAIN.
- DON'T WORRY,
I GOT YOUR BACK.
JUST WALK IN LIKE YOU FOUND
HER FAVORITE BOOK SOMEWHERE
AND WANT TO RETURN IT TO HER.
- NICE ONE.
THEN SHE'LL BE ALL THANKFUL
AND LET ME DECLARE WAR ON THEM
WITHOUT THE WHOLE
BEAT-DOWN THING.
YUUKO!
I FOUND YOUR BOOK!
- ( glass breaks )
- Yuuko: NOOO!
- YOU'RE ALL BIG FAT LIARS.
- YOU'RE JUST A BUNCH
OF HEARTLESS, CRUEL,
MEAN MISFIT-HEADS.
- YUUKO!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THAT TO ME!
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU
FOR THIS!
- HEY, YUUKO. HERE TO SCOPE
OUT YOUR SWEET NEW EQUIPMENT?
- IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE
A JOKE, MONKEY BRAIN?
THERE'S NO WAY CLASS "F"
CAN DEFEAT CLASS "A."
WHY DON'T YOU IDIOTS
GIVE IT A REST?!
- GOOD...
NIGHT.
- I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN SHE WAS
SPEAKING METAPHORICALLY.
- YOU CRETINS SHOULD BE THANKFUL
TO BE IN THIS SCHOOL AT ALL--
YOU'RE THE SCUM
OF THE ACADEMY.
QUIT TRYING TO MESS
WITH THE REAL STUDENTS HERE.
- YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT.
CLASS "F" MIGHT NOT GET
THE HIGHEST GRADES
ON ALL THE ACADEMICS,
BUT I WON'T BE QUIET
WHILE YOU CALL THEM SCUM.
- I GUESS
YOU'RE NOT SCUM THEN?
- ( whimpers )
- I MEAN, IF THINGS
HAD TURNED OUT DIFFERENTLY
ON THAT LITTLE PLACEMENT
TEST OF YOURS...
OR PERHAPS I'M WRONG AND YOU
REALLY FIT IN WITH THESE LOSERS.
- HUH?
- MAYBE IT MIGHT BE
TOO LATE FOR YOU.
WORD IS YOU'VE TURNED
INTO A REAL MORON ALREADY.
- OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH
OUT OF YOU.
HIMEJI IS WAY TOO SMART
TO BE STUCK HERE IN CLASS "F."
- AKIHISA, THIS LITTLE
OUTBURST ACTUALLY STRENGTHENS
HER ARGUMENT ABOUT US.
- ( growls )
- CARDBOARD BOXES ARE READY.
WE MADE SURE TO SHINE
THEM ALL UP FOR YA.
THEY'LL LOOK GOOD IN CLASS "A."
- YOU WON'T BE SO COCKY
AFTER SCHOOL GETS OUT.
YOU BETTER BE READY.
- ( door bangs )
- THE FIRST PHASE OF THE PLAN
IS NOW COMPLETE.
- I STILL DON'T SEE HOW THIS
HELPS US TO WIN AGAINST THEM.
- WE'D NEVER SURVIVE A HEAD
TO HEAD BATTLE WITH CLASS "A."
- THERE'S THAT LITTLE HISTORY
THINGY OF SHOUKO'S,
BUT SOMETHING TELLS ME
IT WON'T WORK TWICE.
- AGREED.
MAKING THE SAME MISTAKE
A SECOND TIME IS
HIGHLY UNLIKELY.
- WHY DO YOU THINK WE DIDN'T
EXCHANGE EQUIPMENT
ON OUR LAST ENCOUNTER?
- HUH?
- THE SEEDS I PLANTED HAVE GROWN
AND NOW IT'S TIME TO HARVEST.
- Yuuko: A MOCK S-T WAR?
- Nemoto: NORMALLY WE WOULD'VE
LIKED TO OFFICIALLY DECLARE WAR,
BUT THAT'S NOT ALLOWED FOR THREE
MONTHS AFTER OUR LAST LOSS.
WE JUST NEED
A TRAINING MATCH.
- I'M AFRAID WE ALREADY
HAVE A WAR WITH CLASS "F"
STARTING THIS AFTERNOON.
SO WE DON'T HAVE THE TIME.
- YOU ONLY ATTACKED THOSE IDIOTS
AFTER THEY WERE WEAKENED
FROM THEIR WAR.
IS THAT THE LEGACY
THIS CLASS "A" WANTS TO BRING?
( chuckles )
ALTHOUGH, IT WOULD BE TERRIBLY
EMBARRASSING TO HAVE TO SAY
YOU COULDN'T WIN BECAUSE
YOU WERE TIRED FROM FIGHTING US.
- I HOPE YOU'RE NOT SUGGESTING
WE'LL LOSE TO THEM,
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE STUPID.
OH, FINE.
SUPPOSE WE COULD USE
A WARM-UP BEFORE FIGHTING "F."
IS THAT OKAY, REP?
- GO AHEAD. I DON'T MIND.
- A WARM-UP, HUH? I WOULDN'T
UNDERESTIMATE US IF I WERE YOU.
- WHATEVER.
I'M NOT GOING TO STRESS TOO MUCH
ABOUT FIGHTING AN
AMATEUR TRANNY.
OH.
- ( bell ringing )
- THIS IS A MOCK S-T WAR
AS AGREED.
CLASS "A" AND "B" ARE
BOTH PRESENT AND READY.
BEGIN!
- LET'S NOT WASTE
ANY TIME WITH THEM.
- Students: SUMMON!
- IT SOUNDS LIKE
THEY'VE STARTED.
HIDEYOSHI, IT'S ALL YOU.
- GOT IT.
- ( gasps )
- HOW'S THIS?
DO I LOOK LIKE A GIRL NOW?
- ( moans )
- TOO FAST.
- ( whimpers )
LOOKS LIKE THE ENEMY OF US GIRLS
HAS BEEN A WOMAN ALL ALONG.
- I FEEL WEIRD.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH WAY
I'M SUPPOSED TO SWING.
- WAY TO FLAUNT IT, HIDEYOSHI!
I TOTALLY KNEW YOU
WERE A HOT CHICK
EVER SINCE THE
FIRST TIME WE MET.
- LIKE I KEEP TELLING YOU,
I'M A GUY!
- CLOTHES...
CHANGED TOO QUICK.
- IN DRAMA CLUB YOU HAVE
TO LEARN THE QUICK CHANGE.
NOW YOU SEE IT...
NOW YOU DON'T.
- ( shuddering )
( screams )
- ( bell dings )
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING, DUDE?
- IF YOU WOULD HAVE TOLD ME,
I COULD'VE HAD MY CAMERA READY.
( moans )
- I GUESS HE'S BEEN
TRYING PRETTY HARD
TO SNAP PICS OF YOU
IN THE BUFF.
- NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE FINAL
PIECE OF DECEPTION.
AHH AH-AH-AHH.
AHH.
AH AH.
HELLO, MY NAME'S YUUKO.
MY NAME'S YUUKO.
( higher-pitched )
AHH. HELLO, MY NAME'S YUUKO.
HELLO, MY NAME'S YUUKO.
HELLO, MY NAME'S
YUUKO KINOSHITA!
YOU'RE ALL JUST A BUNCH
OF FILTHY SWINE!
- WHAT?! YOU CAN'T JUST BUST
IN HERE AND START YELLING--
- YOU SHUT YOUR PIE HOLE!
YOU SMELL LIKE A PIG!
- WHAT?!
- I'M YUUKO KINOSHITA
FROM CLASS "A"!
WE'RE TIRED OF YOUR LAME
POOPY-POOP CLASSROOM.
- POOPY-POOP CLASSROOM?
- THE STENCH OF THIS PIGSTY
YOU CALL HOME IS MAKING ME
NAUSEATED TO THE POINT WHERE
I WISH FOR YOUR DESTRUCTION.
YOU DOMESTICATED ANIMALS SHOULD
BE SOILING OUR WORST ROOM.
- YOU SERIOUSLY TRYING TO SAY WE
DESERVE TO BE PUT IN CLASS "F"?
THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE
AS DUMB AS THOSE LOSERS.
- ( normal voice )
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
LUCKY FOR YOU WE'RE GOING
TO BE TOO OCCUPIED
FIGHTING A SUMMONER TEST WAR
WITH CLASS "F" TODAY,
BUT TRUST ME, YOUR RECKONING
APPROACHES. YOU'VE BEEN WARNED!
- THAT DOES IT.
IT'S ON!
- ( bell rings )
- IT'S OVER!
- I THOUGHT IT'D NEVER END.
BORING! LET'S GO!
- YOU WERE THE ONE WHO WANTED
TO FIGHT US SO BAD.
- I'M CLASS "C" REP
YUUKA KOYAMA!
I'M HERE TO CHALLENGE CLASS "A"
TO A MOCK SUMMONER TEST WAR!
- HUH?
- YOU...!
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU!
- UH?
- UH, YUUKA!
THIS IS
A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
- SO IS THIS LIKE
A REGULAR THING?
- IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
LET ME EXPLAIN. OH, YUUKA!
- Fukahara: AND JUST LIKE THAT,
THEIR RELATIONSHIP ENDED
BECAUSE OF CROSS-DRESSING
CONFUSION.
- READY... CHARGE!
DO NOT LEAVE ANYONE STANDING!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH THEM?!
AREN'T THEY AFRAID
OF GETTING KILLED?
- IS EVERYONE READY?
- Class: YEAH!
- MY DEAREST MINAMI, I HOPE YOU
SEE HOW BRAVE I'M BEING FOR YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS. LET'S GET IN
THIS BATTLE FOR CLASS "F"!
- CLASS "A" IS EXHAUSTED
FROM BACK TO BACK BATTLES.
ATTACKING THEM RIGHT NOW
IS THE ONLY CHANCE WE HAVE OF
TAKING THEM DOWN A NOTCH.
- WE DON'T WANT TO OWE
CLASS "F" FOREVER, DO WE?
COME ON, LET'S HIT CLASS "A"
WITH ALL WE'VE GOT!
- ( panting )
WE'RE CLASS "A."
DON'T FORGET IT.
- I'M CLASS "E" REP,
HIROMI NAKABAYASHI.
I'M CHALLENGING YOU
TO A MOCK S-T WAR!
- WHAT'S WRONG? YOU'RE NOT
GONNA CHICKEN OUT ARE YOU?
- YOU GUYS! SO FAR CLASS "E"
IS HOLDING UP AGAINST CLASS "A"!
- AN S-T WAR TAKES
PHYSICAL STRENGTH AND STAMINA.
WHILE CLASS "E" CONSISTS
MAINLY OF ATHLETES,
CLASS "A" IS FULL
OF BRAINIACS AND BOOKWORMS
WHO CAN'T BE BOTHERED
WITH GOING TO THE GYM.
IF THEY BEGIN TO GET TIRED,
THEIR ATTACKS CAN START TO MISS.
REMEMBER, THEIR BATTLE?
IT'S MOCK.
RECOVERY TESTS ARE OUT
OF THE QUESTION.
- I GET IT!
THAT'S THE REASON WE DIDN'T
EXCHANGE CLASSROOM EQUIPMENT
WHEN WE WON.
YOU PLANNED
ON DOING THIS ALL ALONG.
- NOW EVERY ONE OF THEM
OWES US BIG TIME!
- ACCUMULATING LITTLE VICTORIES
CAN REALLY ADD UP.
THERE'S NEVER ONE BIG WAY
TO WIN A BATTLE.
AND BUILDING AN
ADVANTAGE OVER AN ENEMY
DOESN'T HAPPEN OVERNIGHT.
STRATEGY IS THE KEY
TO WINNING THIS THING!
- ( panting )
YOU GUYS LIKE
TO PLAY DIRTY, HUH?!
- SORRY, WHAT ARE YOU
REFERRING TO?
- I KNOW YOU THINK
YOU CAN BEAT US DOWN
BY TURNING THE OTHER
CLASSES AGAINST US.
BUT WE DON'T CARE.
YOU STILL HAVE TO FACE US ALONE.
WE CAN TAKE IT.
- THIS IS ABOUT WHAT I'D EXPECT
FROM CLASS "A"... NEVER SMART
ENOUGH TO CALL IT QUITS.
- Yuuko: ENJOY THAT SMUG LOOK
ON YOUR FACE WHILE YOU CAN.
'CAUSE YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
- HMPH.
- DON'T FORGET...
- ( shudders )
- ...I'LL BE THERE AS WELL.
- MEH.
ALL RIGHT THEN,
LET'S KICK SOME ASS!
- Class: YEAH!
- Fukuhara: BAKA AND TEST.
- Yuuko:
THEY'RE CLASS-"F" IDIOTS.
THEY NEED TO BE
TAKEN DOWN A NOTCH! WE--
- EXCUSE ME. THIS BATTLE
IS NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
- SHOUKO?
- WE'LL HAVE TO USE EVERY OUNCE
OF OUR STRENGTH.
THAT'S ALL.
DON'T SCREW UP.
- Class: YEAH! SUMMON!
- Shouko:
WHAT'S OUR STRATEGY?
- THERE'S A STAIRWAY
BEHIND CLASS "F."
THE MAIN FORCE WILL ATTACK
FROM THE FRONT
WHILE WE SEND SQUADS
ABOVE AND BELOW THEM
TO MAKE THEIR MOVE
FROM BEHIND.
- Class: YEAH!
- LET'S GET THEM!
- HUH?
- UH...
- THEY'RE NOT HERE!
- MAYBE THEY RAN.
- HEY!
WE'RE OVER HERE!
- HUH?
THERE THEY ARE!
- YOU GUYS SHOULD
PROBABLY GET MORE SUN.
YOU'RE LOOKING
KINDA PASTY THERE.
- WHAT A BUNCH OF JERKS!
- ( groans )
- Yuuko: HOW DID THEY...?
EVERYONE!
REGROUP IN THE SCHOOLYARD!
- HERE THEY COME, AKIHISA!
- OKAY!
- GO! OUTSIDE!
HUH?
- WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?!
- DAMN IT!
- ( avatar humming )
( gasps )
- HUH.
- ( yelps, whimpers )
- EVERYONE, FOLLOW ME!
YOU CAN'T GET--
AWAY FROM--
- All: WELCOME!
- HEY... GUYS.
'SUP?
- GET HIM!
- ( yelling )
- ( screaming )
- REMEDIAL CLASS FOR YOU!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THOSE DORKS
ACTUALLY STOPPED
TO CHANGE SHOES BEFORE BATTLING.
- THEY'RE USED TO COMING
AT US FROM EVERYWHERE
BUT NOW THEY'RE
ALL IN ONE PLACE.
- IF WE ATTACK THEM
ONE AT A TIME IN A BIG GROUP
IT WON'T MATTER THAT
THEY'RE CLASS "A" STUDENTS.
WE CAN STILL OVERWHELM THEM.
- HECK YEAH. ON TO THE
NEXT ONE, RIGHT, AKIHISA?
- ALL RIGHT!
- ( screams )
- EVERYONE, MOVE!
- BUNCH OF JERKS!
COME HERE!
( yelps )
- WHAT THE CRAP?
WHY'D YOU PULL DOWN YOUR PANTS?
- ( squeals )
- ( moans )
- NOW ATTACK!
TAKE THEM DOWN
WHILE THEY'RE WORRIED
ABOUT FLAPPIN' IN THE WIND.
- YEAH!
- THAT'S WHAT I LOVE
ABOUT YOUR AVATAR, MAN.
HE'S FASTER THAN
ANYONE ELSE OUT THERE.
- OH YEAH!
ONE REQUEST...
- AND WHAT WOULD
THAT BE, KOUTA?
- THIS TIME...
- UHHH?
- ...CAN WE UNHOOK THEIR
BRAS INSTEAD!
- SO PREDICTABLE.
- HOW DARE YOU ATTACK THEM!
YOU'LL HAVE TO FACE OFF
AGAINST ME.
- OKAY, KOUTA!
LEAVE IT TO ME!
- ( squealing )
- HOLD ON.
YOU'RE NOT... WHAT?
- YOUR PLAN IS A WASTE
OF TIME AGAINST ME.
I DECIDED I WOULDN'T
WEAR A BRA TODAY.
- ( rumbling )
- NO...
- I GUESS WE'LL FINALLY
GET TO SEE WHICH ONE OF US
SHOULD DOMINATE HERE,
MY LITTLE KOUTA.
- A BATTLE OF THE SEXES...
MALE OR FEMALE,
ONLY ONE CAN WIN.
( growls )
- NO, KOUTA!
- I'M OKAY.
I'LL TAKE HER DOWN
ALL BY MYSELF.
- YOSHII! I'D LOVE TO
FACE OFF AGAINST YOU.
- KUBO! RIGHT!
COUNT ME IN.
- ( squeals )
- A LITTLE OVERCONFIDENT,
AREN'T WE?
ALLOW ME...
DEPANTSING BEFORE YOU
BRINGS NO SHAME.
IT FILLS ME WITH LIFE!
NOW I TURN THAT ENERGY
INTO PASSIONATE BLOWS
THAT STRIKE YOUR FLESH WITH
A RESOUNDING FLESHY SOUND.
A MATADOR IN HEAT!
THE MORE YOU HURT ME THE HARDER
I CAN FEEL YOUR LOVE.
YOSHII, WAIT! WE HAVE
TO RISK OUR LIVES TOGETHER
IN A CARNAL EMBRACE
OF SWEATY COMBAT!
- KICK HIM WHILE HE'S DOWN!
- YEAH!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH
OF THIS PLAYING AROUND.
- IT'S TIME FOR ME TO FACE
YUUJI. WHERE IS HE?
- YUUJI'S BUSY.
YOU'LL HAVE TO TAKE US ON.
- Minami: WE'RE CUTTING THEIR
NUMBERS DOWN BIT BY BIT.
- HEY, GUYS!
- Mizuki: AKIHISA!
- LOOKS LIKE THINGS
ARE GOING WELL.
- SURPRISE AND DISTRACTION...
THOSE ARE THE BEST TOOLS
WHEN YOU'RE FIGHTING SOMEONE
WHO CAN TOTALLY KICK YOUR BUTT.
- YOU MEAN US?
- SO THE ONLY WAY
YOU CAN FIGHT US
IS WITH TRAPS AND TRICKS?
IS THAT IT?
- ( laughs )
NO LAW AGAINST TACTICS.
- TRUE.
BUT THE TIME
FOR GAMES IS OVER.
- YUUJI, I'M GOING
TO DEFEAT YOU NOW.
- MY THOUGHTS EXACTLY.
LET'S GO!
- I APPROVE THIS!
- I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
- SUMMON!
- ( all yelling )
- OUR ATTACKS KEEP MISSING!
- WE'VE BEEN PRACTICING A LOT.
- WITH MY IRON BRACELET
WE CAN SUMMON OUR AVATARS
WHENEVER WE WANT.
- WE'VE HAD LOTS OF TIME
TO FIGURE OUT THE BEST WAY
TO CONTROL
OUR AVATARS' MOVEMENTS.
- YOU DON'T USE
YOUR AVATARS EVERY DAY.
AND BECAUSE YOU GUYS ARE TIRED
FROM ALL THE WARS YOU HAD BEFORE
DODGING YOUR ATTACKS
IS EASY!
- GOT A PRETTY BIG MOUTH...
BUT IT ONLY TAKES
ONE HIT TO END IT.
- BRING IT ON, YUUKO.
IT MEANS NOTHING IF YOU CAN'T
HIT... LIKE THIS!
OUR HITS MAY NOT BE
ALL THAT POWERFUL...
BUT THEY SURE CAN
ADD UP OVER TIME.
- BUT YOU CAN'T!
YOU'RE JUST CLASS "F"!
- GUESS WE'VE BEEN HITTING
THE BOOKS A LOT LATELY!
- YEAH, BUT YOU GUYS
ARE STILL SMARTER THAN US.
- IT CAN'T BE.
- IT LOOKS LIKE HELP'S
FINALLY ARRIVED.
- THEY GOT HERE QUICKER
THAN I THOUGHT. AKIHISA!
- RIGHT.
AWAKEN!
- ( grunts )
- ( clangs )
- NONE OF YOU CAN GET THROUGH
HERE TILL WE'RE FINISHED!
- NO! PUSH IT!
( groaning )
- ( squealing )
- Yuuji: YOU GUYS ARE
ON YOUR OWN NOW.
- BIG DEAL. I COULD TAKE
YOU LOSERS ALL BY MYSELF.
- TALK ABOUT CONCEITED.
- I'LL FIGHT YOU!
- YUUJI...
IT'S TIME.
- COME ON!
- THEY'RE JUST
THE STUPID "F" CLASS.
- BUT HOW?
- WE GOT BETTER.
AND NOW YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
- WAY TO GO!
- LET'S FINISH THIS!
( roars )
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- IT'S THE BRACELET!
- DAMN IT.
THE BRACELET SURVIVED
WHEN THE SCHOOL SYSTEM WAS DOWN.
WHY'S IT CRAPPING OUT NOW?
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW?!
- YOU OVERLOADED IT
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN
STUDYING SO MUCH!
- WHAT'S YOUR POINT?!
- THE BRACELET IS DESIGNED
TO BE USED
BY AN IDIOT ONLY!
- ( explosion )
- ( gasps )
- YUUKO!
- SHOUKO!
- HIMEJI, NO!
- ( pants )
- SHOUKO...
- HOLD ON, AKIHISA!
- YEAH.
I GOT YOU.
- ( both scream )
- AKI!
- ( clangs )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?!
- AKIHISA!
- IS YOSHII OKAY?!
PLEASE TELL ME
HE'S NOT UNDER THAT!
- ( growling )
- ( gasps )
- ( roars )
- ( screaming )
- ( panting )
- CLOSE ONE, HUH?
I REALLY DIDN'T THINK
WE WERE GONNA MAKE IT. HUH?
- Mizuki: I WAS SCARED! AKIHISA!
I'VE NEVER BEEN THAT
SCARED IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
( sobbing )
- ( screams )
- IT'S NOT LIKE SHE WAS THE
ONLY ONE SCARED, AKI! COME ON!
- I STILL CAN'T
GET MY PANTS UP.
- THANK GOODNESS.
- ( groans )
FOR A SECOND,
I THOUGHT I'D LOST YOU.
YOU SEE... IT'S JUST...
I THOUGHT... CAN WE JUST
NOT TALK ABOUT IT NOW?
- TAKE THIS!
- ( screams )
- ( stammering ) NO!
- I GOT YOU.
WHAT?!
IT'S NOT OVER?
- CLASS "A," I DECLARE YOU
THE WINNERS.
- All: WHA-AAAAAT!?
- ( theme music playing )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION 13.
FUMIZUKI ACADEMY ADOPTED
A BATTLE SYSTEM
IN WHICH TESTS ARE USED.
WHAT IS THIS BATTLE CALLED?
- Akihisa:
ENTRANCE EXAM WAR.
- Fukuhara: PLEASE DON'T MISTAKE
THE FUNDAMENTALS OF THIS SHOW.
- NEXT TIME! BAKA AND TEST,
SUMMON THE BEAST!
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.