When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Waking up early can certainly pay off.
You get to meet interesting people.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Nonohara!
Come, Nonohara!
Your opponent...
...will be this combat butler,
Kaede Nonohara!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Yes! I will fight using kendo today!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Even in Defeat, Kendo Rage
Your opponent will be my butler,
Kaede Nonohara!
Your butler?!
So, there you have it. Hello.
I am Kaede Nonohara.
I serve as a butler
for the Azumamiya family.
He's a butler, too?!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Now, Nonohara, that's him!
Defeat him right this minute!
Certainly.
But before I do that...
What?!
Ooh! Down, diagonal left, left, and kick!
What is this, the Tornado Whirlwind Kick?!
N-Nonohara, what are you...?
Did I not teach you this, Young Master?
If you are a man, you must take
on even the impossible opponents.
And yet, you turned to me
without having fought him,
seeking to do nothing yourself.
I do not recall raising you...
...to be such a damn weakling!
Can't show you!
H-Himuro, you wouldn't go
to such extremes, right?
Nonohara certainly is as strict as ever.
But is this all right?
He's a butler, and to be acting like that...
What are you saying?
What?
We butlers are not tools
to be used by our masters.
It is not as if we must
merely do as we are told.
There was a time when only the eldest
sons of nobles could become butlers.
It was an exalted occupation.
In other words, that's just how
much responsibility it entails.
A responsibility to steer your master
or mistress in the right direction.
Isn't that why you want to show her
the joy of participating in a sport?
To your spineless, weak-willed
manga freak of a mistress,
who suffers from acute societal withdrawal.
Who are you calling a spineless,
weak-willed manga freak,
who suffers from acute societal withdrawal?!
I-I-I'm sorry, Nonohara!
I get it! I get it already!
No! Today of all days,
you are not getting away with this.
That depraved nature of yours...
I will beat it out of you,
from the very marrow of your bones!
NOOO!
Would you try not to go on such
a rampage in the kendo training hall?
Nonohara?
Miss Katsura...
This is the educational
policy of our household.
May I ask you not to interfere too much?
I'm sorry, but I can't really do that.
I'm the student council president,
so when I see a student in trouble,
I can't not help them.
Miss Katsura...
Even if Azumamiya
is a wimpy, pitiful crybaby,
I just can't not help him.
Huh?
That's the student
council president for you.
A brilliant attack, precisely pulverizing
your opponent's vital points.
I-I haven't attacked any vital points!
I get it. I get it, Nonohara.
Just as you say, being weak is no good!
Young Master?
So as you said, a man has to fight
and carve out his own path, doesn't he?!
Ah! Young Master! So you understand!
Therefore!
Huh?
Fight me, Sanzenin!
What?!
Um, Azumamiya...
Could I get your reasoning
behind that at least?
I promise I won't get mad.
I figured out that it was wrong.
What?
It's just weird for a master
to fight a butler!
Or rather, I have no
chance of winning anyway.
In which case, the right thing would be
for master to fight mistress
and butler to fight butler!
Is he all right?
Nah, I don't think so.
I guess butlers have a tough job
steering their masters
or mistresses in the right direction.
Ah! Young Master! You do me proud!
What?!
So you have finally realized that fact!
I-I guess he's okay with that.
You heard them, Nagi.
What do you want to do?
That's easy for you to ask...
Then I guess there's no helping it.
What?
Then, I'll be Azumamiya's opponent.
What?!
H-Hey, Hinagiku!
With the shape you're in,
you'll kill your arms if you suddenly
start swinging a bamboo sword.
You haven't been training at all.
Besides, even if Azumamiya's
our weakest member,
his lack of skill means his strikes
are all over the place,
so he's dangerous!
With two opponents who don't know how
to handle bamboo swords,
it'd be terrible if you
hurt each other, right?
Uh, wait. Azumamiya?
I understand.
It seems fighting you is a fate
that I cannot avoid.
Unconsciously hitting one
vital point after another...
Hinagiku really is something.
All right!
In that case, I have no choice
but to use this sword
to prove that I am stronger than you!
Here we go, Nonohara!
Yes, Young Master!
Well, so there you have it.
Good luck to us both, Hayate.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I must win this fight and have
the Miss continue with kendo!
Whether they win or lose,
I have no intention of returning
to the kendo team, though.
I found a 4-leaf clover.
(Yotsuba no kuroobaa mitsuketa.)
It was an accident! Help, Nonohara!
(Tamatama-nandesu. Tasukete Nonohara!)
Incidentally, kids at home,
for safety, make sure you wear
head guards during kendo matches.
In anime, we have grown-up reasons,
like animating it is too much work.
We are going the way of Hell and inhumanity.
Wha?!
Does he have an accelerator device
in his back tooth or something?!
H-He's fast!
All I can do is block him!
Here goes!
I never imagined that
I would end up fighting you!
This is truly a trial of love!
But I will defeat you and prove to you
that I am a superior man!
Azumamiya, I have no idea what
you're talking about, but...
Keep up that chatter
and you'll end up biting your tongue.
Head!
That's the student
council president for you.
The Little Master Azumamiya
is no match for her.
Of course not.
There's no way Hinagiku would
lose against a guy like that.
But I wonder how it will go for the butlers.
What?
At the level he's at, will he be
able to win against Nonohara?
You must be joking!
Are you saying Hayate will lose
to a butler like that?!
Now, then...
Hayate, how are you...
Safety Shutter!
Hayate!
What the heck was that?
You have to ask? That was
a super lethal technique, of course.
Huh?!
When you get to be a first-rate butler,
it's only natural that you'd know
a super lethal technique or two.
In fact, what use are you without it?
Are those like the ridiculously
complicated moves,
like Ryuko Ranbu and Hyakki Moshuuken?
Those are from video games!
I had heard that the Sanzenin butler
was a man of ability,
but is this the extent of it?
Amazing! A lethal technique?!
So this is what first-rate
butlers are capable of?!
But if I lose now, the Miss
will never practice kendo again!
Are you all right, Hayate?!
Come, I will finish this with the next move.
B-But how can I come up with a technique
that will exceed his lethal technique?
Do Not Enter
Authorized Personnel Only
Madness!
Besides, in order
to master a lethal technique,
you need to spend a whole episode on it!
To try to master a lethal
technique in such a short time...
Hayate, I believe in you!
I just know that you can come up
with a counter move,
like how Buffaloman turned
the tables on the Kinniku Buster!
I appreciate your faith,
but I'm not a superman...
You can do it!
As a butler...
As a butler, if you overlook
the garbage that is lying around,
you will never get any cleaning done.
The caterpillar alights
on the green foliage!
That's not it at all...
Here I come.
Lethal...
Garbage that's lying around...
Garbage?!
That's it!
Safety Shutter!
Hayate!
No, it's not! That's...
Wha?! Young Master!
Hayate!
Gojuro Kuwabatake
Head!
I lost.
You are not a Sanzenin butler for nothing.
No, not at all. All I did
was catch you a little off guard.
Seeing the Young Master's
pitiful, unconscious face,
I would be unable to resist driving
my lethal technique into him.
It was a good strategy
that caught me emotionally off guard.
What?!
It was just a simple ninja decoy technique.
A simple...? You know how
to use the ninja decoy technique?
Then we shall excuse ourselves now.
When we meet next time,
I would like to see you
with a lethal technique or two.
What?
Then, I will be able to fight
with you a little more seriously.
So?
Are you at least a bit more
interested in kendo now, Nagi?
What?!
W-Well, watching you and Hayate fighting,
I did think it was sort of cool...
Miss!
But I have no intention
of returning to the kendo team.
What?!
I mean, kendo head gear
absolutely stinks of sweat.
I can't believe people actually
exercise wearing something like that!
Besides, in kendo mangas,
the head gear gets in the way
and you can't tell characters
or their expressions apart.
Don't make fun of kendo!
What did you do that for?!
So, it may be impossible to get
Nagi back on the kendo team,
but what about you, Hayate?
What?
As a butler, you need
to master a lethal technique, right?
I wouldn't mind doing the training with you.
Y-Yes, well,
I'm thinking I ought to train
to master a lethal technique, but...
Hayate, hurry up!
Y-Yes, Miss!
Then, I'm sure you'll have
lots of training to do,
but once you've mastered it, show me
your super lethal technique, okay?
C-Certainly.
Was Hinagiku still mad?
Why did she get so mad?
There are some things that are off limits.
She is a long way from
becoming a sports believer...
Thank you very much, Maria.
To what do I owe this formal thanks?
Well, thanks to you, I'm able to
experience high school life again,
which I didn't think I would have anymore.
I see. I'm glad for you.
So, what did you think
of your first day at school?
I used to think that high
school life wasn't necessary
for me to become a first-rate butler,
but I learned a lot about what I need
in order to become a first-rate butler!
I-I see...
Hayate, come here for a sec!
Oh, yes, Miss.
How may I help you, Miss?
A-Ahem.
I-It made me happy
that you fought for me today.
Not at all. I merely did what
was expected of me as a butler.
Besides, I've now learned that as a butler,
I need a lethal technique.
Yes, that's the thing!
What?
I thought about it myself,
but you should get magnetic coating
or open the Hidden Lotus,
or get the Ultra Bracelet
from Ultra Seven or something.
Th-That's a little...
I'm not a White Demon, nor am I
a bushy-browed boy with a bowl cut.
To say nothing of how I have no
friends among the Galactic Surveyors.
Yes, precisely!
Which is why I came to the conclusion
that you ought to master a lethal technique
through the time-honored method, after all.
Huh?
So, in part to thank you for what
you did today, I built you this.
Oh!
Th-This isn't what I think it is, is it?
Yes!
When it comes to lethal techniques,
it's got to be the Tiger's
Cave's special training!
Go give it your best!
You say that, but only those 40
and older would get that reference...
Meow!
Pipopa, meow!
I knew it'd be you...
I'm not dressed like this
because I want to be, either!
Being a pet cat is a tough
position to be in.
Let's get this training started!
You stupid! Quit it!
Don't turn all realistic without warning!
Good! Seeing how he's
started training right away,
he's definitely happy with it!
Sometimes, the mistress's
considerate care can be meddlesome.
At any rate, this is how...
...the poverty-stricken butler's
first day of school came to a close.
As for next time, he will be battling
cleaning, laundry, and cooking.
Hah!
Lethal Frying Pan Flip!
Bravo!
Ramen-lover Mr. Koike's song!
(Ramen daisuki Koike-san no uta.)
If you happen to see Tama, say, "Tama!"
(Tama-tama Tama ni attara "Tama" tte yonde ne!)
Klaus's Hurray for Gluttons!
I'm hungry...
All right, I guess
I'll do some impersonations.
An impression of Jack Bauer.
"It's Season 5!"
An impression of Optimus Prime.
"Autobots, transform!"
An impression of a certain
foreign film time slot.
"Next time on Sunday Foreign Films..."
An impression of "Sure-Fire Funny Stories".
Sure-Fire Funny Stories!
Now, then...
Ah! Solo word chain game!
Klaus... (Kurausu)
Super-car eraser... (Suupaa-kaa keshigomu)
Muluaka... (Muruaka)
Ka...
Klaus's Hurray for Gluttons!
The End
From the Windows of All the World's Trains
From the Windows of All the World's Trains.
Have we arrived at Rio de Janeiro yet?
From the Windows of All the World's Trains
Next time, we will take
the Marunouchi Line from Ogikubo
The End
to the next stop, South Asagaya.
Doggie of the ***
Doggie of the Day.
Our doggie of the day basks comfortably
in the sun in Nerima Ward, Tokyo.
Nerima Ward, Tokyo
Tama the Whitetigerneko
Tama the Whitetigerneko.
No, no, even in the most generous of
terms, you can't call him a doggie!
Hayate!
Hayate! Hayate, let's play!
Q-Quit it!
What game should we play?!
Quit it, Tama!
Um, how about we play...
And that was Tama, who loves to play
with his master, the butler.
Klaus's Exploration of Homes
Today's home is one of the Sanzenin
household's secondary residences.
Nagi Sanzenin - 13 yrs
The family consists of
the young miss, who fully enjoys her life
as an unproductive member of society
Maria the Maid - a fresh-faced 17 yrs
and Maria, the maid, whose hobby
is to make flower arrangements.
And now, let's go right ahead
and take a look.
The pillars are fantastic, aren't they?
I see!
Well, this is truly labor intensive
workmanship. Real materials.
The sense of security that hits you
the moment you walk in the entrance.
Craftsmanship that you
can really appreciate.
Ah! Look at this!
A sunny salon!
And a tasteful selection of leafy plants
placed around the space.
Oh... I have a leafy plant fetish, you see.
What a joy this is!
Beyond the dazzling archway of sunlight,
we arrive at the LDK
condominium of your dreams.
Next time, we will see a home
that enjoys comfortable space,
enveloped in soft light.
Look forward to next time
Please look forward to it.
Yonday
That was fun!
Well, see you again next time.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful,
it'll be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Sign: Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
And Hinagiku is here with us again today.
I'm Hinagiku Katsura. I'm glad to be here.
Hayate, you seem rather happy somehow.
Well, when Hinagiku graces us
with her presence,
I feel like the anime itself
reaches different heights.
I don't sleep holding a doll like that.
Hayate, you are mistaken!
What?
The heroine of this anime, you see...
Yes?
...is you, Hayate!
What?!
Bye-bye!
Preview
What's wrong, Miss?!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
It seems I lack life experience.
It seems I can't win any manga contests,
because I lack life experience.
I-I see...
In that case, I'll do things
I don't normally do
and raise my experience level, too!
What?!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"For You, I Will Mow Them Down
with Every Ounce of My Being!"
I will now treat you
to super VIP hospitality!
For You, I Will Mow Them Down
with Every Ounce of My Being!
Brace yourselves!
If you are not afraid, come at me!