I come to da conclusion dat
I'ma b yo manager today
S'good meetin you all
Who the fuck does he think he is?
You think you some kinda busta?
Das rite, Mike D'Antoni's the best
Izzat so?
You wanna win or wat?
Yeah son
My brain wheels be turnin'
Really?
Tell us mofo
Okay!
Charles Barkley-san!?
I asked muh old man to coach for today
Charles Barkley-san, u a double-crossin nigga?
Nah son
Mike D'Antoni actually can't coach, we'll crush 'em
Orly?
Gud point
They think them niggas got a chance toa beat us
You're right.
Dem young negros don't know who they messin wit
Dis hood juss got crazy
Oh!
Aright!
Mike D'Antoni's Dick
Tony Parker!
Okay!
Wilt Chamberlain!
What?!
2fast4furious!
Tony Parker!
Okay!
Shootin' like dis?
Dwight Howard!
Dwight....So cool
She good son!
I knew dat nigga
when I say a nigga!
Dat nigga like white on rice
when her beast mode gets out!
Dwight Howard some kinda busta
And Tony Parker's movements........
She's got da skills to pay da bills!
LeBron taught dis nigga well
She's been in da gym 9-5 workin' it with Dyrone
You been workin' it with Dyrone?
Niggasaywat?
Pops ain't playin like a nigga
They muthafuckin' skill level's risin'
Pops, what'd you do?
What do you think?
Oh!
6th Year
5th Year
The lil' niglets r pretty good!
Them speedy lil bastards
They good, son!
Tony Parker is gr8
Nigga was in my grill 24/7
Oh!
Mah main bitch got moves
Alright niggas, get out there!
Will do!
We won't lose, either! Let's go!
Yeah!
Dirk-chan!
I got dis!
Yo, Big Daddy!
I got u all figured out
Ohohoho? Niggasaywhat?
It ain't some kinda nigga tactic
Dis be a white-man thing, you know'm'sayin'?
No
You think I'm some kinda busta ass nigga?
Well, you ARE pretty black
Are you really my father?
That aside, look at  Tony Parker go!
Damn she a fine wench!
Das rite
Aight nigga hear me out, in terms of booty
Larry Bird
Dwight Howard
Wilt Chamberlain
Tony Parker
Yao Ming
Izzn't dat order?
ohohoho
Das mah boy!
You ain't never seen no body with as much skillz as dem
Mhmmm
I tell them bitches they get a reward
Reward?!
TL Note: Iced Cream means semen
I say to them, 'u keep dis up, ill gib u muh iced cream'
Mah nigga
U din't force them want ur dick, umade them want dat
Coachin' aint all about playin'
Sometime's ya gotta 'go down' to 'go up' y'hear?
Damn son, ur pop's a real playa
Get outta here nigga!
Tony Parker!
Here!
Tony Parker din't shoot back den
The nigga shootin' wuz
Oh shit!
Damn Dwight Howard, u a crazy nigga
There's a new hood nigga 'round
Oh!
Dirk!
Yo, ketchup
Check out dese skillz
Larry Bird!
Bawlin! Wilt!
6th Year
5th Year
Yo Kobes! Guard dat chink Yao
aight
Kareem! Tony can't shoot for shit
might as well get off 'er
Yeah son!
Dirk, Lebron! ! Get yo cute asses on Wilt and Larry!
Fuck 'em up good!
Mhmmhmmhmm
Oh!
I'll take dat
Chris Paul!
I'ma go all out, u best be preparin'
Kobe, i'ma wreck ur shit
Fuck off
Name
Tony Parker
Date of birth
Class
Height
Bust size
Rival
Hakamada Hinata
(Crazy siscon bitch, like dat
nigga from OreoImo .)
Mutha fuggin' lolizilla
5th Year, Class D
Blood type
Dat nigga got skillz like Charles Barkley!
Not on my hood!
Iz dat a floater?
Kinda, bitch sucks ass at it
Oh!
Kobe Bryant gon' do a floater?
NOOOOOOOOOOOOO
Yo! LeBron!
Oh!
Nice pass!
She ain't doin 1v1?
Dat's sum teamwork!
I fucken lost nigga
Das rite mane, dont u know wat a mutha fuckin' team is?
6th Year
5th Year
Thanks mang!
God fucking DAMN IT
Pussy Nigga get sum real skillz
O ya nigga, you
ain't neva practiced like a rill team?
Get that weak shit outta here
I swear 2 god if I see u niggas here
I'ma fucken bust a cap in yo ass
Dwight I'll fucking shank u
TL Note: Zim-Zam means Flim-Flam
Bitch I'll go Zim-Zam on yo ass
m-muh skittles
You forgot yo iced tea, nigga
Good game, Nee-sama.
Oh!
Damn u niggas no how 2 party!
Tony Parker-chan, A for effort!
I tried
Kobe, next time I'm seein' u'll be da last time
Okay.
We ain't goin' down either
You bitches did a fine ass job, yo
Bawlin'!
Gotta work like a mofo if ya want the skills 2 pay da bills
Mike D'Antoni, will u be coachin' us still?
Nah son, Hawai'i
And I know a nigga who knows a nigga
I bought sum KFC
Whodat?
Dat's Charle's Barkley's top bitch, Anne Donavan
Sup niggas, I'm Anne Donovan
U a hood rat?
I dunno mang
What fine trunk on dat hoe!
Look dat, mmhmmhm
She's a truNigga
We gon' beat dem six-year's aight!
Fuckin Dirk's gettin his TEETH knocked in
I'ma raep dat Chris Paul
And Kobe'll beat me....again
Let's all work hard.
Let's DO this niggas!
Yeah, das rite
nice work Kobe
I know u mean business
but 2night u showed skill
Nah son
TL Note: 'special workout' means sexual harassment
It's cuz of dat special workout we did
When Yao Ming went up for dat floater, I rememberd y'know? I remembered
I don't remember?
Pass on a move to a nigga?
Ya son
I don't got the real skillz yet, though
Yo bitch, how u holdin' up?
S'Good mang! Just rubbed one out
I sho do love elementary girls
Are you a lesbo?
I'll turn you straight in no time
Fuck yeah, misogyny
I ain't neva had fun like dat b4
I'ma wreck those fuk'n young'uns
TL Note: Oh! means Oh!
Oh!
MHM das rite son!
I's hopin' we be on da same team
But life is like a box a chocolates
Yo Kobe, u finish it?
That 'thing' you wanna give Charles Barkley?
Your birfday invitayshun?
S'all finished
I hope the nigga likes it
It's all good man, juss gotta push through
TL Note: Why is she on an elephant?
Oh!
You gon' giv it 2morow?
Yeah!
I'll do my best!
Yo Charlie, I got a birfday partay dis Saturday
All the street thugs r comin'
U in? Or u out?
Like hell I'm minglin' wit u scrubs
Please?
I'll suck your cock if u come
Fuck u and ur sexual deviance, Kobe
Thanks mang! Dis party gon' be off da hook
I should probably get the bitch a present
Nahhhh
Charles Barkey!
Yo Whatup?
Dis nigga say he know's someone
Oh yeah?
My dealer from downtown say he got a lead on that "lowly ball" you want
You even fronten' me?
THAT dealer?
I think thas tha one
I dunno man
Aight, here's his digits, you best call him
Aight
Oh shit nigga
we gon' be rollin' in lolis now
MHM!
I gotta steal me a bike to celebrate
Yo, Anne Donovan, can a nigga hitch a ride?
I wonder if that pill worked
What pill?
The pregnancy one, you know?
Oh...
Yeah, that pill
I been thinkin' night 'n' day 'bout it
u know how long dem tests take?
I dunno, I thought you had a condom?
If I get pregnant b4 marriage...
But i guess it's awwright
if you my baby daddy, Charles
Nah man, dis nigga flies solo
Damn, though
Yo wat?
I don't even know if Kobe
can GET pregnant
Yeah, Pregnancy
Nigga wat?
Tomoka's pregnancy test
I been ponderin' dem lyfe struggles
K-Kobe?!
Yeah dawg, Kobe!
Yeah. Kobe. Yeah.
Dem birf controls
What's wrong?
Nuthin'
Thanks dawg, U saved me
Anne my brotha my nigga,
S'all good
Hakuna Matata!
Kobe! Happy Birfday!
I 'precicate da invitayshun
Mah pleasure, mang
Dis fried chikken's da BOMB
Yep!
Eat the fuckin' food, niggas
I wonder if dat Kobe can twerk
Yeah, Kobe's ass
I'ma teach her well
Kobe's ass....so firm...so juicy
Charles! Sexualize me too!
Oh! I'll twerk too!
Me too! I may not be very good at it, but I'll do my best!
You can't support a family by twerkin' y'know?
Y-Yeah.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thanks for the food.
Yo Charles, what you wanna drink?
Give me the Kool-Aid!
How about sum piss?
Here.
Thanks LeBron!
LeBron-chon?
Fuck me like the monkey I am!
Yo LeBron!
Slide yo bum over, let Kobe get a spin
That's right!
Charles Barkley belongs to Kobe, yo
Oh!
Das rite!
Sorry, Kobe
Help me out, Kareem!
Okay!
Now put her down in front of Charlie's dick
Now call her Margaret Thatcher the Cum Catcher
Um, please cum outside
Fuck that, It's cozy inside of u!
Oh!
LeBron got your disco stick up?
Aren't dicks great, Kobe?
Aight niggas, time for prezents
Yeah!
I agree!
Oh!
Wow, it's so big!
We all chose dis fo u
You best like it
Can I open it?
Of course.
Oooooh. Wooooow. A basketball
I thought u mite like it!
I'll give ya 20 bucks
to stick it up ur ass
Okay?
Wow guys, just what I needed
a fucking basketball
I got sum moar prezents
Dis be from Anne Donovan
oooooh. woooooh. A ribbon
Kobe I'm done
Dat shit's ka-why
Kobe u da cutest
Damn son, Anne's a baller
Dis ones mine
'ere ya go
You better fuckin' like it, cost me $15
TL Note: Seriously, what the fuck is that?
Damn Charles, u know how to
please a nigga!
Thanks dawg!
TL Note: It's not probably the dick.
I gotta nother prezent for ya
Ballin!
I'm pretty good
Black Jesus musta been guidin' tha ball
The floater.
I'll teach it to you as my other present.
We gon' practice 2gether?
That's right, nigga
I'ma show u the 'ins' and 'outs' of ape-hoop
Okay!
Aight practice time
Damn son, we lost hard
Kobe's like a muthafuckin' godsend
Next time we'll be tha top dwags
I'ma beat up Dirk!
Chris Paul got nothin' on me!
Let's get some glocks and shoot 'em up!
The Stupid Boy
Next episode
Yeah!