Girls' Musical Revue Starlight
AFDDDDD
All right!
Home
Run
Challengers Wanted!
Right-handed
I have to hurry!
Hikari-chan is...
waiting!
Where did you go, Aijo-san?!
She was here a moment ago!
Yeah!
She was stretching, right?
She was!
Actress Dressing Room
Then where did she go off to?!
Wanna do Daiba-san's costume first?
Actress Dressing Room
Yeah, let's do that!
Daiba-san!
What's that girl thinking?
They still can't find Karen-han?
Honestly.
On the other hand, Tendo Maya is always ready with two hours to spare.
Like night and day.
Oh, so that's why you're also...
Comment?
You're nothing like the nervous wreck you were last year.
Well, that might be true.
She's the lead after all.
As a result, Tendo Maya's a right mess.
She's always played the lead,
so she doesn't know how to do anything else.
Her acting is the most nuanced of all of us.
She's too attached to having the lead role.
Even today,
I'm sure she'll be going, "We'll bring those two down and get back our lead roles, Saijo Claudine."
Wh-What?
For how much you're complaining...
Oh, please.
Nothing wrong with a bit of competition.
That goes for you too, Kaoruko...
With you and Futaba recently.
In what way?!
Every single day, she shouts "Aim to be the best in the world!" to try to encourage me.
She makes me stretch for a whole hour after bathing!
And she only lets me spend 300 yen on sweets!
She's smothering me!
I mean, I did say I'd become the best in the world,
but I wanted her to treat me more like her rival!
Wh-What is it?
For how much you're complaining...
Oh, please.
What's wrong, Kagura-han?
Your makeup is completely off!
You seem kinda shaky?
Don't tell me...
...you're nervous?
I've never seen Hikari like this before.
It's just like Karen-han said.
Huh?
Hikari-chan!
Sorry I'm late!
Here we go.
Like I thought, even your fingers are cold.
My grandma would often do this for me whenever I was nervous,
like before my baton twirling competitions.
In that case, I'll go with banana therapy.
And I seem to recall there was a pressure point somewhere around here to relieve stress.
Isn't that point for car sickness?
Herbal tea, my personal blend.
The extra chamomile helps you relax.
It smells nice.
And here's some chocolate.
Sweet things help reduce anxiety.
Kaoruko, could you do Hikari's makeup?
I'll take care of her hair.
Huh?
Sure thing. Leave it to me.
U-Um...
Don't move, Kagura-han.
Aijo-san said...
that if you were nervous before your first performance after your hiatus, we should help you calm down.
She did?
I'm sure Karen-chan will be here soon too.
Hikari-chan, sorry I'm late!
Karen.
Hey, where did you go?!
I went to get this.
Here you go, Hikari-chan!
It's your beloved Mr. White, jumbo version!
With this you'll be super fine, right?
Where'd you find this huge thing?
Is this that home run prize?
Yup! I hit a 160 km/h ball and won it!
Wow. I can still only get up to 150.
So this is why you were practicing swings every day?
Ah, you saw me?
But you're still the lead! It's starting soon!
There she is!
Where did you go so close to the performance?
T-To get this...
Don't you understand your role here?!
I-I do!
Come on! We have to get your costume.
Guys!
Now everything will be super fine!
Come on, hurry!
Honestly, what was she thinking so close to the performance?
Personally, I like this atmosphere that only Aijo-san can bring.
Huh?
Yeah, the atmosphere is definitely different from last year.
Well, Karen-han is the lead after all.
Yeah, it's her after all.
Yeah, I'm super fine.
Everyone!
It's finally time for the 100th anniversary of the Seisho Festival.
It's the cul...
Uh, cul...
Cul...
"Culmination."
Yes, that, of one year's hard work!
Everyone, your hands.
We've gone through a lot, and none of it was very easy,
but we'll make it a part of our performance.
The Actor Training Program's class A.
The Play Creator Program's class B.
Actors, stagehands, all of us...
We'll put on the greatest show ever!
So let's shine the brightest we can until the curtain call!
All of us in Seisho Music Academy's 99th generation...
Let's Starlight!