I'm totally not going to forgive him!
W-What happened?
I just remembered something that happened this morning...
What?
Men!
One point!
I'm really no match for you, Yako.
You're certainly not out of shape.
It's just that you lack determination, Kouta.
U-Um, Yako, this is-
Oh, I couldn't find the keys to the women's changing room.
I changed in here today.
We're the only ones assigned to morning practice, anyway.
It's not really a problem.
B-But...!
By the way, how's it going with the Kendo Club?
You joined, right?
I heard that you were in the best four in last year's Kendo tournament.
Hey!
Someone's talking to you! How about you respond a bit?
Why are you looking that way?
Why?!
Are you not embarrassed, Yako?
You're changing in front of a boy...
No, not really.
I'm tired~
One hundred
practise swings!
What's wrong with it?
I don't know about the other guys,
but this is Kouta we're talking about.
Seeing that boring underwear wouldn't make me particularly happy, anyway.
I can't quite ignore that one.
I'm just telling you the truth.
You haven't got a trace of a chest and yet you're wearing that bra thing.
What did you say?!
There's no need for you to wear a bra!
Let me tell you something.
This isn't a "bra thing".
It's a genuine sports bra!
And that's what happened.
A hopeless twerp, isn't he?
Y-Yeah, seems like it.
That's unforgivable!
How could he not know that sports bras are valid bras?!
That's what you're mad about?!
Kouta, don't you underestimate the sports bra!
That's right!
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Seventh Grade Summer Vacation
So why did he have to get all angry?
Hmm...
Maybe he felt awkward...?
Awkward?
Yeah. Komachi-kun told me once before...
I am a man, so I will see underwear in a dirty way.
He said that boys will look at underwear in a dirty way.
That crybaby Kouta would do that?
No way.
Oh, what's the matter?
Ah, yeah... I think that it's just like Nayu-chan said.
He might be your childhood friend,
but he is still a middle school guy.
He's like family to me, though...
Ah, right! How about you try asking Komachi-kun?
Eh? Ask Cat-Eyes?
Yeah! It should be easy to consult Komachi-kun.
I've got pretty comfortable talking to boys,
and it's all thanks to Komachi-kun.
He always gives me great advice for
the Underwear Appreciation Society!
Well, he does seem smart.
What is this feeling?
I felt something around here for a second.
Those of you who want to practice swimming,
use the right-hand lanes, okay?
Oh? Is that Jinguuji-san?
No surprise there; she's great at all sports.
And there's Hayama-san.
I'm pretty sure that she said her goal this summer was to swim 25 metres.
This is yet another page in their youth.
Hmm?
Shiraishi-san.
Sensei...
How comes that you're sitting over here?
Um...
Perhaps you're not feeling well?
No, it's nothing like that.
It's just that my chest kind of
tightens up every now and then.
"Tightens up"?
Is this because my breasts are developing?
Dammit, those girls have messed up my studies for first semester.
To make up for it, I've got to catch up this summer.
I-I'm sorry! Are you all right?
Hayama...
You again?!
When does it happen?
Huh? It's... um...
Dammit, how were you using the kickboard to let it fly off like that?!
Practice with it like you should!
Sorry! I was playing around with it a little, but it just took off...
What are you, a little kid?
Take it.
Thank you.
Wait!
What is it?
There's the summer festival today; You're coming too, right?
Y-Yeah. We're going together as the Underwear Society, right?
Yup! Are you going to wear a yukata too, Komachi-kun?
Keigo-san has one.
It might be a bit big, but we can adjust that with the obi I think.
TL Note: Obi - A yukata's sash.
Okay?
Um... About your question just now...
Perhaps your chest hurts because your heart is developing.
My heart?
People at your age develop physically and emotionally at the same time.
The tightening that you feel might be from that!
I got it, got it.
I'll just come over to your house this evening, then!
Sure!
Bye, then!
Yup!
I still don't understand.
I suppose not.
It's not something that adults understand well, either.
...I guess that you'll search for your own answer, from now on.
Okay.
Thank you very much, Sensei.
She's a middle school student.
It's only natural that she would become interested in boys.
Like I did!
Back then, whenever I caught a glimpse of Senpai,
my chest would tighten up!
Senpai has always been my shining prince.
Mizuno-sensei...
...seems a bit crazy sometimes.
Y-Yeah...
Make-up is difficult to maintain in the summer.
Hmm? Class Representative.
Wait a moment, are you ignoring me?
What's wrong with him?
That's impossible!
There's no way I'm diving into the pool!
You call yourself a man?
But I'm not a man!
Hayama-san...
Haha! So that's what it was.
Y-Yako-chan! You don't need to take them off.
B-But... People don't wear underwear with yukata, right?
It seems like it was a long time ago,
but if you wear your susoyoke over your underwear, it'll be fine.
TL Note: Susoyoke - A yukata's underskirt.
It's fine as long as your underwear line can't be seen.
Here!
Instead of wearing those burdensome things,
wouldn't a T-back be fine?
Now that's another way!
How bold...
Isn't it tight?
But isn't that a bit early for a middle school student?
These days, there are elementary school students who wear them.
It makes a woman wearing a school-issued jersey appear...
Ah, Sensei, try this.
It's a bra for Japanese clothing.
Hmm? My chest appears smoother than usual.
Yes, women like yourself with large breasts will look better with this when wearing a yukata.
Japanese clothing seems to be about hiding curves.
It's always Underwear Society time for her.
As expected of Nayu-chan.
You say that, but she can't put on her own yukata.
Nayu-chan, I'm going to tug on the collar a bit.
Okay.
You're amazing, Haruka-chan.
I'm really impressed!
Oh, don't... It's just something that I practised when I was a kid.
With all you know about underwear, I'd say that you're more impressive.
Maybe...
It's a text.
Kouta?
I'm sure he wants to make up with you!
If that's what he's up to, I guess I'll just have to...
Idiot! Your flat chest doesn't need a bra yet!
That twerp!
Who are you calling an idiot?!
I'll remember this.
I'll beat you to a pulp at the dojo tomorrow!
What's with her?
Did something happen?
Uh...
This is all your fault, Jinguuji-san.
Hey, welcome.
Change in this room, okay?
Right.
Why do I  have to apologise?
It should be obvious.
Come now, calm down you two.
You keep quiet, Sensei.
Okay.
Boisterous, aren't they?
What are you doing?
It would've been best if you'd screamed like
you did just now when you were with Kouta.
But still, you...
You can't know exactly how difficult it is to be seen as the opposite sex,
unless you're someone with experience.
Not being seen as the opposite sex, huh?
Yako-chan...
Maybe that hurt Kouta-kun's feelings.
K-Komachi-kun, what do you think?
I think it could be either, but...
O-Okay...
Nayu-chan, let's try the goldfish fishing.
Oh, sure.
I'm going shopping for a bit.
Go ahead without me.
Amahara-san, you're going to get separated from us!
I'm not a kid, so it won't happen.
These children do have a lot on their minds.
But honestly...
Senpai said that he had to go to work due to an emergency, but...
I wonder if he'll be back in time for the fireworks.
Fireworks... with Senpai?!
It's beautiful...
Yes, but...
...you are far more beautiful.
Um, my breasts are coming out...!
I don't mind.
My hands will replace your bra...
What should I do if that happens?
Huh? What?
Everyone, where are you?
Wow, look at the goldfishes!
They're pretty.
They've got some long tails.
Huh?
Well then, should we give it a try?
Kouta.
It'd be good to give him a proper explanation.
But...
Men are stubborn creatures.
It's hard to make us apologise.
Cat-Eyes?
What was that?
Create an opening for him!
That's right!
This isn't like Yako-chan!
Nayu...
I agree.
Haruka...
He's your childhood friend, isn't he?
That's something you should treasure.
I understand.
Brooding about it all the time doesn't suit me.
Sorry, I'll be back in a moment.
Okay!
It'd be great if they can make up.
It would.
Yeah.
By the way, why are you wearing a mask?
We can't tell you, Hayama-san.
Oi, what're you doing?
It's fine, it's fine!
Everyone, stop wandering off!
Got it!
Sensei, you're great at this.
Amazing!
Thanks to that mask,
Hayama-san couldn't see your naughty-looking face, correct?
You can pay me later, okay?
How much?
Ten thousand yen.
What are you, an old downtown salesman?!
Class Representative, during the summer, girls open themselves up.
Why don't you try and ask Hayama-san out on a date?
Oh no, you're all red again!
You're so easy to tease.
They look like they're getting along well...
I wonder if it's because they're in the same class.
Yeah, that's possible.
Ah, there's a bunch over here, too!
Haruka-chan, which one would you want?
Nayu-chan, doesn't it bother you?
What would?
Um...
Komachi-kun being-
Haruka-chan!
It tickles!
This is terrible...
You'll be fine over here.
I'm sorry, Haruka-chan...
Don't worry.
Let me adjust the bra first.
I'm going to put my hands in a bit.
Okay...
Sorry! Did that hurt?
No.
What's this sound?
It's louder than it was during the fitting.
Please, don't let Nayu-chan hear it!
All right, it's okay.
Hmm? Your underwear seems more mature today.
I don't really understand why,
but I wanted to try and wear underwear like these.
Haruka-chan, perhaps you're in love with someone?
W-Why?
Ah, I remembered that my grandma once said, "Underwear and love are inseparable."
So I was wondering if wearing this underwear meant that you were in love with someone.
Sorry if I'm wrong, though!
What's wrong?
Perhaps the goldfish bit you somewhere?
No, that's not it.
There might really be someone I'm interested in...
Hmm? What did you say just now?
So I, um...
I-
Around here, I wonder...
Hayama-san, Shiraishi-san!
Yes! We're over here!
Here you are!
Here, I brought a towel.
It's a text from Keigo-san.
What! Senpai?
It looks like he's almost here.
Um...!
It'd be best to go and meet him, right?
Like I was saying-
But...
I'll be fine. Sensei's here, too.
Um, then why don't I go-
I'll be right back then!
Do be careful...
What are we doing, coming all the way out here?
I-I'm sorry about this morning...
...showing you that boring underwear.
T-That's not really what I meant...
But with this kind of underwear, you'll-
I don't want to look above your legs!
What are you doing?
Idiot!
Nobody would show their underwear to a boy,
even if he's a childhood friend.
Yako.
I'll be careful from now on.
I'm also sorry... I said some terrible things.
And that text... I wanted to make up with you, but...
It kind of-
It's really just like what Cat-Eyes said.
Now we're even.
From tomorrow on, I won't go easy on you!
Precisely what I wanted!
Ow!
Got ya!
Oh, please.
You should never let your guard down, no matter what!
That's the way of the warrior.
Like I said, above your legs!
Nayu-chan!
Nayu!
Hey! I settled everything with Kouta!
Er, what? Is something wrong?
Hayama-san got lost.
Huh? Oh, Keigo-san.
They must have missed each other.
She's not picking up the phone!
Haruka, don't cry now-
Anyway, we've got to hurry up and search for her!
Yeah.
Can't she do anything by herself?
I apologise. I was supposed to look after her.
No, it's not your fault, Sensei.
It's okay.
I'll stay with you until your mum finds you.
Here! I've got a candied apple.
Nayu!
Nayu-chan!
Bye-bye!
Sorry, everyone.
The fireworks are over, right?
They shoot fireworks every year.
We can come next year, right?
I'll come next year, and the year after that.
Even when we're adults, I want to come to the festival with Nayu-chan and everyone like this.
Everyone...
Here, enough giving people trouble.
Huh? I dropped my phone...!
What?!
Did you notice that just now?
Y-Yeah.
You're going to have to treat us to chocolate bananas now.
Eh? No way!
We did go out of our way to find the lost property for you.
You've made some great friends, Nayu.
You've been selected
for the Kyoto office, right?
Good job. Congrats!
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
I heard that there's a lot of different breast shapes.
Hmm?
Bell shape, plate shape, rocket shape and then squash shape!
Like squashes, hanging?!
I wouldn't want them even if they were big.
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra.
Stick
Out
Your
Chest