July 22nd
(Fifth loop)
Ushio?
Hizuru!
Thank goodness, yer alive again!
Wait, Nezu! Lemme explain!
This is Kofune's daughter who died yesterday!
Yer with the shadows after all!
Stop, Nezu. Don't rush to judgment.
I died?
Yes.
I see.
The world you observe becomes reality.
The four-armed shadow said that?
Yes.
But why do I have that power?
If your right eye belonged to Haine,
then that eye is made of shadows.
You don't remember when it was printed?
I'm not sure,
but probably after I came back to the island.
Every piece fits now.
The one who gave that eye to Ajiro Shinpei was you, Ushio.
M-Me?
How?
Why do you think you failed the last loop?
One thing was acting separately from y'all after defeating Mio's shadow.
This time, we need to work together.
Wha—
I agree.
Hey, Hizuru!
Th-That was...
Nezu, Ushio is an ally.
She was our ally till the end.
Ms. Nagumo. Can ya hear me?
That's why we have that message and Shinpei's right eye here.
I trust you.
Ms. Nagumo...
It's human nature to believe in fiction.
Let it be riches, religion, or stories.
That's why I'm a novelist.
I ain't fictional.
I know.
That's the first time I saw her smile.
So yer risking yer lives too?
Is the four-armed shadow trying to revive Haine?
It fed a lot of people to Haine at the summer festival.
I don't know what happens after that.
Something about an "Ending."
That massive body is Hiruko's true form.
If the shadow at Shiori's feet is just part of that,
it explains why we couldn't kill Shiori no matter what.
But Shiori ain't very strong.
All she can do is walk around.
Hiruko's too weak to leave the cave.
Is this how it works?
Haine is immobile (weak legs)
True form (Hiruko) is weak and immobile
Can walk around as Shiori
Shadow at her feet is a part of the true form
Shiori is at the funeral right now
What's your plan?
I'd like to go underground now and defeat the true form,
but if we can't defeat the four-armed shadow,
it'll end up like the last loop.
Most of all, I'm worried about Mio.
I need a plan fer Sou and his family too.
I want us to capture Shiori at Koba Mart like last time.
Ya can't kill her, though.
What's the point of capturing her?
Yer right,
but I might be able to erase her.
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps god's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Friend
Yeah, I feel better than I did yesterday.
Now that Shin's back.
I see.
Oh, what's wrong, Sou?
I gotta talk to Dad about Ushio.
Leave. I don't have time for that.
Sei!
Don't worry about him.
Make some time fer him, will ya?
Negoro, take care of the rest.
Dad!
Come to my room tonight at 10 o'clock.
I'll spare five minutes.
Thanks, Mom.
Sure, but what's this about?
Nothing much.
Yes.
Ajiro Shinpei is looking into the shadow sickness.
What's going on?
It was Kofune Ushio, and now it's Minakata Hizuru.
Why are people sniffing around now?
It's unlikely a coincidence that Minakata Hizuru returned.
Ushio must've contacted Shinpei.
Is it true that Ushio's shadow wasn't erased and is now missing?
Don't worry.
We'll find and erase it.
First, we'll get to her family.
Turn the entire Kofune family into shadows?
That's the plan.
Including Ajiro Shinpei.
What is it?
Yes, I'll be there.
Hello? My mother needs me. I must go.
Mama's boy.
Today, we have a report from Kinokawa City.
Wakayama's seasonal treats are delicious...
You're up, Ryuunosuke.
Erase Shiori?!
In the last loop, I felt Haine coming in and trying to mess with my head.
So maybe I can reverse that channel.
You can do the same?
I don't get it, but seems like it's worth trying.
Yes.
I'd like to put her down myself, though.
Nezu told me last time.
Ryuunosuke was killed by a shadow 14 years ago.
There were ligature marks on his neck.
Did Haine kill Ryuunosuke?
Yes.
And she was my friend.
What?
Yer friend?
Kofune Mio
Oh, it's Mio.
Answer.
We can talk more later.
I wanna hear Mio's voice! Should I answer?
Dummy!
I was just joking.
She's alive.
Kofune Mio
The phone is vibrating to tell me she's alive.
I won't let Mio die again.
Hello? S-Sorry.
Repeating the previous actions should yield the same result.
In other words, we can capture Haine with Plan B.
Haine is the one who took you and Asako from me.
If it weren't for Haine, Kofune Ushio would still be alive, and so would a lot of other people.
Let's end this, Ryuunosuke.
Roger that, Sis.
Are ya ready?
I was ready before ya were even born.
I'm good to go.
Erase Haine,
whom the four-armed treasures.
Right here and now.
Then we'll save everyone from the end of that summer festival.
Hi! Hizuru!
Hey, did I catch ya... I mean, you at dinner?
I had some gifts to give you.
Oh! Ya shouldn't've!
Come in.
Thank you.
No one's looking.
Ya can come out, Ushio.
Whoopsie.
Ya transform, ya fight. Yer like a Precure.
What? Really?
That was my dream in kindergarten! It finally came true!
Ya know about Precure?
My granddaughter used to like it.
This is great, Shinpei.
Huh?
I realized something amazing!
The nail gun that the four-armed shadow destroyed?
W-Wow.
So this means...
ya can bring the data ya scanned the last time to the next loop!
Ain't it great?
Yes!
Yer amazing, Ushio!
Was that outfit scanned last time too?
It's too bad, though.
I wish this wasn't damaged.
Should be fine.
Since I got the original.
Nezu was holding two guns:
his Nail Gun A and my Nail Gun B.
Ushio rescans the data from Nail Gun B.
Nail gun A
Nail gun B (shadow)
She overwrites the old data, then destroys the original.
I see.
Now I can use Nail Gun B again.
We'll put copying Nail Gun A on hold because Ushio's storage is full.
It's been five minutes since Ryuunosuke went in.
It's about time he tells us to switch to Plan B.
Yes.
Then two minutes later,
Shiori comes down from the balcony.
The third shot misses and she flees,
but I capture her by the green tea soft serve banner.
Finally, I'll erase her.
Yes.
First, we wait to hear from Ryuunosuke.
What the?!
Run... away...
Ms. Nagu—
Wait!
This is no longer... like the... previous July 22nd...
I see you're all together.
Summer Time Rendering
H-Hizuru!
I-It can't be.
Why?
Why are ya here?
You don't play fair, Shinpei.
What?
Did ya forget what I said back then?
"Found ya."
That's a mark.
I can find ya in any world ya go to.
Get it?
I've been following ya.
Didn't our eyes meet at the end of that summer festival?
I can loop too.
I knew y'all would come here because
I read Ryuunosuke's memory last time.
No... That can't be...
We don't need two observers.
It's either Mother...
or you.
The one who survives will decide...
which world is real!
Come on!
I'll kill ya!
Three shots.
What?
The three shots didn't stop him?
No!
If I scan everything, I'll disappear.
But I'll take that one arm!
Whatever.
That was just a greeting, Ajiro Shinpei.
Loop as many times as ya like.
I'll find ya every time and seal that power away in the end.
Haine!
I was careless.
I should've known that the enemy could have the same power as me.
Haine also came from the summer festival.
My carelessness got those two killed.
Ushio! Where's Ushio?!
Right here!
Sorry. Did yer neck hurt?
I tried to make it as quick as possible.
Th-Thank goodness yer here, Ushio.
I'm fine.
Ya did great.
Actually, how're ya doing?
Feeling good?
I thought I could figure out who the four-armed shadow was,
but it was empty.
It has no data in it.
How's it even moving?
I see.
But there was something weird.
It smelled just like Haine.
Can we win against an enemy who can loop?
Haine is most likely just using yer power to loop.
So she'll loop to the same starting point as us.
We're on even footing.
We can win. I know it!
Thanks.
Huh?
This is our house.
Bistro Kofune
Even if the starting point changed, when were we here?
This is odd.
It shouldn't be raining.
July 22nd was sunny.
Hey, hold on.
Wait up fer a sec, Sis.
That's...
No way.
Ms. Nagumo?
Thinking ain't gonna get us anywhere.
Let's follow 'em, Shinpei!
Right.
The setting changed?
Huh? It looks busy today.
Welcome, Hizuru and Ryuunosuke.
I knew it. Those two are Hizuru and her twin Ryuunosuke.
Wh-What's going on?
When I died the first time, something similar happened.
Welcome. Fer two?
Why are ya wearing an apron, Akemi?
It's Bistro Kofune's 10th anniversary,
so everyone came by to eat here today.
Is that right?
Congrats!
Thanks. That's why I'm helping too.
M-Mom?
It's really Akemi. Wow!
So this is the past.
It's 14 years ago.
When I died the first time,
I was with Mio and the same thing happened.
I was at the beach where ya died.
It was the past, and I saw everything.
That must've been Mio's memory.
Then is this Ms. Nagumo's memory?
Dessert's on us today!
Awesome!
I don't like crowds, so I'm going home.
Hey, wait a sec!
Asako? Didn't see ya there.
It's a special day fer Bistro Kofune.
We have to celebrate together.
I don't feel the need to make a fuss to celebrate.
Ya don't need to go home, either!
Don't ya have a heart?
I'm human, so I have a heart. But I want to leave.
Ms. Nagumo really hasn't changed.
Happy 10th anniversary, Bistro Kofune!
You should leave.
Oh, if it ain't Hizuru.
Ya look so happy to see me.
I'm flattered.
Oh, Tooru and Masahito. Thanks.
Those ten years sure went quick.
Alain, your food is always great.
Please don't change.
Hey, did ya look in the mirror?
Ya haven't shaved! Yer hair is messy too.
Oh, sorry. I forgot.
Yer dad came too.
This must've been quite a day.
Yeah, it's amazing.
They're moving.
Their voices. Mannerisms.
That's how they were.
What jobs did yer parents do?
They were nautical archaeologists.
They dove underwater.
Masahito, so yer finally a priest.
Yes. I have a lot to learn, but I'm doing my best.
What's new, Tooru?
I'm thinking about diving to that point I mentioned before.
Hitogashima has so much unique history.
I'm glad I moved here.
The food here's great too.
Hey, Ryuu. Why's Hizuru in a bad mood?
Well, it's actually my fault.
I never should've told ya.
Huh? What is it?
She says she made a friend.
What?
Unbelievable, right?
So I told her she's dreaming.
I told her it was an imaginary friend, and she got mad.
That's just mean.
Actually, I can't believe it either.
Hey.
I'm joking. Sorry, Hizuru, I believe ya.
You're joking?
I don't need a joker to believe me.
Asa didn't mean it like that.
It's fine, Ryuu.
Tell me about yer friend.
We have less than 20 kids at school.
Where'd ya meet someone new?
Mt. Takanosu.
The setting changed again.
Hishigata Clinic
Shinpei, this is...
Yes.
The old Hishigata Clinic.
Was she really here?
Is she from the island?
I think so.
Ya think so?
She's probably not from our time.
You'll get it once ya see her.
She usually appears around now.
There.
The light on the second floor will turn on.
It's gotta be a ghost.
This is too creepy!
I hear there are ghosts here.
I don't see anyone.
M-Maybe she won't come today.
Hizuru, we should head back.
Our parents will be worried.
It'll be dangerous to go back once it gets dark.
I promised to meet her today.
I keep my promises.
Hizuru!
I'll take ya home, Asa.
Sis gets stubborn like that.
It can't be.
Good evening,
Haine.
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time