Thank you for riding with us.
Please watch your step on the way out.
That man is a Shadow.
That message just got a lot more believable.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Orbital Resonance
Welcome back, Shin!
Hey!
Are ya tired from yer long trip?
Shin.
Shin... Shinpei.
Ajiro Shinpei.
It's that boy from earlier.
No, it can't be.
There's a funeral?
Kofune...
Ushio?
Ushio!
Hitogashima Hall
I've arrived at the funeral site at 11:45 AM.
Kofune Ushio passed away.
Funeral
of Kofune.
Ushio..
I know her.
Hizuru?
Why, I don't believe my eyes!
You're Minakata Hizuru, aren't ya?
You sure are perceptive, Karikiri Masahito.
Why, ya've become so pretty!
How many years has it been?
It's been fourteen years.
No reaction when I step on his shadow.
Has it really been that long?
He is not one of them.
Don't tell me this Kofune Ushio is from the Kofune restaurant.
She is. There was an accident on the beach yesterday.
Did ya hear about her from someone?
No.
Oh? Then what're ya doing on the island?
Yer not returning home, are ya?
No. Right now, in Tokyo—
Oh, wait! Lemme guess!
Yer smart, Hizuru, so...
You must've studied to become a teacher or a lawyer.
Maybe even a doctor?
I'm starting to remember why I couldn't stand you on a physical level.
And I still can't!
Oh, yer such a kidder!
Unfortunately, it's the truth!
Alan!
Do ya recognize her?
The truth'll knock yer socks off!
Y'see, before comin' back to the island...
I'm Minakata Hizuru.
Oh, just please let me say it!
What? Hizuru?
Ya mean that Hizuru?
It has been quite some time, Alan.
I was in my second year of middle school,
and I was a frequent patron at the Kofune restaurant.
Alan had two daughters.
Ushio and Mio.
Alan's wife soon passed away after giving birth to Mio.
The customers would look after the children while Alan worked.
Can I read that book?
Keeper at
the Sex Zoo
Taming a Mother
and Daughter
Keeper at
the Sex Zoo
Taming a Mother
and Daughter
This ain't a picture book.
Ya better not read it to her!
Why the heck not? No fair!
Read it, read it, read it, read it, read it!
Why don't I tell ya a special original story of mine?
Huh?
Orangeenal?
Wow, lucky you, Ushio!
This is Hizuru's newest work.
Once upon a time, on a certain island...
Death comes to us all.
Say, Ryuunosuke, it's been fourteen years.
That's a long time.
It's not so strange that someone would die.
What? Ya fell?!
What's the matter?
Mio and Shinpei fell in the ocean, so they'll be a little late.
My word! Perhaps we should wait.
Alan, just now, you said Shinpei?
Yeah. Ya'd already left the island, so ya wouldn't remember him.
He's my best friend's son.
His name's Ajiro Shinpei. I took him in.
Ajiro Shinpei...
About ten years ago, both of his parents died in a boating accident.
They were his only family, so it was pretty hard on him.
Excuse me.
Hizuru.
Well...
The boy who was sitting in front of me in the ferry is Ajiro Shinpei, just like I thought.
I must avoid him. At least for now.
I can't trust a single person.
Please wait, Hizuru.
Strangle marks?
Yes... On Ushio's neck,
there were signs of a struggle as she was strangled...
Wait a second, Alan.
Are the police here incompetent?
The victim would often have the criminal's blood and bits of skin underneath their nails.
Did they check Ushio's nails?
N-No...
This is baffling.
Doesn't this remind you of that time?
When Ryuunosuke died on that day fourteen years ago.
Ryuunosuke!
Haine!
Move aside!
Hey!
Hey. Whaddya think yer doin'?
Let go, idiot!
What's with that? I'll arrest ya, I swear!
Nothing seems amiss at first glance, but...
Who dressed the body?
R-Right... It was a nurse from the Hishigata Clinic.
What are you doing?
That's disrespecting the dead!
Well, Doctor, she's actually a friend of mine.
I don't think I'm the one disrespecting the dead here.
Hizuru...
Hizuru!
Pardon me for making a scene.
Sorry, it's my fault for bringing it up.
Just forget it.
I have one last thing to ask you.
Before Ushio died,
has she mentioned anything about seeing a doppelganger?
Doppel—
Hizuru?
Isokane...
Isokane Asako.
I wanted to contact ya for so long,
but ya didn't even leave us an address or phone number.
Have ya been doing well?
It depends on your definition of "well."
But my heart is still beating, yes.
Ya really haven't changed.
Do ya remember Ushio?
Yes.
Last night at the wake, everyone was sharing stories like "I used to change her diapers."
Why... Why did this happen?
Ushio... She died saving my daughter!
Asako, Ushio was herself until the very end.
I'm sure she's glad Shiori is safe.
Why is it crying?
Your third-rate acting makes the bile rise in my gullet.
You damn Shadow!
Asako!
Asako is most likely dead. She died long ago.
"She died saving my daughter"?
Unforgivable.
Just how much are you planning on insulting Alan and Ushio while wearing Asako's face?!
The three Kobayakawas are all Shadows?
Yes, I am certain.
I confirmed it myself.
So the Shadows are growing in numbers after all.
Apparently, one of them has the ability to produce more Shadows.
That's not like the Shadows I know.
What is happening on this island?
Dunno. I ain't got a clue.
How about this?
Kobayakawa Shiori was drowning not by accident,
but because a Shadow was attacking her.
The Shadow killed and erased her, but it played the part and acted like she was the one that was drowning.
Then she was saved by Kofune Mio.
And after, she killed her parents and replaced them with Shadows.
Are ya crying?
It's gonna snow tomorrow.
As if it would in the peak of summer!
If anything, it will rain.
But the forecast says it's blue skies for tomorrow,
you ignoramus.
What's this?
That is my second cell phone.
Let me know if it rings.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Hitogashima Hall
I'll repeat what I did last time for the funeral.
Relying on just my memories,
I do the same movements, have the same conversations...
Shiori.
I hear ya saw a girl that looked just like ya.
Be careful. That might actually be a monster called a "Shadow."
If ya see that girl again, stay far away.
Got it?
I re-enacted things perfectly.
And as I expected, Kobayakawa Shiori left me alone.
We start the funeral procession just after 1 PM.
Good, you're doing well.
Hey, Shinpei.
Earlier, ya said Shiori saw a Shadow?
Did ya hear that from Mio?
Ah, yeah, back when we were little.
Th-These two!
Shinpei?
Oh, it's just something Mio heard from her grandma when she was a kid.
Sorry about mentioning something so strange.
Let's go, Asako.
Okay.
How could this be...
All three of them are Shadows!
The real ones are already done for.
Where are you, Miss Nagumo?
Time's slipping away!
Shin? Are ya all right?
Yeah...
Mio, can I ask ya something?
Were ya wearing white panties yesterday?
Ya haven't been back in two years and that's the first thing ya ask me?
I desperately need to know what color they were yesterday!
Have ya lost yer marbles, Shin?!
When Mio's Shadow killed me in the second loop,
I happened to have caught a glimpse of them.
Indeed, Shadow Mio was wearing white panties!
But Mio wasn't wearing those this morning.
After the wake last night, I stayed here and changed.
Y-Yeah, I-I think they were white, b-but what of it?
So Mio was copied yesterday?
I can't go back that far.
My only option is to defeat them in order to protect Mio!
I see.
Ya didn't know either, Dad?
Seriously, where'd ya go,
Sis?
At 1:30 PM, Ushio's casket enters the furnace.
Afterwards, we collect the remains and we have lunch in a special room.
I'll have anyone I suspect answer two questions.
Question 1: Have you heard of the shadow sickness?
Ain't that just a spooky story?
I heard about the same thing earlier, actually.
Of course I've heard of it.
My great grandfather was the one who named it.
Well, it's true that a certain form of mental illness has cropped up in localized groups.
Question 2:
Have you seen a well-endowed lady around here?
Oh, you bet your ass I have!
They were G-cups!
Are ya talking about Hizuru?
I don't know her.
Do ya know Hizuru, Shinpei?
She used to come eat at the restaurant all the time.
She did?
I can't believe we never ran into each other!
Say, Shinpei. Would ya mind taking a look at this?
When I asked Hizuru for her contact info, she gave me this.
But I can't make heads or tails of it.
This is Miss Nagumo's contact info!
Th-This is...
'Scuse me, Shinpei. Nature calls.
This code...
In Miss Nagumo's book Drifting Ashore, this appears as an uncrackable code from "The Tamam Shud Case"!
Out of order
Hello? Is this Miss Nagumo?
Who's askin'?
U-Um, my name is Ajiro Shinpei.
This isn't Miss Nagumo.
And you?
I see. That was faster than I expected.
The name's Nezu. Nezu Ginjirou.
I'm an acquaintance of Miss Nagumo's.
How'd ya find this number?
She gave my Alan a secret code, and I...
And ya solved that?
Y-Yes.
A similar code appeared in one of her books.
Yer at the crematorium right now, ain't ya?
Y-Yes, I am.
Leave and go back down to the funeral hall.
Alone!
I'll contact you again.
Um, hello?! Hello—
Out of order
Hm? It's open—
Wha—
Hello? Nezu, I-I'm here.
Connected
Um, what do I do now?
Don't move.
Connected
Just stand perfectly still, like a scarecrow.
This'll be over soon.
Huh?
What?
The time, the place...
If you were going to attack, it'd be when Alan was alone.
I'd calculated for 17 different scenarios.
But the bathroom? Really?
Why're ya here? This is the mens'—
So normal.
I just heard a huge boom from the next stall!
Yikes! What made that sound?
Nezu Ginjirou
I finally get to meet Miss Nagumo!
Nezu
Hizuru will meet you at the ruins of Battery 4
If you can really go back,
then find me and say your name.
I swear I'll save you.
If I can get her help from the very start, we can win!
We can defeat Mio's Shadow!
How does she know about the Shadows, anyway?
I have so many questions.
So yer Nezu?
Huh? Have we met before?
Oh, right.
So, uh, you know about the Shadows as well?
Ya got questions, eh?
Well, yer gonna be answering mine first.
The keys to solving that code were two phrases.
The author, Nagumo Ryuunosuke, and her real name.
But she hasn't told anyone but me that she's actually Nagumo Ryuunosuke.
Which means, no one else could call the phone unless a Shadow that copied Hizuru is out there.
But you are human.
Miss Nagumo!
P-Please make it out to Ajiro Shinpei.
That's A-j-i-r-o S-h-i-n-p-e-i.
Um, basically, I'm a fan!
I even have all your books!
I told her my name, just like she instructed.
I don't even need to take a step back to see how much of a creep I come across as!
Now, what happens next?
It seems in this situation,
you're not normal.
Lord Byron once said, "Truth is stranger than fiction."
I'm not one for fantasy, but even after meditating upon every possibility,
To Ajiro Shinpei
Nagumo Ryuunosuke
I arrived at this decision.
To Ajiro Shinpei
Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Um... Thank you very much.
If what I'm about to say is false, please correct me.
You didn't know who I was this morning on the ferry.
There's no way for you to know my identity, aside from me revealing myself.
Which I haven't done yet.
To Ajiro Shinpei
Nagumo Ryuunosuke
This isn't the first time you've experienced today—July 22nd.
One could say you've repeated it multiple times.
Which means you must be a time traveler.
Yes.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Enemy