Why?
I...
Satomi Kou
What? I'm bus—
Huh? What's with that look on your face?
Was it really that big of a shock? It must've been.
He was... a friend to you, wasn't he?
Just kidding.
I can't actually see you right now.
Did I get you?
Chinatsu-chan, are you sure you can handle this?
Because next on my list...
I told you there's no turning back anymore, didn't I?
Born into memories everything is given life
born memory subete ga umare
Everything is erased, everything is overcome
subete wo keshite subete wo koete
The memories that make me whole scream throughout my head
watashi wo kumitateru kioku sakendeiru wa atama no naka
find my real
Where did it all begin to change?
doko kara kawatta no
The things I believed in have all become lost
shinjiteta mono maigo ni natta
Even if the seasons turn
kisetsu wa sugitemo
The place from my memories remains forever unchanging
omoide no basho wa ano koro no mama na no ni
Pull me from this maze of fear
nazo fuan oshiete
Should I continue on?
susunde mo ii no
I'm searching for my past and future
kako mo mirai mo sagashiteru
Dive into memories, if only I could see you
dive memory aetara ii ne
Smiling like you did back then for our promise
ano hi no egao ano yakusoku
In these endlessly repeating days
kurikaesu nichijou no naka
Distorted by the ever-present static
noizu ni makare yugandeku
I still don't know, I still want to, I still can't lose it
mada wakaranai mada motometai mada nakusenai
Flip open the card of your broken heart
oreta mune no kaado wo hiraki
Lost in the storage of my memories
samayou no kioku no naka
find my real
The Two
Suzuko and Chinatsu
Welcome.
Come on in. Hanna's in her room.
Thanks for having me.
Hanna-chan? It's me, Suzuko.
I made you chocolate banana muffins. You liked them, right?
Eat them whenever you're up to it. I'll come back again.
Hanna-chan!
Admiration. Chocolate banana is divine.
Gratitude.
You don't need to thank me. It's only natural for an apprentice to worry about her master.
Pathetic.
I'm a failure as a master.
You sure are.
Warning. Allow me to advise you.
Would you consider refraining from battle and waiting until the ninety day limit is up?
Even if you win, I'm sure it wouldn't make you happy.
That may be true. But this whole thing hasn't been all bad.
For one, I never would've met you otherwise.
Agreement. That much is true.
I... simply don't wish for you
to suffer the same feelings as me.
You're the one who told me, Hanna-chan.
If I have something to regain,
then I need to be serious.
And I do have something.
Curse. Is that not an attempt to bring back the past?
It's not the past.
What I want is the present, and where we go from here.
Acknowledgment.
Thanks.
Re
birth
Hanna?
Did Suzuko-chan leave?
Yes.
I finally understand.
Progress.
From now on, I'll live for the future.
Oh yeah?
Yeah!
Hey, Ril.
Do you have anything you want to protect?
I do.
Right now, I want to protect you.
Thank you.
Shirai-san?
Don't tell me...
Dona-san?
No way...
Satomi provoked him over Chinatsu-chan.
There's something I forgot to say.
Don't forget your true wish, no matter what.
Also, I really did... have feelings for...
You know what, I'll see you later.
Let's stop, Shou-chan.
Stop what?
You only have one coin left!
So what?
"So what"? If you lose again, you'll completely disappear!
You can't hide it from me!
You're pretty talkative today.
It's all for Chinatsu-chan's sake.
You're battling for her, right? Why?!
I can't leave her alone.
Not when Morikawa's acting like that.
I want her to be like she used to.
Bright and cheerful and always smiling.
Shou-chan...
I can't believe it...
In the end, everything went the way Satomi had designed.
Then, Shirai-san is...
Please!
Shou-chan's...
Grant Shou-chan's final wish...
Please...
Go file the new contracts.
Get on it.
Here.
Um...
I'm telling you to do it!
Get your ass moving!
Contract
Satomi Kou
Shirai Shouhei
You seem like you're enjoying yourself, Kou.
Can you blame me?
She makes such delightful expressions.
You know,
I'm thinking of picking up soccer again.
I wanted to bring you here to tell you that.
Such a shame about Shirai-kun, huh?
If you'd known it would end up like this,
maybe you could've done him a few favors along the way.
But you understand now.
It's all in vain unless you win.
And he lost, wretchedly so.
Your own limit should be approaching soon,
so you might as well settle things...
Once and for all.
I know that.
Are you...
Scared?
About what?
I don't mind, if this is what you want from me.
Chii-chan, are you okay?
That's right, this is what I wanted.
To become my true self
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
I will erase
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Shirai Shouhei
Number
Email
Delete
everything unnecessary.
Chii-chan.
Chii-chan
Calling
Slide to answer
We'll be fine if we're together.
Hello.
Tomorrow morning.
I'll be waiting at that park.
Okay.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
I'm about to have dinner.
What about you?
I already ate.
I see...
Chii-chan
Call ended
Then would you like some tea?
We haven't really talked much lately.
And, so, I'd like to spend some time with you.
Sounds good.
This looks great!
Dad's work is going well,
so we decided to treat ourselves.
Chinatsu.
As it is, we shouldn't have any trouble
affording your first choice university.
Thank you.
I'm off.
I will become my true self.
You'll be fine. Chii-chan is strong.
I'm with you too.
Let's grant your wish.
Chii-chan.
Why did you choose this place?
You love this park.
I decided on a whim to let you see it
one last time before you lose your memories.
I see.
This park is full of irreplaceable memories.
For both of us.
I've battled to discard those.
I will fight to protect them.
Open!
Ril, Grow.
Mel, Grow.
I use the Seasoning Arts to banish two opposing cards.
Ril!
I'm fine.
Ril, Grow.
I place SIGNI and end my turn.
Are you trying to avoid my counter when I use Berserk?
Looks like you learned to think for yourself.
I told you I would become strong.
It doesn't matter. If you won't give me Ener, I'll just make some myself.
Spell: Three Swords.
Attack with all SIGNI!
Ril!
Keep going, Suzu!
I will protect your wish!
Your LRIG is such an eyesore.
She's just like...
Hey, why won't you just disappear?
Set me free.
Even if I disappear, it won't make you free!
You'll just lose yourself!
It doesn't matter if you care about those memories or not!
It won't change the fact that I'm still a part of you!
I thought that I'd still be myself even if I lost part of my memory...
But that was wrong. I can't accept it.
What would you know?!
You have no idea who I truly am!
No matter what you say,
I will win and discard you!
I'll bring you back!
Even if you forget, so long as I still remember,
no matter how many times it takes, I'll bring you back!
I swear that I will never lose!
Why... Why do you care about me that much?
Just leave me be!
There's no way I could leave you!
I can't just leave you alone.
I never stopped thinking about you,
even when we were apart!
I really did... have feelings for...
Shut up!
It's too late! I can't turn back anymore!
Coin Bet!
Berserk.
Attack... with Saizou.
End of Heart.
Zhurong... attack.
I counter and banish it!
Zhang Jiao... attack.
Knife Bat!
Inside Out!
Ril...
Ril!
It's over, Suzu.
I am... the manifestation... of Suzu's emotions.
I'll grant Suzu's wish, no matter what!
Don't forget your true wish, no matter what.
My true... wish.
Light is such a funny thing.
I hated it.
The light that casts shadows.
Even so,
when I yearned for the light,
I hated myself.
That feeling of greed...
I hated it.
My self who couldn't do anything without you...
Don't go... don't leave me...
If I can lose them, then I never should've made them!
That's a lie.
The truth is, I wanted to be with you forever.
What I wanted to discard was myself.
I was the one restraining you.
I'm sorry... Ril...
Berserk was canceled?
Chii-chan.
That's enough...
I've had enough!
I don't want this...
I don't want to lose anything else!
Help...
Help me, Suzu...
Ril!
Arts: Perfected Firedrake!
Chii-chan...
Chii-chan!
Suzu, I'm sorry.
I... don't deserve to be your ideal.
Whenever you were with other people,
I called out to you on purpose.
I pretended I needed your help
and lead you away on purpose.
I wanted you to look only at me!
I didn't want anyone else to have you!
That cheerful Suzu was my ideal...
I always...
I always wanted to be true friends!
So did I.
That's why I swallowed my fear and spoke to you.
I'm Homura Suzuko.
What's your name?
Suzu...
Sorry... I'm so sorry!
Thank goodness.
I was so worried that I'd lose you.
I was scared... I was so scared!
Sorry... I'm sorry...
Suzuko?
What's with that sappy crap?
Apologizing in the arms of someone who beat you, with tears running down your face?
That's just bullshit.
Weren't you going to settle things?
But look at you now.
Want me to finish her off?
Weak, little Chii-chan...
Well, whatever. I never cared which of you would win.
I only wanted to see you drown in despair together.
Are you mad? Do you want to shut me up?
Then drop that loser,
and come have some fun with me, Suzuko-chan.
Flashback to a faint memory just outside my consciousness
flashback bouyaketa mama no kasuka na kioku
It's always kept me going until this very day
zutto tsunaidekureta kyou kono hi made
Someone pulls back their tiny hand
chiisana te wo hiku no ga
But I can no longer remember who
dareka omoidasenai
Before I lose the something resounding in my heart, I will fight
mune ni hibiku nanika wo ushinau sono mae ni tatakau
I don't want to erase everything that makes me whole
keshitakunai watashi wo tsukuriageta mono
So I will reclaim it in my heart
ima kokoro ni torimodoshite
I'm undeletable and nobody else
keseyashinai hoka no dare ni mo
Can change who I truly am
hontou no jibun wa kawaranai kara
And finally I can remember
ima nara omoidaseru
Be sure to satisfy me, Suzuko-chan.
Memories aren't rubbish.
Come on, already.
I will fight for what I believe in.
This is our battle!
Thank you.
We'll always be friends.
Daybreak
Next time: Daybreak.