Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start!
When watching Kaleido Star,
please keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I came to America all by myself
with aspirations of joining Kaleido Stage.
Everything is new to me,
but I'm doing my best in the spirit
of "try it rather than think about it."
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, that'll be super lucky.
And if I'm gonna do it, I just
gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! That's me.
Well, well, well, does everyone
know the story of "The Little Mermaid"?
It's a really wonderful story.
This time, I attempt to get the leading part,
but I make a mistake and
have a really scary experience.
And I can't get it out of my mind.
Oh! I've really found myself
in a pinch this time! I have! I have!
What is it that you want to do?
Every time I was asked that
I looked up at the blue sky
The answer is only in my heart
I don't easily say the
words that are really important
I start running towards
the place the light points to
There's so much in my heart
that I want to embrace, I could cry
I'll keep painting my way,
I promise, take it someday
Beyond the horizon,
where the white clouds drift
The future is lined up and
it'll always be there by my side
Dad!
I brought you lunch!
Thank you, Marion.
Everyone, it's time for lunch!
Yeah!
Why don't we sit here today?
Well, I'm going to read you the
story of "The Little Mermaid" today.
"Once upon a time,
there was a very beautiful mermaid princess."
"My Amazing Challenge For the Lead Role."
Thank you for coming to
see us at Kaleido Stage today.
Due to stage equipment maintenance,
the performance of Cinderella
will be suspended for two weeks.
We look forward to when
you come visit us again.
Great work, everyone!
Finally, the vacation that we've
dreamed of will start tomorrow.
Do the two of you have any plans?
Practice.
To be ready for the audition.
Huh?
There's going to be an audition
on the last day of vacation...
Wait, you don't know?
No, I don't. No, I don't.
--Why am I the only one who doesn't know?!
--It should be posted on
the dorm bulletin board.
Oh! So, what's posted?
Since last summer's
performance was so popular,
they're going to stage it again.
"The Little Mermaid"!
--No way!
--Oops.
What?
I've only seen this on video!
Oh, I can't believe this! Really?!
I'll get to see the real thing!
I'm so happy!
It's a real tear jerker, you know?
Especially at the end,
when the Little Mermaid
jumps off the ship into the ocean!
It'll make you cry a river no
matter how many times you see it!
There, there.
Since Miss Layla is going to try
a new swing maneuver this time,
the cast auditions seem mainly for
people who are good on swings too.
Really?
This is your chance, Sora!
What?
It's your specialty, after all.
Is it my specialty?
Sora, you're the one who
mastered the Golden Phoenix.
Well...
You could get the
supporting role right off the bat!
You think so?
Maybe I will make a serious effort.
You could get a raise while you're at it!
Really?!
You'll get chauffeured to
and from work every day!
I don't know if I should be spoiled so much.
I can't believe her.
She's already acting like
she's passed the audition.
It's like, she makes me sick.
"So, in order to get a human
body, the Little Mermaid..."
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well...
How is the preparation
for the production going?
Everything is going smoothly.
I see, very good.
Then, since I'm busy,
I want to see the performance right now.
The audition is scheduled
to be held in two weeks.
Quiet!
I want to see it right this minute!
If I can't see it right now,
I will call the whole thing off!
No, if you would settle for only my
scene, I could show you right away.
Are you displeased with me for some reason?
No, you're a wonderful star
and I'm very aware of that.
However, don't you have
any stars other than Layla?
He's so nasty.
He's like the sea witch
in the Little Mermaid.
Well, how about it?
This will be a special
audition in front of a client.
If you successfully complete this audition,
you will be given the part of
the Little Mermaid on the spot,
and you will play the
leading role in this production.
However, if you fall, the Little Mermaid
performance will be cancelled.
Is there anybody who will
accept this challenge even then?
He said if she falls,
the show will be cancelled.
It sounds like, super bad and risky.
Isn't there anybody
who'll accept this challenge?
Why don't you take this opportunity
to try for the part of the Little Mermaid?
It's the leading part. The leading part!
What? The leading part, huh?
Oh-ho...
Oh? What's going on?
That settles it then.
Sora, play the part of the
Little Mermaid right this minute.
What?!
But isn't the Little
Mermaid Miss Layla's role?
So what?
You said you were good
at swings just a while ago.
You sounded like, so confident.
Really...
And you said if you got the part,
you'd get them to raise
your pay by ten times.
What?!
And buy a tropical island...
I see.
If you've planned that far ahead,
I'll really have you play
the part of the Little Mermaid.
What?!
Is everything ready?
Yes, sir.
Hey, Ken, what do I need to do?
Don't worry, Sora.
I'll explain the details of
the performance to you now.
From where you're standing now,
you just need to use that swing
to jump to the swing on the other side.
When I press the buzzer, jump out there.
Then your timing will match with the
swing on the other side of the waterfall.
What? What waterfall?
What?
What?!
Well, well...
Okay, begin!
Yes, sir.
We're starting.
Don't worry.
I'm sure you'll be able to pull it off, Sora.
Well, you tell me not to worry, but...
I can't see the other side because
of the waterfall. What am I gonna do?
No, let's just give it a try
instead of thinking about it!
Sora!
No, too late! Come back!
Good, I can do it.
What?
What? I didn't make it?
It's over...
Good, you're awake.
You saved me?
Yes.
From the look of it, you should be fine now.
Oh, yes. Thank you.
Then I'll be leaving now.
What?
Excuse me, where are you going?
Our castle, Kaleido Stage.
Then, me too.
You cannot come this way.
Why...
Huh?
What?
You cannot come to our world.
You should go back to
the world that you belong to.
Oh, wait!
Please wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait...
Oh, she came to.
Hey, you seem okay!
Thank goodness.
I still have them!
What are you talking about?
Ouch! Ouch...
Come on, you should still take it easy.
They said that you dislocated
your shoulder just a little.
But if Mr. Yuri hadn't been there,
you would've suffered a lot
more than a dislocated shoulder.
What?
Yuri rescued you in the nick of time.
I'd never seen real mouth-to-mouth
resuscitation before.
So that wasn't a dream.
And then, and then, when Ken saw that...
Oh, yeah, Ken got...
Yeah, Ken got...
What?
Sora, what are you doing?!
Don't "What?" me!
Don't push yourself, Sora!
The doctor still doesn't want
you to do anything, remember?!
I'll be fine.
If I don't show Mr. Kenneth
that I can do this soon,
they'll cancel the show.
Huh?
Huh? What's wrong?
Huh? What? Huh?
Something's wrong... Huh? What?
Wha...
Sora. Sora. Can you hear me, Sora?
Huh? What just...
Sora, you have to take it easy.
Right. I'm sorry.
I think today's not a good day for me.
I'll go home and rest for today.
Wait, Sora.
What?
I want you to be honest with me.
Sora, could it be that you're afraid?
Is that it after all?
Sora, if you're afraid...
Leave me alone!
Don't mind me!
Please stop her right away.
Oh, Sora...
What?
Sora...
What happened?
So, how was it?
For the time being, I was able to
talk him into giving us another chance.
The rest is up to the performer.
Sora!
Hey, Sora!
The dining room will be closing soon!
If you don't eat,
you won't be able to heal quickly.
Please leave me alone.
How truly pitiful.
Oh, be quiet.
Why did you skip today's practice?
I'm injured, you know.
Why won't you come out of there?
My shoulder hurts.
--Why?
--Who cares anyway? Just leave me alone.
So, it is the same as that other time.
That other time?
Once, there was a man
who was able to see me.
That man also became
unable to jump due to injuries,
for he was not able to overcome
the fear of when he injured himself.
Was he able to appear on stage?
Yes.
How?!
How did he overcome his fear?!
I see. So as I thought, your shoulder
injury has nothing to do with this.
Never mind that!
How did he do it?! Answer me!
This is...?
The Hanged Man.
Sora,
if you want to change your current situation,
you cannot just keep running away.
I'm not running...
The man gradually became unable to see me.
Oh...
This is...?
Sora.
Ken...
Just like I thought.
I knew you'd come, Sora.
Ken, I'm sorry about what I said earlier.
Don't worry about it.
It didn't bother me at all.
Anyway, you're going to do it, right?
Practice, I mean.
What?
I got things ready because
I figured you'd be here.
Got things ready... You mean this?
Yeah, that's right.
For your practice.
For me?
Yeah.
I'm sorry I wasn't being
considerate of your feelings earlier.
Oh, no. I should apologize to you too.
But don't you think these swings
are too low to provide good practice?
No, I want you to gradually build your
successes starting from a low height
and get you to picture
the perfect image of yourself.
The perfect image?
That's right.
Do it over and over
until the image of falling
is erased from your mind.
But still, don't you think
this height is just too easy?
Well, we'll see about that.
What?!
I can't do something like this, Ken!
This is all for the sake
of your image of success.
Still...
I'll coordinate the timing,
so jump when I give you the signal.
Are you ready, Sora? Here we go.
Forget about the time you made a mistake,
and just focus on
synchronizing with the sound.
Okay.
Ready? One, two, three!
Are you all right, Sora?
No. I'm sorry, Ken.
I can't do this!
Sora, be strong!
I can't do this.
Sora, look at me!
Please trust me!
I'll lead you to success, I promise!
I can't rescue you heroically like Yuri did,
but I'll make sure to
make you the Little Mermaid!
Sora...
Okay. Thank you, Ken.
Then, one more time.
Okay.
Well...
He is a Kung Fu Master, Master Linn.
Master knows a breathing
technique for mental concentration,
so you should learn it
and improve your focus.
What?!
Don't whine, just do it.
Look, Master Linn is
saying he wants to test you.
What?
He says if you can keep up with him,
he'll teach you the technique
for mental concentration.
Oh, okay.
Please don't be too hard on me.
Oh, yes.
Huh?
He says you passed the test.
What? Already?
That's right.
Take a deep breath and calm your emotions.
I'm okay.
One more time...
I can't do it right.
That's not true at all.
Master Linn says that he is
very satisfied with your progress.
What?
That is the technique
of mental concentration!
You're amazing, Sora!
I can't believe he's going
to teach you that technique!
Come on, what are you doing?!
Sora, hurry up and do what he's doing!
Oh, yes!
Be one with nature and
resign yourself to nature.
Then you will be the wind,
the water, and the earth.
Abandon yourself and be
one with your surroundings.
This is indeed the secret
of mental concentration.
Sora!
Resign myself to nature...
You want to take a little break?
No, I'm fine.
I think I'm almost there.
Well, I think you should
be ready to do this soon.
But maybe I should do a
little more rehabilitation before...
The doctor's told me that you're
already completely recovered.
Don't tell me you're afraid.
If you're saying that you can't jump,
there's no point in you being here.
There's no point in you being here.
Calm down, Sora.
You don't need to worry.
Why?
Why can you say that?
You've worked hard all this time practicing!
It was a practice.
That's why I could do it!
I probably won't be able to do
anything when it really counts.
I can't jump anymore!
I'll probably...
I'll probably never jump again!
So, you're never going to
jump for the rest of your life?!
I still remember how I felt when I learned
that I would never be able to
jump because of my weak heart.
I can't jump even if I want to.
And you're the same now, Sora.
But the truth is you can jump.
When you were practicing the Golden Phoenix,
I wondered how you could jump so happily
when the practice was so tough.
There are many good
performers at Kaleido Stage,
but you're the first one who made me wish
that I could jump like that too.
Remember how it feels
when you're jumping, Sora.
How it feels when I'm jumping...
Don't give up, Sora.
I don't want my Sora to
be defeated by her fears.
Sora...
Thank you, Ken.
Sora?!
A blindfold? Will she be all right?
Of course.
Please begin.
Yes, sir.
Here we go, Sora.
Are you ready?
Yup!
Go, Sora. One, two, three!
If you're saying that you can't jump,
there's no point in you being here.
Be one with nature and
resign yourself to nature.
Be one with your surroundings.
Then, you shall be the sky,
just as you were named.
Wonderful!
You did it, Sora.
You really are the most radiant
person at this Kaleido Stage.
When you're lonely, what do you do?
Never say you don't get any of that
Sleep, play, flip through a magazine
When you're lonely, you're lonely
Like always, invisible vibes fly
around the city today, tulututu
Anyway, the vector of my heart
is talking about so many reasons
I want to be free and fly the skies
But I don't have space to spread my wings
But I have faith
There is a future yet to be shaped
And there's a me that I want to shape
Even if I'm sad, even if it's a mistake
I'll do what I want and
fly towards the freedom
"Next Kaleido Star"
Go, Sora! You're the leading lady!
And so, this is my first leading role.
I tried performing it
perfectly like Miss Layla, but...
Fewer people are coming to see us...
And the sponsor doesn't like it either.
Oh, what in the world am
I doing wrong? What? What?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Facing An Amazing Wall."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...