Thanks for packing me lunch, Sis. You could make this a habit.
This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
But why the weird ethnic food?
Oreki! Thanks for looking after the stand!
Sure.
We won, man!
It was a close call though.
Congratulations.
Thank you! We couldn't have done it without you, Oreki!
No... Oh well.
But I never would've thought you'd do something like that.
In fact, you're the last person on Earth I'd expect that from.
The whole festival atmosphere got to me.
Never again.
That reminds me, Oreki.
There's something I'd like you to see.
The cooking club has lost their ladle.
Juumonji
Look at this.
The cooking club has lost their ladle.
Juumonji
Today is a real mess, but I get over it with a sigh
You get the idea, right?
What do you wanna do?
You act as if nothing happened
As if your heart didn't ache
It almost feels encouraging,
the way you're rushing me
Hold it and let it overflow
We're all imperfect
I can't see it well in the light,
but if we can change our future selves
Wake up and run
Go and surpass the mirage
Try to change and run
with the discomfort of freedom
We can reach that shining light
Follow it into the present
Don't hesitate to act
Deep or quick, just keep breathing
Hyouka
The Juumonji Incident
So your ladle got stolen?
Yeah. And only ours.
Somone must have lot of free time.
And it's not just the Cooking Club!
It happened to the Go Club and the A Capella Choir as well!
And the Fortune Teller Club! They got a note just like that!
A claim of responsibility...
Someone must have an awful lot of free time.
And this spice smells just...
Oreki!
This is bad!
Real bad!
It's coming...
Chitanda Eru's curiosity...
is going up in flames!
Who would do this during the culture fair, of all times?
Why would they use the Juumonji family name?
Why would they steal one item after another?
I can't stop think—
We don't have time for that.
The anthology—
Yeah, the anthology!
Even though we're promoting it at events,
it's not exactly flying off the shelves.
Yeah, we should do something more flashy.
Yes, exactly!
Why don't we sell this mystery to the News Poster Club?
It'd be great if we could get some time on the school radio tomorrow too.
With that kind of publicity, even this anthology would sell!
I see!
That's a good idea!
And what did you plan to tell them?
That incident has nothing to do with the Classics Club.
How about this...
The Classics Club's super sleuth, Oreki Houtarou,
has caught the thief sowing discord throughout the culture fair behind the Juumonji name!
Read all about this and his other great achievements,
exclusively in the Classics Club anthology, Hyouka!
That's a wonderful idea!
Not bad.
I know, right!
This way we can expose Juumonji
and promote the Classics Club at the same—
Give me a break!
"Super sleuth," my ass!
I won't be your mascot panda!
Let's at least try, Oreki.
Even if I were willing to dance to your little tune,
the student body alone makes a thousand subjects,
and that's not even counting the outsiders!
How do you expect me to find the culprit in that crowd?
Would it be that difficult?
It's impossible.
If only the thief would target the Classics Club...
Well...
Then let's stage—
No thanks!
I'm kidding, I'm kidding!
Target us, huh?
Which clubs got hit so far?
The Go Club, the A Capella Choir, the Cooking Club,
and who else?
The Fortune Teller Club!
Yeah, that!
A Capella... Go... Fortune Teller...
Cooking Club...
ABC!
Hello, Suzuki?
The clubs whose names start with an "e" sound in Japanese are
Has anything gone missing from your club?
the Movie Lab, the Gardening Club, the Acting Troupe, and the SF Club.
Yeah, exactly!
What do you mean?
I was afraid you'd say that.
It's a pattern, and a pretty simple one at that.
A Capella Choir. Go Club. Fortune Teller Club.
Then there's a missing letter, then we have the Cooking Club.
So if a club starting with the "e" sound shows up, we'll know for sure.
They're in Japanese alphabetical order, right?
Correct.
Yeah, thanks!
Gotou
In call
Ending call...
Gotou
Call ended
The Gardening Club got hit.
They took their eyes off it for one moment and one of their water guns was missing..
A water gun?
To put out the fires when frying potatoes.
There was a guy from the Gardening Club yesterday who had it with him.
Wait a moment...
In Christie's ABC Murders,
someone whose name began with 'A' got murdered in a place beginning with 'A', and so on.
The Cooking Club lost their ladle...
Hold on.
Chitanda, do you know what got stolen from the Fortune Teller Club?
Yes! It was the Wheel of Fortune, the tarot card.
Okay.
That means...
A Capella Choir       ->     (drink)
Go Club       ->   (Go stone)
Fortune Teller Club->   (Wheel of Fortune)
Gardening Club  ->    (water gun)
Cooking Club    ->      (ladle)
The Gardening Club's water gun was an AK.
AK? What's that?
A Russian assault rifle.
And if that works,
we could just call the "go stone" a regular "stone" as well.
Probably.
And the A Capella Choir...
It doesn't matter. You just need to figure it out.
Why do you say that?
How did the culprit sign their messages?
Juumonji.
Why do you read it like that?
If you read it normally, it's "juumoji," or "ten letters"!
Ten letters!
Ten letters
I see! The first ten letters in Japanese are a-i-u-e-o then ka-ki-ku-ke-ko!
Which means the tenth will be...
"Kotenbu"! The Classics Club!
I'd say we're involved enough for some publicity, wouldn't you?
I'll go and ask the News Poster club right away!
Aren't we enthusiastic?
What's wrong?
I just realized something.
This incident...
No, never mind.
I'm gonna go investigate some more.
What's gotten into him?
Who knows?
You're not going back to the Manga Lab?
I am.
What? You got a problem with me being here?
Why are you angry?
I'm not!
Biology
Prep Room
The basics of negotiation...
Firstly, make the other party believe you expect great things of them.
Secondly, downplay what you have to gain.
And lastly, ask a boy in private.
Okay!
Roger! I'll go interview the Gardening Club!
What about the A Capella Choir?
I'm calling them now!
And the Cooking Club?
Hurry up!
Yeah, exactly!
How many times do I need to tell you?!
Don't ask questions, act!
Sorry, Chitanda, we're kinda busy.
Could you come back later?
Sure, then I'll...
Sorry, I can't do that!
It's about the Classics Club!
Sorry, but we can't cover you unless you've got a story.
I've got one!
And what would that be?
I don't really have time. Could you hur—
Where are you taking me?
This is something I can only tell the News Poster Club about.
I... you know...
I expect great things of you!
Oh...
Thanks.
But the Classics Club would hardly gain anything...
I see.
What do you say?
Don't you think we should at least try?
I don't really see what you're getting at.
I thought so.
Like I said, we're full up already.
If you don't have a story, I'll catch you later.
Please wait!
I've got a story!
Someone's stealing things all over the culture fair!
The culprit is—
Juumonji! Juumonji, right?
Do you know something?!
Uh... I...
I see.
Japanese alphabetical order.
The Fortune Teller Club got hit too, huh?
That's why...
That's why what?
The News Poster Club starts with a "ka" sound in Japanese, right?
That means you're—
We lost our cutter knife.
That's why everything seemed so hectic?
Yeah. It's kind of a pain, but this is exactly the kind of story we were looking for.
I'm impressed you figured it out.
It was Oreki.
I see.
Anyway, thanks for the help.
Tougaito, please wait!
I gave you your story,
so please write about the Classics Club too!
Okay? Please!
But if I carried on like that, I'd basically be saying I didn't trust him.
Sor—
Chitanda!
How was it?
Did you succeed?
Well...
I'm not sure.
Never mind. Just talking to myself.
Oh.
Anyway, I asked the A Capella Choir!
They had a box of apple juice stolen!
I heard the News Poster Club got their cutter knife stolen.
That's "ka" for you. It's definitely Japanese alphabetical order.
Next up is "ki", and the only one starting with that sound is the Magic Club.
Their next performance is coming up.
If we watch it carefully...
You want to stake out the location?
Yeah.
That's the thief's weakness.
They're bound by their own rules.
And therefore, they shouldn't be too hard to catch.
But if you catch him at "ki"...
Then he won't make it to us?
Don't worry, we'll work something out.
I guess, but still...
Anyway, I'm off to stake out a magic show.
Let's hope we're not late.
Later!
When light and dark are in balance.
Autumn Equinox
Hyouka
Program
Prelude
Living Dead
Takamura Youichi, first-year
Rainbow Chain
Nagai Kaori, first-year
Ubiquity
Tayama Kazuya, second-year
Close-up Card Magic
Takamura Youichi and Nagai Kaori, first-years
Bowl and Jewel
Tayama Kazuya, second-year
Finale
First Performance
Fifth Performance
It's only 2pm.
Well, if it isn't Fuku!
Hey, Tani.
If you're here, then I guess you know about it too, huh?
What?
Don't play dumb with me!
You're here for the Juumoji thief!
Yeah.
Then this shall be our next clash of wits!
Did you hear about the News Poster Club?
They lost their cutter knife. I know.
The News Poster guys have got their heads in the game.
Their next issue will be headlined by the Juumoji incident.
And whoever catches the thief
gets a whole special issue about their club!
Sorry, but I'll be winning this.
You might not realize it at first, but I'm a huge mystery fan!
Please be gentle.
Earth Sci. Prep. room
Ibara, you've read Christie's ABC Murders, right?
Of course.
Then I have a question.
Was there any reason the murders took place in alphabetical order?
If I told you that, it'd spoil the whole story.
I don't mind.
You're wondering what kind of lame story would have the murderer kill alphabetically
just 'cause they felt like it, right?
And I bet you feel the same way about this case as well.
Yeah.
Anyone could've figured out it was Japanese alphabetical order.
This Juumoji guy must've known that too.
Guess you're right.
So I was wondering whether there was any deeper meaning or intention behind these thefts.
Unless he's just doing it for fun.
Oreki...
You want to catch Juumoji, don't you?
Why would I?
You're so eager.
I couldn't care less.
But if Chitanda's gonna get stuck into it, I can't exactly avoid it either.
You could just ignore her.
She's not the kind you can just ignore. That's why it's such a pain.
You dweeb.
And that's that.
You're going?
Yeah.
Thanks for the flour, by the way.
It was a real help.
Oh, right!
You want me to pay you?
That hurts, you know.
I traded that flour, just like in One Red Paperclip.
What's that?
Give me something in exchange.
Though I guess we could just end it here.
I see... Fair enough.
You can have this.
You sure?
But...
Without that, your cosp—
Don't call it that, stupid!
It's almost time for the Magic Club's fifth performance!
Good afternoon, Irisu.
Oh, it's you.
Do you like magic tricks?
"Like" might be too strong a word, but...
Why? Is it weird?
No, just a bit unexpected.
Don't tell me...
Yeah, right.
You don't have to put it like that, though.
That's Mayaka's senior.
I saw her yesterday at the Manga Lab.
This looks fun!
Hey, look!
Whoa, and here's Tanabe with none other than
His Highness the student council president, Kurayama Muneyoshi himself.
Hey, Empress.
Hello.
Hey.
Ah, Fukube.
Sir!
Thank you for your patience!
The Magic Club's performance will now begin!
Thank you very much for coming today!
Without further ado, please enjoy the fruits of our labor,
as we perform for you the art of magic!
Showtime.
But how does the thief known only as Juumoji plan to strike before so many watchful eyes?
Now then, Takamura Youichi's Living De—
What is it?
Um...
A candle!
Sorry!
Dammit!
When was it?
No, that's not it!
No one went near the stage except the performers!
Which means...
it was missing from the beginning?
What am I even doing here?
Now that I think about it,
no one said Juumoji would steal it during the performance!
Welcome to the
Manga Lab!
Sales seem to have picked up since yesterday.
Yeah, they have!
It's probably thanks to the posters.
I'm glad.
You should've just listened to your elders in the first place.
We would've sold more yesterday if a certain someone hadn't been in the way.
Aww, give her a break. I'm almost feeling pity here.
Don't worry about it.
I know.
Seriously, you couldn't find it?
I bet she made the whole thing up.
She just got scared of showing us some crappy manga.
She tried to win the argument by naming some obscure indie title nobody's ever heard of.
Totally!
As if there'd even be a manga like that in the first place!
Hey!
Stop!
That's the end of it.
If you haven't heard of it, keep your mouth shut.
We're back.
B-But...
Weren't you listening?
I said if you haven't heard of it, shut your trap.
Oh, President, how was the Magic Club?
It was fun.
I thought I might stop by tomorrow.
Yeah, check it out!
When was it again?
They have lots of shows each day, so you can catch them anytime.
I see. Then—
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Gotcha!
Fuk—
I'm pathetic.
Running off to Fuku and the others.
Ibara!
Ah, Yuasa.
I'm sorry it had to end up like this.
Why are you apologizing?
Because I didn't say anything, even though I wanted to take your side.
But if you did, it'd turn into all-out war between you and Kouchi!
I don't want that... This is fine.
I don't think Ayako really meant it.
Ayako?
Kouchi.
Kouchi Ayako.
What do you mean, she didn't mean it?
Because she and I are friends.
That's all?
Ayako and Haruna were friends too.
Haruna? Who's that?
Anjou Haruna. Co-author of Dead at Dusk.
You mean it was a collaboration?
Someone else drew it. Ayako might know who.
Do you know what year and class they're in?
Haruna doesn't go to this school anymore.
She transferred.
I see...
But how do you know she didn't mean it,
just because she was friends with Anjou Haruna?
Well... That's a good question.
But I can't explain it any further.
Ayako's my friend after all.
Are you worried the explanation would make her look bad?
Give me a minute to cool down.
Ibara...
I'll be back right away.
Hyouka
Extra! Extra! Read all about it!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Special
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Kamiyama
High
Monthly
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Who's the next target?
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Phantom Thief!
The
Juumoji
incident!
Not to mention that this outrageous fellow dared to strike us, the News Poster Club, and stole our cutter knife
from right under our noses! Can you believe it? This is a clear and obvious challenge against the press!
And that is all the information we were able to gather thus far. From this, our dear readers, we conclude that Juumoji will
strike for the last time between 12 and 2 pm on the third day, targeting either the Classics Club or the Artisan Workshop.
Classics Club
Tougaito!
They won, Houtarou.
A candle was stolen from the Magic Club.
There was a note claiming responsibility, as always.
Isn't that for the best?
We don't want to catch Juumoji before they target us, after all.
That's true, but...
I thought I'd be able to catch them in the act.
You thought they'd strike during the performance?
Yeah.
Juumoji never announced when it was going to happen.
The Cooking Club's ladle also went missing beforehand, didn't it?
If you realized that, you could've said something.
I didn't know you were planning to stake out a magic show.
That's true.
I'm back!
Irisu said that the 20 copies I left with her are selling well!
She's the one handling it, after all.
And one more thing.
The News Poster Club's 4pm issue featured the Juumoji incident.
They wrote about how the thefts were in Japanese alphabetical order.
The Classics Club was mentioned too.
Juumoji's last target will be either the Artisan Workshop or us.
There's an Artisan Workshop too?
There is, now that you mention it.
If they get hit instead of us, our whole plan is ruined.
I thought I might talk to the Radio Club tomorrow.
Hopefully we can get the Classics Club mentioned during their broadcast.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You just look a bit tir—
Hey, guys!
Hey, Mayaka!
How many did we sell today?
16, if you don't count the 20 we gave to Irisu.
Excellent!
Excellent?
I guess.
137 remaining
It's my job to negotiate with the other clubs, but...
It's so... exhausting...
Body Talk.
It's not as good as Dead at Dusk, but it's better than nothing.
Yeah, this'll do.
Mine don't hold a candle to either.
Houtarou's changed.
Or at least, he's showing progress.
Ever since he met Chitanda.
He's turning into someone full of those surprises I love so much.
Am I truly happy about it?
There are over a thousand suspects.
There's no way anyone could simply deduce the culprit's identity.
Which means that our only choice is to catch them red-handed.
This incident isn't fit for Houtarou. I'll unveil its truth myself.
Houtarou,
I'm gonna catch Juumoji!
Mail-order Sales
Oh, they're doing mail-order sales?
Next time: The Final Target.
The Final Target