That sound can even wake the dead.
A Day in the Squad
Rio Runs!
Let's eat!
How was it?
It tastes good, doesn't it?
Umm, so good!
Well, it's okay, right?
Good.
This is a dish from my hometown.
Is it the one that's called miso?
It's cooked the same way the rockfish is.
Yes.
I brought a little bit of miso that my mom made.
We still have a lot, so please eat as much as you can.
To Treize?
Yes. Communication has finally arrived from the people sending us supplies.
I will go and retrieve them with Kureha-chan.
Ammunition, medicine and commodities. There should be a lot coming in.
With this, I can finally breathe easy.
How about Noeru?
You will be in Karl's studio, right?
I see.
Kanata!
We will be practicing the horn seriously this afternoon!
Really?
Time for lunch.
Good grief.
Those are bad manners.
Your dad will cry if he sees you.
How could it matter?
Here for you. Some teacakes.
Aren't these fortune cookies?
You look as if you still hate them.
Those kids at the church are innocent, right?
Hmm. They just spread useless superstitions and tease for money. They are the same anywhere.
Oh. It's not like that at all.
What we have here are the really delicious ones.
Oh, my!
Great luck.
Wish
Your dream is coming true but it's off to a rocky start.
Business
It's adapted to the production
You have to make an effort.
Studies
Study with confidence
Disagreement
Delegate
Love
Answer honestly
Marriage Proposal
The beginnings are difficult but ... promising
Health
You can confide to ...
But Kana-chan seems to have gotten used to her life now.
She's always working hard. How cute!
Really?
I do recognize her eagerness and seriousness.
But you can't be so naive and think that she's gonna be okay.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Se-cr-et.
Why? I'm not happy.
Atrocity
Wish
Don't worry, your prayers will be fulfilled
Business
Being in a hurry, you miss important things
Studies
Study mathematics and foreign languages
Disagreement
Wait for the storm to pass
Love
You lack modesty and it ...
Marriage Proposal
You won't find ground ...
to oppose your parents
Health
... choice of doctor isn't ...
We are going then.
I guess we'll be back late.
Yup. Be careful.
Don't make trouble for Rio-senpai!
Ok.
Departure commence.
See you!
I won't ask you to do it at this level,
but using only the mouthpiece to control the tone is basic.
Try it.
Y-Yes.
How do you find the life on the base?
It's a lot of fun.
From the way you declare it, it must be true.
Your optimism makes me a little bit envious.
By the way, why did you join the military?
That's because, well,
I heard that you can learn to play musical instruments for free...
But, excuse me!
P-protecting the country is also very important!
It's okay. It doesn't matter if you are doing it for money or anything else.
People with a clear purpose last longer than those without one.
Well, I'm really thankful.
Then, why would Rio-senpai...?
I...
Actually, I was totally different from you.
But, it's pretty rare these days.
Especially for the brass, because you probably won't even hear about it unless you are in the military.
I heard it... before...
Something like... senpai...
Kanata!?
The sound of the skies...
What's wrong with you! Hold on! Hold on, Kanata!!
Answer me!
No!
Please! Calm down.
It's so hot.
It's so hot, mom.
It's hot? It's like that?
Don't worry. Don't worry!
M... Mom.
What's wrong with you, Kanata?
Kanata!
Snow... I wanna eat...
I got it. Please wait!
Snow. Where is the snow. Where is it?
It's not possible to find it here!
Calm down. Calm down.
Medicine!
... No. That can only be the last resort!
Medicine! Medicine! Medicine! Medicine!
Here it is!
Everything's running out.
Those idiots from the supply department!
Damn.
What to do...
What can I do?...
DAMN!
Oh... Hi there...
How may I help you?
Are any of the children bothering you again?
I apologize for all of my bad behavior before.
So, please...
I need your help.
Drink it.
Right.
She has a high fever,
But she should be fine after drinking this medicine.
Is it a serious illness?
I think it's probably tertian malaria.
Tertian malaria?
Isn't that a disease that only occurs in children?
It can also occur in adults if they are totally exhausted.
It was common for children to get infected when they had just arrived at our church.
It's common that those who seemed perfectly normal suddenly get a fever.
She must have tried really hard to endure this.
Then... Will Kanata recover from this completely? Will she be like this forever?
I think she will be fine.
That's great...
Thank... Thank you very much... Er...
My name is Yumina.
Ah.
This is made from herbs.
Please have her drink this later.
Eh... I am sorry for causing you all this trouble.
No worries.
Serving the people in the city...
is our pleasure and responsibility.
And also... May God bless you all.
I really appreciate your help.
Ouch!
Ah...I am sorry!
Are you all right?
I am sorry.
I... am just the miso.
That we drank in the morning?
No.
Miso-gasu... it's the bean residue left after miso is filtered out when making the soup.
Those are the unnecessary things, the unwanted things.
Since I was a kid, everyone called me that.
Therefore this time, I tried my best not to be a burden on others.
But it turns out...
You are much more fragile than you appear to be.
And you are self-willed and naive.
Did I... say something?
A lot.
By the way, senpai,
What... What's the matter?
The music you just hummed.
What... What music?
This one...
It's so amazing that you can recite it after hearing it only once...
Not just once.
A long long time ago... I heard it,
And I thought "It would be nice if I could play that song too."
Therefore I...
really want to play that heavenly music.
But it seems that wherever it is, miso can only be miso.
Kanata.
I don't want to seek help from the Church.
This Takemicaduchi is a treasure from the ancients.
And there are lots of things hidden inside it.
Lots?
For the details, ask Noeru later on.
Good. This is it.
Let's begin!
This... This music...
This is probably a complete version of that song.
All of the instruments, all of the parts are in harmony and form a complete song.
This is the same as driving a tank.
Commander, gunner, driver and communicator. Everyone dedicates their power to drive the tank.
There is no redundant one.
Unnecessary sounds do not exist.
Don't look at me like that. I just repeated what I was told.
From the person I looked up to and respected the most.
In that person's words, Kanata, do you know why senpai and superiors exist?
They are here so the juniors have someone to trouble.
Even if you can't accomplish something, just keep your unwillingness and powerlessness in mind.
And also the warmth of being taken care of.
Someday when it is your turn to take care of others, all of these will become your support.
Therefore, feel free to trouble me. I did the same when I was a junior.
Of course, if you are not doing well, you will be scolded and punished.
But, speak out if you find things difficult, and also when you feel they are too hard.
Is that okay?
Affirmative!
From now on, I will try my best and be sure to give you lots of trouble.
Well...
Please do be considerate...
Ah...well. I should have just stayed behind.
Being looked after by Rio-senpai... geez that Kanata...
It's nothing special. She's just too exhausted.
Just let her sleep and she'll be fine.
Takemicaduchi was activated.
Ah. I am sorry. I just used it... Is there any trouble?
Nope.
You went to hear that song?
Ya.
Didn't you say that you didn't want to hear that again?
I suddenly wanted to.
Why is that?
It's a secret.
Rainy Season Sky - Quartz Rainbow
Next time:
Rainy Season Sky
Quartz Rainbow
This story is fiction and it's not related to any real people, organizations or incidents.