Haruka's Room
Number 6
This is Haruka's Room, got it?
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Or at least, that's how it's supposed to be...
Actually, this will be the final episode of this program.
Thank you for watching, everyone!
Since it's the last episode, I'd like to hear a word from each of the people I have already introduced.
Manabe Yoshihisa here!
The last episode already? How sad.
I'm sorry we couldn't show more lovey-dovey scenes between Kotoura and myself.
Maybe we could do some right now?
A little hugging and some kissing...
No way!
Mifune Yuriko here!
It's really sad that this is the last episode.
Was I able to get you all to recognize the importance of ESP research?
I don't think so!
But that's all right!
Next time, we'll be starting Yuriko's Room! Look forward to it!
There's no such show!
Muroto Daichi here.
You're not fully showing on screen, Muroto-senpai!
Is that okay? It's the last episode!
Push
Muroto Daichi here!
Who the heck are you?
Moritani Hiyori here.
So it's the last episode...
I was the guest last time, but I guess that doesn't matter.
The program wasn't cancelled because of me, right?
Maybe, maybe not.
You're making it sound like it is!
And lastly, me.
Kotoura Haruka here.
I hope you've come to like this show, at least a little.
It's unfortunate that this program is coming to an end,
but let's meet again, in the main show!
Farewell, everyone!
The End