Though one may gaze skyward from the very same place,
they will never see the same clouds twice.
The days of our lives leave their mark on the march of time.
Woo-hoo! I won tickets to the screening!
Hooray!
Oh god, I sound just like Arashiyama.
Is she starting to rub off on me?
Uh-oh, I better be careful.
Well anyway, I've cleared the first step!
Kailong
The Tokugawa Ninja Force
Now to get Sanada to come with me!
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
10 days left until the screening
Art Room
Toshiko Tatsuno Can Not Be Broken (From Vol.1 Chapter 6)
Hey, what's that?
I wanna go! I wanna go!
It's the final showdown of the evil syndicates!
Sorry, but I'm gonna go with Sanada.
But whenever I try to ask him, I chicken out!
Oh, how very bittersweet. Yes, Miss Haribara?
'Tis the joys of youth, Madam Arashiyama.
Yes indeedy!
Quit it.
It doesn't have to be at a screening. Why not a regular movie?
Just play it cool and ask him if he wants to go catch a flick or something.
Yeah, go see something more "suitable".
The movie itself is irrelevant.
Since the screening's at a specific date and time, I've got a better chance of success!
Makes sense.
Saying, "let's go sometime" is kind of vague, I suppose.
So there's only one chance to catch the screening?
Yep. That's why I picked a less popular movie that wouldn't be hard to win tickets for!
Aww, I  wanna see it, though!
It's hard to turn down a rare event like a screening, too.
Pretty clever, Tatsuno.
Excuse me girls...
You're not eating in the middle of art class, are you?
Care for a handful, sir?
Hey! That's no fair!
I'm checking everyone's progress, Arashiyama, so show me what you've got.
You got it, chief.
Hey, this is pretty good!
Isn't it?
A bit abstract, but there's a real sense of life in this horse dashing across the plains.
It's supposed to be a sleeping dog, though...
That's a dog?
Yes, sir.
Okay, next... Ebisu!
What, no follow-up?
Follow me!
7 days left until the screening
Today's the day!
When Sanada comes today, I'll invite him!
Ugh, so hot...
What's with that slovenly appearance!?
And you call yourself a maid!?
I'm ashamed to let you out in public!
Where the heck did that come from!?
The sky's the limit.
Yeah, but it's too hot in this outfit.
Sew me a summer uniform, granny.
Well, I could probably throw one together in a day or so.
Okay... Tomorrow, the day after...
So you could do three outfits in three days!
If she worked three days straight, her little old heart would give out!
The hell it would!
3 days until the screening
Gotcha!
Damn, I must be in a slump.
I'm getting sucked into Arashiyama's giddy "tee-hee" pace.
There's only 3 days left!
Today. I have to do it today.
I have to invite Sanada today, or else...
Hey! How's that romantic invite going?
I'm gonna do it right now, just watch.
Woo-hoo!
Knowing you, I'm sure you're up to something here.
I bet you'd go right up to your crush and say...
Heya! How's about we see a movie?
...or something, I'm sure.
Here goes. I got it this time!
Hey, Sanada...
Huh?
Movie...
Hmm?
Umm... movie...
Mov... movi...
You'd better get your butt movie-ing and finish cleaning up.
Swing and a miss!
Sanada's leaving, you know.
If you run, you can still catch him.
Would-you-like-to-see-a-movie?
Why can't I say a simple 8-syllable sentence?
Want me to ask him for you?
No... I'll go.
How could I have felt relieved at the idea of an indirect invite?
A measly 5 or 6 staircases...
...can be cleared in no time!
Ack! It's Kameda, the western history teacher!
Lu-THERRR!
LUTHER 1483~1546
GERMAN RELIGIOUS REFORMIST
PUBLISHED A COLLECTION OF GRIEVANCES AGAINST THE POPE IN 1571
THAT PAVED THE WAY FOR RELIGIOUS REFORMATION
Of all the people...
CZARRR!
Czar
Title held by Russian emperors.
Derived from the Latin "Caesar"
Adopted in the 16th century by Ivan IV
Kameda, the history teacher who is said to drone on for eons once he begins a lecture.
Better known as Kameda the soft-shelled turtle!
W-Why you...
Arashiyama would probably just try to laugh her way out of a tongue lashing...
What would she say at a time like this?
How would she get herself out of it?
No! No, no, no!
What would I  do?
What would I do?
I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Kameda.
I slipped on my way down, but I'm okay.
A-All right then. Just be careful next time.
Yes, sir. Excuse me.
Day of the screening
Hm? Weren't you supposed to go see a movie with the fishmonger's kid?
I decided it'd be better to let life work for me instead of me working for it.
That's how I choose to wield my feminine charm.
Huh? What the heck are you talking about?
Oh, I see what you're up to.
Well, I guess I'll throw you a bone.
Umm, what about the café?
Gramma's gonna go hit the slots.
I’ll let the maids hold the fort today.
In order to have sweet rice-cakes,
one must first make the effort to build a shelf to keep them.
Welcome!
But once in a while,
Yay, free movie passes! Woo-hoo!
without lifting a finger,
there are those who's luck grants them both.
People's true nature are reflected in their sneezes.
Detectives are valued for their keen observation and their investigative instinct.
The job of a Japanese detective
is to investigate his target's actions and secrets from the shadows.
Only the most brilliant of men can perform such a task.
I'll follow you around and observe you!
Sure you will, Detective Yukikonan.
Go on and expose all my dirty little secrets.
AYE-AYE SIR!
I've got no boobs or hips.
That's your secret!
You've got quite an eye for detail.
Pillbugs are edible but they taste terrible.
The Amazingly Weird Card (From Vol.4 Ch 33)
Get 'em! Blazing Fireball Burst!
I repel it with my Mirror Shield!
4 life points.
Zombie Detective is defeated!
But when Zombie Detective dies, he can take a lower-level enemy monster with him!
Crud! Faerie Warrior defeated!
Next, I attack you directly!
I guard with Turtle Knight!
It's useless!
My weapon is a spear-type, so I can slip past a single monster's guard!
Aw, man...
Zero life points remaining. I'm dead.
Argh, you win.
You're good, Takeru!
You're invincible!
Your cards are lame, but you're still tough!
I bet you could take on Yamamoto from class 4!
Let's go duel during lunchtime.
Excuse me, boys!
Do you think it's okay to bring that stuff to school?
Yeah!
Shut up, Rock Lobster!
Rock Lobster carpaccio!
I'll mention this at next week's assembly.
Let's go, Ebi.
You're such a nag, Rock Lobster!
Girls are so obnoxious.
Year
Class
Okay, class.
Does anyone understand what Hans was thinking here when he suddenly ran down the stairs?
Anyone know the answer?
Dear Arashiyama,
Can I come over   and hang out
at your house    on Sunday?
- Ebi
This will be on the test.
Huh?
Whaaaa?
No way.
She won't actually show up.
There's no way she'd come!
Oh, sorry. Bathroom's free.
It's okay, that's not what I was waiting for.
Pardon me!
I-Isesaki...
Good afternoon!
Well, well, well... Hi there!
So you were waiting for your little friend, huh?
I wasn't waiting, and she's not my friend!
Dried bonito is the hardest food known to man.
I never thought she'd actually come...
So why'd you come over, Isesaki?
To hang out, remember?
O-Oh yeah.
Takeru!
Wait just a sec...
What is it?
Here's a little extra for your war chest!
Awesome!
yen
for a piggy bank
for candy
for cards
Hey, this ain't for personal use.
Okay, gotcha.
You bagged a real cutie! Go get 'er, tiger!
Get what?
Tears aren't for show.
Well, she gave me some money, so you wanna go somewhere?
Sure.
If the guys happen to see me with a girl, I'm done for!
INNER ASSEMBLY
Takeru, you were with a girl, Isesaki of all people last Sunday, correct?
Yes.
The very same Isesaki who threatened to tell on us at the assembly!
I plead guilty.
Takeru!
Huh?
This is boring! Say something already!
Uh, well...
Hey, how come you're using my first name?
You always just call me Arashiyama.
Huh? I can call you whatever I want.
You call me by my first name too, Takeru.
What!?
Oh yeah, what was your first name anyway?
S-Sorry! I just forgot, that's all!
I'm trying to remember...
Gimme a hint!
Eri...
Huh?
ERI!
My bark goes "arf arf", not "woof".
E...
E?
E-E...
Eeeh forget it, I can't do it!
It's embarrassing enough to say the name of a girl comic book character!
No way!
Can I please just call you Ebi?
All the girls call you that.
Fine, whatever.
Hey, you up for ice cream?
N-Nah, I'm fine. It's kinda cold out.
Well I want some, so buy it!
And don't act like such a little boy!
You're just being selfish!
What flavor do you want?
Vanilla.
They're out.
What else do they have then?
Pretty much everything but vanilla.
Okay then, I'll take strawberry.
Sorry, they're out of that too.
And I kind of feel like I'm hypothermic.
Okay, I'll have the same as you.
Cool, you picked chocolate melon!
T-Thanks.
It was just at the top of the pile.
Thanks!
Hey, Takeru!
What's up? On a date?
Hey, hey, hey, not bad!
No, that's not it.
Umm...
Oh, right.
She's a friend of my sister.
Hey.
Good afternoon.
Hey, she's pretty cute!
Good luck, munchkin!
With what?
Sorry to bother you. Later!
She sure is pretty.
Y-Yeah...
I thought the guys had found me.
The market's encounter rate is way too high!
There's gotta be some place I can hide.
Hey, Isesaki.
E-Ebi, would you...
You're coming with me to my regular joint.
Oh boy, where? I wanna see!
So she hits me if I say a banned word?
Would this count as censorship?
Su
zu
ya
Come on in!
Good afternoon!
Oh, are you on a date, Takeru?
And I guess you could call this a false accusation.
Wow!
I've never been anywhere like this before!
I've always wanted to visit a candy store!
Oh, I've seen these.
These are those cards you boys collect.
Yeah.
I'll take this, please.
Sure, 1.5 million yen.
But I'll cut you a deal at 150.
Umm, thank you very much.
Aww, lame. It's a duplicate.
You gonna buy some cards?
Just one pack.
This is bad!
He still hadn't spent this month's allowance?
I've got nowhere to run! No good excuses!
My grade school life is over!
Oh, it's them...
Takeru. Go hide in the VIP room.
You sure?
Candy Shop Suzuya's VIP Room
A room for eating Okonomiyaki
Normally, grade schoolers aren't allowed
Hey granny, you seen Takeru?
Uh-oh!
We went to his house, but he wasn't home.
I think Takeru might have gone to the world of adulthood.
Huh? Where?
Let's go check out the shrine.
Whew! That was just like a clichéd chase scene!
Like they say, if you keep looking, you'll find a way.
Takeru. This is for you.
Huh? You sure?
Yep.
Open it up!
Okay.
H-Hey, you're a little close!
Did you get any strong ones?
Nothing but really weird ones, actually.
Well, are these strong?
Yeah, if you know how to use them.
Makki wanted this one,
and I could trade this one to Kabaya.
Hey, Takeru.
You better take good care of those.
Y-Yeah, sure.
Don't even think about trading them.
Okay.
She's totally different outside of school.
What?
I won't... I mean, I ain't gonna use these.
How come? Aren't they real strong?
If I put them in my deck, I'll forget which ones are yours.
You can do it, Takeru!
There, just hold onto me!
Okay, I'll let go now.
Wait! Don't let go yet!
Youngsters these days have no shame, flirting in broad daylight.
Well, I like her. She remembers her manners.
What? I didn't say I was referring to her.
Go tell them lunch is ready, would you?
Mkay.
By the way, where's my lunch?
You can all eat together.
You get along great with grade-schoolers.
What's that supposed to mean?
But I decided to dine in their company.
Lunch is rea... dy.
Year
Class
The next morning
Hey, Takeru!
Hey, good morning.
Were the heck were you yesterday?
Umm, just visiting a relative’s place.
Hey Makita, check this out!
Huh, check what out?
Whoa, tubular!
Good morning, Ebi.
Don't you dare call me that.
Huh?
Did I...
I mean, what'd I do?
Cold, cold, cold!
Beep!
Sorry, sorry. Were you watching that?
Look, it's not over yet.
I wanted to see the transformation scene!
They do the same thing every week, though.
Women are such mysterious creatures.
Oh man! Takeru, that was hilarious!
Oh, m’god I gotta write that down!
Iron Maiden
Oh, Takeru!
It makes me sick when people use two 50 yen coins.
A Japanese detective's job is to expose crimes committed by the citizens,
but it’s the police who determine and execute their punishment.
Okay, have you dug up any dirt on me?
Yeah, I sure did.
Ta-daa!
Exchange Diary
Hotori Arashiyama
Middle School Chapter
W-Where the heck did you find that!?
Everything you don't want the world to see, is written right here.
You win, you win! Great work, detective!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
Living for rock!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living alone, blasting my music.
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
but my beloved has yet to confess to me.
Kyou mo kare ni wa naze ka kokurezu
We devote our beings to table tennis,
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
so we build our endurance by playing the drums.
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
We're the Maids, yeah!
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
Seaside's the best maid cafe around!
Shisaido wa zessan eigyouchuu
Thank you very maid for coming!
And the Town Still Turns
Next Episode
You know that old myth about Pandora's Box?
Yeah, you're not supposed to open it, right?
If you do, all kinds of bad stuff comes flying out.
But the last thing to fly out was hope!
But hope was just a ruse!
If it weren't for hope, we could just accept giving up.
When the bonus round comes, I think, "I can win it back!" and keep wasting my money!
Granny, did you get cleaned out at the slots?
Cafe Seaside
Next time: 6th Street: Pandora Maid Service.
Yep, it goes round 'n round.