♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1
LET'S JAM. ♪
[SNIFFING]
[BARKING]
[SNARLING]
SHUT UP!
[DOG YELPING, WHINING]
[CAN CLANKING AND ROLLING]
HA HA HA HA!
[CRASH]
HUH?
UNH!
[GROWLS]
[WHINES]
UNH!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
HMM?
HUH?
GRRRR!
AAAH!
[GRUNTING]
UNH!
AAAH!
[WHINING]
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE CONTINUE]
[RAIN FALLING]
[LOW THUNDER]
[THUNDER]
HEY, JET.
HUH?
I'M ASKING YOU,
HOW MUCH LONGER BEFORE
WE LAND THIS DAMN THING?
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON.
[BEEPING]
HOW LONG WERE YOU THERE?
I DIDN'T HEAR YOU COME IN.
I'VE BEEN HERE FOR A WHILE.
OH, I SEE.
WHAT'S HE SPACING OUT ABOUT?
LET'S LAND THIS TUB ALREADY
SO WE CAN HAND OVER
THAT PATHETIC BOUNTY HEAD.
I WANT MY REWARD IN NICE, CRISP
BILLS, YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
HMM?
WHOA, JET,
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN GOTTEN
PERMISSION TO LAND YET.
I'M WORKING ON IT.
YOU TWO ARE SO
OBNOXIOUS, I SWEAR.
YOU CAN'T RUSH GENIUS,
MY FRIENDS.
CALL THE CONTROL TOWER
FOR ME, WILL YOU?
GANYMEDE'S YOUR HOME
SATELLITE, ISN'T IT?
YOU WEREN'T THINKING
OF SOME SWEET THING
FROM YOUR PAST, WERE YOU
SOMEONE WHO CRIED
OVER YOU, HUH?
[CLEARS THROAT]
OR MAYBE IT WAS SOMEBODY
WHO MADE YOU CRY.
DIDN'T I JUST SAY
YOU WERE OBNOXIOUS?!
HELLO.
THIS IS GANYMEDE POLICE
REGARDING YOUR...
- HUH?
DONNELLY!
OH, MAN! JET!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YEAH, IT'S YOU, ALL RIGHT.
TOP OF YOUR HEAD'S
LOOKING A LITTLE SPARSE,
BUT OTHER THAN THAT,
SAME OLD DOG.
YEAH, YEAH.
LONG TIME NO SEE, BUD.
WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN,
WHAT, 7 YEARS, MAYBE 8?
WHAT'S UP WITH
THE SUDDEN HOMECOMING?
YOU HERE FOR WORK,
OR JUST GETTING INTO
TROUBLE LIKE THE OLD DAYS?
I'VE GOT A BOUNTY HEAD
TO HAND OVER TO YOU BOYS,
VERIFICATION NUMBER EX41285
BAKER PANCHORERO.
SO, YOU'RE A BOUNTY HUNTER.
NEVER THOUGHT I'D HEAR THAT.
A GUY THEY CALLED THE BLACK DOG,
BECAUSE ONCE YOU GOT
YOUR TEETH INTO SOMETHING,
YOU NEVER LET GO OF IT.
I FIGURED YOU'D
BE RETIRED BY NOW,
'CAUSE YOU WERE
A VET WAY BACK THEN.
NO WAY. I'M STILL
ON ACTIVE DUTY.
HELL, I'M BUSIER THAN EVER.
NOW, DON'T JUDGE THINGS
ON YOUR TIME SCALE,
YOU OLD RIP VAN WINKLE!
WELL, WELL.
HE USED TO BE A COP, HUH?
THAT EXPLAINS IT.
WHAT'S THAT?
WHY WE CAN'T GET
ALONG FOR 5 MINUTES.
NOW, LET ME THINK HERE.
WHAT WAS HER NAME?
UH... YOU KNOW...
YEAH, ELISA!
UH!
[PIANO PLAYING]
YEAH, SHE'S GOT A LITTLE
JOINT OUT AT MARVIS
YOU REMEMBER, THE OLD PORT.
BAR'S CALLED LA FIN.
SINCE THE RECESSION HIT,
I HEAR SHE'S GOT A LOT
OF DEBTS TO PAY OFF.
WELL, I'M SURE IT'S NOT
EASY FOR A WOMAN LIVING ALONE,
TRYING TO KEEP BODY
AND SOUL TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
♪ THE TALKING TREES
ARE SILENT IN A NOISY WAY ♪
♪ THE STARS ARE BRIGHT
BUT GIVE NO LIGHT ♪
♪ THE WORLD SPINS
BACKWARDS EVERY DAY ♪
♪ HEY, LOOK AT THAT. ♪
♪ A RAINBOW RAT,
A CHECKERED CAT ♪
♪ GO TAIL-AND-TAIL
ALONG THE ROAD... ♪
[BEEPING]
SENSE OF JUSTICE
AND DUTY, HUH?
FIRST TIME HE'S HOME IN YEARS.
OF COURSE HE'S GOING
TO GO SEE HER.
YOU KNOW, HE'S KIDDING
HIMSELF IF HE THINKS
HIS OLD GIRLFRIEND'S
STILL CARRYING A TORCH FOR HIM.
AND YOU'RE KIDDING YOURSELF
IF YOU THINK
EVERY WOMAN'S LIKE YOU.
THEY'RE NOT, YOU KNOW.
DUTY CALLS!
3 O'CLOCK TEA!
[SEA GULLS CRYING]
REALLY. MEN...
THEY ARE SUCH
HOPELESS ROMANTICS.
MMM...
HEY, FAYE, WHAT DO YOU
PUT THAT STUFF ON FOR?
BEAUTIFUL SKIN CAN ONLY BE
MAINTAINED BY TIRELESS EFFORTS,
WHICH ARE ULTIMATELY
TOTALLY FUTILE.
UNDERSTAND?
MMM!
UGH!
YES! FUTILE!
USELESS!
[BARK]
[GROANS]
[CAR AND BOAT HORNS BLOW]
[DOOR OPENS]
EXCUSE ME.
THIS IS LA FIN, RIGHT?
YEAH.
WHO ARE YOU?
HMM.
AN OLD FRIEND OF ELISA'S.
I... HAVEN'T BEEN AROUND
HERE IN A WHILE.
ELISA IS... GONE.
- JET?
- HUH?
WHAT A SHOCK.
IS IT REALLY YOU?
RHINT, HE IS MY GUEST.
YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY.
IT WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
[DOOR OPENS]
YOU DON'T MIND?
NO.
SO, HOW ABOUT IT?
[CLINK] YOU'LL HAVE
A LITTLE DRINK, WON'T YOU?
[DOOR SLAMS]
YOU'RE MY LAST CUSTOMER.
HUH?
I'M CLOSING SHOP.
THE SHIPS DON'T
COME IN LIKE THEY USED TO,
AND THE WHOLE AREA'S
GETTING RUN DOWN.
I'M THINKING ABOUT MOVING OUT
TO ANOTHER TOWN SOMEWHERE.
YOU GET IN OVER YOUR HEAD?
NEW ISLAND MORTGAGES ARE HIGH,
AND THE BANKERS AREN'T
TOO UNDERSTANDING.
MUST BE HARD FOR YOU TO MANAGE.
[LAUGHS]
IT'S SO LIKE YOU TO WORRY
ABOUT THINGS LIKE THAT.
I'LL WORK IT ALL OUT
AFTER I'M RESETTLED.
DON'T WORRY, I'M HERE
WITH RHINT. IT'S OK.
[ICE CLINKING]
UH... YOU MEAN
THAT GUY THAT WAS HERE?
YEAH. WHY?
HMM.
YOU KNOW WHY.
YOU'VE HEARD WE'RE MARRIED.
WE HAVE 3 KIDS, JET.
[GASPS] OH.
[LAUGHING]
KIDDING. JUST KIDDING.
IT WAS A JOKE.
RHINT'S MY BOYFRIEND.
AND... HOW ABOUT YOU?
YOU MUST BE MARRIED.
NO, JUST WANDERING AROUND
WITH SOME WEIRDOS.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
I'M A BOUNTY HUNTER.
UH...
YOU REMEMBER?
[BEEP]
WHERE'S JET?
DOING SOME PERSONAL STUFF.
YOU'RE HIS PARTNER, RIGHT?
YEP.
I'VE GOT SOME INFORMATION
ON A NEW BOUNTY HEAD.
OH! THIS ISN'T PUBLIC YET.
GOTCHA!
WHOA... WHOA, WHOA!
NAME'S RHINT CELONIAS,
A THUG WHO OPERATES
DOWN AT THE PORT OF MARVIS.
LAST NIGHT, HE HAD A RUNIN WITH
A MONEY GUY NAMED LAW RENTSUO,
ANOTHER LOWLIFE SCAM ARTIST.
THE GUY'S DEAD.
YEAH, AND?
RHINT IS ELISA'S MAIN SQUEEZE.
I THOUGHT YOU BOYS
WOULD WANT TO KNOW.
MAN. WHAT'S THE BOUNTY
ON THIS GUY?
HUH? AH!
AAH!
[SPLASH]
[GROANS]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
BACK THEN, WHEN
I GOT HOME FROM WORK,
YOU WERE ALWAYS
THERE WAITING FOR ME,
AND THAT WAS
ALL I NEEDED... JUST YOU.
BUT ON THAT DAY...
[THUNDER, RAIN FALLING]
WHEN I CAME BACK HOME,
THE ONLY THING THERE
WAS THAT POCKET WATCH
THAT, AND A SMALL
PIECE OF PAPER
THAT HAD JUST ONE WORD WRITTEN
ACROSS IT: "FAREWELL."
FOR SOME REASON, I DIDN'T
FEEL SAD OR BROKEN UP.
IT JUST DIDN'T SEEM REAL.
BUT SLOWLY I REALIZED THAT IT
WAS REAL, THAT YOU WERE GONE.
AND LITTLE BY LITTLE, I FELT
SOMETHING INSIDE OF ME GO NUMB.
AFTER 6 MONTHS, I MADE A KIND
OF BET WITH MYSELF... A PLEDGE
THAT I WOULD LEAVE THIS
PLANET AND START A NEW LIFE...
IF YOU DIDN'T RETURN
BY THE TIME THE WATCH STOPPED.
I DIDN'T COME HERE TO BLAME YOU.
I-I JUST WANTED TO KNOW WHY
WHY YOU DISAPPEARED LIKE THAT.
THE WAY YOU TALK ABOUT IT...
YOU SEEM TO THINK THAT TIME
REALLY HAS STOPPED HERE.
THAT'S A STORY FROM LONG AGO.
AND I... I'VE
FORGOTTEN ABOUT IT.
TIME NEVER STANDS STILL.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
BYE, JET.
UH!
EXCUSE ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR A PLACE
CALLED LA FIN.
OVER THERE.
[HORNS HONKING]
[BOAT HORN BLOWS]
A BOUNTY HUNTER?
CAN HE BE...?
RHINT.
HE'S AFTER ME.
I HAVE A BOUNTY ON MY HEAD!
IT'S ALL OVER!
[WHIMPERING]
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
IT'S BECAUSE I BORROWED MONEY
FROM A CROOK LIKE HIM.
I SHOULD HAVE NEVER LET YOU
GET MIXED UP IN THIS.
IF I GET CAUGHT,
NOTHING CAN SAVE ME.
NOTHING.
I KILLED HIM.
LET'S GO.
HUH?
WE'VE GOT TO RUN, RIGHT NOW.
[SEA GULLS CRYING]
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE ALL MY GOOD
KARMA IS FINALLY PAYING OFF.
SORRY, BUT THIS IS BUSINESS.
[BEEPING]
GRAB THE WHEEL! HURRY!
UNH!
[GUNFIRE]
WHEW.
WHAT'S UP?
I'M AFTER A HEAD
WORTH 1.8 MILLION.
WHAT?
HERE, I'LL SEND YOU THE DATA.
[BEEP]
THERE'S A BOUNTY ON THIS GUY?
YEAH.
INSIDE INFO FROM
YOUR PAL DONNELLY.
APPARENTLY, HE GUNNED
DOWN A LOAN SHARK.
UNH!
[GUNFIRE]
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
YOU CAN GO BACK.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
LET HIM GET AWAY, ARE YOU?
WHEN I WAS A COP,
THIS WAS MY BEAT.
I'M THE BLACK DOG,
AND WHEN I BITE, I DON'T LET GO.
I HAVE NO REGRETS ABOUT HER,
BUT I'LL SETTLE
THIS SCORE ON MY OWN TURF.
JUSTICE AND DUTY, HUH?
ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN CAREFULLY.
CUT YOUR ENGINES NOW.
UNH!
- JET!
- ARRGH!
UNH!
ARRGH!
AAAH!
UNH.
UNH!
[SEA GULLS CRYING]
[GASPS]
UH!
[CRYING]
[AIRCRAFT APPROACHING]
STAY BACK!
[CRYING]
LEAVE US ALONE!
PLEASE, JET!
THERE ARE OTHER
BOUNTY HEADS TO CATCH.
YOU DON'T NEED THIS ONE!
IF I LET HIM GO NOW...
SOMEONE ELSE WILL
BE AFTER HIM TOMORROW,
AND BY THEN,
YOU'LL BE AN ACCOMPLICE.
STAY AWAY!
YOU STILL HAVE TIME, ELISA.
STOP PROTECTING ME!
[GUNSHOTS]
[CRYING]
THAT'S JUST HOW
YOU WERE BACK THEN.
HMM?
YOU DECIDED EVERYTHING.
IN THE END,
YOU WERE ALWAYS RIGHT.
WHEN I WAS THERE WITH YOU,
I NEVER HAD TO DO
ANYTHING FOR MYSELF.
ALL I HAD TO DO WAS
TO HANG ONTO YOUR ARM
LIKE A CHILD WITHOUT
A CARE IN THE WORLD.
[SOBBING]
I WANTED TO LIVE MY OWN LIFE,
MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS...
EVEN IF THEY WERE
TERRIBLE MISTAKES.
[CRYING]
[GRUNTING]
OH!
NO! LET GO!
STOP! I DON'T WANT
TO GO TO PRISON!
WAIT! LET GO!
HELP ME. HELP ME, PLEASE.
PLEASE HELP ME.
YOU GOT TOOHH!
UNH! UNH!
[WHIMPERING] OH, UH...
YOU'LL SURVIVE THIS.
BE STRONG...
AND TAKE CARE OF HER.
[SEA GULLS CRYING]
[POLICE RADIO]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
THEY THINK HE'LL GET OFF
WITH A SELF-DEFENSE PLEA.
[SIREN]
SO WHAT ARE
YOU GOING TO DO NOW?
WELL, I WON'T BE ON THE RUN.
I'LL JUST WAIT THERE
AT MY TAVERN FOR RHINT.
I DON'T THINK
YOU'LL BE WAITING VERY LONG...
BECAUSE TIME NEVER
STANDS STILL, YOU KNOW?
HUH?
AH.
A TERROR NEVER SEEN BEFORE...
HAS ASSAULTED
THE BEBOP. AAAH!
CAUGHT BY THE VENOMOUS
FANGS OF THE UNSEEN ENEMY,
ANOTHER VICTIM FALLS. NO!
WHO OR WHAT
IS THE FEARSOME ENEMY
THAT REFUSES
TO SHOW ITSELF? AAAAH!
A SYMPHONY OF SHIVERS
THAT WILL SEND YOU
INTO THE DEEPEST
TRENCHES OF TERROR.
NEXT EPISODE,
TOYS IN THE ATTIC.
ONCE THE CHANNEL IS SET,
YOU WILL NO LONGER
BE ABLE TO ESCAPE.