What would Takasu-kun do if I showed him the real me?
Huh?
Would you fall in love with me?
Would you?
W-Wait just a moment...
I...
Taiga? Were they there?
Taiga?
Huh? We're in a bad situation? Maybe Ami-chan's timing was really bad?
Th-This is not what you think!
TA!
I!
GA...!
Minorin!
Looks like nobody's here!
Just where did they go?
My, why are you deceiving her?
Could it be that... you don't want to accept it?
That he let a girl other than you into his house.
Idi-! Don't say it like that!
Aww, but...
No buts!
Come on, just tell her the real deal!
Huh? "The real deal"? No way! Takasu-kun, you're so...
H-Hey! Taiga!
Taiga!
Pool Opening Day
Good morning!
Huh? Taiga-chan, did anything happen?
No, I don't even have anything anymore.
I wonder what today's dinner is going to be?
We're having a rice bowl dish. You like those, don't you?
Is that so?
Shouldn't you have made red rice instead?
What?
Right, ugly bird?
Ugly?
Hey, Taiga. About what happened this evening...
Ugly... ugly... ugly...
I was just being teased by Kawashima. And, um...
It looks like it left a bad impression.
Ugly! Ugly... ugly! Ugly...
I'm sorry.
Exactly what might you be apologizing for?
Ryuuji is quite a weird guy, isn't he?
I-Inko-chan!
Hang in there, Inko-chan!
Get a hold of yourself!
Taiga! Wake up!
Oh man, it's so late-
That hurt.
Huh?
S-Sorry.
What?
I mean, we've overslept!
Hurry up and get yourself ready as quickly as you can!
What's for breakfast? Why did you wake me up this way today?
There's no breakfast or lunchbox! If we don't leave in five minutes, we'll be late!
Ah jeez, if we don't go by a convenience store, we won't have any lunch!
Hey! Are you listening?
Tai... ga?!
I'm listening, perverted dog! The convenience store, right?!
What's up with you?!
Just because you haven't had any breakf- Ow!
Made it!
Ah, he's finally here!
Thanks for doing all that you did for me yesterday.
No- Uh, um. Yeah.
What's that? Were you dazzled by my summer uniform?
Just kidding!
You're blocking traffic, stupid chihuahua.
O-Oh, you were here, Aisaka-san? Good morning.
Good morning, Kawashima-san. I see that you're still in heat.
Hey... you two...
Oh, I see. My, how awful.
Don't get so jealous over such a trivial matter.
It was all Aisaka-san's misunderstanding, after all.
You're one dumb woman, aren't you?
What happened yesterday was just-
Forgotten!
Good morning, everyone!
Oh! I could tone my upper arms by doing this!
Minorin, don't use me for muscle training!
.
Information
about the
pool opening
day
Okay! Tomorrow is our long-awaited pool opening day!
I'll explain the important points now.
Summer is the season for love. The final chance of my twenties!
Oh no, my stomach...
And my thighs...
My upper arms are even worse!
What the hell are you lot saying?
Just being young is enough, for crying out loud!
Really? Swimming classes at this school are co-ed?
Oh no, that's so embarrassing.
Why worry?! You're super cute. And you're a model too! What's so embarrassing, huh?!
.
Information
about the
pool opening
day
Swimsuits
can only be
black or
navy blue
Bikinis
are not..
HUH? What is? Huh?! What is, huh?! WHAT IS SO EMBARRASSING, HUH?!
Teacher, that's about it for homeroom.
All right, finish it!
Rise!
Taiga, come on!
No way! I don't need to buy a swimsuit!
Since last year's has already gone rotten, it can't be helped!
You've got to wash and dry swimsuits right away after all.
I said I don't wanna! And why is that here?
Because this is the only shop that sells swimsuits.
I-It's not like I invited her!
Hey, hey!
Wouldn't this look great on Aisaka-san?
Actually, it would fit her way too well!
Calm down, Taiga! We're in public!
Takasu-kun, what do you think about this one?
U-Umm... I-It'd l-look g-great on y-you-
Hey.
How's this?
It's not weird, right? It's not too conspicuous, right?
What's up with the length of those legs?! You're being really conspicuous!
Oh, really? I even went and picked a plain swimsuit too...
K-Kawashima-san! Which brand is that swimsuit? Where did you find it?
Over there. You want to get matching ones?
Anything but that! Spare me from that!
Kushieda...?
Hey, hey!
Ami-chan's super-duper-super cute in this! So cute that it's scary!
And in this plain swimsuit! How far can I go with it?
With this cuteness, this beauty, this body! Hiding it is like some kind of crime!
You think so too, don't you, Takasu-kun?
Huh?
Hey! You okay in there, Tai-?
What are you do-?!
I don't know what to do anymore.
Why? What's wrong?
No matter what I do, I can't decide.
What about them is bothering you?
You can't pick one in any other color than navy blue or black.
That's not it! I can't find one that fits!
Umm... How about child-size...?
Over my dead body!
Don't say what the stupid chihuahua said.
I-Isn't this one rather small?
It's not too expensive and it's thick and sturdy. You can even put it in a dryer.
Did you try it on?
I tried...
putting that one on...
It was... more or less okay...
But it was... um...
Then this one will do... won't it?
Yeah... you're right...
Taiga, what do you want for dinner?
I'll make whatever you want.
Oh, yeah! Did you prepare for the pool tomorrow?
Don't forget a towel. A bath towel.
Shut up.
Why you...!
What are you so disgruntled over?
The swimsuit?
Or are you still angry about last evening?
No, that's not it!
Then what is it?!
I... can't swim! That's what's bothering me!
When you say it like that, there's no way that's the real reason!
Oh no, I'm going to be late!
Hey, wait up!
Drink this before you go.
Thank you, Ryuu-chan!
Ow, hot.
What's that?
Ryuu-chan's special soy milk!
He says that the soybeans and the isonobonbons or something that it has will make my breasts bigger!
Isoflavone.
I can't have them shrivel up, so this is a precaution.
Yacchan's so smart!
Taiga-chan's perverted, sketchy, one-touchy!
Don't sexually harass people's mothers!
I'm going out then~
Sheesh, she's so noisy.
What's up with you? You're being weird.
Soybean...
Hey!
That was horrible, gimme more!
What the hell are you doing?
I want to stock up on isonobonbons too!
What? Why would you wan-?
The size of her swimsuit...
and isoflavone...
Taiga, could it be that you-?
No, don't say it! Don't say anything else!
You're...
flat-chested?
Sheesh... why would you fret over that?
Fretting over the size of your breasts...
Here I am.
Y-Yeah...
How is it?
It's flat, right? Really flat-chested?
No... w-well...
What about the cups?
They're in, but...
Th-They're collapsing.
This is why I don't like going to the pool.
E-Either way, go put something on. You'll catch a cold otherwise.
What's this?
By looking at that, even you will be able to understand my grief.
Pitiful
Breasts
This is...
Pitiful
Breasts
rather mean...
Pitiful
Breasts
"Pitiful breasts"? "Pitiful"? I'm being pitied for the flatness of my breasts!
Pitiful
Breasts
No - well, that's only the opinion of the person who wrote this.
Pitiful
Breasts
Naturally, I made it rain blood over the photography club that I got it from.
Now that you mention it, the photography club did suddenly cease operations...
And now I've got to expose this pathetic appearance to Kitamura-kun... I don't want to...
I don't want to...
Hey, Taiga?
Okay. I'll do something about it.
Huh?
I'll make sure you'll be able to stand before Kitamura...
with your chest out proud.
It's all right, you can go home and sleep.
No, I'll stay here and wait for you to finish.
I will stay up until Ryuuji's finished.
Hey.
Yeah?
Like... like, well...
I was being stubborn and moody... so...
I'm sorry.
How is it?
When I become a bride, I will take these with pride!
Maruo!
Maruo, you look better without glasses! Switch to contact lenses!
Really now?
For sure! Right?
I'm not wearing glasses either, you know...
Yes.
Girl's dressing room
Bye, then, Aisaka-san.
I'm going on ahead.
Taiga.
Hurry up! I'll do your hair for you.
O-Okay...
Maya-chan, I'm sorry!
I was having trouble getting my hair right!
Sorry for making you wait!
Ami-chan!
Wow, that's a model for you!
Your body sure is nice.
No, not at all.
I'm just... so moved!
No, really, you're completely different from us.
It's a goddess!
Again...
You're damn right I am!
Ami-chan's cute today too!
Behold, foolish mortals! I will allow you to grovel in my angelic presence and worship me!
Come now, lick my shadow! It's like the highest quality gourmet food to you, right?!
Don't tease me like that, Maya-chan.
Aha! Takasu-kun!
Minorin, don't run! My hair will fall apart again!
Okay, it's time for warm-up exercises!
Doing some running...
...but it's a feint!
Minorin?
Kushieda?
I've figured it out!
Huh?
I figured that as long as I'm in the water, I won't need to show my stomach to anyone.
And thus, I am now going to do some swimming. Ciao!
Minorin...
My, Aisaka-san, you're finally here.
I was afraid your swimsuit might be so baggy that you'd be too ashamed to come out.
Huh? What are you saying, are you talking in your sleep? Are you asleep?
Sheesh!
Man, I don't want to get sunburned.
It's perfect.
I'm so impressed she's come this far in one year! I'm a fan of Taiga after all!
Oh, so you've got a normal figure.
The scale's completely off as always, though.
Success!
Yeah!
Fake breast special force.
She knows.
That's Minorin for you.
Aisaka?
Huh? You're Aisaka, right?
I can't see too well since I'm not wearing glasses, but with that figure, you must be Aisaka!
Why are you hiding yourself? Especially when you are looking great with the mouse hairstyle.
G... Go away!
Huh?
What?!
Did I say something wrong?
Wh-Who knows?
Hey, show us your biceps!
Like this?
Wow, amazing!
Being all...
popular on his own!
We raise an objection to this desparate society!
'THIS IS SUMMER' DROP!
Maruo!
Hey.
Hey, are you all right?!
Let's do it too!
Usually you're allowed to do whatever you want in this class, but...
Isn't this a little too dangerous?
Right, Tai-?
Kitamura-kun said my hair was cute...
No, he said it looked great...
Target spotted!
Let's go, softball club comrade!
Yeah!
All right! Next!
Acknowledged, Big Boss!
Yay, you got tossed in.
That really looks like fun, doesn't it, Aisaka-san?
Y-You!
Let's play and have some fun!
This isn't personal, now!
Whoa.
Hey, hold back a little!
Why should I? We're just playing!
Hey, Taiga! You okay?
Taiga?
She...!
I... can't swim!
Don't tell me...
She really can't swim?!
You're kidding me!
Wai- Stop it!
Come now, come now!
Taiga!
Teacher!
N-No!
Calm down, Taiga!
What should I do?! The cup came off!
There's only one side left!
Wha-?!
Hey, isn't that bad?
Aisaka!
Taiga!
I'm coming now!
No, don't come!
Taiga!
Damnit!
Now that it's come down to this-!
Taiga!
The humiliation...
Look, I'm saying that I'm sorry!
I didn't know that you can't swim.
Everyone's gone home already, so just get over it already.
This won't be settled by a mere apology.
Because you did that crap...
My br-breast... br-br-bre-!
Either way!
Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize!
At any rate, if Aisaka-san can't swim, she can't come along to the pool or the sea together with us.
Hey, Takasu-kun, my vacation home is by the sea. If you'd like, how about we spend the summer vacation together?
What?
Wait a sec. Weren't you just apologizing to Taiga?
Then, well, how about I bring Yuusaku along too? You'd come then, right?
Oh? Is something wrong, Aisaka-san?
If you keep this crap up...
I'll spread around the footage I took of you doing 100 different imitations in rapid succession.
Wait, it was 150, wasn't it?
If you do that, I might just sue you for infringing on portrait rights.
Not even a Palmtop Tiger can win against the hand of the law, can it?
Hey, you two.
Stop this right now!
Your fists...
will get hurt.
But, but! Listen, Minori-chan, Aisaka-san's been treating me-
It's this moron chihuahua's fault!
Wa-! What the hell are you saying?!
The one who started-
Shut up right this instant!
If you want to develop your friendship using your fists...
don't do it with fighting, but instead...
fight it out with sports!
S...
Sports...?
Next Episode Preview
For whose sake?
Takasu competition!
Ami-tan VS Taiga?!
Why's Takasu getting into all the good stuff?!
Wah, snatch me away and mess me up too!