No one's home.
Well, I am, but I'm not.
Just drop it off.
Now then...
Dammit!
What a big box.
Must be delivered by Feb 13
Hm?
Valentine's Gift
Yup, this is it.
Interesting.
I'm home!
Sasami, your brother's home!
Would you like to have dinner, take a bath, or do you want me to—
Dinner.
Okay.
I picked up a fine piece of fish today. Spanish mackerel—
And?
For dessert, there's jelly and—
Pudding.
I'm surprised you knew I bought pudding.
But I should've known better.
You know everything about me.
Because you love me so much!
Now, eat up.
Feed me.
What a baby.
I'm gonna starve to death.
Oh all right then.
Say ahh.
Ahh.
Brother!
How may I be of service to you, Sasami?
Come wash me.
You're such a baby.
Sasami.
Why don't you try going to school soon?
Can't.
You're still 16.
A young person like yourself has a bright future
and an infinite amount of potential.
You know there's nothing you can't do.
Nope.
You didn't get into highschool for nothing.
Why don't you try enjoying highschool life a little?
Can't.
Oh, if only you came! My uneventful, boring job
as a teacher would become much more exciting.
Stop depending on me.
Dry me.
Okay, Sasami.
Dress me.
Immediately, Sasami.
Brush my teeth.
Aye aye, Sasami.
You're not going to sleep yet, Sasami?
Staying up late is bad for your skin.
Shut up.
Oh, don't be afraid to yell if you need anything.
Otherwise, I'll see you tomorrow!
Oh, it's time for that new anime.
kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
It all starts at the tips of gods' fingers
watashi no kisetsu tachi
They are where my seasons begin
hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
Disturbing me from a long slumber
nemuri wo yusabutta
Slumber so long, longer than the stars
Sasami@Unmotivated
mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
When I covered my ears walking in the crowd
watashi ga kieta mitai datta
It felt as if I had disappeared
kokoro wo enjiru ni wa
Yes, I want to express my true feelings,
zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm too immature to use pretty words
deatta kouya no hana
I see flowers blooming in the wild
kowakkute yasashikute
They're fearful and gentle
fureta shunkan ni jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I brush through them,
it turns dioramas into realities
kamisama no itazura de egakareta
The map of my future is drawn by the gods
watashi no miraichizu
Drawn by mere whims of the gods
ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
It rings with thousands of sounds
oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
And breaks through tomorrow, chasing after today
hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
When we tightened our bonds under the watch of the stars
nukumori ga mieta yo
I found your warmth
kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our bond forms with the blood we shed
mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
But it's the kind of bond I'm compelled to protect
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 1
I'll start trying tomorrow
Say ahh.
Ahh.
Again.
I'll be going to school.
Please come whenever you feel like it.
Brother.
Here.
Lunch.
Lunch from you?
Oh, what a wonderful day it is.
I'll make today a Sasami Day.
Wait a minute, but today is February 14th!
The Day Sasami Licked
The Day Sasami Made Eye Contact
The Day Sasami ate Cream Puffs
The Day Sasami felt Warm
Sasami's Suzuki Day
The Day Sasami Munched
The Day Sasami Stumbled
The Day Sasami's
The Day Sasami
Felt Soft
Sasami, you're so, so, so cute!
The Day Sasami Felt Squishy
The Day Sasami Looked Urban
Sasami's Beautiful Sunday
Sasami Sasamii Sasamiii
We're already celebrating today as the day you stumbled
The Day Sasami Stumbled
and the day your love for me was immeasurable.
The Day Sasami's Love for
Brother was Immeasureable
Oh, but it's okay.
I'll note this as also being Sasami's
Lunch Day and celebrate it all the same!
Stop!
It's lunch.
You have to wait until noon.
Oh, I see.
If you say so.
Have a nice day.
Thanks, see you later!
Initializing the Brother Surveillance System.
Well, I'm off.
Kamiomi
Tsukuyomi
Sasami
It's as if Sasami and I are married.
Jeez, just go to school already.
Oh?
Ribbit, ribbit.
I'm a cute, healthy froggy!
Tama!
Good morning, Paparin!
What are you doing?
You'll catch a cold.
Well, I couldn't find any froggies...
So I decided to become one!
Ribbit, ribbit!
The froggies are hibernating right now.
Hibernating?
How would you feel if someone
was being noisy while you slept?
I'd kill them!
Right? You should let them sleep.
You can play with them again when it's spring.
Okay.
I won't wake them up!
Oh no, I'm hungry.
Oh dear...
Here, you can have this.
I was going to eat this for lunch, but I can just get something at the store.
What an idiotic brother.
I won't let you have your way today!
Not again...
I...
can't...
Brother...
I really...
can't...
Ribbit, ribbit
Barf
I still can't do it.
Stupid brother.
That was the first time I ever gave anyone chocolate.
You can pop my cherry
Miss Tsurugi, I don't think you should be playing adult games in the office.
Shut up~ Go to hell (^o^)
That was some perfectly good barley tea I just spit out.
By the way, Tsukuyomi.
Did you get any chocolate?
No, not really.
I see.
Take this.
D-Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm just taking pity on you.
Hm?
Basically, your very first Valentine's chocolate...
came...
from...
me.
I was going to give him his first...
You prepubescent hag! How dare you!
Ribbit, ribbit
Barf
I give up.
This life's just impossible.
The more I try, the more gone to waste.
I feel sick watching you.
But you see, Kagami, I'm bored.
Oh, I know!
Kagami, why don't we talk?
Pick a topic of your choice.
Sasami today, Sasami yesterday, why Sasami looks appealing,
the day I had a fight with Sasami, or maybe you'd
like to hear about embarrassing things she's done?
Let's talk and talk endlessly about Sasami until we're bored out of our minds!
There's no better topic to talk about!
Hello?
I was asleep.
Kagami!
What do you want?
Tama!
P-Paparin.
Oh, well, you see...
I love you too, Paparin, but I think
we should start as friends, I mean...
What am I supposed to do?
I'm dying...
Well, whaddya know.
All of us sisters are here now!
S-Sister...
Tsurugi!
I don't know what you're talking about, but you better not leave me out of it.
You see, you see...
Paparin proposed to me!
Come again?
She must've gotten the wrong idea about the chocolate.
Valentine's Day?
Well, basically, it's the day you give chocolate to someone you like.
I-Is that true?
No, it just can't be!
Unlike me, Sasami has common sense,
meaning she'd know about Valentine's Day.
She loves me, I know, but I didn't get chocolate from her.
Oh, I got it!
She must be planning to give it to me at dinner in a maid outfit, as she tells me she loves me.
Over my dead body.
I have no time to waste.
I must swiftly go buy a ton of chocolate.
But that makes me feel better.
He just didn't know about Valentine's Day.
Fine, I guess I'll buy him more chocolate.
(To your beloved brother)
Valentine Chocolate
Customers who bought this item also bought
Oh, I didn't know a new volume of this manga was out.
Let's see what happens in this volume.
Unable to be honest with themselves, they get in a fight.
But seeing Choco's tears, Cocoa repents and aims to to be a professional chocolate chef?
Chocolate is my life!
Chocolate is amazing!
I don't care about Choco anymore!
A shocking new plot development!
That's too much development...
I thought I was reading Angels' Love.
Angels' Chocolate...
Where did the Chocolate come from?
Huh?
A new Blu-ray release, Choco and Choco and and Chocolate?
This one's only about chocolate.
What happened to love and elections?
With the school festival approaching, their chocolate becomes even closer?
Action packed battles with swords, magic, and chocolate?
This work contains radical artwork and chocolate.
Chocolate gets stolen by chocolate and gets chocolated. A sad tale about chocolate.
The two who chocolated to each other as if to chocolate became chocolates?
Now it doesn't even make sense.
Oh, duh!
This must be some joke they're doing for Valentine's Day!
The other sites should be fine.
Chocolate Department Chief Expresses Chocolate.
Chocolate Chief
Re: I was told I won't be able to succeed in life unless I went to the Chocolate Party.
Chocolate Party
Regarding the Chocoslovakia Problem.
Chocos
Today's weather is chocolate with a chance of white chocolate.
Some places may experience
chocolate with macadamia nuts.
Chocolate Time
What's going on?
Don't tell me...
Wow, look at all of these different chocolates.
I'll buy her a ton of chocolates! And then she'll be like,
"I can't eat all this. You can have some too, my dear brother.
Don't get me wrong. I just don't want to get fat from all of this chocolate."
I can picture her being shy like that.
That way, I can legally get chocolate from her.
Shoot...
The world's already being altered.
This is straight out of Hansel and Gretel.
Tama, you can eat as much as you'd like today.
Really?
Bring it on!
I'll beat the crap out of you!
Time to eat!
Delicious!
You're too mild.
No pun intended.
You'll have to do bitter than that.
Pun intended.
Now eat this.
No pun intended.
You idiot!
That was the perfect moment to use your boob missiles!
It doesn't matter if you're flat!
Nobody asked you.
Chocolate! Chocolate! Oh, chocolate!
All right.
Objective: Tsukuyomi's house.
Know your place, evil god!
Kagami, copy the world.
Restore the world of man to its original state.
I'm home!
Sasami, your brother's home.
Did you know it's Valentine's today?
It's supposed to be a day where women give men chocolate,
but since my love transcends age, gender, and blood,
I don't see any issues with me giving you chocolate!
S-Sasami!
I see...
This must mean... "Eat me!"
Then I'll help myself! I'll lick you, bite you, and chew you, and I'll... I'll...
You've... got...
to be...
kidding me...!
Go to hell!
We... didn't have another choice...?
Get out!
This is my house!
Sasami@Unmotivated
I'm so tired.
I'm never ever trying, ever again.
Oh, but the world doesn't work the way you want, Sasami.
You're going to be singing the
ending theme every episode, okay?
Get a mic!
Sing your heart out, loud and clear!
What?
And whose genius idea was that?
Give me a break. I'm gonna kill him.
Sasami, you're being too blunt.
You need to be cuter.
End your sentences with "meow."
You're asking for way too much.
But look.
I have the song recorded playing in the background.
Isn't that good enough?
I don't have to sing every time, do I?
I don't, right?
Oh, but being able to broadcast your beautiful, lovely voice to the entire nation's living rooms
is as priceless as the world itself.
Hello, Sasami, can you hear me?
No, don't get in bed.
Oh, you think you can just go to sleep?
Let's put in a little effort.
Effort won't ever betray you!
Well, looks like Sasami decided not to get out of bed.
But next time, I'm sure we'll broadcast her beautiful voice to all of you!
Get your hopes up!
Sasami@Unmotivated
It's time for the unmotivational fortune.
Unmotivational Fortune
This week's love fortune.
Normalfag Capricorns
This Week's Love Fortune
Unmotivational Fortune
It's a great week for normalfag-Capricorns in relationships.
Spend time with your lovers like normalfags with lovers should.
Your lucky item is light blue. Something good might happen.
Capricorns without lovers will... be fine.
Capricorns Without Lovers
Something good will happen if you're alive... probably.
Don't worry about it. Quit crying.
Next time, episode two:
Next Time
Episode Two
In-House Security Guard.
In-House Security Guard