Germany, Einzbern Castle
—Eight Years Ago—
My lord Kiritsugu!
Your child is born!
She's so cute.
So small, so delicate...
She has your eyes.
I'm so glad we were able to have this child.
Iri.
I will cause your death...
I know.
This has been the wish of the Einzberns for generations.
It is the very reason I exist.
I am the person I am now because I internalized your ideals,
and I intoned your prayers.
You have guided me.
You offered me a better life than that of a simple puppet.
You needn't pity me.
I'm a part of you now.
So...
I...
I have no right to hold that child.
Kiritsugu, do not forget.
You're striving to make a world where no one needs to cry like that.
That is the ideal of Emiya Kiritsugu.
Eight more years, and your fight will come to an end.
And our ideal will become reality.
The Holy Grail will save you. I'm certain of it.
So take this child, Illyasviel, and hold her.
And be proud, like any other father.
Torino, Italy
—Three Years Ago—
A command seal?
Yes, the mark that appeared on your right hand.
It identifies you as a participant in the Holy Grail War.
A stigmata, bestowing upon you the power to command a Servant.
Kotomine Kirei.
The Holy Grail War.
The battle for a relic that performs miracles...
And I have been chosen?
Normally, the Grail chooses seven magi, as Master to the Servants.
It's highly unusual for someone like you,
with no connection to magic, to be chosen so early.
Servants...
I still think it's strange...
to summon and command the spirits of ancient heroes to fight for you.
I know it's hard to believe.
Heroes from every age and nation will rise again,
killing one another to establish their supremacy.
That is the Holy Grail War.
Naturally, there is an unspoken agreement among all involved parties,
that the battles are enacted in secret.
To ensure that is the case,
we of the Holy Church send an observer.
Can one of us really act as a judge
in a battle between magicians?
A Magus Association member
would be too partial to one party.
And thus, as he did sixty years ago,
we will have your father watch over our battle.
My father will be coming to Fuyuki City?
But doesn't it pose a problem,
for one of the judge's children to be a participant?
Tokiomi.
Let's get to the point.
Kireo, so far, everything we've spoken of is known to all participants.
But there is an additional reason
I've summoned you and Tohsaka Tokiomi here today.
And what would that be?
Actually, many years ago, we found proof
that the Holy Grail that will appear in Fuyuki City is not
the fabled relic of the Son of God.
I can believe that.
Otherwise, the order would have been given to us,
of the Eighth Sacrament Assembly.
But the Holy Grail in Fuyuki is too powerful to ignore.
It is an omnipotent wish-granting device.
Who knows what disaster it could unleash,
should it fall into the wrong hands.
Then, as a fail-safe,
if we could ensure that it at least fell into the right hands,
we would be fools not to see that through.
The Tohsaka family are magi,
but magi with a long history of friendship to the Church.
We know what kind of person Tokiomi is. And more than anything,
their intentions for the Grail are plain...
To reach the root of all knowledge.
That is the Tohsaka family's one desire.
But the Einzbern and Matou have both forgotten the wish we once shared with them...
Never mind the other Masters.
Who knows what dark plans they may harbor for the Grail.
So you are saying that the goal of my participation is to ensure
Tohsaka Tokiomi's success.
Of course, we will maintain the appearance of enemies.
But in secret, we will work together,
to defeat the other five Masters and attain certain victory.
This is the plan, Kirei.
You will be transferred
from the Church to the Magus Association, where you will become my student.
The official orders have already been issued.
You must go to Japan and study magic,
and become a magus sufficiently strong to
command a Servant in the Holy Grail war, three years from now.
Now then...
Any questions, Kirei?
Just one.
What is the Grail's intention, when it selects its Masters?
The Grail prefers to choose the Masters who need it most.
So all the Masters have a reason to covet the Grail?
Not necessarily.
I'm told that in the past, there were cases in which command seals appeared
on those whom you would never have expected to be chosen.
I see.
Kirei,
are you still upset at being chosen?
I didn't expect that he'd agree so quickly.
My son would jump into a burning fire if the Church ordered it.
To be honest, I'm almost disappointed.
From his perspective,
he's been caught up in a war that has nothing to do with him.
No, perhaps this will be best for him.
Only a few days ago, he lost his wife.
A new place and a new mission
may be exactly what he needs to recover.
Fuyuki City, Japan
—One Year Ago—
Aoi.
Kariya, it's good to see you again.
Are you back from your business trip?
This one took a long time.
Yeah, I guess it did.
Kariya!
Kariya, welcome back.
Rin.
Did you bring me a present again?
Rin!
That was rude!
Here.
Thanks, mister!
I'm happy you like it.
Where's Sakura?
Sakura's gone now.
Aoi?
You see, Sakura is no longer my daughter nor Rin's sister.
She's gone to the Matou.
Why?
You know why the Matou family would desire children
who carry the blood of magi.
The Tohsaka family elders decided to give our ancient allies,
the Matou, that which they requested.
It wasn't my place to speak out.
You're all right with that?
When I married into the Tohsaka family
and consequently took a magus for husband,
I was prepared for this.
And you're all right with that?!
A clan bearing magus blood
can never expect the happiness of a normal family.
That's not true!
When you chose him, you wanted happiness...
This is between the Tohsakas and the Matous.
You left the world of magi.
It doesn't concern you.
If you ever see Sakura, be kind to her.
She was always fond of you...
I'm amazed that a failure like you would dare show your face here.
I told you to never let me see you again.
Kariya.
I heard you adopted the Tohsaka's second daughter.
You have good ears.
Is it that important to keep magi in the Matou lineage?
And would you tell me we're wrong to?
You, of all people?
Whose fault do you think our present condition is?
Kariya.
Had you agreed to carry on the family name,
and learn the secrets of the Matou,
things wouldn't be this bad.
Stop this nonsense, you vampire.
You only want the Grail to make yourself immortal.
By next year, sixty years will have elapsed since that time.
But the Matou have no pawns to offer for the Fourth Holy Grail War.
While you might have,
your brother Byakuya lacks the power to control a Servant.
But even if we let this round pass,
we could still win the next.
The Tohsaka girl's womb will produce a powerful magus.
She has quite the potential, that one.
So as long as you get the Grail,
you don't require Tohsaka Sakura for anything?
What are you scheming?
A trade, Zouken.
During the next war, I will retrieve the Grail.
And you will release her.
Don't be stupid.
You're a failure, and you haven't trained a day in your life.
In a single year, you're telling me you'll attain the power to control a Servant?
You have the ability to make that happen,
with your control over insects.
Implant a Worm Crest inside me.
Kariya, do you want to kill yourself?
The Matous should be the ones to achieve their own goals.
I won't let anyone else get involved.
I don't expect you will worry much about me, will you, Father?
If you're trying to keep her out of this, Kariya,
you're a little late.
You old bastard, you can't have...
For the first three days, she screamed rather loudly.
But on the fourth, she stopped.
This morning, I threw her in, to see how long she'd last.
It's been twelve hours, and she's still breathing.
The Tohsaka are very powerful.
Sakura!
Well, what will you do now?
A single broken girl, violated by insects from head to toe.
If you still wish to save her,
I might consent.
Very well.
But I shall continue her education until you show results.
I shall still aim for victory in the war after this one.
But should you somehow manage to retrieve the Grail, that's fine.
I won't need the Sakura girl then.
In that case, her education will only last a year.
You won't renege on your word. Right, Matou Zouken?
You can serve as their breeding ground for a week.
If you don't die or go insane, then I'll concede that you're serious.
It's finally here.
What does it say?
It's a message from the spies I sent to the London Clock Tower.
It says the Grail chose a Master from within the highest authority
with the Magus Association, the Clock Tower.
Who?
A man who will be a problem.
The eldest son of the famous Archibald family,
which has produced nine generations of magi.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald.
London Clock Tower
—Present Day—
In the world of magi, bloodline is everything.
The secrets of magic cannot be discovered in a single generation.
A parent passes on the result of a lifetime spent training, to their child.
Thus, the older the family of magi, the greater their power.
Doubtless, you're wondering why I cover what you must already know.
It is because a student submitted this paper to me yesterday.
The paper is entitled "The Magus of the New Century".
It objects to the standard model,
stating that greater understanding of the spell
and more delicate control over prana
would enable one to overcome this handicap.
Thus, even someone with thin blood could become a master magus.
To be honest, I've learned something from reading this.
Quiet.
Let me be as plain as I can.
This paper contains nothing but juvenile fantasies.
Blood determines a magus' power.
This is hard, unchanging reality.
Waver Velvet.
I am very, very disappointed that one of my students
would indulge in this nonsense.
But, sir, I was only trying to raise a question the Magus Association
has become too reluctant to address—
Waver, my boy...
Your family has contained magi for about three generations, correct?
Listen to me.
Compared to the Magus Association's history, your family is akin to a newborn baby.
Shouldn't a baby learn to speak,
before it talks back to its elders?
Frickin' teacher! Frickin' teacher!
Frickin' teacher!
Is that how an educator should act?!
He read my paper, and he was jealous!
He's afraid of my talent.
That's why he embarrassed me in front of everyone.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Aren't you a sudent in the Evoker's Circle?
What about your lecture?
Well...
Professor Archibald asked me to run an errand for him.
So I was in a hurry...
I see.
That's great.
Would you give this to him?
This?
Thanks.
It's supposed to be important.
Important?
It was sent from Macedonia.
This is it.
Those rumors that Kayneth would be fighting
in some kind of tournament in the Far East were true.
The Holy Grail War.
Two hundred years ago, the families known as the first three,
the Einzbern, Makiri, and Tohsaka,
worked together to summon the Holy Grail,
said to have the power to grant any wish.
But the Holy Grail would answer only one prayer.
And their cooperation turned to merciless warfare.
That was the beginning of the Holy Grail Wars.
Ever since then, once every sixty years,
the Holy Grail appears in the town of Fuyuki.
It selects seven magi, carefully chosen,
and grants them the power
to summon the powerful Heroic Spirits known as Servants.
Archer.
Saber.
Lancer.
Rider.
Assassin.
Caster.
Berserker.
Divided into these seven classes, Servants fight to the death,
to determine who is worthy to win the Grail.
So this Holy Grail War is a battle of pure skill,
where titles and influence mean nothing.
It's the perfect place for me.
It also says that to summon a Servant,
a relic of theirs is needed, to act as a catalyst.
A relic...
No matter how often I see it, this device still strikes me as unseemly.
I have a report from the Clock Tower.
Lord El-Melloi has acquired another relic.
His participation is certain now.
It troubles me that two spaces are still unaccounted for.
Don’t worry.
When the time comes, the Grail will select seven,
regardless of skill.
The ones it completes the group with are nearly always weak.
There’s no need to concern ourselves with them.
Speaking of concerning matters,
no one saw you enter the mansion, Kirei?
Don’t worry.
There are no familiars or magical devices, visible or invisible,
watching this mansion.
I guarantee…
I guarantee it.
No matter what tricks they use,
no one can deceive the eyes of Hassan, master of strategems.
There is no trace of anyone following my Master.
Be at peace.
Once a Servant manifests, my father will know.
The other magi will not act for a while yet.
Assassin, you may go.
Continue guarding the surrounding area.
As you wish.
However it’s only a matter of time until they do.
Eventually, the other Masters’ familiars are sure to flock to this place.
What is that?
Something else entirely.
I was gathering information on the Einzbern Master.
Nine years ago, the Einzberns,
a family famous for their pride over the purity of their bloodline,
suddenly allowed in a magus from outside the family.
The Einzberns have devoted themselves solely to alchemy,
making them unfit for combat.
Their losses in previous Holy Grail Wars can all be traced to that fact.
They must have run out of patience.
The man they chose was perfect for the role…
Emiya Kiritsugu.
The man known as the Magus Killer.
The relic we've been searching for in Cornwall these past years has finally been found.
If you use it as a catalyst,
you'll be able to summon what is likely the strongest
of the sword-wielding Servants.
Kiritsugu.
This is the greatest gift the Einzbern can offer.
I am honored, Elder.
This time, there are to be no survivors.
Slay the other six Servants,
and complete the third true magic, "Heaven's Feel."
Understood.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
I know that name.
So even the Church has heard of him?
Emiya, the Magus Killer, was quite infamous in his time.
On the surface he was a rogue magus, who didn't belong to the Association.
But the higher-ups found him quite convenient when he served their own agenda.
Is he like our Executors?
Worse.
Essentially, he's a freelance assassin who specializes in killing magi.
He knows magi and what they're capable of,
so he deals with them in the most remote way from magic as possible.
Read this.
Sniping.
Poison.
Public bombing.
He brought down an entire jetliner,
just because his target was on it.
A man who will do anything without a second thought.
The world's laws do not apply to magi,
so we must carefully obey the laws we set for ourselves.
But he lacks any trace of a magus' pride.
His methods are unforgivable.
Then what does this Emiya Kiritsugu
hope to gain by killing?
Money, I would imagine.
As you can read in the reports,
he's been involved in more than just magus assassinations.
He's appeared in war zones all over the planet,
offering his services as a mercenary.
May I borrow this report for a while?
Let’s go over what we know, Iri.
Of the seven masters the Grail will choose, we know four.
Tohsaka Tokiomi,
the Tohsaka family head.
A magus of the Fire attribute, specializing in Jewel Magic. Very strong.
Matou Kariya.
So they took the kid who left the family and made him a Master, huh?
That old man must be desperate.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald.
He has an affinity for Wind and Water,
and is an expert in Necromancy, Summoning, and Alchemy.
And…
Emiya Kiritsugu.
Newest member of the Einzbern family, and their trump card.
The man I love.
And the fourth… no, fifth, is an agent of the Church,
Kotomine Kirei.
The Church?
He’s the son of the judge, Kotomine Risei.
The report says that he studied under Tohsaka Tokiomi for three years,
then took his leave after his command seal appeared.
Is something wrong?
It has his personal history here…
Read it.
“Kotomine Kirei…
followed his father on pilgrimages since childhood.
Graduated from the Saint Ignatius School of Divinity, in Manresa.
Skipped two years, graduating as valedictorian.”
That's pretty impressive.
But he suddenly leaves the primrose path
and volunteers for the Holy Church.
Why would someone like that
go to work for one of the Church's secret organizations?
Maybe because of his father?
It says he's a member of the Holy Church's Assembly of the Eighth Sacrament, see?
If that's the case, he should have normally pursued that path from the start.
But until he arrived at the same place as his father,
he changed positions three times.
He was even an Executor.
An Executor?
A heretic hunter.
So sort of like...
Exactly like I once was.
A magus killer.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
His assassinations were never
isolated cases, far and few in between.
During the same general time periods, he appeared in war zones,
at times when the fierceness of combat reached its peak.
It's as if he had some obsession with chasing his own death.
His actions were clearly suicidal.
What does this mean?
Alchemy, Necromancy, Summoning, Divination, Healing.
Look at all the types of magic he's studied.
Why so many?
He gets almost to the point of mastery,
then switches to another type and never looks back.
It's like he throws away everything he learns.
Iri.
This Kotomine Kirei terrifies me.
The entire concept of self-interest is foreign to him.
His actions are
completely disconnected from any thought of risk versus reward.
There's no way he's just a freelancer, in it for the money.
The man has never experienced passion in his entire life.
He believes in nothing.
He has no wish of any kind to be granted.
For a man like that...
Then what is he after?
Why would he risk his life for the grail?
But the Grail chose Kotomine Kirei as one of the Masters.
That's right.
He must have some reason to want the Grail.
But I can't imagine what it is.
And that terrifies me.
Kotomine Kirei.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
His endless string of battles came to a sudden halt, nine years ago.
His encounter with the magi of the north,
the Einzberns, is where he found his answer.
So I must ask the question...
What did he seek in those battles?
And what, exactly, did he find?
You just barely made it.
If the Grail's chosen you,
that means you've made some progress as a magus.
I'll give you that much, Kariya.
But you look awful.
Does your left leg still work?
Don't get mad.
If you get the worms inside you worked up, they'll devour you.
Either way, I'd give you a month at best.
That's plenty.
What?
I said that's plenty.
Kariya, this is your present, for surviving an entire year.
I found the perfect relic for you.
Don't let your father's kindness go to waste.
I've got a command seal, too!
The Grail chose me!
The Grail recognized my power!
I can't just sit here...
I have to prepare to summon my Servant!
The sixth-grade girl who went missing in Fuyuki City two nights ago,
Serial Killings in Fuyuki City
Good morning, Waver.
Miki Nishimoto, was found dead this morning in the woods nearby Fukuyama Town.
Morning, Waver!
Morning, Grandpa... Grandma.
Fuyuki's getting bad these days.
It really is.
Anyway, Martha, the roosters have been pretty loud this morning.
What's going on?
We have three roosters in our yard.
Roosters?
That's right.
I wonder where they came from.
Waver, you want some coffee?
Waver, what happened to your hand?
Crap!
That mark!
Mark?
You didn't have a mark like that yesterday.
Jeez...
I wish you hadn't noticed...
Wh-What's wrong, Waver?
Waver?
Nothing's wrong.
Have some coffee.
I put lots of milk in it.
You like coffee, right?
Do I have to constantly put up the act of being their grandson,
returning home after having studied abroad?
I'll need to think of something for those roosters I stole, too.
I can't believe they really found the legendary Excalibur's scabbard.
There's not a scratch on it!
Is this thing really 1,500 years old?
The object itself is a type of Conceptual Weapon.
It doesn't rust or degrade, as ordinary physical objects do.
Just like in the legend,
it heals its bearer's wounds and keeps them from aging.
Of course, that's only with the prana its original owners supplied.
In other words, it can be used in tandem
with its summoned hero to protect its Master.
That's just like you.
A tool is just a tool, isn't it?
That goes for the Servant, too.
No matter how famous the hero,
when summoned as a Servant, they're nothing
but a tool for their master.
Anyway, one who is blinded by lofty delusions,
will never be able to win this battle.
And because you are such a person, my great-grandfather decided
that this scabbard was the relic for you.
What do you think?
Does his present not satisfy you?
Of course it does.
Acht did a wonderful job.
None of the other Masters have something this powerful.
Then what's wrong?
Given how strongly the relic is connected to it,
the spirit we're after will surely respond to the summons.
The legendary King of Knights, Arthur Pendragon.
My personal issues with his philosophy is a secondary concern.
But Excalibur's wielder
is sure to be the strongest Saber-class Servant.
That's right.
I'll have a Servant far stronger than any other.
The question is how to use that power.
To be honest, in terms of ease of use,
Caster or Assassin would be far better suited to me.
Worrying about that before you even summon it won't help.
We don't know what the King of Knights was like.
Furthermore, no matter what you decide,
once he learns of your ideal,
of your dream... he'll understand.
Just like I did.
What?
I've found my strategy...
The way I can get
the best use from the strongest Servant.
Hello, Rin.
Hello, Kirei.
Heading out?
That's some heavy luggage you have.
That's right. I'm going to live with the Zenjou family.
You're staying to fight with my dad, right?
That's why I'm here as his student.
Kirei...
Can I believe in you?
Will you promise to protect my father to the very end?
That's impossible.
If this battle were simple enough that I could make that promise,
we wouldn't have to send you or your mother away.
I guess I just can't bring myself to like you.
Rin, you shouldn't just blurt out what you're really thinking.
That will reflect badly on your father,
since he raised you.
My dad has nothing to do with it!
Listen, Kirei!
If you slack off and my dad gets hurt,
I'll show you no mercy!
Run, what are you doing?
You're yelling?
Um...
Well...
She was giving me words of encouragement before we said goodbye.
Let me help you.
That suitcase is too heavy for you.
It's fine.
I'll carry it myself.
Mr. Kotomine, please take care of my husband.
Help him achieve his wish.
I'll do my best.
Don't worry.
Excuse me.
Excellent timing.
The relic I prepared finally arrived this morning.
Have a look.
What is this?
The first snake's skin, shed long ago.
If we use it as a catalyst,
and are lucky enough to summon what we're after,
our victory is certain.
Hey, Sakura.
Surprised?
Your face...
Yeah, you know...
Seems I lost a little bit to the worms inside me.
I guess I'm not as tough as you...
You're turning into a different person, aren't you?
Maybe.
I don't have to go to the worm room tonight.
Grandfather said there will be a more important ceremony.
Yeah, I know.
So I'm going to the basement tonight.
Are you going away?
I have an important job to do, and it might take a while.
I won't have much time to talk to you.
I see.
Hey, Sakura.
When my job's over,
want to go somewhere and have fun?
With your mother and sister?
I don't have anyone I can call Mother or Sister...
Grandfather said I should think of them as if they never existed.
I see...
Mister?
Then let's take Aoi and Rin
from the Tohsakas, and go somewhere far away.
We can play like we used to.
I could see them again?
Yeah, you will.
I promise.
I have to get going.
Okay.
Bye-bye, Mr. Kariya.
Bye-bye...
You learned the summoning spell, right?
Yes.
Very well.
But I'll have you add two additional lines to the incantation.
What do you mean?
It's simple.
Kariya, your rank as a magus
is slightly below that of the other masters.
That will affect the Servant's base abilities.
This means that we have to pick the Servant's class,
so we can use its modifiers to make up for that.
Kariya.
I want you to add the enhancement of madness to the Servant you summon.
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill!
Repeat five times.
But when each is filled, destroy it.
A base of silver and iron.
A foundation of stone, and the Archduke of Contracts.
And my ancestor, my great Master, Schweinorg.
A wall to block the falling wind.
The gates at the cardinal directions close.
From the Crown, come forth and follow the forked road leading to the Kingdom.
Is a simple ceremony like this enough to summon a hero?
Surprisingly, yes.
The summoning ceremony doesn't require an elaborate invocation.
The Grail itself actually does the summoning.
As a Master,
my job is to allow the hero to stay in this world, once it's arrived,
and to give it enough prana to take physical form.
That should do it.
Iri, put the relic on the altar.
That's the last step.
Heed my words.
My will creates your body, and your sword creates my destiny.
If you heed the Grail's call and obey my will and reason,
then answer me!
I hereby swear...
That I shall be all the good in the world.
That I shall defeat all evil in the world.
But let thine eyes be clouded with chaos.
Thou, who art trapped in a cage of madness,
and I, who doth hold thy chains!
You, Seven Heavens, shrouded by the three great words of power,
come forth from the circle of inhibition...
Guardian of the Scales!
We've won, Kirei.
The battle...
is ours!
This is...
I ask of thee...
art thou my Master?
Episode 1
Summoning of the Heroes
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
I think what you and Kiritsugu seek is right.
You don't need two lords.
I promise you this.
You aren't worthy to look upon me.
You're so cool!
Your first mission is to slay Tohsaka Tokiomi.
Next Time:
False Start