I am the jumping.
Perfect!
Mou, we worrie about you!
Sorry, sorry .
A problem if this pace which they play there cannot be.
Seems go.
You let the dogs out for the extension, isn't 't?
Yeah.
We're the same view.
We want to see how strong the really you is .
As for whether or not my admittance agrees, it is best for the team to stmaina and experience !
If your instist, It cann't be helped.
U-Um
You say first, Hii.
Huh? You say first, Tsuba.
What's wrong ?
D-Do your best  e-extension.
W-We're cheering for you, you know.
Sure. Thanks.
Y-Yeah.
Hey, gather everyone up!
Of the things that are issues, my wish is fix one.
That really sounds good .
Yeah. I think that would be best.
gives me an feeling so complicated .
Yoshi is on full power.
Do avoid the burn in early game.
You are depend on.
A year ago, I thought a year ago that we'd all be fighting like this together.
I cannot hold on the excitemnet of better improvement basketball.
This team has a real wish!
OUr knowledge of things that we have learned up until now is weapnry.
Your opinion is irrelevant in of three minutes.
Give it your all!
Sure!
I am late.
Just now, we left off something to continue that we should.
Hey, is your leg doing fine?
Oh? Are you worry about it?
Thanks
That's not
Maho!
Pkay.
Here I go.
Airi!
Got it.
Hina-chan!
Oh~!
Nice Hina!
Hey, hey, have you not seen anything?
Are you Saa? Do you care ?
Huh? Of course.
Why are you [INAUDIBLE], then?
If the cause worry is my leg, you are not for worrying.
It was just a small scratch.
I'm not
If you do not become your potential, you have regerts.
Holding back I don't recommend come at me.
Im going on full power.
Hey, if you are to be like that, I am going to steal you (?).
What you want to do I won't let you
My going all out I'll show you what my full power is like.
mice shoot rena!
Now that's mor like it.
Fihgt!
Yu~tto.
Hey, alright is.
13, illegal use of hands
Five fouls; release.
You've seen my full power.
Yeah. Good defense
Next time, a foul won't be gotten by because of me.
Nex time I'll be playing keeping in mind that I'm a five-player team.
My expectations.
She to us has to apolologize, as well.
Next time if we fight, we are better.
We'll also show her how a five-player team like.
Yeah.
Two shots, [inaudible]
Everyone relaxes a bit.
Not good at this rate...
My duty of making this happy team is minee!
Nice sho Maho!
Maho-chan has grown a lot!
Yeah!
Maho's spirit is the inflience of the team as a whale.
This is fireworks.
But the only one who has grown is not Maho alone.
It's me who has defense Suzuridany, you shall not pass!
Maho!
Everyone knows how much Hina is working.
She's trying her innocence, thus attracting attentions.
Airi!
We've worked so hard and now reached up to here.
A step back cannot be!
Prismatic budo.
The bud of talent is open.
Usher, Airi!
These are they getting good?
isten up, make secure defense!
Space close!
Okay.
Even though is tense, she can see things .
She's the calm sage, the Keishin key member.
This.
As expected from Suzuridani, they shooting no matter the distance.
It's a competition, isn't it?
They're going on full power for real.
But our is not exactly losing, either.
, there's an ace (?) in Keishin.
I'll leave it to you, Tomo!
You are not to pass!.
Yosh!
What's laugh in this situation?
I'm sorry. It's just that I've got lot of fun.
[INAUDIBLE]
Therefore thank you.
Um...
Miyu is somewhat thank you for your existence.
Miyu is fightingat her full power, so I hope you'll lose.
No I'm not going to lose.
Because this match to win wants not only me.
I am connected with everyone so I know
Amazing! You're amazing, Tomoka-chan!
Tomoka, you're my shiny gift; an irreplaceable treasure!
Aya, here!
Miyu-sempai
Only thirty seconds
Krutsch time.
Hina!
Sakki!
Airi!
I am together Suzuridani a team so I fight!
Airi-san!
I'm absolutely not going to
give this ball.
But! To be connected
for the last shoot.
Tomoka!
Go Tomoka!
You win not!
Such distance she came back from?
Suzuridani loses not like this!
No count !
50-51; Suzuridani Girls' Academy victory!
You did it, Miyu!
That was good!
Thank you very much!
Sorry I didn't make in time.
There's nothing to apologize for.
啊! This fun!
Yeah!
Oh~, true, true.
Hey...
Um... well...
It was fun!
Miyu was had fun, too...
but I want to completely win,
let's play basketball in middle school again, Tomoka.
Yeah. I also want to play a match against you again
leave it to you, Aoi.
Okay. I'll take responsibility. see them off.
It's hateing but the sixth graders were really good.
Yeah. We need to work harder.
Can we that much?
We'll be able to.
One time surely
Whee. We will succeed.
Could we talk that matter?
Yes.
Um, Subaru's heart however...
Oh, I'll take him home when it's time.
Thanks.
These girls have the bound I create cannot .
Sorry I couldn't let you win yet again.
What you say Subarun?
Oh~ Onii-chan's loss is not his fault.
You're support always provides us courage and the power to fight.
That is how it is. Addendum, this match is when we did our best so far.
It's just that Suzuridani was a stronger than us.
Thanks, this match was the last lost with coach.
Today was the day the basketball ha d fun the most!
Besides...
Besides is not last
So it is, we basketball play over and over middle school.
Honestly, such fun I cannot [inaudible]
From now please teach us more.
Oh~, more more improve will make onii-chan happy happy.
Even in middle school, even high school...
You'll always be our coach!
Gals...
Why is everyone crying ?
You 're the same.
Odd It's not I'm sad.
Oh~, I'm no sad, either.
I wonder why is it.
I also...
I also we will through basketball always havee connection.
Through dick,unity
basketball perist...
Subarun
Onii-chan
subaru-san!
Sorry for making you come.
No. I don't at all.
Tomoka?
Once the match has end, I want to ask you.
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊!
pretty
啊, that day, I remember.
There are some stars I'd like to see.
You remembering makes my happy.
Um, which stars are you looking for?
Probable those
those numberous starts interconnected there I think.
Somehow they remind me of us.
It's the Player constellation.
But it's actually Taurus.
In Japanese where we call Subaru
It's a [inaudible] and distant constellation.
I'm so small it gives me an feeling so complicated .
But I'd like to reach up to it one day.
Me too... Everyone has did her best until today that in mind.
Our kind guard couch taught us about a lot of ways of the fun basketball.
Always, I wanted to express my feelingI've always wanted to tell you that.
Grade schoolers cannot play with you anymore,
but may I be the same feeling to you from now on as well?
On the contrary; I'd like to ask you something.
I'll try to shine more and more.
So stay by my side forever.
Okay.
Tomoka, you're the best.
It's morning, Subaru-kun!
You're so cute!
Good morning!
Are you saying is middle school uniform?
Yes
Subaru-san, I wanted to show soon!
It looks really good, really cute.
Thank you.
I see. Tomoka-chan and the otheres are eating an entrance ceremony.
It's thoughtful.
My Airi has mature, too.
In one place staying is bad
That's right Subaru!
The man basketball club is revive!è
We can meet staring next week.
During the break of summers, signatures were collected for a council for stuents and postpone
I'm the vice president starting this year!
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊!
Thank you Kazunagi!
Now that that's that, train!
Yeah!
I hope that you'll study strive to excercise(motion excercise) spend your future in good health and be a succesful person who contributes to the community even after having entered middle school.
please lead a polite, fulfilled life.
Yoshi! We're playing today, too!
Oh, you're enthusiasted?
It'll be our fist timing playing basketball in middle school.
Oh~, eight grades done!
I'm looking forward to it.
The first time, huh?
First time playing basket has been a while ...
That reminds, why did you start playing it Tomoka?
Huh?
When I was small, but...
Actually, my mother
Mokkan! Subarun!
Hurry hurry!
Okayaaaaay!
Even though she was said the ball will be played with mroe...
[inaudible] stupid.
It's empty, just as the rumors said.(the field is empty)
yes Only ninety-nine more( going in⁾!
Were you use the goal?
I see. I thought youplay basketball, too.
Basket?
Yeah basketball.
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊!
It's a sports where you throw in the ball to that hook.
The team throwing in the    most wins.
Can I also?
Of course!
Super fun!
I also can .