(interjection of jumping)
Peace, mang!
Peace? Cold War's over, you know?
Love and peace!
Editor's note: Wow our TL or timer is shit, he didn't even notice the background talk here.
I'm glad I wasn't born in the third world.
That's racist...
Come to think of it, aren't you Japanese, too?
Yeah.
Why are you asking that, Euphemia?
We want to see how strong you really are.
It's not like we're asking you to kill all Japanese or anything.
The only ones who should kill in basketball are those prepared to be killed.
U-Um...
You say it first, Hii.
Huh? You say it first, Tsuba.
Soup /b/?
W-We have... we have to pee.
W-We're going to let it out right here, you know.
Sure. Whatever.
O-Oh...
Hey! Hey! Listen! Hey!
QC note: Holy shit, why is this still in the final release? Text is too close to the stupid credits nobody reads!
Everyone got their fix of drugs for this match?
[Useless foreshadowing intensifies]
8.8, could be better.
What? Only 8.8?!
Shut up and roll with it.
Editor's note: She says "full power" there, but I'm in favor of translating Engrish to English.
All right! Let's rearrange their shit!
Don't overdo it, Mami.
Don't lose your head over it.
Wasn't that already two years ago? Why are you still here?
Oh~! Good question!
Let's do whatever the useless foreshadowing told us to!
>tfw no loli gf
You only have three minutes.
Give it your all!
Thai!
I'm late.
How's it goin', sis?
Hey, is your leg all right?
I thought I asked you what's up?
Baka.
Th-That's not an em dash—
Mami!
Freedom!
Here I come!
Airi!
Watcher's Note: If you pause right when this line begins, you can see that Airi actually is wearing a bra underneath. That's a pretty nice detail; make sure you appreciate it.
Got it.
Hina-chan!
Oh~!
Nice, Hina!
Whoa, I'm trippin' balls, maaaaaang.
Excuse me, but do you even have any stuff?
Huh? Of course I do.
Why are you so nervous, then?
If ya worryin' 'bout me, dun' worry ok
just scratch
I'm not an em dash—
You hear my ball bouncing from the ground with regrets?
;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;
Cogito ergo I own you.
Please fondle my buttocks.
Monty Python is so 90s.
I'll show you what my buttocks are like!
Nice shoe, Rena!
Now that's more like it.
TL note: Note that "Shoubu" can mean "battle", "duel", "fight", "rape" and "shoe club" in the sense of a club at school. The correct translation is most likely "duel", but as some fags on  /a/ think they need to be weebs, I'll leave this up for you to decide. I'm really sorry for writing a huge TL note like this, but it can't be helped.
Shoubu!
(interjection of respawning)
Look, I'm a foreigner.
Number 13, iiigal usu ofu handosu!
Five fouls; dismissed!
You've seen my buttocks.
Yeah. Now if you could stop going on about them...
I won't get a foul for it next time, no matter what.
Next time, I'll play with awkward grammatical constructions.
I have expect.
She's gotta apologize, too.
We'll have improved next time we're fighting.
We'll also show her how a to lose a game with style.
Nin.
If I score twice, it'll be a (neck-)tie.
Everyone will take another injection.
I won't get my fix at this rate...
It's my duty to make this team happy.
Nice shoe, Mami!
Mami-chan has grown a lot!
Ah!
When Maho sets fire to Dumbledore's chicken, the whole team follows suit.
So as I pray, Unlimited Fire Works.
But not only Mami has grown.
Rena told me to fondle your buttocks.
Mami!
Everyone knows how much Hinata-chan is stroking.
People want to stick it into their eyes (wtf TL?).
Airi!
We've worked so hard and got so far.
But in the end, it doesn't even matter.
Prismatic Butt.
Editor's note: I guess that's not the only butt that's opened to Subaru...
The butt of talent is opened!
Hell yeah, Airi!
Aren't they getting better and better?
Requesting backup!
Stop wasting your tibbers when you don't even have stun!
Okay.
She's aware of her surroundings, even in this tension.
She's Ice Age, Keishin's key member.
Gibe ball plox.
Sasuga Suzuridani; they're shooting no matter the BR spam.
They have the potential to become great trolls...
They're rearranging shit for real.
But we're not exactly losing, either.
Besides, there's an ape in Keishin.
TIMER, YOU ARE SO FUCKING FIRED
You're not going past my armpit smell!
Blatant lies!
What's there to laugh about?
I'm sorry. It's just that my fun senses are tingling.
If I, by any chance, hadn't lost my virginity to Subaru-san,
I wouldn't have known basketball was this fun.
So, thank you.
Quoi...
Miyu (I) is grateful that you're here.
Mais parce que je pense, tu existes.
Non. Je vais pas Padro.
Because it's not just me who wants to win this match.
I know it because I'm one with the team's AIM waves.
Amazing! You're amazing, Tomoka-chan!
Tomoka, you're my slippery slope, my Shiny Gift, my irreplaceable treasure!
Aya, gibe ball plox!
Miyu-senpai!
Watcher's note: Interestingly, you'll find that she says thirty seconds here, but the game ends in one minute if you go by video time. What a lying cunt.
Only thirty seconds left.
Clutch time.
Hina!
Saki!
Airi!
I will fight with full power, as a member of Suzuridani.
Airi-san!
I'm absolutely not going to
hand over this ball.
Since we need to be hugging naked in space...
for the last shot.
Tomoka!
Go, Tomoka!
I won't let you win!
What the fuck?!
Suzuridani isn't going to lose like this!
No caunto!
50-51; Suzuridani Girls' Academy wins.
You did it, Miyu!
Fan-fucking-tastic!
Thank you very much!
I'm sorry I didn't make it in time.
Just suck Subaru's dick and it's all good.
His one-inch manlihood, haha!
Yeah!
Oh~, true, true.
Hey...
Um... well...
It was fun!
It was fun for me, too...
but I want to get an overall win,
so let's play basketball in middle school again, Tomoka.
Yeah. I also want to play a match against you again.
Fuck it, you do it, Aoi.
Okay. I'll take responsibility and see them off.
The sixth grader's A-cup angst is annoying.
Yeah. They need to grow a pair.
I wonder if we can do that.
We'll be able to.
Sooner or later.
Oui. We will succeed.
Could I show you how to increase your girth?
Yes.
Um, what about Subaru?
Oh, I'll take him home when it's time.
Thanks.
He just doesn't let me get as close as I want to...
I'm sorry, I couldn't get any panty shots.
What are you talking about, Subarun?
Oh~, it's not your fault we've lost, Onii-chan.
Hasegawa-san is a master troll.
Yeah. Besides, I can't into basketball at all.
It's just that Suzuridani was a slight bit longer than us.
Thanks, but it can't be helped.
Today was the day I had most fun that it can't be helped.
Besides...
Besides, it can't be helped.
That's right, we'll be playing basketball all the way through middle school.
I'm so euphoric, I tip my non-existent fedora.
Please teach us a lot from now on as well.
Oh~, we'll make you so satisfied by getting better and better.
Even in middle school and in high school...
You'll always be our coach.
Doubt it.
Jesus Christ on an unkempt illegal immigrant's pogo stick... Why is everyone crying?
You're not any better.
It's strange. I'm not even sad.
Oh~, I'm not sad, either.[BLATANT LIES]
I wonder why.[Because you're not choking on his dick right now, duh]
I also...
I also think that we'll be connected through basketball forever...
As long as there's basketball, forever.
I wish I grew a basketball tree.
Subarun!
Onii-chan!
Subaru-san!
Sorry for making you come.
No worries. I enjoyed the ride.
Tomoka?
I wanted to ask you to do a scoop shot after the match.
SUGOI!
They're beautiful!
Yeah. It reminds me of that day.
There are some stars I'd like to see.
I'm glad you remember it.
Um, which stars are you looking for?
Probably those.
I believe that this looks like Madoka and Homura hugging in space.
Somehow, they remind me of us.
It's the Player constellation.
But it's actual name is the Taurus constellation.
It is name is Subaru in Japanese.
It's a dazzling and distant constellation.
I'm so small I can't reach it.
But I'm just human, so I can't reach it. But I want to.
I... Everyone has died their best until today having that in mind.
Our kind, guarding couch has taught us a lot about how fun basketball is.
I've always wanted to tell you that.
I won't be playing any more matches as a grade schooler,
but can I be the same to you from now on as well?
Quite the contrary, I'd like to ask you something.
I'll try to shine more and more.
Editor's note: "shine"? Does it really say so? No clue what this loli casanova means.
So please stay by my side forever.
Okay.
Tomoka, you're the best.
It's morning, Subaru-kun!
You're so cute!
I commend your ability to get up this early!
Is that your streetwalker uniform, maybe?
Yes, it is.
I was hoping to show it to you before anyone else.
It looks really good on you. You're really cute.
Thank you.
I see. So Tomoka-chan and the otheres are eating an entrance ceremony.
It really makes me think...
My Airi has blown up, too.
Well, we can't stand in one place, either.
That's right, Subaru!
The male basketball club has been revived.
We can meet starting next week.
Huh?
Fuck that shit...
But why?
I've gathered signatures and handed in an application to the student council during the break.
I'm the vice president starting this year!
Nobody cares!
Thank you, Kazunagi!
Now, since that's settled, let's practice!
Yeah!
Typesetter's note: Keeping three-liner here because this guy just doesn't shut up and the long subs reflect that well.
I hope that you'll study, strive to exercise, spend your future in good health and be a successful person who contributes to society, even after entering middle school.
words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words words
All right! We're playing today, too!
Oh, you're pretty euphoric, huh?
It'll be our fist timing playing basketball in middle school.
Oh~, eight grade's over!
I'm looking forward to something.
The first time, huh?
It's been a long time since the first time I played basketball.
Come to think of it, why did you start playing, Tomoka?
Huh?
It happened when I was still a microbe...
Actually, my mother—
Mokkan! Subarun!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Okay!
And she even said we'd try to insert the ball...
Stupid Mom.
It's empty, just as the rumors said.
All right! Only ninety-nine more!
Were you using the ape, maybe?
I see. I thought you were playing with cowbells, too.
Cowbells?
Yeah. Basketball.
SUGOI!
It's a sport where you need to throw in the ball to that ook.
The team throwing in the most wins.
Can I also become basketball?
Of course!
It's a lot of fun.
Me too...