Where... am I?
I can't remember anything.
Are you awake?
Who are yo-
Welcome.
To the To Hell With Dying Warfront.
I know it's sudden, but won't you enlist with us?
Huh?  Enlist?
The fact that you're here means that you've died.
Huh?  Um, I don't really understand what you-
This is the world after death.
If you don't do anything, you'll be erased.
Erased?  By who?
By God, of course.
Then, what do you mean by enlist?
Enlist in the To Hell With Dying Warfront.
Well, the name of the unit changes sometimes.
Previously it was the Shinda Sekai Sensen, or the Afterlife Warfront.
But if you go ahead and call it the afterlife...
That makes it sound like you're accepting your death, right?
We changed the name because of that,
and we're in the process of working on the new one.
Right now, it's To Hell With Dying Warfront.
Before that, it was Don't Feel Like I Was Ever Alive Warfront.
That came off as a bit of a joke, though...
So we changed it the next day.
Um...
Is that a real gun?
Everyone who comes here always asks that...
You need to work on your adapability.
React to things as they come to you.
As they come to you... so what should I do?
You should fight.
Fight what?
That.
That thing's the enemy of the To Hell With Dying Warfront.
Tenshi.
As I thought... To Hell With Dying still isn't working for me.
Hey you, start thinking of a better one.
Hey, hey... no matter how you look at it, that's just a normal girl, isn't it?
What's this girl talking about?
Excuse me.  Do you mind if I go over there?
Huh?!
Why?  Why the hell would you do that?
What the hell makes you think that's a good idea?
Are you a complete idiot?
"Maybe I'll go see what dying's like"?
"You wanna die?" is a common joke here in this world.
What do you think?  You gonna laugh?
The joke's fine.  More importantly, though...
She looks like she'd make for a better conversation partner than the one aiming a gun at her.
I'm your ally here.
If you tell me not to point the gun, I won't do it.
Have some faith in me.
Hey!  Yurippe!
How's the recruitment going?
We're so low on members, we'll use whatever we can get!
Huh?
I'm going over there now.
Ahhh!  My invitation didn't work!
I don't get what's going on at all...
What's with those people?
Excuse me...
Ah, good evening.
Uh... you just had a gun aimed at you.
They were saying you're an Angel or something.
Hm?  I'm not an Angel.
As I thought.  Then...
I'm the Student Council President.
Ah... I'm too naïve.
That girl was just teasing me.
Damn.  I don't even know who I am, so I'm falling for stuff like that.
Whatever, I'll just go to the hospital or something.
There are no hospitals here.
Huh?  Why not?
Nobody ever gets sick.
Never gets sick?
Because everyone's dead.
Ah, I've got it.  You're in on it, too.
You're trying to trick me.
What the hell... is this amnesia your doing, too?
Many people lose their memories when they come here.
Maybe you were in an accident and hurt your head.
Fine, then prove it to me!
I'm already dead, so I can't die, righ...
Hand-sonic!
Huh?
Where am I?
I'm alive...
But, it hurt so badly.
Shit.  Shit!  I don't know what's going on, but...
I can't stay here!
W-What's with this guy?
It was you.  The one who insulted Yurippe...
and spat on our warm welcome.
H-Hey.  Wait.  Calm down...
You wanna die?
Ahhh, that.
What the hell?
Very funny.  That's a joke in the afterlife, right?  Good one.
100 Strikes!
Die die die die diediediediediediediediediediediedie diiiieee!!
Next time you insult Yurippe, we'll dance again.
A while later...
You're gonna kill me?  Talk about a sharp wit...
What kind of joke is that?
You hurt so bad you could die, and then you can't!  This sucks.
This is the world after death.
If you don't do anything, you'll be erased.
That's right!  I can just get erased!
If I do that, I can say goodbye to this crazy world.
Medical Office
School Infirmary Room 1
Authorized
Personnel
Only!
But what should I do?
I'm your ally, here.
Have some faith in me.
Is there anyone around here that looks trustworthy?
That's right!  I'll look for an adult.
But where are the adults?  The teachers?
Principal's Office
Maybe I'll ask the Principal...
Huh?
You have a point... well then, how about this?
You're The One Who's Gonna Die Warfront?
That makes it sound like I'm gonna die!
Ah, well of course we're talking about that woman.
Alright, well look this way, then.
Where am I?
You're The One Who's Gonna Die Warfront.
Ugh... crap.  You're right; it does sound like I'm gonna die.
Any others?  Any good ideas?
How's this one?  Life Flashing Before Your Eyes Warfront.
That's only the verge of death.
Well then how about this?  Suicide Corps Warfront.
It sounds like you want to die.
Stalemate Warfront.
Uh huh, oh yeah, that's right, oh yeah, oooh, nice
It's not a stalemate!
How about, Invincible Armada?
Now it's not a warfront.
Dying Without Surrender Squadron.
Don't think I won't punch you...
The Wright Brothers!
Mystic Chop!
It has to end with warfront.
I won't surrender that point.
We're the front line of this battefield.
Can't we come up with something more suitable?
Hey, that guy's awake now.
Huh?  Oh!  You're up now?
That's right.  I told him to think about it, too.
You've had plenty of time to think.  Let's hear it.
Hear what?
A new name for the To Hell With Dying Warfront, of course.
Do Whatever The Hell You Want Warfront.
Ohhh.  You've got some guts to go against Yurippe.
I said, do whatever the hell you want!
What'd you say?!
What's with you guys?!
Don't drag me into this!
I'm just gonna disappear soon!
You want to disappear?
Even though you're still here, existing?
Yeah, that's right!
I already explained it to him.
You're going to just meekly accept your erasure?
Damn right.
You're just going to meekly turn into a water flea?
Damn righ...
Huh?  Water flea?
What?  You thought only humans had souls?
How foolish.
You might reincarnate as a corn barnacle.
Or maybe as a hermit crab.
You might even be a wharf roach.
Huh?  No way.
You look so confused that you can't even joke about why we're only concentrating on sea creatures.
Incidentally, there's not really any reason.
You thought you'd just get out of here, go be a yes-man for the Angel and reach Nirvana, right?
Maybe you'll become a corn barnacle and just get eaten by a human.
Sounds great, right?
Corn barnacle?
Huh?  You can eat those things?!
Yeah, they're edible.
Wow, I never knew that.
How foolish.
Now, now, everyone.  Let's not try to drive him out so fast.
Poor thing.
Right now, we of the... what are we now?
Corn Barnacle Warfront.
Right! We of the Corn Barnacl-
We're going back!  Shinda Sekai Sensen!
That was a good kick...
As long as you're here in the Warfront's HQ, you'll be safe.
You knew that and made your way here, right?
Uh, no.  When I tried to enter, I suddenly found myself flying.
And anyway, in the next life, I might not be a human?
That's a joke, right?
Not a joke at all.
Yeah, but how would you even know that?
Did someone come back and tell you?
Of course we can't check for ourselves.
But in Buddhism, there's no guarantee that one will be reincarnated.
No way... a corn barnacle...
Well, religious beliefs are just things that humans made up anyway.
But still, listen well.  This is important.
In the world we used to live in, "Death" was a random and indiscriminate visitor.
That's why we had no way to resist.
But this world is different.
Here, we can even go against the Angels, and continue to exist.
We can fight.
But, wait.  What will happen after that?
What are you people after?
Our objective is to erase Tenshi.
And then, this world will be ours.
You only arrived here recently.  It's no surprise that you're confused.
Work on your adaptability, and then react to things as they come to you.
And then... fight... Angels?
That's right... together.
Don't apologize.  Yuripp-whaaa!
What a moron.
He got caught in his own trap...
That happened to me, too?
You need a password in order to come in here safely.
Principal's Office
This is the anti-Angel military headquarters, after all.
There's no other place where we can safely talk.
Can I have some time?
As long as you stay here, go ahead!
Okay!
What's the password?
No Angels, Gods, or Buddhas.
I'm Yuri.  The leader of this warfront.
And, he's Hinata-kun.
As you can see, he's pretty useless, but he has his moments.
What's that supposed to mean?!
That's Matsushita-kun.
I'm being ignored?
He's a Fifth-rank in Judo, so he's well respected and we call him Matsushita-godan.
Nice to meetcha.
This is Ooyama-kun.
His distinguishing trait is his lack of distinguishing traits.
Welcome to the warfront.
Come on, let's dance!
Uh... I don't dance...
Oh yeah, don't be afraid.
That's just how he says hello.
Feel the groove man.  Yeah.  Look inside yourself.
Everyone calls him TK.
Nobody knows his real name.  He's a bit of a mystery.
Is it really okay to hang with a guy like that?
The one who's always pushing up his glasses and sounding intellectual is Takamatsu-kun.
He's actually a moron.
Huh?
My pleasure.
Yeah...
The last one is Fujimaki-kun.
I'm Fujimaki, punk.
I'm not a punk, buddy.
The one who went flying earlier is Noda-kun.
The one in the shadows who keeps saying, "how foolish", is Shiina-san.
Sitting over here is Iwasawa-san.
She's the leader of the diversionary squad.
Uh huh, oh yeah, hmmm, yeahhhh, where's the beat?
They're not here right now, but we have dozens more members within the school.
Which reminds me, what's your name?
Huh?
Uh... um... uh... Oto... Otonashi.
First name?
I can't remember.
You're an amnesia-type, huh?
Don't worry, it'll come back soon.
Hey, shouldn't we give him a uniform?
Ah, that's right.  I'd forgotten.
Now that you mention it, why is mine different than yours?
You're not different.  We're the ones who're different.
Your outfit is for the "good" students.
This is the uniform of the SSS.
UTW Presents:
Study Building A, Rooftop
It's a huge campus, huh?
We have over 2,000 students.
It's an enormous boarding school.
Who in the world came up with-
Hey.  Is it alright for us to talk here?
Yeah, as long as it's not about operations.
I feel duped.
What?
Nothing...
So what's that?  Canned coffee?
It's called Key Coffee.  It's great.
Was that your question?
Er... no.  Who are they?
Right now is club activity time.
You guys aren't gonna join in?
If we did that, we'd disappear.
Huh?
If we join in club activities and classes, we humans would disappear.
We humans?
You make it sound like those guys aren't humans.
That's right.
Those guys are just NPCs.
NPCs?
You don't know the term?  Non-Player-Characters.
Is that a gaming term?
It's a metaphor.
It means those guys have been in this world since the very beginning.
So they have no self-consciousness?
Like if I talked to them, they'd only repeat the same line?
Why don't you try it?
You're still a newcomer, so you can't sense why we're different.
Can I converse with them?
Go try and kancho one of the girls.
Kancho?
They'll probably run, or kick you or something.
P-Pretty well-designed.
The teachers, too?
Yep.  Incidentally, the NPCs never age, either.
Same as us.
Anything else?
What's with Tenshi's brutality?
She stabbed me right after I met her.
I was watching that.  Wasn't that your own fault?
If you tell an Angel to prove that you won't die...
she'll just stab you right in the heart.
From her perspective, it's just like if you asked where the teacher's lounge is.
So Tenshi is obedient to the rules of this world?
More like she's just awkward.
Is she self-conscious?
Who knows?  It's a mystery.
In terms of emotionlessness, bluntness, and lack of vocabulary...
she's more unique than the NPCs.
So, is she usually able to kill so easily?
I mean, do things like that?
For those students who don't engage in "proper" activities in school...
First, she gives a warning.
If you run, she'll chase you, then outrun you and block your path.
And use of force?
An eye for an eye!
At least, whenever we've challenged her.
So she's gotten you guys before too, then?
Of course.
And don't even pretend to act like the good students.
There are those who disappeared for that, as well.
Got it.
Okay, last question.
It's about God.
Does God exist?
I believe so.
Although, I've never seen him.
Haven't you ever asked Tenshi?
Questions about this world are met with, "no comment".
That's all!
The study session is complete.
To be honest, I'm not really planning to join their fight.
Right now, I'm fighting for something more important.
I'm just trying to buy enough time to safely recover my memories.
That's all there is to it.
After that...
I don't know.
Anti-Angel Operations HQ
Here, Otonashi-kun.
You might be new at this, but give it a try.
Will it work?
Aim for her legs.
Then she can't pursue you for a while.
I'm fighting against that girl, right?
Won't her injuries heal right away?
You need to learn from experience.
That's how we've all come this far.
Very well.
Good answer, Otonashi-kun!
The first order of business is to get you acclimated.
So, we'll be having you participate in a nice simple operation.
The operation will be called:
Operation Tornado.
Oh man, this sounds like a big one!
T...Tornado?!
We're going to steal lunch tickets from the students!
We're stealing what?!
That's not big at all.  This is just petty bullying.
I'm in despair!
You've got all these members and weapons for this?!
Bastard!  Are you trying to insult Yurippe again?
Take it back.
Why should I?!
We of the Corn Barnacle Extinction Warfront would never threaten students with power or superior numbers.
They're going extinct?
Someday, probably.
But you said you were going to steal from them!
Well, maybe we should have said "lift" the tickets.
Listen up.  You're part of the barricade group that that will be stopping Tenshi's advance.
You'll surround the operation's target, the cafeteria...
Then, wait on standby.
Don't worry, I'll put you somewhere easy.
Talk with Takamatsu-kun or Ooyama-kun for the rest of the details.
Iwasawa-san, I'm expecting another fine performance tonight.
Right.
If Tenshi appears, open fire.
That will be the signal for reinforcements.
If you hear shooting, make sure you help out, as well.
The operation will commence at 18:30.
Operation start time
Intended completion time
Current time
Concert ending time
Operation... START!
Academy Cafeteria
Second Contact Bridge
How the heck are we supposed to "lift" their tickets peacefully with this plan?
Academy Cafeteria Interior
This is Yusa.
Lighting and acoustic teams are on standby.
It's about time.
The fans have noticed and are gathered.
Okay, let's get started then.
Haigo ni wa shattaa no kabe
Behind me is a wall of shutters
Hey, it's Girldemo.
The live show just started!
Yubisaki wa tetsu no nioi
My fingertips smell of iron
Tsukure, hajike. Dono michi komu desho
Building up, busting out. Anyway, it's crowded
FLY AWAY koko kara
Fly away from here
FROM NOW mitsukeru
From now I will find you
ROCK wo kanadero
Play that Rock out for me
Koko mitsuero
Put your eyes upon me
Ikizuki sae dekinai machi no naka
Can't even catch my breath inside of this town
Hoshizora wa saigo no butai
The starry sky is our final stage
She appeared.
She's here... she's coming towards me.
Does that mean I'm the weak point in this operation?
She's belittling me.
Shit!  I'll shoot!
But... a bullet into that delicate body?
If I don't shoot,
she's gonna get me.
Without an ounce of mercy.
It hit!
Wait... I wanted her legs.
Isn't this good enough?
Come on-
Guard skill: Hand Sonic.
No way.
No way!
Why?
Why isn't she stopping?
W-What the hell was that?!
Damn it!
Ugh.  I missed?
Sorry we're late.
Give your little kiss!
Going for our weakest member, huh?
She's still only using Hand Sonic.
Get her into the open!
We'll attack in numbers as we pull back.
Understood.
Let's do it!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
Fire!
Shit!  We're too late!
My god!
This is why guns are useless.
FLY AWAY koko kara
Fly away from here
FROM NOW mitsukeru
From now I will find you
ROCK wo kanadero
Play that Rock out for me
LOVE wo utau yo
I'll sing about love
Itsumade datte koko ni iru yo
No matter how much time passes, I'll be right here
Toorisugite yuku hito no naka
Passing right through everyone around me
Shit!  What's going on with the lifting?
We're just buying time...
I had no idea it would be this epic.
Anata datte tsukareteru desho
Even you must be tired by now, right?
Sono senaka ni mo todoke to ii ya
I don't care if I'm only getting through to your back
The show is at its apex.
Start it up.
Start it up, please.
Hikari no uta wo
That song of light
Sono uta wo
Play that song for me
Meat Udon
Academy Food Court
You all good?  Let's go!
Here you are.  Meat Udon.
Mmm, so delicious.
Is it really okay?
Relaxing here and eating?
Won't she come after us?
We're just eating.
Is that how it works?
Itsumo hitori de aruite iru
I always walk all alone
With this kind of power and leadership...
she could do whatever she wanted to.
But she's just sitting here relaxing and eating.
Furikaeru to minna wa tooku
When I turn around, everyone is far away
I really have only one enemy.
That's Tenshi.
We're fighting against her.
Mou nani mo kowaku nai
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
But, are we really in the right?
What we're doing?
No.
It's too soon to worry about that.
Sou tsubuyaite miseru
That's what I try to tell myself
After all...
I don't even have any memories, yet.
Itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
Eventually, everyone will be alone
Omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
They'll continue to live only through their memories
Kodoku sae aishi waratterareru yori
Rather than try to love and laugh at this loneliness
Atashi wa tatakau n da
I will fight
Namida nante misenai n da
I will never show you my tears
UTW Staff:
Translator: Ershin
Timer/Typesetting/Editor: Nikon
TLC/QC: Raze
Next episode preview
c8: Operation Descent
c10: We call it a guild.
c147: It's your turn, next.
c71: Uaaaaaaaaa!
c43: It seems you still don't understand.
c60: Run!
c37: The trap isn't disarmed yet?
c83: Oh crap!  I forgot!
c182: Because you resisted at first...
c193: I don't know... I don't know anything about that!
c317: Tenshi is waking up!
c312: Shooooot!
c347: What am I doing?
c211: You don't find a life like that to be unforgiveable?