I found you.
You're my friend, aren't you? You're "her."
I... loved you.
We took a photo of us together, right?
We drank Mom's honey ginger
milk and sang the love song.
Why didn't you tell me?
You're so warm. You must still have a fever.
Only the bear who killed
Mom could have that pendant!
Why do you?!
Yurikumaaaaaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
"BRIDE-IN-THE-BOX"
Viens avec moi
Church chimes echo in the distance
Offer up a prayer and betray today
Wander in a dark forest, then become
the morning moon at the Wall of Severance
I won't join the Invisible Storm
Once I've made you stickier
with sweet, thin honey
Please, approve me, I'll be a good girl
Picture-book pages dancing on
the breeze shake up shadowy memories
Always
I'll be waiting you-know-where,
in an empty world
Even if everything falls apart
Even if you have to gracefully writhe,
even if you have to bend space-time
Find me
Flower petals will slowly
enfold us on a starry night
Come on...
J'ai besoin de toi
"Approximately 20 Years Ago・(History)"
I was once an unwanted bear,
abandoned in the human world.
I found you.
That was when I met Him.
Don't worry, I'll shelter you.
This school is my "box."
He liked boxes.
Yuriika, this world sullies anything pure, okay?
Here.
If I do this, the flower
can stay unsullied for eternity.
You see, in this world,
only the unsullied has value.
Purrowr! Purrowr!
You're so beautiful, Yuriika. You're special.
My most especially precious treasure.
I went in his box.
I was happy.
Inside his box, I was an especially
precious, unsullied creature.
I was an unwanted bear no longer.
But then, one day...
I'm afraid I've found my next
wonderfully unsullied creature.
So I'm going.
Wait... Wait!
My precious one, don't abandon me!
Purrowr!
Bear shock!
I understood, then.
You have to box up your precious things.
Or else they'll walk right out of your life.
They'll be sullied.
From now on, this is my box.
Why are you cutting them?
If I don't cut them before they're
sullied, I can't put them in a box.
Why box them up?
To protect my pure,
precious things from the world...
My box lets me be special.
If you're un-special...
If you're unwanted, no one will find--
I found you.
You... found me?
Yes. So unbox yourself.
If you don't open the box, look
at your precious things, and touch them,
it's the same as not having them at all.
The same as not having...?
I'm empty. The world is invisible.
Open up your boxes and
show me your precious things.
And so Reia and I became friends.
Reia gave color to my blank, invisible world.
I found all sorts of precious things with Reia...
And she let herself be sullied with me.
Reia, I...
I...
I love you!
Reia, do you love me?
Yes, I love you a lot.
We'll be friends forever, won't we?
Yes. Friends forever.
Reia.
Mmm?
Happy birthday.
Yuriika!
This is proof of our friendship.
A pledge to never forget love.
As long as you don't forget love,
you'll never be alone.
If you don't give up on love,
even if you lose something,
you'll never be invisible.
Reia, I love you. I love you so much!
I knew all along that Reia's
love was different from mine. I knew...
But even still, I wallowed
in that sweet, fleeting dream.
"17 Years Ago・(History)"
Her name is "Kureha"! It means "red wing."
Stop that, honey.
She really loves this pendant!
I see.
Now, Kureha, say hi to Mama's dear friend.
See, didn't I tell you? You have
to box up all your precious things.
Otherwise they'll be sullied. You'll lose them.
Now Reia's love has been lost.
That baby took it from you because
you foolishly left your box and got sullied.
Babies are the purest
things in this world, after all.
I...
...give up on love.
I'm sullied, so I'm empty. I'm invisible.
I'm not precious enough to box up anymore.
So now I am a box.
I've become an empty box,
just wishing for something to fill my void.
The stars rained down
on the still-invisible world
and the Wall of Severance was formed.
We can never go back again.
And...
Reia... Reia... Reia!
Fulfill me! Fill in my gaps!
I'm so lonely! Please, Reia!
Help me!
Reia!
Take this pendant with you.
It's a love charm. I know it will help you.
Purrowr...
Why did you give that pendant away?
Do you love that girl?
No! She's Kureha's...
Ah, I see. You threw the
proof of our friendship, purrowr...
You threw my love away! Purroooowrrrr!
Chomp, chomp, purrowr.
I ate Reia.
To put her in the box of myself.
That would fulfill me...
Or so I thought.
Even after eating Reia, I was still starved.
The emptiness in me wasn't filled.
Before I knew it, I was interrogating her.
And how did she answer?
Well...
"Flashback"
That pendant disappeared
the night Mom was killed by a bear.
Why do you have it?!
I...
She just said, "I can't tell you right now,"
and then this morning,
they were both gone without a trace.
What are these?
Undeniable proof those two
are bears disguised as humans.
And Ginko Yurishiro,
the one with Reia's pendant, is...
The bear that killed Mom?!
Without a doubt.
No...
You were young, and she got close
to you by saying she was your friend.
Then she killed the one
most precious to you: Reia.
You can't expect love or friendship
from them. You have to exclude them.
Exclude them...
That's right, believe me.
You stole Reia's love from me,
and now you'll pay for that with your flesh.
You can't escape now. Kureha Tsubaki,
you're going to be my boxed bride.
"Flashback"
"To the Criminal-Bear"
"Ginko Yurishiro, I know the
grave crime you committed. You are"...
Ginko, how about we go back
to the other side of the wall?
No matter how true your love is,
when she knows you're a bear,
Kure-chin won't forgive you.
Promise Kisses only exist in picture books.
Kumaria is the goddess of the wall!
Her job is to separate bears and humans.
She'd never make us friends.
I made you give up kisses, Lulu.
I won't go back now, growl.
Even if it means a grave sin?
Growl. I know what you did, Ginko.
So let's go home! If Kure-chin
finds out, you can't get love.
But you can't do a Promise Kiss
without telling her the truth.
Let's go home! Ginko, even if
you give up on love, I love you!
I don't care if I can't ever kiss.
As long as you're with me...
Lulu, I...
"Incoming Call: Blocked Number"
Yes?
Is your love the real thing?
Yes.
Absolutely.
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance.
Kureha Tsubaki,
if your love is true, go to the roof.
The bears are waiting for you.
All right.
We were friends... I loved her, but she...
I'll never forgive bears.
I'll ruin bears!
Wait! Wait, Ginko!
I don't mind if you still love Kure-chin!
Growl! Just don't leave me!
Ginko! Ginko! Ginko!
Give yourself over to the humans,
and your love will be approved.
I'm sorry, Lulu.
Ginko!
Growl.
She's so cool.
But was this really right?
Eh, why not? At least
we'll find out whose love is true.
Sparkle!
But it's horribly...
Order, please.
We dwell in the space
between human and bear.
All must be as Kumaria wills it.
That is the sexy way.
Perhaps it will rain. Shaba-da-doo.
The time has come at last.
Now come here, Kureha Tsubaki.
Because I cast aside beardom
and became human for you.
"Flashback"
Defendant-bear Yuriika Hakonaka, I ask you:
Will you give up on boxes?
Or will you give up on love?
I won't give up on boxes. I'll give up on love.
Please make me a human!
I want to watch Kureha Tsubaki grow up.
Reia's love is inside that girl.
I want to fill the box of myself with it!
You won't regret it? If you do that,
you're doomed to be a box for eternity.
Reia gave my love to some
other cub like it was nothing!
I won't forgive her.
I see. I shall now declare the verdict.
Yuri approved!
The bear opens!
Miss... Yuriika...
I've been waiting for you, Kureha.
Why?
She's over there.
Ginko Yurishiro.
She is the bear who killed Reia.
She's our mortal enemy.
My mother's killer!
Ginko Yurishiro betrayed you.
She claimed to be your friend,
and she tricked you.
That's how she stole
the one most precious to you!
Kureha.
You ate my...!
I didn't eat her, growl!
Then why do you have that pendant?!
Your mother gave it to me.
She said it was a love charm.
Love charm?
I'm a bear. But we were friends anyway, growl.
But then one day,
we couldn't be together anymore.
You started to think of bears
as humans' enemies, Kureha.
Obviously. Bears kill people--killed
my mother! They're all enemies!
No! I was an unwanted bear, but you found me.
You approved me and gave me love, growl!
Lies!
I won't forget the love I got that day.
I won't give up on the love I felt.
That's why I crossed the wall.
For you, Kureha...
To become true friends with you again.
True... friends...?
Don't listen, Kureha!
She's a liar, a murderer-bear!
She killed the girls in our class!
To protect Kureha from the Invisible Storm.
I won't forgive those who exclude her.
I'm a bear. That's all I can do.
No...
Didn't I tell you? Bears feel no love or friendship.
They're sullied beasts! That's their true nature!
Go on, shoot her to death!
But...
It's okay, Kureha.
I finally get it. When Kumaria
told me about the "Promise Kiss,"
she meant your bullet, growl.
What?
I'll accept it as a criminal-bear.
That'll prove my love's the real thing.
It's the only way to
become true friends with you.
What are you hesitating for?!
Punish the criminal-bear, now!
Give me the Promise Kiss!
"Flashback"
Promise... Kiss? From me to you?
And me to you. Then everything
will awaken, and everything will change.
What are you doing?!
I can't shoot her.
Don't be ridiculous!
Killing her won't bring Mom back.
It won't change anything.
You mustn't forgive her! Give this
woman-eating bear the bullet of judgment!
But she... But Ginko saved me
from the Invisible Storm.
She jumped into the fire and risked
her life to protect Sumika's letter!
You little fool. She's just a
criminal-bear pretending to be pure!
Still!
Kure-chin!
Lulu...
Kure-chin, I know what Ginko did to Sumika.
That's right. Ginko committed a grave crime.
Ginko was Sumika's--
I'll...
...never forgive bears!
I'll ruin bears!
"Is your love the real thing?"
On the boundary that severed
ripe moon from sleeping forest
Break the law God shackles us with and smile
I turned away from the bleating flock
of shadows and howled my bloodthirsty ego
Here amidst the Invisible Storm
Overflowing honey and soul
I want to rend silk with my fangs
I'm afraid you'll vanish
like the world's last ray of hope
The savage beast inside me
tore out the throat of innocence
Come on, shoot me through the heart
with your sweet-scented Barrett of love