Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Good morning, Kagami.
Yo.
You're in a good mood.
What happened?
I got a new cell phone.
Finally, huh?
Seriously?
Then you can use songs for ringtones and set screensavers.
You're actually like a kid.
Wait a sec.
Do you watch anime and stuff then?
I already switched to one of my favorites.
Mi-Mi-Miracle! Mikurun-run! Mi-Mi-Miracle! Mikurun-run!
That's some song.
But you know...
You have to pick up before it gets to the chorus...
...which makes you stress out and regret it, right?
And if you don't pick up, they'll hang up anyway.
I don't really care about that stuff...
Is that how it is?
Ring
If I had to choose, I'd say Kagami's...
...an orc!
Why?!
I'm the only one who's a monster?!
Yes, hello?
This is Hiiragi.
Yeah...
Too used to answering the phone at home.
She was all mad at me a second ago...
I got a sandwich with balsamic vinegar sauce today...
How come women can switch moods so quickly?
But the other day, my mother...
I'm home!
Yes?
Hello?
Miyuki?
Geez!
Miyuki!
Here, phone!
From Konata-chan!
Um...
Did I do something wrong?
No.
My mother is really bad at deception...
...so you can tell when she's mad.
I believe she just hit her leg against the table.
But that wasn't exactly an issue of deception...
She's exactly the way she seems.
It's a good thing Miyuki knows so much.
I can ask you about anything I don't know.
I enjoyed being praised by Mother...
...so I became accustomed to looking things up.
Miyuki knows more than Mama does.
Now, I enjoy learning as well.
So in other words...
...I did a wonderful job of raising you, right?
That's how the conversation went.
That's some silly conversation.
In any case, I now know that you're
undeniably your mother's daughter.
Are we similar?
Down to the very last gene.
But...
Miyuki isn't just good at studying...
She knows a lot about all kinds of stuff.
There are many sources of information these days...
...and it's fun to learn a lot.
I couldn't do it.
No motivation!
Wanna play!
Rely on others in a pinch!
They say that only children and oldest children tend to be selfish...
That's right.
Aren't you an only child?
I guess it depends on the person.
Not at all.
You could say that I had a model...
...or someone who was like an oldest child...
...in my life.
I don't feel like cleaning!
Laundry is tiring!
Can we order out?
In our family...
...we have two older sisters...
...and meals turn into battles...
...which helps build character.
Yay!
Sukiyaki!
Eat up.
Let's eat!
And then, Kona-chan...
Oof.
...said that cell phones go out of service because
of a thick concentration of these something particles.
Mine.
Really...
And when her battery runs out...
...she says her phone's out of commission.
This one.
Modern girls use some strange words.
Hey.
Leave enough for Tsukasa.
Tsukasa.
You can have mine.
Thanks.
You sound nice...
...but weren't you stuffing yourself?
So having a lot of siblings can be good and bad.
You can say that about being an only child as well.
That's right.
Miyuki-chan spaces out sometimes.
Space out, is it?
You know...
Like the other day...
I can never get sick of the name elegant sea urchin.
What happened?
I was walking and thinking...
...and I ended up running into the door.
You have incredible concentration, Miyuki-san.
That happens a lot, huh?
Not often, though it's embarrassing.
Huh?
Doesn't it mean you have no
concentration if you start thinking about something...
...while you're doing something else?
Huh?
Which way is it?
That sounds like something Miyuki would do.
Indeed.
The other day, I was warming a drink...
I forgot.
I'll have to reheat it.
Many minutes later—
One more time...
And again...
Geez, Miyuki...
You forgot again, didn't you?
Sorry, it just happens.
You're so hopeless.
I'll bring it to you.
Thank you so much.
Click.
Many minutes later—
I forgot.
Like mother, like daughter.
Though it's embarrassing.
When did you start wearing glasses, Miyuki-san?
Midway through grade school, I believe.
So you weren't born nearsighted.
When I was little...
...I loved how my mother would read to me before I went to sleep....
...but my mother would fall asleep first...
...and I would want to know what happened...
...so I would read by myself in the dark room...
...and eventually, my eyes...
But it's best when you're close with your parents like that.
The reason kids these days tend to be cold and apathetic...
...may be a lack of...
...parental love or intimacy.
That's right...
I wonder when the last time Mom gave me a big hug was.
You're clingy...
...so you were really close to Mom until middle school.
Really?
That might be why you're such a good girl.
My dad is still clingy about me.
That might be why you haven't grown up, in a manner of speaking.
Speaking of kids...
...there sure have been a lot cases of kidnapping and confinement.
You seem to be sensitive to that stuff.
Well, first, I'm worried about my dad.
Don't just blurt out scary things.
Well, it more or less has to do with the games I play.
I wish they'd stop since it creates problems for other users.
At the very least...
...this stuff doesn't happen in the games I play.
Oh, yeah.
It's almost been a year.
Since what?
Since I started working.
My coworkers...
...said they're going to do something to celebrate.
That's right.
We've never gone before.
Maybe we'll check out the place you work some time.
As payback for New Year's.
Sure.
It's okay?!
Don't people usually hate that?
Well, half my job is to let other people look at me.
It's called a cosplay café, right?
Let me know before you come.
It can be pretty crowded at times.
We'll do that.
Hey, you guys.
Class started.
Hello?
We just left the station.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll buy it for you.
Okay. Okay!
Did Kona-chan say it was okay?
It's okay...
...but she wants us to go over there and buy this month's Comp...
...and the Lelou** comic for her.
I wonder if we can find it quickly.
She said to remember to ask the clerk to stamp the receipt...
Sounds complicated.
Excuse me.
Do you have a minute?
Can I take a picture?
I'm not Kamigishi.
I'm Hiiragi.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Could I also get a picture?
Sheesh!
Stop that!
Excuse me then.
Could you say Hiroyuki-chan?
Hi-Hiroyuki...
...-chan?
We're leaving.
This is the first time I've been in one of these places.
It's so big that I'm quite nervous.
She said on the phone that we'd see it once we got there.
Kona-chan would know.
I'd get lost if I were alone.
Is this it?
Now we just need the Lelou** comic.
Not here.
I can't find it.
Excuse me.
Where would I find the Lelou** comic?
That would be this.
Code Ge**s.
You could at least have told us the title...
Can I put this on a point card next time?
Then you'll have to bring this receipt with you.
Okay.
Thank you very much!
Now we just have to go find Konata.
I'm hungry, Sis!
I'm almost done working.
Hold on a bit.
How are we supposed to find our way?
Here
Gamers
I looked it up just in case.
I believe it's this way.
That's our Yuki-chan!
Guess we can only count on Miyuki.
This is the place, right?
Yes.
On the third floor.
Welcome back, Master!
You can have a seat here.
The first hour is 800 yen.
All the soda you can drink.
All the games you can play for free.
All the sweets you can eat.
Can I get this broiled eel?
Currently not available.
Then the shrimp pilaf...
Currently impossible.
Then spaghetti with meat sauce.
It will take fifteen minutes.
Permission?
Okay.
Do it.
They can do business like that?
You people.
What do you want to drink?
H-Hold on a sec!
Hurry it up.
There's a penalty if you take too long! A penalty!
Is this how you should treat a customer?
It's how we do things here.
You're done deciding, right?
I'll have a melon soda.
I have no interest in an ordinary menu.
I'll have milk tea.
What do you want?
I'm looking!
A brigade member shouldn't be this slow!
When did I become a brigade member?
That's the setting in this place.
You're a hundred years too early to be defying the chief.
What a pain...
Then give me an ice coffee.
Order from the chief!
Wait here!
Oh, boy...
Hasn't stunk in a while...
We're going on stage now, so watch.
If we can solve all the mysteries on this planet...
...we can all go anywhere we want!
Even to the end of time!
Boooon!!
Encore! Encore!
Amazing!
They're all very talented.
Ponytail version next!
Ponytail version, please!
She's an exchange student.
A first-year at our school.
My name is Patricia Martin.
Nice to meet you.
We've even put out a CD.
[Konata and Patty]
Here.
[Cos it! Oh My Honey]
[Konata and Patty]
Should you really release something like that?
Excuse me.
Could I get some tea?
Do you want warm tea?
Yes.
Hot tea please.
I'd like a melon soda, please.
Got it.
Uh...
What's this Up-To-Us Mixed Juicy Juice like?
Classified information.
House rules!
This café really exhausts me.
M-My height...
Don't worry.
I'm sure you'll grow in time.
Th-That's right.
Big Sister!
Yu-chan.
And here's a person to crush my hopes...
H-How much taller have you grown since you entered high school?
Man...
I haven't grown in either direction.
You'd better prepare yourself.
No need to fret.
You're still in demand.
Hey, you two.
Have you ever been to a class reunion?
Not yet.
Me neither.
But where did that come from?
Isn't the phrase "you haven't
changed" usually supposed to be a compliment?
But the only people who want to hear
that have probably changed considerably...
...in various places...
So it does concern you.
Okay!
Golden Week's starting...
...but listen up.
You've also got tests right after break...
...but don't forget that you're preparing for exams...
...and use your vacation wisely.
Also...
...you still have a few days left of school before break.
I won't let you take any sick days.
Kamchatka!
The aura emitting from her whole body...
No question about it.
She's Legendary Girl A.
Is today's target that new book?
Or is she after some goods?
Use your head!
Don't forget that we're having a spring audio/visual special!
Not yet!
Give her enough room.
Recommend an item once she's let her guard down.
That's right!
Slowly wait to approach her.
That's it!
Now!
Approach her!
Heading out!
Welcome!
We have these new releases!
Mi-Mi-Miracle!
Kagami?
You made it?
Be right there.
Just killing time while waiting for someone?!
When you're boiling something...
...you use rough cutting...
...and cut them into random shapes.
My...
Really...
That increases the total surface area...
...and lets the taste soak in.
Once you've scooped out the Iye...
...you let it cook on medium for around ten minutes.
It'll become soggy if it sits too long...
...so take it out once you can poke through.
I see.
Somehow, when it's home economics...
...Miyuki starts looking below average.
Now I know how you see us.
Hiiragi-chan.
Want to study for the test together in the library?
Sounds good.
Club activities are on hiatus right before a test...
...so there's nothing to do.
That's why you study.
That's the point.
Well...
I know that...
But when my club time is suddenly free...
...it's like a whole new world is open to me.
When you look at it that way, I can't waste the time on studying.
It gets me all excited.
Anyway, you should realize you're
half the reason for this study session.
Pooped!
That was fast!
Let's take a break!
Maybe you can't concentrate because you have no goal?
Don't you have any dreams for the future?
Dreams?
Not really for the future...
But this time of year, don't you wish you could win the lottery...
...and live the simple life?
Everything's a drag.
Minegishi.
Do something about her.
When I use my head...
...I need sweet stuff!
Once we're done, I'll give you some cookies I baked last time.
Hang in there.
So you bake sweets and stuff.
Can't compare with that Ajiyoshi boy.
Nah, you've got that Ajiyoshi boy licked.
Studying's a pain!
Sis.
I tried making a madeleine.
What's wrong?
Oh, yeah...
I wouldn't lump you with them...
...but I was just thinking that you tend to make similar friends.
Haven't you been overly relaxed...
...because you thought it was only stomatitis?
There sure are a lot more medical programs like this these days.
That's true.
It's scary since it could really happen.
Especially for me.
Actually, after watching this...
...I start feeling like my time's almost come.
Too many possible causes.
Please stop the depressing talk.
I beg you!
Live!
Sis!
Teach me this part.
Um...
Curses, like chickens, come home to roost?
This means...
...that Kazu likes chicken.
When you go home, you'll find roast chicken...
...I think?
Sis.
Translate the next part.
Let's see.
When you make the contract...
Did we ever learn this?
That's right.
This one time when I was working as a shrine maiden...
...a foreigner told me about why the gate is called a torii.
What'd he say?
In the past, people believed that birds would carry the dead...
...so they named it tori (bird) i (here)
because it was a place for birds to rest.
They know way more about Japan than we do.
It might have been faster to ask Kagami...
The freezing Sea of Japan...
Where have my loved ones gone?
Lucky Channel
Production
AKIRA
KOGAMI
BIG
SHOW!!
Now she swims solo through the
raging waters of the entertainment industry.
Here's a song.
Akira Kogami with "Cape of Thirty Years."
Hey!
How is this a concert?
This is the best we could do on our budget!
Don't think you'll get away with this!
It's starting!
Who do you think I...
Would you mind if I talked to myself?
I softly whispered to the seagulls.
Woman, led by a sincere heart...
Frozen by the northern sea winds...
Gone astray...
Love falls apart...
Drinks are taking a while.
Resentment crumbles...
Yes.
I've brought your drinks.
Unable to reach you so far away...
Thanks.
I stand still...
Soaked in...
W-W-Wait!
The brown one's mine!
Cape of Thirty Years!
Lucky Channel
Production
AKIRA
KOGAMI
BIG
SHOW!!
Good stuff!
We break down in tears in our own little lodge...
Let's see...
"Exhausting Life Returns" is...
Regretting that night of love...
Man, making selfish promises...
Never keeping a single one...
Thrown right into...
Yes?
That's right.
Extension...
...the spray of the waves...
It's okay.
Yes. Thanks.
Five minutes left.
Unable to meet you so far away...
Time to clean up, clean up.
Bye-bee!
I wish to offer you my yearning...
Man...
I want to release a song by myself, too.
Soul of Thirty Years!
For-For-For-Forgot my something...
Would you mind if I talked to myself?
I softly whispered to the seagulls.
Woman, led by a sincere heart...
Frozen by the northern sea winds.
Gone astray...
Love falls apart...
Resentment crumbles...
Unable to reach you so far away...
I stand still...
Soaked in tears...
Cape of Thirty Years!
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Gloomy!
Nagato.
Nobody's gonna watch if you're like that.
Sound more like somebody...
...happily moving from the TV to the
tearoom at 6:30 on a Sunday night.
One more time.
Go!
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Nothing changed!
Forget it.
「Under the Sun」
Next time:
Under the Sun.
Look forward to next time.
Er, no.
Rock, paper, scissors!