Looking back, I don't quite get it.
But, in a way, I do.
Anyway, it would change my life.
But, in a way, nothing changed at all.
It was, at the same time, very, very strange,
but also the sort of thing that could happen to anyone.
Here in Ikebukuro...
Exit
First
Words
I-I'm sor...
I want to go home.
I ask you not to laugh.
In both elementary and middle school,
I stayed home from class trips.
Bye!
Here I am, a fifteen year old boy on his first trip
to Tokyo, never having left my hometown.
That's me, Ryuugamine Mikado.
And you ask why I'm standing dumbstruck
in front of the Tobu-Tojo line?
In April, I'll be starting class
at Raira Academy, in East Ikebukuro.
It's got an above average academic ranking, is pretty,
and has all the facilities you'd want.
But mostly, I'm going 'cause a friend of mine
since elementary school invited me.
My parents wanted me to go
to public school back home.
But I'd always wanted to see Tokyo.
Mikado!
Huh?
Kida-kun?
Do I detect a question mark?
Here's the answer. Pick one of the following!
One! Kida Masaomi!
Two! Kida Masaomi!
Three! Kida Masaomi!
Kida-kun! It's really you?
I spent three years coming up with that,
and you ignore it?
Man, I've missed you!
You look so different!
I barely recognized you!
I never thought you'd dye your hair.
And your joke sucked.
It's been four years, after all.
And you look exactly the same
as in elementary school.
And my joke was awesome.
Yes. This is my best friend, Kida Masaomi.
I haven't seen him since he moved
away in elementary school,
but beyond appearances, nothing's changed.
OK, let's go!
Let's get outside the station.
Today, I feel like going west!
So, one might expect us to take the west exit,
but we're actually taking the Seibu exit...
His jokes suck, but he's a good guy.
We chatted online every day,
so I hadn't ever realized how far apart
we were or how long it had been.
Hey, know what the difference between
the west exit and the Seibu exit is?
But after meeting him for the first time in four years,
it really feels like we've been living apart.
In Ikebukuro, the Tobu department
store is on the west side,
and the Seibu department
store is on the east side.
Ah, darn it... Why do I always explain my failed jokes?
But inside, he hasn't changed at all,
especially the way his jokes suck.
Ah, whatever.
Any place you want to check out?
Hmm... Sunshine 60, maybe?
Right now? That's the place
to take a girlfriend, man.
Th-Then, what about Ikebukuro West Gate Park?
Call it Nishiguchi Park like everyone else.
But don't all Ikebukuroians call it that?
Ikebukuro-what now?
Oh, wait. You really want to go?
Huh?
No, well... W-Wait!
N-Never mind!
It's nighttime!
Those color gangs will kill us!
You've gotta be kidding me, man.
And it's like 6 o'clock.
I see you're still as much of a wuss as ever.
Tanaka Tarou-san has
joined the channel.
Hey.
'Evening.
Hey, Setton-san.
I'll be living in Ikebukuro, starting tomorrow.
Oh, really?
You might end up living near me, then.
Maybe so.
Right now, I'm still at home,
but starting tomorrow,
I'll be living in an apartment near Sunshine.
Welcome to Ikebukuro.
Wow...
A whole world that I've only seen in manga
and on the internet stands before me.
It's more amazing than Kamisakuramachi-Ginza.
Then I'll take you to Shibuya some time.
Or, if you like crowds,
maybe you'd prefer a horse track.
Lately, there aren't as many color gangs.
There were a lot of really showy
ones around last year,
but they picked a fight with Saitama,
and a bunch got arrested.
Ever since then, if you get a bunch of people
wearing the same color clothes in one place,
the police are on 'em in a second.
Then, Ikebukuro's safe now?
I don't really know too many details myself,
so don't take me for an expert,
but there are lots of other dangerous
people around. Be careful.
I see...
By the way, this is Sixty Floor Street.
There's another road called Sunshine Street.
I wonder if they made Sunshine Street first.
S-Sorry!
Oh, it's Kida-kun.
Hey, Karisawa-san and Yumasaki-san. Howdy.
How've you been?
Yo.
How's it hangin', Kida?
Long time no see!
Who's this kid? Friend of yours?
Yeah, this is an old friend of mine.
He just moved to Ikebukuro today.
Ah, cool.
This is Karisawa-san.
And this is Yumasaki-san.
Over there are Kadota-san and Togusa-san.
U-Um, my name is Ryuugamine Mikado.
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
A pen name?
Why would a high schooler have a pen name?
Oh, maybe he's on the radio or
writes for some magazine?
U-Um, it's actually my real name.
No way! It's your real name?
Wow, what a cool name!
Like the star of a manga series!
Aw, you're embarrassing me!
What should I do?
I can't keep up with this conversation.
You guys were out shopping?
Yup.
Dengeki Bunko just released their latest
publishing run. I picked up thirty copies or so.
Dengeki Bunko puts out
thirty books a month?
No, of course not!
One each for him and me, and then, oh...
Ten more for other stuff.
"Other" stuff.
What do they mean by "other" stuff?
Like a copy to keep, or a copy for work,
or a copy just to look at or something?
Well, we're gonna get going.
See you guys soon!
Right. Peace.
Oh, hold that by her head.
See you.
Hey! Don't let it bang into the car!
Well, they're a bit odd,
but if you're nice to them, they'll be nice to you.
I didn't know you had friends like that.
I get involved in all kinds of things.
I know where all the shops are, where to get good used clothes,
even how to get street vendors to cut their prices.
I wonder what kinds of experiences he's had over the
last four years, while I was sitting alone at home.
Well, if you know everything going on, it makes
it that much easier to talk to all the girls.
He's a perv.
Found her.
Sure?
Complete match to the provided description.
Roger.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Don't use too much.
If she doesn't wake up,
they take it from our pay.
It's all good. It's a teenage female.
That's a fifty percent bonus, right?
Twenty percent, dude. Twenty percent.
Our first good target in a while, a teenage girl!
Yeah. Thank god for that info broker.
Good evening.
Kanra-san!
I didn't know you were here.
I was on the phone.
Oh.
I just finished reading the scrollback.
You're moving to Tokyo?
Congratulations.
Want to get together IRL?
Yeah. That sounds fun.
Doesn't it?
Oh, speaking of meeting offline,
ever heard about suicide meet-ups?
Yeah, those were big for a while, weren't they?
People find each other on the internet,
then commit suicide together.
Horrible, isn't it?
But you don't hear much about them anymore, do you?
Maybe they're not successful in offing themselves...
Or maybe there are a bunch of them,
but people haven't found out.
Like they haven't found
the bodies or something.
Don't be creepy.
Come to think of it,
a lot of people have gone missing lately.
Huh?
Really?
Hmm...
Mostly illegal aliens,
or kids who've run away from home to Tokyo.
A lot of them are going missing
between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Mazenda-san?
Yes.
Oh, are you Nakura-san?
Good! I figured it was you.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Shall we get going?
OK.
We're almost there.
Two others are there already.
Oh, OK.
That's it.
Hey.
Hello.
We clear?
There's no one around at all.
OK, then... Sorry for tricking you!
But there is someone here.
Kida-kun just kept on talking.
I was getting tired.
Either from walking,
or from listening to his bad jokes.
There's so much to talk about when
you meet in person, huh?
Probably both.
Y-Yeah.
I figure I've only gone over about
5/400ths of what I had to cover.
Oh, that 400 includes
Karisawa-san and the others.
I was debating whether to humor him or not,
and that's when I saw him.
Hey, miss. It's been a while.
Dressed like a sushi chef
and recruiting customers...
No, a black guy dressed like a sushi chef,
who was really big...
No, someone dressed like a sushi chef was trying to draw
in customers, but for some reason, they were black...
Mister, long time no see.
Hey, Simon!
How are you?
Oh, Kida!
Want sushi?
It's good.
I'll give you a discount.
Sushi is good!
Nah. I'm broke, so not today.
I'll eat here once I get a job and some money,
so how 'bout some sushi on the house?
I can't!
I'd disappear into the seaweed
of the Russian tundra!
Seaweed in the tundra?
See you.
Mister, long time no see.
You know him?
Yeah. His name's Simon.
He's a black Russian.
He pulls customers in for that
Russian sushi place over there.
Sorry. I'm not following your joke.
I'm serious.
His real name is Semyon, but everyone reads
it like English and calls him Simon.
Mister, long time no see.
I don't know the details, but his parents took
asylum here from America or something.
Anyway, a Russian friend of his started a
sushi place, so he started working there.
Don't piss him off.
I once saw him stop a fight by picking up
a guy as big as him with one hand.
Speaking of people you shouldn't piss off-
Wh-What's that?
What's going on?
Speak of the devil.
Just stay away from a guy
named Heiwajima Shizuo.
Of course, just live a normal life
and you'll never talk to him.
Wh-What kind of person is he?
They aren't here yet.
That's weird.
The higher-ups are a bunch of slackers.
They need to be more careful.
Who cares?
Not like we've got anywhere to be.
True that.
A man's body needs times like these.
A temporary respite from the
brutalities of modern life.
By the way, I saw that black bike today.
Black bike?
Um...
You haven't heard of it?
Everyone in Shinjuku and Ikebukuro's
talking about it.
It's been like an urban legend for a while, but a lot
of people have been taking pictures of it lately.
Oh, I've heard of that.
But isn't it just a normal bike gangster?
Not that anyone's ever seen it in a
group or anything, but you know...
If they're riding a bike with no lights, they're an idiot.
Assuming they're human...
What do you mean by that?
Um, well, you see...
It's like a monster.
Hey.
Um... You one of the higher-ups?
Obviously not.
Then who is that?
Are you screwing with us?
We're kinda busy here.
If you're gonna get in the way, then die!
Y-You've gotta be shitting me...
Oh, crap!
H-H-H-Hey!
No! Get off me! Let go!
I said to get off me.
Oh, shit, shit, shit!
Wh-What is this guy?
What is this guy?!
What do you mean it's a monster?
Dotachin calls them the Grim Reaper.
Dotachin?
Who's Dotachin?
You see, the man on the black bike...
You're ignoring my question about Dotachin?
Damn it!
Take that!
Damn it...
...doesn't have a head.
Their head's cut clean off, but they still move.
Wh-What the hell are you?
Wh-What are you?!
Hey, are there any other people
I should stay away from?
Well, the yakuza and the gangs, obviously.
Also, there's a guy called Orihara Izaya.
Orihara Izaya?
That's a strange name.
You're one to talk.
They're all dangerous, so stay away.
Well, he mostly hangs out in Shinjuku,
so you'll probably never see him.
Oh, and stay away from the Dollars.
The Dollars?
Yeah, pronounced like "Wanderers".
What the heck are "Wanderers"?
I don't know details, but there are lots of them.
And they're all a little nuts...
Seems they're a color gang,
but no one knows what color, etc.
Of course, they can't really get together currently,
so they may have split up by now.
I see.
Hey! Are you OK?
You OK?
Um, I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Um...
No... No! No! No!
Hey!
What was that?
Not even a thank you?
I wonder what happened to her.
I don't know. Anything can happen in this town.
You're lucky.
Just today, you met Kadota-san
and the gang, and Simon.
Plus you saw Shizuo throw people and vending machines,
and you bumped into a really pretty girl.
Is that honestly good luck?
I'm happy.
Huh?
I'm happy I get to go to school with you here,
and that we can hang out again.
So am I.
You really are lucky today!
You get to witness an urban legend, too!
Kida-kun!
You saw the black bike, Tanaka Tarou-san?
<Tanaka Tarou> Good evening.
<Tanaka Tarou> I saw it today!
<Tanaka Tarou> The black bike!
Was it around 9 PM?
Ah, did you already hear about it, Setton-san?
Yeah. I was there too.
What?
What do you mean, urban legend?
The black bike!
The Headless Rider!
Just then, I realized that my body was shaking.
I wasn't scared.
I think I was moved.
I'd seen something amazing.
Right here, in this town, I experienced something
I'd never experience anywhere else.
An impossible reality, that I never thought I'd experience,
was before my very eyes.
It may contradict what I said at first,
but at the least, it's what I thought then.
I was shaking with the premonition
of a new reality beginning for me.
Really?
Then we might've passed each
other without knowing.
Maybe so.
By the way...
Who's Dotachin?
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Highly
Unpredictable
A girl with a certain darkness to her
glimpses a reality unknown to her.
A reality that everyone almost meets,
but never quite does.
What that girl, who should've been dead, saw was...
Next time:
Unpredictable.