The low sky looks like it's about to cry.
I spit a mixture of saliva and agitation on the sidewalk.
I cower at the thought of tomorrow,
Worrying that everything might fall apart.
In my heart, I know that looking ahead
To the day after tomorrow won't give me a single answer.
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
A lot of people wearing yellow have started to appear in the city.
The Yellow Scarves?
Have you heard?
People are saying that the Slasher is actually in the Dollars.
We still really need you...
How's he been lately?
He visits me from time to time.
Before that...
The air in Tokyo is very filthy.
Wouldn't you agree?
Pinworm!
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
Good evening, Kanra-san.
Evening~
Good evening, everyone!
Have you heard?
Good evening, Kanra-san.
Evening~
Good evening, everyone!
A student from Raira Academy was attacked by the Slasher just a little while ago!
What? Seriously?
How frightening...
Dead serious!
A freshman who happens to be a girl!
Please excuse me.
I need to make a phone call, so I'll just be lurking for a bit.
Relax.
It wasn't your girlfriend who was attacked.
Thanks.
But I'm still a little worried, so...
Hmm...
Do you know where this happened?
Let's see...
it's a little beyond the East Ikebukuro Subway station along the metropolitan expressway.
There are a lot of police cars around the area, so it should be easy to find.
I see...
Oh, please excuse me. I'm going to sign off for a bit.
Are you curious enough to go look, Setton-san?
Setton-san has left the chat.
Aww, geez!
Sorry,
I'm going to sign off as well.
Huh?
Were you able to reach her?
She's apparently at the police station right now...
She says she witnessed the crime.
I'm going to go check up on her.
Setton-san has left the chat.
Tanaka Tarou-san has left the chat.
Hey...
Well then, me three.
Tanaka Tarou-san has left the chat.
Kanra-san has left the chat.
There is currently no one in the chat room.
Saika-san has entered the chat.
Today.
There is currently no one in the chat room.
Saika-san has entered the chat.
Today.
I cut.
Saika-san has entered the chat.
Today.
I cut.
Wrong.
More,
strong,
love,
wish,
The Slasher...
love,
wish,
means
I want
strong humans
Who listen?
I want, to hear
Who? Strong
Ikebukuro
Wish
At that time, I was totally oblivious of the fact
Ikebukuro
I
that the cause of these bloody incidents
was related to one girl's destiny,
and at the same time, my own past.
I want
Mother
Unrest Prevailing
I'm home!
Just wanted to say...
I'm home...
I'm home, Selty!
Hey.
What's wrong?
I witnessed something disturbing...
Something disturbing?
Don't make me say it! I'd like to forget!
That was refreshing.
Why don't you at least take that mask off when you're in the shower?
Nope, the air is dirty in Tokyo so I can't take it off no matter what.
Oh right, Selty.
Thanks for yesterday.
By the way, what's with those insolent fools dressed in yellow?
You must be talking about the Yellow Scarves.
They emerged about the time you left for America.
I've heard that they've calmed down a bit after getting into a fight with another group called the Blue Squares, but...
I hope they all die in the sewer after they beat each other up.
Don't be as reckless as you were yesterday.
Anyway,
Selty brought you back here safe and sound, so pay her.
I guess I'll put it on your tab.
No can do.
Then I guess I'll just take a little walk.
I was just testing you there, Selty.
If you free me immediately, I'll-
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Hey! It's going through!
The tip of your shadow is stabbing me a little bit!
Shinra!
I'm in a crisis here!
You're my son, so you know what you're supposed to do here, right?
Of course.
Come again.
Be well aware that I'm not leaving you any inheritance.
Not like I need it.
You've become completely deceived by the monster...
I'd be satisfied if Selty were to deceive me and steal my soul.
Oh?
What is this, Selty?
Don't tell me... you've fallen for Shinra?
I knew my son was strange enough to be head over heels for you,
but I never would have thought that you'd return his feelings!
That's right.
Selty!
I wasn't expecting you to acknowledge our relationship so frankly!
I'm so touched that my one-sided love has progressed to a fruitful one that I'd not be ashamed to release to the public!
I could dance with joy!
You're embarrassing me! Shut up!
I'm just full to the brim with happiness that our love has been confirmed!
Do you think I'll approve of this?
What?
You're an unwelcome guest in society.
Do you realize that people refer to you as a monster?
Of course.
If so, then...
And?
Is there a problem?
I guess my plan to poke at the opponent's anti-social nature in order to take the upper hand failed miserably.
Sorry, that's hardly convincing when coming from you.
Besides,
Shinra says he loves me the way I am.
Fine.
I approve.
However, you're to refer to me as...
"Father" from now on!
Shut up!
Moving right along...
You won't be able to get your memories back if you stay headless like that.
The memories of when you were a Dullahan in your home country of Ireland, when you still held on to your head.
There's... nothing I can do about that.
To make up for your lost memories,
let's spend the rest of our lives creating memories that are even better.
Shinra...
Let's start things off with a wedding!
I need to take measurements for the wedding dress,
so would you be kind enough to take off those shadow clothes-
Now that I recall, you've always been a twisted kid who'd smile amusingly whenever you'd perform dissections.
That's clearly your influence!
Call me "Father!"
Geez... I just warned you about this,
but you're still as rash as ever.
That's why you didn't even realize when I stole your head-
Oh, crap!
W-W-W-What did you just say?!
Oh no, I accidentally leaked a secret...
Well, it should be fine.
Selty's a blunderer, so she won't notice.
Huh?
Selty the Blunderer! Selty the Blunderer!
Shut it!
Why did you have to say it twice?!
It's so easy to predict the attacks of a blunderer in a frenzy!
Even if it's you, I won't forgive someone for making fun of Selty.
Okay! Okay! I can explain.
No use hiding it now.
Indeed, it was I who stole your head and handed it to the pharmaceutical company!
Don't get defiant!
Fine. Follow me.
I'd like to show you something.
Whoosh!
Huh?
He ran away!
That creep...!
I won't let him get away!
Did she leave?
Well, my plan to only press the elevator button seems to be a success.
I'll be back eventually to get my belongings.
Farewell.
Damn him... where did he go?
Oh, Selty-san.
Something wrong?
You're looking absent-minded in the middle of a park.
I was just thinking about some things.
Tell me.
Tell me what you're thinking about.
You look depressed.
It's about the Slasher...
There have been odd rumors on online boards and stuff.
Odd rumors?
Yeah.
People are saying that the Dollars may be behind it.
That's ridiculous...
Do you actually believe that?
Of course not, but...
If the rumors continue to stand on their own like this, I have a feeling something dangerous may happen.
And even without all that, tensions are rising between the Dollars and the Yellow Scarves.
He's right. The current state of the city is dangerously unbalanced.
Mikado.
I'll do some research on the Slasher as well.
Selty-san...
So hurry along.
Sitting here like that in a daze is almost like asking for trouble.
You're right.
Thank you very much.
The Slasher, eh...?
Sorry, I have no idea.
Oh...
I don't think you need to be making such a big deal out of this for the sake of the Dollars.
It's not just for the Dollars.
The Slasher and I have a bit of a history between us.
I would have been dead had I not been headless to begin with.
Idiot.
People say that those who call others idiots are the real idiots.
I don't care if I'm an idiot, so I'll call you one.
Idiot! You should have told me this earlier!
Okay! He's dead!
I'm going to kill him for sure!
He's totally dead, guaranteed!
Well no, I'm the Headless Rider!
I'm totally fine.
No, no, no.
That's not even the problem here.
If he pulled a blade on you, that's instant death.
Gonna kill him, gonna kill him, gonna kill him...
What about your job?
Aren't you on your break right now?
I don't give a shit.
Come on.
I'm not going to let you get fired because of me.
Besides, I still need more information before I can track him down.
I'll make preparations first, so just wait for now.
Fine.
But try to make it quick.
Gonna kill him, gonna kill him, gonna kill him...
There was a reason why I needed to part with Shizuo at that point.
Wow, I'm happy you came here to see me.
So, how's it going?
Have you found your head yet?
It's not about my head.
I'm going to be direct.
I want to know about the Slasher.
30K will do.
But wow, even your clothes and your wallet are made of shadows.
Could it be that if someone flashed you with a bright light, the shadows will disappear, leaving you naked?
Why, do you want to peek?
Not really.
Unlike a certain underground doctor or a student,
I'm not as abnormal as to lust over a headless body or just a head.
I don't care what you say about me,
but look down on Shinra again and I'll make you pay.
You two sure love each other.
But hey,
if another Dullahan appears and seduces him, he may have his heart stolen just like that.
I'd like to think that wouldn't occur,
but if that happens, then...
You'll kill him and kill yourself afterward?
Nope.
I just won't be able to approach him.
Another headless woman aside from me, huh...
I wouldn't know what to do because now, I love him back.
Now this is a surprise!
You've really started to become more human-like.
But you should really be careful.
The closer you get to becoming human, the bigger the gap that'll be created when you get your head back.
I can worry about that after I get my head back.
Well actually, I'm starting to not care about getting it back.
But more importantly, give me some information about the Slasher.
You'd better not tell me you don't have any information after taking my money.
Rest easy.
I have some tasty information that hasn't even been leaked to the cops, the media or the net.
I was actually waiting for you to come here.
What do you mean?
This incident has to do with evil spirits, you know.
Ever heard of a katana called 'Saika'?
Saika?
It may be hard to believe,
but Saika is a demon sword that used to exist here, in Shinjuku.
A demon sword?
Sort of like a Muramasa Blade?
Yes, a katana that holds mysterious magic...
What's up?
I heard of the story of a demon sword called Saika from Izaya.
Apparently, there's a folktale that Saika has a soul that can take over humans.
Also, all the victims who have been attacked by the Slasher say that the attacker had red eyes.
So you're suggesting that Saika may be behind it?
Yeah.
And every night that the Slasher appears, a nick called 'Saika' appears on the net.
There is currently no one in the chat room.
Saika-san has left the chat.
But when I was attacked, I didn't sense its presence when it snuck up on me.
If Saika weren't human, I should sense something from it...
Saika only takes over the mind, and what's actually moving is the human's body.
Maybe the thing you usually sense doesn't exist in it.
You seem to know a lot about Saika, Shinra.
Oh, well,
you once told me to look it up for you.
Come on, hurry along to bed with me!
"Shinra's definitely hiding something."
Those were my thoughts.
Welcome back!
I was independently searching for Lady Namie's whereabouts after Nebula merged with Yagiri Pharmacy,
and I found her frequenting your place.
So that's why I threatened her with this model gun to let me enter as well.
A model gun?!
Oh, did I forget to mention that?
Shouldn't we hand him over to the cops?
Whoa, I think it would be you guys who would get in trouble if you were to do something like that.
If they believe my testimony and do some searching,
they'll find the head of a young woman in the room!
Wow, it'll be the sensation of a century, just as big as the slashing incidents.
I knew it. Shinra's distorted personality came from you.
I won't give you anything even if you praise me like that.
Well to be honest, I don't need the head back right away.
The higher-ups of my company were astonished when Selty appeared on TV screens earlier.
They decided that they wanted to study her body first, before her head.
And so, at my own discretion, I've said that the head is currently being looked for.
You seem to be attempting quite an interesting approach against the head.
With the theory that a valkyrie is a dullahan,
you're going to place the head amidst a power struggle and have it awaken by itself.
That's quite a unique idea.
Well, I've tried a couple of things.
There may come a time when I'll have to resort to taking it to an area with strife.
Anyway, it would be great if we're on the same side.
Very well.
I've always had an interest in you.
There's no one around me that would dare experiment from a mythological point of view.
Including me.
Why, thank you.
Okay, let me give you a word of advice.
If you're planning on starting false strife here in Tokyo in order to spur Selty's head or perhaps her soul,
it would probably be better to throw the people around her into calamity,
instead of dragging her into the strife of others.
That's what I was planning on.
Well, things have already started rolling in that direction faster than I expected.
Anri.
You're already feeling well enough to help prepare for the sports festival?
Y-Yes...
I was worried sick.
Why were you with the students who were slashed at?
Don't tell me you were being bullied again?
I'm worried.
Seriously, I am.
The Slasher may target you again,
so it's dangerous to be alone.
Sexual harassment again?
That's not good, teach.
I'm just worried about Anri.
Wow, calling her by her first name?
This is dangerous!
If you worry about her too much,
she'll transfer schools just like Niekawa-senpai.
You were Niekawa Haruna-san's homeroom teacher last year, weren't you?
What?
You know Niekawa?
Yes, but just the name.
Well then, we'll be heading home now!
I wonder who this Niekawa Haruna-san is...
Hey, Anri.
Mikado hasn't even confessed to you yet, has he.
Huh?
Thought so.
But you've realized that he's madly in love with you, right?
Ryugamine-kun's a good friend of mine.
Since my best friend seems to love you with all his heart,
I'm going to watch how things develop for now.
And besides, I need to get along with the beauties from around the globe!
Masaomi!
Sonohara-san!
Look, here comes the coward.
Sorry, did I make you guys wait?
Waited so long, I thought I was going to fossilize!
What?
You get a score of sqrt(3).
Square root?
What the heck is that?
Couldn't you at least rate it with something easier to understand, like '-20'?
Later!
See you guys tomorrow!
See you guys tomorrow.
You finally came to visit.
Selty.
About Saika...
There was a time when it was in the possession of my father.
But apparently, he sold it to a secondhand dealer friend of his a few years ago.
Shingen?
Why did he do that?
People refer to Saika as a katana that can slice through the soul.
Could it be...
Yeah, my father used Saika in order to steal your head.
To sever the soul that connected your head and your body.
And you knew this?
Yeah.
Well, I only realized he used it to steal your head later after I researched.
I didn't want to bring it up since you had already begun to try to forget about your head...
But...
Could you...
Let me think alone for a bit?
I knew it.
Love brings about confusion.
And on the same night, the demon sword Saika was trying to love a certain girl.
A girl who can't find a place to belong in this reality...
Sonohara Anri.
"Do dreams exist at a time like this?"
I've gotten tired of speaking like that.
I've been walking this entire time,
but recently, even that seems fruitless and in vain.
"I want to see you."
An irrelevant phrase
often heard sung round and round the city.
Something like that
No, something like that
isn't enough to satisfy me.
I know exactly how I feel.
We're free. We pray that all dreams eventually come true.
Just like that,
everyone searches for their true selves.
What we find after a long journey
is the answer.
We're free. We seek the light.
We float freely like butterflies.
Our hearts reflect the great blue sky.
Even if we happen to lose our freedom amidst a strong wind,
we never want to feel regret.
We're free. We seek the light.
We're free. We long to reach a new height.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Even a Fool May Give Good Counsel
Ikebukuro...
I just wanted to know.
Where does this city, something that resembles a box crammed with junk, get its energy from?
I wanted to know the truth of the city whose greed increases day by day.
Next time: Even a Fool May Give Good Counsel.