Scrub, scrub!
Blossom, let's hurry!
Right!
Let's do a simultaneous kick!
Got it!
Blossom!
Marine!
Well, in that case...
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
What's the matter?!
We have to save him!
I'm going to remove the rubble, all right?
Marine Impact!
Here I go!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
So cool!
Although I dunno about you...
This isn't the time to be feeling down!
We must find the Blossom Tact!
Your Tact is right here.
I've heard rumors...
but the weakest Precure in history is still just as weak now that there are two of you.
Weakest...
And just who are you?!
One of the Desert Apostles...
Commander Kumojacky!
Commander?!
Please give back the Tact!
I suppose it would be boring to defeat such a weak Precure.
Here you go. Consider it a present.
First Sasorina, and now a new commander...
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
I ended up causing trouble for Erika, didn't I...
Even if you're no good right now, you just have to grow one step at a time.
So I am no good after all.
Tsubomi!
Good mornin'!
Morning!
Good morning!
Morning.
Keep your spirits up today, all right?
R-Right.
It's like Erika says!
I have to stay positive!
The Precure Partnership
is Already Dissolved?
Is that so?
Then the second Precure has finally appeared.
Her name is Cure Marine.
She seems more capable than Cure Blossom, at least.
Even if there are two Precure now,
I, Kumojacky, bear the strength of a hundred!
More importantly, Kumojacky, why did you give Blossom her Tact back?
I care not for this trivia.
The only foe I care for is the world itself!
Huh?
It is true that our objective is indeed the world itself.
We shall make the hearts of its people as barren as the desert
and then subjugate the entire world!
Leave this one to me.
Tsubomi, turn off the alcohol lamp, will you?
Huh?! But I'm scared...
All you're doing is putting a cap on it.
Capping your ears instead isn't going to help.
Sheesh...
I'm sorry...
We've got soccer next, right?
All right then! We'll leave the cleanup to you!
Hold it!
Why do we have to clean up after you?!
That's right!
Stop making such a huge fuss.
I'm not!
Let's settle this fairly with Rock Paper Scissors!
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
Gotcha!
Yaaay!
Erika really is amazing...
Erika, you're so cool!
Do your best too, Tsubomi!
Right!
Are you all right?!
I'm fine...
I'm so lame...
"He fled all alone through the window of the classroom..."
I guess I just can't compare to Erika...
As a Precure, all I do is hold her back...
"I lay in the grass of Kozukata Castle, my heart of fifteen drawn into the sky..."
My heart of fifteen, drawn into the sky...
Sounds almost like me...
Though I'm still not fifteen yet.
Hanasaki!
I'd like you to answer that question.
Um, well...
It's Tankobu! The answer's Tankobu!
It's "Tankobu"!
It's "Takuboku"! The author's name is Ishikawa Takuboku.
Erika, if you're going to tell her, at least tell her properly.
Okay!
Erika's the most popular girl in the class...
Compared to her, I'm just...
No, I can't be so negative! That'd be unfair to Erika!
Change! I'm going to change!
Hey, why not come to my place today?
I've got a great idea!
Let's go to Fairy Drop!
Wow, these are really pretty!
We keep the accessories and all the small stuff on the first floor.
Tsubomi!
Up here!
Now, what outfit do we go with...
Erika, what was the idea you had?
It's about recruiting for the Fashion Club.
Wearing our school uniforms won't exactly be persuasive.
Really, it'd be better if I designed something special, but I really don't have the time.
Do you think this'll do?
Huh? Do for what?
For you to wear, of course!
I think it'll suit you! Take a look!
It's really too flashy for my tastes...
I guess.
How about you pick one out?
That one?
I've done some studying about color therapy.
Apparently people tend to pick black and gray when they're feeling down.
Are you feeling down, Tsubomi?
You're... not completely off the mark.
Then you should go for something green!
It'll ease your worries, and make you feel ready to try again!
It's cute too, isn't it?
I don't think anyone will ever find out we're Precure,
but it'd be embarrassing to make our entrance without wearing cool clothes, right?!
I guess you're right...
If I don't, I guess I won't be worthy of teaming up with you, Erika...
Tsubomi!
Huh?
Let's go for a run!
What?!
Wh-Why are we running?!
Something bad's happened to you, hasn't it?
It's times like this when you just need to get on your feet and move!
I'll run along with you!
Well, um... I dunno if I'd call it something bad...
What do you mean?!
It's Mao and Ayumi.
Are they students here?
Yeah, they're really good.
They made nationals in doubles.
Mao!
Erika...
What's the matter?
Ayumi says she wants to train on her own for a while.
I'm always relying on Ayumi in our matches, so she probably got fed up with me.
So if she stops playing with me, she can partner up with someone better...
With someone better?!
What, that's it?!
Why don't you just partner up with someone better too?
Partner up with someone else?!
I'm going to go be a Precure with someone else, Tsubomi.
If you start talking like that, Mao's gonna...
You have to look toward the future!
Your partnership dissolving is a new start!
Partnership dissolving...
That's enough! Just leave me alone!
What's wrong with her?
Hey, Tsubomi!
Huh?
Tsubomi!
Wait! What's the matter with you?
We might not have known each other very long...
Huh?
But when you do find someone else...
please don't forget about me!
What're you saying?!
Tsubomi!
Are our Precures already splitting up?
That mustn't happen!
Tsubomi's so weird!
Why'd she get so depressed all of a sudden? I don't get it.
You stuffing yourself full of candy again?
Momo!
You have a photo shoot here?
I've got a gravure shoot for a fashion magazine today.
Though I'm on my break right now.
Did you fight with Tsubomi again?
We didn't fight!
This other girl was feeling down, so I just gave her some advice...
and then Tsubomi got all depressed on me!
You do tend to spit things out without
thinking about the people you're talking to.
You need to be more careful.
I just tried to get her to be more positive!
Maybe so, but sometimes that can do more harm than good.
Momoka! If you'd join us, please!
Okay!
Not everyone's like you, Erika.
I know that already!
I know that...
Master Coupe!
Why did I become a Precure?
I'm spineless, shy, and completely unathletic...
I have absolutely no right to be a Precure...
I...
Is it all right for me to cry?!
You're so nice and fluffy...
Isn't he?
Grandma!
I did my best!
Partnering up with another girl would just be cruel...
Who's there?!
I am a Commander of the Desert Apostles...
Kumojacky!
The Flower of your Heart is about to wither, so I shall take it!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
We won't be needing this.
You're up, Desertrian!
Roller!
This is bad!
We have to tell Tsubomi and Erika!
Tsubomi,
if there were a "right" to be a Precure,
it would be due to having a strong and kind heart.
To believe that everything is worth treasuring,
and to believe in your ability to keep trying, no matter how hard it gets.
And you possess both of those traits, Tsubomi!
If it's you, Tsubomi, you can do it.
Yes!
There's trouble!
A Desertrian's...
Tsubomi.
Sheesh! I don't get Tsubomi or Momo!
Should I apologize?
But for what?
Here she is!
A Desertrian has appeared!
What?!
Erika!
Tsubomi...
Roller!
Mao's Flower of the Heart is the one that was stolen!
I worked so hard because I wanted to be doubles partners with Ayumi,
so why do I have to partner up with another girl?!
At this rate, the Flower of Mao's Heart will wilt!
Let's hurry and restore it!
Got it!
Seeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
My partnership with Ayumi worked so well!
Blossom, let's go for a double punch!
Right!
Double Precure...
I'm sorry!
You really are the weakest.
You're... Kumojacky!
You two...
bore me!
Finish them!
I'm sorry! All I do is hold you back, Marine...
That's not true!
Even though I practiced so hard so I wouldn't hold Ayumi back...
Marine!
I'm causing you trouble again!
I really am no good!
You should partner up with someone better, Marine!
Wait, is that why you were so worried when I said she should partner with another girl?
Yeah...
So that's what it was!
Why didn't you just say so?!
If you don't tell me, there's no way I can understand!
So now you're fighting?
Not only are you the weakest, but your partnership is also a disaster!
We aren't the weakest!
We're the greatest partnership!
I like Blossom!
She's clever, really perceptive, and brilliant!
Marine!
I'm sure that we need each other's strengths!
And Chypre's too!
Coffret's too!
Both of us are Precure!
We are Precure...
You... you really don't mind pairing up with me?
I don't mind at all!
No, what I mean is...
It has to be you, Blossom!
Yes!
I have no time for your blabbering!
A man must weather alone the stormy seas of life!
This nonsense about "partnerships" and "not being alone" is nothing but foolishness!
It's not foolish at all!
The desire people have to band together is precious!
You're just using Mao's feelings to make that monster rampage...
I've had it up to here with this!
I'll listen to your whining once you've defeated him!
Roller!
Use your combined attack!
Now that both of your hearts are as one...
You'll bring forth an ultra super attack!
Marine!
Let's do it!
This is our combined power!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
How very interesting.
It seems I will have to stop referring to you as the weakest after all.
You should become even stronger!
And only then shall I defeat you.
We must return the Flower of the Heart to her!
Mao... Mao!
This is...
You scared me!
When I came back to the court you were just lying here.
Ayumi, I promise I'll practice harder,
so please don't break up our doubles team!
Huh? What are you saying?
That's my line!
I thought that if I didn't sharpen my skills, you'd be the one to leave.
So I thought I'd practice on my own for a while...
So I just assumed that you'd gotten fed up with me?
I assumed that's what you were doing too.
We really are silly...
We didn't trust each other, so we made ourselves worry needlessly, didn't we?
Let's stay together from now on!
Of course! After all, we're the greatest partnership there is!
Ayumi!
In the language of flowers, a
tweedia means "a trusting heart."
By trusting in each other,
their friendship has become even
stronger than it was before, hasn't it?
I think a Heart Seed is going to be born!
I think our friendship has become stronger too, hasn't it?
It has!
Well then, I guess that makes us best friends.
Huh? Best friends?
Right?!
Yeah! Best friends it is!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
A most treacherous man has appeared!
Looking toward the back of his father, who sacrifices everything, even his family, for his ramen serves
to touch the young boy's heart!
Wait, it doesn't?!
Akira is sad because his father
makes no time to play with him!
Be on your guard! They're here to take his weakened heart!
The enemy this time is a real hottie! What do we do?!
How about we go grab some ramen ourselves?
What?
HeartCatch Precure:
Rejected Ramen!
Heal the Father-and-Son Bond!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!