For the time being,
I'll have you practice with just the mouthpiece.
Eh?!
Got a problem with that?
No! Umm...
But, I was hoping to learn quickly so I could play music like Rio-senpai...
I'm pretty strict, you know.
All right! I'll be in your care!
It's time for breakfast.
The mess hall is over there.
Get going.
Yes!
It's so rough and rugged...
Please take care of me from now on.
Good morning!
You suck!
Wow!
Actually, we were supposed to welcome you last night.
This is a little something for you.
Thank you very much!
Oh, that's right, Rio.
The things that were drying upstairs, did you take them down yet?
Nope, I didn't even know about them.
That's odd...
Hang in there, Noel.
You can go to sleep after breakfast!
I'll do my best...
That's not doing your best...
I'm doing my best...
That's...
Rio-sempai's...
Hurry up, the food will get cold.
Now then,
allow me to formally introduce you to everyone in the 1121 Platoon.
First off, the captain.
Lieutenant Felicia Heideman.
I'm a tank commander.
Let's be sure to have fun!
Nice to meet you!
This one is...
Hey, Noel...
Kannagi Noel...
Corporal Kannagi.
She's a pilot, as well as our mechanic.
Nice to meet you!
And last up is...
Private Suminoya Kureha.
Gunner.
Listen up.
I may be younger than you, but I'm still your senior, so you'd better listen to my orders-
She collapsed, eh?
Thanks for your hard work, Noel-chan.
Now then, let's eat.
But...
That's all!
Well then, shall we eat now?
Itadakimasu.
Ah...
I'm so happy...
That bacon is homemade,
so be sure to eat a lot!
Okay!
Both soldiers and trumpeters need stamina.
Be sure to eat up and grow strong.
I'll do my best.
Kureha.
Y-Yes?!
When we're done with breakfast,
show her around the base.
Understood...
Attention!
I'm actually very busy, but this was an order,
so I'm showing you around because I don't have a choice.
Y-Yes! Please take care of me, Kureha-san!
Don't be so informal, Private Sorami!
My apologies!
Umm...
Private Suminoya-dono.
Fine.
First of all, face toward the platoon and national flags.
Salute!
Currently, there are five members of the 1121 Platoon.
There's one lieutenant, one sergeant,
one corporal, and two privates.
In total, five.
Understood, Private Suminoya-dono.
That's the bare minimum, so...
...in other words...
...we're all elites.
Understood!
The equipment that our platoon has been given includes:
Tanks: 1, heavy machine guns: 1,
light machine guns: 2, rifles: 4, handguns: 5.
With these, our mission is to defend Trois, the national border around Seize.
Um...
P-Private Suminoya-dono, I have a question!
Very well then.
Permission to speak granted, Private Sorami.
I thought...
If my memory serves me right, what lies beyond Seize is...
Of course, it's a no man's land beyond the mountains,
but Helvetia's borders only extend this far.
That makes this a national border! The front lines!
A crucial base!
Consequently, we must always keep watch during the night, the five of us.
Falling asleep on watch is strictly forbidden.
And this is a hotline connected to the Capital. The only one in the city.
Which means...
When it rings, it means something big is about to happen.
If it does, everybody wakes up and is put on high alert!
Understood?
Understood, Private Suminoya-dono!
On the second floor, there's the Captain's quarters and the briefing room.
Under normal circumstances, entry is...
...perfectly fine.
However, make sure you knock first!
This is the latrine.
Bath drawing, as well as cleaning duties, are assigned by rotation.
And...
Baths are taken in order of ranking, right?
Wrong.
That's because baths are more fun if we all get in together, right?
Captain!
What are you doing?
Cleaning the bathroom...
But it's Noel's turn today!
But she just seemed so tired.
You're setting a bad example for the newcomer!
I'll do it myself later,
so just go do something captain-worthy for now!
And now... BEHOLD!
This is the 1121 Platoon's main tank.
Vector-class Zero Autonomous Tank Walker,
the "Takemikazuchi".
Compared to the one on the training grounds, this one is huge!
This here is a so-called Zero Generation tank.
There's less than ten remaining in the country. It's almost an antique now.
I've heard of them before.
They're supposed to be really amazing.
But the legs...
It's being repaired.
There aren't enough parts.
W-Well, there's no manual for it,
and we can't find most of the parts...
But, Noel will do something about it somehow, so it'll be all right!
Don't even think about calling it useless!
I'm sure this tank...
Some day, it will...
Don't make fun of us...
I know we're too relaxed.
We're really relaxed...
They call us the useless squad in Seize, or call us decorations.
We're a pink squad, yet we don't even have a tank that works!
But...!
Kureha-chan.
End of tour.
Dismissed!
Looks like they're getting along.
Really?
Just like when we first met.
Yeah.
But there's a little problem.
Last night, after I sent you after Kana-chan...
Captain! Why is she communications?!
You told me the new recruit would be a loader or a pilot!
We can't do anything about it.
She was sent by command.
This is the army, you don't always get what you want.
But...!
There, there.
It's all right.
Rio will take care of you too, no different from before.
And of course, so will I.
She has pretty good intuition,
so she might have realized something.
You think so?
We need to do something.
I saw it.
Huh?
Saw what?
A ghost?!
Yeah.
As if.
You were probably just half asleep.
As I thought.
What do you mean by that?
I saw it too, the ghost.
It was in the barracks, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Don't encourage her!
But, things like ghosts are normal, aren't they?
I told you to stop already!
You too, Noel!
You're an engineer; go investigate like one, and then report back!
No.
Why?
Because I'm scared.
What are you saying?
There's no such thing as ghosts!
There aren't! There aren't! There aren't! There absolutely aren't!
I agree with you.
You do?
Yup, there are no such things as ghosts.
There aren't!
No way!
Absolutely no way!
All right!
Thoroughly investigate the area.
If you encounter the enemy, blow your trumpet.
Reinforcements will come!
Why this?
Um... Private-dono...
What is it... Kana-
Private!
This is...
...kinda fun, isn't it?
The thunder sounds like a marching beat.
This is a mission!
Not a game.
Listen up, Kana- ...Private Sorami!
You're in front.
I'm backup.
Understood!
Forward, march!
This area is still looks the same as it was before it became a fort.
What was it before?
How am I supposed to know?
Get going already!
Okay.
Ideographs.
I wonder what's written here.
You can't read it, so put it back already.
I'd love to be able to read it.
It's probably some junk from a long time ago.
Hurry up, let's go.
You...
You're not scared?
Nope.
Idiot.
Well, ghosts protect us, don't they?
Huh?
Well,
in the village where I was born, we held a festival to celebrate and thank the ghosts every year.
Where were you born?
Well, ghosts, you know, possess people,
drink their blood, move corpses,
and lots of disgusting stuff like that.
That was close.
Rats carry bad diseases sometimes...
What?
So you are scared of...
Coast clear?
Looks like it.
Hey, Kureha... Private-dono.
I was thinking...
This could have been a school before.
What?
There aren't any schools this big, not even in the Capital.
But, there used to be a lot more people, right?
So, I'm sure there were a ton of kids our age at this school.
All studying together...
Oh!
What? What? What?!
I'm pretty sure they taught music here!
Outside of the army?
Because, look here!
It hasn't changed.
I can't read the writing, but...
D-sharp.
The sounds
don't change.
What are you doing, just standing there?
W-What?!
Hey, Kureha-chan!
It's wonderful, isn't it?
What is?
All of it!
Huh?
The town of Seize, this building, everyone in the platoon... they're all...!
We're just a tiny troop in the middle of nowhere.
Our tank doesn't work, they forget about our supplies most of the time.
We never get any real missions.
We're all so relaxed...
But you love it, don't you?
What?
What's that?
What? What?
What?!
I-I-It's-
IT'S HERE!
Wait for me, Kureha!
Kanata!
Wow.
Of course it is!
I'm the gunner of the 1121 platoon,
the place I love more than anything!
So, they found our ghost, huh?
How is this a ghost...?
Hey, you.
You look a lot like the thief from yesterday...
Why you...
I'll eat you up!
No, Rio, don't scare her when she's hurt.
But...!
I'm sure she has nowhere else to go.
And what is our symbol again?
It would be wrong to cook her.
Right, Shuko-chan?
She even gave it a name...?
But I think that's wonderful.
You almost died because of this thing yesterday...
But, today I had this great adventure thanks to it!
Right, Kureha-chan?
What are you talking about?
You couldn't even call that a little adventure!
Sheesh.
I guess majority rules?
Nope.
Captain's orders.
But next time you steal food, you'll be disciplined.
All right?
That was Rio this morning, right?
If Kanata did it every day, we'd get complaints from the town.
I'm sorry.
That's your chair, Kana-chan.
Kureha-chan?
I just happened to find another chair like it.
I didn't really do it for you...
Thank you!
Hey!
Stop it!
That's dangerous!
What are you two doing...?
What about breakfast...
Next week: A Day With the Squad.
Rio Runs.