Yoshii Akihisa was studying.
I have to win in tomorrow's Exam Summoning Contest!
For Himeji's sake, I can't afford to lose!
Japanese History
Okay! Let's start with something I'm not too bad at, Japanese history!
You're working hard, Aki.
Sis!
I made a late night snack for you.
I wanted to cook something myself,
but I didn't have time, so please make do with this instant ramen.
Th-This is?
Do your best!
I wrote that out with mayonnaise.
I put all of my heart into it so that you can try your best, Aki!
I-I see.
No, it all starts with a challenge!
I'm digging in!
This red broth almost resembles that in Szechuan-style super spicy ramen,
but it's not quite spicy and actually, mysteriously sour,
and combined with a flavor that's neither fruit nor vegetable.
It's a taste that really makes you think "déjà vu!".
I mean... what the hell is this?!
When I first wrote it out in ketchup,
it dissolved.
You ruined the instant ramen.
I have rice balls, too!
Oh, these look normal.
The seaweed wrapping carries the scent of the seashore,
the coarse sea salt stimulates the appetite,
and the rice, cooked a little sweet, round and soft, has a crunchy feel that-
Crunch crunch
crunch...
Sis, I don't think this is the kind of texture a rice ball should have.
Aki, I know what you're talking about.
You know the Spanish dish, Paella, don't you?
It's my favorite.
Paella is delicious when cooked "al dente", where the rice is cooked crunchy to the bite.
I cooked the rice with all my heart just to delight you!
Then, amazingly,
Al dente's feelings
X
Program is starting...
the rice was cooked al dente as if my feelings came across!
Al dente's feelings
X
No one needs their rice balls "al dente"!
Red: For god's sake, stop messing with food
Blue: Rice balls
Green: Al dente
Purple: How?
Yellow: Rice cooker
Orange: No one wants it!
How the hell did you even make these with a rice cooker?!
The world is still full of mysteries.
kongaragatta akai ito wa
こんがらがった赤い糸は
It's our tangled red thread of fate!
isso gouin datte choucho musubi kyu
いっそ強引だってチョウチョ結び きゅ。
I'll tie it into a butterfly knot!
mune ni hazumu kimi to no mirai
胸にはずむキミとの未来
My heart leaps at the thought of a future with you,
hodoicha dame! yakusoku ne
ほどいちゃダメ! 約束ね
so don't go untie it! It's a promise, yeah?
haato kintore
ハート筋トレ
I am training up my heart
rippa ni joujushite misemasu!
立派に成就してみせますっ
I will show you just what I can do!
Love! dame na koi no
LOVE・ダメな恋の
Love! After a failed love
Cry! deeta wa mou
CRY・データはもう
Cry! Now my data is
Trash! yaku ni tatanai no
TRASH・役に立たないの
Trash! It isn't any good at all!
atarimae
あたりまえ
I should have known
So! kimi no mae ja itsudemo
SO・キミの前じゃいつでも
So, whenever you are here, I am always
hatsukoi reberu dana kawaii
初恋レベルだな… 可愛い?
just like a beginner in love... Am I cute?
wakatta you na koto itte
わかったようなコト言って
I always act like I know it all
wai wai wai
ワイワイワイ
Why? Why? Why?
oshaberi na tomodachi
お喋りなトモダチ
Everyone is so friendly
dakedo minna
だけどみんな
But in fact, everyone
shiritai no wa jibun no
知りたいのは自分の
really wants to know how they rank
koi no hensachi
恋の偏差値
in the game of love!
arere
あれれ
Huh?
heikinten ja rongai uwate na daarin
平均点じゃ論外?うわてなダーリン
Average isn't enough? You're so great my darling!
jissai wa tonda kataomoi
実際はとんだカタオモイ
It is in fact, a crazy one-way love!
reberu ageteikou
レベルあげていこう
Let's raise our level up together!
High!
High! High! High!
kongaragatta akai ito wa
こんがらがった赤い糸は
It's our tangled red thread of fate!
isso gouin datte choucho musubi kyu
いっそ強引だってチョウチョ結び きゅ。
I'll tie it into a butterfly knot!
mune renda panikku kimi to kyuutenkai
mune renda panniku kimi to kyuutenkai
胸連打パニック キミと急展開
My heart is hit by panic! Things with you just took off!
acchi muicha dame tsuite kite
あっち向いちゃダメ! ついてきて♪
Don't go looking elsewhere! Just follow me!
haato
ハート
I am training up my heart
kintore
筋トレ
angai tafu ni kyou mo moumoku!
案外タフに今日も盲目っ
Amazingly, today was pretty tough too
FFFpeeps presents
Day 2
"Idiots, Fireworks, and the Summoning Contest"
It's the second day of the Refresh Festival.
These are our sales from yesterday!
X
Office
Deposits
X
Withdrawals
Balance
X
Fumizuki Credit Bank
Balance
X
Withdrawals
We can afford some amazing new facilities with this!
However, the upgrading of our facilities is conditional.
We have to win the Exam Summoning Contest.
The Contest will be a randomized tournament between teams of two.
Himeji and Shimada will be the leading team.
Akihisa and I will participate as backup.
The two of us don't need to take part?
I'll have another task for Hideyoshi and Voyeur to do.
Got it! Leave it to us!
If we gear up and do well in the Contest, we can improve Class F's appeal, too!
We must win, so that Himeji won't transfer at the very least!
So, Akihisa, I hope you've studied well and came prepared.
If you don't get enough points in the recovery exam before the battle, you won't stand a chance!
I've got it! I focused especially on studying Japanese history!
I see. Good work, Akihisa.
Huh?
What's this?
Japanese history won't be in today's Contest.
Are you serious?!
No one told me~!
We hereby commence the Exam Summoning Contest!
Exam Summoning Contest
Takahashi Youko
Fukuhara Shin
The main event of the second day of the Refresh Festival at Fumizuki Academy has finally begun.
What do you think, Ms. Takahashi?
I hope to see the students doing their best.
Blue corner, Class 2-F, Sakamoto Yuuji, Yoshii Akihisa!
Class F
Yoshii Akihisa
Sakamoto Yuuji
Let's win this!
Sure.
Come on! Don't be so down just because you didn't cram the right subject!
Red corner...
Class F
Yoshii Akihisa
Sakamoto Yuuji
Look, we'll fight a team from Class E first.
We can win as long as we focus.
Right. We did fight them in an Exam Summoning War once before.
Class 2-B, Iwashita Ritsuko, Kikuiri Mayumi!
Class B
Iwashita Ritsuko
Kikuiri Mayumi
What?! It changed?!
Suddenly we're up against Class B!
Excuse me! What's the meaning of this?
Shouldn't it be a team from Class E?
Well, I don't really...
What's wrong?
It seems we're having some technical difficulties.
We'll deal with that later. Hurry it up!
Oh well.
Mayumi!
All right.
Let's go, Ritsuko!
This came out of nowhere.
What should we do, Yuuji?
We'll have to beat them, of course!
What do you think about this match, Ms. Takahashi?
Takahashi Youko
Fukuhara Shin
This match between Class B and Class F might be too one-sided.
We're still in the first round, so there will be quite a few unbalanced matches.
Battle Subject
The battle's subject is... Math!
Math
Begin!
Summon!
Not bad, as you'd expect from Class B.
However...!
Summon!
That's awesome, Yuuji! How'd you get such a high score?
You know, I've been studying hard so we can win against Class A next time.
Against Class A?
Yuuji, you're so...
Shouko asked me...
What?
Yuuji!
...where I want to hold the wedding ceremony.
My... My life depends on beating Class A!
Yuuji, you're so...
We're in this together! So don't go letting me down!
Of course. I've been studying too!
Summon!
You're so helpless.
I can't help it!
It looks like they won't stand a chance against us.
Let's clean things up quickly and get ready for the next match.
Ritsuko!
Mayumi!
Let's go!
Oh, their coordination looks pretty good.
It's not half bad for a girls' pseudo teamwork.
Let us show you the true meaning of combination!
That's right, Akihisa!
Yuuji!
You do the rest!
We shouldn't both be leaving things to each other!
That's my line, you moron!
It seems we're equally matched in terms of teamwork.
Okay Akihisa. Let's go with that strategy.
Strategy?
Akihisa, you lure out one of them...
Mhm.
...and then you take out the other one!
That means I'll be taking on both of them!
Then there's no choice. Let's cooperate!
No choice?
I'll take the offensive, so you shield me.
Human shield
Then I'll be the only one getting beaten up!
Y'know it hurts when I get hit!
At this point, petty tricks are useless!
We'll take them out one on one in a head-on showdown!
Head-on
showdown
And the plan?
Oh no!
My attacks aren't hitting him!
As Akihisa is a Punishment Inspector,
he is used to controlling his Being for doing chores, and nimble movements are his specialty.
It's my turn now!
Good! How about Yuuji?
Why?
This is it!
This is an
imaginary scene.
Huh?
Don't we look like the bad guys here?
Takahashi Youko
Fukuhara Shin
This is quite an unpleasant sight.
As an educator, I'd like the Sakamoto-Yoshii pair to lose.
No way! That's so mean!
Winner, Blue Corner, Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
Class F
Yoshii Akihisa
Sakamoto Yuuji
Class B
Iwashita Ritsuko
Kikuiri Mayumi
This is so frustrating!
I'm so embarrassed that we lost to guys like them!
Everyone's trashing them.
We did it...
Refresh Festival
Exam Summoning Contest
Tournament Roster
The first round continued as shown, and the defeated teams were removed.
Blue corner, Class 2-F, Sakamoto Yuuji, Yoshii Akihisa!
Class F
Yoshii Akihisa
Sakamoto Yuuji
Red corner, Class 2-B, Nemoto Kyouji, 2-C, Koyama Yuuka!
Class B
Nemoto Kyouji
Koyama Yuuka
It's Class B again, Yuuji.
This time it's them, eh?
Yoshii and Sakamoto?!
So you're our opponents.
What's wrong, Kyouji? They're that pair of idiots from Class F.
We won't lose this match.
Y-You're right.
The battle's subject is... English.
Battle Subject
English
Begin!
Summon!
Yuuji...
What is it, Akihisa?
I thought you studied hard to beat Class A!
I can't study all the subjects at once!
Both of us have such low scores! What are we going to do?!
Don't worry. Because it's them, I can work something.
Voyeur, bring me that.
Th-That's?!
Nemoto Kyouji's
Personal Photo Album
Nemoto Kyouji's Personal Photo Album.
You can see how I've completely changed!
Featuring the model Nemoto Kyouji in a girl's dress as part of the Exam Summoning War events,
it's an exclusive masterpiece photographed and edited by Tsuchiya Kouta.
We'll use this to negotiate.
I see.
That guy did some horrible things to Himeji back then.
We won't hold back!
Nemoto, if you don't want this photo album made public-
Hold on, Akihisa.
Why? Don't tell me you're going to forgive him!
You're being too soft.
Nemoto, look at this!
Th-That is...!
I-I understand, Sakamoto. We surrender!
You guys can have this match.
So, those photos...
Class C rep, do you want them?!
Fine. We lose.
Winner, Blue Corner, Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
Sakamoto . Yoshii WIN
Please, Yuuka! Let me explain!
Kyouji...
We're over.
Yuuka!
Bump.
Bump. The next matches were resolved in a similarly smooth manner.
You did it, Aki!
That's great, Akihisa!
Mister, you're awesome!
Thank you, Hazuki.
How did you do, Himeji?
We won too.
It was a piece of cake.
I hope we can meet in the final round!
Something's wrong.
What's the matter, Sakamoto?
Our opponents have been a little...
Since it was randomized, weren't we just unlucky?
I don't think that's all it is.
Hideyoshi, Voyeur, prepare to execute the plan.
Roger!
Understood.
Plan?
If I'm correct, we won't be able to win head-on against our next opponents.
Class F
Yoshii Akihisa
Sakamoto Yuuji
Red corner, Class 2-A, Kirishima Shouko, Kinoshita Yuuko!
Class A
Kirishima Shouko
Koyama Yuuka
I knew it! We're up against these two from Class A.
It's just as we thought.
We're counting on you, Hideyoshi!
You did it! Hideyoshi is disguised as Kinoshita. The strategy works since they're twins!
Did you think it would all work out so well?
Huh? Hideyoshi?
"Hideyoshi"? Are you talking about that idiot?
Exam Summoning Contest
Sorry. I messed up.
What?!
I can see through what Yuuji's thinking.
Then we'll have to use our backup plan!
Backup plan? Are you saying you have a different strategy?
Of course!
Yuuji, say exactly what I tell you to.
All right. I'll leave it all to you this time!
"Shouko, listen to me."
Shouko, listen to me!
"I really want to win."
I really want to win!
"If I win this contest, I'll propose to you."
If I win this contest, I'll propose to you!
"I love you, Shouko."
I-
As if I'd say that, asshole!
Damn it!
If I win this contest, I'll propose to you!
I love you, Shouko~!
I'm defeated.
Class Rep!
I'll defeat you alone.
Battle Subject
The battle's subject is... Health.
Health
Begin!
Summon!
I still have a plan!
Let's go! I'll show you my most powerful summon!
Summon!
Behold, the special proxy summon!
I dare you to defeat it!
Sir, he's breaking the rules.
Oh no!
I love you, Shouko~!
We withdraw.
Class Rep!
Because the Red corner withdrew,
Sakamoto . Yoshii WIN
the winner is the Blue corner, Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
FFF
Recruiting Members
Pay
Monthly salary: 1 AP (the actual item)
Wow
5 AP can be exchanged for 1 HP!
Also
additional percentage pay depending on your performance!
For details,
please submit an inquiry.
Accepting applications 24/7!!
Please contact Sugawa Ryou of 2-F.
Bastard, what have you done?!
It's your own fault for coming up with such a flimsy plan.
Are you kidding me?! You've just endangered my life!
It's amazing you guys actually won when you're like that.
It's because you're such a dumb idiot! Idiot!
Idiot!
It doesn't matter, does it? Both our teams got into the semifinals!
Idiot! idiot!
Yeah, you're right. Since both teams came this far, winning the contest is no longer just a dream!
That's awesome! I'll do my best cheering for you so you can win!
Thank you, Hazuki! I'll do my best!
Now we'll begin the semifinals.
Class F
Yoshii Akihisa
Sakamoto Yuuji
Red corner, Himeji Mizuki, Shimada Minami!
Class F
Himeji Mizuki
Shimada Minami
No way!
It's okay. Our goal is to have a team from Class F win the tournament.
We don't need to go out of our way to win.
Yeah. We should just lose so they can save their strength for the next round and-
Mr. Stupid, do your best!
Hazuki!
I'll be cheering for you, so don't you lose!
Sorry, Hazuki.
We've got reasons that a kid just wouldn't understand.
If you win, I'll give you an adult's kiss as a reward!
And not just a kiss, I'll have a bath with you, too!
A bath... together?
I'll rinse your back and your fatigue right away!
Every match should be fought seriously, shouldn't it?
H-Hold on. Our goal is...
Die!
It'd be rude of us to go easy on you, after all.
No way! If we fight for real, the feedback's going to hurt me...
Kill him!
Why?
We're all in Class F, but I feel really left out.
Give it up, Akihisa. We'll lose quick and pull back.
If you lose on purpose, I won't forgive you.
Shouko?!
Yuuji, you said you'd propose to me if you win.
If you lose on purpose, we'll marry immediately.
Then there's no difference either way!
Wh-What should we do?
Then we'll just have to win to shut 'em up!
But how are we going to win against Himeji's team?!
Battle Subject
The battle's subject is... Classics.
Classics
Begin!
This is an
imaginary scene.
Summon!
This is an
imaginary scene.
A Being with six points left is as good as done!
Of course!
Let's go, Akihisa!
Yeah!
Summon!
Akihisa!
I do regret my failings.
You're so persistent! Just get knocked out already!
One blow and you'll be in the netherworld.
If I'm hit with those scores, I really will die of pain!
Akihisa, block Himeji's weapon! I'll do something about it!
Got it! I'll try!
What are you doing?!
Let go of her!
Yuuji, now's your chance!
Now, don't involve me when you-
Eat this!
Huh?
Yuuji!
Winner, Blue corner, Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
So it didn't really matter who took me out, did it?
Kill!
Help! Help me!
Why only me?
Don't worry. Your ignominious death won't be in vain.
Ignominious deaths are in vain by definition!
I've acquired new information.
Information?
It's just as Yuuji surmised.
I see. I knew it.
Akihisa, we'll get serious in the finals.
Meat
Yeah!
Final Match
It's finally time for the final match to take place, and all students are watching.
Surprisingly, a pair of the lowest-ranking Class F students have fought all the way up to the finals.
Takahashi Youko
Fukuhara Shin
We might have to change the way we view Class F.
They will be facing off against a pair of third year students from Class A.
Class 3-A?!
Red corner, Class 3-A, Shunpei Natsukawa, Yuusaku Tsunemura!
It's the Eversummer pair!
Akihisa!
Aki!
Good job making it to the finals.
But this is as far as you'll go.
We'll pound on you till we're satisfied!
You've still got that on?!
I can't get it off!
You're a pervert!
You stuck it on me!
Upperclassmen, are you done playing your petty tricks?
Tricks?
You manipulated who we'd fight, didn't you?
We did it so you could lose quickly without embarrassing yourselves.
But, dang, you've really stuck it out.
Now's the time to settle things from yesterday!
Sounds good. We'll take your challenge.
Just you wait! I'll crush you with my best subject, English.
Battle Subject
English
Both teams, get ready for the match!
Battle Subject
Japanese
History
It's not English?!
Well done, Voyeur!
This is a piece of cake.
Yuuji...
They've been messing with us quite a bit. This much of a handicap seems fair.
Damn it! Summon!
Summon!
What?!
We're even?!
Aki usually scores around 60!
That's awesome, Akihisa!
I'm not going to hold back!
Shut it!
I'll be your opponent!
What?!
Damn you, you're just a class F student!
Now's my chance!
I'll teach you the value of experience!
Be grateful!
I heard you're a Punishment Inspector. That must have hurt.
Akihisa!
You bastard, hang in there!
Are you ready, pal?
Of course!
This is futile!
We'll finish you off!
Go!
Oh, you threw your weapon! All right, bring it on!
I've got you!
0 points
What?!
Akihisa!
Winner, Blue corner!
Wh...
What?
The winner of the Exam Summoning Contest has been decided.
It's the pair of Sakamoto Yuuji and Yoshii Akihisa from Class 2-F.
We did it, Akihisa.
Yeah!
Damn, this is all bullshit!
What? You're still complaining?
Of course! You cheated in all your matches!
We won with our wits.
You cheated, too!
Oh? Then we'll expose everything that's happened!
The contest will be invalidated!
They're going to expose our tricks using the school's broadcast system!
You're kidding! If our hard-earned victory becomes null and void...
Akihisa!
That's it!
Let me borrow this for a second.
Wh-What are you...!
No one will get in the way of our victory!
We have to win and buy new facilities!
I'm not going to let Himeji transfer!
We did it!
Well done, Akihisa!
Oh.
This is bad.
You scumbags...!
Not there!
Are you all right, Mr. Stupid?
My goodness. There's a limit to what you can do.
But they...
The funds for purchasing new facilities have mostly gone to pay for the school property you destroyed.
What?!
With this much, we can only afford tea tables.
Preposterous, indeed.
Then, will Himeji transfer...
Akihisa!
Himeji!
Where were you, Mizuki?
I was talking with my dad for a minute.
Was he here to see it?
This is hopeless.
My dad...
said I should also strengthen my body if I'm going to study here.
That means...!
Also...
he told me I have nice friends!
Yeah, that's right!
Monday! Monday! Monday!
Monday!
yasumi no yokujitsu wa yasumi ni suru beki da!
休みの翌日は休みにするべきだ!
The day after a day-off should also be a day-off!
Monday! Monday! Monday!
Monday!
yasumi no zenjitsu mo yasumi ni suru beki da!
休みの前日も休みにするべきだ!
The day before a day-off should be a day-off too!
Monday! Monday! Monday!
Monday!
owaritaku nai!
終わりたくない!
I don't want to see it end!
tsuzuite hoshii!
続いて欲しい!
I want it to go on and on!
heya kara wa detaku nai!
部屋からは出たくない!
I don't want to get out of my room!
shinjitaku nai!
信じたくない!
I don't want to believe it!
shinjirare nai!
信じられない!
I can't believe it!
getsuyou wa kirai
月曜はキライ
I really hate Mondays!
Good morning!
okinakya owaru
起きなきゃ終わる
If I don't wake up it will end.
Good morning!
sakaraenai suima ni
逆らえない睡魔に
I can't fight against this drowsiness.
Good morning!
ato chotto dake nebareru
あとちょっとだけ粘れる
I can hold out just a little longer.
Good morning!
yume no naka wa shiawase!
夢の中は幸せ!
I'm happy in my morning dream!
okitara ii tomo
起きたらいいとも
It'd be best if I got up,
owatta "dame kamo..."
オワッタ「だめかも…」
but it's over. "Maybe that's no good..."
yume no tsuzuki wa horaa na genjitsu
夢の続きはホラーな現実
After the dream comes the horror of reality.
imasara jitabata shitemo
今更ジタバタしても
Even if I struggle against it now,
jikan wa modorya shinai
時間は戻りゃしない
that time won't come back to me.
futatabi yume no sekai e daibu
再び夢の世界へダイブ
So I dive back into the world of dreams!
Now we commence the festival after-party.
All students, please assemble at the school building.
There were misunderstandings here and there, but they were all just unfortunate mix-ups!
So please give me another chan-
Wait for me, Yuuka!
Yuuji, you promised. Propose.
Damn it!
Testimonials obtained under duress can't be used as evidence in a court, you know!
Um, Akihisa...
I-If you'd like to...
we could...
Folk dance!
Do it with me!
Oh, shall we dance, Hazuki?
No way!
Akihisa!
There's no helping them.
And so concluded the Refresh Festival.
The burning flames colored their cheeks,
and each one kept their sentiments in their heart, all as the night of the festival was deepening.
The End