"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Then, this problem...
Shiraishi!
You just called on me!
I see... then, Izumi.
Izumi!
No, I'm not asleep, okay?
I haven't said anything yet.
"A Question of Motivation"
I forgot my English textbook.
Why don't you go
borrow it from Kagami?
They had English class too
today, right?
Man, it's because you're so careless!
Thanks!
You have to check the night before.
Tsukasa tends to
forget a lot of things.
Come to think of it, Konata,
you hardly forget stuff like textbooks.
I'm pretty reliable
about things like that.
I leave all the textbooks
in the classroom in advance.
Yeah, that's right!
You're not reliable at all.
But if you leave all
the textbooks here,
you can't review what
we learned in class at home.
I never study at home.
After all, you leave
all the textbooks here
until the night before the exam...
But Kona-chan is good at doing
the one-night study plan!
Oh!
Maybe that's why I always
forget my homework.
In your case, it's not that you're
forgetting the homework.
You just don't have the will to do it.
So can I see this afternoon's
Japanese class homework?
Already?
I always wonder one thing.
Since you two are in the same class,
why don't you have Miyuki
show you her homework?
How do you put it...
Miyuki-san is just such a good person
that it's hard to ask her.
Maybe you don't
understand this feeling.
I kinda get it, but that isn't
a satisfactory answer.
Izumi!
What, is she late?
Stop! I'm not late!
I was a bit tardy as a result
of helping someone out.
I usually spend my time
with this person,
but I just couldn't bring myself
to say goodbye today.
I see.
He said, "I'm fine, so let's disband,"
but when the other five members
got what they wanted,
and that one person is
the only one who couldn't get it,
it just leaves such
a bad taste in your mouth!
Since we were in a party for so long,
we said, "At times like this,
we need to help each other out,"
and cheered each other up.
Oh, having good comrades
really is a good thing.
I see...
And so you spent all night playing
a net game again last night?
On and on, after I logged out?
Izumi! Izumi!
What, is she late?
Stop! I'm not late!
In front of the shopping strip,
a girl bumped into me,
and that girl suddenly grabbed
my hand and started to run.
And, upon listening to
what she had to say,
apparently she stole a piece
of taiyaki and was on the run.
I thought, "Why do I have
to run away with her
and get involved in all of this?"
But since I couldn't help it,
we entered a café to escape
from the taiyaki shop owner...
Uguu, there are so many places
in this story to nitpick!
But it's a bad thing to
point out all the flaws,
both as a teacher and
as a human being...
I caught a summer cold...
Hey, Izumi, what's wrong?
Oh, Ma'am, I'm sorry,
I'd like sick leave today...
Come on, playing games
too much again?
You really use the same trick
over and over.
Oh, no, I want to take sick leave.
You're not going to say that you've
caught a summer cold, right?
The rainy season is already over,
and we've got good weather now.
You shouldn't be saying
you're sluggish all this time,
so hurry up and get here!
And so, yesterday, I really felt like
I was being treated like
the boy who cried wolf.
You reap what you sow.
Kona-chan, are you all right already?
I think my fever's gone down,
but my throat still hurts.
Oh, that means that you breathe
through your mouth, Kona-chan.
Huh?
Well, of course she'd breathe
through her mouth too,
but isn't it usually through your nose?
Oh, but the percentage in which
Kona-chan breathes through
her mouth is higher.
I mean, you know, when the
cold virus enters your throat,
you get a throat cold.
And when it goes in through your
nose, you get a sinus cold, right?
Then, those that get
a throat cold, you know,
have a higher rate of getting
the virus in from their throat...
You know, at times like this, how
about we let Miyuki-san handle it?
Yeah...
Huh?
So hot...
I don't feel like doing anything.
Hey, Kagami? About that
birthday party today,
how about we do it
at my place after all?
I'm so hot I can't
move one more step.
That's a shame... I'm baking cookies
at my house right now.
I'm coming.
Yeah, hurry over!
Welcome.
Happy birthday, Tsukasa
and one other person!
Don't abbreviate me!
Happy birthday,
Kagami-san, Tsukasa-san.
Oh, thank you!
Thanks!
And this is something really simple,
but I thought it would
make a nice gift...
What is it?
Please open it.
Matching earrings!
I thought about all sorts of things,
but couldn't come up with one.
Then shall I give you two
something as well?
What's this thing?
Open it.
What is this?
A brigade leader's armband.
Try it on.
Why do I have to put on
something like this?
I thought you'd look
perfect in it, Kagami.
I think it suits you better than me.
Then, what about this?
To Heart?!
It was expensive!
Treat it well when you wear it.
Don't try to make us both cosplay!
It's not that different from
the uniforms we wear.
Oh, that's a problem if it's too big.
Right. Another problem
is when it's too smelly.
You know, it's someone
else's birthday,
so why don't you hold back a bit?
The cookies Tsukasa bakes
really are good!
Oh, I helped out today.
She was teaching me.
What's wrong?
It's strange, but upon hearing that,
I feel like there are tasty ones and
not-so-tasty ones mixed together.
What was that?!
Maybe this is one of yours, Kagami?
While you're at it,
have some cake too.
And so, Kagamin works diligently
only on her birthday.
Shut up.
By the way, don't you end up arguing
over how to cut the cake?
Why?
Well, like when you cut it
into many pieces,
what to do with the
strawberries on top,
or who gets to eat the
chocolate sign plate.
Sis, you like those sign plates, right?
Oh no, I went out of line.
Somehow, it's not moe
when it's Kagami.
What was that?!
I'll have some now!
I'll have some!
What is it?
My strawberry is so small...
What is it? Is there
some cake on my face?
I just found another charming
point about Kagamin, that's all.
Stop it! You're really
sounding like him!
It's almost summer vacation already.
You're right.
The beach, the pool,
summer festivals...
Are there any must-dos out there?
Brakes.
Speaking of summer, there is
the twice-a-year festival!
The war zone in Ariake!
No matter what you say,
it's gotta be Comiket!
No, no, no, no, that's only for you!
"Comiket?"
What kind of kit?
Well, for certain people
there are all sorts of events,
like going home for the holidays.
Good morning.
Miyuki, do you have a staple thing
to do during the summer?
Let's see.
For now, we're planning to go
overseas again this summer.
Again?! Did you say again?!
Damn you bourgeois...
Is that yogurt?
"Bourgeois?"
You said that you started
working in a cosplay café,
but don't those places only hire
people with good figures and all?
Well, I've been lamenting my lack
of breasts for all this time too,
"Flat"
but you know, in a certain
game, they were saying,
"A flat chest is
a status symbol! It's rare!"
And stuff like that.
"Small Breasts as a Status Symbol
Rare and Valuable"
And when you think about it,
there are needs of
that sort as well, right?
So I'm a valuable person!
I want to know how you can be
that confident thanks to a game.
Then, maybe I'm fine too?
Geez... it's almost finals.
Are you all right,
playing games so much?
If you could channel that passion,
if only a little, into studying,
I'm sure your grades
would improve quite a bit.
If she's that easily swayed,
if some game that
lauded studies came out,
something incredible might happen.
There are those moe
quiz drills out already...
What's wrong?
There are so many
teenage crimes lately...
When things like that happen,
they ask all the neighbors,
and they always say something like,
"He was usually such a quiet boy,
he never seemed to be
the type that would do that."
Well, that shows all the more
that superficial personalities
really aren't of any use.
If you were to commit a crime...
"I always thought that she would
do something like this someday,"
would be exactly what I would say.
Hot...
It's so hot, I don't feel like
doing anything at all.
I completely understand
how you feel...
But you always have
one excuse or another
to not feel like doing
anything all year long.
Lucky Star!
"Hiiragi family"
Hello, Kagami.
S'up? How's your
exam studies going?
I was just cleaning up
my room right now.
You know, when you're
pressed for time,
don't you just get the urge
to clean up and stuff?
I understand how you feel,
but do your best.
All right!
I'll do at least a little today.
I'll take a 30-minute break.
My concentration doesn't last.
Darn, it's already time.
30 more minutes... 30 more minutes...
It's almost time for Haruhi to start.
Turn it on...
Is Nagato's long scene
the production staff cutting corners?
That Ya___oto really
isn't much lately...
Oh, they're flaming away already.
It's already 2 AM...
I can't really get to it today.
I'll sleep a bit, and study some
early in the morning.
If I'm going to get up at 5:00,
I can sleep for three hours right now.
In the end, I wasted all my time
last night with manga and anime.
That's just like you, Kona-chan.
You know, Konata, you have
strange tastes in manga and games.
You only read boys' magazines, and
your games are mainly dating sims.
Dad's always read manga
and played a lot of games,
so I think that's what influenced me.
Ever since I was little, I've been there
watching him read or play.
I can understand
the boys' magazines,
but what kind of father plays
dating sims with cute girls
in front of his daughter?!
With both a father and
a daughter like that,
doesn't your mom feel bad about it?
Oh, we don't have
a mom in the house.
She died when I was really young.
I see...
Since I always do
the household chores,
I can do much more
than you can, Kagami.
Don't go stating
something unnecessary
in the middle of
a conversation on a hard topic!
You're good at most cooking,
right, Tsukasa?
I'm not sure if I'm good at it,
but I love to cook.
What about Miyuki-san?
She seems rich, so she might be
bad at doing household chores.
Oh, cooking?
Actually, I only help out
every so often,
so I'm not too good
at household chores.
It's a bit embarrassing to say.
See, just as I thought.
Oh, but Miyuki is too good
in all other aspects,
which makes her sense
of quality different.
So her "not so good"
shouldn't be taken literally.
I see.
Oh, that's not true...
Then what about our teacher?
She says she lives alone,
but she really has a slacker image.
In this day and age, you can get by
even if you can't cook at all!
There are convenience stores and all.
Just kidding!
I properly do my housework!
I can handle as much as anyone else.
Please don't make jokes
that we can't tell are jokes!
Oh, Tsukasa still has my dictionary.
Tsukasa, sorry, but can I
have my dictionary back?
I thought about cleaning my room
a little to change my mood...
You too?
S'up? What's wrong?
All of us at work
are supposed to think of new
menu items for the summer.
Oh, they have those?
Or rather, have you given up
on studying for the exams?
How about having something
really spicy because it's hot out,
and going for ultra-spicy ramen?
How about something that's
more fitting for a café?
Then, an ultra-spicy parfait!
Can you stop with that knee-jerk
reflex way of thinking already?
I can't stand up...
Why doesn't our school have
any swimming classes?
We have a pool, after all.
It's good for me that we don't.
Why?
Actually, I cannot open
my eyes underwater,
so I can't swim that far...
It's so embarrassing to say...
Your weaknesses, each and
every time, are so unfair!
Oh, the summer Comp-Fest
is finally going to begin!
That's right...
You know, I started
my job just for this.
A festival... Everything about
it brings up memories!
What's with that old routine?
Well, when customers join in
and get all energetic and stuff,
you get the feeling that you're making
the festival rowdier together, right?
If you could turn even
a little of that passion
towards what goes on at school...
I can't get to sleep,
so I think I'll read a book
until I get sleepy.
And I just happen to have
bought a new book, too.
Not only did I not get sleepy,
it's already morning.
And now I'm tired and
ready to go to sleep...
"Silent Mode"
Stare...
I know to turn the power off
near the priority seats
because it has something to do
with pacemakers and stuff, but...
Yeah.
Why is talking on the phone
basically not allowed in trains?
Isn't it because when you talk,
it's a nuisance to
everyone around you?
But, you know, aren't there people
out there that talk too loud,
even if they're not on the phone?
Regardless of age or gender.
Well, yeah, that's true, but...
Are you going to do some
priestess thing like New Year's?
No, we don't do that kind
of stuff in the summer.
Come to think of it,
it's already that time of the year.
What? Aren't you
on a diet right now?
Well, maybe it was because of
fatigue from all the exam studies,
but when I got on the scale yesterday
I had lost a little bit.
So I'm like, it's all right, you know?
So quick... Or rather, so weak-willed!
Morning!
Morning, Kona-chan!
Huh? What's wrong, Kagami?
Konata!
It's my weight again!
I gained it all back in,
like, the blink of an eye!
It's because you put yourself off
guard and ate too many snacks.
Wait, is that a senryu poem?
"It's my weight again!
I gained it all back in, like,
the blink of an eye!"
There isn't much
difference in appearance
when you gain or lose
a kilogram or two...
Why does she look
so ecstatic or depressed
with a matter of a few kilograms?
This is why girls are so...
You are supposed to be a girl, too.
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
This week, Lucky Channel
has started up again!
Have all of you been doing well?
This is Akira Kogami,
always at 120% energy!
--This week...
--Nyoron! Just kidding.
I'm Minoru Shiraishi, the assistant...
Hey, you.
Yes? What is it?
Don't talk over me!
Oh... I'm so sorry!
This isn't a kid's errand,
so learn to do your job already.
Or do you want to quit
this job that much?
Oh, no! I'm so sorry,
I'll do my best, my very best!
Now, this time... Ta-dah!
There is big news for all of you!
The big request for
Akira's Fashion Project
in the November issue of Comptiq...
We got this many letters
from all of you already!
I believe that project also involved
someone besides Akira-sama.
Thank you for all of your entries!
I am mammoth happy!
--I don't get those '80s references.
--Now, from all these entries,
I'd like to introduce the ideas that
were chosen after a strict ruling!
Here goes...
Let's see, the Akira Fashion
Project from "Cherry"
in Satte City, Saitama...
Well... "Kagami looks good
in twin pigtails,
so how about you try
twin pigtails as well, Akira?"
Twin pigtails, huh--
Yeah... How wonderful!
That's right. Long hair
is the life of a girl.
And splitting it in two is, like,
giving it a very elegant
look to it, you know?
Doing it or not, Akira-sama,
the length of your hair
makes it impossible...
But it's not like making your hair
longer automatically makes it better.
--It gets heavy, you know.
--It's almost showing, so, please, lower...
--It gets harder to shampoo too.
Honestly, right now,
it's not the in thing.
They say "guys like girls
with long hair" so easily,
--It's about the people who're inside it.
--but do they know exactly how much time,
money, and effort go into its upkeep?
--The people who are inside it...
--It's not about you, Akira-sama!
--Furthermore, despite the effort,
nobody notices the difference...
--Are you listening to me? Please, come on...
It's already time to say goodbye!
Then, what would I be
like in twin pigtails?
The rest will be on my homepage,
or talked out on the radio!
I hope you guys listen up!
--I'll wait for ordinary mail too! Bye-bee!
--Then, please look forward
to the next episode.
What was that attitude earlier?
What do you mean by attitude?
You kept snapping at me!
What was that?!
Did you get irritated because
I corrected you in the beginning?!
No, I was just wondering
if people nowadays
would catch the Nori-P reference...
I'm so sorry. Let's have
a new, fresh feeling to this!
You know...
Yes?
I hear they're holding an audition
for the role of Minoru Shiraishi.
Are you serious?
This is the first I've heard of it!
Looks like you can apply.
--I'm going to apply?!
--Good for you!
--But I'm the actual person!
The actual what?
Kona-chan, you're amazing!
You can sing anything!
Though it's limited to anime songs.
You use various types of voices,
and sing very well.
It's the fundamental law
of singing anime songs
to perfectly mimic the original singer.
I see...
All right, I guess I'll sing!
What are you going to sing, Sis?
The title came up a while ago,
but it was a song that I didn't know.
Miyuki, you don't know this song?
I don't.
Practice what you preach, Kagami.
Oh, I've heard this song before!
You were watching the drama series
with me until recently.
Oh, really?
I prefer the movie version after all.
Are you an old guy or something?
♪ Goodbye is not a word of farewell ♪
Hey, she's good.
Amongst my sisters, she's the best singer.
♪ But a distant promise for
the day we meet again ♪
♪ Even if regret is left in the place
where the dream used to be ♪
♪ It only leaves the heart in the cold ♪
♪ Just like this, for
however many hours ♪
♪ I would like to hold you ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with
the next episode of Lucky Star?
Miyuki here.
They say that Golden Week was
an industry term named so
because during this time period,
the number of moviegoers
increases dramatically.
Next episode: The Famous Shooter.
"The Famous Shooter"
Look forward to it!