[narrator] At long last,
seven million years of human history
is about to come to an unforeseen end.
The apocalypse shall not occur
from the fallout of nuclear war,
extraterrestrial invasion,
nor catastrophic asteroid collision.
But rather, something else.
The extinction of mankind shall be
ushered forth by the will of the gods,
the very beings
who created the human race,
and who have now chosen to destroy it.
THE YOUNGEST OF THE 13 VALKYRIE SISTERS GÖLL
Great. It's time now, Brünnhilde.
Looks like everyone's ready.
THE COUNCIL OF VALHALLA
COUNCIL HALL
[gods chattering]
[gavel hammering]
ONE OF THE 12 GODS OF OLYMPUS HERMES
[male god clearing throat]
Well then, everybody,
it's been some time since
we've all been together, hasn't it?
Let the council of Valhalla now begin.
Deities have assembled here
from the world over
to decide on the fate of humanity.
PRESIDENT OF THE COUNCIL ZEUS
So, let me ask you...
Should we allow mankind to exist
for another 1,000 years
and forgive their crimes?
[ringing]
Or alternatively,
do we put an end to them for eternity?
[buzzer sounding]
By the will of the gods,
you will show me what you have chosen.
[male god 1] Over here.
Huh?
I say we finish off the wretched things.
GOD OF DESTRUCTION AND CREATION SHIVA
I've watched them for a millennium,
and I haven't caught any sign of them
learning from their mistakes.
Let's give them
the old fire and brimstone.
[female god] Shiva's right.
Everything is just as he says.
As time goes on,
the world becomes uglier and uglier.
GODDESS OF BEAUTY APHRODITE
The sea fills with trash and oil,
the forests have disappeared,
and countless creatures have gone extinct.
So, if I may, mankind is out of control.
They have become a cancer
that threatens to destroy the earth.
- [all chattering]
- [male god 2] Aphrodite speaks the truth!
[male god 3] We should crush them.
[male god 4] It's unforgivable!
[female god 2] An evil, plain existence.
[male god 5] I'm sick
of trying to guide them.
[male god 6] Here, here.
Now then, it seems the meeting
has reached consensus.
Let the records show
that the Council of Valhalla
has managed to agree
on a unanimous decision
to end the human race!
Just a moment!
[gods muttering]
[male god 7] Who does she think she is?
[all gasping]
[male god 7] Did that Valkyrie speak up?
THE ELDEST OF THE 13 VALKYRIE SISTERS BRÜNNHILDE
Huh?
[whimpering] What in the world
do you think you're doing, sis?
You can't just raise your voice
against the all-powerful like that!
Pardon my intrusion, your eminences.
But with all due respect, there's
something I'd like to discuss first.
[male voices] Be silent, Brünnhilde!
[screaming]
SUPREME NORSE GOD ODIN
Bastard, you're nothing
but a common demigod!
HUGINN
MUNINN
How dare you loosen your tongue
in the presence of greatness!
You halfling!
Are you asking for a challenge?
[Muninn continues shouting]
I will admit, it's true that the sins
of man are indeed unforgivable.
Hey, stop ignoring us!
[Brünnhilde] Despite that fact,
for you to simply wipe them out,
well, it just seems quite dull.
Oh.
Consider this, then.
A proposal.
A trial to decide if humans might be
worth keeping alive for years to come.
To demonstrate the power
and the benevolence of all the gods,
why not put humanity to the test?
What's your plan?
To flood the earth
into one big ocean again?
Or are you thinking about
starting another ice age to freeze them?
Neither.
Because I've come up with
a far more effective method.
- Hmm...
- [gods chattering]
- [male god 8] What could she be planning?
- [male god 9] Tell us your plan, then.
[male god 10] Halfling bastard.
I propose the ultimate trial
between the gods and mankind...
the Ragnarok!
No!
You can't be serious.
It's a special provision from article 62,
clause 15 of the constitution.
It stipulates the following.
"A final battle between the beast
and his creator."
"A one-on-one showdown."
[narrator] Behold,
the God versus Man Final Battle Law,
known as the "Ragnarok."
It is a series of duels
between 13 fighters representing the gods,
and the human race.
First side to seven matches wins.
If humanity loses,
it would face destruction.
Of course, should man reign victorious,
the gods must let them live
for another thousand years.
However, this law has never been exercised
in the entire history of civilization.
Their reasoning,
that man would never prevail.
THE REASONING
Their success would be impossible.
IMPOSSIBLE
In other words,
it's an extra-judicial clause.
A superfluous technicality
enacted purely for divine amusement.
[gods laughing]
[Huginn] Ha!
What are you blabbering about?
Surely even a Valkyrie
can comprehend the ridiculousness of that.
Man is nothing in the face of godly power!
[both] What a pointless idea.
[male god 11] I agree.
[male god 12] It's barely even...
[shouting continues]
I see.
So, the gods have decided to obliterate
the human race and be done with it.
To be clear...
you're trying to avoid a direct
confrontation with them.
Would you say that's correct?
- Hm?
- Huh?
You'd prefer to destroy them
without having to fight them yourselves.
Sounds like you'd rather
not be put in the same ring.
And if that's true... No, don't tell me...
I might be wrong, but that means...
you're all completely
terrified aren't you?
[echoing]
- [Göll whimpering]
- [Brünnhilde sighing]
If that's the case, then 1,000 apologies
for my careless outburst,
your greatnesses.
[stammering] Uh,
that's a joke, right, sis?
Silly me. Feel free
to disregard everything I just said.
Let's forget about that Ragnarok nonsense
and get back to it.
[whimpering] Hey, enough kidding around.
Forget about them wiping out mankind,
'cause at this rate
they're gonna wipe you out first.
Just hurry up
and apologize to them for real.
Say you're sorry,
and they might show us mercy!
[gods laughing]
Huh? What's so funny?
Shouldn't they be mad at us?
They're all laughing.
[rumbling]
Ah!
[narrator] Of course,
Brünnhilde knew what she was doing.
[Göll screaming]
[Brünnhilde] Just as I thought. The gods
have much shorter tempers than humans do.
[Zeus laughing]
What a fascinating idea!
A proper Ragnarok.
I must admit,
I'm quite pleased you brought it up.
Why, I could almost begin
to picture it in my head.
Surely I'm not alone here?
Please, the rest of you
are intrigued as well, no?
The mighty wrath of the gods,
overwhelming power,
a gratuitous display
of strength and authority.
How very exciting, isn't it?
Tell me, everyone, what do you think?
Let's have a brawl between man and maker!
A death match unlike any
the world has ever seen!
[gavel hammering]
[raucously cheering]
[both cawing]
[narrator] And thus,
the supreme joust between the eternal
and ephemeral was set in motion.
GOD VS. MAN - FINAL BATTLE RAGNAROK
Hear that, Brünnhilde?
The humans need a vanguard
to represent them.
I'll permit you to choose candidates
on their behalf.
You do want to assist them, don't you?
A curious inclination
for a tragic Valkyrie like you.
A half-god, half-human,
who hopes to save mankind
despite having once
been slain by them, right?
There's over seven million years
of human history.
I will select the 13 most worthy
of this particular challenge.
[Zeus chuckling]
- [Zeus laughing hysterically]
- [Göll sighing]
RAGNAROK
[fanfare playing]
VALHALLA ARENA
[crowd cheering]
[Göll] Whoa, looks like
they're almost ready.
So it'll start soon then?
Yes.
There are so many gods here.
I wonder which of them
they're going to send out first.
At long last.
I've been waiting for this for ages.
THE GUARDIAN OF THE END HEIMDALL
[speaking excitedly] The moment
I finally get to blow the Gjallarhorn!
It's time to raise the curtain
for the main event!
That's right,
the wildly anticipated Ragnarok!
[yelling] Let's get loud, everyone.
Are you ready?
[crowd cheering wildly]
The rules are straightforward.
It's a fight to the death,
whether they're human or a god.
The victor shall be decided the moment
that one party annihilates the other.
Our first round begins.
Introducing god number one,
the legend himself,
Everybody knows who this is.
His trusty Mjölnir can crush the earth!
And if he can't do it, no one can,
because he lives for battle
and dies for battle.
[crackling]
The strength of the Norse.
The one and only, Thor!
[crowd cheering]
[whimpering] They're really
starting off with the god of thunder?
No. There's no way we can win
against that monster, is there?
I have faith in our warrior, Göll.
Don't worry. He's got this.
[gasping]
Of the men I've encountered
on the battlefield,
he's the boldest.
STRONGEST
EVILEST
No, the most savage
and deranged beast that I have ever met.
CRAZIEST
Moving on.
Here's the guy
who's representing the humans today.
First up for the idiots, here he is!
[gong sounding]
[yelling]
What was that?
Is this where your legacy ends?
[all] No!
Seven million years of history,
is this where you yield your pride?
[all] No!
[horse whinnying]
[gasping] Whoa.
Oh dear.
[Heimdall] That's right. He's determined
to carry the torch for mankind.
There's no one else like him.
He's a brute!
He's ravenous enough to devour the gods.
Is there anybody more bloodthirsty?
[all] No!
[Heimdall] He's one of the most
vicious barbarians since the dawn of time.
Any objections?
[all] No!
[Heimdall] He's the champion of China!
The flying general,
Lü Bu!
[crowd cheering]
My liege...
Hail, Amitabha Buddha.
- [Brünnhilde] Enough. Stop praying, human.
- Hail, Amitabha Buddha.
Huh? Huh?
There's something you should realize
about the deities you're praying to.
They're the same ones we have to defeat.
Your prayers, they're for the enemy.
[Heimdall] We're off!
It's a dispute of destiny.
The last stand-off between god and man,
the Ragnarok!
We've got a hard pair
of heavy-hitters for our first match-up!
Representing the gods,
here comes the Nordic force,
the berserker of thunder himself...
Give it up for Thor!
[crowd cheering wildly]
And his opponent from the human side...
The toughest hero from the records
of Three Kingdoms...
Let's get loud for Lü Bu!
[cheering wildly]
It truly is
the strongest versus the strongest!
The energy in the arena
is fully off the charts!
You can do it, Thor!
GOD OF PEACE FORSETI
The other guy's only a measly human.
Come on,
you can knock him out in a single blow!
- [man] Strike them down, Lü Bu!
- Huh?
What the heck are you waiting for?
Go and tear those sons of bitches
into mincemeat! [laughing]
Huh? That's awfully vulgar.
- [glugging]
- [creaking]
Hm?
Ah, nothing better than a high stakes
battle royale to help the drinks go down.
ZHANG FEI
Am I right, or am I right?
Hm, I don't understand.
Since when was he the toughest
hero from the records?
LIU BEI
Shouldn't that refer to the being
who was actually deified?
And wouldn't that be you,
the great Guan Yu?
[Guan Yu] If we're only
considering tactical prowess,
then I concede that point.
On the other hand,
the answer might be different
if one were measuring strength
by one's pure ability as a warrior.
Which would make the toughest man
in the Three Kingdoms,
none other than Lü Bu!
[Zhang Fei] Ha! Ain't that right!
That being said, when it comes
to his army, things never change, do they?
[cheering and clanging]
[cheering stops]
[Chen Gong] My liege,
all your men are here.
ADVISOR IN LÜ BU'S ARMY
CHEN GONG
Let us watch over you.
Whenever you are on the battlefield,
we shall be right there beside you.
[voice breaking] Such glory.
I never imagined it, sir,
the day I'd get to gaze upon
your gallant figure once again.
It's indescribable.
[Göll] Lü Bu may be strong,
but Brünnhilde,
do you think that he can win?
It seems you doubt
that humanity stands a chance.
Is that what you honestly
choose to believe?
[stammering] Ah, I don't know.
[laughing] I'm certain every god gathered
here today believes the same thing.
Every single one of them.
That's why man has a chance.
The gods have fucked with
the human race for far too long.
Now's the best time for them
to kick their asses.
Uh, you did not just say "fuck."
[Brünnhilde] I said what I said.
- So we're kicking their asses?
- That's right, sister.
Jeez.
You know, you have
a filthy mouth sometimes, sis.
[Heimdall] Here we go.
Do you know how long
I've yearned for this?
I finally get to play
that wonderful sound.
[narrator] According to the Edda
of Norse mythology,
when Heimdall, the guardian of the end,
blows the Gjallarhorn,
it signals a cataclysmic event.
That momentous struggle
of epic proportions.
Let the Ragnarok begin!
May they be extinguished.
[cawing]
I'm not sure what I imagined,
but it's starting.
The battle between gods and mankind.
[horn sounding tunefully]
THE FINAL BATTLE BETWEEN GOD AND MAN
ROUND ONE
THOR VS. LÜ BU
THE BATTLE BEGINS!
[gasping for air]
Now then, the mightiest
of the gods is primed,
and the mightiest of men is ready!
Without further ado,
may the first round commence!
- Huh?
- What are they doing?
Why aren't they...
[crowd murmuring]
[Heimdall] Look at that.
They've lowered their weapons!
And they're... They're defenseless!
It seems like they're about
to approach each other.
How unpredictable!
And we've only begun.
Both fighters have left
their guards completely open.
Yet it appears they're starting to close
in on the distance between them!
Huh. Neither looks interested in
their enemy's next move.
As if they don't care about
taking advantage of any strategies.
I had a feeling things might go this way.
[laughing] He may be an odd one,
but that's our guy!
Hm.
Who does that lowly ant think he is?
That insolent mortal
ought to be cowering in fear!
[all chanting]
[crying]
[chanting continues]
[Chen Gong] Breathe, my liege.
Brünnhilde,
the guy who's defending humanity's honor
does know what he's doing, right?
'Cause the impression that I'm getting
is he's kind of underestimating
what he's up against.
[Brünnhilde] That's how
the so-called strongest live their lives.
[narrator] Thor and Lü Bu.
Although these two come from
different lineage,
they share one thing in common.
A penchant for slaughtering
their foes in one fell swoop.
[grunting]
[growling]
Huh?
[straining]
[heavy metal music playing]