Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start!
When watching Kaleido Star,
please keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I came to America all by myself
with aspirations of joining Kaleido Stage.
Everything is new to me,
but I'm doing my best in the spirit
of "try it rather than think about it."
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, that'll be super lucky.
And if I'm gonna do it, I just
gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! That's me.
Well, well, well, does
everyone have a lot of friends?
Friends you can have
fun with and laugh with.
Sometime you have fights,
but you help each other
even during sad or rough times.
Precious friends like that.
I'm going to work hard with
the help of Mia and Anna too!
I'm gonna! I'm gonna!
Yaritai koto wa nani
Sou kikareru tabi
Aoi sora miageta
Kotae wa only my heart
Honto ni daiji na kotoba
wa kantan ni wa iwanai
Hikari ga yubisasu
basho e to hashiridasu yo
Dakishimetai mono nara
nakitai hodo mune ni aru
Egakitsuzukete yuku kitto take it someday
Shiroi kumo ga nagareru
chiheisen no mukou ni
Naranderu mirai wa itsumo soba ni aru kara
Guiding you to a fantastic,
exciting, and intoxicating world,
Kaleido Stage's new production, Cinderella!
Of course, the main cast members
are Layla Hamilton and Yuri Killian.
In addition, we have
boldly included new members
who joined our troupe this year.
We're going to present a dramatic
stage with an unbelievable illusion.
Anna got the role of the prince's attendant,
and Mia won the role of the fairy godmother
after she went through the final
selection process with several others.
I wish I could've been in it too.
So you want to be in it.
Well, of course.
Oh! What? A child?
The audience should be all gone by now.
But you're not allowed on stage.
Oh, well... There are a lot
of circumstances behind this,
and it's not exactly that I'm
"not allowed on the stage"...
You must be pretty bad.
If you put it that way, you
could say that I'm pretty bad.
But you know, everyone's
bad when they first start out.
--Even someone terrible can
get better if she works harder...
--What a loser.
So, who was that kid?
"Try Hard and You'll Get an Amazing Chance."
Wow!
Mia's giving everything
she's got again today.
Amazing!
Jump higher!
Yes!
Too slow!
Too low!
Yes!
Do it like you're drawing the
audience into your performance!
Yes!
--They've been working since this
morning without any breaks at all.
--Gracefully!
--Yes!
No breaks?
No way...
I'm sorry!
Miss Layla!
It seems like you are not very
motivated. You can go home now.
I'm sorry. Please, one more time...
That won't be necessary.
I'll find someone else more qualified.
Or if that's not possible, I'll have
to have the production cancelled.
What?
This scene is the climax
in the first half of the show.
If this is how it's going to be,
we're better off not doing it.
Please wait!
I'll try harder! Please
give me one more chance!
Miss Layla!
I figured as much.
Or rather, she has way too little talent.
It's like, I might be the
only one who can do it.
I wonder if they're going to cancel the show.
If that keeps up, they just might.
Mia!
Are you all right?
You've been doing this
every morning without breaks.
I'm all right.
Idiot! If you keep this up, you'll get hurt.
But I have to. Because I can't do it.
Why don't you quit then?
It's so third-rate to give
up for a reason like that.
Such a loser.
It's her again!
You know her?
Marion, don't interrupt
their practice! Marion!
Okay!
Who's that?
No idea.
No idea?
That's Marion. She's the
daughter of Jean, the sceneman.
So that's who she is.
Still, she went too far with what she said.
Her mother used to be a star trampoliner.
She loves the trampoline, too.
She's also talented, and people
used to have high expectations of her.
But after her mother died,
she quit trampoline.
Her mother?
Yeah. She collapsed
suddenly, and died soon after.
After that, Marion
became sarcastic like that.
I see...
But still, she said too much.
I guess.
Oh, Mia.
I'm okay. Please leave me alone.
Mia...
Mia's grandma is hospitalized,
and her surgery date
is the same day as the
opening day for Cinderella.
Surgery? So Mia can't show her real abilities
because she's worried
about her grandma's surgery.
Not really. It's more
like she's trying too hard.
What?
Her grandma is the one most
looking forward to seeing Mia on stage.
I heard that when Mia
learned she'd been cast,
she sent her grandma an e-mail
saying that she would do her best,
so her grandma should do the same too.
I see. That's why she
was pushing herself so hard.
But Mia has the tendency to lose
her cool when she tries too hard.
Sorry, Grandma.
I may not be able to keep my promise.
Make the fairy godmother
role a part for three people?
What do you think?
Three?
Oh, I think it sounds great!
Wouldn't that make it even more difficult?
But I'd feel more reassured
if Anna and Sora were with me.
What?
That means...
In short...
The cast members would be...
So the cast members
are Anna, Sora, and myself!
What?! Me?!
Yeah. You don't want to?
No. I'm not saying that, but...
I'm okay with it,
but I'm not sure if we can
get him to change the cast now.
Fine, then.
It's an interesting idea.
I'll tell the director about it.
Make sure to come up with
something Layla will be satisfied with.
Then you mean you don't
mind me going on stage?
I'll decide that after I see the results.
But the time limit is three days.
If you're not ready in three days,
I will cancel Cinderella
as Layla suggested. Got it?
Yes, sir! We will do our best!
I can't believe Boss said okay.
Since we've gotten this far,
we have to be ready for the show.
I'm grateful to both of you.
No, I'm the one who should be grateful.
Sora?
What's the matter?
I have fun handing out toys
to kids in the audience now,
but I still want to appear on stage.
And now, thanks to Mia,
my wish may come true.
Let the three of us join forces and
appear on stage together!
Yeah.
After that, this is the climax
and all of us jump towards
the center like this.
Oh...
I wonder if handing off wands while
doing a cross jump is impossible after all?
Yeah. It could be.
Mia, why don't we change it
into something more simple?
We can't, because we have to
convince both Boss and Miss Layla.
I wish I could find a better idea.
When you think of Cinderella...
Glass slippers! When you
think of Cinderella...
A pumpkin prince!
There's no such thing.
Oh, really?
That's it.
That's it!
What do you mean?
A pumpkin prince?!
All right! I'll take that role!
No, that's not it.
No way!
Wait; let me try the idea on the simulator.
We'll install some kind
of device in the wands.
When we cross jump, we
spread out a big cloth like magic.
And then make it look
like a big pumpkin, like this.
What do you think?
Ooh...
I see. A pumpkin.
Which means if we don't fall at the
right moment together from the top,
it won't become the shape of a pumpkin.
I know. And once we
successfully make the pumpkin,
Cinderella will appear from inside.
Amazing! It's like magic.
If we can make the audience
think that, it'll really be magic.
A spell cast by the three of us.
Oh, it needs a name.
How about something like "Triple Illusion"?
Triple Illusion?
Yeah, this maneuver's name.
It sounds good.
All right, intensive training for
the Triple Illusion begins tomorrow!
Let's do our best!
Yes!
I have to work hard.
For Mia's sake and for myself.
This is a long-awaited chance.
Why are you so flustered?
Any normal person would be!
I need to tell you something. Lay down here.
No, thank you.
Then I will talk to you like this.
Like this?
I will get right to the point. You
should not pair up with those two girls.
What?
Your skill levels are far too disparate.
I already know that.
It's true that I suck, but this is my chance.
No, I did not mean it like that. Oh.
Please make sure to turn
off the light. Good night.
The reverse Star. A failure.
Hurry up and turn off the light.
Right.
Sorry...
It's my fault.
Don't keep blaming just yourself.
I just couldn't catch it.
I hate it!
I just keep making mistakes.
I'm sorry.
We failed because our moves didn't match up.
So, it wasn't just your fault.
Right, Mia?
Mia...
If you think I shouldn't be part
of it, please feel free to say so.
I didn't say that.
No, you didn't.
My timing was also a little
off, so it could be my fault.
It's my idea's fault.
My idea was just impossible to begin with.
As I thought, you're third-rate!
I don't want people like
you up on the trampoline!
Moping around about whose
fault it was. You guys are losers!
What's the matter with you?
This has nothing to do with you.
It does too!
Because... Because...
the trampoline was...
my mom's... my mom's favorite...
Marion...
Marion!
Sorry about the weird things Marion said.
Please let me know whenever
you need a trampoline adjustment.
Come on, let's practice, practice.
Miss Layla...
Um...
I think having three people
play the fairy godmother
will be a selling point
for the upcoming show.
Thank you.
That is why we need to make sure
it's perfect before the show starts.
Yes, we will do our best.
Sora and Anna, please
step down from this role.
What?
Perfect this routine using
you, Charlotte, and Julie.
But the Triple Illusion is supposed
to be done by Sora, Anna, and myself.
We are not doing this for fun.
And I'm only inviting you to be a part
of it because I heard this was your idea.
If you don't like it,
I will ask you to step down as well.
Mia...
Anna, let's go.
But...
Never mind. Please excuse us.
I guess it's just the
difference in talent, you know?
It's like, sorry for being so talented.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you very much.
Sorry about that.
You're upset about what
Marion said, aren't you?
Oh, no. I'm okay about that.
But...
Well, it's kind of a long story, but...
So that's what happened.
And the three of you were
working so hard at it, too.
Oh, don't worry about it. It's my fault.
By the way, where's Marion?
Oh, she's probably hiding
somewhere here in the lesson hall.
She's always like that when she's sulking.
Oh well, she'll be back once she gets hungry.
Excuse me...
--What is it?
--About what Marion said earlier...
Oh...
Does it have something to
do with the way she behaves?
That is, if you don't mind,
would you tell me about it?
Have you already heard
that her mother passed away?
Six years ago,
my wife, Cynthia, was a
star at Kaleido Stage.
She was an earnest
woman who loved to practice.
There is no such thing as wasted practice.
We can be confident
because we practice every day.
Without that confidence, our
performance wouldn't make anyone happy.
But because she seldom took a break,
she might have made Marion lonely.
Then one day, Marion had a fever.
It was unusual for her, but Marion
asked Cynthia not to go on stage that day.
But since there was no one
who could substitute for Cynthia,
she went on stage.
However, on that particular day,
Cynthia made a big mistake.
--Mom, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
She was taken to the hospital right away,
but her condition wasn't good.
--It's because I was being so spoiled.
It's not your fault, Marion.
It was my mistake, so it's no one's fault.
Besides, Mom's going to recover
from these injuries really soon,
and I'll show you even
more amazing performances.
Those were Cynthia's last words.
She passed away without ever
setting foot on the stage again.
Ever since, in Marion's opinion,
no trampoliner better
than Cynthia has appeared.
She can't be satisfied
with anyone's performance,
and she's become sarcastic like that.
So that's what happened.
Marion must've really loved her mom.
And she must also love the Kaleido
Stage that her mom loved so much.
Thank you.
I'd like to thank you too.
I'm glad that I had a
chance to hear your story.
When you think about it, it's weird
for me to get depressed about it.
Mia's the one who gave me the
possibility of appearing on stage.
Yet, I made Mia feel bad.
If I'd been able to do everything properly,
Mia wouldn't have had to be so torn.
I'll practice much harder.
Good morning, Marion.
Dad...
She's been practicing
since before the crack of dawn.
Your mom used to do the same
before a new show opened, remember?
Yeah.
Mom!
Ouch!
Oh? Anna, good morning.
Don't "good morning" me.
You're still the same reckless risk-taker.
Sorry.
This is no time to be laughing.
I'll practice with you.
Mia...
Where are Charlotte and Julie?
You're not practicing with them?
I stepped down from the role.
What?
But you already told your grandma...
I thought about it, and I'd
rather perfect it with you two.
I'm sure my grandma would also
agree that's the better thing to do.
Mia...
I'm sorry.
I should have said so right away yesterday.
Are you really sure about giving up on this?
No, I haven't given up yet.
What?
I asked them, "Please give us a
chance to show you our Triple Illusion.
If it's still not good enough,
we'll resign from our roles."
I see.
Mia...
I believe they will become
first-rate Kaleido Stars.
Me too.
Then, let's practice right away.
Okay.
I'll try slowing down my spin a little,
so, Sora, can you try to speed up yours?
Okay, I'll do that.
Then I'll throw in my
orangutan pose in the middle.
Don't!
We have one day left. Let's work hard.
Yeah!
Just now, Mom...
No, it's nothing.
Dad, I'm hungry.
Okay, let's have breakfast.
The upright Star. Hope.
She changed the future.
Come on, you three, it's
almost time to start.
Okay!
What do you think?
You can hardly call this first-rate.
But it looked like you were
also on the edge of your seat.
Those girls certainly are
strangely captivating.
Kalos, you take the
responsibility to perfect it.
I guess this means that they passed.
The Triple Illusion.
When you sabishii toki doushitemasuka
Never say sonna no wakannai
Nemuru asobu magazine mekuru
Sabishii toki wa sabishii yo
Mienai denpa ga kyou mo
tulututu machi ni tobikau
Anyway kokoro no bekutoru
so many reason hanashiteru
Jiyuu ni sora o tobitai keredo
Hane o hirogeru basho ga nai
Demo shinjiteru
Katachi no nai mirai ga aru yo
Katachi ni shitai watashi ga iru
Kanashikutemo machigai demo
Omou mama fly to the free
"Next Kaleido Star"
Sora, let's go home together.
I'm not leaving for Japan until
you say that you're coming with me.
And so, on the opening day for Cinderella,
my dad suddenly came to America from Japan.
He says he's going to
take Sora back with him.
I understand how your dad feels,
but let's do our best together!
Everyone, I'm sorry.
What?!
My feelings for my family and my dream.
What should I do,
I wonder? I wonder? I wonder?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"My Amazingly Distant Family."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...