I've thought about this for a long time now.
I thought I had gotten past it all,
but I still wonder if I can honestly say I understand Nagase Iori.
Who is she really?
I know this probably isn't the best time.
But I have to tell you.
I mean, I want to tell you.
I really do like you.
I want us to be more than friends.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Something just doesn't feel right.
So let's just pretend that I never said I liked you.
Bye.
Wh-Why?
I'm...
I'm not the person you think I am.
I gotta go.
Yamaboshi Academy
It's February 14th.
Valentine's Day.
Love is in the air, even at Yamaboshi Academy,
but my rejection yesterday is still keeping me down.
Hey, Yaegashi.
What's wrong?
Did you catch a cold or something?
You won't get any chocolate
with a face like that.
This isn't the time for me
to be depressed, though,
since we're right in the middle
of Heartseed's latest antics.
Three days ago, Heartseed
appeared in front of us again.
Thought transmission.
Basically,
even if you don't say them out loud,
your thoughts might still be heard by a
.select few, no matter where they are.
So it's a type of telepathy?
Sort of, but it's not your
.garden variety telepathy.
It'll happen randomly, and whoever hears them will be different every time.
What does that mean?
What was that just now?
It's like Taichi's thoughts
.suddenly echoed in my head.
Was that what you were talking about?
Student Cultural Society
Yes.
The transmitters will know
who heard their thoughts,
but the receivers won't.
It's true. I could tell who
.my thoughts went out to.
Well, that's all for now.
If you have any questions,
I can answer them now.
Who was that "Number Two"
who appeared last time?
Student Cultural
Oh, that.
They've taken an interest in me.
Student Cultural  Society
I guess I've become interesting.
Have I said too much?
Well, now you know.
Bye.
We aren't beginners anymore.
If we go on with our lives like nothing's wrong, then they should leave us alone.
That's right.
They just want to be entertained by us.
If they don't think we're interesting
anymore, they won't bother us, right?
Yeah.
We'll make it through this.
Right, Nagase?
O-Oh yeah.
We can do it!
We're not gonna give them what they want, and we'll get them to stop bothering us.
I'm getting fired up now!
We've made it this far. This new
.phenomenon isn't gonna stop us.
Yeah.
You're the one I'm most
.worried about, though.
Come on, Inaba.
The Days Fall Apart
It's been three days since then.
We're in the middle of a thought transmission episode.
But I thought that shouldn't affect how we act.
That's why I asked Nagase to go out with me.
So let's just pretend that I never said I liked you.
Can you come with me for a moment?
Yaegashi, you have relationship problems, don't you?
Today's Valentine's Day.
It's supposed to be a day for love,
so I can't have you ruining the mood with that gloomy face of yours.
I know. I'm sorry.
Did Nagase reject you?
Did she really?
You two were getting along so well, too.
So she did.
I appreciate your sympathy, but you don't need to get depressed too.
The tables have turned! This is my chance!
Oh, sorry.
I couldn't control my happiness.
You still haven't given up on Nagase?
I might've been rejected by Nagase,
but that doesn't mean you've won.
Yeah, okay. Cry more, loser.
Damn you!
Seriously, though.
You two were practically an item
.already, yet you got rejected.
That's hilarious.
Have you always been like this?
It looks like you're feeling a bit better now.
It's tiring using facial muscles
.that I don't normally use.
Were you trying to cheer me up?
Is this what they call a "lucky break"?
How fortuitous.
So you really are happy about this.
Cheer up, Yaegashi.
This is a good chance.
Why don't you try going out with Inaba?
Wait!
How do you know about me and Inaba?!
It was obvious with the way she acts.
I notice things most people miss,
for I am...
the love god of Class 1-3.
You're a little too scary to be a love god.
I wonder when I should give him my chocolate.
Inaba...
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Well, after you figure things out,
.why not get together with Inaba?
And while you two are getting it on,
I'll take Nagase for myself.
That's what you're really after, huh?
Student Cultural Society
Taichi, you're finally here.
We've got a big problem.
What's wrong?
Did Heartseed do something again?
No.
Mr. Go might stop being our advisor.
I see.
Why?
Mr. Go is the advisor for our club and the jazz band at the moment, right?
But it seems next year is his turn to do some administrative tasks for the teachers.
He'll be really busy and only
.be able to supervise one club.
Normally, I'd just say to change
our advisor and call it good,
but we have Heartseed to consider.
It's good that we have a supervisor like Goto who rarely comes in and checks up on us.
It'd be a problem if we got a serious teacher who checked up on us all the time.
Well, the club that earns more points at the club presentations at the end of the year
gets to keep Goto.
Club presentations?
Oh, right.
That exists, huh?
Hey.
How about we go check out
what the jazz band is like?
Good idea, Iori!
I'd like to know what Mr. Go
does when he's there.
Yeah.
Gathering information is a basic part of war.
Now you understand why we
.don't want to let go of Mr. Goto.
Mr. Go's amazing.
He's actually good.
So you're part of the jazz band here, Shiroyama.
I'm still not at the level of the upperclassmen.
Shiroyama, you're being too modest.
You're the best out of all the freshmen.
That's not true.
Shiroyama's pretty popular.
I can see why he's called a "prince."
They said some pro bands scouted him too.
I guess you really can't judge a book by its cover.
Beating the jazz band's gonna be tough.
Hold on!
It's true that we've been forced into a battle we can't afford to lose,
but even so, today is February the 14th!
Isn't there something way more important we should be thinking about, gentlemen?!
Huh?
No one's with me?
We have this thought transmission thing going on.
You don't need to bring up a topic like that.
That's exactly why!
Rather than letting it slip at a weird time, I'll just blurt it out first.
It's better that way, isn't it?
I guess.
I can't stop thinking about
.who you'll be giving yours to,
ever since you asked me to
teach you how to make chocolate.
Really?
You have a guy you like?!
Well, about that...
As if I could come out and say
that I love Taichi right now!
What's wrong?
Did you guys just hear someone's thoughts?
Oh, uh...
I figured there was something between you two...
D-Don't worry about it.
I knew I'd have to tell you two eventually, but I could never find the right time.
That's right.
Iori and I are fighting over Taichi at the moment.
We're in such a weird situation. Funny, right?
Inaba and Iori are fighting over Taichi?
But you don't need to worry that
it'll get awkward and messy.
Right, Iori, Taichi?
Yeah, it's fine, even though that might sound weird coming from me...
considering how I got completely
rejected by Nagase yesterday.
Everyone heard that just now, right?
So he confessed to you...
...and you rejected him?
What the...
What the hell? What about my feelings?
No, I...
Sorry.
"Sorry"?!
Why, Iori?!
Why did you reject him?!
Calm down, Inaban.
It's true I rejected him,
but I have my reasons.
I was going to explain to you after, so...
It's none of your business.
Why are you getting pissed at me?
That was Iori just now, wasn't it?
Th-That's not it, Inaba!
I didn't mean to blame you.
That was just...
You're the one who started it, after all.
How selfish.
I didn't mean that just now. It was a joke.
Okay, I guess I can't say that.
She's completely different from what I thought.
Uh, wait. That was...
Iori's scary.
Was Iori always this kind of person?
Oh, uh...
I didn't mean that, Iori!
Wh-What?
Did a thought transmit over from Inaba to Iori?
And so Nagase Iori broke.
I'm back.
Welcome home, Taichi.
How was it?
Did you get any choco...
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you didn't get a single one!
I got a few from friends.
Oh. Isn't that good?
Oh, I know!
You didn't get one from the girl you like!
And maybe you saw her
giving one to some other guy.
Sorry.
Let's talk later.
Wait up!
Seriously, what's wrong?
Here, I'll give you my chocolate, so cheer up!
This is my true love chocolate!
Sorry.
Hey, what's wrong?
Hey!
Morning, Iori!
Oh, good morning, Nakayama.
Hey, did you give anyone chocolate yesterday?
Well, I did give some chocolates to the people that take care of me every day.
Not those, true love chocolates!
You're popular after all.
Don't you have someone you like?
The one I love is Mariko.
Only you!
Oh Iori, you're so sweet.
What is this? I don't even...
There's really nothing to it.
He asked me out, and I rejected him. That's all.
Did something happen for you
to fall out of love with Taichi?
Why are you even asking me that?
Because I'm not convinced.
Convinced about what?
I'm sorry, Inaban.
You wouldn't understand why,
but I really don't want to
.go out with Taichi anymore.
So you don't need to worry about me.
Does it have anything to do
with the thought transmission?
I can't say it doesn't have
.anything to do with it.
Then you should rethink all this!
You're letting our situation
.influence your decisions.
You should wait until
.things get back to normal.
And when'll that be?
Of course this'll eventually end.
But what're we gonna do
when something else happens?
That's...
People are influenced by
their surroundings, right?
What's the difference between
Heartseed and other external factors?
And the stuff between Taichi and me only started when we had our bodies swapped.
Doesn't mean our decisions
were already influenced?
And you wanted Taichi and me to go out.
What do you really want?
What should I do?
Nagase said that...
And then there's Inaba...
Did you hear that as well, Inaban?
Yeah.
Class is gonna start soon. Let's go.
What's wrong with me?
I'm sorry for being a day late.
I'm so happy I could die!
Inaba.
Sorry to call you out like this.
I wanted to apologize for yesterday.
You don't need to apologize.
That was all my fault.
I was just a bit surprised.
I thought that you would've said
.something to me before asking Iori out.
Well...
I was scared.
If I went to Inaba first and she stopped me,
I wouldn't've been able to go through with it.
You...
You actually have trouble
deciding between Iori and me?
N-No, you're wrong!
I am?
Okay, you're not wrong, but...
I loved Nagase,
but that doesn't mean I hate you.
I've always thought that you're the most amazing person I've met.
R-Really?
You're being really straightforward.
And you're really smart.
You always think about
.what's best for everyone else.
And you're actually really nice.
Mature and beautiful.
You can also be quite cute.
You can't play sports or cook, but
...everything else more than makes...
W-Wait! Give me a moment!
Okay. Continue.
Do I really have to?
Come on!
No! I didn't mean anything by that.
That came out wrong!
I just got tongue-tied!
Um...
Here. It's a day late, though.
Thank you.
You're still in love with Iori, right?
Yeah.
Do you feel obligated to go out with me because you got rejected by Iori?
No, I'd never do something horrible like that.
I can't say I feel as strongly about that as you do.
I don't know what I should do either.
My head's a mess.
But I do know that I love you.
Okay.
You can look forward to White Day.
Okay, I will.
Student Cultural Society
Hold on a moment!
Yui, you gave Taichi the same
chocolate you gave me?!
I had two of you, so I just had to!
Huh? You had "two"?
What do you mean by that?
I can't let this slide either.
Even though I absolutely, seriously, honestly couldn't care less about Aoki.
You really didn't need to emphasize it that much.
T-Taichi's helped me out a lot,
so I was just being nice!
There's no special meaning behind it!
Is that really it?
It's true!
I don't like Taichi in that way!
I only love him as a friend.
Love, you say?
I told you there's nothing else to it!
You must really love Taichi, Inaba.
You got a problem with that?
No! Not at all, Captain Inaba!
Anyway, it's good that Yui's
.getting over her androphobia.
She was able to give out
.chocolate to boys in her class.
Oh yeah.
We even heard her think that some of the guys in the dojo had good stances and were handsome.
What?! I have a problem with that!
You didn't have to say that!
Maybe I should start training at that dojo...
Okay, let's discuss what we can do for club presentations.
And what we should do to win against the jazz band.
Let's brainstorm some ideas for now.
I'll go!
We should have our female members cosplay
and melt the brains of the the male teachers and student council members that will be judging.
I'll consider doing that if you dance naked to get us sympathy votes.
How about we put together our most popular articles from past issues?
But we won't beat the jazz band with just that.
Yeah.
They'll be performing for the judges, so they'll leave a greater impression.
Why don't we make something elaborate especially for the presentation?
Then we can appeal to those teachers who are always like, "Effort is more important than results."
The teachers would be disappointed to find out your real intentions for making such a project.
There's some disparity between your
appearance and your heart of darkness.
I didn't really mean anything else by that.
Me next!
How about we make an article about
recommended places around the school?
We'll be able to show how much work we do by
doing lots of research and including it as an extra!
If we make it all super elaborate and handmade, maybe the judges will go easier on us.
And it'd be useful information for everyone.
That's a great idea.
Okay!
We'll split up and start researching tomorrow.
We'll look for interesting places around the neighborhood and compile them into an article for the presentation.
Does that sound good to you, Ms. President?
Yeah.
What's wrong, Iori?
You're not acting like yourself.
Do I have to act like myself?
I knew it. I can't handle this place.
They already have their own
ideas of who Nagase Iori is.
I-Iori?
Don't mind me.
I'm going home.
W-Wait, Iori!
C'mon, Iori.
Why are you suddenly trying to change into the cool, beautiful type?
Are you making a statement about how Inaba has totally changed as a person?
What happened, Aoki?
Did Iori's thoughts transmit to you?
I thought the best thing I could do was to be my usual self.
If I continued being my usual self, then Yui
and the others would be able to do the same.
But that didn't accomplish anything today.
Hello, Aoki.
Doesn't feel like I say the name Aoki much.
Why did you come to me?
Aoki, what do you think of this episode?
It's the worst.
Of course.
Then what do you think you can do?
Just be my usual self.
Isn't that the same as not doing anything?
That's not it.
Well, I suppose that's wrong.
It's not that you aren't doing anything.
You can't do anything.
You're the most useless.
I'll ask you again.
What can you do?
What will you do when you can't do anything?
I wonder how Aoki's doing.
Yui!
If Yui is thinking of me, then I can fight.
I'll fight as hard and as long as I need to!
I'll be my usual self.
For me, for Yui, and for everyone, of course.
I'll do everything I can for the club presentations.
You really are the most useless.
And boring.
Then just leave us alone already!
Um.
Well, that's all.
Shall we end our conversation, Aoki?
Okay, then.
Don't look down on us!
The SCS won't fall to something as petty as this.
Next Time
You Don't See Anything,
You Don't Understand Anything
Whoever confesses to me and whoever I reject are none of your business.
Do you really wish for that, Inaba?
This isn't Iori at all!
You're the worst!
Should we just dissolve the SCS?
You think I'm a liar, don't you?
I am lost and confused
and yet I know that someone is holding out their hand for me
Inside the little box I locked
was the taste of a path I thought I knew
One by one I soothe my wounds
and again jealousy, ardor, coldness, light,
rejection and hope,
all become one and I stand screaming helplessly
My feelings are like melting chocolate, black and sweet
My dreams have long since turned to ash
I am weak, and ringing fills my ears and I hear nothing else
Please find me
mi     chi     ra      n      do      m
The Girls' Squad dazzles with their cosplay
Good job, me!
Let's beat the jazz band!
The battle for Mr. Go
Frankensteiner!
The outcome will decide our club's future
No-rope barbed wire barricade mat double
hell megaton electric explosion death match!
Guys, this is serious!!
Just keep going!
Tune in next time!
Yaegashi Taichi
Preparation for the club presentations
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
How to get points from the judges
A bonus extra for the SCS paper
Wanna picnic?
Let's go to Disneyland again
The Physics quiz
didn't go so well
I'm the president
How about
curry doria?
I wanna go to
Disney Sea
Inabaaaan!
Cheep
A map that shows
recommended places
around school
Places people haven't heard about
Yui's favorite shops
Yui's favorite date spots
Yui's favorite sweets
Inaban's white rabbit
Universal Studios
sounds good too