When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
My name is Klaus Seishirou.
I'm a retired butler who now lives as a farmer in Brazil.
Hey! I haven't retired yet!
I will be a Sanzenin butler to the very end!
There's nothing left for you to do.
We even found a replacement for Himegami,
so you don't have anything to worry about, do you?
How dare an animal try to understand my feelings?!
Doesn't it bother you more that an animal is talking?
That impoverished butler looks like he can handle the selfish lady.
I can't leave it to a rookie like him.
I'm going back to Japan!
I don't think so.
You're going to spend what's left of your time here in Brazil with me.
What? That's...
No, that's...
Tama! Was that you?
We're starting off with a dream this week?
Now farewell, everyone.
No, a tiger can't possibly talk.
I must be tired.
What's this?
Looking to be a coffee plantation owner in Brazil?
When was this put here?
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
The kanji for my name is made of "Kura", as in warehouse, and "Usu", as in mortar.
I am pure-bred Japanese!
Perfect temperature.
Ironing the newspaper.
This is a butler's first chore in the morning.
As I thought, postponing the release of
Dragon ***** is causing the stock to drop.
I had a strange dream of being an owner of
a coffee bean plantation in Brazil and doing nothing.
Sure.
If you want to retire, go ahead.
What?!
Absolutely not!
I plan on burying my bones with the Sanzenin family!
That was only a dream I had!
According to Freud, a dream is a vision of your hidden desires.
So deep down, you feel tired and want to retire.
Th-That's not true!
Besides, what would happen to
the Sanzenin family if I disappeared?
Nothing at all.
Hayate and Maria take care of everyday things.
If it's about asset management, you don't have to worry.
You can't handle IT-related stocks, can you?
Anyway, we'll be fine.
I mustn't run away. I mustn't run away. I mustn't run away.
Um, Klaus-san?
An A* Field. It's a barrier made by the soul.
Maria-san!
I don't understand.
I wonder what happened to Klaus-san; he's so depressed.
Yes. Maybe he suffered a great shock?
I don't know. But I did say that he can retire.
You didn't have to take his dream seriously.
Usually, a butler who served for years would...
...receive a room in the mansion and live like a family member.
He must have been shocked to hear you say retire.
He wouldn't possibly quit because of that!
Milady. So you like Klaus-san deep down in your heart.
H-He's only a character who's easy to fool around with.
Then don't tell him to quit.
Right now, he might be getting consumed by the Dirac Sea.
I agree.
Then get a forced salvage operation going or something!
Okay.
What was that giggle about?
I'm coming in.
Chief butler.
Maria. I've resigned from my job.
I will now spend the rest of my life in Brazil.
What? It's obvious she wasn't serious when she said you can retire.
But! But!
If you have your mind made up, then there's nothing I can do.
Eh?
I'll let Milady know.
Wait! What Milady said has merit!
There must be a loose end in my heart for me to have a dream of retirement.
I will return to the days when I aimed to becoming a footman!
Footman?
Footmen are people who work under butlers.
So you know, there are no footmen in the Sanzenin.
As a footman, I challenge Ayasaki Hayate to see who can serve Milady better!
Wh-What a roundabout way of doing this.
Way to ruin it.
And I was almost able to go to Brazil.
A fight to see who can serve Milady better?
I don't recall asking for any of this.
It's what Klaus-san started.
Boy! You indeed learned a lot in a short period of time!
But, you have a fatal flaw!
What? Where?
Like how you look so cute when you cross-dress.
Don't worry.
Boy. Butlers are supposed to be their master's shadow.
Yet, you have an attitude like that of a main character.
In fact he is, so there's nothing he can do about that.
I think he's more of a reserved type of main character.
Is that a compliment?
Anyways, for the next 24 hours,
we will use all of our skills as butlers to serve Lady Nagi.
If she finds me inferior to you,
I will leave this mansion!
Okay. I will do my best as to not be rude to the chief butler.
And so the who-can-serve-Milady-better battle started.
Boy. Do you know what the most necessary attribute of a butler is?
Maybe like how they're hated in episode one, but they are loved by the final episode,
or swapping bodies with the master from a strange cause and solving mysteries?
No!
It's the inspiration to read ahead!
You need the strength to read ahead
and understand what the master wants.
A noble's morning starts with a morning tea.
Oh, that's already taken care of.
What?
It's ready, Milady.
Thank you, Hayate.
You fool!
In England, it's an important job where they even have a person in charge of making tea!
If you don't know the proper way of making it,
you can't call yourself a butler!
It is a teabag the English royal palace uses.
What?
That sounds nice.
Would you like to use lemon or milk?
Listen! Lemon tea does not exist in England!
The only thing that starts the morning is milk tea prepared by the butler with his fine-tuned pouring skill!
Then I'll go with lemon.
Huh?
The lemon tea you make is great, Hayate.
Thank you very much.
Th-This can't be...
Nagi, go easy on him a little.
No... No... You got it wrong...
So you will go to school today, Milady?
Yeah. Since I feel bad fooling around with Klaus too much.
Then why do you?
Klaus and I go back many years.
Because we know each other well,
it's fun to fool around with each other.
Right now, we get two extra drumsticks.
And it comes with nuggets, too.
A-Are they low on chicken stock?
Looks like he didn't come chasing us this far.
You're right.
You there!
Be quiet!
Milady!
Th-That's a perfectly polished piece of silverware.
And that's a sign of a professional butler!
SFX: DoGyaaaaan!!
Boy! I quit being human!
Klaus-san!
Y-You're a Sanzenin butler!
Uriiiiiiiiiiii!
The origin of the word "butler" comes from "bouteiller", the position of those who take care of wine cellars.
Wine... A vintage wine...
Violet Over Drive!
Bordeaux...
Burgundy!
These are no wines for a drunk to drink!
Zugyuuuuun!
Wait!
Both of them have left.
Yeah...
The best thing to do on a sunny day like this is to skip classes.
Thinking that everyone else is studying makes me relax even more.
And things would be perfect if we had a butler who would make tea for us.
Sunlight **** Over Drive!
SFX: Dobabababa
A dummy?
Butler ninja skill: Dummy no Jitsu.
She was an unexpected interference.
And now-
M-My back...
Hey! It's Nagi-chan's place's chief butler!
Tomarigi sagashitemasu.
Tomarigi sagashitemasu = I'm searching for a branch to land on.
Suppai Omoide daze.
Suppai Omoide daze = What a sour memory.
Wow!
It's premier cake and tea!
Thanks.
I wanted the people who saved my life to enjoy it.
Thank you.
Itadakimasu.
"Thank you", huh...
A butler is his master's shadow.
But inside, they are waiting for that one word of gratitude.
It's better than what we find at the store by the train station.
This tea is fabulous, too.
It's exquisite.
I found you!
Katsura-chan!
Yukiji!
There's a reason behind this.
Whatever, I don't care!
Give me some, too!
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me!
You have some vintage wine, don't you?
Yukiji looks dangerous.
Yeah...
Onee-chan!
Why are you being violent against the elderly?
"Elderly"?!
He came falling from the sky a while ago.
He's an old man to whom no one knows what may happen at any moment.
RIP.
You're right, but...
K-Klaus-san?
How far did he go?
Well, I'm sure Klaus has recovered from it by now.
Klaus-san!
Oh, if it isn't Klaus-san, a legendary figure in the butler world.
If I'm right, you must be the Oukouchi family's butler.
I'm Saeki Himuro.
And this is Sir Taiga.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
What?
Traditionally, it is the butler's pride
to be called under their master's name.
The Oukouchi's butler doesn't even know that?
Really, Himuro?
Sir, the flowers.
Yes!
It's the Heisei era, and you speak like Edward.
It's sad to see the famous butler aging.
It's sad for you to cling to your former status.
Y-You're amazing, Himuro!
With your reflexes, you can't protect your master in an emergency.
How about you retire and think of a new life for yourself?
You're still young, Oukouchi butler.
What?
I am my master's shadow.
A shadow does not have a private life to begin with.
When you realize you can't be of aid to
your master anymore, you just disappear.
You don't think...
...he decided to retire because of that, do you?
What?
Is he serious?
Isn't there any way to have Klaus-san stay?
There is a hidden trick.
Really?
Yes, but you'll have go through a little change.
Surely you mean lend a little hand.
I-I've got a bad feeling...
Everything is all a memory now.
My life was spent with these Sanzenin
and my bones were supposed to be buried here.
But what the Oukouchi's young butler says has merit.
It's about time I step down.
Klaus-san.
Y-You're from sometime ago...
You're the pillar of my heart I saw in the garden sometime ago!
I'm such a genius.
Hayate-kun's feminine sex appeal really works.
I'm sure Klaus-san will feel better after this.
W-What is your name?
Ayasaki-
Ayasaki?
I'm Hermione.
Oh, Hermione!
What a fantastic name! Sounds like you can use magic.
Yes... In fact, I'm a goddess that resides in Lake Sanzenin.
Oh, I knew you weren't an ordinary woman.
Klaus-san. I've always been watching you from the bottom of the lake.
R-Really?
You must not quit the chief butler position.
You're not that old yet.
What's the matter?
I've become so old my hair is all white.
That's not true.
It's a nice romantic grey.
Y-You think so, too?
People often say that to me
at Ikebukuro's adult social gatherings.
Then you won't think about retiring, will you?
But lately, my shoulders have been getting stiff, and I can't keep them up.
I-I'm sure it can be massaged off.
See?
Look how hard it is.
Can you do my back and waist, too?
Sure.
Yes, right there. That's where I like it.
Be convinced already, you egghead geezer.
Who is Klaus talking to?
More to this side.
No, I can't touch there.
I-Itadakimasu!
Hermione-san... I-I've...
Honey!
I've aged enough to hallucinate, huh?
It had the reverse effect...
This stupid tiger.
What is this?
Forgive me!
Tama... Don't tell me you were after this female tiger...
I fell in love with her.
But as a tiger, I can't go to Brazil alone.
That's why you tried to use Klaus-san?
You will want to go to a plantation in Brazil.
You want to go... You want to go...
That's all I said!
Let me tell you one thing.
Tiger's don't exist in Brazil!
Oh yeah. I'll tell him the dream of Brazil he had isn't because of his underlying mental state, but Tama's planning.
No, I can't. Nobody knows that Tama can talk.
Klaus! What's the language of flowers for this?
It's loyalty to my Milady.
Really?
Yes. I just decided.
I'll give this to you!
Lady Nagi...
Klaus-san.
It's okay, boy.
There isn't anything that you can't do that I can.
Hey, Hayate!
Lady Nagi.
Today's Butler Economics and Industry Newspaper is drenched in morning dew!
I can't read the stock market section well!
Chief butler. I've yet to learn how to iron the newspaper.
Boy!
If you can't even iron a newspaper, then Klaus wins the match.
Milady!
Get moving, Klaus!
You leave me no choice.
Perfect temperature.
Looks like Klaus-san has recovered.
Yes.
Thanks to you, Milady.
He is part of the Sanzenin family.
I don't want to be the one who kicked him out.
How about I make some lemon tea?
That sounds good.
Next week, instead of fighting,
we'll try to coexist with small animals.
Wataru and,
Saki's,
Butler Network!
A bright smile and ample stock.
I'm the manager of Rental Video Tachibana, Tachibana Wataru.
And I take care of him.
His maid, Kijima Saki.
Now that we have the store's image song,
how about we make some merchandising goods next?
But what would appeal to the public?
How about giving out the happy-embarrassing photo of Video Tachibana's cult maid, Saki,
since we've seen people coming to see you recently?
Stop joking, Sir!
TA-CHI-BANA.
Hayate. What type of girls do you like?
Well, let's see...
I guess normal girls.
Normal?
I don't think someone like you would understand.
Don't make fun of me! Are you saying that I can't be your ideal kind of girl?
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
I Want to Return to Being a Normal Girl. But Do Buy my Character Song.
I see. So Hayate-kun likes normal girls.
Did you know, in Okinawa, the statues of lions you see at lion mansions are of Shisa.