I will wipe you out.
Yes.
Ah.
I'm here.
Hey, wait! You're showing the door to your best friend who came to visit you so late at night?
I don't have a best friend. Go home!
What?
Open up! This is the FBI! You have the right to remain silent.
Ah, stop it. I got it. I got it. So give me five minutes. I'm going to clean up my room!
Are you trying to hide your ecchi books?
It's not like that. Anyway, wait outside...
You're a manga artist?
Yeah. I'm already an active professional.
I see.
I thought it was strange for you to skip school all the time, even though you're a diligent person.
Don't tell anyone.
Okay. However, there's a condition.
Condition?
I don't have the right to tell him my feelings.
Ah, is this Kei? I need to talk to you about something.
It hurts.
Is it that amusing to make fun of people?
It's all thanks to you saying something weird.
When I scout for an actress, I have a higher chance to succeed by doing that.
What about an actress?
When will this become interesting?
It will be like this throughout the whole thing.
How long do I need to watch this?
About two more hours.
Don't show me boring stuff. Because I don't have time.
Which parts were boring?
Which parts...? The actors were bad, the story was cliche.
I thought it was interesting at the beginning, but it became boring as it went along.
Why did you think it was interesting at the beginning then?
Hm, that's because... it looked beautiful.
The acting was bad, but they, somehow, appeared lively.
Eh, you have an eye for it.
The director and scenarist were my senpai in the film research club, but I was the cameraman.
It's a nice film, isn't it?
And it seems Kyosuke wants to make a new film.
With you as the leading actress.
Eh?
Kei-chan, can you participate in my film?
You're the only character.
You just need to come along with me whenever you're available.
I will then follow you around with my camera.
But I'm an amateur when it comes to acting.
It's okay. There's no script.
I will just record the way you're living and your feelings just as they are.
My... feelings?
Is it something like a documentary?
Nah, it's neither a documentary nor a drama.
I'm not going to assume anything beforehand.
I will polish the film from the material I get.
Hm...
What?
Can you do it without a vision to start with?
I don't want to be bound by the vision I created at the beginning.
With only an ideal that's hit-or-miss, you won't be able to produce something good.
Even if I produce something good, it will be meaningless if it's not a film I want to make.
Let me give you a word of advice from a professional's point of view.
It's not that easy to make something.
Do you think it's easy to just make it at will?
It's even more difficult than those professions with fixed boundaries.
Professionals have to struggle with those boundaries.
It's a different meaning from freedom gained without fighting.
The area I want to fight in is different from yours!
I want to make my film without being bound by the evaluation of the audience and judges!
Do you only consider the readers when you draw?
I'm also trying to draw something that I want to draw!
It won't work if I only consider the readers, will it?
Do you shoot your films without considering the audience?
Whether it's just one scene or one cut, I want to make a film that shakes the souls of those who see it.
For that sake, it won't work if that moment doesn't shake my own soul.
If you say so, try and do it.
Yeah, I will do it.
Hey, don't decide on your own.
I didn't say that I would participate in the film.
Heh?
Well, take your time and think about it.
It's pointless to wait for me, so please give up.
Well then, I will look forward to your favorable reply.
Listen to what others say!
I wonder what he's planning to do with the movie he's making of me.
If you plan to appear in his film, be careful.
That guy is a womanizer.
Hm, you're worrying about me, eh?
Ba~ka.
Onii-chan.
Does Miyamura-senpai always come to your room?
She's only been there two to three times.
Really?
Hey, Onii-chan.
Do you, perhaps, think I'm... annoying?
Huh?
I come to wake you up in the morning, and I nag you to go to school.
Onii-chan, don't you think I'm annoying?
What are you saying all of a sudden? That's not true.
Whenever I talk to you about something serious, you're unwilling to listen.
You weren't like that before.
It's different from before. I'm not a kid anymore.
Onii-chan, you matured too soon.
It's Chihiro.
She's talking about Renji-kun again.
Chihiro was able to make a friend?
Yeah. Lately, she looks happy.
Could it be... her boyfriend?
Hm, I wouldn't say so, but it looks like it will be soon, from the way it's going.
I see. That's good.
Yeah.
Hey, Onii-chan.
Our basketball club has a match on Sunday, will you come and watch?
Match?
That match, I'll win for sure.
If I win, I will have something important to tell you.
Something important? What is it?
Right now, it's a secret. I will tell you by then.
Hey!
I'll win for sure!
A
The furigana next to it says "Dentatsu," which means "Communication."
Have you read Chihiro's novel?
Yeah, it was quite amazing. How come Chihiro could write something like that?
For Chihiro, writing down her words is the same as surviving.
Surviving?
She's conveying her image to another person.
Herself in the past and the one reading it are two different beings.
Chihiro uses her diary to connect her gradually disappearing self to the future.
How accurately can she convey her own image to a different being?
What she's doing is the same as a writer.
Chihiro's writing skill is the same as a novelist's.
That skill won't improve without a good memory, will it?
It might be her natural talent.
Even if you lose your memory, there might be something that permeates through your body.
It could also be because she desperately wants to convey it, that's why such an ability resulted.
Well, since you have already come this far, just pray that she will finish writing it.
Himura-san, who on earth are you?
What do you mean?
Like what you do for a living.
How come you're always at this church?
I have been... waiting for someone.
Waiting for someone?
I'm not a pastor nor a counselor.
But, to guide, I dare to give you advice.
Don't get too involved with Chihiro.
"The girl began to paint."
"Books, musical instruments, pictures."
"Among those things, it was the tool that's most likely to create a human."
"But it didn't go well."
"She got tired of it many times."
"It didn't matter anyway, even if she got tired of it."
"When the season changed, she had enough."
"She finished the painting before long."
"She found out that she was more suited for drawing realistic scenes."
"As long as she was able to draw something that looked like it, it was fine."
"Something that didn't exist there."
"Drawing humans might be something hard to do."
"That's what she thought."
Let's take a break.
Okay.
Is there some place you're stuck?
Yes. About the castle that the girl lives in...
I can't come up with an image of the warehouses.
Warehouse, eh?
The warehouse for food.
The warehouse that stores the stuff she needs for living.
And the warehouse of books where she reads to gain knowledge.
There are others as well, including the landscape of the island and the shapes of wild plants, since I have no idea.
That means we need more data, eh?
Only if there was a library.
Yeah.
The only library in Otowa is the one at school.
Let's go and take a look.
Where are we going?
To school.
And? What business do you have with me?
I'm sorry for saying something boring to you the other day.
Something boring? What was it?
I have been hanging out with Hirono-senpai since we were children.
Yeah, I know.
When he was small, Hirono-senpai didn't have any friends.
I couldn't stand watching Hirono-senpai, who was always alone.
Because of that, I brought him to my home.
You brought a boy back home all of a sudden?
Kei-chan is pretty bold.
Is that your way of changing the subject?
Serious subjects are hard to follow.
I had a lot of shoujo manga in my room.
That was the first form of entertainment that Hirono-senpai ever touched.
Senpai was really absorbed by it.
But I never thought that he would become a professional.
Hirono-senpai's talent is amazing.
I think...
Just watching someone doing his best and thinking he's amazing is not good enough.
Someone who's doing his best wouldn't accept someone who's doing nothing after all.
At least, I don't think he would like her.
I guess that's the reason you started playing basketball?
You told me that I was showing my honesty in the wrong place, right?
To Onii-chan, I...
It's been like that since a long time ago, and it will be like that forever from now.
My feelings will go on forever.
Because my feelings, even up till now, have never stopped once.
Even if you're telling me this...
Just like that, you should just keep playing dumb.
I will never lose to you.
I will wipe you out from Onii-chan's heart.
I am...
going to disappear
from Hirono-kun's heart...
Together, Onii-chan and I will start from there.
He will then say farewell to you.
And then, it will be over.
I will end this.
I'm going to disappear... I'm going to disappear again...
A
The furigana next to it says "Yasuragi," which means "Peace."
Say, Mom. Is there anyone who has a spare uniform?
Like someone who didn't get to graduate.
My, is it torn somewhere?
I'm not talking about mine. I'm wondering if there's any spare girls' uniform.
I want you to ask around in cooking class, could you?
Ah. It's for Chihiro-chan, right?
If it's used clothes, I can borrow from everyone, so it's fine.
Really?
Now thinking about it, Kuze-san also has a uniform.
I'm talking about a girl's uniform though.
That's right. A girl's.
Why does Kuze-san...
Ah, I do have one.
Where did I put it?
Erm, it's okay if you don't want to answer, but why do you have something like that?
Oh my, you're a boy too.
In other words, it's a souvenir, plus now when it feels like the relationship is lacking freshness,
I'll let her wear it, then strip half of it away.
Even though it sounds like a roundabout way, it's too easy to understand. Forget it.
What are you two talking about?
Ah.
Ah?
You're going to let Chihiro-chan wear it, eh?
Please don't imagine something weird.
Erm, what are you two talking about?
I wonder if this size fits you. Want to give it a try?
Size... are you collecting them?
A little.
You're hopeless.
Now thinking about it, why does my mom know that you have girls' uniforms?
Ah. Because I think she's cute, so by all means, I wanted her to wear them.
What on earth are you asking someone's wife to do?!
Erm, do you have a moment?
Ah, the size didn't fit you?
The size fits me, but I think the type is not right...
Kuze-san, this...
When one talks about uniforms, this is what it means after all.
You're really hopeless.
Erm, I'm done changing.
This is Otowa's school uniform, right?
Yeah.
It's the same as Onee-chan's, right?
Yeah, that's right.
How is it?
It suits you really well, Chihiro.
Okay.
Let's wear that and go to school tomorrow.
What's wrong?
Erm... can't we go now?
Yeah.
Chihiro...
Jan.
Today I used a lot of effort and made unagi no hitsumabushi.
Eels killing time?
A
The day of the ox is a calendar system that counts the days according to the twelve zodiacal signs. For 2007, that day was the 30th of July. It's a tradition in Japan to eat eels on that day.
That's right. After the day of the ox during midsummer, the eel has a lot of free time...
Who said it's eels killing time?!
Miyako said "Unagi no Hitsumabushi" (鰻の櫃まぶし),
while Hiro heard it as "Unagi no Himatsubushi" (鰻の暇つぶし).
It's unagi no hi-tsu-ma-bu-shi.
Say, Hirono-kun. Do you have work to do this weekend?
Ah?
Sunday, let's go somewhere to play.
Between deadlines, I make sure to sleep as much as I can on holidays.
I don't have the time to play.
You liar.
I know. The basketball club has a match, right?
Oh. I didn't lie. I just forgot about it.
Are you going after all, then?
I didn't really promise to go.
Really?
Yeah.
In that case, make a promise with me.
Go out on a date with me on Sunday.
Eh? Nah, I just said on holidays...
You can't?
Nah...
Let's go. Together.
Kei-chan!
Don't be so depressed. There will be another match, right?
It's not that.
It's not about that.
I told you I would use my right hand if you shot without my permission again, didn't I?
Yeah. You can hit me as much as you like.
This is a moment that I can't find otherwise.
If I let it go now, I won't be able to get it back again.
"I won't be able to get it back again..."
I want to catch irreplaceable moments like that.
For the sake of that, I will do it no matter what.
Even if you do it, everything will be over if you fail.
It won't be over.
As long as I don't give up, it won't be over.
I will keep challenging it.
How's Kei?
Onii-chan, why?
Well, I contacted him.
Are you all right?
It's dizziness caused by light anemia and dehydration.
And it seems she hit and injured her knee when she fell.
Onii-chan...
You idiot.
Geez, I said I'm fine.
This is embarrassing. Let me down.
Shut up. Be a good girl.
Geez, you're always doing stupid things.
What? You've been calling me an idiot since earlier.
You're an idiot for pushing yourself until you collapsed.
I just tripped a little.
It's okay, be quiet. Don't force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself.
You're always overdoing it.
Aren't you the same?
It's fine for me.
What's that?
Onii-chan, you're wearing your good clothes.
Eh?
You were on a date with Miyamura-senpai, eh?
Ah, I stood her up.
Is that okay?
Stupid, I can't just leave you alone, can I?
I have to apologize to her.
Ah, this is bad, I dropped my cell phone.
What?
Nothing.
By the way, didn't you say you had something to tell me after the match was over?
It doesn't matter anymore.
A
The furigana next to it says "Sukui," which means "Relief."
School...
Eh?
My heart is pounding.
It's okay. If you walk as usual, nobody will notice.
How do I walk usually?
I can smell the books.
Thank you.
Thank you, Renji-kun.
What I want to reach you are not words, but myself.
Next episode, ef - a tale of memories: I...
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?