Elen.
What is it?
Nothing,
I just wanted to see the face you'd make if you were called that way.
You've... found him?
Where is he?
Where's Scythe?
Yes, I appreciate the car you sent to pick me up,
Colonel Roshunenko.
Oh, it's an honor for me that you remember my name,
Doctor Giuseppe.
Being addressed by that name makes me recall the times in Moscow.
But to see such an able person as you cornered and fleeing...
Fieldwork differs quite a lot from working in a laboratory, no?
"There's a tide in the affairs of men."
What?
It's from Shakespeare.
Their tide is mine as well.
The things I must create here...
...have been created.
There is some unusual activity around a weapons dealer, Roshunenko.
He seems to be Scythe's old acquaintance,
but these days he runs a territory here at San Francisco's gulf region.
Scythe has been spotted heading this way.
So basically that snake bastard is trying to make his escape from somewhere around San Francisco.
Clau?
You...
Do you understand what you're doing, Clau?
He helped Phantom, who pointed her gun at us, escape!
And yet you're telling me to bring him along?
Yes, indeed.
Jeez!
You're such an elusive woman!
That goes for both of us.
I will be the one giving orders at the scene.
The place Scythe is heading to...
...is Woodland pier on East Bay.
It seems some of Roshunenko's men are posted there.
Fine.
Come!
Make sure you kill him.
If you do that...
A pity we could not get Zwei,
but considering the situation, we can do nothing about it.
That fox can have Zwei.
Master...
...why did you...
Since when did you start asking questions?
I'm... sorry.
Is there something wrong, comrade Roshunenko?
Is that so?
We've been found?
Indeed, you need not worry.
My personal staff will entertain the people that wish to see us off.
You are sending us backup?
I thank you for that.
I will see you then.
By sending a few extra men, he wants me to owe him a favor, huh?
Ein.
Will you still be able to live up to my expectations?
Ein...
Use this.
It's an appropriate adornment for tonight's little stage show.
There are two spare magazines.
As you know, it's a gun with a quite powerful recoil.
Try to avoid rapid shots if possible.
Understood.
Finish it with diligence.
This will be your last mission.
I will.
Miss Garland will arrive at the pier at any moment now.
I'm certain she will carry out the job.
I heard you let Zwei tag along too?
Quite so.
He is a man who betrayed Inferno once.
If this proves to be of harm to the organization,
I will accept any punishment.
Do you put that much trust in Zwei?
If there is something I put trust into,
that would be...
...that someone who killed only because he was ordered to...
...wants to kill a person of his own free will for the first time.
It's something he longs for.
To be honest, I still have my doubts...
...whether I should set you free with a gun in your hand.
True...
One round ready to be fired,
fifteen rounds in the magazine.
If I killed everyone here, I'd still have bullets left.
What did you say?
What're you trying to do?
I won't be able to fight you off with just one round.
But this will be just enough to kill Scythe himself.
That's a pretty big speech for a little boy.
It's better than being shot in the back by you.
Up there!
That snake bastard!
Hey, wait!
Scythe!
Where are you?!
I won't let this slide, you traitor!
I don't give a shit about number one or two or whatever,
You treated us like pawns...
My brother died because of you!
Even if the big shots forgave you...
I will never...
...forgive you!
Elen...
Let's go home.
It's not too late.
Please...
Together...
Scythe!
Ein.
I see.
Well done, Zwei.
I always felt you had the potential to surpass Ein someday,
so I'm not surprised that fox wants you.
Not only did you perfect your skills so quickly,
but above all, you used Ein as your stepping stone.
A stepping stone?
You, of all people, should understand that.
Stop!
Please.
Don't do it.
You don't need to worry.
If I kill him, Inferno will let you off the hook.
So come with me...
Elen.
Ein.
Kill Zwei.
Doing that is the proof you are my Ein.
Let's go, Ein!
You idiot!
This is how you end up after bragging so much?
How did you fare?
We managed to clean out most of them.
There are a lot of casualties, but I'm just peachy as you can see.
Get up!
You're gonna kill Scythe, right?
I've received information that there is a boat docked for us on the fifth pier.
At the southeastern edge.
Understood.
Scythe!
Come on, you snake bastard!
Shoot me!
Pin her down.
I will go ahead.
Understood.
He's one of Roshunenko's...
Master!
Scythe!
Rei...ji...
Such an interesting outcome.
What a perfect finale.
Elen.
What?
Nothing,
I just wanted to see the face you'd make if you were called that way.
Am I expected to smile at a time like this?
I'm sorry.
I will make you smile someday.
It will come back to you.
You will smile when you are happy,
and cry when you are sad.
You will be a normal girl.
Normal?
So please keep on living until that time comes, Elen.
I will protect you.
Elen...
The promise...
...with you...
Your... smile...
I've lost everything.
All I have left...
...is the title of a killer.
Phantom.