After careful consideration of the times, we feel that intense scenes in this show are important to the story.
-Rainbow Production Staff
The rain that fell on the night of January 28th was skin-piercingly cold.
It's Ishihara, Bro! He's making his move!
Are you listening, Bro?!
I think he's after that suicide note!
He probably already knows about our hideout, too!
Hurry! You gotta tell Setsuko!
Bro!
I'm not worried about Setsuko.
Huh?!
It looks like Ishihara is after me...
Listen. You're safe as long as you're there.
Leave the rest to me!
Bro! Bro!
Interpreter. Can you give this military officer my thanks?
Huh?
Okay...
And I'd like you to tell Mario something too.
I'm sorry I couldn't see his fight...
Behave like a real man on the outside too.
I will.
Soldier!
Soldier! Congratulations!
Don't you dare come back!
Wait for us, okay?! Underneath that tree!
Introduce me to some girls when I get out!
All right, you guys! Get back to your cell!
Don't make us throw you in the hole!
Those your friends?
Yes.
They're the dear friends I met here.
"If he could've just left me alone, neither of us would have to get hurt.
Is this fate?
My friends will never have happiness until I take down this twisted man..."
Rokurota Sakuragi prepared himself.
You look well, Sakuragi.
Yeah. How about you?
Nothing much to say. My life's screwed up now because of you.
So?
You're an eyesore.
You're nothing but a filthy stray dog.
You're a piece of law-breaking shit.
So doesn't it seem strange to you, Sakuragi?
Why are you allowed to be happy?!
I can't understand it!
First you break out, then you live happy-go-lucky on the outside!
Why?! Why do I have to live with all this stress and fear?!
I've had enough! No more!
It ends here, Sakuragi!
What're you doing out there, kid?!
You can't beat the American with right haymakers only!
Listen. Don't try for a one-hit K.O. Use your left and—
This is how I want it, Mister.
This is how I want it.
Corner men, out!
Lilly.
I'll show you in the next round...
I'll show you America being defeated!
Did you think you could kill me by using speed and getting a gun?!
I will kill you! And then I'll kill that girl next!
That nurse is wasted on you! I'm gonna rape her over and over!
And then I'm going after those brats! I'm gonna kill every last one!
I'm gonna kill 'em nice and slow!
Doesn't that sound like fun, Sakuragi?!
What was that you said, Ishihara?!
You're going to do what to my friends?!
He doesn't stand a chance...
Not yet.
It's still alive...
The look in his eyes...
You're bluffing...
Aren't you?! You don't have the balls!
You don't have the balls to kill—
S-Stop! Don't kill me...!
You're out of bullets.
Now you can't kill me, Ishihara.
Screw you! I refuse to let it end like this! There's no going back now!
Either you're gonna die or I'm gonna die!
Is this what you wanted?
Let's end this...
Mario! Assume you'll only have one chance!
The moment your opponent lets his guard down
and throws a straight right...
That moment...!
Watch closely, Lilly!
Watch America get beaten down!
Mario attempted to snare the G.I. in the trap he set inside the ring.
Meanwhile, Sakuragi was about to ring the final bell
of his long death match against Ishihara.
Both of them bet everything on this moment.
I'm sorry Hagino. Please understand.
The regret and despair you had
after Ishihara and Sasaki drove you to choose death...
Your suicide note was filled with those feelings,
and now I'm about to give it to Ishihara...
I'm sorry... I really am sorry, Hagino...!
Hold on Sakuragi. Why did you give it to me?
I want to end this. That's all.
If it weren't for that, Ishihara, none of this would've happened to you.
B-Bullshit!
You can't trick me!
Ishihara!
I'm not asking you a favor.
I'm telling you not to mess with my friends any more!
The two of us have nothing to do with each other anymore.
You can do whatever you want with that letter now.
But, if you still have any conscience at all,
you can at least leave some flowers at his grave.
"The happiness of Setsuko and the other six rests on your dying letter...
Please, understand. Forgive me..."
Sakuragi apologized to the late Hagino.
Two!
Three!
What an amazing kid! He really did beat the American!
No, look!
What?! How is he getting back up?!
I'm fighting a G.I.
Definitely not the kind of guy who'd go down in one hit...
Hey, kid! Give 'im all you got!
Even your right punches'll hit him now!
Will it really be that easy?
With my busted right hand?
"Please don't get up. Please stay down."
Unfortunately, the G.I. took a fighting stand at the count of eight
after crawling around the canvas like an octopus.
"My opponent's a man, too! He's a boxer!"
The men's fight began once more.
What am I doing?
Hey, Sakuragi...
Tell me...
Sakuragi... How can a pathetic stray dog like you live like that?!
How?!
Sakuragi!
Please... Wait, Sakuragi...
Hear me out...
Americans... are tough...
I hit him with my left... just like Bro taught me...
But that G.I.... he just got right back up...
It's crazy...
That's enough, kid! You've fought enough!
No one'll hold it against you if you give up now!
I'd love to...
Then I'll tell the ref...
But...
What would Bro do?
What would you do?
Yeah... You'd keep fighting, wouldn't you?
Kid...
Corner men, out!
Bro... I won't give up yet!
I have nothing more to say to you.
Never come looking for us again.
Don't ever show your face around us again!
It was just a little side money!
Sasaki kept insisting on it, so I couldn't say no!
I never thought he'd kill himself...!
I was afraid... I was always afraid...
I'm through with being a guard!
What do I do? What do I do now?!
Tell me, Sakuragi! Tell me!
Tell, me Saukuragi!
You know, don't you?!
Right, Sakuragi?!
Sakuragi!
The blade thrust into his body was cold at first,
but eventually grew burning hot.
That hurt, Sakuragi?
Does it hurt?
You drug addict... You're a real dumbass...
You can't kill me with this thing, Ishihara!
Now move, Ishihara... I need to go.
Move...
H-He just won't die...
No matter what I do, he just won't die...
I can't seem to kill him, no matter how hard I try...
Mario...
What are you doing, kid?! Mix in some right punches!
He can't.
He's been fighting with a busted right hand from the very start...
That's enough, kid! Just go down already!
I promised...
Make sure you win, Mario.
I promised Bro...
Bro told me...
...to win!
Mario...
This is the police! Give yourself up!
Drop your knife!
Is that him?
Yes, there's no question about it.
He's Rokurota Sakuragi!
As his blood flowed out, so did his strength.
With weak, staggering steps, Sakuragi headed for the boxing arena.
"I want to see it... The moment Mario becomes a man..."
That was the only thought in Sakuragi's mind.
sameta manazashi
This sharp gaze
nani o mitsuzukeru no ka
What is it focused on?
mamoru beki mono?
Something that
needs protecting?
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
Not even this body
matters to me
Even if I rot away
Just keep on running
So far away
But I never give it up
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
will now start to
intertwine with fate
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuite yuku
and continue into the
endless future
And I will get over it, it's now
A far-off distance
The rain pours down. Gunshots go off.
As Sakuragi collapses, he sees the faces of his friends in his mind.
And then...