Mika was alive.
We were fighting the vampires in Shinjuku alongside the Moon Demon Company.
There I was reunited with Mika, who was still alive, but had turned into a vampire.
I couldn't bring him back,
but he's alive.
For now, that's enough.
Mika,
I will save you.
Run!
It's a vampire manhunt!
No! Let me go!
Fear not, I won't kill you.
But at least let me get a taste of you.
N-No!
Stop!
You're not taking them on my watch, vampires!
How dare you, human scum!
Go, Gekkouin!
Curse you!
It's about time you took us seriously!
We'll save your family, too.
Quit trying to act cool and focus on the battle, stupid Yuu!
Don't get cocky, humans!
Just so you know, you owe me one.
Thanks, Shinoa, Mitsuba.
"Thank you," my ass, stupid Yuu!
Don't break formation!
Really?
But come on Mitsuba,
they were attacking that family.
What if I hadn't gotten there in time?
We're saving them fast and reliably.
Yuu-kun, Kimizuki-kun!
Are you okay?
Yep, we're fine.
I'm not done!
Well now,
I see you guys are taking it as easy as ever.
Guren?
I-I'm really sorry, Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
Though truth be told,
you did a good job protecting that family.
"Good job"?
In case you didn't notice,
I just took your job.
Well, I'm just happy to have my work finished for me so quickly.
So happy, in fact, that I already have another mission for my terrific subordinates.
Can you do it?
Yeah, leave it to us.
Shahar the Vampire
Then without further ado,
I'll now go over the mission details.
And to think we just fought the vampires in Shinjuku the other day...
The Lieutenant Colonel is quite a slave driver, wouldn't you say?
Whatever.
Just get to the briefing.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, it's actually a pretty simple mission.
We're to dispatch the vampire in hiding,
and rescue the girl they've captured, Riko-chan.
They took a child?
There's nothing strange about that.
Child or not,
humans are humans, and kidnapping them is perfectly normal for vampires.
Still, there is one thing that I'm curious about.
Riko-chan's mother told us this,
but initially it was a vampire manhunting squad that attacked them.
Then, strangely, another vampire appeared,
wiped out the entire squad and took Riko-chan for himself.
A vampire attacked its own?
That is a bit weird.
I wonder if there's some reason behind it.
Who cares about the reason?
Tearing a family apart is unforgivable.
Yuu-san...
Lana,
have you been a good girl?
How many times do I have to tell you,
my name is Riko!
Not Lana!
Come now, Lana, what are you talking about?
Oh, I know.
You want a hairpin to match your clothes, don't you?
Just wait, I'll get you one.
I don't need that! Just let me leave!
What are you saying, Lana?
This is where you and I live.
Lana?
What's wrong?
No! Stay away!
Just like I thought. It looks great on you.
Lana, my lovely little sister.
So she's your new doll?
Ferid Bathory? Crowley Eusford?
Ah, no respect for nobles?
You must not be interested in living very long, Shahar-kun.
Who are you?
Why are you here!?
It's not like I wanted to come, you know.
Ferid-kun insisted.
As it happens, I've been hearing some interesting rumors.
Supposedly, someone in the area has been stealing livestock.
Is this blood so tasty that you would lower yourself to thievery for it?
D-Don't you dare touch Lana!
No!
Just let me have a little taste.
Oh, you took her back.
Did you remember something from your past, perhaps?
No...
I didn't...
I...
I swear Ferid-kun, you always were a bully.
If I remember, weren't you the one who turned him?
Hm?
Couldn't say, I don't bother remembering stuff from so long ago.
Well, not like it matters.
Was that all we came for?
Nah, of course not.
The important matter I had to
attend to is something else entirely.
Important matter?
Not telling you.
Anyway, let's be on our way.
Let me warn you though,
if you don't get along with the rest you'll be in for some pain.
Well, have fun playing house with your new doll.
What that vampire said...
Is it true?
You used to be human?
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry, Lana...
That's the vampire's hiding place?
I think so,
but we won't know for sure until we look inside.
To rescue Riko-chan, we'll have to deal with the vampire first.
As such, we'll act at noon.
Lana...
I won't let the bad guys have you...
I won't let anyone have you...
Please forgive me.
I...
Your blood,
Lana...
What that vampire said was true, wasn't it?
Lana... Lana...
We'll always be together.
Based on the report,
it sounds like it's just one vampire,
but we don't know that for sure.
It's possible there could be more, so be careful.
Now then, let's begin.
Pretty big place.
It'd be preferable to split up and search the place,
but we're not sure how many vampires there are.
It'll take more time, but let's stick together.
Who are you?
Look, that girl...
Yes, she's probably the girl in the report.
Are you here to take Lana from me, too?
Lana?
You can't have her!
Yuu!
Let's back him up!
We've found you, traitor!
Demon weapons?
A vampire extermination squad.
We have no business with you this time, get out of here!
If you get in our way, we'll kill you too!
Lana, let's go.
Let her go, vampire!
Now, Lana!
Yuu!
She's in danger!
We'll handle this, you go after her!
Lana!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Our brothers are preoccupied with the humans.
We'll take care of Shahar on our own!
Hide in here.
What are you going to do?
I'll deal with all of them, vampires and humans.
To stay with you,
I'll do anything.
Be a good girl and wait here, Lana.
Where did they go?
Oh, great, you're okay.
I'm here to save you.
Save me?
Really?
Yeah.
You're Riko, right?
Good.
But why is he calling you Lana?
He thinks I'm his little sister.
I think Lana was her name.
Why did you go with him?
It looked like you did that willingly.
I thought that maybe I could help him.
Huh?
What do you mean?
I think he used to be human.
I felt so bad for him.
He was apologizing...
and crying.
It was scary,
but he was always so nice to me,
so I...
I see.
You wait here.
My friends will be here soon.
Are you going to kill him?
I'm part of a vampire extermination squad.
I'm here to return you to your family.
Die!
I won't let anyone have Lana!
I'll kill anyone who tries to steal her from me!
That girl is not your sister!
Lana is my little sister!
I won't let you have her!
Maybe you used to be human...
but right now you need to be stopped!
That's all of them.
Those vampires seemed strange.
Yeah, seems like we've gotten mixed up
in a pretty abnormal situation.
I'm worried about Yuu,
let's go join up with him.
Hey! Weren't you a human before?
You hate the vampires and want them dead, don't you?
Then—
I won't let you have Lana!
I won't...
Stop this!
I don't—
Lana will never come home again.
I couldn't bear it so I drank her blood.
You...
I'll kill anyone who tries to steal her away.
Anyone and everyone, I'll kill you all!
Lana...
You won't take her...
It's my fault.
Lana, please forgive me.
Damn it!
Wait!
Lana!
Lana! Lana!
Lana, I'm so sorry!
I...
Again, I...
I'm...
okay...
Lana... Lana...
You...
really are human.
Vampires don't cry.
I see.
I'm...
human.
I have a request.
While I'm still human,
send me to where Lana is.
Please.
I understand.
Yuu!
I'm sorry I kept you waiting, Lana.
Apparently they've taken Riko-chan and her mother in at the Shibuya base.
I see.
She gets to live with her family, then.
Yes.
Now that we've finished scouting the place,
let's meet up with Kimizuki-san and the others.
Yeah, sure.
Riko-chan told me about that vampire.
Unfortunately,
we still have no way to cure people once they've been turned.
Yuu-san, your judgement this time—
I know.
My job is to kill vampires.
And we managed to save her.
You're right.
But if you're feeling down,
you're free to cry into my chest.
Let the lovely angel Shinoa-chan take your pain away!
What?
There you go again.
Hurry up.
Get in the car already or we'll leave you behind.
Damn you, Kimizuki!
I heard all about it.
Quit moping.
You have family to save, don't you?
You don't have time for that.
Yeah.
Yuu-kun, hurry!
What are you sitting around for?
We've got another mission waiting for us!
Let's go, Yuu-san.
Yeah.
Oh, this is where you were.
The cold shoulder again?
But I have good news for you.
You see, I was out checking on things today.
Things like Hyakuya Yuuichirou-kun.
I only saw him from afar, but he seemed to be doing well.
Well, that's enough chitchat.
Let's be on our way.
The great war between the vampires
and humans is about to begin,
Hyakuya Mikaela-kun.
Wait for me, Yuu-chan.
I will take you back.