You know, Armin.
It's nice that I could be a "good person" for you.
For now, at least, it looks like you won your bet.
But...
I'm going to gamble, too. And here's my wager!
Uh!
We believe we've uncovered the
Female Titan's true identity.
She's one of us.
Annie...
What's the hold up?
Erwin's never late.
They should be here.
At this rate the damn MPs'll show up first.
That'd be our luck.
Yeah, who can say?
Maybe they're all takin' a shit. Duty calls, right?
You're, uh, sure in a talkative mood today.
So what if I am?
Doesn't mean I was talkin' to you.
It's my fault, sir. I made the choice.
If I'd have thought this through none of this...
We wouldn't...
You made a judgment call.
Look, no one expects you to be clairvoyant.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sir.
What the...?
Why... Why are you all here?
We believe we've uncovered the
Female Titan's true identity.
She won't slip away this time.
The day after tomorrow, we'll be passing
through Stohess District en route to the capital.
That's when we'll strike.
It'll be our first and only chance to do so.
Once we've set foot in the interior,
the government will assume custody of Eren,
and the Scouts' authority to
continue operations will be limited.
Thus, unless we wish to concede defeat...
we must flush out the enemy now.
So here's what we do.
While in Stohess, we use Eren as bait,
luring the target into this underground passage.
The deeper, the better. Get her well beneath street level.
That done, she should be easily
immobilized, even in Titan form.
If she transforms before reaching the tunnel,
well, at that point she'll be your responsibility, Eren.
Right. So we know she'll be in Stohess?
There's no chance she'll bolt before we get there?
No. She won't risk going AWOL.
Wait, you mean she's...
Armin, here, identified her.
She's an MP. Likely responsible for
the deaths of Hange's test subjects.
And a fellow trainee in the 104th Cadet Corps.
Wha...? You can't be serious.
I trained with her?
I'm sorry, but yes. She's one of us.
No. It can't be.
Her name is Annie Leonhart.
God...
No.
Damn it! That ring!
She must've known I was lying
to her from the very beginning!
She knew we were leading her into a trap!
I could've... I should've taken a different approach.
Save the "should've's" for after we're out of this.
The question now is what do we do next.
Okay. First we rendezvous with Squad Three.
Then get the hell above ground.
We... We fight her out in the open!
That means we're switching to Plan B.
She's all yours, Eren!
Got it?
Yeah!
Over here!
Squad Three!
Hey, what happened? Is Plan A a no-go?
Afraid so, yes!
As of now we're going with the backup option!
She caved in the ceiling!
We've got to pull them out of there!
Eren! Get back!
What? No! Wait!
What was that?
Does she not care if she kills you, too?
She took a chance.
It was risky, but she gambled
on Eren's being able to survive.
We're dealing with someone
who's been backed into a corner.
She's desperate. That makes her all the more dangerous!
Damn it. We're cut off. If we try to get airborne
with our ODM gear, she'll swat us like flies.
And if we...
If we stay here, it's only a
matter of time before we're crushed.
I know what I have to do! I'll change!
I'll shield you guys just like
that time with the cannon fire!
Get in close!
But...
Alright. Brace yourselves!
Oh no! Not again!
Why now?
We don't have time for this. Just work, dammit!
Don't try to force it. You have to
have a clear goal in mind like Hange said!
C'mon, you can do this. We know you can!
Believe me! I'm trying!
Really?
Are you sure you're not having second thoughts?
Doubts about Annie?
Eren.
It's her. The Female Titan.
No matter how much you don't want to
believe it, that won't stop it from being true.
What did we see? Back there just now.
She's a murderer. Period.
This isn't complicated.
Get off my back dammit! I'm not stalling for time!
You think it's Annie?
Where's...
Where's your evidence? Tell me!
Obviously the Female Titan knew what
you looked like before she attacked.
Plus, she reacted to my use of
your "Suicidal Maniac" nickname,
something only our classmates would know.
But the biggest reason I suspect her
is that I have strong reason to believe
she's the one who killed Sawney and Beane.
You're kinda goin' out on a limb there.
Killing two Titans at once
required a precision ODM strike.
It only makes sense that the killer would've
used the gear they were most familiar with.
But, there was that whole equipment inspection.
Annie's totally checked out.
Except, the gear she presented. Well, it...
It wasn't hers. It was Marco's.
I don't understand.
What's Marco got to do with all this?
It's unclear.
Maybe you need to get your eyes checked...
Eren. I know what I saw, and the fact is...
Okay, we get it. Do you have anything else on her?
Any sort of concrete evidence?
Nothing, sir.
There's the fact that she looks like the Female Titan.
That's something, isn't it?
Really? What the hell's wrong with you?
What kind of evidence is that?
So basically, we're going after her without proof.
You're kidding me, right?
This is insane! What if it's not her?
What if she's not the monster you all say she is?
If it's not her, she'll be cleared. End of story.
No one wants to condemn her
prematurely, least of all me. But...
Either we make a move on circumstantial evidence, or
we sit back and let the central government condemn you.
Do you even hear yourselves? You're talking about Annie.
Eren. Don't stand there and tell me
this conversation isn't ringing any bells.
You fought hand-to-hand against the Female Titan.
Was there anything about her
techniques that seemed familiar?
Dig deep.
It's Annie.
You know it is.
And you know you have to fight.
Unless... Unless there's
something deeper keeping you from it.
What?
I know what we have to do!
Mikasa will head for that opening. At
the same time, I'll make a run for the exit.
I'm sure Annie will go for one of us.
When she does, run in the opposite
direction for all you're worth!
Are you out of your mind?
What the hell good's it gonna
do if one of you gets killed?
If we stay here, all three of us will!
Mikasa! You ready?
Yeah. Good luck.
Mikasa! Armin!
Don't do this!
I'm not worth it! You hear me?
You don't have to go!
What choice do we have?
The world is a cruel place.
Oh, no! Eren!
I won't let you take him! Not this time!
Eren!
Eren! Hold on! I'm coming!
Come on, stay with me!
Don't let her get away!
We have to contain her, whatever it takes!
What the hell's going on?
Escort Squad! Have a look! I'll hold this position!
Sir, yes sir!
This is bad. What in the hell
could be going on this far in?
Nile.
Deploy all troops immediately. We should
assume that a Titan has already appeared.
Are you out of your mind? This is Wall Sina!
There's no way a Titan would just suddenly show up here!
Who told you to move, Jaeger?
How 'bout this damn wig said I could, moron?
Call me Jaeger again and it's your ass, you got that?
Commander! What's the plan?
Ask Squad Four for equipment.
Sir!
Like the brass balls, but try not to
swing 'em so hard they get you killed.
Sir.
Hold on. What the hell?
Commander! Here!
Well done.
Thank you, sir.
Wait just a damn minute!
Alright! All of you with me!
We're rendezvousing with the Capture Squad!
No! The hell you will!
This is outright treason! I am well
within my rights to shoot you where you stand!
Think, Nile. I find it hard to believe
you're actually as thick-headed as you look.
You're a hair-trigger away from
making the biggest mistake of your life.
Take off the gear before I shoot you!
It's a Titan! It's a Titan!
How is it even this far in?
Something's happened to the wall!
Whoa. So that's what they look like.
Evidently , yeah.
Watch it!
Useless MP bastards.
Can't believe there was a time I'd
have given my left arm to be one of 'em.
I don't know what the hell I was ever thinkin'.
Right! Don't kill 'er!
Our orders say we only have to stop her!
Damn it! It's like she knows every
move we're gonna make in advance!
Try that with me! I dare you!
Eren! Talk to me!
Wake up!
What the hell's going on?
Help me! He's stuck in here!
Why didn't he just change into a Titan?
He couldn't transform! I... I think there's something
holding him back from being able to take on Annie!
What?
We'll worry about that when he's safe.
Help me get him out!
He really couldn't do it.
That's it! Enough of your bullshit, Eren!
Did I or did I not tell you
this day would eventually come?
Look at yourself! Our fate's in your hands.
We're out there puttin' our lives on the line, and
this is all we can expect from our last best hope?
Is this what Marco...
What he... Damn it!
Eren!
Leave him! We can't do anything until we take care of her!
Listen. I said something to Jean recently.
To rise above monsters,
we have to abandon our humanity.
What we fight, we become.
Fire with fire.
Look at her. Annie can do it.
I don't know why, but there it is. Simple.
You have to match her heartlessness to win!
Annie!
Are you gonna kill me or not?
I seem to remember you making a wager!
Well here's your chance to make good on it!
Armin, follow my lead!
You got it!
Yes.
Commander, you uh...
You've got that look in your eye again.
Nice! And here I was convinced having
a Plan C was nothing short of paranoid.
Oh, Commander Erwin, you genius.
Right. So.
Do us a favor.
Behave yourself.
Oh, and calling your co-horts to dinner isn't an option.
So let's not waste that lovely singing voice.
In fact, let's not waste anything.
No, no, I'm going to read you like bull entrails.
Every part of you has its own precious story to tell.
She broke free?
Ugh. Dammit, we didn't have time to set enough traps!
Don't let her get away!
To rise above monsters...
...we have to abandon our humanity.
Yeah. I know.
That's why... That's why my comrades died.
Because I couldn't let go.
I swore... to kill them all!
Every last one!
Right or wrong, it doesn't matter anymore.
Just kill. Consequences be damned! Damned!
Mikasa!
Because it is a cruel world.
What now?
Eren!
Eren.
"I'm going to kill them all. Every last one."
A vow made in the throes of fury and
despair takes on a new, terrible meaning.
For death recognizes no boundary.