Here at the Fumizuki Academy,
a school festival called the
"Refreshing Festival" will soon be held.
"The school festival is around the corner!!"
Since this school is using special systems,
such as the Summoner Test War,
there's a huge turnout for
the school festival every year.
In order to live up to people's expectations,
the students rouse themselves
and strive to prepare for it.
Around that time, Year 2, Class F was...
Come back... Come back to life, Muttsulini!
...trying resuscitation.
If the red threads of fate are tangled
I'll tie them into a bow
even if I need to do it by force
Don't untie that exciting
future of ours! It's a promise, okay?
I'm training my heart muscles
I'll accomplish my love splendidly!
(LOVE) The data from (CRY) a failed love
(TRASH) can no longer be
of any help, it's so obvious
(SO) Whenever I'm with you
It's like it's my first love... Am I cute?
We talk like we understand,
noisily, noisily, noisily!
My friends are chatty
But what everyone wants to
know is their own score in love
Oh? An average score is out of
question? My Darling is a cut above
In practice, it's a terrible unrequited love
Let's start leveling up. High! High! High!
If the red threads of fate are tangled
I'll tie them into a bow
even if I need to do it by force
Thumping heart panic!
A sudden development with you!
Don't look that way! Come with me!
I'm training my heart muscles
Surprisingly, today again,
I'm tough and blindly in love!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Day 1"
"Me, Maids, and a New Start"
A few days ago...
...the students started preparing
for the Refreshing Festival.
Around that time, Year 2, Class F was...
Play ball!
...playing baseball.
C'mon, Yoshii!
I'll take you on, Sugawa!
For the next pitch...
Throw a curve ball...
...at the batter's head...!
Hey! That's a foul play!
Don't hold back! Throw with all your might!
Of course I'll hold back!
You brats! Why are you slacking off?!
Oh shoot! It's Iron Man!
Yoshii! You again?!
Why do you always have something against me?!
There's no question that the
ringleader is Yuuji, the class rep, right?!
Hm? Throw a forkball...
...at Iron Man's...
...crotch?!
Hey, stop messing around!
Besides, I'm the one who'll get scolded!
All of you, just go back to your classroom!
You're the only class that hasn't
decided what to do for the school festival!
Okay...
So... we're gonna decide
what to do for the school festival.
Raise your hand if there's
something you wanna do.
Okay, Muttsulini.
A photo studio.
What kind of photos are
you planning on displaying?
It's a secret.
A secret...?
In the room, we'll display
precious photos that offer a peek
into a mysterious world.
At least it's a suggestion.
Write it down on the blackboard.
Okay...
Photo studio...
A secret... A... A secret?
Peek... I-In the room...
Is there anything else?
Ah... Himeji.
Uhm... How about a wedding café?
Similar to maid cafés,
waitresses will wear a wedding dress.
Oh, that might be cute. Sounds like
it's something girls would really like.
Guys might like it, too.
Marriage is the graveyard of life.
Akihisa, write it down.
Wedding... Life...
Anything else?
How about a Chinese-style café?
To do something different from
other classes, we'll serve dim sum.
They say that there's no other
genre as deep as Chinese culture...
...although it's being overshadowed
by European culture these days.
Akihisa, write it down.
Uhm... Chinese style... European...
Hey, Akihisa. Aren't you writing
only those words stuck in your hea--
You brats! Have you decided
what you're gonna do in the festival?
There're three ideas so far.
"Photo studio" "Secret peeking room" "Wedding café"
"Graveyard of life" "Chinese-style café" "European"
Maybe I should increase the
amount of remedial classes.
Ah! What the heck is this?!
Geez, why don't you do
things a little more seriously?
Don't you wanna make a profit so
you can improve your class equipment?!
Do you mean us buying
desks with the money we make?
Whoa! I didn't think of that.
Is that allowed, Teacher?!
You may be really stupid,
but I never expected your desks
would go even below the cardboard boxes.
Although it is a penalty,
if it interferes with your studies,
then we're getting our priorities wrong.
I'll negotiate with the principal
to give you permission to do so
as part of the school events.
Really?!
So we won't have to study with a
drawing board and a mat like this, huh?
That will allow me to
get the better of my father!
Your father?
Ah! Nothing... Never mind.
I-In any case, that
sounds interesting, doesn't it?
Okay then, I'll take a vote!
--Splendidly done.
--Raise your hand for what you wanna do.
"Fumizuki Academy Refreshing Festival"
Okay, this should do it.
I hope we'll have a bunch of customers.
We can't afford to fail this time,
so try very hard, okay, Aki?
Hm? What do you mean by "this time"?
Well, I was asked not to tell anyone, but...
...Mizuki may have to change schools.
Himeji may have to...
...change schools?!
Oh no... when we still have to
make a lot of fun memories...!
She's the only one who brings
a breath of fresh air to Class F!
What's gonna happen if she changes schools?!
Everyone will lose their
hope, the class will fall apart
and we'll enter a hell
where violence and looting rule.
We'll all have mohawk haircuts,
just like in Fist of the North Star,
and spend every day fighting
over the single heroine, Hideyoshi!
Akihisa's having a system meltdown.
He's bad at dealing with unexpected situations.
Akihisa! Wake up!
Hideyoshi...
Will you still like me even
if I have a mohawk haircut?
What kind of thought process would lead
from Mizuki's changing
schools to this kind of reaction?
Why is Himeji changing schools?!
She said her parents are worried
about her studying in Class F.
We can't blame them.
She's among guys with low marks
and is in a very bad environment.
It's just natural that they worry.
If she changes schools, she can
study in a normal environment.
So that's why she said she
could get the better of her father.
I see. If we buy a full set of decent equipment,
she might be able to persuade her father, huh?
If that's the case, we can't fail, huh, Akihisa?
Right.
We're back!
Himeji!
Tsuchiya made a dish for the
Chinese-style café. Could you guys try it?
Sesame dumplings.
Well then, I'll try.
Whoa! This is good!
Yeah! It's crispy outside and sticky inside.
It's good that it's not too sweet.
This makes me want to drink some tea.
I'll go make some.
Oh, I'll help you.
So this is that good? Maybe I'll try, too.
Yeah! It's hard outside and gluey inside.
It's not too sweet or too spicy. It's very...
What's wrong, Akihisa?!
Muttsulini, did you really
make those sesame dumplings?
I'm certain of it.
I made three...
Why were there more than three?
From the symptoms, there's no
doubt that it was what Himeji made.
That was close! It was
Russian roulette with 50-50 odds!
--Woosh... Grandpa, I'm coming now...
--He really is a guy with bad luck.
And then, on the day of the school festival...
"Chinese-style café"
Welcome to the Chinese-style café, European!
Someone! Please, someone resuscitate him!
We've already done this scene.
Akihisa, we don't have enough people.
Could you help in the kitchen?
I guess it can't be helped. I'll do it myself.
"Chinese-style café: European"
Thank you very much!
Welcome! We're currently asking our
customers who their favorite waitress is.
Please vote on your way out!
It now looks like a café more or less.
Yeah. We're getting many
customers, too. Looks like it's a success.
Hey, just how long are you gonna make us wait?!
Hm?
What's the problem with this café?
Aren't you gonna take our orders?!
Y-Yes, I'll be right there.
Hold on a second, please.
Huh?! We've been waiting all this time!
We've got other places we gotta go too.
Don't make us wait forever, you idiots!
I-I'm sorry! Hold on a second, please!
What's their problem, acting so big?
Those Year 3 guys... Troublesome customers...
Seriously, we're hungry!
"Sesame Dumplings: 200 yen" "Sample"
Oh?
Hey, those look good.
It's hard outside and gluey inside.
It's not too sweet or too spicy. It's...
Oh shoot! This is bad!
300 joules! Charge!
300! Roger!
Three, two, one!
Phew, that was close.
You guys seem quite used to it.
I'm always hovering
between life and death, so...
But what on earth happened?
Th-This is...
To think that there're
people who'd eat sample food...
Wh-What the hell's with the food here?!
Are you trying to kill us?!
I-It's no laughing matter, you bastards!
This isn't good. We have to
somehow smooth things over.
Congratulations! You're the
first one to hit the jackpot!
Hit the jackpot?
Do you have a gift or something?
What? A gift? Let's see...
Here! Say "ahh"!
No way we can eat that!
You bastard! You won't get away with this!
We're gonna make it so that
you'll have to close this café.
What?! You ate them on your own!
Shut up! Who's in charg--
I'm the class rep, Yuuji Sakamoto.
Is there something you're unsatisfied with?
N-Natsukawa was just knocked off his feet.
That was my special
negotiation skill, "start with a punch."
Stop messing around, you bastard!
And, this is my special negotiation
skill, "follow up with a kick."
Ow, ow, ow... Hm? Tsunemura!
Also, I can finish up with
my special negotiation skill,
"strangle them with a pro-wrestling technique."
N-No thanks. That was enough.
I see. Then...
...this concludes the negotiation.
That's a pretty good lock, isn't it?
That's the Karl Gotch style, huh?
"Order" "Food Name -- Amount" "Sesame dumpling -- 2 pieces" "Punch
and kick -- 1 each" "German suplex Karl Gotch style -- Complete set"
Thank you very much.
It's somehow gotten slow.
This is strange. It's lunch time right now.
If it stays like this, it won't be good.
Welcome! Ah...
Hello, Stupid Big Brother!
Haduki! You came!
Yes! This is the long-awaited
school festival! I'll help you!
Thank you, Haduki.
You don't have to worry, since
this is my future husband's café!
Also, I've already
given you my first kiss, so...
Huh? Why am I on the floor?
Tsuchiya! Give me some forks.
Five should be enough.
I need some, too, so ten forks, please.
We're now starting the inquisition.
At any rate, immediate death penalty.
--Ow! Ow! Hey! Hear me out, guys!
--I know you took the trouble to come, but our café is so deserted
that it even looks like it's run-down.
So it's not like we need help.
I see... I wanted to wear a Chinese dress, too.
One hundred meat buns, rush order, please.
Get them yourself.
This may be because of that rumor.
Rumor?
Yes.
"First School Festival ~Haduki's Story~ Episode 1"
On my way here, I got lost, so I asked people,
"Where is stupidest Big Brother's café?"
Then everyone told me this place right away.
You're already like a landmark.
Are you talking about me?!
But they also told me that this
place was filthy so I'd better not go.
What?!
Oh no...
We all cleaned this place together
and even decorated it neatly!
Those customers who came
earlier didn't seem unsatisfied.
I'm sure they were happy with our café.
Except for two.
Ah...
Probably that Toko-Natsu Duo
is spreading a bad rumor about us.
Toko-Natsu?
Their names are Tsunemura and Natsukawa.
So if we put the first Chinese
characters in their names together,
it's read Toko-Natsu.
I see.
Now that it's come to this, we have no choice
but to find them and negotiate one more time.
Haduki, where'd you hear that rumor?
At a café where there are
a lot of pretty big sisters!
Okay! I'll search high and low!
It seems like the goal has changed...
"Maid café"
So this is the café Haduki was talking
about, huh? Nothing seems unusual.
It's too soon to judge.
Welcome home, Master.
Wow, you look pretty, Kirishima.
Thanks, Yoshii.
Welcome home. I won't let
you leave tonight, my darling.
Can I leave now?
Here is the menu.
Let's see... I'll have...
...water, please.
Certainly, sir.
What about you, Master?
Shouko, what's with this menu?
Today's Special. Honeymoon with a maid.
Lovey-dovey date with a maid.
A sweet kiss with a maid.
Supplies are limited, so please order soon.
Fat chance!
Whoa! This place is neat and nice!
The Chinese-style café by Year 2,
Class F that we went to earlier was terrible.
What a difference!
Their café is filthy and has a weird smell.
Their waitresses are ugly. On top of that,
they named a Chinese-style café, "European."
Are they stupid or what?
Those bastards!
They're telling nothing but lies!
One of those is true, though.
I won't let them get away with this!
Hold on. If we attack them here, our
bad reputation will spread even more.
Use your head.
Then what're we gonna do?
Well...
Shouko, let us borrow your maid costume.
Okay.
Wait! Wait! What're you doing?!
You said you wanted me, so...
Not you, a maid costume!
And, I meant let us borrow
it if you have an extra one!
I'll go bring one.
Don't make it so obvious
that you're disappointed!
Yuuji, what're we gonna
do with the maid costume?
Obviously, we're gonna ask Hideyoshi for help.
I see, that's a good idea.
"Changing clothes"
How's this? Does this look womanly?
Whoa... Well done, Hideyoshi.
That looks pretty good.
I'm very good at this kind of makeup.
E-Even a bra?!
If you aren't prepared perfectly,
you can't get into the role.
Normally, even underwear is...
Th-That's...
"Maid café"
Seriously, I don't understand
why a person would go to
that filthy Chinese-style café!
After all, it's Class F. It can't be any good.
Hm?
What do you want, lady?
Wow, you're quite a cutie.
Hm? What's the matter? Did you fall in...
Go to hell!
Shoot! It wasn't far enough.
Y-You are a guy from Class F...!
Crap!
Eek! This guy is peeking up my skirt!
What?! H-Hold on a...
To think that you act so
shamelessly in public... You slimeball!
What're you saying?! We're the victims!
Shut up! You rubbed the
waitress's breasts, didn't you?!
Ahh! This guy is a perv!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hm? What the hell is this?
What? I can't get it off!
See? He's rubbing them.
That's totally different!
Tsk! Things are looking bad for us.
We're getting out of here, Natsukawa!
Hold it!
"Haunted House"
"Entrance"
Hmm... They're made well,
but fakes are fakes, after all.
I wonder if there's something scarier.
Those bastards! They won't get away with this!
Now that it's come to this, we'll do
whatever it takes to make them pay!
What're we gonna do?!
I have an idea. Let's go!
Wh-What was that?
I must've had a dream since
I was really hoping for scary stuff.
But if I hope for pretty stuff instead, I bet...
H-How pretty...
Oh no!
I've got my sweet honey, Yoshii, in my heart!
But her unearthly beauty is...
No! It means that I'm denying
my feelings towards Yoshii...
Shoot! I didn't ask her name and class!
But I've got Yoshii...
If I go after her now...
Ahhh! What should I do?!
Please do whatever you want.
"Chinese-style café: European"
Welcome!
We're getting more customers, aren't we?
Aki and Sakamoto might've pulled it off.
I'll help you out a lot!
You bastards!
Tsk! We let them get away.
What're we gonna do, Yuuji?
If they spread bad rumors
again somewhere else...
Hm?
What's the matter, Muttsulini?
We've got a problem.
Our waitress got kidnapped.
What?!
Hello?
Hey. You really went and did it earlier!
We're having your cute
waitress play with us right now.
Your sales must be coming down
by now without your poster girl, huh?
Give Himeji and Minami back!
Oh-oh, you should try not to upset me.
Don't worry. We'll have plenty
of fun with that waitress of yours.
Those bastards...! I won't forgive them!
Muttsulini, can you figure out
where the Toko-Natsu Duo is hiding?
It'll take a while.
Okay, do it.
"Boys Changing Room"
Are those images from the
surveillance cameras within the school?
But many of them seem to be
positioned at too low an angle for that...
These are my surveillance cameras.
I've set up video monitoring
in 32 places within the school.
It doesn't look like the
Toko-Natsu Duo is in any of those places.
I've set up audio monitoring in 57 places.
Switch to audio monitoring.
Right? They were pissed.
Serves them right.
Bingo!
Where is it coming from?
PE storeroom.
Okay!
Whoa!
Ahh!
What the...!
Whoa!
Oof!
What?!
Sorry!
Whoa!
Just wait, Himeji! Minami!
What?!
How did you figure out where we were?!
Himeji! Minami!
What's the matter, Akihisa?
Those two are working at the café.
Hideyoshi... Why are you here?
They forced me to come here
and made me play a game with them.
So you were having plenty of fun.
Bummed...
Thus, the first day of the
Refreshing Festival ended.
"European Sales List"
"Amount" "Total"
How were the sales, Shimada?
This is amazing!
Even after subtracting the cost,
we have enough to buy system desks!
Really?!
Hm?
What're these huge sales?
Hm? Let's see...
Splendid photo collection
set A by Muttsulini Trading...
...500 copies, all sold out.
Refreshing Festival limited edition.
Well, anyway, it means today was a success.
Stupid Big Brother, this is
amazing! I'm happy for you!
Thanks, Haduki. This is thanks to your help.
The sales are thanks to our waitresses
with great customer-drawing power.
"Results"
I'm done with the voting results.
Today's most popular waitress is...
"Aki"
"I didn't know we had such a cutie"
I'm not even saying that
I want to be No. 1, but...
This frustration... How should I deal with it?
I'm happy for you, Akihisa.
You got first place for a change.
I'm not happy about it!
All right! Listen, everyone. This is important!
Hm?
I went to negotiate with the
principal on your equipment.
As a special case, she says you can
buy equipment with the café's profit.
However... under one condition!
On the second day of the Refreshing Festival,
a Summoner Test Tournament will be held.
If the champion team belongs to your class,
she'll allow your replacement purchase.
Summoner Test Tournament?
It's a random tournament by
selected teams throughout the academy.
They're all formidable enemies.
Oh no...
What do you wanna do, Akihisa?
Of course! We'll do it!
Those who'd like to participate,
come up with teams and register!
That is all!
The day after a holiday should be a holiday!
The day before a holiday should also be a holiday!
I don't want it to end! I want it to keep going!
I don't want to leave my room!
I don't want to believe it! I can't believe it!
I hate Monday
If I don't get up, it'll be over
I can't resist this sleepiness
I can stay like this a bit longer
I'm happy in my dreams!
When I got up, the "iitomo"
show had just ended, "Oh no..."
The dream turns into a horrific reality
At this point, even if I struggle,
I can't get that time back
So I'm going to dive into
the world of dreams once again
Thus, the dreams of Year 2,
Class F carried on to the second day.
And, here's also a man
who chases after his dream.
Ahh... I wonder who that was...
I've got a good bargain photo today.
Th-This is...!
H-How much?
Oh? What're you two doing?
Yoshii! No...
Y-You've got it all wrong!
Huh?