The me from back then...
couldn't understand the concept of getting along with other people.
couldn't understand the concept of a person living alone.
Hey, Chihiro...
let's go!
Let's play!
Let's go!
Go where?
To our house.
Hold on a second.
That small encounter made a big difference in the path that I took.
I believed that those fun times would always continue.
But...
Hey.
Something's here.
It's a present.
A present?
Sorry about the day before yesterday.
For breaking the promise.
It seems so...
Seems so?
Actually,
I really can't remember it well.
But thank you very much.
Chirp?
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
It's cute.
Thank you very much.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
I'm fine now.
It's great that you are feeling better.
You know...
What is it?
There's something that I'd like to talk about.
With me... Would you like to try and write a novel?
Huh?
Why are you asking such things?
Why, you ask?
Because it sounds interesting.
Let's try it.
It's impossible.
There's no way that's possible.
Why?
Why, you ask?
Renji-kun knows that I can only retain thirteen hours of my memory, right?
Yea, but I would also help and-
I don't want to write it.
That's...
Why are you teasing me like this?
Teasing?
Me?
Yes.
You were much more kind before.
I wanted to try writing a novel for Chihiro.
Why is it for me?
That's because...
Chihiro, you said that writing stories was your dream.
That's...
the me from a week ago.
It doesn't matter if it was a week ago or today.
Chihiro is Chihiro.
And dreams are dreams.
I'm going back.
Chihiro!
I just feel kind of lost... about you.
That's true alright.
I don't even understand it myself.
So you broke our promise and went to see Miyamura-senpai instead?
Idiot.
Kei-senpai?
Let's exchange manga for this week.
Ah, sorry.
I haven't bought it yet.
Eh! But senpai is in charge of buying the Mimi monthly magazine.
Sorry.
You can just read ahead.
Write it for me, Mizuki.
I don't have any money left over this week.
I had to lend some to Hiro-senpai already.
Why did Onii-chan...?
It looked like Hiro-senpai got dumped by Miyamura-senpai.
I paid for Hiro-senpai because he didn't have any money.
I really don't understand what you are saying.
The day before yesterday, Hiro-senpai made Miyamura-senpai angry, so she left first.
That means Onii-chan...
Hiro-senpai even with looks is not good with girls.
I see.
It flies so well even though it's so light.
I wonder if the money will come any faster.
Miyamura?
Umm, err... Miyako-san?
No adding the '-san' at the end.
I won't answer next time.
Uh, right.
Good.
But because of your honesty, I'll forgive you this time.
Forgive, you say...
Did I do something that bad?
Hirono-kun, what's that?
I know, it's emergency food in case of a disaster.
That's right.
At the end of the month, being in debt is always an emergency.
That seems lonely.
I know!
I really will pay this time, so let's go and eat.
You think I play around every day?
I have work to do.
Even though it's Sunday?
It makes no difference.
Is that so?
Then...
Let's go.
Go where?
Obviously, to Hirono-kun's house.
It's the end of the month so there definitely won't be anything decent left to eat.
Alright.
That girl without a doubt was Hirono's...
It was that girl.
You live in a pretty decent house.
Aren't you a little lacking on awareness?
Why?
First off, you're a girl.
Don't just barge into a bachelor's house on your own.
It's okay, I know.
Know what?
Hirono-kun is a person who will be nice to me.
You know, your mind is way too simple.
What's with the sudden change in topic?
There's no way I'd understand a girl that I don't know personally.
I know what kind of person that person is, and what they think.
Liar.
Not to be arrogant...
But I have good eyes for knowing people.
That's because, I...
Because what?
Ha! I found a perverted book!
You're interested in these types.
They're just magazines.
Sounds like the truth.
I want to start working right about now.
Ah, go ahead.
Don't mind me.
I'll just observe quietly.
You know...
I can't show other people the manuscript before publishing.
Then show it to me after it is published.
Let me borrow the manga that Hirono-kun made.
Then I'll return it quickly.
Why do I have to make a trade for it?
Let... me... see...
I guess I have no choice.
It's a short piece that I drew before publication.
I only have the copy because I don't have the original.
It's all good.
Then I'll borrow this.
Kyousuke.
Sorry, Miss President.
I'll take my camera.
Really?
Call me when you don't have any materials.
Thanks.
There'll most likely be trouble during the next project.
Cine-Festival.
They're really looking forward to it, so they'll definitely win.
What about you?
Are you filming it alone?
Yeah. There is a picture I must take no matter what.
How is it, Mizuki?
Is it good?
That's a pretty arrogant question.
This is beyond good or bad.
It's at the level where it will cause injuries when eaten.
Th-That much?
Just what did you have to do to make such bad-tasting food?
You don't really need to put it like that...
Even though this is just one, rice shouldn't be wasted like this.
It's not one, it's three.
There were three made.
These were the ones that were finished.
Where are the other two that are left?
They just left my hand when I grabbed them.
Kei-senpai should never cook again.
Don't be so angry.
But first of all, why are you acting like this all of a sudden?
To suddenly be cooking... It's not like you, Senpai.
Because...
even I have things like responsibilities.
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
The reason why Onii-chan is working so hard is...
partly because of me.
Onii-chan, look.
This is also interesting.
Read it, read it!
Wait a second.
Amazing!
It looks exactly the same.
Draw more.
Okay.
Onii-chan might be a genius.
Maybe, I guess...
Amazing!
The me from back then... enjoyed being with Onii-chan.
The me from back then... enjoyed seeing them both happy.
But, now...
The me of now...
What is it that I'm searching for?
The lacking color in the world that I see.
To find that, I...
Hirono-kun!
When did you...?
Besides that, Hirono-kun...
Manga!
I'm drawing it right now.
It's not that, but...
the other ones.
The manga that Hirono-kun drew.
Do you have any more?
About three more short pieces.
It's in publishing up to now.
Let me borrow it right now.
Right now, you say?
Was my manga that interesting?
Hirono-kun, you look nervous.
S-Shut up!
You know...
It was really interesting.
Hirono-kun, you might be a genius.
Yes, hello?
Mizuki?
The pork cutlet won't fully cook on the inside even though I cook it completely.
Maybe there's something wrong with the pan?
This is Senpai's fault.
Stop being mean and tell me already.
Listen carefully, Senpai.
For fried food, the temperature of the oil...
Fire! Fire!
The pan is on fire!
Water, water, water!
No! Don't use water! Don't ever use water!
The fire will just spread more!
What should I do?!
Mayonnaise, put in mayonnaise!
Squirt it all into the pan.
Squirt it you say? O-Okay, wait a second.
Senpai?
It's out.
It's out, Mizuki.
Amazingly genius!
It's not something amazingly genius!
It's nothing short of a miracle.
Welcome back.
It shouldn't be,"Welcome back."
You should stop putting the spare key under the flower pot.
What are you doing?
As thanks for letting me borrow your manga...
I was thinking of making dinner for you.
Go home! You!
Why?
You...
Don't you know that humans can't digest raw starch?
Yes.
Do you know that intake of excessive artificial flavoring will cause numbing of the hands and feet?
So, what is that?
I made the decision to never eat anything a girl made for the rest of my life.
It seems like you have some kind of painful memory.
Don't do anything unnecessary!
These things I can eat with a peace of mind.
Okay!
Miyako's special herb rice is complete!
What do you think? Do you want to taste it?
It's good, right?
Good, right?
Yeah, it's delicious.
See?
Dang it... I didn't want to admit that to this girl.
To hear that it's delicious...
makes it all worth it.
It's not as fulfilling when you eat alone.
Alone, you say? What about your family?
That's a no-no, Hirono-kun.
You're holding your chopsticks weird.
Since you are Japanese...
you should hold your chopsticks properly.
I have tenosynovitis on my right hand.
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
It's all right. It's something like a work-related injury.
Is it bad?
Just some minor symptoms.
There are times when I just endure the pain while I'm drawing, but...
I'm not like that.
Sounds tough.
It's nothing.
It's a big problem.
You don't sleep, eat, play, or go to school.
Is that...
what you think?
What I...?
Do I look like an idiot who is pushing himself by doing what he's not fit for?
It's not like that.
To work diligently... there is value just in that.
Hirono-kun isn't a idiot.
What are you doing?
You can't hold the chopsticks well.
Ahh~
It's okay, I'll feed myself.
No.
If you are going to work, you need to rest your hand.
Here. Ahh~
Stop it. I said it's all right.
It's not. Ahh~
What are you doing?
Kei.
Kei...
Wait up, Chihiro.
Why can't you do it?
Let's try it. The novel.
You said that it was your dream.
You said that you had a story that you wanted to write.
Let me help you.
Do you think that you are saying something good?
Do you think that you are saying something cool?
Because I'm someone whose time has stopped.
Because I don't have anything to do, nor do I have anything I want to do.
So to make my dreams come true...
Such...
Simple...
It is as you say.
Chihiro...
You're right.
The one who is wrong is me.
But, because of that...
What are you telling me to do?
Save me.
Why?
Why would a person other than myself want to know about me?!
Truthfully, I want to write about it.
The dream... Before the memories disappear.
It's all that is left.
But I absolutely don't want to.
Why?
I'm scared.
If I can't even do that...
It'll turn out that I can't do anything.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Umm...
Is it okay if I kiss you?
Kisses are for lovers.
Can't we be lovers?
Renji-kun today is mean, so no.
I see.
It would've been all right if it was yesterday.
I slept alone yesterday.
It was very lonely.
I wanted to meet with Renji-kun.
And...
because I liked you.
Yesterday's me... wrote it in the diary.
I see.
That's too bad.
I don't like the Renji-kun of today.
But it's not that I don't really like you...
Just please hold me for a little longer.
Hold you?
Yes, because it's warm.
Chihiro?
Yes?
The story that Chihiro wants to write... what is it about?
You're very persistent.
Let me hear it.
The thing I'm thinking of writing...
is in a world where everything came to ruin.
The story of a solely surviving girl.
Kei-senpai!
What are you doing, Senpai?
Nothing.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Is it okay if I try one?
Come on, Senpai. It's not good if you don't put anything in it.
The bread and the vegetables-
Senpai?
It's nothing.
The thing that's connected...
is a sad story.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
Outline.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?