Wow.
This is even cooler than Ginza Kami-Sakura.
Well, that's all I know. I really have no idea.
And there are a dozen other dangerous folks around here,
so you'd better watch out.
Oh, you saw that black bike?
We haven't had such a sweet deal for a while now.
And it's fucking jailbait.
Props to the informant.
At that moment I noticed that I was trembling.
Is the reality you perceive "real"?
The familiar scenery is still the same.
I'd like to congratulate everyone on their admittance.
Currently, Japan is suffering from issues like declining birthrates and class stratification.
However, when I see the fine young people lined up before me,
I can only see a bright future before us.
I believe that Japan is still in good shape.
It brings a smile to my face.
Today must be a good day for you...
I wonder if today will be mellow again.
I-I'm Ryuugamine Mikado.
A shy boy that just recently came to Tokyo...
I'm Sonohara Anri.
Nice to meet you all.
A girl that gives off the feeling of naivety...
I am Kida Masaomi!
Despite looking a bit mature,
I'm actually a fragile, easily hurt fifteen-year-old kid like all of you.
A boy that lives in his own saccharine dreamworld...
I'm Kamichika Rio.
Nice to meet you all.
A girl with an enigmatic past...
They're people you'd see on the street.
Harima...
Is Harima Mika here?
Absent...
A mundane, familiar scenery.
Nice going on the first day.
We were introducing ourselves.
You can introduce yourself from there.
I'm Yagiri Seiji.
Nice to meet all of you.
However, there are unexpected moments
when reality shows its other face.
Take your seat, Yagiri.
I won't.
I don't think I'll be able to come to school for a while.
No, perhaps I'll never come back.
I just stopped by to say that.
Please excuse me.
Hey, Yagiri, what's the meaning of this?
That's it.
I have to take care of something very important to me.
I can't deal with you people.
Bye.
H-Hey, Yagiri!
Wait!
Wait, I said!
A sudden crack in the peaceful life disturbs the people.
And we have a girl who took a peek at that crack.
Actually, she was supposed to be dead two days ago.
She was born in a normal household.
She lived a life without any problems or poverty.
However, when she entered middle school,
an envelope was sent to her, like an ambush.
What was in the envelope?
Pictures.
Looks like my dad's having an affair.
He's seeing another woman.
And there was a letter.
"Could you forgive him?" it asked.
I think the person who sent the letter is somehow related to that woman.
Of course, your father isn't completely innocent,
but neither is the one who sent the letter.
I was so perplexed that I didn't know what to do.
I decided to hide the envelope for the time being.
Since then,
I became disgusted with the normal atmosphere in the house.
It was hard, wasn't it?
What's the matter, Rio?
I could only endure it for six months.
I thought everything would get better if I confronted him about it.
You don't have to talk about it if it's too hard for you.
There are things I don't want to share with others too.
It's okay.
I want you to know.
I can't believe I thought the TV remote was my cell phone.
Nothing had changed.
I know. That was silly.
I wasn't sure if my mother had decided not to bring it up, or if they'd discussed it before.
Both my father's lame jokes, and the overly sweet taste of my mother's stew...
Nothing had changed.
So I thought, "I should disappear to cause a change."
Lately, my mind has been full of such thoughts.
I'm in a situation like yours.
It's not as serious as yours though.
What happened?
There was a girl I was going out with,
but she was impregnated by my dad.
That's horrible...
But the person I absolutely couldn't forgive was my mother.
What did she say?
She said it happens all the time,
and that we have a reputation to protect, so we shouldn't make a fuss about it.
She didn't say anything about how she felt.
I thought she cared more about our reputation than about me.
But maybe she was thinking about my future.
I doubt that.
You think?
She isn't thinking about you at all, Nakura-san!
She's just selfish! Only thinking about herself!
Dinner's ready.
I'm coming.
Say, Magenta-san, will you disappear with me?
If both of us die,
I'm sure they'd finally realize...
what they should have cherished.
In retrospect, it was a pretty foolish decision.
But she left the house with determination.
She felt some strength in Nakura's words.
She wanted to see the person who shared her thoughts with her own eyes.
Even if it had been a lie, she had nothing to lose.
Or so she thought.
Yes?
Magenta-san?
Yes.
Are you Nakura-san?
All right. I knew it was you.
When she saw him, she thought...
Nice to meet you.
"Is this man really Nakura?"
Likewise.
She followed him
Should we go then?
because she wouldn't forgive herself if she ran away.
Okay.
So, even if this happens...
Hey.
Hello.
Anyone around?
Not a single soul.
Well...
Sorry for tricking you!
Various emotions such as fear, regret, and resistance
were juxtaposed in her,
but before she lost consciousness, she thought,
"This must be my fate."
Was there really any reason to care about herself?
She would just vanish from this world,
without anyone noticing.
However...
Someone is around.
Even when she was unconscious, the world kept revolving.
Well, it's not really a hard job.
Either way, be careful.
Her feelings and will were irrelevant.
I can't.
I just couldn't get the money together.
I'm not saying that I can't pay it back.
But if something were to happen to me,
Shiki-san from the Awakusu group wouldn't stay quiet—
Listen, old man.
I don't have time.
It's not that I'm busy,
but the time that I'll waste on you is just two and a half minutes!
And the other guy you shouldn't piss off is...
Yo!
I don't think it's necessary to tell an excellent transporter like you how to do it,
but you don't need to do more than I've asked.
Just smack some sense into them.
Have fun.
The world is revolving.
Things were going a bit astray from the "fate" the girl believed in.
Hey.
Wh-What the fuck are you?
It read, "I've been asked to bring you to a certain place."
The bike moved silently.
But sometimes it neighed like a horse.
It felt unreal.
Yet this empty feeling was real.
The girl wondered what lay beyond that warmth.
What were that person's thoughts? What did they know? How did they live?
How did she appear to that person?
Okay.
Magenta-san.
Nice to meet you. I'm Nakura.
Are you really Nakura-san?
Correct. The Nakura who wants to disappear.
I'm really delighted to meet you.
Did you save me?
Yes, it was me.
Thank you.
Were you scared?
Yes.
You must have felt terrible.
Yes...
But how did you know I'd been kidnapped?
Well, because I asked them to.
And it was also me who saved you.
What's going on here?
You were suicidal, but you got kidnapped.
And you were a bit frustrated at yourself for getting scared.
But if you'd resisted, it'd mean that you'd denied the you that wanted to die.
So you just accepted the events, forcing yourself to believe it was your fate.
But now that you've been rescued, you feel relieved.
I just wanted to see that expression.
In other words,
I wanted to see your dumbfounded face when someone saw through you.
Why?
Good question.
Well, I believe the answer might sound quite philosophical to you.
Okay. If I had to explain it...
It's because I like humans.
Humans are so interesting and amusing.
I just can't help myself.
Oh, to make it clear, I just like humans.
That doesn't mean you in particular.
Keep that in mind.
It was all a lie?
Have you finally realized your place?
Come on.
Quite a few people have jumped from here.
Well, not enough to make this place famous.
But if you jump from here, your death is certain.
Look at that stain.
Say, don't you think you're special?
That's not true.
We're all the same.
No one in the world can live honestly.
Even you have a secret or two.
Haven't you ever wondered why you're so perfect while your parents are so pathetic?
Well...
If I came to a conclusion...
The show goes on, and everyone laughs at lame jokes or eats overly sweet stew,
regardless of whether they're having an affair or whether their wife knows about it.
Take a good look.
Despite all their worries, they're all bloodstains adorning the pavement now.
Nothing more. Without exception.
All are equal in front of the Lord.
Should I let go of your hand?
See?
Anyway,
I'm glad I was able to see your ugly feelings today.
I'm not really interested in your problems,
but in the way you live when they stress you out.
Oh, and you were awfully boring. Your life was just as I imagined.
I knew from the beginning that you weren't serious about dying.
Have a good night.
It was fun, Magenta-san.
She hesitated for a second.
Would she be able to hurt him if she jumped?
But then she thought...
Maybe she'd just been waiting for the opportunity.
And that opportunity came from that man's words.
But without being aware...
Hey...
Why did you...
Sheesh, acting on your own again...
Then, she thought about her parents.
Her dad and his lover.
Her dad and her mother.
And she also thought about the times she didn't see them.
Maybe they weren't as wicked, selfish, and hate-filled as she thought.
Perhaps they weren't veiled by her own weakness and compromises.
As she tried to find her way back home,
she thought about forgiving them.
Ever since that day, the world has appeared completely different to her.
There are as many feelings and secrets as there are people.
She realized that it was very normal.
Where do ya wanna go?
I'll take you anywhere, so uh, treat me.
Let's see...
How about a bookstore?
Well, there are a lot of them...
Even these two normal school boys have their secrets.
Feelings they can't share with anyone.
Please wait!
Yagiri-kun, what's bothering you?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Y-You can't skip school on the first day.
Leave me alone!
Wait!
Hey.
Is something wrong?
What's up?
I'm such a lady-killer.
That girl with glasses has fallen head over heels for me.
I could see her anxiety about the dangerous and risky days awaiting her.
Mind translating that into Japanese?
And he...
And she...
What they see might not always be reality.
And so, she started to ponder...
Will a day come when she can say those words to someone?
"Because the world isn't as cruel as you think it is."
I didn't know you became a Champion of Justice.
I thought I asked an excellent transporter...
No way!
Me, Orihara Izaya, a mere informant, isn't that relentless.
But I'm not nice enough to stop anyone who wants to die.
It was fun, excellent transporter.
Ikebukuro.
He, she, me, and you...
We came here searching for something,
seeking something,
to change something.
Next time: Rampant.
You want some sushi? It's yummy.
Hey, Mister, long time no see.