In order to save Sakuragi's life, the six prepared themselves for their war.
All right, that's how we're going to bust Bro out.
Wow, not bad.
I knew you'd come through, Uncovered.
It sounds like it might work.
No "might" about it.
First, we've got to get out of here.
The door can only be opened from the outside.
I thought of that, of course.
It's Sunday. There aren't many guards.
The night watch only comes around at 11 and 3.
We'll take that chance to get out of here.
But how are we going to get the key?
The guards aren't the only ones with keys.
The doctor on duty has one, too.
One of us has to pretend he's sick and talk his way into the infirmary.
Once he's there, he'll steal the key.
That's going to be tough. Sasaki's on duty today.
Yeah, I know.
All right, I'll do it!
If worst comes to worst, I can chomp right into him.
No, I will.
Turtle, if you go, he'll just feed you some medicine and send you right back.
You don't need to worry about me, Uncovered.
If I don't go, it won't work.
But Joe! If you go, that old pervert's gonna-
Don't worry about me, Turtle.
I'll get this door open.
For sure.
My heart can't be scarred any worse.
My body can't be defiled any further.
Joe cared about only one thing...
Saving Bro's life.
If we pull this off...
No, not "if."
We're going to do this.
Then we'll have a nice long smoke with Bro.
Then all seven of us will meet up...
under that tree where we carved our dreams.
It hurts! It hurts!
Are you okay, Joe?!
Guards! This is an emergency!
Dr. Sasaki, I'm coming in!
This is Yokosuka Jou from cell 2-6.
He's come down with a stomach ache.
If it's nothing serious, we can just give him some medicine and send him back.
W-Wait, let me take a look first.
What do you think, Doctor?
Well, hmm.
Let's see.
Just to be safe, we should keep him here overnight.
Really? Got it.
All right, I'm leaving him to you.
Okay, Yokosuka.
Why are you pretending to be sick?
Are you after tobacco? Or maybe speed?
If I do exactly what you say, I can get out early, right?
Well...
Of course.
Then, I'll do whatever you want.
Really?
Yes.
Then what are we wait-
Just a minute, please!
This is my first taste of freedom in a while. I'll be more relaxed after a good meal.
Okay, Doctor?
Yeah, of course.
Of all the times to fall asleep...
I wonder if Joe's okay.
What if-
Don't even think about that, Turtle.
I'm sure he'll do it exactly like Uncovered planned.
All we can do now is believe in him.
Is that enough, Yokosuka?
I can't wait anymore!
C'mon!
Okay. You're right.
Wait for me in bed, Doctor.
I'm turning off the lights.
Hurry up!
Don't tease me anymore, Jou!
Okay, Doctor.
Now!
I'm gonna strangle you!
Don't show me your ugly body, you perverted old bastard!
Who'd want to do it with you?
When I'm through with you,
they'll laugh at you for the rest of your life!
Sorry to keep you waiting, guys.
It's your turn, Mario.
Joe!
You're okay!
There's no way I'd let that old man work on me.
All right, let's go save Bro.
Yeah!
Almost!
You're almost dead!
Go to hell, Sakuragi!
It's you!
Let's hurry, Mario.
Bro!
We came for you, Bro.
Mario...
Your hand...
Don't worry about it.
Let's go, Bro.
We're all busting out of here!
Are you okay, Mario?
Isn't he too heavy for you with your injuries?
He's light.
What made Bro this light?
Mario holds bitterness in his heart.
He swears that someday he'll make Sasaki and Ishihara pay for what they've done.
Soon we'll be outside these walls!
We'll be free to do anything!
Is someone there?
D-Dr. Sasaki!
Mario. Soldier. This is good enough.
Bro...
He's pretty weak. We've got to hurry.
A guard's passing by up ahead.
If he spots us, it's all over.
All seven of us need to make it out.
What's that, Uncovered?
If we get spotted, it'll slow the guards chasing us.
Just to be safe.
Wow, Uncovered. You really are a genius.
I'm glad you're our friend.
Yeah, you're awesome!
Yeah!
Aw, c'mon, guys.
Wait, are you blushing?
Escapees!
There's a breakout from cell 2-6!
Lock the gates!
I won't let you get away.
You're not getting away!
They're on to us!
This is too soon.
What do we do?
What do we do, Uncovered?
Uncovered!
I never expected them to catch on this quickly.
What do I do?!
How do we make it to the gates?
Uncovered...
Uncovered!
They need... me.
They need me.
Don't panic!
Leave it to me!
Uncovered...
Mario, take care of Bro.
If you let them get Bro, I'm never gonna forgive you.
Turtle!
Once you get out, find me a woman out there!
I don't wanna die a virgin!
Uncovered, are you-
I thought this might happen.
Anyway, leave it to me!
Wait!
Hey, Uncovered!
That idiot!
We don't have time to be angry!
We've got to do something about Bro!
There he is!
Over here!
Wait!
Stop!
I understand now.
We can't pull this plan off without sacrifices.
Bro's the first person to ever call me "friend."
I'm going to save him!
Live, Bro!
Wh-What?! What happened?
A blackout?
Did Uncovered do this?
All right, now's our chance!
This brat!
The others are probably still around here.
All right, find them!
Yes, sir!
Run...
Run!
I may have been the first one to get caught, but I've done my part.
Even in baseball, someone has to make a sacrifice.
I'm always the one that gets caught.
Yeah. Nomoto Ryuji is just the name my parents put on my birth certificate.
They always find me out!
That's why I'm Uncovered! Understand?
Haven't you caught the others yet?
Not yet. It's too dark.
They're trying to escape.
Search for them near the gate.
No, the back gate.
They'll have to try the back gate, because it's not guarded.
That's probably what they're thinking.
I see.
Everyone, head to the back gate!
I don't want to go out the back.
Why, Mario?
There are no guards back-
Bro's behaved himself for two years.
I don't want him to sneak out the back.
He's not escaping. He's being released.
I want him to walk out the front gates a free man.
I didn't think there'd only be two guards here.
Mario. Joe. Hold them down.
Hurry, Soldier.
Of course.
Dammit.
Is this it?
Nope.
Not this one, either.
Shit!
What are you doing, Soldier?!
Damn you!
Hurry up, Soldier! They're coming!
Which one is the key to the gate?!
There they are! At the gate!
Mario! Take care of Bro!
I'm kinda dumb, so this is all I can do.
Cabbage...
C-Cabbage...
Bro!
Hold it right there, you damn kids!
Cabbage!
I'm not letting you by!
Move it!
Even if I die, I'm not letting you pass!
Cabbage...
It's open!
All right!
Hey, Mario!
What are you doing, Mario?!
Cabbage is-
Mario! Worry about Bro now!
I broke the key.
They won't be able to get out the front gate for a while.
Soldier! Why...
Go.
I'll bring Cabbage along...
to where we promised.
Soldier...
Dammit! Get off me!
I'm with you, Cabbage.
I can't work out if you're not there.
S-Soldier...
So, Bro, how do you like the air outside?
We've saved Bro. Right, Mario?
Right.
Bro's free now.
Uncovered... Cabbage... Soldier...
They all risked their lives to save mine.
I won't let you take it.
Die, Sakuragi!
Ishihara!
If it wasn't for you... If it wasn't for you...!
I'm going to kill you!
Mario! Bro's hurt!
Bro!
We've got to get him to a doctor.
What comes next in Uncovered's plan?
Nothing.
It ends with us escaping.
I see.
Now it's our turn!
Everyone risked their lives for Bro.
But when I could've protected him, I wasn't able to.
What are you doing, Mario?!
This is no time to space out!
We've got to keep going!
Quit worrying about it, Mario.
Without you, we wouldn't even have tried to break out.
Yeah, even though it didn't go like we planned.
Bro is still breathing, thanks to you.
Give me a turn, Joe.
I'll carry Bro.
Bro isn't dead yet.
He's out on the streets. He's free.
No villains are seeking his life.
Mario hopes that a better life is in store for Bro.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
A brief calm respite from life on the run.
Mario enters the ring to earn a living.