[GINKO] From the beginning,
we hated you,
but also we loved you
from the beginning, as well.
All we wanted was to become
true friends with you,
so we had to cross the wall.
[YURIIKA] A bear has crossed
the Wall of Severance,
our only line of defense.
Tragically, Sumika Izumino
lost her life to that bear.
At this time,
we have been unable
to reach Katyusha Akae
and Konomi Yurikawa,
along with several other
students from our school.
[STUDENTS murmuring]
The fact is, we face
our greatest crisis
since the Day of Severance.
That being said, a bear
was shot last night
that we believe to
have been the invader,
but we mustn't let
our guard down.
It's important for
you all to understand
that the friends
sitting next to you
are the keys to your
protection from here on out.
Never be alone for a moment,
even on school grounds.
Ladies, you must
protect each other.
There is no other way.
[MITSUKO] Don't worry.
I'll be the one to protect you.
[gasps]
Is something wrong?
I can't, I'm sorry.
But why not?
What about yesterday?
Yesterday? I think
you got the wrong idea.
Fine, be that way.
It's your decision.
[MITSUKO] Damn it.
She rejected me?
It's okay, though.
It's okay.
The truth is I kind of
like this side of her.
The fun's only beginning,
Kureha Tsubaki.
I'm gonna work
you over real good,
and then I'll eat
you right on up.
[GINKO, LULU]
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Arashi!
[YURIIKA] How are you?
Have you calmed down a bit?
[KUREHA]
Yes, ma'am.
[YURIIKA]
Liar.
[KUREHA]
What?
[YURIIKA laughs]
[YURIIKA] You're not
very good at it, though.
Reia was like that,
too, honest to a fault.
[KUREHA]
Reia? You mean my mom?
[YURIIKA]
I do.
My, you remind me of that girl.
So much like your mother.
[YURIIKA] You mustn't
suffer in silence, Kureha.
The more you try to hide the
pain of losing a loved one,
the more that pain will grow
and become unbearable.
Unfortunately, I know
this all too well myself.
[gasps]
Your mother? I lost
Reia that day, too.
She was such a wonderful person.
She was my best friend,
and I'll never have another
like her again. Never.
That's why I was so happy
when you came to this school.
And when you decided to bring
the flowerbed back to life,
it touched my heart.
I'm sure you didn't realize
that place held special
memories for Reia and me.
[KUREHA]
I hate bears.
[YURIIKA]
Yes, so do I.
After all, they took the ones
we loved away from us.
There's another bear.
[YURIIKA]
What?
There's another bear
still out there!
But how? Wasn't the bear that
attacked Sumika taken care of?
I thought your friend
Mitsuko killed it?
--[thud]
--[gasps]
She only killed one!
I saw them! Two bears!
I'm positive it's in this
school. It has to be here!
That bear is somewhere close!
Too close!
[MITSUKO]
This school set up
really is an excellent
system for me.
All I have to do is
hang out here for a while
and wait for the right
opportunity to present itself.
[MITSUKO giggles]
[ERIKO]
Hey, Mitsuko!
I wanna volunteer.
I was thinking since
Konomi's missing
that maybe I could
fill in for her today.
That's a great idea, Eriko!
Class friendship
naturally starts
with individual
responsibility.
The leadership you're showing
is awesome. Keep it up.
[gasps]
[MITSUKO] Strong people
are beautiful people.
[ERIKO]
Uh, thank you, Mitsuko.
We should be best friends.
[ERIKO sighs]
[FEMALE VOICE]
♪ Yuri ga aku. ♪
[MITSUKO] There's my good girl.
I can't waste any more time.
I need to eat Kureha Tsubaki
as soon as possible!
[gasps]
Growl?
There's one more bear.
I know it.
[gunshot]
[KUREHA]
I'll never forgive the bears.
I'll ruin them. Every one!
[gunshots continue]
[LULU]
Growl. Look at that girl.
She's totally itching
to shoot a bear.
This sucks, the only reason
we came here tonight
was to beat that sticky,
icky Mitsuko Yurizono
to the dinner punch!
But we can't get
close to her, now!
[LULU cries]
So stupid. Who knew there'd be
a rival bear at that school?
Punch, punch.
Saw through our disguises,
too! Punch, punch!
Delicious smell. Growl, growl.
Aw, jeez. You're so not even
listening to me, Ginko!
Kureha Tsubaki must
be the tastiest girl
in the whole world, huh?
[TEACHER] Pope Urban the
Second's moving sermon
at the Council of Clermont
proved to be highly effective,
summoning the armies
of kings and nobility
across most of Western Europe.
This effort formed the first
army of crusaders in 1096.
Thus began a long
series of wars
in an attempt to regain the
Holy Land from the Seljuk Turks.
Here, I think you
forgot something.
[gasps]
[SUMIKA]
Uh.
[giggles]
[TEACHER] All right, girls,
guess what will be on the test.
[STUDENTS]
Please, not this!
[TEACHER]
Are you kidding me?
I'm not just talking
to hear myself.
[STUDENTS giggling]
[KUREHA]
Oh, Sumika.
The time moves so slowly when
you're not in class with me.
[TEACHER] What this means
is that the Crusades
exposed the people
of Western Europe
to the drastically different...
[KUREHA] Will I start
to forget everything now?
Forget that day, that moment?
Will I eventually forget love,
and be invisible
just like everyone else?
[SUMIKA]
Your mother's flowerbed?
[KUREHA] Yeah, mom told me that
back when she was a student here
she built it with her
best friend at the time.
[SUMIKA]
Ah, so that's why you love it.
Of course. I want to fill it
with lots of flowers again
because I think she'd like it.
That's so sweet. You didn't
give up on her love either, huh?
Never.
[SUMIKA]
Your mother's precious garden.
It's like your love for her.
Uhh. Like my love how?
It's beautiful.
And that's why I'm not
gonna give up either.
Not on you. Not on my
precious love. Our love.
[KUREHA]
I won't forget.
I'll never forget.
Sumika, I swear I'll
never give up on love.
Attention, ladies!
Above all things we
must remain invisible!
The time has come to begin
the Exclusion Ceremony.
Friends are more important
than anything else, agreed?
The friends here in this
classroom right now are Us.
We are Us.
Those who dare to
contradict Our feelings
are nothing but a disgrace.
As are those who want to
stick out from our crowd.
The ones that refuse to
fit in with Us are a nuisance.
People like that, those who
don't follow social cues
are evil.
Sumika Izumino
was eaten by a bear
because she was one of them.
It's only natural, after all.
People who are evil get killed.
We're here to decide who
that next evil will be
so we can exclude them.
Let's search evil!
[MITSUKO]
Select!
The moment has finally come!
I'm going to eat that girl.
Kureha, you're mine.
Slurp.
[BOTH growling]
[REIA] Kureha, did you have fun
with your friend again today?
Aww, you really love her,
don't you, sweetie?
[REIA] I want you to know as
long as you don't forget love,
you'll never, ever be alone.
Just remember that, okay?
Right.
If I don't forget about love,
I won't really be alone.
[ANCHORWOMAN] That's correct,
a storm and flood warning
has just been issued for
the greater metro area.
We're seeing
violent rain and wind.
Residents in the
following districts
have been advised to evacuate.
If this applies to you,
evacuate immediately...
Oh, no, I gotta
protect the flowerbed!
[SUMIKA grunting]
[gasps]
You came out, too.
[KUREHA]
Aren't you cold?
[SUMIKA] I'm perfect
since you're here with me.
[KUREHA]
I, um, I just wanna say...
...thank you, for being
my friend, I mean.
[SUMIKA]
Uhh.
Sure, and thanks
for being mine, too.
[KUREHA] I won't do it.
I won't back down on love.
[MITSUKO]
To live is simple.
One must continually forget,
back down, and cast away.
[scissors snip]
[MITSUKO] Those who cannot
replace the old with the new
will eventually perish.
Beasts like us never live
in the past, after all.
The only thing that
exists is the present.
Emotions we feel in the now.
The mood, the rhythm of this
moment. That is everything.
[MITSUKO] The invisible ones
think they're in control,
but they can only decide
how to run closed worlds.
[growling]
[LULU]
Oh, Ginko.
Lulu will never forget the
wonderful day she met you.
Do you remember?
That was when you found her
love. You brought it to her.
So no matter what happens,
Lulu won't ever give up on love.
It seems the time for
judgment has come.
Growl, growl.
Yes?
[LIFE SEXY]
Is your love the real thing?
[KUREHA]
You bet it is.
[LIFE SEXY] This is a challenge
from the Wall of Severance.
Kureha Tsubaki,
if your love is true,
go to the roof immediately.
The bears are waiting for you.
Give yourself over to the bears,
and your love will be approved.
[KUREHA]
I'll never forgive the bears.
I'll ruin them. Every one.
[MITSUKO] I've been waiting
for you, my dear Kureha.
[KUREHA] Mitsuko?
What are you doing here?
[MITSUKO] Getting ready
to eat you, of course.
[gasps]
[MITSUKO]
So, I've got some information
you might want to know.
I'm the one who ate your
beloved Sumika Izumino.
Yes, it was me.
I'm a big bad bear.
[KUREHA]
What are you talking about?
[MITSUKO] This is probably
hard for you to believe,
but it is the truth.
To be specific, I'm a bear who's
just pretending to be human.
[KUREHA]
A bear pretending to be human?
You got it! Wanna know
who that bear I shot was?
Konomi Yurikawa!
[KUREHA]
Konomi?
But... I thought she was your--
What, my friend?
Well, I suppose
technically she was.
She obeyed me at least, and
that was pretty swell of her.
[gasps]
[MITSUKO] Let me give you
a piece of advice.
Whenever you're deciding
to be friends with someone,
it's imperative to
make sure the lucky girl
is just a little bit
inferior to you.
They're always so much
easier to control that way.
You don't have to look so
incredulous. Okay, fine.
If you need proof I'm telling
the truth, I can give it to you.
[KUREHA gasps]
Wait, those are Sumika's.
Uh-huh. I take it
you finally believe me.
I'm telling you,
that girl was a freak job.
I mean, there she was,
literally being eaten alive,
and yet, all she did
was worry about you.
[gasps]
[MITSUKO]
I'm sorry. Oh, Kureha!
I can't fix your love now,
or your mother's flowerbed.
And I promised I wouldn't
back down, too.
I hope you can forgive me
one day, Kureha!
I'm sorry. I'm so, so sorry!
[gunshot]
[KUREHA crying]
Oh, come on, as if you
have it in you to shoot me.
Yeah, that rage there in your
eyes is the reason I love you.
In fact, it's really starting
to get me off. So hot.
And your blood, I can
sense it furiously boiling
its way through your veins.
Your scent is amazing.
I can hardly stand what
I'm smelling off you.
Come on, get angrier for me.
[gasps]
I'll never forgive the bears!
I'll ruin them.
I swear. Every one!
I already said it once.
You simply don't have
it in you to kill me.
[MITSUKO]
Grawr, grawr.
Grararawr!
No way! This can't be happening!
--Such bad aim.
--[gunshot]
Missed me again.
--What a shock,
--[gunshot]
--you missed me again.
You keep missing me!
Rawr, rawr, rawr!
[MITSUKO chuckling]
[MITSUKO] Don't worry. I have a
plan to make everything better!
[gasps]
[MITSUKO] In place of the
Sumika I ate, I'll love you!
[KUREHA gasps]
[screaming]
[GINKO, LULU]
We want to eat that girl!
We want to eat her
right this minute!
[LIFE SEXY]
This court is now in session!
Let the Yuri Trial begin.
[GINKO] Your Honor,
we need Yuri approval, fast!
[LIFE SEXY grunts]
I want to save Kureha Tsubaki.
Growl, growl.
You say you want to
save Kureha Tsubaki,
well, that hardly makes sense.
Why? You two are bears!
Growl. We will still
eat humans, I promise!
If we don't eat them,
we can't protect Ginko's love!
Ah, so you're blatantly
admitting your crime
in a court of law, then?
Ha. Damn it, I'm cool.
Objection!
Surely you realize for a bear,
eating humans is hardly a crime!
Sparkle, sparkle!
[LIFE COOL growls]
[GINKO]
Please rule quickly!
We have to save her now.
[LIFE SEXY]
I see.
For that is sexy.
Shaba-da-doo.
Defendant bears, I ask you.
Do you want to be invisible?
Or would you rather eat humans?
We'll eat.
Bring on the humans!
[BOTH]
Growl, growl!
[LIFE SEXY] I am now ready
to declare the verdict.
Yuri approved!
[GINKO]
Growl, growl, growl!
Yuri approved!
[LULU]
Growly, growl, growl,
growly, growl, growl, growl!
[KUREHA]
I won't back down.
[gasps]
[KUREHA]
Where am I?
[KUREHA gasping]
You won't back down
on your love, Kureha.
Growl, growl.
We know the truth. Only love
can change the world.
Love can change the world?
Yes, love.
Your love.
[KUREHA]
What is this?
Their tongues feel rough,
but they're also warm and kind.
I've felt this
before, but where?
[GINKO, LULU]
Smooch.
Now, you can do it.
[KUREHA]
I can do it!
Give it to me,
the Promise Kiss!
[MITSUKO]
Grawr!
Grawrr-rr-rrr-rr-rr!
[thud]
[KUREHA]
I hit her. I think--
I think I killed her!
No, it can't be! A bear
in human form. No!
[gun clatters]
[ERIKO] What did you
want to talk to me about?
If it's the Exclusion Ceremony,
I'm sorry, but no can do.
You aren't allowed
to participate
because you can't be our friend
until you take part
in the Invisible Storm.
[GINKO]
I don't want to. Growl, growl.
[LULU]
Growl!
So instead, we'll tell you
something you'll want to know.
How's that sound, Eriko Oniyama?
[ERIKO]
What is it?
[LULU]
First answer this question.
Where do you think
your missing friends are?
[ERIKO] Missing friends?
You mean like Katyusha?
[GINKO]
They're right there.
[ERIKO]
Uh?
I don't-- What is this?
This is the place we
buried Katyusha Akae.
Well, the parts we didn't eat.
[LULU giggles]
[LULU]
Aren't we the best?
You what?
Are you saying that... that you
ate her? You ate my friend?
I don't understand. Why tell me?
[BOTH giggle]
[growling]
[LULU]
Growl.
Because guess what
we're gonna do!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Shock!
Kuma shock!
It's time to eat.
Slurp.