The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
My motorcycle engine roars as if it's singing a song.
Blow up louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Blow up louder!
Yagiri
Seiji
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Yagiri
Namie
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Heiwajima Shizuo
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Yumasaki
Walker
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Togusa
Saburo
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryuugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Kida
Masaomi
Anri
Sonohara
I think this is a sign that Biribiri's going to become the heroine!
You're...
Help me!
What are you going to do with a head that supposedly lives a life of its own?
I want to see her no matter what!
If I recall, those guys are from Yagiri Pharmacy.
Don't worry. Just leave everything to your sis.
To be honest, I was pretty skeptical...
All the cards are in my hand.
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Durarara!!
I have to go...
I have to go and get her back...
My sister won't be able to do it.
It...
It has to be me.
She wasn't there?!
That's right.
Apparently, the girl was already gone by the time they arrived.
The student who lives there...
His name is 'Ryuugamine' or something, right?
What about him?
They were going to hear what he had to say when he returned,
and if the situation was right, have him come here...
But apparently, he had people on his side...
Why didn't they just drag both him and his friends down here?
How useless.
What should we do now?
Hello?
Is this Yagiri Namie-san?
And you are?
My name...
is Ryugamine Mikado.
What do you say we make a deal?
Sturm und Drang
Man, I'm hungry.
My-
Welcome, welcome!
Russia Sushi is fantastic!
Cheap, too!
"What is life?"
"Why do people live?"
Someone asked me that, and I beat him within an inch of his life.
Definitely.
It would have been acceptable if he were a poet in middle school or something.
But that coming from a yakuza past his twenties is just criminal.
You're right.
You really don't understand what I'm saying, do you, Simon-san?
I totally agree.
Have I changed...
from spending twenty years in this city?
It wasn't for nothing.
What you've been doing for the past twenty years served a purpose.
As long as you make good use of the rest of your life, there isn't a single thing that was useless.
"Make good use of"?
And how do you suppose I do that?!
For example,
you should marry me.
Shinra...
Are you that Mikado-kun?
You seem a lot gentler than I'd imagined.
Or could it be that in today's world, people like you are the most dangerous?
So...
what is this 'deal' you speak of?
I have the person you're looking for.
Oh?
And how much would you like?
No, I don't need money.
Then what do you want?
The truth.
What did you just say?
I'd like you to acknowledge what your little brother did to Harima Mika-san...
and also what you all did to Mika-san's body.
Unfortunately, I only have circumstantial evidence.
I'll say this directly.
Please turn yourself in.
I see.
So that's the type of person you are.
Interesting...
I won't forgive you for getting in my brother's way.
You're not allowed to exist...
Those who get in my brother's way aren't allowed to exist!
Oh... so that's the type of person she is.
Hey, tell me.
Where's my sister?
I have to go.
'She' needs me.
'She' needs me by her side!
Hey...!
Tell me!
So that's the reason...
Someone died for a petty reason like that...
And did such a thing using her body...
And even going after me...
You took someone's life for a reason like that?
Do you plan to make Yagiri-kun miserable for your own pleasure?
What are you saying after all this time?
Poking your nose into a world like this at such an age...
It'll be okay, right?
If you're just going to tell a story that has already been told,
just shut that unpleasant mouth of yours.
As you say, I may just be saying the expected.
So what?!
The fact that one should reflect on is that murder isn't anything new.
Aren't you the one that doesn't understand the simplest things?!
You watch too many dramas.
All that comes out of your mouth are expected pre-established harmonies.
This is reality, you know?
This will work, right?
We're not part of a film set.
You're no hero.
Know your place!
And what's wrong with that?!
What's wrong with pre-established harmonies and the expected?!
And opportunism and forced happy endings?! I love them all!
What's wrong with having those as my goal?!
I won't go as far as to say that it's for the sake of others or the world.
It's just that I want to see them happen!
I want to believe!
That's right. I believe.
I believe in them.
They'll surely...
As you say, these may just be your ordinary, run-of-the-mill views and ideas.
But if something is commonplace, it just shows how much people think about stuff like that!
Is that all you have to say?
I don't have the strength or wisdom to stand up against someone who is insusceptible to reason.
You won't even give me time to make an effort.
That's why...!
I'm going to rely on numbers!
What?!
Amazing!
Are all these due to that?!
Incredible!
It's almost like the supernatural from "Missing"!
You have mail, young master.
Wanna try to die once?
Here it is!
Seriously?
Okay...
I'll leave the rest to you, Togusa.
Sure.
Let's go.
I wonder just how many there are!
Wow, I'm surprised so many people gathered for the first ever meeting!
So this is...
the Dollars?!
TL Note: Watch Baccano!
NE, AIZAKKU!
NANDAI, MIRIA?
Are these people a part of the Dollars too?
That's exactly right, Miria!
Wow!
Listen well.
Now we're a part of the group that the hipsters of the street spread rumors about!
What's this?
Don't tell me, these people are all...!
You've... You've got to be kidding!
Oh my!
Even though we all just met for the first time today?!
Sugooooooi!
The sky in my hometown was seemingly endless.
But...
there was nothing to see.
When I was a kid, even a town like this was filled with adventures.
I wonder... when I started to feel like this.
I wanted to change something.
But I didn't have a reason or the courage to leap out.
And that was when...
Twice... twice...
There were many different worlds spread across the internet.
Worlds that I was unaware of, and those I couldn't reach.
I started to get in touch with Kida-kun, who moved to Tokyo.
I made new friends, too.
One day, a thought crossed my mind.
Although it was nothing but a joke at first.
A team?
Yeah.
I've heard that there are many teams in Tokyo.
So you're going to make an online team?
No, I'm actually going to make people believe that it exists in reality.
I'll say that the team exists in Ikebukuro,
and I'll spread those rumors online...
We didn't actually reveal that we're a part of the Dollars.
We spread rumors as though we heard it from somewhere else, and quickly spread the name.
I've heard that the leader is an ex-CIA special intelligence operative, and is an Arabian oil baron.
No, he's a famous screenwriter and Dollars itself is a giant preparation. True story.
I even made a site for the team.
Completely restricted with a password.
I leaked the password via email and various message boards.
I also fabricated many posts from 'members' on the message board.
Naturally, a lot of people didn't believe it.
Soon enough, there were people that started to defend us.
Everyone was so happy.
I had a bad feeling...
People started to call themselves the Dollars in the real world.
That's not all.
The number of members was also increasing before I knew it.
Even though we stopped leaking the password...
It was almost as if someone out there was leaking information...
Can everyone see this?
Yoooo...
They may have gotten scared.
The people with whom I created the Dollars all disappeared.
But even then, I didn't stop.
No, it's that I couldn't stop.
I don't know why, either.
But...
That's not true.
There may be some bad people,
but I know there are many who aren't.
Why don't those of us just make Dollars into a group filled with good people?
We can do something so good that it would wipe away the memories the public has of those who do bad things.
We could go and pick up trash,
or go and clean up graffiti...
And so, the people living here were stunned.
There was graffiti on this wall until late last night,
but in the morning, it was all gone.
It was such large-scale graffiti that it would be almost impossible for one person to be responsible for the cleanup.
The people living around here are very confused...
It couldn't be.
I came to Tokyo after being invited by Kida-kun.
And there...
Dollars?
I don't know much about the details either,
but apparently there are a lot of them.
I heard they're part of the color gangs,
but no one knows what color they represent.
You shouldn't go near them out of mere curiosity.
Don't go around trying to investigate them.
But the strongest in this city right now would have to be the Dollars, don't you think?
So, what are the Dollars like?
Well, if I had to put it into words... 'colorless.'
Dollars?
Of course I've heard of them.
Actually, I'm a part of them.
I found a girlfriend after joining the Dollars!
Posting random crap on message boards...
Someone always responds.
Once you get old like me, there's no other way to bond with others apart from work.
Did you hear?
Apparently, the Dollars rescued someone from that rumored kidnapper!
Dollars is awesome!
I don't know...
It's fun, so I guess it's fine?
This is more than I expected.
This is fun.
The people who aren't looking at the text on their phones right now are our enemies. Don't attack them; simply stare at them.
So fun!
What?
What?!
What are these people?!
Hey, which one do you think is the Dollars' founder?
Do you see anyone who looks like an Arab oil baron?
Nope.
Togusa-san, the person who responded to us is the real founder, right?
Yeah...
apparently.
Togusa!
You're running red lights! Red lights!!
A person of few words, eh?
Dotachin! Dotachin!
I keep telling you not to call me that...
Look!
Someone replied to a thread on the Dollars' message board!
I've mapped out a plan.
I'll let you see her.
But in return, I want your help as well.
Selty.
He's gone...!
Pay attention!
Hurry up and look for him!
Yes, ma'am!
Move!
Where did he go?!
Dammit!
Move!
Where did he go?!
I've come to my senses!
Huh?
Who's talking?
That's right. I don't have a head!
I'm a monster!
I don't have a mouth to speak, nor do I possess eyes to display passion to others!
I can hear something.
Whose voice is that?
So what?!
Selty...
I'm right here.
I exist.
Who the hell are you?!
You-
Hey-
If you say I don't have eyes, stare at my behavior with keen interest!
Die-
Hear the cries of those who angered a monster!
Th-The Headless Rider...
It's the Headless Rider.
That?
That's the Headless Rider?!
I'm right here.
That's right... I'm here.
I'm already screaming.
Screaming!
I was born right here and now!
In order to carve my existence into this city!
Are you Ryugamine Mikado?
Give...
Give back Selty!
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My dear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My dear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My dear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Durarara!!
Next Time
Being and Non-Being Mutually Exist
That's right.
I've discovered one truth in this city.
I've discovered something so run-of-the-mill so easily.
My guess is, that boy has also...
Next time: Being and Non-Being Mutually Exist.