Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Kagami, good morning!
Yo.
You're in a good mood.
What happened?
I got a new cell phone.
Finally, huh?
Seriously?
So you can have real ringtones and use screensavers now, right?
You're just like a kid!
What, you watch anime and stuff then?
I already have my favorites in.
Mi-Miracle! Mikurun-run!
Love Lege
Mikuru Asa
That's some song.
But you know,
you have to pick up before it gets to the best part.
It's rather unfortunate and stressful.
And if you don't pick it up, the person hangs up.
I don't really care, but...
...is that how it is?
Ring
If I had to guess, I'd say Kagami is...
An orc!
Why am I the only one who's a monster!?
Yes, hello?
This is Hiiragi.
Yeah...
It's a habit from answering the phone at home.
She was just throwing her anger onto me a second ago...
Today's was a sandwich with balsamic vinegar...
How can women switch modes so quickly like that?
But the other day, my mother...
I've returned home.
Yes?
Hello?
Eh, Miyuki?
Geez...
Here Miyuki, the telephone!
It's Konata-chan!
U-Um, did I say something wrong?
Oh, no.
My mother wears her heart on her sleeve,
so you can tell when she's mad.
It seems she kicked the leg of a desk.
But I don't think that was necessarily an example of her inability to hide her emotions...
She's exactly the way she seems.
It's a good think Miyuki knows so much,
it helps me out quite a bit.
I can just ask you about anything I don't know.
I was so happy to be praised by you...
...that looking things up became a habit.
Miyuki-chan, you know more than Mama does.
And now I enjoy learning, too.
So in other words,
I did a wonderful job of raising you, right?
That's how the conversation went.
What a raw conversation.
All I can say is that you are undeniably your mother's daughter.
I can see the similarities.
You think so?
Down to the very last gene.
But...
Miyuki isn't just good at studying.
She knows a lot about all kinds of stuff.
There are many sources of information these days,
and it's fun to learn new things.
I could never do that.
No motivation!
I want to play!
When I'm in trouble, I just rely on others!
They say that the only child and the eldest child tend to be selfish, but...
Speaking of which,
you're an only child, right Miyuki?
You're both the only child, yet you're so different.
Not at all.
You could say I had a role model...
...or someone who was like an older sister...
...in my life.
I don't wanna clean.
Laundry is tiring.
Can we have takeout tonight?
At our house,
we have two older sisters...
...so there's always a fight at dinner.
But I guess that's what builds character.
Yay, sukiyaki!
Eat up, okay?
I'm digging it!
And then,
Kona-chan said that...
...your cell goes out of service because the high density of the something particles.
Really...
And when the batteries in her phone run out...
...she calls it "perfect silence".
I see...
Kids nowadays use some interesting language.
Hey, leave some for Tsukasa, too.
Tsukasa, you can have mine.
Thanks.
So you say, but weren't you stuffing yourself earlier?
So there are pros and cons to having lots of siblings, huh?
You can say the same thing about being an only child as well.
That's right.
Yuki-chan, you tend to space out sometimes, don't you?
Space out?
You know, like the other day...
I never get tired of the name "elegant sea urchin".
What happened?
I was thinking while walking...
...and ran into the door.
That's some amazing concentration, Miyuki-san.
You do that a lot.
It's rather embarrassing.
But...
...doesn't the fact that you start thinking about something,
while doing something else, mean you can't concentrate?
Huh?
Which is it?
That does seem like something Miyuki would do.
That's true.
The other day I was warming up something to drink, when...
Oh no, I forgot about it!
I'll have to warm it up again.
Many minutes later-
Once more...
And again...
Oh Miyuki...
You forgot about it again, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
I just...
You're so helpless.
Mom will bring it up for you.
Thank you very much.
Just a bit.
Many minutes later-
I forgot all about it!
Like mother, like daughter.
Though it's rather embarrassing.
Miyuki-san, when did you start wearing glasses?
Halfway through elementary school, I believe.
So you weren't born nearsighted.
When I was little...
...I loved how my mother would read me bedtime stories.
But my mother would always fall asleep first,
so I would continue to read by myself in the dark room.
I guess that's what did it...
But it's best when you're close to your parents like that.
They say the reason children these days are cold and apathetic...
...may be due to a lack of parental love or intimacy.
Speaking of which,
I wonder when was the last time Mommy gave me a big hug?
You were pretty spoiled...
I think Mom clung onto you until sometime around middle school.
Eh, really?
Maybe that's why you're such a good girl.
My dad is still clingy about me.
Maybe that's why, in a manner of speaking, you haven't grown up.
Speaking of children,
there have been a lot of cases involving kidnappings and confinement lately.
You seem to be sensitive about that sort of thing.
Well, I'm more worried about my dad.
Don't just blurt out such scary things.
Well, I suppose it has something to do with the games he plays.
I wish they'd stop if it's going to cause problems for other users.
At the very least...
...I don't have to worry about that kind of stuff in the games I play.
Oh yeah, it's almost been a year.
Since what?
Since I started my part-time job.
My coworkers said they want to do something to celebrate.
That's right, we've never seen you at work,
maybe we should take a peek sometime.
As payback for New Year's.
Sure!
Sure!?
Isn't this the part where people normally say, "No"?
But half of my job is being in the spotlight.
It's called a cosplay café, right?
But give me a call before you come...
...because it can get pretty crowded sometimes.
We'll do that.
Hey, you guys.
Class has already started!
Hello?
We just left the station.
Huh?
Okay, okay...
We'll buy it for you.
Okay, okay.
Did Kona-chan say it was all right?
It's fine...
But she wanted me to get this month's Comptiq...
...and the Lelou** comic for her.
I wonder if we'll be able to find it quickly.
She said to also remember to ask the clerk to stamp the receipt.
Sounds complicated.
Excuse me, do you have a minute?
Can I take a picture?
Eh?
But I'm not Kamigishi...
I'm Hiiragi.
Hey, you!
What are you doing!?
Could I get a picture, too?
Stop that!
Then, excuse me.
Could you say "Hiroyuki-chan"?
H-Hiroyuki-chan?
We're leaving!
This is the first time I've been in one of these places.
It's so spacious that it makes me feel uneasy.
She told me on the phone that it'd be easy to find once we got here but...
I guess it's easy for Kona-chan.
I would probably get lost if I was alone.
This is it.
Now, for the Lelou** comic.
It's not here.
I can't find it.
Excuse me, where can I find the Lelou** comic?
That would be right here.
Code Ge**s?
You could have at least given us the title so we'd know...
Can I put this on the point-card next time I come?
Then please bring it in with this receipt.
Okay.
Thank you very much!
Now we just have to go and see Kona-chan.
Onee-chan, I'm hungry!
I'm almost done with work, so just wait a little, okay?
How are we supposed to get there with this?
Here
Gamers
How are we supposed to get there with this?
I actually looked it up just in case...
I believe it's this way.
That's Yuki-chan for you!
I guess you're the only one we can count on.
This is the place, right?
Yes, on the 3rd floor.
Welcome back, master!
Please have a seat right here.
The first hour is 800 yen.
All the soda you can drink.
You can play as many games as you want,
and eat as many snacks as you want, too.
Can I get this eel on rice?
Currently unavailable.
Huh.
The shrimp pilaf then.
Currently impossible.
Eh?
Then, I'll take the spaghetti in meat sauce.
ETA is fifteen minutes.
Permission?
All right.
Do it.
How can they make money like that?
You people!
Eh?
So what do you want to drink?
H-Hold on a sec!
Hurry it up!
There's a fine if you take too long.
A fine!
Is that how you treat your customers?
It's how we do things around here.
You've decided already, right?
I'll have a melon soda.
I have no interest in ordinary menus.
Eh?
I'll have milk tea.
What do you want?
I'm deciding right now!
A brigade member shouldn't be this slow!
Since when did I become a brigade member?
That's the setting here.
You're a hundred years too early to be defying your chief!
How cumbersome...
Just give me an ice coffee then.
Orders from the chief.
Wait right here!
Oh boy...
And it hasn't stunk in a while...
We're going to be on the stage now, so watch!
nazo nazo mitai ni chikyuugi wo tokiakashitara
If we can solve all the mysteries on this planet...
minna de doko made mo ikeru ne
...we can all go anywhere we want!
jikan no hate made
Even to the end of time!
Boooon!!
Encore! Encore!
Encore, encore!
Amazing!
They're all very talented.
Woot, woot!
Ponytail version next!
This girl is an exchange student.
A first year at our school.
My name is Patricia Martin.
Nice to meet you.
We've even put out our own CD.
Konata and Patty
Look!
Cos it! Oh My Honey
Konata and Patty
Should you be releasing something like that?
Excuse me, could I get some more tea?
Do you want that hot?
Yes, hot please.
Could I have more melon soda please?
Understood.
Uh, what is this "House Mix Juice Juice" like?
Classified information.
House rules!
This café really tires me...
NURSE'S OFFICE
M-My height...
Do not worry.
I'm sure you'll grow in time.
Y-Yeah, right?
Oh, Onee-chan~
Oh, Yu-chan!
A person who could destroy my hopes appears!
O-Onee-chan, how much have you grown since entering high school?
Not only have I not grown taller, I haven't grown sideways either.
You'd better be prepared, Yu-chan.
Eh!?
Touch
No lumps, no bumps...
But still in demand.
Hey you two,
have you ever been to a class reunion?
Not yet.
Me either.
But why do you ask so suddenly?
You hear it often, but when someone says, "You haven't changed at all,"
it's supposed to be a compliment, right?
But the only people that want to hear that are the ones that have changed considerably.
In various places...
So it does concern you.
Okay, Golden Week is right around the corner,
but listen up!
You all have tests when you come back...
But don't forget the fact that you're also preparing for exams,
so spend your vacation wisely.
And also...
You still have a few days of school left before break.
So don't try to call in sick, or I'm going to call you out.
Kamchatka!
That aura emitting from her entire body...
There's no mistake.
She's Legendary Girl A.
Is today's target that new volume?
Or is it some goods?
Use your head!
Do not forget we're in the middle of a spring audio/visual festival!
Not yet!
Lure her in more.
Then recommend an item once her guard is down.
That's right, wait for her to close in...
That's it!
Now!
Approach her!
Here I go!
Welcome!
We just got these in!
Mi-Miracle...
Oh, Kagami?
You're here?
Be right there.
Just killing time until your friend came!?
When you're boiling something,
you roughly cut them diagonally into random shapes.
My, is that so?
When you do that, the total surface area increases...
...and it makes it easier to bring out the flavor.
After you scoop out the lye,
you set the fire to medium heat, then let it cook for about 10 minutes.
If you cook it too long, it'll become soggy,
so make sure you stir and take it out once it's done.
I see.
Somehow it's weird that Miyuki seems below average...
...when it's time for home economics.
I can understand how you see us now.
Hiiragi-chan.
Want to help each other by studying for the test together in the library?
Okay, sure.
Whenever tests come near, club activities are canceled,
so there's nothing to do.
That's why you're supposed to study...
Isn't that why the clubs take a break in the first place?
Well I know that, but...
When my time, that is usually spent doing club activities is suddenly gone,
It's like a whole new world has opened up.
When you think of it that way, you can't waste your time studying...
It's such a waste.
It gets me all excited.
Well, please be aware that you're half the reason for this study group.
I'm tired!
That was fast!
Let's take a break!
Maybe you can't concentrate because you don't have any goals?
Don't you have any dreams for the future?
Dreams?
Not much about my future...
But right around now, haven't you guys ever thought about winning the lottery...
...and living the rest of your years out peacefully?
Life's a drag.
Minegishi, do something about her!
When you're using your brain,
you need something sweet!
When we're done, I'll bring the cookies I baked the other day,
so hang in there.
Minegishi, you bake sweets?
Can't compare with that Ajiyoshi boy though.
Nah, it's totally better than that Ajiyoshi, boy.
Studying is such a pain!
Onee-chan, I tried making some madeleines.
What's the matter?
Ah no, I was just thinking...
I wouldn't put you in the same category as them,
but I was wondering if I tend to make friends with certain types of people...
"Have you ever been negligent...
...just because you thought it was an ordinary stomatitis?"
Lately, there have been a lot more medical dramas like these.
You're right.
It's scary because it could happen to you...
Especially for me.
Actually, after watching stuff like this,
it makes you feel like your time has almost come.
There are so many causes.
Let's stop the negative talk.
I beg of you, live!
Ah, Onee-chan, can you teach me this part?
Hm?
Um...
"Curses, like chickens, come home to roost."
This means,
Kazu likes chickens.
And when he comes home he'll find roast chicken.
I think...
Ah!
Nee-san, can you translate the next part?
Let's see...
"When you make the contract..."
Did we ever learn this stuff?
Oh yeah,
the other day when I was working as a shrine maiden,
a foreigner was telling me about the origins of the torii.
Oh, what did he say?
A long time ago, they believed that birds carried the spirits of the dead,
so they named the gate tori-i because it was a place that allowed them to rest.
He knew a lot more about Japan than we do.
It might have been faster to ask Kagami-oneechan...
The freezing seas of Japan...
Where has my loved one gone?
Lucky * Channel
Production
Kogami Akira
BIG SHOW!!
Now she swims through the rough waves of the entertainment industry itself...
Here is her song.
Kogami Akira-san, singing "Misoji Misaki".
Hey!
How is this a concert?
This was the best we could do on our budget!
Don't think you can get away with-
It's starting!
Who do you think I am!
Would you mind...
If I talk to myself?
I softly murmured to the seagulls.
Woman, led by a sincere heart...
Frozen by the northern sea breeze.
Gone astray, love falls apart...
The drinks sure are taking a while...
Resentment crumbles...
Yes?
I've brought the drinks you ordered.
Unable to reach you...
Thanks.
So very far away.
Standing still, tears...
H-Hey, that brown one is mine!
Cape of Thirty Years!
Lucky * Channel
Production
Kogami Akira
BIG SHOW!!
That's the stuff!
That inn, with just the two of us...
Let's see, "Exhausting Life Returns" is...
Our eyes welled with tears.
That night we loved...
Is meaningless to regret.
Man, with his selfish promises...
Yet in the end nothing will have changed.
Yes?
Feelings thrown right into...
Ah, that's right.
Um, extension?
No, that's okay.
The spray of the waves.
Yes, thank you.
Five more minutes.
Longing for you, far in the distance...
Time to clean up, clean up...
Bye-bii!
I wish to offer you my love.
Man...
I wouldn't mind having a song of my own, too...
Soul of Thirty Years!
For-Forgot my something...
hitorigatari shite mo ii desu ka
Would you mind if I talked to myself?
kamome ni sotto tsubuyaita
I softly whispered to the seagulls.
onna ichizu na magokoro nosete
Woman, led by a sincere heart...
kita no umikaze itetsuita
Frozen by the northern sea winds.
hagure
Gone astray...
koichiru
Love falls apart...
uramibushi sae
Resentment crumbles...
tooi anta nya todokanai
Unable to reach you so far away...
tatazunde
I stand still...
nakinurete
Soaked in tears...
misoji misaki
Cape of Thirty Years!
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star is:
Hey, Nagato!
No one's gonna watch if you're like that!
You need to sound more like...
...a person happily moving from the TV to the tea room at 6:30 PM on a Sunday night.
Now, once more.
Action!
And next week on Lucky Star is:
That was exactly the same!
Forget it.
「 Under the Sun 」
Next week: "Under the Sun"
Look forward to it.
Just a bit more...
Er, I mean...
Rock, paper, scissors!