I've been thinking all this time about who I really am.
When Nana passed away, I felt so lonely and sad.
I started to wonder why I even exist.
And then I finally remembered.
I...
was just a Shadow in that world.
One day, a Shadow living in that
world awakened to human emotions.
He made himself forget that he was a Shadow.
He wanted people to like him,
and that's how he came to look like this.
But Shadows aren't allowed to stay in the human world.
Master,
when you meet Nana in Heaven, please apologize for me.
Tell her I'm sorry I couldn't do anything.
Teddie,
Nanako's alive.
R-Really?
Nana's...
Wow! That's wonderful!
Someone who meets all of the criteria must be here in this town.
The killer must have a connection to both Konishi and Ms. Yamano...
as well as be in a position to observe our actions periodically to some extent.
Finally, it must be someone who could approach your house without arousing suspicion.
We should review the information with everyone again.
Sorry, but I'm returning to the hospital.
Very well.
Take care of Nanako.
Yeah.
Yu!
We need to talk.
Well,
there's something I wanted to tell you.
What is it?
I...
Somewhere deep down,
I didn't trust you.
No, it's more like I was jealous of you.
Huh?
I thought you were like me.
Coming from the city to the countryside,
I thought you'd be bored out of your mind here.
But as soon as you got here, you called your Persona
and brought us together. You're a real hero.
I like you for that,
and I'm proud of you...
What is this about?
It's a problem with how I feel.
At this rate, I...
I won't be able to look you in the eye.
So, Yu...
I want you to hit me!
Huh? Why?
I think out of everyone,
I wanted to be acknowledged by you the most.
Give me a good one to knock out all this crap inside of me.
I want us to be equals, so c'mon...
Is that what you wanted?
That hurt!
This is my second time punching you.
Now that I think about it, this doesn't make us equals at all.
You may be right.
Aw, man!
I'm just going around in circles on my own again.
How humiliating!
Yosuke.
We'd be equals if we both hit each other.
I got it now.
I guess you're right.
Okay,
here I come!
Your punches are brutal.
I was seeing stars there for a second.
My bad.
But thanks, man.
I feel a lot better now.
I do too.
Let's go, Yosuke.
Sure thing, partner!
Chinese Diner
AIYA
He's the culprit?!
There's no way!
Naoto, are you serious?
I'm serious.
There's something that's been bothering me about him for some time now.
What would that be?
I'm not sure how to put it.
But if the possibility isn't zero, then we can't rule him out.
I get that, but...
But...
I mean, he said he came to escort Ms. Yamano and...
Are you certain?
I imagine he had contact with Konishi since she found Ms. Yamano's body.
Does that fit the criteria too?
Isn't that just a coincidence?
Narukami Yu
Ignore
Answer
Narukami Yu
Ignore
Answer
Narukami Yu
Starting with Amagi,
the people who went missing
had been thrown into the TV by Namatame who was disguised as a deliveryman.
Yeah. He came up to their front door and brazenly rang the doorbell.
But only Kubo Mitsuo testified about what happened when he went missing.
He blacked out in the police interrogation room when he turned himself in.
He turned himself in? I had no idea.
My uncle confirmed the story.
Apparently, no one took Kubo's confession seriously.
So that's when...
Kubo was investigated by...
Huh? What are you guys doing here?
Why do you look so angry?
Nanako's room isn't around here, right?
Hey, Adachi.
D-Dojima, what are you doing?!
You guys...
You shouldn't be up. You need your rest!
Adachi, where's Namatame?
Namatame's already been relocated.
I was looking for you so I could tell you that.
You did what?!
Hey, who authorized that?!
There's still more I need to ask him about!
G-Give me a break...
Those first two murders have been bothering me.
His motives are shaky,
and his alibi is rock solid.
Is this more of your "detective's intuition"?
But he's already been relocated.
It's no use hassling me about it.
And you kids should really get home, too.
You're getting in the way of police business.
What are you guys doing here?
We came to confirm something with Adachi.
With Adachi?
Could you tell us about the time Ms. Yamano went missing?
Huh? Uh, let's see...
Reporters were forcing their way into the inn,
so I went to serve as an undercover bodyguard.
My memory's kinda hazy that far back.
Did you ever speak with Konishi?
Of course I did. She discovered the announcer's body.
But she didn't know much about it, so I only talked with her once or twice.
Did you learn anything about the warning letter?
Warning letter?
Uh... I don't really remember.
Hey, I gave it to you to take down to the crime lab for processing!
You're telling me you forgot?!
I'm sorry.
Your accident was right after that, and what with one thing and another, it sorta slipped my mind.
Geez, what're you asking me all this for?!
I'm going back.
I need to get to the station and report in.
Just one more thing, please.
Huh?
We know for certain now that the first two murders weren't Namatame's doing.
Someone else killed them.
Adachi, do you have any idea who that might be?
I-I have no idea what you're talking about.
'Cause we think it mighta been you!
Th-That's ridiculous!
Fuckin' admit it!
N-No!
We already know Namatame's the one who put them all in!
What did you just say?
Put them all in?
Do you know something about the method behind the murders?
Adachi...
I've been fixated on something you once said.
Now I finally understand why.
Do you recall when I read Namatame's diary at the scene of Dojima's accident?
Even the victims who survived and were never released to the public are written here.
I note that Mr. Morooka's address is absent from the list.
Wow... Then that settles it.
How, I wonder, would that "settle" anything?
It's odd you'd say that.
At the time,
the police had no idea there had been other attempted murders related to the case.
Yet when Naoto read the list of names,
you raised no objection.
What do you say to that, Adachi?
I-I don't know!
I-I said I'm busy!
Wait, Adachi!
I swear he ran this way.
Dammit. Where the hell'd he go?
Damn...
Uncle!
Leave the rest to us.
Teddie?
Nana...
Thank goodness.
Teddie, in my dream, you vanished.
I've been calling for you.
I'm glad you're still here.
I heard your voice.
Thank you, Teddie.
Nana...
So what if I'm just a Shadow?
There must be something I can do!
I'm done running away!
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Rock Solid
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Sage
It's no use.
I can't find his exact location.
Darn it, Teddie!
Why aren't you here when we need you?
Please come back!
Teddie!
Master! Guys!
Y-You little... Where the hell were you?!
You idiot! Bad bear!
You're so late! Who do you think you are?!
I'm bear-y sorry...
Where have you been this whole time?
I figured out a lot of things.
Stuff about me... and that world.
I wanted to tell you all...
A Shadow?
Yeah...
So? What's the problem with being a Shadow?
Huh?
But you now possess the power of Persona.
Doesn't it follow, then, that you must've developed an ego?
Oh! Teddie's practically human, then.
Yeah, you're the same as us.
I'm the same as humans?
Teddie,
stay with us.
We don't want you to go away!
Everyone's been waiting for you.
Welcome back, Teddie.
Th-Thank you! I-I'm so glad I met you guys!
I'll do my best to look for him too! Leave it to Fuzzy!
Ooh, I'm getting something!
Thattaway!
You guys are very persistent.
Adachi, are you really the killer?
So what if I am?
Our world will probably become just like this place soon enough anyway.
What do you mean?
Soon, this place will be reality.
Humans will turn into Shadows.
What the hell's he talking about?
Don't change the subject!
You're the one who threw Ms. Yamano into the TV, aren't you?!
Wait! That isn't his real body.
The real Adachi is somewhere else.
Wow, I'm impressed.
You can tell that much?
Wait, dammit!
The shopping district?!
Things are somehow different this time.
It feels like he's gained some strong power after coming here.
I'd say this world has taken a real shine to me.
I feel like it's given me everything I've ever wanted.
And the monsters don't attack me at all.
Maybe they can tell we have the same goal?
If you want me, come and get me.
We'll see which of us this world favors.
Shut the hell up, dammit!
Here I go!
Persona!
We'll handle things here.
Go on and get Adachi!
Got it!
What the?
Isn't this...
Amagi Inn
my inn?!
This shithole's been so boring that I spent every day glued to the TV.
I had been secretly rooting for this woman,
but then she...
Who're you?
And what'd you call me out here for?
All that talk about you having an affair and whatnot... It's all a lie, isn't it?
Why do I have to explain myself to you?
So you don't deny it...
You caught my eye,
but it turns out you're just another worthless bitch.
Don't make me call for help!
Ugh, shut up, shut up, shut the fuck up!
I think you need to see what it's like to fear for your life. It'll get your head straight.
Sh-She fell in...
Wow! So people can go completely inside!
That happened in our lobby?
I learned about the Midnight Channel through some rumor.
But it was pure coincidence that I touched the screen and discovered my powers.
I burst out laughing when I found out.
I knew right away this was going to be interesting!
So you tested it out on Yamano Mayumi?
No, not at all. I'm a very sincere fellow.
I was just trying to punish the stupid bitch a little for betraying me.
You're disgusting!
Burn in Hell!
Amagi! Satonaka!
There's no point in fighting back.
Inaba will disappear into the fog soon.
This will become reality.
You guys can go on ahead!
Teddie, don't lose sight of Adachi!
You can count on me!
Isn't this...
K-Konishi!
Stop it!
What's this about, anyway?
Didn't you call me in for more questions?
You were getting pretty cozy with that Namatame...
N-No, I wasn't!
Hey, it's all cool.
I'll keep your little secret if you do as I say.
Huh...
So I'm not good enough for you.
Well, that's okay.
I know how to deal with girls like you.
No, stop!
Geez, high school girls today.
This world's gone straight to shit.
Get on your knees and beg, and maybe I'll let you out!
Yeah, right!
As if I'd walk into a deathtrap like that.
I was supposed to be the best of the best, and instead they stick me in the boonies.
But I guess I got this sweet power to make up for it.
You bastard! I'll never forgive you!
C'mon, gimme a break.
I didn't know it was dangerous inside the TV.
It's not like I was trying to kill them.
Those bitches and whores were just gold digging.
They got exactly what they deserved.
I didn't do anything wrong at all.
Shut the fuck up!
What a chump!
Didn't I just tell you the real me is somewhere else?
Shit! What a tough bastard.
This Shadow's on a completely different level from the others.
We're doomed!
This fog is going to drive everyone insane!
What'd you do to Namatame?
He called the police in the middle of the night,
just after they found that Saki girl's body.
Huh... That's the pattern to the two deaths so far?
And now you're seeing a girl in a kimono on that weird program, and you think she'll die too?
Namatame, do you seriously expect us to believe something like that?
But it's true! If there's any way the police can protect her...
Listen.
There's no way the police
are going to make a move based on a ridiculous story like that.
It does sound interesting, though.
B-But...
I have an idea!
If you really wanna save her,
why not do it yourself?
Like, you could shelter her somewhere. Somewhere no one could find her.
Where no one could find her?
Save her yourself.
You can do it.
Isn't that amazing?
Of all the people who could've received Namatame's call, it ended up being me!
All I did was give him a little push.
The more people you guys saved, the more he'd kidnap.
Both sides had the best of intentions, so the cycle would never end.
It was awesome.
Dammit! Because of you...
I'm going bear-serk!
Yu, leave this to us!
Okay, thanks.
You threw Kubo into the TV, didn't you?
Yeah... he turned himself in pretty quick, actually.
This was back when we didn't even know enough to issue a search warrant.
But the other officers decided it was just a prank, so they pawned him off on me.
I didn't think anyone would come forward and take the blame for all the incidents.
If we closed the case, Namatame would stop "saving" people.
I couldn't let that happen, or the game would be over.
That's why I told the others I sent him home but threw him inside the TV instead.
Pretty good idea, right?
The game would be over?
That was your reason?
You gotta have some excitement in life, don't you agree?
But then you guys had to get involved and ruin my fun.
Thanks to you, Kubo was arrested,
and everyone acted like he was the true culprit.
Couldn't they see how badly he copied the crime scene?
It worked out in the end, though, because good ol' Namatame kept saving people.
I guess the guy started to develop
some kinda messiah complex, huh?
What an idiot!
Wow, I'm surprised you made it this far.
Seriously, I'm impressed.
Adachi, why are you doing this?
Why? No reason, really.
I did it because I could, and it was fun.
All I did was put people in here.
It's the world that really kills them, isn't it?
This world reflects people's thoughts.
Which...
Oh dear... Does that mean the real culprits are everyone on the outside, including you?
And aren't you high schoolers?
Shouldn't you be studying instead of worrying about this crap?
Study hard, go to a good college, and marry a cute girl.
Why get so worked up over things you can't change?
Because you've got nothing better to do?
You're all a bunch of lonely losers!
Who's the lonely one here?
Huh?
Don't act so high and mighty.
Fucking cocky brats!
"We'll catch the true killer ourselves!"
Don't make me laugh!
How old are you again?
Oh shit, my sides.
Didn't I tell you?
Once your world is devoured,
everyone'll turn into Shadows.
You're too late.
I pity the fool.
Brats like you are so damned naive.
You piss me off!
Your very existence is pointless!
I don't need annoying fucks like you in the new world.
Let's put an end to this.
Shit...
I thought I could just leave you be, but you're like a plague.
I'll kill you! Let's find out which of us this world favors!
Magatsu Izanagi!
Izanagi!
Be a good boy and die!
Here we go!
Reality isn't a game!
What would a brat like you know?!
At this rate, the two worlds will collide!
I'm counting on you, partner!
Persona!