'Sup!
Riko.
I spent all night racking my brains over the love advice thing.
Oh, that?
Shooting him through the heart.
Great way to make it skip a beat, right?
You're racking your brains over the wrong thing!
How cruel!
I created that mechanism myself!
This is no time for that!
We got four requests for love advice, and we have no means to give it.
To top it all off, some weird duo's scoping us out!
I know.
I'm taking this state of affairs very seriously myself.
And after much deliberation,
have come to this conclusion!
We must research the everliving hell out of love!
Why?!
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
To the Kurahashi Residence!
This is like one of those heartwarming stories on the evening news.
I am not a cat stuck in a tree!
And I shall prove it to you.
I'm scared!
You're awful!
A monster! That's what you are!
You're blaming me for that?
I'm so scared!
Want me to help you?
I will not accept a sworn enemy's help!
This is our first meeting. Why am I your sworn enemy?
You don't remember?!
What're you up to, Sayo?
You're the root of all evil!
What's your problem?
I'll make you cry uncle some day!
Uncle.
I actually did it!
Have some more on the house.
Uncle. Uncle. Uncle.
From me too.
They're even harmonizing it!
Yay!
Calm down, Nana.
Momo!
Are you okay?
I was wondering where you'd run off to.
Kurahashi threw something out the window earlier, which got President Maki all flustered.
I figured I'd go pick it up first,
so I tried to take a shortcut over the wall.
But this thing's so high!
I lost what could've been my chance at a scoop!
My, what a loud voice you have, Nana.
Sorry about that, Sayo.
Do you know her?
There might be some real trouble brewing.
Please knock
before entering!
I see.
Maybe we really should scale down the love research, then.
What?
If it came down to it, Mizushima wouldn't bat an eyelid at having to eavesdrop or trespass.
She's perfectly fine with using dirty tactics.
And she's calling this girl troublesome.
Kurahashi.
I'll have you know I'm quite scary when I get mad.
I was just kidding!
Well, I don't think anyone in Fuji Girls' could sneak in and get up to mischief without me noticing.
Only the best from you.
Wow! I need to take a page out of your book.
That's a book you don't want to take a page out of.
Momo's not like me. She's a different type of beast.
You mean she'll try to take us on fair and square?
She'll take a plan that she can barely fit
into the strike zone of "fair and square,"
and throw it as a breaking ball.
That's weird.
Doesn't sound much different than you.
You seem to know her well. Were you two close?
I have no idea who she is.
Not really.
I was just in the same group as her once,
back when I went to a public elementary school.
Um...
In the end, this means we can
only wait and see what they do.
Until they actually do something, we could make sure our security is perfect and continue our love research.
Come on...
This is still a cause for worry.
What's the big deal?
Let's do it.
I don't like this!
I'll help you with your love research!
Thank you.
Well, you're unusually proactive.
Eno loves manipulating people,
but she hates getting manipulated herself.
Quiet!
Well, then.
Today, we'll study ways to make boys' hearts skip a beat!
No guns allowed, by the way.
What?
Let's start with Kurahashi, then. Teach us some techniques.
What?!
I wanna know!
You can do it, my gray cells!
Think of something...
Think of something!
Uh...
Puppy dog eyes?
Maybe you could stick your tongue out,
or make some light physical contac—
No!
Is this... the wrong way to go about it?
Now you realize?!
Where did I go wrong?
Everywhere.
If I had to pick one thing,
it'd have to be the excessive contact.
But we don't know to make light physical contact.
Right. Let's see...
Beginners should start by putting a hand on his shoulder, I guess?
Hang in there!
I think I could do that too.
Me too!
Give it a shot, then.
O-Okay.
What is this, a red light district?
Ri, my girl. You look down in the dumps.
Who the hell are you calling Ri?
You can't even do this?
Maybe you have no talent.
You're amazing, Yuiko.
Could you do the same for me?
Huh?!
No Makios allowed!
And why do you act so timid around Makio?
That's a girl, you know?
Sh-Shaddup.
Even if you're able to pull it off in practice,
doing it to real guys is a completely different ballgame.
Real guys?
Not happening!
Not happening?
What exactly are you studying love for, then?
Jeez.
W-Well...
They are gonna be a bit different
from your ideal man. Get used to it.
But there could be someone like Huggy out there!
Or perhaps, if I keep embracing him and treating him with great care...
his soul might awaken someday!
Hey!
What's with that horror clip?!
Okay, so maybe you don't like Jan.
But there are all kinds of guys out there.
Really?
Including much worse ones.
Some of them lick the flute of the girl they like, for example,
like a certain big brother I know.
Who?! Whose brother does that?!
You're the only one I can't tell, Eno.
That's as good as telling me!
G-Guys are such...
Now that it's come to this,
I must take much better care of him so that a soul awakens in him!
First, we'll sleep together.
Gosh!
It kinda makes me nervous.
You're awakening to something else entirely!
No more Huggy!
Well, do you wanna come over to my place and practice with my brother?
Huh?
He's younger than us, and his face resembles mine, so you'll probably find it easier to talk to him.
Really?!
This day has finally come!
I can go over to a friend's place!
You're getting way too excited.
It'll be all right.
I prepared for this day by running
the perfect simulation in my head!
Okay. Now throw it into the trash can.
It gives me very bad vibes.
What?
Just be yourself.
That sounds fun. Count me in.
I wanna come too.
I-I could grace you with my presence if you so insist!
It's not like I got scared of boys after what Maki did earlier or anything, okay?
Don't get the wrong idea!
This character type is such a pain to deal with in the real world.
Mom.
My friends are coming over this Sunday.
Friends from Fuji Girls'?
Yeah.
Graceful ladies?!
Maybe I should stay home this Sunday, then.
Dad, Mom.
"Birds of a feather flock together" is a nice saying, don't you think?
Rentarou.
Wh-What?
Got any plans for Sunday?
I'm probably going out with friends—
Oh, you're free? Stay at home, then.
Don't ask if you don't wanna know!
I don't wanna.
It's gonna be a bunch of girls coming, right?
Girls are so annoyingly noisy.
Plus they're persistent and get easily jealous.
Always talking about who they're friends with and who they like.
And they're violent.
Prim and proper ladies are nothing but a fairy tale!
Easy there, kid.
You're a little too young to know that.
Answer it, Ren.
What?
What a pain.
I bet it's just a bunch of girls as crude and noisy as Sis.
Yeah, yeah, come on in.
Are you Riko's brother?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Maki Natsuo.
Striiiiike!
U-Uh...
Ren! What're you standing there dazed and confused for?
Come on in.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Rentarou.
My room's upstairs.
O-Okay.
It's not much, but I brought something.
Is that cake?
Thanks!
My room's just at the top of the stairs. You go on ahead.
Okay.
Mom! Maki brought cake.
That was totally unexpected!
Another one?
Welcome!
Massive!
Tiny!
Bushy brows!
Suzu and you aren't all that different, pipsqueak.
What about the eyebrows?
Say something about his eyebrows!
I'm still an elementary schooler.
She doesn't look like a middle schooler at all.
What about the eyebrows?!
Even elementary school kids don't look this childish.
Stop crying! That was nothing!
And you should start crying.
Sorry about my brother. He's so rude.
Oh, right!
Bitch at him. Let him have it!
Huh? What am I supposed to say?
You look like you're good at bitching, Mizushima. Show us how it's done!
Like sister, like brother, I guess.
You look like you're fond of the algae in a fish tank.
You sure you weren't a shellfish in your past life?
Too cruel!
Oh, all right.
You were a great shellfish that cleaned up the
algae in a fish tank and made people very happy.
Move on from shellfish already.
You can just say something you
wouldn't like hearing from others.
It's impossible to miss out on promotions at supermarkets or convenience stores.
I hope you miss out on them, though!
I feel kinda refreshed now.
Good for you.
Hey, wait a second.
Apologize for calling the eyebrows of an older person you just met bushy!
Ack. He actually said that?
I'm sorry. I just went with the flow.
The flow?!
But what's the problem? It looks good on you.
If it was weird, I would've said so.
I-I guess I could accept your apology.
He's gonna be a lady killer.
Something wrong?
Ren went around making a fuss.
S-Say what?
Do you want some cake too?
Maki brought it.
No thanks.
It's a bit messy, but don't let it bother you.
This room is kinda girly.
Well, it is a girl's room.
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Unpopular
Girls
Read
This!
Huh? What is this?
I forgot to hide it!
What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
Why do you have that book, oh-so-popular Kurahashi?
W-Well...
My brother gave it to me for my birthday.
He doesn't know I'm popular.
Oh?
What are you talking about?
Kurahashi has this book, you see...
What's happening?
Nothing at all!
Photo Booth Album
Isn't this a photo booth album?
Yeah. Wanna see?
It's from back when I was in elementary school.
May I?
I want to look!
Let's see...
Riko's so cute.
Why aren't there any pictures of you with guys?
Huh?
Now that you mention it...
If you were popular, you could've taken tons of pictures with guys, right?
Yeah, I don't see any.
That's...
Is she finally gonna come clean?
The truth is...
All of your boyfriends weren't allowed to have their photos taken, right?
Huh?
Foreign spies who couldn't reveal themselves,
or VIPs whose lives were in danger.
And an old-fashioned guy would refuse to take pictures, scared that he'd have his soul taken.
Are you okay in the head?
No way that's true.
It's obviously someone in showbiz or something!
You've dated all kinds of guys, haven't you?
Y-Yeah, that's right!
Wow!
Are you really okay with that, Kurahashi?
Calm down.
Calm down!
Ren, go buy some juice from the convenience store.
Why me?
Because Riko bought that bottle so we could serve it her guests.
I'll go.
Get some snacks while you're at it.
That'll be 514 yen.
Okay.
Promo!
Lottery
You'll win a
grand prize!
Promotion
If you make a purchase of over 500 yen,
you get a shot at this lottery.
Welcome
Total
Yen
You paid 600 yen.
Your change is 86 yen.
Promo!
Lottery
Thank you very much.
Promo!
Lottery
Welcome.
We're currently running a promo
lottery for purchases over 500 yen.
Feel free to give it a try.
I missed out!
My bad.
I had no idea Ren treated girls that way.
It's okay.
That was the first time I managed to talk back to someone too.
I always find it hard to speak in those situations.
It's amazing how you two can argue with guys so easily.
Nah, not really—
All right.
Let me teach you some simple yet highly destructive abuse.
Stop! Don't corrupt Suzu!
I couldn't argue back well either.
How
Maki
saw
it
Are you an idiot?
I'll give it to him the next time I see him!
"It takes one to know one!"
"If I were to use eel lunches as an example,
I'd be regular, whereas you'd be extra special!"
So you accept that you're both stupid?
"And if it had to be curry, I'd again be regular,
whereas you'd be the target of
challenges from gluttons everywhere!"
Yeah, you are stupid.
I wonder what kinda discussion they're having right now.
Mean-
while,
Ren...
I'm sure it's a very intellectual one.
I'm home!
Thanks for helping out.
Don't mention it!
Someone's in the kitchen?
Don't tell me...
Mom, I'm back from my errand.
Oh what, it's just the pintsize?
Oww!
Oh yeah, I missed out earlier.
Missed, not pissed!
I missed out on the
impossible-to-miss-out-on 500 yen lottery!
Did you curse me or something, Pintsize?
How awful!
I need to hurry up and give it back to him.
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Is he... waiting for me?
What?
You got nothing?
Huh? Um... um...
I'll use what Mizushima taught me earlier.
Serves you right! You'll be bald 21 years from now!
What the hell's with that weirdly prophetic abuse?!
Screw you, you dumb runt!
Ow!
I thought he was a meanie, unlike Riko,
but maybe he's actually a little nice.
Why do I have to do all this?
Quit your whining.
Oh, I'll take those upstairs.
Okay. H-Here...
Thank you.
Why the dreamy look, kid?
One of Sis's friends is really pretty!
Really?
Yep!
She's pretty, has a sweet body, and she's prim and proper!
Sis totally pales in comparison. I pity her.
I think I'll be pitying you in a second.
Damn that Ren.
I can do it too!
Good day.
I'm Kurahashi Riko!
Hey, Ma!
There be a fun show happenin' out here!
There's a high-class lady in our house too!
R-Ren!
Rentarou!
Do you want me to keep my mouth shut?
I'm out of pocket money, you see.
You can have mine.
I want your share of the ice cream too.
Feel free.
Also, ask Maki if she likes younger men.
Generally speaking, I mean.
Maybe I should ask Maki what to do with my cruel little brother.
Y-You're playing dirty!
Give me your share of the ice cream,
and I'll tell Maki that you're a nice kid.
You can have it!
Thank you for having us.
Later.
Feel free to visit anytime.
Ren, my boy.
Earlier, Maki...
Maki?
Elementary schoolers are so naughty and cute!
I feel like a mother.
That's what she said.
Too bad!
The next day
I'm home!
I'd hidden that test away!
You're going to cram school starting next week!
Serves you right.
Told
on her
'Sup!
Hey, Satch!
Who are you calling Satch?!
That's what I used to call you.
Because you were so cute.
I told you plenty of times to stop calling me that back then too!
Kurahashi?
Jan!
I heard you played with Maki's feelings by calling her cute!
Huh?
Maki was mad at you.
She called you an extra special challenge curry.
Excuse me?
Sure, I called her cute, but that was—
You seriously did?!
Let me finish! That was—
She must've been gorgeous if you complimented her.
I wanna take a look at her now!
Listen to me, dammit.
What the heck?
Didn't you like me in the past?
Wait, you saw her with me the other day.
Huh?
Oh, I only had my eyes on you then.
N-No! That's not what I meant!
D-Don't get the wrong idea, you idiot!
You what?!
It takes one to know one!
What's wrong with them?
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
When it comes to cutting people deeply, no one is better than Mizushima.
Ren was tearing up at the end.
You're exaggerating.
Oh, Eno, you've got shredded seaweed on your head. Is something wrong?
She cut me! She cut so deep...
Oh, come on.
As long as you've got a strong spirit, you can endure most anything.
Kurahashi the heartbreaker, you're so wonderful.
I bet you have boys confessing to you every day.
To the Wild One.
Why are you crying even though she complimented you, Riko?