This looks like Eichi's room.
What is this cold feeling?
A shadow filled with the smell of death
surrounds this house.
Why? What's going on?!
You need to put it out of your mind.
That was an unfortunate accident.
But...
They were...
They were so happy.
Why did they have to...
No way!
DEAR GRANDMA,
Who are you writing the postcard to?
A friend from school?
No, to my grandmother.
Because I left Grandma's home
in that manner.
And also...because I'm
worried about her.
You're very kind, Mitsuki.
Huh?
Because you're very considerate
of your Grandma at a time
when your head is probably
filled with thoughts of Eichi.
N-No it isn't.
You don't have to hide it!
- That's right.
- I'm not hiding anything!
- I wonder whether he figured out
- But you're blushing!
the meaning of Eichi's name
appearing backwards.
- Hey, hurry up, Takuto!
- Stop it, Ms. Oshige!
I can't believe it.
No way.
Before it happened,
I had a bad premonition.
When I think to myself
that didn't I stop them...
You can't think about
stuff like that now.
But they were
living so happily.
To think that all three of them
had to die.
That too is our fate.
We have no choice
but to accept it.
I can't believe it.
Mitsuki worked hard
to see Eichi.
You want to become
a singer that much?
Yep...it's a promise.
A promise to Eichi.
I like you, Eichi.
I will work hard so that my songs
will reach you in America,
so wait for that day.
There's no point unless these feelings
are conveyed to you, Eichi.
Eichi...
Eichi... Eichi has passed away.
If Mitsuki finds out...
Those backward letters...
Don't tell me that...
We'll be there soon.
You'll get to see Eichi soon.
How do you feel?
You probably feel like you've
grown wings and can fly, right?
Yes, because I've worked hard till now
just so I could see Eichi again.
I see. If we continue down this road,
we'll get there.
Just be patient a little longer.
Okay.
Takuto... What should we do?
We're almost there.
What happened?
Could it be a flat tire?
I don't know,
but the car suddenly veered.
In any case,
let me take a look.
I'll look too.
Man, just when we
were almost there.
- Takuto...
- Huh? Takuto?
Could this be Takuto's doing?
What is it?
It's a flat tire.
Takuto!
Where in the world were you?
Go home right now!
Huh?
What?! Why?!
Because! Just go home!
No way! Tell me the reason!
I don't have a reason!
Just go home!
It looks like it would be better
not to go to Eichi's house after all.
Shall we go home for today?
Huh?! Why?!
You see, it was written in
the Death Spirit Handbook
that today is
a day of bad fortune!
Huh?
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Let's call this off for today!
If today's no good,
then when is?
Umm... Next week...
Let's do it next week!
See...
It's good fortune to visit
people next week. See?
Huh?
It doesn't matter!
We're going to turn back!
Why?! I'm so close to seeing Eichi!
I can't let you see Eichi.
Why?!
You just can't.
You're awful!
Why do you say such mean things?!
That's right, I'm mean!
That's exactly what I am.
A mean guy!
Where's Mitsuki?
She's probably talking to Takuto.
But the mood feels different than usual.
Look, when I say you can't go,
I mean you can't go.
- Please understand.
- No.
Even if you say I can't,
Takuto, I will go...by myself.
H-Hey!
That's absurd,
saying you'll go alone!
Come on,
let's go home, Mitsuki.
Hey, Mitsuki!
Could that be...
Eichi's house?!
Hey, Mitsuki! Don't go!
Today just isn't good!
No!
I will not let you go!
Mitsuki!
I have been living for this day.
If I can't see Eichi, then what is
the meaning of all my perseverance?
I know that.
I know all that.
Then why are you
getting in my way?
Eichi is so near!
You're wrong.
It's not like that.
Eichi isn't there.
Huh?
He isn't there.
I don't understand
what you're saying!
I can't tell you more than this.
In any case, Eichi isn't there.
So let's go home.
Why isn't he there?
Why?!
Takuto!
Shouldn't you stop her?
- I can't stop her.
- Huh?
I saw that expression
on her face.
I can't.
That Takuto... He always says
weird things when it comes to Eichi.
But I wonder what he meant
when he said Eichi isn't there?
Umm... Is this Eichi Sakurai's house?
Yes. Who are you?
My name is Mitsuki Koyama.
I came from Japan because
I wanted to see Eichi.
M-My goodness.
That's very far.
Please come in.
Thank you.
I apologize for coming here
out of the blue like this.
But I wanted to
surprise Eichi.
Who is this girl?
She came from Japan
to see Eichi.
What?
How do you do?
Umm... Where is Eichi?
A photo of Eichi!
Eichi isn't here.
U-Umm... What do you mean?
Eichi died two years ago.
Huh?
My son and daughter-in-law
adopted Eichi,
but all three of them died
in an automobile accident.
He...died?
Mitsuki!
Eichi...died?
That can't be true.
No way.
That means that...
that Mitsuki's wish...
Mitsuki.
Here.
TO MITSUKI
This is a letter that Eichi left behind.
I've kept it unopened.
He probably never
intended to send it.
TO MITSUKI
I'm sorry that I have to give it to you
under these circumstances.
TO MITSUKI
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki! Mitsuki!
She finally fell asleep.
I see.
All that had happened...
I'm so sorry that you came
all the way from Japan.
Don't worry about us.
But Mitsuki...
When I think of how
Mitsuki must be feeling...
Please stay awhile.
Thank you very much.
Why kind of a boy was Eichi?
He was a quiet
but thoughtful boy.
He gradually became
accustomed to living here
and had just started
making a few friends.
But...
Mitsuki... I'm coming in.
Eichi...
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki! Where are you?
Eichi... Where are you?
Eichi... Answer me.
Eichi isn't there.
Why do you...
Why do you say things like that?
Eichi...
What's this?
Eichi's...handwriting.
Two months have passed since
I began living here in America
and I've come to realize
that I really do like you.
I like you even more than
I did when we lived together.
But I wonder if
you will forget me.
When I think that you may forget me
as time passes and we grow up...
To be honest, it's unsettling.
I don't want you to know that
I am such a pathetic man.
But it's okay since this is a letter
that you will never read.
I will express
my feelings honestly.
Mitsuki, I like you so much.
I like your sparkling eyes.
The way you live life
to the fullest.
Your dedication.
The tranquility of your voice
when you sing.
I wanted to tell you
I've always liked you.
I wish I had told you
many times that I liked you.
But I was too shy to say it.
But someday
we will meet again.
And that's when I'll tell you
that I like you...
until my voice is hoarse.
Eichi... Where are you?
I want to see you.
Eichi...
This is where you were?
Wait!
Wait, Eichi!
Eichi!
I caught you!
I can stop now, right?
I worked so hard
up to this point.
I persevered believing
that I would see you, Eichi.
But...I don't have to
persevere anymore, do I?
Mitsuki, where are you?!
Answer us!
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki...
Can't I be some kind
of support for you?!
I'll go to sleep here just like this.
If I do that, I'll probably be by
Eichi's side when I wake up.
I won't let anyone get between
me and Eichi any longer.
Eichi, please hurry and get me.
I'm here. I'll be right here.
Come here by my side, Eichi.
Hurry to me.
I can't believe it.
Eichi is...
What are we supposed to
say to her at a time like this?!
Takuto...
I won't give up.
I'll...I'll make her want to sing again!
I won't let it all come
to an end like this!
Next time on Full Moon:
"I Won't Sing Ever Again!"
- Look forward to it!