Nobody's home.
I'm not here.
Go away already...
Now then...
Stupid!
This is overkill!
2/13 Express Order Enclosed
Valentine's Day Gift
Oh, it's here!
I'm home!
Sasami!
Your brother has returned home!
Would you like a meal? Maybe a bath?
Or perhaps your bro—
Food.
Right. I found some excellent mackerel today, so...
So?
Tonight's dessert will be gelatin and—
Pudding.
You predicted that I'd buy pudding too!
Oh Sasami, you see through me every time.
This must be the power of love!
Now, enjoy the feast!
Feed me.
I spoil you so much.
I'm starving here.
I suppose I'll have to.
Brother.
What do you need, Sasami?
Wash me.
I spoil you so much.
Sasami...
how would you feel about going to school again?
I can't.
You're only 16 years old,
so your whole life is ahead of you.
Your future has limitless possibilities.
There's nothing in the world you can't do.
I can't.
But you've finally entered high school.
Why not savor the student lifestyle a bit?
I can't.
But my work as a teacher is so dreary and uneventful,
and seeing you there would make every moment as lovely as a rose!
I'm not spoiling you.
Dry me.
Right away, Sasami.
Dress me.
Right away, Sasami!
Brush me.
Right away, Sasami.
You're still not asleep, Sasami?
Staying up late is bad for your skin.
Leave me alone.
Please, call me if you need anything!
And so we part, until tomorrow!
Oh, it's time for my late night anime.
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
I'll Try Tomorrow
No passage beyond this point
From 2012/12/1 to 2013/5/5,
Please Take This Detour
No Entry
I'll be off to school, then.
Sasami, if you feel up to it, you're welcome to come with.
Brother.
Here.
For lunch.
Sasami, for me?!
Ah, today is a wondrous day!
I'll make this a Sasami anniversary!
My oh my, what's this?
Today is February 14th, is it not?
Sasami's Licking Anniversary
Sasami's Eye Contact Anniversary
Sasami's Cream Puff Anniversary
Sasami's Fluffy Anniversary
Sasami's Suzuki Anniversary
Sasami's Chewing Anniversary
Sasami's Stumble Anniversary
Sasami's Soft Anniversary
Sasami's Cute, so cute...
Sasami's Squishy Anniversary
Sasami's Gentle Anniversary
Sasami, Sasamiiiiiiiiii
Today already has...
Sasami's Stumble Anniversary
"Sasami's Stumble Anniversary"
and "Sasami's I Luvvy Duvvy My Brother Dynamite Anniversary" marked for it!
Sasami's I Luvvy Duvvy My Brother
Dynamite Anniversary
Oh, but no matter.
I'll just add "Sasami's Lunch Box Anniversary" to it!
Now, this calls for a grand celebration!
Don't!
It's for lunch.
So don't open it before noon.
Oh, I see...
If you say so...
Well, have a nice day.
Right, I'll be off!
Brother Observation Tool,
activate!
Now then, I'm off!
Sasami and I are just like newlyweds.
Tsukuyomi             Kamiomi
Sasami
Just go to school.
Ribbit ribbit!
I'm a cute little froggie!
Tama!
Morning, Paparin!
What are you doing? Have you caught a cold?
You know the froggies?
They're gone...
That's why I'm a froggie instead!
Ribbit ribbit!
The froggies are hibernating right now.
Hyburnayting?
What do you do when people are making noise when you want to sleep?
Murder them!
Exactly, so let them sleep.
You can play with them again in the spring.
Okay! I'll let them go sleepy!
My tummy's grumbling.
Oh dear, it seems I'll have to help.
How about I offer you this?
It was meant to be my lunch,
but I can always purchase more.
Brother, you idiot!
Today, you really crossed the line!
Not again...
This is...
too much...
Brother...
I told you...
I can't...
Ribbit
Barf
I knew I couldn't...
Brother, you idiot...
It's the first time I've given you chocolate...
rother.
first time is all yours.
Ms. Tsurugi,
I don't think you should play porn games in the staff room.
Ms. Tsurugi, I don't think
you should play porn games
in the staff room.
Ms. Tsurugi, I don't think
you should play porn games
in the staff room.
STFU and die
I want my tea back.
So, Tsukuyomi,
get any chocolate?
Not particularly.
That so?
Then take this.
D-Don't get the wrong idea.
That was just because I felt bad for you.
Huh?
The point is,
the first person to give you a Valentine was...
lil' old me!
But I gave him one first...
You've really done it now, you midget hag!
Ribbit
Barf
Forget it...
My life's on Nightmare Mode...
It's a waste of time to try.
Teacher, you are disgusting me.
But my job is so uneventful, Kagami.
Oh, Kagami, how about a story?
You can pick whatever topic you like.
Be it today's Sasami, yesterday's Sasami,
Sasami's charms,
the day I fought with Sasami,
or even Sasami's embarrassing moments!
Let us talk to our heart's content about the most fascinating topic in the world, Sasami!
Let us speak until we're sick of it!
I fell asleep.
Kagami!
What happened?
Oh, Tama!
P-Paparin...
Um, umm,
I really like you too, Paparin,
but I think we should start as friends...
Oh, what do I do?
C-Can't breathe...
Look at that, the three sisters in one place.
S-Sister...
Tsurugi!
I dunno what you're talkin' about, but don't leave me out!
Hey Tsurugi, listen, listen...
Paparin proposed to me!
Huh?
She misunderstood what that chocolate meant.
Valentine's Day?!
Simply put, it's a day where you give chocolate to the person you love.
Is that true?
No! It's a lie! Say it ain't so!
Sasami's the one with common sense,
so she should have known about Valentine's Day!
And yet, despite all the love she's given me,
I've never once received chocolate!
I know!
When dinner comes, she'll be in a brother-loving mood,
and she'll give me the chocolate in a maid costume!
Like hell.
But I must not stay.
I have to make haste and buy a mountain of chocolate!
But that's fine.
He just didn't know about Valentine's Day.
Oh well.
Guess I'll just have to give him more chocolate.
"To My Beloved Brother"
Valentine Chocolate
We Recommend These Other Popular Products
Hm? This manga has a new volume?
duct Description
Content Description
This volume's plot/
The two hid their true feelings and got into an argument, so a world class chocolate
What's the overview say?
"The two hid their true feelings and got into an argument."
"But having reflected on his actions after making Chiyoko cry,
Cacao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate chef."
"Chocolate is everything. Chocolate is glorious."
Content Description
This volume's plot/ Even though they love each other,
Cacao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
"Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore."
Content Description
This volume's plot/ Even though they love each other,
Kakao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
Content Description
This volume's plot/ Even though they love each other,
Kakao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
Content Description
This volume's plot/ Even though they love each other,
Kakao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
This volume's plot/ Even though they love each other,
Kakao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
Kakao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
What a shocking twist!!
Kakao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
What a shocking twist!!
Kakao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
What a shocking twist!!
Kakao focuses on becoming a world-class chocolate
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
What a shocking twist!!
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
What a shocking twist!!
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is glorious.
Chiyoko doesn't matter anymore.
What a shocking twist!!
"What a shocking twist!"
It's twisting too hard!
Wasn't this called "The Angel's Love"?
The Angel's Chocolate
"Chocomanga Greatest Hits"
"The Angel's Chocolate"?
Where'd the chocolate come from?
Choco, Choco, and Chocolate
(Complete Limited Edition)
The Blu-ray collection of "Choco, Choco, and Chocolate?"
This is all chocolate too!
What happened to the love and elections?
All Products
Chocolate
School
Swords and Sorcery
Product Description
Content Description
The school festival draws near,
and our couple's chocolate is growing more and more!
"The school festival draws near, and our couple's chocolate is growing more and more!"
"Action packed battles filled with swords, sorcery, and chocolate!"
Product Description
Content Description
Action packed battles filled with swords,
sorcery, and chocolate!
"This work contains images of graphic chocolate."
Product Description
Content Description
This work contains images of graphic chocolate.
"A heartrending chocolate tale of Choco's stolen choco that was chocochoco'd."
Product Description
Content Description
A heartrending chocolate tale of Choco's stolen
choco that was chocochoco'd.
The choco'd pair are caught
in a choco royale, and must chocolate.
"The choco'd pair are caught in a choco royale, and must chocolate."
I can't even understand this.
Oh, that's it!
It's just a Valentine's Day joke.
I'll just go to a different site...
The Director of Chocolate Agency Declares Chocolate
"The Director of Chocolate Agency Declares Chocolate."
ChocoChief
"I was told that if I didn't attend this chocolate convention, I'll never go anywhere in life."
I was told that if I didn't attend this chocolate convention, I'd never
go anywhere in life
ChocoCon
"Concerning the Chocoslovakia Problem."
UN Security Council
Concerning the Chocoslovakia Problem
Chocoslav
"Today's Weather is Choco with a Chance of White Choco."
Today's Weather is Choco with a Chance of White Choco
Some Areas May Experience Macadamia Nut Choco
"Some Areas May Experience Macadamia Nut Choco."
ChocoTime
What's going on?
It can't be...
They make so many kinds of chocolate these days.
I'll buy a huge amount and give it to Sasami as a present, and then...
"I can't eat this all by myself! You have some too, Brother!"
"Don't get the wrong idea. It's just because I'd get fat if I ate too much!"
She'll play that hard-to-get act for me!
And just like that, Sasami will have given me chocolate!
Shoot, it's a Transformation...
It's like Hansel and Gretel.
Tama, you can eat as much as you want today.
Really?
Come on!
We're cookin' fondue!
Rub a dub dub, thanks for the grub!
Yummy!
You are soft.
For you are chocolate.
I will chew you up.
You will be consumed.
For you are chocolate.
You moron!
Boob missiles woulda been perfect right there!
Huh?
Don't back down just 'cause you're flat!
That is none of your concern.
Choco choco chocolate!
All right!
Our target is Tsukuyomi's house!
Think you're some evil god?
Kagami, reflect the world.
World of Humans, return to your original form.
I'm home!
Sasami, your brother has returned!
I heard that today is Valentine's Day!
True, it may be a day where boys receive chocolate from girls,
but my love transcends age, gender, and blood relation,
so there is not one problem!
Sa-Sasami!
I see... that's what you mean!
You want me to "eat you up," is that it?
Then I'll lick, chew, and savor without any reservation!
Your brother will... I will...
Don't you even...
dare!
Die!
We had no choice...
right?
Get out...
This is my house!
Sasami
Ganbaranai
I'm so beat...
I'm never trying anything again.
I wouldn't be so sure!
Things rarely go the way we wish, Sasami.
Next time, Sasami will be singing the ending theme.
Even though we say our goodbyes,
Now, take your mic,
I start to miss you right away (In the stream of love)
and raise your voice in song!
Who's the moron that came up with that retarded idea?
Until I board the train,
Seriously, he's a dead man.
Sasami, you're letting your true colors show!
I want to listen to your voice (Just feeling your heart)
Pretend to be a cat!
End your lines with a "meow!"
You're a slave driver.
I'm stunned when you smile and ask
Come on, the recording's already been playing in the background.
Isn't that enough?
to walk home together
Do I really need to sing next week? No.
That's not true!
If your lovely singing voice could reach living rooms around the country,
I can hear your voice
everyone would hold you as dear as the Earth itself!
Hey, Sasami, are you listening?
everywhere like a resounding symphony
Oh, you're in bed.
You really want to sleep through this.
The light shines the color of love
Well, do your best!
Hard work never hurt anyone!
Let's hold hands forever
Oh, so Sasami stayed in bed to the end...
I want to feel the osmosis grow
But next time,
Sasami's lovely singing voice will reach you all!
Let's all look forward to it!
Sasami
Ganbaranai
It's time for Half-Hearted Horoscopes.
Half-Hearted Horoscopes
This week in love,
This Week's Love Fortune
Half-Hearted Horoscopes
Capricorn Normalfags
Capricorn normalfags are doing fine.
Treasure the time you spend with your normalfag lovers.
Water-colored items bring fortune...
or maybe something nice.
As for abnormal Capricorns,
Capricorn Abnormalfags
take a guess.
Good things may happen if you just stay alive... probably.
Don't worry! Dry your tears.
Next time, on Episode 2,
Next time, on Episode 2
"Home Security Guard".
Home Security Guard