saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
along with my food!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
gomennasai
but sorry for finding out!
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Getting lost in silly conversations
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Chatting about love and relationships
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
Say, why can't you make friends?
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You came right out and asked?!
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
iitai houdai ne
You two never quit!
mitsuba ga daibousou
The three leaves are on a rampage,
dare ni mo tomerarenai
and there's nobody who can stop them!
I'll play the role
of a married woman.
A faithful dog who runs free.
Who might you be talking about?
You'd have better luck with
an SLR camera and a telephoto lens.
It is you, Onee-chan!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Usuda Sakura.
issei no mae mitekou
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
mae mae miteru
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
sannin yoreba monju no chie
Three heads are better than one!
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora going my way
Everything's going my way,
susumesou my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
Let's go full steam ahead
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
I'm living the best days of my life,
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
Futaba
Miss Youko
Teru
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
I'm sure that this is a
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
Three Leaves,
Three Colors
Yamaji? Yamaji?
You called, Youko-sama?
I've invited my classmates
to visit tomorrow.
We'll be playing in the garden.
That's wonderful!
Begin preparations immediately!
Of course, Youko-sama.
Welcome to my abode!
Shall we play house?
That sounds delightful.
Yes.
I'll play the role
of a married woman.
I'll be the wife of a chairman.
And I, the wife
of a real estate magnate.
Today I'm going to
the beauty parlor and nail salon.
Meanwhile, I'll have my pet groomed.
Perhaps we'll dine on sautéed foie gras
with caviar this evening.
A tradesman is stopping by
the house today.
Actually, This Is What I Live For
And that's just one of the heartwarming memories
from Youko-sama's childhood.
Stop telling stories
from when I was young.
You're a rich girl
through and through.
Not surprising at all.
But really...
...has Sonobe-san always been like that?
Yes. She said she was already
well into adulthood by then.
What were you like
when you were little, Futaba?
Hmm, when I was little?
Futaba's
Memories
I'm home!
Welcome home, Futaba!
What's for snack?
Is bread okay?
Yup!
Yummy!
I was an energetic girl
who ate a lot.
Even as a kid...
What about you, Hayama-chan?
Well, I...
Teru-chan, what's wrong?
Santa-san... Presents!
What about presents?
I told Santa-san I wanted a white tiger,
but he just gave me this.
And if I couldn't have one,
my second choice was a puma,
my third choice was a snow leopard,
and my fourth choice was a saber-toothed cat.
That's terrible. What a slacker.
He needs to retire, huh?
Teru-chan,
cheer up.
Okay...
But it's probably my fault.
Santa-san didn't get me
what I wanted because I've been bad.
I'll be a good girl and study hard.
Yeah... Even if it's just for show.
One Moment Please
And that's when you awakened!
What do you mean?
It seems your sister
has always been kind.
Sounds like it. I'm jealous,
since I'm an only child.
Teru-chan!
Oh, Onee-chan.
Can I have lunch
with you all today?
Oh, we've already finished our—
I'm having bitter melon today.
Stir-fried?
Nope, it's raw.
Still jealous?
Oh yeah.
It comes out tomorrow, right?
Tomorrow?
You see, Teru-chan has...
Grand Prix
This Month's
Grand Prize
Tama (1 year old)
No way. My kitty is just as cute.
My kitty is a hundred times cuter!
It's got a silky coat,
and the cutest eyes!
Bel Hayama (1 year old)
What?!
Morning!
Hmm? What are you
looking at at, Nishiyama?
Nishiyama?!
Always... always...
You're always, always...!
That won't do.
Collection of Popular Cats!
None of these kittens
have done anything wrong.
Oh, is that...?
There's a picture
of my kitty in here!
There's so many of them,
and they all look the same...
What?!
It's obvious that he
shines brighter than the others!
Are you blind?
Ugh, what a doting parent...
Hayama-san.
So it really was your cat.
He's a cute one.
Mine's cuter, though.
Why, thank you.
The kitten you got from me
is rather cute.
Not as cute as mine, though.
My cat is cute, but yours is too...
So is yours...
My, my...
My, my, my...
I don't get it!
My, that's amazing, Hayama-san.
How lovely. It wouldn't be as lonely
living on my own if I had a pet.
But my apartment
doesn't allow them...
You need to find another place, huh?
I don't have the means for that.
Oh, but you do have a dog.
Huh?
A faithful dog who runs free.
Who might you be talking about?
Oh, not at all.
To think of Yamaji as a dog
is quite unpleasant.
Youko-sama.
Throw this and say "fetch!"
Fetch!
Here.
That's creepy!
What?!
I won't lose.
I definitely won't.
I can do it too!
I'll take a cute picture
that's magazine-worthy!
Hey, wait!
Let me take your picture!
Come back!
Nishiyama?
Animal photographers
have a tough job.
Nishiyama-san?
You'd have better luck with
an SLR camera and a telephoto lens.
Are you seriously
thinking about it?!
You actually own that stuff?
So photography's a hobby
of yours, Hayama-chan?
Oh, it's not my hobby.
It's my duty.
Duty?!
Do you have other hobbies?
Hmm, I suppose not. Maybe reading.
Like international guides to torture?
I finished reading most of those
in middle school.
Is that so?
Is eating your hobby, Futaba-san?
It's not a hobby.
Humans have to eat, right?
So I do.
Humans...
Why do you have
a look of pity in your eyes?!
What's your hobby then?
Why are you asking so nicely now?
My hobby?
I like cooking.
You're kidding.
That'd be the lamest joke
of your life.
Wha—?
You mean you like
to eat cooked meals?
Or that you like
eating a ton of food?
No, I actually like making it!
I like eating, so I can actually cook!
Even though I eat bread for lunch.
You can tell us
your real hobby now.
You don't believe me!
I really do enjoy cooking!
I'll order something at a restaurant
and try making it at home.
So it really is eating.
Well, then I guess my hobby
would be eating out.
U-Um...!
I have...
...a request.
I've always wanted to try this...
On the way home,
while chatting with friends.
I can't believe
you've never eaten here.
Since Futaba-san said her hobby
is eating out, if you wouldn't mind...
Actually, this is what I live for!
Th-This...
This food is the stuff of my dreams!
What a humble dream.
Now let us talk endlessly
about vague and silly things while eating!
Go ahead!
What should I say?
Anything is fine.
I don't mind if you talk about
food or animals like you normally do—
Those aren't silly!
How is it? Good?
I feel like there's something missing.
It would be much better
with mayonnaise.
So you still need some, huh?
Youko-sama?
This might not be the right place
to ask this, and it's not a silly question,
but I feel like it's okay to ask now.
Futaba?
What are your parents
doing right now?
I don't know.
My mother passed away
when I was young, but my father...
Your dad?
When my father lost everything
and decided to start over, he said this:
"All right! Daddy's gonna
do something big!"
From then on,
he's been sending money regularly,
but I don't know where he is
or what he's doing.
You've had it hard, Youko-sama.
But that's not news, I guess.
So that's why you're
living on your own.
Yes.
If you ever need anything, just ask.
We're happy to help!
Thank you for making
my dream come true!
You're exaggerating.
Invite us again!
As long as it's
related to food, right?
Onee-chan?
I knew it! It is you, Onee-chan!
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
"Onee-chan"?
Youko-sama, you have a brother?
Oh, no.
Yuu-san is—
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takezono Yuu,
Youko-oneechan's betrothed.
What?!
Betrothed?
Sounds like rich people business.
You have the wrong idea.
I've known Yuu-san
since we were young.
It's nothing formal.
I'm serious about it, though!
Right, right.
I see.
So that's how it is.
I have money,
so you'll have an easy life.
Money?
Oh! I need to go to cram school.
Onee-chan, I'll see you again, right?
Yes.
Please continue to get along
with Youko-oneechan.
We will.
Yup.
Well then, I'm off!
It's been a long time,
Young Master Takezono-sama.
You worked at Onee-chan's place.
Yamaji, right?
What are you doing?
I have something
to deliver to Youko-sama.
Are you still pretending
to be her servant?
Can you stop?
You're getting in my way.
Stalker.
He's just a child.
A child...
Hey, hey, about that boy
from yesterday...
You mean Yuu-san?
He seemed pretty attached to you.
Yeah.
It's been a while since I've seen him,
so I'm glad he's well.
He seems like a reliable boy.
Rich kids are just
a little different somehow.
Oh, that's right.
I can't walk home
with you guys today.
Oh?
What are you doing?
My cousin's staying
with us for a week.
I have to go pick her up.
Your cousin?
My, I would like to meet her.
Oh yeah?
Well, I could use some help.
Help?
West Park
Sakura!
Oh, Futaba-chan!
Sorry, were you waiting?
Jeez, you're late!
I'll introduce you.
These are my friends,
Youko-sama and Hayama-chan.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
This is my cousin, Sakura.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Usuda Sakura.
My, you're adorable.
Yes, I know!
What?
Sorry, she's a little weird.
D-Don't worry.
She really is cute.
Hang on; why does
she have so much luggage?
Just my clothes and other things.
This is pretty standard for a girl.
So this is why you needed help.
I really appreciate it...!
You summoned me?
I told you, that's creepy!
I don't think I'm amazing,
but I am pretty great.
I see...
That's why I've got
my life all planned out.
Sakura's
Life
Sakura
Occupation:
Student
Age:
In the summer when I'm fourteen,
I'll be scouted in Harajuku and debut as an idol.
Idol
After being in some movies and commercials,
I'll get married at twenty-three.
Bride
I'll give birth to a boy
at age twenty-five.
Mom
At twenty-eight, I'll debut as a model
in a young women's magazine.
Model
At fifty, I'll move overseas
and live a carefree life.
Socialite
That's the plan so far.
You never know
what life will bring.
Former Rich Girl
Youko
Depressing...
This guy is rather handsome.
I'm accepting of
many types of people.
He's actually...
...more of a stalker
who pretends to hold down jobs.
Ugh, that's the worst.
I don't need you in my life.
I'm not even in your life.
Onee-chan!
Oh?
Yuu-san!
I'm so glad I ran into you!
Here! It's some wagyu beef
I received as a gift.
Wagyu beef?
We can't finish it all,
so I wanted to give you some.
It's yummy!
Yuu-kun!
Usuda! What are you doing here?
Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef.
What? You two know each other?
The sweet juice of the meat
floods your mouth!
Yeah, we're in the same class.
Right now, he's the top candidate
to be my darling.
Don't decide that on your own!
Aw, you're just embarrassed.
I am not!
It'll be so wonderful!
Why not? You two
would make a good couple.
You think so too?
Wagyu beef...
No! Youko-oneechan is my betrothed!
What do you mean, betrothed?
That is...
Is it over for me?
Do I still have a chance?
Well, it's a promise they made as kids,
so nothing formal.
And Youko-sama
isn't serious about it.
Right, Youko-sama?
Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef.
Youko-sama...
See you, Onee-chan!
Wait, Yuu-kun!
Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef. Meat!
Er...
What should we do?
Youko-sama!
So, how was the meat yesterday?
No fair. That marbled wagyu beef
must've been delicious.
I'm jeal—
Huh?
You bully! Shame on you.
What?!
My first time
eating meat in so long...
It's fine. I can cook this!
All you do is fry the meat.
The outside was crunchy,
yet the inside was rare.
You messed up cooking it, huh?
Hey, you still have
some left, right?
Yes, but...
All right. I'll cook it for you.
What?
I told you, cooking is my hobby.
It's good quality meat,
so the trick is not to cook it too long.
Dinner is served!
Oh, this is it!
Ouch.
You really didn't believe
that I could cook?
What kind of eater would I be
if I couldn't cook?
I'm sure most people
think you just eat.
No way!
Well, anyway,
let's eat while it's hot!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
So tender and juicy!
Ah, this is what meat
is supposed to taste like!
The Japanese radish sauce
was good too.
I don't usually make
gourmet or expensive foods.
In other words,
mom's cooking is my specialty!
Mommy!
Be in awe and worship me!
A mom's cooking?
My mother...
She often made a dish of veal spare ribs
simmered with chickpeas.
Veal...
It was delicious...
...but today's food was just as good!
Thank you for the meal!
It's been a long time
since I've eaten at home with others!
Youko-sama...
How about seconds?
I'll fry up all the meat!
Futaba-san!
Eating delicious food
makes people happy, right?
It puts you in such a nice mood.
So you should keep eating
yummy things, Hayama-chan.
What are you implying?
I'm going to learn
to cook delicious dishes too.
And then I'll invite you both over!
I gladly accept!
What will you make?
I will poêler bakery-fresh bread crusts
topped with fresh-squeezed mayonnaise.
Then, on a whim, the chef will flambé it
with a special balsamic?
Make it on the crunchy side
with the works!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The vicious class rep,
the poor girl who lives on bread crusts,
and the walking black hole.
Their days lived in their own colors
are so entertaining!
Isn't it wonderful?
And now, please enjoy
"Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
nakami ga makkuro demo
Even if it's turned black inside
zeitaku dekinakutemo
Even if I can't be extravagant
ryou ga ookutemo
Even if there's too much to handle
sannin dakara tabechaou
Three's a crowd, so let's eat!
youryou yo ga kashikoku
I'm not wasting electricity at night
takumashiku ikitemasu wa
I'm leading a strong and healthy life
onaka ippai no mainichi nan desu
Every day, I'm eating 'til I'm full!
egao ni nareru mono
Things that make me smile?
gohan, okane, koko de wa ienai
Food! Money! And things I can't say
shiawase datte sansha sanyou
We're a happy bunch, living in our own colors
omou made tanoshimou, hachamecha na
Let's have fun and make silly memories
hora guuchoki parade, sannin atsumareba
When we're together, this Rock Scissors Parade
janken wa, aiko de, eien ni owaranai
Will continue forever in just the same way
hajimatta parade, kyousei sanka desu
This parade we've embarked on is wonderful
ichi kakeru san no kotae shiritai nara
If you want to know the answer to one times three
nee koko ni oide
Then come on over here
I'll do it!
I'll sell delicious steak
for cheaper than this place!
And so, the cooking showdown began.
Futaba went to search
for ingredients.
I bet something
like that'll happen.
This Will Not Happen
My, that would be good.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
A cooking story
needs a taste tester!
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Nishikawa
is waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste
tester.
Next
Time:
Your Birthmarks
Have Faded
Next
Time: