There are lots more yellow people in town lately.
Oh, the Yellow Scarves?
Did you hear the rumor that
the Dollars are the Slasher?
We need you.
How's he been?
He comes by sometimes.
Right up to there.
The air in Tokyo is dirty.
Don't you agree?
Pinworm!
<Kanra> Did you hear?
Somebody from Raira Academy
was attacked by the Slasher!
<Tanaka Tarou> Seriously?
<Setton> Scary.
<Kanra> I'm serious!
It was a freshman girl.
Sorry.
<Tanaka Tarou> Gotta make a call. AFK.
Don't worry.
<Kanra> It's not your girlfriend, supposedly.
Thanks.
But I'm still kinda worried.
Do you know where it happened?
Hmm, a little ways from the Higashi-Ikebukuro
subway station, near the freeway.
With all the cop cars in the area right
now, it should be easy to spot.
Oh...
Oh, sorry.
I'll be right back.
Setton-san's rubbernecking?
Ah, geez.
Sorry. I'm out, guys.
Your GF pick up?
She says she's at the station right now.
She even witnessed it or something.
I've gotta go see her.
Ah, well. Guess I'll head out too, then.
<SinSong> Today.
Cut.
Did cut.
More.
Stronger.
Love.
Wish.
The Slasher...
Is.
Want.
I had no idea that this bloodthirsty
crime would be so tightly entwined
with the fate of a single girl, and my own past.
Want Mom.
Mom.
Mom. Mom. Mom. Mom. Mom. Mom.
Turmoil Reigns
I'm back!
It's time to welcome me home!
Celty, I'm back!
Welcome back.
What's wrong?
I have seen the face of hell.
Hell?
Don't make me talk about it!
I need to forget.
Whew, I feel alive again.
Would you at least take the damn
mask off when you shower?
Absolutely not! Tokyo's air is so
filthy I must never remove it.
By the way, Celty-kun.
Nice job yesterday.
But tell me, who were those yellow fools?
They'd be the Yellow Scarves.
They showed up right after you left for America.
Though I could've sworn they went underground after they
fought with some gang called Blue Square or something...
I hope all those gangs destroy each
other and then die in the sewers.
That's absurd.
Anyway, you should pay Celty for
escorting you back here safely.
Put it on my tab.
Not happening.
Then I'll just skip out on the debt.
I was just testing you there, Celty-kun.
If you release me now-
Ow! Ow! They're poking me!
Those pointy shadowy things pricked me a little!
Shinra!
I am in grave danger here!
If you are my son, you should
know what you need to do!
Of course I do!
Pleasure doing business.
I'm writing you out of my will.
Fine with me. I don't need it.
The monster has made you her slave, I see.
I'd have no problems with Celty taking
my soul and enslaving me.
Oh me, oh my! Celty-kun! Are you in love with my son?
I knew my boy was strangely attached to you...
But you couldn't possibly be in love
with him as well, could you?
I am.
Celty!
I am overwhelmed with joy!
To think what was once a mere unrequited love
has developed so profoundly that you
would gladly tell others of our bliss!
Shut up! You're embarrassing me!
Do you think I'll allow this relationship?
I beg your pardon?
You are an uninvited guest in human society!
Do you realize that the people call you a monster?
Of course.
"Of course"?
What of it? I fail to see the problem.
My plan to take advantage of your inability
to adapt to society has failed.
Says the man who wears a gas mask all day.
And...
Shinra says he likes me exactly as I am!
Very well.
I shall allow it.
However! In exchange...
You are to call me "Daddy!"
Shut up!
In any case, without your head, your
memories will never return.
Your memories of being a Dullahan
in your homeland of Ireland.
There's nothing I can do about that...
We'll make lots of good memories
to replace the ones you lost.
Shinra...
Let's start planning the wedding.
I'll need your measurements for the dress, so
if you'd just take off those shadow clothes-
He's always been an odd boy.
Come to think of it, he did enjoy
those dissections a tad too much.
A trait he obviously inherited from you!
You mean, "from you, Daddy!"
Goodness... I just said it and you forgot already.
That carelessness is why you didn't
notice when I stole your head...
Oh, fiddlesticks!
W-W-What did you just say?
Whatever shall I do?
I have spoken aloud a most important secret!
Fear not!
Celty is too careless to notice.
Careless Celty!
Shut up!
Why'd you have to repeat it?
The attacks of an angry, clumsy girl are easily avoided!
You're not allowed to pick on Celty, Dad.
Fine, fine. I'll explain.
There's no hiding it now, I suppose.
I was indeed the culprit who stole your head
and gave it to the pharmaceutical company!
It's not something to be proud of!
Very well, come with me!
I have something to show you.
What the... He took off!
That old lech is not going anywhere!
She gone?
My plan to just push the elevator
button and hide has succeeded!
I'll come again to retrieve my luggage.
Farewell!
Damn it... Where is he?
Celty-san?
Something wrong?
You seem out of it.
I was just thinking...
About what?
You look down. Something must be bothering you.
It's just this strange Slasher rumor
that's all over the net...
Strange rumor?
Yeah, that the Dollars are behind the Slasher attacks.
That can't be... Do you believe it?
Of course not.
But if the rumor spreads, then I've got this feeling
that something terrible might happen,
especially now that tensions are mounting between
the Dollars and the Yellow Scarves.
He's right. The balance of Ikebukuro
is in danger right now.
Mikado.
I'll investigate the Slasher.
Celty-san?
You should go.
If you just sit here spacing out,
somebody's bound to mug you.
Good point.
Thank you very much.
The Slasher?
No clue, sorry.
I see...
What's the point in breaking your back for the Dollars?
It's not just for the Dollars.
I've got a bit of a score to settle, myself.
If I wasn't headless, I would've died then.
Idiot.
I'm proving I'm the idiot by saying that,
but I already know I'm an idiot, so it's fine by me!
Idiot!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
I'll kill them.
I'll kill them for sure.
And I'll kill them dead!
I'll kill them deader than dead!
Um, well, I'm the headless rider, so it's OK.
That's not the issue...
If they pull a knife on you, you've
gotta rip out their spines!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
But aren't you working?
Are you on a break right now?
Who the hell cares?
Hey! I won't have you getting fired because of me!
Besides, I need information first
if I'm going to find them.
I'll get some stuff together,
so don't do anything just yet.
Fine.
But do it quick.
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
There was a reason I left Shizuo alone for a while.
I'm happy you came to see me.
So tell me, did you ever find your head?
I'm not here to talk about that.
I'll make this quick.
I want to know about the Slasher.
Three bills.
Man, your wallet and clothes are both shadow, huh?
If I shine a spotlight on you, will you end up naked?
Wanna try it?
Not really.
I'm no pervert, unlike certain underworld
doctors and their students.
I can't get it up for headless chicks,
or just heads, for that matter.
Say what you want about me,
but the next time you insult Shinra, you pay.
True love, huh?
But you know,
if another Dullahan showed up to seduce
him, he might be easily swayed.
I'd like to think that wouldn't happen.
But if it did...
You'd kill Shinra and then off yourself?
No, I just wouldn't let any other headless
women get close to him.
I love him now, after all.
Wow, didn't see that coming!
You've become even more human!
Better be careful, though. The gap between your
head and neck might be bigger than it was.
I'll worry about that when I get my head back.
To be honest, lately I've been thinking
that I don't even need it.
Anyway, I want info on the Slasher.
Don't take my money and then
tell me you don't have any.
Don't fret, my pet.
I've got special info that neither the cops,
the media, nor even the net's privy to.
I've actually been waiting for you to come.
What do you mean?
This Slasher stuff is supernatural.
Ever heard of a katana called Saika (SinSong)?
Saika?
It's hard to believe, but Saika was a cursed
blade that actually existed here in Shinjuku.
A cursed blade?
Like the Muramasa, or something?
Yes.
A blade empowered by dark magic.
Something on your mind?
Izaya told me about a cursed blade called "Saika."
According to legend, he says, it has a mind
of its own and can possess people.
And he says that all of the Slasher's victims
said their attacker's eyes were red.
And he thinks this "Saika" is behind it?
Yes.
Every night that there's a Slasher attack,
someone with the nickname "Saika" (SinSong)
shows up on the net.
But when I was attacked, I didn't
sense them approaching me.
If Saika isn't human, I should've
felt a presence of some kind.
But if Saika's taking over their minds, then
it's a human body that's actually moving.
It's possible that the presence you
speak of doesn't actually exist.
You seem to know a lot about Saika.
Well, you told me to look into it, didn't you?
Anyway, come to bed, OK?
Shinra is hiding something, I thought.
Hi! Welcome back!
When Miss Namie here vanished
after the merger with Nebra,
I did some investigating and discovered
that she occasionally visits you.
So I used this model gun to threaten
her and we came here together.
Model gun?
Oh, I didn't tell you?
Shouldn't we report him to the police?
Oh? Wouldn't you be the ones in hot water if you did?
If my statement makes them search this room,
they'll find the head of a young woman!
It would be bigger news than the Slasher.
I guess Shinra gets his twisted personality from you.
Flattery will get you nowhere.
Though to be honest, I have no need
to recover the head right now.
My company's executives were quite surprised
by Celty's television debut.
They feel we should research the body before the head.
That's why I've decided that we're
still searching for the head.
After all, you've taken a very
unique approach to it.
Your theory that Dullahans are Valkyries,
and that you can awaken the head by involving it
in some type of power struggle is unprecedented.
Well, I'm trying everything I can think of.
If all else fails, I'll have to take it to a warzone.
For the moment, I'd like to cooperate with you.
Very well.
I've been interested in you for a while.
Nobody else I know tries to experiment
from a mythological standpoint.
Including myself.
Thanks.
Before I go, let me give you one piece of advice.
If you do create an artificial struggle here in Tokyo,
one to stimulate Celty's head, or perhaps her soul,
it would be best not to involve
her in someone else's war.
Instead, you should get the others caught
up in fighting over her body.
That's my intention.
Actually, things are progressing in that
direction faster than I thought.
Anri!
You OK getting ready for gym day?
Yes.
I've been worried! Why were you with
the students who were attacked?
Were they bullying you again?
I'm worried.
Honestly.
The Slasher might strike again...
It's dangerous to be alone!
Sexually harassing a student again?
That's naughty, Sensei.
I'm just concerned about Anri.
Whoa, first-name basis! Dangerous!
Worry too much and she might
transfer, like Niekawa-sempai!
Weren't you her teacher last year?
Niekawa Haruna-sempai's.
What?
You know Niekawa?
Sure, but just by name.
Well, it's about time we students headed home!
Who's Niekawa Haruna?
Say, Anri.
Hasn't Mikado asked you out yet?
Didn't think so.
But you know he's crazy about you, right?
Ryuugamine is a good friend...
Since my best friend seems genuinely in love with you,
I'm going to just bow out for the moment.
After all, girls all over the world need my love!
Masaomi!
Sonohara-san!
Speak of the coward.
Sorry, you guys wait long?
I thought we were gonna fossilize!
You get square root of three points.
Root? What the heck?
Say -20 points, or something I can understand!
Later!
See you tomorrow!
See you tomorrow.
You finally came.
Celty...
About Saika...
My dad had it for a while.
He sold it to an acquaintance of
his who was an antiques dealer.
He did?
Why?
Saika is said to be able to cut souls...
No way...
Yes, he used it to steal your head.
He cut the soul that held your body and head together.
And you... You knew that?
Yes.
Of course, it was only later that I learned
he used it to steal your head.
Since you were finally starting to forget about your
head, I thought it was all right not to mention it.
But...
I need to be alone for a while.
That doesn't surprise me.
Love brings confusion.
That night, the cursed blade Saika
was trying to love a girl.
A girl who couldn't find her place in reality.
Sonohara Anri.
Ikebukuro...
All that I wanted was to know the
source of this junktown's energy;
the truth about its greed, growing greater by the day.
Next time:
Even a stopped clock is right twice a day.