I will make your wish come true.
Even if it means hurting someone.
Even if it means hurting myself.
So please, once your wish comes true...
All I'll ask for...
...is your smile.
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
What, really? Iona's playing WIXOSS, too?
Hey, WIXOSS is fun stuff, really! I even bought a starter deck.
What We're Into
Yeah, but isn't this just, like, boys stuff?
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Daikichi Apartments
Ruu-chan, welcome home!
Grandma!
Kominato
I'm back, Grandma!
Long time no see, Nii-chan!
Hey, Ruuko.
Grandma!
C'mon, at least put your bag away...
It looks like they're constructing an
apartment building. It's my win.
I was so sure it'd be a office building.
Now I have to clean the bath for one week...
But at the end of the day,
either of those is just a big pillar.
A big pillar?
When the construction work is over, it'll be just like they planted a big pillar in that alley, right?
A pillar...?
Oh...
Yes. And with a pillar right there...
it'll feel like the city is just about to disappear.
All right! Grandma, your
custom-made stage was pretty hard.
My, I guess it's time for our dinner.
I'll help you!
You just came home, so relax for a while.
Yeah, you just left your bag wherever, too— Ah, crap!
Serves you right!
That's what you get.
It stinks! Onii-chan, take off your socks before you get in there!
Have some more...
I'll catch athlete's foot all over!
Grandma, I'll help you after all!
It sure is lively with your brother around...
But he's stinking the whole place up!
You must really love me to
walk me all the way out here.
Wrong! It's just that there's a vending machine around here with my favorite milk tea.
Ruuko, don't make Grandma too worried, you hear?
Worried?
Grandma told me you still haven't made friends at your new school.
I don't really need any friends...
Well, you're a tough one, so I don't mind either way.
But Grandma, you know... she can't stop worrying about you.
Here.
What's that?
Just take it.
A buddy from my part-time job told me these cards are a hit with the girls now.
I've seen some girls in my class play this.
Use this to push your way right into their group of friends.
I'm making Grandma worried...?
See ya!
Weren't you cold out there?
Coldy-coldy, warmy-warmy.
Uhm, I'm... I'm going to go study now!
Ruuko
I don't really care about making friends, but... I don't want to worry Grandma...
"The LRIG card is the player's avatar"... this one?
Cute!
So, "On the player's turn, you may..."
Her voice is cute, too!
Wait, what?!
Ouch...
Ruu-chan? Goodness, what happened?
Grandma!
Did you fall on your butt, Ruu-chan?
You... you don't hear that voice?
Voice?
I'm the only one who can hear it?
I-I'm fine! I'll go back to studying now!
You can take your bath first, okay?
Ruu-chan?
It's cold, so make sure you keep yourself warm in there!
Right, right.
Good night!
No! It's disappearing!
Don't make it disappear!
Jeez, this is all because I'm hearing that strange voice of yours!
So who are you?
And why can a card speak—
Battle!
"Battle"? You mean you want to have a card battle?
You can't eat, you know? You're made out of paper.
The noodles will make you all wet when you try to eat.
Battle!
Well, even if you tell that to me...
It's a bit too hard to ask someone here.
Wait, their cards don't talk like you do, right? Why is that?
Found you!
Huh?
You're a Selector, right?
S-Selector?
Ha! Found your LRIG!
Huh? You can hear her voice?
Of course.
See, I have a LRIG, too.
This is Hanayo-san!
Come at me!
"Come at me"?
Nice!
Perfect! No one's around!
Your card, Hanayo-san, isn't like my card at all.
She doesn't purr like a cat but speaks normally.
Your name was Ruuko-san, right?
So you can hear Hanayo-san's voice, too.
Huh? You can't hear her?
Well, I'm not a Selector after all.
I have Yuzuki speak in place of Hanayo-san for me.
"Selector"?
Let me explain.
Selectors are WIXOSS players who
strive to become the "Eternal Girl."
Huh? "Etern—
If a Selector wins battles,
she can become her ideal self.
And that self is what we call the "Eternal Girl."
You mean that her wishes come true?
Well, something like that I guess.
To be more precise, this is not entirely correct.
You become the person who can make the most outrageous wishes or dreams come true.
You can make wishes come true?
Having your dreams and wishes fulfilled is nothing but fantasy.
However, these cards can make it happen.
For that, you need to keep winning in battles.
Yet, not everyone has a deck featuring a LRIG with a mind of their own.
Only the chosen girls, the Selectors, have them.
Lately, public figures like female celebrities and athletes mentioned that they are playing WIXOSS.
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
Everyone's playing
this during
their breaks!
They are looking for other Selectors,
making it known that they own LRIGs, too.
Just saying, my card's a bit special
Won't anyone send a challenge my way?
Anyone know someone with one of those decks?
Eh? An urban legend?! lol
I heard it has a special card
Flowerhead
But don't forget this one thing.
If you lose three battles, you also lose the right to be a Selector.
The right?
The moment you lose your third battle, we disappear.
Your dreams won't come true,
and you will be barred from the world of WIXOSS and its strife to become the Eternal Girl.
Thanks, Hanayo-san!
All right then, Ruuko, let's battle!
B-But I don't have any wishes right now, and—
That's fine!
You can battle even without a wish.
Battle!
Battle! Battle!
See? She wants to fight, too. One battle won't hurt.
I guess you're right...
Great!
Yuzuki, isn't it too sudden to jump straight into a battle when she doesn't even know the rules yet?
No mercy! I'm gonna win this before she gets to know the rules!
Open!
Where... is this?
Uhm...
Battle!
"Battle"?
Yuzuki-san! Hanayo-san!
All right, I get to go first!
Okay, it's your turn now, Ruuko!
Wh-What do you mean by "turn"?
Can you hear me?
Kazuki!
The rules are simple. Summon a SIGNI, call out the name of your LRIG, and then attack.
Hey! Kazuki! Why are you on Ruuko's side?!
He can't hear your voice from the outside.
Call her name!
Name? Uhm...
T-Tama.
Why "Tama"?
Well, the sounds she makes remind me of the cat me and Grandma used to own.
Tama!
I'll give it a try!
Level 1, Grow! I summon a SIGNI! Tama, attack!
Tama!
I-It's gone... It's really gone! Hey, is it okay?!
Relax, this is only a game.
The card will recover by the next battle.
It'll recover? I see...
See what you've done, Kazuki?!
I could've won this easily if she hadn't known the rules!
Yuzuki, can you hear me, too?
I don't think you've been fair at all.
Aren't battles supposed to be fought fair and square?
Even more so if you wager your feelings to grant your wishes through them.
Level 3, Grow!
Battles are fun!
T-Tama?
More battles!
Why? Why is she so strong even though she's barely started? If this keeps up...
Hey, Yuzuki! Do you want to lose here or something?!
Hanayo-san...
Get a hold of yourself! You said that you wanted to make Kazuki your own—
D-Don't say that out loud! Hanayo-san! Hanayo-san!
Both of you, get back!
What are you kids doing?
Lunch is over! Hurry and get back to class!
Yes!
H-Hey, wait! What about our battle?
If an external influence terminates the battle, the losses are not counted. It's a Non-Game.
Th-Thank goodness...
Uhm, about earlier...
Let's go, Kazuki!
See you later!
That... That was weird. Right, Tama?
Oh?
She's been asleep since right after the battle. So cute!
She's cute, but...
They use up their power in battles.
They usually fall asleep when a
battle ends. Hanayo-san's the same.
Yuzuki-san...?
Huh? Kazuki-kun isn't around?
We don't have to be together all the time just because we're twins.
Hey, could you keep quiet about what you heard?
What do you mean?
Stop playing dumb!
I-I really don't know what you mean!
Uhm, do you want to come over to my house?
You're Ruu-chan's friend?
H-Hello.
Do you mind if we hang out?
Not at all.
Right, I was going to step out for a second.
Help yourself to the rice crackers.
Man! So you really didn't hear me!
Ruuko
I think so...
Well, there goes all that worrying.
The thing you didn't want me to know is your wish, right?
Yeah.
A wish that I want to come true.
The kind of wish that can't be fulfilled just by doing your best or anything.
Yuzuki-san...
Ever since I learned about WIXOSS and Hanayo-san, though,
I realized that things like miracles can happen.
That's why I want to believe in it!
The miracle of WIXOSS can turn me into an Eternal Girl,
and then I can realize another miracle.
A miracle through cards...
In that case, let's battle again! I'll lose to you, Yuzuki-san.
I'm not interested in this Eternal Girl thing anyway.
Nah, it's alright.
I mean, it'd defeat the purpose of my wish if Kazuki ended up hating me for that...
What do you mean?
Never mind...
Pardon my intrusion!
Grandma?
I guess young girls would prefer these over rice crackers, right?
Cake!
Tarts, macarons, bavarois...
Grandma, we can't possibly eat this a—
Thanks for the treat!
So good! They're really delicious! All of them are!
How nice. Ruu-chan, you've found a wonderful friend.
I'm recharged now. Well, see you again.
Yeah, see you.
I don't know WIXOSS too well yet, and it's a bit scary,
but I owe it to you for making Grandma happy.
Ruu-chan, dinner is ready!
Coming! Grandma, I want to show you something!
What's that?
I made one more new friend.
This
Miracle
is
Fearful
Her name is Tama.
Once you give yourself to the shadow of the clockwork
tokeijikake no kage ni unadzuitara
darkness begins to encroach from the door of the end
owari no doa ga hiraki hajimaru yami
Menacing answers lie hiding in wait
ayaui kotae soko ni miekakureru
Today's wish will become tomorrow's taboo
kyou no inori wa ashita tabuu ni naru
Lost in a labyrinth where the world is turned upside-down
ten to chi wo utsusu sakasama no meiro
the gears slowly start to turn
mawaridashita haguruma
Quietly from within the waves of people
hitogomi no naka de mimi wo sumashitara
a bell rings out, beckoning my very being
tamashii wo maneku ano suzu no ne hibiku sora e
I have no choice but to walk the endless path
mugen no hate made wo susumu shika nai
for this is the future I willingly chose
jibun de eranda mirai dakara
In the wake of the unreachable summer clouds
todokanai natsugumo yureru kagerou
lies the place of smiles I'll one day reclaim
itsuka torimodosu egao no basho
It's me and...!
I can't lose.
Tama!
Please battle with me!
Urazoe Iona?
Please!
That meeting was toxic.
That
Meeting
was
Toxic