akogarete iru no you
I always wanted
anata to sukyandaru
to have a scandal with you
itomenai no kokoro
My heart wants to win you over
ano ko yori mo hayaku
before that other girl does
hito wa
Why do we
nande nande
Why, oh, why?
nando
- even though each and every time,
kizutsuitemo
we end up feeling hurt -
koi ni
fall in love?
koi ni ochiru
Why do we fall in love?
ikimono nano
Ah, but such is life
marude marude mirukutii
Just like milk tea
betsubetsu no tokoro de umareta futari
Our hearts lie in separate places
amai amai no mirukutii
Just like this sweet, sweet milk tea
atsu atsu yo ima sugu kyun to nomihoshite
It's steaming hot, so I want you to drink it up in one go
marude marude mirukutii
Just like milk tea
zetsumyou na kagen ga wakaranai no ne
I can't make sense of this breathtaking feeling
torotorokeru no mirukutii
It's liquid velvet, just like milk tea
saigo dake chotto dake honnori to nigai
Even though it tastes slightly bitter at the end