Everything has been prepared according to the plan.
Got it.
Operation begins...
Are you going out, Kana-chan?
Good morning.
Are you going to spend your first paycheck all at once?
Not all.
I am sending some back home. Since this is a rare opportunity, I'll send some presents too.
And also...
Buy yourself some gifts?
Yes.
You were a trainee during the first month and not really doing any work...
You're happy now, right?
Ya. But I am really amazed.
I heard that late payment was commonplace.
And that they normally distribute bills instead of cash.
This is for you. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much!
I didn't expect that I would actually receive it.
That's for sure.
That's why our team is doing side jobs...
Kanata... Well...
The market opens today. This is your first time there, right?
First paycheck and first holiday, it's great to have all these "Kana-chan's firsts..." together, right?
Forget about your duties, go and get yourself relaxed.
Yes Ma'am!
Kanata's Day Off
Hairdressing
I am leaving now.
I've told you not to make Kanata aware of this!
But it is common knowledge that even the deliveries are usually delayed. It isn't possible for them to pay the salaries on time.
But still, Kanata simply believed it.
Being ingenuous is a virtue of Kanata.
Indeed.
She is totally different from you two, who immediately doubted the source of the money.
I knew I was right.
Good.
Now...
Let's forget about our original duties too.
This is really great.
I told you.
But there is still a problem.
There's no more discount.
I'm really sorry... I was too engrossed...
It seems to me that you are ready now.
Ya. No problem here.
I actually have a problem here.
I've got an idea, are you interested?
Could you explain it in detail?
This one is also cute.
So it's you guys?
Are you the seller of these?
Are you interested in it?
It's not bad.
But...
There is a problem.
Oh... What is it?
We will have to put in a great deal of effort and time to deal with such a large amount of goods in the desert.
Thinking about that, it doesn't seem so advantageous to us.
May I...
Not offering discounts is one of my business principles.
Same as the price and the taste.
I'm not asking for discounts.
I'm having it all!
Stop it.
Fire as you like.
But before that, this guy will go off.
Next time, I'll  be leaving a hole in the head of that hat's owner.
Then, I will...
You really are silly...
This is punishment for looking down on us.
Good night, little boys.
I told you.
Hey. Are you with those guys?
Mishio-chan!
Our car...!
Big brother...
Forget about it.
But... What about the gift for the boss?
Our lives are more important!
Big brother!
I didn't know that they were so dangerous!
I'm not coming to this town again!
They left.
I see.
That's enough, everyone.
I was really scared...
It seems we've fooled them.
Thank you for your cooperation.
It's okay. If the Mafia from Central got in town,
it would be hard for us to do business.
So we are helping each other out.
But for the show we just performed, I suppose we deserve some sort of incentive.
Oh you really love to joke, Migel-san.
Nope. I'm not joking.
Now we are talking about the business world, right?
Let me pay you the incentive.
Was it you guys who smashed that car back there like that?
So it wasn't you?
What's up?
Well... Nothing. Just that someone helped us destroy that car...
Inside of which, there are things they bought from the market.
I'll take it all and share half the profit with you. What do you think?
Deal.
Good.
So it finally comes to an end.
But I was really shocked.
About what?
Because Rio-senpai was so enthusiastic about it.
Unauthorized wine-making...
If this gets out, it is not just as simple as getting court-martialed...
We could be charged with breaking state monopoly law and tax law, and ultimately treason.
You are right. Even though this is a side-job inherited from our senpai,
Rio didn't object to it even once.
It was a bit surprising.
I was shocked at the very beginning...
that the fortress was producing my mother's beloved Calvados...
Then... Your contribution to this team...
Might be caused by your mother.
I'm leaving now.
Yumina-oneechan.
I've finished. Look!
It's really nice, Seiya-san.
Mishio-san, this is our first time going to a ceremony.
The bishop will be there as well... So, at least for today,...
No!
Don't make trouble for Oneesan, Mishio!
What bothers you about having your hair done?
No! Never!
Why!? You always ask me to be tidy!
Seiya you are so annoying!
Don't do this, Mishio-san.
Mishio-san!
10 dollars and 25 cents...
It is dangerous, girl.
I am sorry... I was too engrossed...
Be careful!
They are a problem.
It seems that they know about our transaction.
Are you alright?
By the way, Naomi-san...
What should I do?
It's the first time I've got enough money in my pocket...
I can buy it if I say "Please give me one"...
Hey, what would you do if someone wanted to compete with you for it?
Someone else wants it too?
Nope, it's just an example.
Well... I would...
Right, tell him that dolphins are terrible creatures that eat human beings
and ask him to forget about it.
Oh, you are really brilliant!
Ah...  I'll hold that dolphin for you until you tell me that you don't want it anymore.
You can just keep on considering it.
Then I will buy presents for others first.
Well... Dad, Mom, Grandpa, Grandma...
Waren's Grandpa, Grandma and Great-grandma...
And also neighbor's aunt Nanaya.
It's amazing... There are a lot of goods here...
Something that looks like this...
I'm really sorry.
Could it be... Mishio-chan?
What are you buying?
She's looking for a box.
A box?
Something like this. Have you seen it?
I'm sorry.
May I help you look for it?
Kanata, what are you doing here?
I'm buying presents.
I'm looking for something to send to my relatives in my hometown.
But I'm not in that much of a hurry...
I don't need it!
What's wrong with Mishio-chan...?
Well... This one is a bit...
It's really nice.
Word on the shirt: Yoroshiku (Please)
This one is also cute.
Yumina-san...?
Excuse me, Kanata-san...
Have you seen Mishio-san?
A box?
Ya... She said that it was very important to her.
I see...
When her mother passed away, all their property were taken by others.
It seems that that box was a keepsake from her mother which was taken away at that time as well.
Whenever the market is open, she goes and looks for it.
I said something rude...
I got my first paycheck yesterday...
and I said I want to get my family some presents...
You did nothing wrong.
Now, I... We all treat Mishio-san as a family member.
If Mishio-san feels jealous of you...
That means I am not doing a good enough job.
Mama...
Which one is more important to you, your precious box or Mishio?
You!
Mama...
Mishio-chan...
Mishio-chan!
Come and have a look! The famous firecrackers of Treize!
It sounds beautiful, wanna get one?
Oneechan! Yumina-oneechan!
Oneechan!
Mishio-chan!
Our car!
I am sorry... I'm not Yumina...
Oneechan! Yumina-oneechan!
Thank you.
Thanks for your work.
Now...
Excuse me...
Oh... What is it?
It wouldn't happen to be that... that car...
is Naomi-san's?...
Could it be you...?
I am really sorry...
Well... I have 150 dollars here as compensation...
Well done you guys!
Just keep that money.
I've earned a lot already.
Naomi-san... That is...!
An Idea meaning "Beautiful Spike"...
Having this carved on the seal will wish that the kid has a bountiful life like a field having big harvest.
It's great that you've got a good name, Miho.
Have you found Mishio-san?
I've tried my very best to become her family...
But it seems I still have a long way to go...
Nope... You are doing very well.
Mishio-san!
You've found it!? That's Great!
Please treasure it.
This is an irreplaceable memory of your mother...
No...
I hope you can accept this...
Mishio-san is a child adopted by the Church after she lost her family.
First, her father enrolled in the army and never returned.
And her mother...?
Mishio's family used to live in the Eastern part of the country, in Benedant.
Ah... Could it be...?
Right... In the town invaded by the invisible God of Death.
When they moved into Seize...
Her mother got sick and soon passed away...
Mama said...
I am sorry that I can no longer do your hair for you...
So...
From now on, let the person who treasures you the most do them for you.
Yumina, can you help me do my hair...?
We have to keep living...
Although we have to say goodbye to our loved ones, and are left with miserable memories...
Even so, we're alive, and we have to keep living.
And this hardship is sad but lovely.
I am sorry... Thank you...
Oneechan.
We all finished our bath.
Okay. I'm going to bathe then.
You look really tired...
Ya... I don't want to wash my hair if possible...
But a lot of things happened...
Ok then.
Please let me help you dry your hair, senpai!
I have been looking for a chance to touch it...
So in the end, you didn't buy the dolphin?
I thought it was your gift to yourself.
Rio-senpai, do you believe in fate?
Why suddenly ask this?
Well... Something that happened today made me wonder about it...
That is enough as a gift to myself.
I don't believe in it.
I hate everything being decided and granted from the beginning.
But you may be right...
A coincidence created by someone may introduce a radical change into another's life by creating a chain of affection.
If this is the so-called "Fate"...
Maybe...
D-flat.
It seems that senpai had a nice day as well.
Chirping Crickets - Spirits Down the River
Next Time :
Chirping Crickets.
Spirits Down the River
This story is fiction. It has no relation to any persons, groups or incidents in the real world.