Meet Mitsuki Koyama, 12 years old.
Her dream is to become a singer.
But, poor thing,
she only has one year to live.
Her manager's been assigned to her,
and she came by to meet Mitsuki,
and Dr. Wakaoji!
We had quite a time trying
to keep her true identity a secret!
But thanks to my efforts,
we got through it successfully!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
This embarrassing behavior
must stop, Mitsuki.
All through the meal,
you kept minding your skirt...
When you sit down to dinner,
you must...
What's that?
I-It's nothing.
I'm sorry.
I'll be careful from now on.
Good night.
Wait a minute...
I'm not done talking to you!
She didn't let me finish!
Phew! That was close!
H-Hello...
Oh, Mitsuki? It's Oshige.
Ms. Oshige!
I know this is sudden,
but we're going to
release your debut single.
What?
What? Debut?!
Thoughts on a Song
Mitsuki, this is Mr. Takasu,
the executive producer.
I'm Mitsuki Koyama,
it's very nice to meet you.
The theme for your debut single is
"a cool Lolita's dynamite love."
Um, can you repeat that
for me one more time.
Oh, if you're talking about that,
just do as I instructed you
and there should be no problem.
Oh, don't worry.
I've already told them to
make the costumes and
choreography very sexy.
S-Sexy?
Oh, you sent it? Okay!
And these are the lyrics
for your debut single
that the lyricist just sent.
Love...Me...Do?
"Love Me Do Forever."
You're a high school student, right?
Weak in English, huh?
Oh, yes. I'm sorry.
"The kiss of seduction...has them both in a
Non-stop Love Hurricane"?!
In any case,
we should just concentrate
on your debut process...
- Um...
- Huh?
Am I going to be singing this?
Do you have a problem with it?
Well, not a problem, but...
This is...
E-Excuse us for a second.
Mitsuki, what are you thinking?!
You have to look happier!
Mr. Takasu is the producer
for those wildly popular singers
like Genki Matsushita
and Rika Kobayashi!
I know...
But with that song,
Eichi won't understand.
Eichi?
Then, why don't you try writing
the lyrics yourself?
You want to put your feelings
into the lyrics, right?
Then the only way is
to write it yourself.
My feelings into the lyrics?
Why don't you try writing it
if you can?
Mitsuki, thank him and
say you'll go with his lyrics.
Newbies these days are so cocky!
Well, now that you understand,
it's okay.
I'll write it myself!
Huh?
You're exactly right.
I'll put my feelings into the lyrics.
Thank you so much for you advice.
Th-That wasn't advice.
What?! That's no good...
All right.
I'm coming over now.
Well, this will be
pretty interesting.
But you only have three days.
Let's see what a total amateur can do...
in three days.
I-I'm so sorry!
Mitsuki?
Yes...
I want to make sure of
something as your manager.
Y-Yes...
Can you tell me
about this Eichi?
So there is someone special
in your life.
Yes...
But he went to America,
and I have no way of contacting him.
I thought of becoming a singer
in the hopes that
he could be listening to my song
and realize that it's me.
All right!
If that's the case,
I'll support you.
Really?
Yes. Besides, there was nothing good
about that song.
But his songs sell, right?
Just because it sells doesn't
mean that it's a great song.
I want you to be able to debut
with a great song.
Miss Oshige...
Write beautiful lyrics and
let's show that Producer Takasu.
Yes!
Now, let's write!
What's the matter,
hurry up and write.
I want to, but...
How do I write lyrics?
Don't tell me that
you don't know how?
Nope.
Then why did you say that
you would write the lyrics?!
Well...
You get into these situations because
you get excited and
don't think before you speak!
What do I do?
I only have three days.
Leave this to me...
Do you have any CDs
or song books?
Sure. Hold on.
You always leave it there?
Yeah, if it's found,
it would get thrown away.
Here.
It's really old and frayed.
Yeah...
This is the only thing I have left
that relates to music.
I cherished it and
read it a lot.
You really are sweet.
By the way, Meroko...
what're you going to do
with that beat-up lyric book?
Well...
What?!
H-Hey! Meroko!
What are you doing?!
I have no idea
what you're saying!
Look!
Let go of...
my hand!
That was a hint.
What?
Now guess what it is?
What are you talking about?
You just bit my hand!
Exactly! I'm going to take
a bite off of it!
But, won't we get in
trouble for plagiarizing...
Of course we would!
Don't worry!
I'm just going to use
her favorite songs as reference.
I wonder...
Just do as you want!
Uh?!
W-What now?!
Now Takuto will be totally
in love with Meroko.
Geez, she said to
leave the lyrics to her,
but I'm so fed up with this...
Huh?
Mitsuki...
Oh well,
I guess it can't be helped.
You're up early...
Oh, Takuto...
Good morning...
Yeah...
Say, are you okay?
You were up pretty late.
Yeah, I think I'm okay.
I totally forgot about
my illness too...
You forgot...
This is the first time ever that
I got so focused
that I forgot about my sickness.
It feels really good to put
everything into something you love.
And...
This was from you...
wasn't it?
That's why I'm okay.
Thanks.
Never mind that.
Were you able to write the lyrics?
Yeah, I was able to but...
Let's see...
Meroko...
W-What do you think?
I-I don't know what to say...
Well then, I'll look at it.
When you laugh,
my heart turns into
a sunshine mark,
If you cry,
it turns into a flood.
Always be next to me, smiling!
Peace!
What is this?
No good, huh?
I-I didn't say that
it wasn't any good...
Yeah!
The first draft is
always a bit rough.
It's okay.
I realize that it's really bad.
But I've never experienced
these things,
so I can't really imagine
what it's like.
Then!
Why don't you
go on a date?
What?!
Then, you should be able
to write it, right?
But how?
I don't even have anyone
to go on a date with.
Oh...right...
I thought
it was a good idea.
Good morning, Mitsuki!
How are you
feeling this morning?
Oh!
There's that someone...
you can date!
What, a date with Dr. Wakaoji?!
Huh?
Wow! I've always wanted
to go to Harajuku.
It makes me glad to see
you so happy.
I never would have thought
that you'd ask me out on a date.
Well, if you're this energetic,
I'm sure your body can take it.
Yes!
All right then.
It's the start of our date.
Yes!
Wow! This is so good.
Isn't it?
I thought that you'd like it.
As expected, he's quite used
to taking girls around...
Huh, he's just showing off!
So how was the date?
Will it help with your work?
Yes, it was a lot of fun.
It seemed like I was
on a date with Eichi...
Oh!
No wonder you seemed
a little distracted. It was Eichi, huh?
Eichi, Eichi...
You're so cute!
Not really?
Well...it's about time.
Let's head home, shall we?
Yes.
Mitsuki!
Are you okay, Mitsuki?
Yes... I'm okay.
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki, hang on now.
It seems like
the medication is working.
Your fever has gone down and
your coughing has stopped.
I'm sorry, it's because
I insisted on this.
No, it was my fault for being lax.
No, that's not it!
It was because
I stayed up late last night.
Stayed up late?
Don't tell me that
was for work, too?
I did say that I'd help you.
But if you're going to push
yourself so much,
then I'm going to have to
stop your modelling job.
Doctor, please not that!
I want to make my debut
at any cost.
I have to debut and let Eichi
know that I'm here.
If I don't, I...I...
- I get it.
- Huh?
You're so determined,
I think you'll get worse
if I stop you.
No need to worry,
I'm still going to support you
on this.
Really?
Yes.
But really, you can't
push yourself too much.
Yes!
Eichi again?
Eichi is so lucky to have someone
who cares that much about him.
It's just like how much
I love you, Takuto!
G-Get off of me!
I'll be on my way.
What are you doing?
The medicine is working,
so I thought I'd...
No, you should be sleeping.
I can't sleep.
I only have one more day
until I turn in the lyrics...
Hey Takuto, make me
a 16-year-old again.
Then I wouldn't have
to worry about my body.
You're right, but...
Why do you have to
push yourself so hard?
It'll be all right, wouldn't it...
if you use the song
that Producer Takasu composed?
It's supposed to be a hit, isn't it?
No, it can't just be a hit.
My feelings have
to reach Eichi.
Well, I've had it!
Takuto?
You can forget about my support.
What do you mean?
Just give it up!
It was impossible for you
to write the lyrics to begin with.
H-Hey wait, Takuto!
Takuto! Takuto!
I can't talk!
If I don't have Takuto, then I'm...
I'll never be able to...
What do I do?
Geez, who does she think she is?
Every single sentence she utters
is about Eichi this and Eichi that...
I'm so sick of it!
Takuto! Wait!
Wait!
What's wrong with you?!
Saying such things to her?
Why are you stopping all
of a sudden!
Meroko...
Huh?...
Seems like they're arguing.
Let's go.
Oh, yeah...
What do you mean by that!
What do you mean that
the song is already finished!
Just as I said, I'm not going to
change her song for her debut.
But you promised to wait for
Mitsuki to write the lyrics!
Do you have any idea of
what it's going to cost us
if we fail on this project?
Will you take full responsibility for
leaving it up to a total amateur?
W-Well...
A promise is a promise.
So naïve...
You won't be able to survive
with that kind of thinking.
Serves him right!
You totally deserve it!
You can't even start to understand
what Mitsuki is feeling!
That's right!
You have no idea how important
a promise is to her!
I should have known better,
yet I said such a horrible thing!
I'm going home!
Hey!
Oh! What's going on?!
Mitsuki...
Earlier, I...
Hurry up and apologize!
Yeah...
Earlier, I!
Takuto?
Huh?!
What? Then this?!
I curled up this blanket
so I could fool Grandma
in case she came to check up on me
while I was working on the lyrics.
Oh...boy!
Takuto, I'm sorry about earlier...
No! That's my line.
I rely on you and
Meroko for everything.
Debuting and seeing Eichi again
are my dreams...
I'm pitiful for not
putting my own effort into it.
So you kept on writing?
Yeah...I wasted a lot of paper.
But it was fun thinking
about what I wanted to write.
Huh?
I realized that
I love singing, after all!
Earlier I thought that I would
never sing again,
and I got sad and depressed...
I do want to see Eichi,
but my desire to sing is
just as strong.
This feeling,
it's so powerful...
I can't stop it!
That's it!
What? What do you mean "that's it"?
Put those feelings that you
just spoke of into lyrics.
My feelings into the lyrics?
Yeah.
But I wonder if I can
get my feelings across?
I totally got it.
What?
Me too.
Okay! I'll try it.
That's the spirit!
Do your best.
Yes!
This is the best that I can do.
I hope this will be sufficient.
Well, I'll take it, just in case.
I guess it can't be helped!
Huh?
Oh, it's me Takasu.
Tell the writer that
we're going with different lyrics
for Mitsuki Koyama's song.
What?!
Does that mean?
I lose.
Now that you've written
these great lyrics...
we'll have to change the concept
and wardrobe all together.
Then...
You did it!
They're going to use your lyrics!
What?! Is that true?
Yeah. We're already tight
on our schedule,
and thanks to you,
it's all messed up now.
You better be prepared,
it's going to get busy.
Yes! We'll do our best!
By the way, what about
your stage name?
Huh?
That's right. Do you want to use
your real name?
N-No, that wouldn't be good.
Hey Mitsuki...
There's no need to worry
if we ever get separated.
Why?
No matter where you are on earth,
you're always able to
see the moon in the sky.
So I'll look up in the sky
to look for the moon.
So Mitsuki, you have to shine
even more than now,
so I can find you right away.
I've decided...
I'll go with Full Moon.
Yodel lay ehooo!
What was that all about?
Takuto, look! Look!
This view...
This blue sky, the green mountains...
the fresh air tastes soooo good!
We're not here to play!
It's her first assignment,
so we have to keep
an eye on things.
I know!
But can she really do it?
Well...
she is a 12-year-old inside...
Next time on Full Moon:
"Her First Assignment!"
- Look forward to it!