Having spent an eventful few weeks at Kawai Complex,
my relationship with Kawai...
Kawai, aren't you leaving yet?
...is still awkwardly distant.
Let's get outta here, Usa.
She lives in the same dorm as you, doesn't she?
You interested?
Stop it, you idiot! She'll hear you!
You've got weird tastes, dude.
I mean, she's always reading alone, she's gloomy and unsociable, and she doesn't seem to have any friends.
It's not like I'm "interested," or that I'm in love with her.
I just... want to get a little closer to her.
It's raining incessantly outside
But I don't mind since I feel at ease here
I'll turn over a new page to face
The unpredictable future lying in wait
Every morning feels incredibly bright
When I'm woken up by the hustle and bustle
And you're always right there
Standing next to me
Show me your world
And what it can be
Because look
Even your most casual of gestures
Shoots an arrow into my heart
What should we talk about tomorrow?
Let's go see how this story unfolds
The Kawai Complex Guide to Manors and Hostel Behavior
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Episode Three
Why Do You
Usa, that thing you wanted arrived at last.
It's in the backyard.
I took out all my savings and splurged on this baby!
One day, with my girlfriend seated behind me on my beloved steed
and the setting sun to my back,
I'll spend some tender moments...
Yahoo!
She'll say, "Well, aren't you in a good mood?" and—Hey!
I haven't even ridden it yet, and I own the thing!
You're such a spoilsport.
Calling dibs on the maiden ride is a sign that you have both a tiny heart and a tiny manhood.
The hell are you talking about?
You even stole the double maiden ride from me as well!
Wow, so it's a double maiden ride you dream of, huh?
Actually, how have you not done it yet?
When I was a student...
Oh... yeah...
That was really...
Wait, was that the peak?
This rope's for the luggage rack, huh?
Did my life peak back then?
Wow, this one looks nice and sturdy.
All done!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Damn, I can't get it off!
Well, Shiro is really good at tying things up.
He's a huge help when we have to
bind and dispose of old newspapers.
You're making the newspapers sound really indecent!
You all ganged up to crush this tiny little dream of mine...
We're home.
What's all the fuss about?
Oh, welcome back.
I'm home.
"I'm home," she says.
This is kinda nice.
You bought a bike?
Don't you walk to school, Ricchan?
Why don't you ride with him from now on?
I don't mind.
See, it's even got a luggage rack.
Dinner will be served soon.
Help me out, Ricchan.
Oh, right.
Whenever it looks like I'm about to get closer to her, something always goes wrong. Every single time.
Do you like Ricchan?
Th-That's not it!
I just want us to be friends.
I mean, we're both residents here, and we go to the same school.
Also, she seems fun to talk to.
Oh, crap.
And I'm a little worried because she's always by herself.
If they find out, my life is over!
Is that last point important?
I-I should go help Sumiko!
Later!
What's this?
I feel like smashing something to bits.
I don't like his chances.
We're off!
Starting today, I'm riding to school!
Good choice.
That bike looks pretty durable.
That's the first thing you thought of?
Yeah, I guess so.
Have you always walked to school?
Yeah.
W-Wow!
Isn't it kind of far?
I'm having a normal conversation with her!
Um...
Just play it cool. Play it cool.
I-If you'd like...
do you want to ride with me?
I'd rather die.
She vehemently rejected me!
F-Figures.
Who'd want to ride with me?
Sorry to weird you out like that.
I'm gonna head off, then.
No.
It's not what you think.
I don't have a problem with you.
I'm just too shy.
I mean...
The truth is...
I actually love...
As if!
Oh, man! Ricchan's quite the blossoming young lady, eh?
But I don't see why she couldn't have taken that bike ride.
It would've been a whole different story if he'd said "Wanna ride me?" instead!
You're awful, Mayumi.
Smells like teen spirit!
I, too, want to muster up all my courage to ask a
girl like that and get mercilessly rejected in return!
Yeah. Though in your case, I could see her
pulling off the seat and hurling it in your face.
I'd be overjoyed!
I feel sorry for Usa, though.
Yeah, he's got a Kawai complex, eh?
Couldn't resist the pun, could you?
Did you know?
Kawai Complex originally belonged to my grandfather.
Indeed.
All I'm doing is renting it out and acting as the landlady.
The legal owner is actually Ricchan's mother.
I could use my position as the owner's daughter
to raise the rent by fifty percent!
That doesn't sound too bad, actually.
You started this by poking fun at them, Sayaka!
Well, you joined in too!
Do you want to ride with me?
Sorry, Ricchan!
I couldn't handle a fifty percent hike!
It's not like we're that close.
Like hell she was ever gonna ride with me.
She must've found that totally weird.
And I've got library duty now, of all times.
Library
Is she here?
She probably is.
Though, well, not like she'll notice me anyway.
Usa.
I'm sorry about this morning.
I mean, I said "I'd rather die" and all that.
I realized I'd gone too far.
Though I really would rather die.
Th-That so?
But, uh...
It's not like I have a problem with you.
It's just...
I like reading books while walking.
Also...
It'd be embarrassing to ride a guy's bike.
Especially yours.
I mean, the others at our complex would definitely make fun of us.
That'd be a real pain.
Now it feels like I do have a problem with you...
Calm down! That's enough!
I appreciate the thought!
Th-That's how it is, so you don't
need to bother with me anymore.
Uh, I wish you all the best.
You too.
You know we'll still see each other at dinner, right?
Did I get closer to her or not?
Doesn't even matter anymore.
So weird.
Maybe he was right.
Maybe I do have weird tastes.
Hey, that hurts!
Knock it off, Sayaka!
You're wide open, Mayumi.
Gimme more, Sumiko!
What is this living room bedlam?
I'm tired of stepping on you.
Mind if I jump now?
Gotta love this belly.
What's the problem? We're both girls.
First off, don't just assume I got dumped!
But you make it so obvious.
You're not trying to coordinate your underwear at all.
What the hell are you doing?!
What's the problem? We're both girls.
You've got some messed-up ideas
of what girls can do to each other!
Usa!
Don't you stare at me.
I'm not as easy a woman as...
you... think!
Stare.
What was that for?!
Stop taking it out on Usa.
You're not... an easy... woman... right?
What's wrong?
Oh...
It's nothing.
Nothing?
Wasn't she crying just now?
Oh, I got a call.
Incoming
Aren't you gonna take it?
An ex, huh?
Plus, judging by that reaction...
...she's not over him yet.
A text?
Sorry
I want to hear your voice
Wow...
Hey, I just found it pathetic that he's
clinging to a woman he broke up with.
I didn't break into a smile or anything. Absolutely not.
We haven't spoken in ages, so what's his deal?
It's like he's got his back to the wall or something...
I can't believe she was able to
make her own heart skip a beat.
Why do you keep empathizing with guys so easily?
Well...
Incoming
Man, what a pain.
But I get the feeling he'll keep calling until I answer.
This is so freakin' annoying.
Hello?
What happened? Mayumi just walked
off with the biggest smile on her face.
I knew it.
She knows he's no good, so why?
I don't get it.
I think I kind of understand now.
She understands now?
I just misheard her, right?
What's with that look on your face?
Well? Are you gonna make up?
Of course not.
I'm just humoring him because he won't leave me alone.
He was three-timing earlier,
so does that mean he's two-timing now?
He says he stopped right after breaking up with me.
A likely story, right?
Not that it matters.
I'm not that easy.
Thanks for the food.
Man, he's so persistent.
Jeez...
Mayumi's so easy it hurts just to watch.
She's totally fallen for it, hasn't she?
You've got to realize that by
yourself and give it up, don't you?
I'm going back to my room.
Something's clearly up.
Don't tell me she's got a
boyfriend or someone she likes...
No way.
She's always by herself, as per usual.
I'm just overthinking this.
What are you making, Shiro?
A rapid-fire rubber-bullet gun!
Sounds fun!
Doesn't it look like something Mayumi would love?
You know, like the soap bubbles.
You're already assuming this
will end in disaster, aren't you?
Of course not.
Perish the thought.
I'm back.
Hey, Usa.
Good timing.
Could you tell Sumiko that I don't need dinner?
You're going to see him?
Thomas Three-timer?
Don't give him weird names!
I'm not going to make up with him or anything.
He keeps begging to see me, so I figured I could at least get dinner with him.
Mayumi.
Shiro made a rapid-fire rubber-bullet gun.
That's great.
Oh, and we're having chicken-and-egg bowl for dinner tonight.
Sounds good.
Take care.
What's with him?
Oh, welcome home, Ricchan.
You're going out?
To see T.T.?
Who's that?
Mayumi...
Are you happy now?
Were you always the type to ask these questions?
I just felt like asking, is all.
They're so weird.
You're quite a light eater, aren't you?
You think?
Hell no!
I just can't stand Italian cuisine!
Didn't I tell you back when we were dating?
Are you... nervous?
As if!
Juuust kidding.
Quit stretching your vowels!
Damn, I'm starting to get pissed off!
Hey...
When you're done drinking that, let's head over to my place.
At least try to talk things out!
Huh? What's the rush?
I get it.
You want dessert, don't you?
You girls really like your sweets.
And that's what makes you so cute,
but let's just get a cake to go, okay?
Who the hell do you think I am?
Sorry, did I end up giving you false hopes?
I wouldn't mind spending the night with you if I had fun, but frankly speaking, I wanna go home already.
Also...
I don't feel like faking it when I don't even like you,
so I'm gonna have to pass.
Bye-bye!
Dammit!
I should've borrowed that gun from Shiro!
Is there any chicken-and-egg bowl left?
I got a sudden craving for some, so I hurried back!
But we're having rice omelets today.
I just felt like saying that before.
I'm sorry.
Welcome back!
Ricchan!
She shed tears for my sake...
Who's that?
Was Ricchan always like that?
Books?
The protagonist resembles Mayumi in
that she keeps falling for hopeless men.
Plus, it's an epic.
You do tend to get influenced by books.
I really empathized with you until just before.
But now,
I just want you to get your act together. You're a grown-up, you know.
Give back my tears!
Yeah, Kawai really is weird.
Calm down.
And here I am, heaving a sigh of relief that there's no way she could be in love with someone,
so I'm just as weird.
Hang on.
Didn't you say you loved me?!
But that was...
Let go of me!
What's with the sudden change of heart?
You're hurting me!
S-Sayaka?
Usa...
Who're you?
What's Sayaka to you?
What, you ask?
We just live in the same complex. Right?
Y-Yeah...
Why are you looking downward?
We just... live...
That's all!
Why are you mumbling?
Please don't cause any trouble!
Stop rubbing it in.
No, really. That's all there is to it!
Oh man, what do I do?
This sounds fishy even to me!
What do you see in this snot-nosed brat?
I've always wanted an older brother, you see.
I guess I looked up to you as one.
Sorry if I gave you the wrong idea.
But they say we love the very opposite of what we admire...
Why are you looking at me?
I just found a younger guy fawning over me to be the most adorable thing,
and before I knew it, I...
Wh-What's going on?
You asshole!
You're making Sayaka say all these
things without a word of your own?
I have no idea what's going on, but I do know that things are getting worse.
H-Hey! Sayaka!
Sorry!
So casual!
On second thought, keep your mouth shut.
Lemme hit you once, and it'll be over.
But it hasn't even begun yet.
Quit your whining!
Ow!
What was that?
K-Kawai!
Uh...
Sorry. A sudden gust sent my book flying.
Huh? A gust that just hit your book and nothing else?
Yeah.
It really gave me a start.
Also, I'd like to go inside.
R-Right.
Not you.
Figures.
You better not tell me you got something going on with that high schooler too.
What?
She obviously tried to save you back there!
She tried to save me?
Your ass is grass!
Usa!
What's the matter?
Right back at you!
What a disaster, right, Usa?
Man, I was busy trying to sneak a porn mag out of a discarded stack of magazines without untying them
when a cop stopped me, went, "Not you again," and marched me back home.
Man, good thing I had, huh?
I find the idea of being saved by your retarded junior-high-level escapades really humiliating.
Thank you!
I'm really sorry I caused you trouble, Usa!
It wasn't your fault!
Listen to yourself, you idiot.
It was totally her fault.
She has a bad habit of provoking guys she doesn't even like and leading them on.
I didn't mean to!
That act of yours is seriously annoying!
But, Sayaka...
While you're free to live life how you want outside these walls,
I can't say I approve of you
bringing trouble home with you.
If this happens again, I really will raise your rent.
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure it doesn't happen again.
I thought I'd kept my address a secret.
Guess I was too naïve.
That's the moral of the story for you?
You just have to stop leading them on, woman!
But I'm not.
They fall for me all by themselves.
You set the snares yourself, so don't give me that crap!
They don't give up even when I reject them.
Hey, Mayumi.
Would you happen to know of a good way to turn people down?
Oh my god, you piss me off so much!
Maybe taking off your makeup in front of them would do the trick.
Shiro...
Thanks for that hardcore... bleurgh.
Kawai.
Thank you so much for earlier.
Earlier?
When you threw your book at the guy who was about to hit me.
Oh, that. You guys were just blocking the way.
Still, you were a great help.
Thank you.
You threw one of your beloved books at him.
Weren't you scared, though?
I was shaking in my boots.
N-Not really.
You're amazing.
Come to think of it, you tried to save Mayumi that one time too.
You're pretty reckless, aren't you?
You should be more careful.
Oh, but your recklessness saved me,
so thanks a lot!
If you hadn't done that, he
would've knocked my block off.
Stop it. You're making a mountain out of a molehill.
Hey... Your face is all red.
Because you just won't shut up!
It wasn't even that big a deal!
But you really did save me.
I told you to stop it!
Hey...
Why?
Did I piss her off?
Wait, don't tell me...
Did she get all embarrassed because I thanked her?
What on Earth?
What's with those flowers?
Now I really wanna hit him.
Usa, you see...
To tell the truth, I've been very worried.
Ricchan looks like she's fine by herself, but I think she's actually really lonely.
So please be there for her.
I'm sure you can do it.
I mean, you've gotten so close already.
I'm rooting for you!
Sayaka, you...
You're a total bitch, you know that?
What? Why?
Sayaka.
Like I said earlier,
if you bring trouble home or
mess about within this complex,
I'll get a teensy-weensy bit mad, okay?
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can hold our heads high and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
I have to disagree
I may be alone, but I'm not lonely
All the singles out there can't stand how beautiful I am
I feel bad that you fell for it, but we're just getting started here
Be it in order or chaos
We need only be ourselves
I don't care
But I can't stop thinking about it
There's a little panic in the air
So we try to help each other out
One for all, and all for one
We offer a tired mind some respite
And a lonely heart some warmth
There's always trouble brewing
And never a moment of peace
But that's the kind of place we call home
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can smile at each other and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
Preview
I swear Kawai's been looking at me—
no, me and Shiro—all weird lately!
What's wrong, Usa?
Who the hell recommended a gay novel to her?!
Gay? You mean a BL novel?
But Ricchan enters her own little world when she gets engrossed in a book,
so I wanted to see what'd happen if she read a romance novel.
That doesn't mean any romance goes!
Not to mention I'm being paired with Shiro, of all people!
Come on, do it for Ricchan. No skin off your back, right?
Very well.
Usa, feel free to tie me up with this rope!
Episode Four
For the Time Being
That's a different genre, so no thanks.