If I win, could you dress up like a girl?
You're good at joking.
Nice joke.
Could you dress up like a girl?
How did I end up in this situation?
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
"Episode 4 Me, True Colors and a Man's Dignity!"
It all began one hour ago...
Yuuji, do you wanna play "I doubt it"?
Oh? You seem confident, Akihisa.
What? I thought you learned after you
had to treat us to burgers the other day.
Thanks for the food.
I'm gonna get my revenge today.
Interesting. Why don't
I make your wallet super light?
Okay, then. We'll follow
the same rules as usual, okay?
Fumizuki Academy,
Class F's "I doubt it" Rules...
Each player plays a card, face down.
This is an ace!
The other players determine
if the player is lying or not.
If a player thinks it's a lie, they declare it.
I doubt it!
"Lie"
If it really was a lie, the person who
put out the card gets all the played cards.
On the contrary, if it wasn't a lie, the
one who declared "I doubt it" gets the cards.
The game continues until
someone has no cards left...
I doubt it!
"Lie"
The first player who runs out
of cards to play is the winner.
I doubt it!
"True"
Class F's local rule!
The player who has only
two cards left is the winner.
"Class F's local rule" "Winner"
This way, we can end the game quickly.
The key is the strategy for
the fourth card from the last.
The one who received the cards can
start with the number he or she likes.
If you say a number carelessly,
you'll be digging your own grave.
Yep, yep.
Well then, I go first, right?
Ace.
It's my turn next, right? Two.
Three.
I'm the next, huh? Fo--
I doubt it!
I didn't finish saying it!
It's so obvious.
It's totally written on your face.
Card games aren't your strong suit.
In order not to have problems later on,
I purposely put out a wrong car...
Not even a single person... was honest!
Tick-tock...
Now I don't have much room for error.
Three.
Four.
Another "four," huh, Akihisa? I doubt it!
You dummy! This is a present for you!
Seriously?! You must've had
the "four" from the first round!
So the one earlier was a set-up!
Not bad.
I can't tell them
I overlooked that card now.
Tick-tock...
I'm finally down to six cards.
Hideyoshi's got four cards.
This is the turning point.
How are those two going to play?
Six.
Muttsulini, the next is seven.
Seven!
I missed the timing to say "I doubt it"!
He's good! If someone says that in that
timing, you'd play without thinking, huh?
Then I'll...
Hm?
Oh? What're you guys doing?
I thought you went home, Himeji.
No. One of the teachers
asked me to give him a hand.
As reward, he gave this to me.
If you like, you can have this.
Thanks, Himeji. Is it okay if we
wait until we finish "I doubt it"?
We're betting...
I shouldn't say "betting."
No, i-it's not betting! The loser
just gets a small penalty game.
A penalty game?
Yeah, that's right.
The one who loses will take
off his clothes little by little.
Clothes...?
Hideyoshi...
N... No, Akihisa.
Th-That's depraved!
Himeji, it'll be just among us guys.
You don't have to get upset like that.
I doubt it!
Why are you giving me those cards?
Even if it's just among you
guys, what's wrong is wrong.
Let's have these chocolates and...
...talk...
Okay, okay. Just this time, okay?
Now, let's finish it quickly.
Hm? Hime... ji...?
Well then, eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Jack.
Queen.
I doubt it, Hideyoshi.
So as I thought, you
had four Queens, huh?
I guess I can't help it.
Since we're all guys, I can take off...
What's the matter, Hideyoshi?
--Hm?
My, my... You shouldn't sleep
in a place like this, Kinoshita.
I guess it can't be helped,
huh? I'll play for Kinoshita.
H-Hey, Himeji, that handkerchief is...
Kinoshita is tired.
B-But, Himeji, Hideyoshi was just...
But that bottle--
Muttsulini!
Looks like Tsuchiya is tired, too.
What the heck...?
I can't help but think
something's very wrong with Himeji.
Something must've...
Something must've... Ah!
Could it be... Th-That's...!
Geez... To think that he tried to
take off his clothes in front of Akihisa...
Kinoshita is tired.
There's no doubt about it. Himeji's
out of control because of that chocolate.
Is something the matter, Akihisa?
Well, we don't have enough
players since we're three now.
Why don't we stop playing?
Stop playing? Oh, don't be silly.
We do have four players, don't we?
Huh?
I'll do my best.
Shouko?! When'd you get here?!
It's a wife's job to forcefully
strip off her husband's clothes.
Dammit! There's so many things wrong
with that, I don't know where to start!
Well then, we'll play boys vs. girls, okay?
Yeah, we can finish it quicker that way.
What do we do, Yuuji?
It can't be helped.
Let's beat them quickly and end it.
But we can't let them take off their clothes.
Well, when the push comes
to shove, we can stop playing.
Yeah... you're right!
Akihisa! Just a sock isn't fair!
Yuuji, your behavior is very unmanly.
Himeji, why don't we stop?
This is just the beginning!
Shouko, you've played enough, right?
Double up.
But getting naked in
front of girls is... you know...
Don't worry, Akihisa. If you
don't wanna take off your clothes...
I can't see it! I can't see the
girls' school uniform at all, okay?
It's your own fault that you didn't
listen to me when I said it was wrong.
"Akihisa, did you notice?"
That's the emergency signal.
"What?"
"Now that it's come to this, we
must win by any means necessary."
"Shall we make a move?"
Sorry. Then, shall we
go back to the game?
Oops!
Okay! Now!
What?!
You guys made a mistake
in deciding your roles.
Yuuji, you don't make simple
mistakes like that in the game.
You sure do like to misbehave.
Naughty, mischievous kids.
Tick-tock...
Seven.
It's coming to the turning point.
If I make a mistake now,
we'll be in big trouble.
Hm?
Kubo?
"She's lying."
Kubo... You're taking my side, huh?
Thank you.
I'll make the most of this
chance you've given me!
I'm going to say it with all my heart...
That seven... I doubt it!
Sorry. It's really seven.
Kubo?!
I'm sorry, Yoshii!
"Not..."
What're you doing, Akihisa?!
As long as it involves taking
your clothes off, he's our enemy!
Why?!
Tick-tock...
Playing this game is kinda
giving me mixed feelings.
Himeji...
This really is a bad idea...
friends going against each other...
Moreover, a penalty game...
To think that Akihisa will become
a net idol from tomorrow on...!
Just a moment, Himeji!
I never agreed to the cross-dressing,
the pictures, or the net posting!
Yuuji, if you feel embarrassed,
you can close your eyes
when I take your picture.
Dammit! We're not gonna lose!
By the way, Akihisa...
Wh-What is it, Himeji?
Even if I end up having
to take off my clothes,
I'm not going to end
the game in the middle.
Shouko! You're not...
I'm somewhat confident in
the lingerie I'm wearing today.
Oh no!
They're not hesitant
to take their clothes off!
Oh...
That King you're going to play...
I'll go ahead and say, I doubt it!
Four.
Five.
Six.
"Close to victory"
I... I doubt it.
Hurry, Akihisa! They'll catch us!
I don't wanna be a net idol!
--Hey! Didn't I tell you not to run in the hall...!
--Iron man! Help us!
We'll take a remedial class or anything!
What're you guys
doing dressed like that?
We'll explain later!
On no! Akihisa, they're here!
Please wait, Akihisa!
Please put this on already!
I won't let you get away.
What did they do to end
up in this kind of situation?
Idiot Test.
What?! An Avatar system test run?!
Yeah, I want to ask
you guys for help on that.
Why us?
Because you guys are perfect for that.
If we use high-score Avatars and
things go wrong, it'll be a problem.
"Incidents in the past"
I see... Yeah, it went
out of control before.
Pointing that out hits a sore spot
for me, but in short, that's the concern.
So, keep Class A and Himeji out of this.
I wanted to help, though.
Too bad...
Well, it can't be helped, then.
I appreciate your thoughts.
Then, can I count on you guys?
What? Why do we have to do
a troublesome thing like that?
As a probationary student,
I've got chores to deal with as it is.
Who was it that was running
around in his underwear?
I'm sorry.
Well, I guess it wouldn't be
fair to have you do it for nothing.
I can at least give you some meal
tickets at the cafeteria or a book coupon.
Whoa!
Well then, I'll create a test run field
throughout the entire school building.
Those who'll be in the test run
are Tsuchiya, Kinoshita, Shimada,
Yoshii, and Sakamoto.
I'm counting on you guys.
Hold on a sec, old hag.
I thought I had high scores.
I don't care what happens to you.
Hey!
Why do we have to do this?
Yeah.
What's the problem? Why don't
we just hurry up and get it over with?
Let's see, we just have to summon
them and move them around?
Sounds like it.
Okay.
Well then...
Summon!
Oh? So in a test run, we
wear school uniforms, huh?
We're not holding weapons.
--How cute.
--This reminds us of the time we were in Year 1, doesn't it?
Hm?
Whaaaaat?!
The Avatars are talking.
The old hag said that the update was
about usability improvements, though.
At any rate, what should I do
about the incident this morning?
What, Hideyoshi?
Did something happen this morning?
I didn't say anything.
To think that a neighbor middle
school boy would confess his love to me...
What?! So someone outside of
school finally confessed his love for you?!
Th-That's not possible, right? I'm a guy.
That was the third person this month.
He's just telling secrets on his own.
It's rare to hear Hideyoshi's secrets.
Kinoshita is good at
making a poker face, so...
No, no, you guys.
I'm always acting natural.
She complimented my acting! I'm happy!
But, the truth is, I'm happy!
Hey, hey, Muttsulini.
What?
If it's naughty talk, I'm all for it!
I like that kind of talk, too,
but this one is a little different.
I'm only interested in what's
underneath your leggings.
He really talks a lot, doesn't he? How funny!
It's not funny.
I wanna see underneath your leggings.
I don't want you to smack me.
He's honest.
Maybe I'll have a little fun.
Are you interested in what's under my skirt?
I'm not interested in that stuff.
Under the skirt lies
romance, dreams, and hopes.
My interest knows no bounds.
There're many kinds of skirts such as,
straight, mini, long, flared, pleated...
Each one has its own attractiveness.
But I don't think culottes
should be called a skirt.
No, I'm really not interested.
So they actually say what
their summoners really think.
What? I can touch Minami's Avatar?
This is just crazy.
Aki, give her to me.
Pfft!
No! I'm staying with Aki!
So they go against their summoner's will, too?
They're like kids who
say what they really think.
I see... Kids, huh?
Aki! Hold me!
No cuddling! Let go of him!
No!
Now, now, Minami.
Don't worry. I'm used to things like this.
What? What do you mean you're used to?
For some reason, kids like me.
Because your brain is about
as developed as theirs, right?
Shut up, Yuuji.
Listen, listen, Aki!
Hm? What is it?
I always do harsh things
to you, but actually, I--
Eeeeeeek!
Argh!
Hey, what are you trying to say?!
Aki, are you okay? Are you in pain?
Listen to me!
I'm sorry.
I'll tell you this beforehand, Aki. I have no secre--
Actually, yesterday, a Year-1
girl confessed her love to me.
Ahhhhh!
Th-That's dirty, Aki, trying to find
out my embarrassing secrets like that!
Isn't she digging her own grave?
Don't waste your breath!
You summon your Avatar, too,
and tell us what you really think!
Whaaaaat?!
I can't participate in a revealing
contest like this. I have to do something.
They tell us what their
summoners really think...
Hm? What is it, Himeji?
Hm? Oh, no, nothing.
By the way, how do you read this?
Err... "kaku...sa...mon...dai" is it?
Yes, that's correct!
What? Why?!
"Sa-mon"
[Summon]
Oh craapp!
I'm sorry, Akihisa.
But there's something I want to hear
your true feelings about at any cost.
Nice job, Mizuki. Now, Aki,
answer me. Who do you like?!
I need to get distracted!
Oh shoot!
Oh no, I can't use that idiot.
You, too!
What'd you say?!
Hey, hey, both of you,
Be... care... ful.
I normally wear leggings...
...but I'm not wearing them today.
What're you...
Please let me flip up your skirt!
...saying, Kudou?
That's right. It's no use...
Wait! I go first!
...teasing us.
Aki, come over here.
Akihisa, I need to talk to you.
Yuuji...
We'll be right back.
This is because you're always
thinking about naughty stuff.
Please reflect on what you did.
I'm not wearing leggings, either, you know.
I'm sorry. I teased you guys a little.
Ow, ow, ow...
That wasn't nice, Kudou.
Please be a little more sensible.
So, anyway, I overslept
a little this morning,
so I didn't have time to put on my bra.
Please have mercy on us!
What's that about your bra?!
Yuuji...
It's not like that, Shouko! I'm a guy, so...
Come here...
"Boing"
Wh-What're you doing?! L-Let go of me!
Are you happy?
S-Something like this...
there's no way I'd be happy...
Yahoo!
I'm not!!
Geez, you act like you've got it bad...
I envy you, Yuuji! I'm jealous! I'm jealous!
...but look at what I have to deal with.
We'll be right back.
So, there's a proper order for
doing things. Do you understand?
Yes, Ma'am.
That's right. You don't just do stuff,
you have to come to love each other first.
Aki and I love each other!
Akihisa...
Wh-What is it, Himeji?
I-I know this is sudden, but is
there anyone whom you like?
Huh? What is this all of a sudden?
I'm realizing it anew,
but you really don't understand the
question at a time like this, do you?
Huh? What?
Well then, I'll ask you in a different way.
Oh, I bet she'll... I won't let her!
Who do you like?
Samon in Class G, maybe...
What? What? S-Samon [Summon]...?
Ahhh!
Now, let's continue this
conversation on who we like!
This isn't fair, Akihisa!
You have a secret or two that you don't
want people to know too, right, Himeji?
I-It's okay. I don't have any secrets.
To tell you the truth...
...when you had naughty thoughts earlier...
...I had strange thoughts...
Nooooooo!
How's it going?
What did they do...
...to end up in this kind of situation?
Flash! Shine! Light bulb, shiny flash!
I'm not making progress.
Someone's interfering... No, no!
The issue is, I don't have
enough common multiples
Okay, I basically get it.
What is the truth... Baby?
If you see this, draw a
diagram and explain it, Baby!
No word or number can describe you
My heart is being shocked by
the magnetic force between S and N
(S! S! Super! Sticking together,
Number! I say No.1 boy!)
Congratulations! From here on
out you're My, ma-my "treasure"
You're special to me,
no matter what happens
I'll hold you ever so
tight and never let you go
I want to be in love, in a
dream you can forget about limits
It's special, right? After all,
we came to know each other
Forgive me for being like this
Flashed! Shined! Right answer, perfect match!
Did you want something? Err...
I'm Nakabayashi. I'm the Class E rep.
I called you here because I wanted
to tell you my pent-up feelings...
Ah, no, it's not "pent-up feelings"
but heartrending feelings? Agony?
Ah, well, at any rate, I can't express it well,
but I wanted to tell you at any cost...
Are you busy right now?
I've got time. No problem.
What?!
I'd like you to go out with me!
I wonder why Yoshii is so
defenseless and charming!
His actions, his words, his gestures...
Everything about him is adorable!
Woo hoo...
Nakabayashi...
Yes...
I'm sorry.
I don't wanna be turned
down in such a humiliating way!
Question 5.
Explain the correct way to treat a burn.
Pay palimony.
That's for adults' philandering.
Next episode!
"Me, Peeking, and Training Camp!"
This will be on the test.