Nayu glasses scope!
Underwear searcher Nayu's sensors respond even to a wind swaying in for a millisecond.
By detecting the slightest disturbance in atmospheric currents,
she never misses a billowing skirt.
Everybody is in a hurry to hold down their skirts.
And here I was wondering what you were looking at so excitedly.
Good morning, Nayu-chan.
Good morning, Haruka-chan, Yako-chan.
Good morning.
You shouldn't stare at girls' underwear.
You know, it's embarrassing when your underwear can be seen.
T-That's not true!
There's nothing embarrassing about underwear!
Firstly, they retain heat.
In case of adults, they help in maintaining your figure and protect your body.
Lace, frills, embroidery and prints.
Don't you think they're all cute and pretty?
As women, we should feel proud about wearing such wonderful things.
At least, that's what my grandmother used to say.
Y-Your grandmother?
Hayama Nayu.
You made my life difficult since childhood.
I'm telling you, I'm going to put an end to this matter right now!
Hey, Hayama!
See? You feel embarrassed too.
N-No! This is, um...
E-Enough already! Let's just go to the classroom.
Oh, right. I may not be able to go home with you today.
Why not?
I was thinking of taking a look at some club activities.
Really? Which ones?
A Windy Day
Damn it, I was so distracted by Hayama that I didn't pay attention to the lesson at all.
I should hurry up and talk to her so I can be done with this.
Hey, Class Rep.
I need your help with something tomorrow morning.
Haya-
N-Nothing.
I guess I'll just wait for an opportunity to come by.
It's just my brother...
Hello?
What? Taiyaki?
That store is near your school, right?
Hey, are you listening?
But why do I have to-
I'll tell her this time for sure.
Nice shot, Sensei!
You should have been the Basketball Club advisor.
No one ever comes close to that.
She's the undisputed MVP.
Well then, your next class is about to start soon.
Okay.
I run into her so much that there must be some unseen force at work.
What? The underwear from the entrance ceremony?
Yeah. According to a company-wide survey, it seems most people feel a lot different.
It became the deciding factor to commercialize them.
Really? Wow, Keigo-san.
It's all thanks to your report.
Keep up the good work, monitor.
Sure. I'll take care of it.
At this rate, you'll end up with your own production line of underwear.
Oh, it's the train.
We'll continue this conversation later.
Nayu-chan, let's go clean somewhere else!
Be careful on your way home.
Okay, bye.
Did you hear that?
The black underwear I wore to the entrance ceremony...
I-Idiot! How many times have I told you not to talk about underwear so loudly?!
This wind is ridiculous.
I see, The Crafts Club, eh?
Yes. I thought I could be discreet about making underwear here.
Are you sure you don't mind being here?
Not at all. In fact I'm finding it interesting.
Yako-chan, you wanted to go see the Kendo Club, right?
I-I've already decided on the Kendo Club.
I'm just worried about you two.
In that case, I'm opening the door.
The troublesome trio!
Oh, are you here to join the club?
Or are you here to observe?
Are you the highest ranked student Hayama-san?
What? Oh, um... yes.
I'm so glad you're interested in our club.
Hey, that girl...
I can't believe she can suck up to teachers this much.
Anyway, take your time looking around.
Every year at the Crafts Club,
we choose a theme to work on for the Culture Festival exhibition.
We make use of everything, from woven toys to beads,
provided they live up to the festival's standards.
Wow, look at those beads.
Are you interested in the beads accessories?
I think they're cute.
But I'd rather learn sewing and other techniques for fixing clothes.
Don't cry.
T-Then what about you?
I-I'm just tagging along.
I'm not interested in such petty things.
She must love this stuff.
Beads could be good, though.
I bet they'd look cute on panties or bras.
Your mind always wanders around those things.
Are you three planning to join the club?
We can work on anything, right?
Of course.
L-Like, underwear.
Underwear?
That's ridiculous.
It'd be too embarrassing.
How can you say that?
But it's the truth.
A project is a project, but...
I don't have the courage to exhibit that.
Me neither.
They're right. Members of the opposite sex attend the Culture Festival too.
Underwear could be a little embarrassing.
E-Excuse me.
They just can't leave us alone, can they?
Don't let it get to you, Nayu-chan.
Nayu-chan?
Thanks for coming with me today.
I guess we should get going.
It's been windy all day, hasn't it?
I guess you're right.
Hey Nayu-chan, why don't you join the Cooking Club with me?
You know, you get to make pudding. It's fun.
I understand what you're trying to do,
but Nayu doesn't want to make pudding.
I know.
Why don't you make an Underwear Club?
What?!
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
No, I'm serious.
You even mentioned it a while ago.
Too bad there isn't an Underwear Club.
But how are we going to make a club?
First, we'll find people who wanna join.
In that case, we can ask a teacher and-
Wait!
What are you two saying?
It'd be great to have one, but we can't.
You're smiling.
Don't worry. You of all people will be able to accomplish that.
What happened to the passion you showed when you made me a bra?
But I don't know how to make a club.
We can find out.
But I just got enrolled.
The seniors are just three years older than us.
But I don't have the courage.
Then allow me to restore your courage.
And we'll help you do it.
But... but... but...
No one knows or loves underwear more than you.
So, I can make an Underwear Club if I put in the effort?
I've finally found you, Hayama Nayu.
I wouldn't be exaggerating if I said that I was waiting the entire day for this moment to come.
This time, I'll tell her sure!
Hayama-
It really is windy today.
All right. Let's plan our next step!
Nayu?
It's morning. Are you awake?
Nayu! You're gonna be late!
A Leaver lace strap silk bra...
Here, Nayu. A present for the future you.
It's the only bra of my creation in the entire world.
What is this, grandma?
Junior winning underwear.
W-Winning?!
Am I going for some fight?
Yes. From love to studies, there's a lot to fight for,
but you've got to pick yourself up and create your own destiny.
Wear it when you go to battle.
Don't give up until the very end.
A-All right!
I'll make an Underwear Club!
She's got a lot of energy this morning.
Good morning, Yako-chan, Haruka-chan!
Good morning, Nayu-chan.
You're pretty lively today.
Yeah, I'm going to do my best!
Today's the day I take the first step in forming the Underwear Club.
Oh, right.
But today, we're both busy with our respective clubs, so we can't help you.
Hey!
Will you be okay by yourself?
I'll be fine, thanks.
Hey!
Well, I'm going to the faculty office.
Listen up, Hayama Nayu.
I might have lost the fight against you in delivering the opening ceremony speech,
but I won't lose again from now on!
That's all.
Later.
Do you know him?
Huh? Um...
Who is he?
What?! You don't know him?
I'm Komachi! Komachi Hiroki!
Komachi from Class E, you always robbed the first place, be it the elementary or cram school!
Hey, watch yourself.
How could you hit someone with your shoe?
L-Later.
What a weirdo.
Do you remember him now, Nayu-chan?
Huh? Um... I guess he looks familiar.
Wasn't he your classmate?
That wasn't actually fun time for me.
Maybe that's why I couldn't remember.
I need to go to the faculty office.
I'll see you later.
Exactly. In other words, you need nine more members excluding yourself.
Do you have some people in mind, Class Rep?
She's starting her own club.
Hayama-san must be very motivated.
What kind of club do you want to make?
A-An Underwear Club.!
U-Underwear Club?
Yes. A club for making and studying underwear.
That's unusual.
I know, why don't you ask your assistant homeroom teacher Mizuno-Sensei?
I'm already the advisor for the Judo Club,
and a female teacher would probably be better suited for helping you with your club.
Well, you can worry about that after you get more members.
Don't be ridiculous.
Are you really serious about making an Underwear Club, Hayama-san?
Tsukamoto-Sensei...
You should consider your role as the Class Representative more carefully when you act around.
You saw the reaction of Crafts Club members, didn't you?
Gathering members for your morally questionable club will be difficult.
U-Um...
E-Excuse me!
That was rather harsh.
I have high hopes for Hayama-san.
I'm just making sure she doesn't take the wrong path.
I don't think it's right for us to call it a "wrong path".
I-I think she has courageously chosen to take a difficult path... you know..
I-I'm sorry. I didn't mean to butt in.
I-I'm so sorry! I'm just a new teacher.
An Underwear Club?
What is that?
S-She seems a little down.
She's not even doing her underwear check.
She was so cheerful this morning.
Gathering members for your morally questionable club will be difficult.
Nayu.
When you are in need of a strong heart,
wear this underwear.
Grandma...
You're right.
Things won't be easy at first.
E-Excuse me. You're wearing a cute bra.
You really think so?
It was a mail order, but it was cheap.
She's back!
You seems to be interested in underwear.
W-Would you like to form an underwear club with me?
W-What? That's a club?
I guess anyone would be surprised.
She's got it.
Y-Yes. It's a club for studying underwear.
Eh?
That sounds kind of perverted.
We've already decided to join the Basketball Club, anyway.
Don't worry about it. The battle has just begun.
Something we can help with?
T-That's okay. I've got it under control.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Thanks, Yako-chan.
What? An Underwear Club?
Sorry, not interested.
What? Seems like a naughty club.
I'm in the Going Home Club.
I can't get anyone to join.
No, no! I can't give up this easily!
Hey!
Are you interested in underwear?
Oh, are you asking about the Underwear Club?
Y-Yes...
T-Then isn't it better to join the Crafts Club?
I'm worried what the boys will think. That would be embarrassing.
I heard scary teachers like Tsukamoto-Sensei, will go harsh on you if you join the Underwear Club.
Sorry, Hayama-san.
Haruka-chan and Yako-chan might be still busy with club activities.
Maybe I'll wait for them.
Today, during Japanese Literature, the teacher told us to...
It's been a while since I've been alone.
I haven't been like this since elementary school.
Don't you think that's too much, Hayama-san?
Eh? Why?
Isn't it cute?
What? It's dirty.
You're a little strange, Hayama-san.
Grandma...
Is liking underwear really something to get embarrassed about?
Hey. Does your stomach hurt or something?
Hamachi-kun...
Komachi!
T-That's it! Komachi-kun, why don't you join the Underwear Club?
There's no way I'd join your club!
I'm aspiring to become a man.
How did you expect that I'll join some girlish club for women and children?!
Are you having trouble getting members?
Everyone's too embarrassed.
Is that what you think, Hayama?
To be honest, I'd be embarrassed.
No way!
What do you expect? I'm a guy.
You're wrong. There's nothing embarrassing about underwear.
It's embarrassing.
I'm not interested in your underwear or whatever you talk about,
but don't you think communicating your vision of underwear, would help you gather members?
My vision of underwear?
Such a relaxing bath.
Nayu, you're still in your towel?
You'll catch a cold. Go put on some underwear.
Hey, Nayu...
This is it!
Preview
Hey, do you think we could call the Underwear Club something else?
The Lingerie Club?
Underwear Club.
Inner Club.
Bra Club, Panties Club, Bra-Panties Club.
Maybe we should stick with Underwear Club.
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!
Our Respective Forms