When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Hey, Sanzenin Nagi! Be a good girl and get caught by this robot!
Don't joke with me! Why should I?
Because, there's a person who'll profit from your death.
It's impossible for the following five reasons.
What?
First: you're stupid.
Second: you're really stupid.
Third: you're extremely stupid.
Fourth: you're revolutionarily, cosmically stupid.
And fifth is...
That's enough out of you! Die!
Hayate!
What?
Did you call me, Milady?
Hayate...
Wh-Who are you?
Ah, me?
Um...
Hurry. The opening song's about to start.
Um... I'm this Sanzenin family's-
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Hey, the narration is too fast!
I'm, um...
Mr. Santa Claus, why do you never bring presents to me?
That's because your family is poor.
What? Th-Then what am I supposed to do?
Work!
Those who do not work do not deserve to eat.
If you have something you want,
do something about it with your own strength.
B-But...
But have faith.
The last one to smile is the diligent and earnest one.
Mr. Santa Claus.
Even then, I still won't give you a present.
What do you mean?
Wait, hold on!
Hey!
The last line bugged me, but I decided to believe in Santa's words and live.
Until today!
What are we going to do? If we don't have the manuscript in five minutes...
This week's volume is over!!!
Rest easy!
The fastest bicycle delivery service in the market is coming!
The fastest?
It's here! That's it!
Sorry to make you wait!
Ayasaki Hayate from the bicycle delivery service.
Signature, please?
Thank you very much, fastest bicycle delivery service in the trade with an inhuman-like sturdy body!
But seriously, are you okay?
Please don't worry.
I'm well trained.
Well, thank you for your patronage. I hope to see you again.
Hold on!
Don't worry about me.
Really.
No, in front of you! In front!
I'm sorry! Are you all right?!
How pitiful, when he's such a good boy.
Really.
That boy has terrible luck.
That hurt.
Oh man...
And it's supposed to be Christmas Eve?
Yes, right now, the boy is an ordinary high school boy that commutes to an ordinary public high school.
Hey, it's Hayate.
Why hello, my ordinary classmates that commute to my ordinary public high school.
Sorry, we're ordinary.
So what's up with the gathering?
Oh, could it be a Christmas Party?
Yeah. If you're free, you should come, too.
I'm looking forward to the party.
You can eat and drink all you want for ¥3,000.
We've got to eat a lot.
But I don't have any money, and I'm still in middle of work.
You better be ready.
You're unsociable as always.
Hayate-kun, you're very athletic, so join a club.
But that reduces the amount of time I can work.
"Work", "work", is all you say! Are you a money monger?
You can't buy friendship with money!
Besides, why do you need money that badly?
That's because... well...
My parents are unemployed.
S-Sorry, we were a little too hyper.
Bye.
Yes, if the reason they were unemployed was due to corporate downsizing, there would be room to pity him.
However, Hayate's father is...
Note: 父 means Father
Yay! You know what "searching for oneself" means?
I think there's a job more suited for me out there.
...in his own little wonderland.
Note: 母 means Mother
You see, your mother's not wasting money.
I'm investing it in my dream!
And his mother boycotts house chores and wanders the streets.
Those who do not work do not deserve to eat.
But I believe!
The last one to smile is the diligent and earnest one!
Ayasaki-kun, you're fired.
You hid your age, didn't you?
I hear you're still in high school.
H-How did you find out?
Your parents just came over and notified me.
I thought you were a diligent young man, but you betrayed me.
Anyways, your pay for the month, ¥170,000, is with your parents-
Y-You gave it to them?
If you give that much money to them,
they'll spend it all away as investments for some dream!
Ridiculous. How could there be parents like that?
Because there are, I'm working with my age hidden.
What has he done?!
They better know that that's precious money.
Dad! Mom!
Where's my paycheck?!
Thank goodness, they haven't used it yet.
Sorry~ I tried investing in my dream, but I failed.
Tehe.
Mommy.
H-How are we supposed to greet the New Year with this?
We don't have any more savings, either.
Dear Hayate-kun.
Your Christmas present.
What's this?
One... Ten... Hundred... Thousand... Ten thousand... Hundred thousand... Million... Ten million... Hundred million?
An IOU for ¥156,804,000?!
We borrowed money from very generous people!
And so, thanks for paying them back.
You idiots!!!
But you know, we can't do anything about it now that the debt has been made.
Don't turn defiant about it.
But it's a pain to work off, and we don't have money in our family anymore.
After your Daddy and Mommy did lots of thinking, we came up with a great idea.
Great idea?
I know!! We'll give it to Hayate-kun as a present!!! It is Christmas, after all.
D-Dad! Mom!
Hey, Ayasaki-san, you home?
We're here to take your son away.
Would you be the very generous people?
That's right, we're the generous people that lent money to your parents.
O-Oh please, dear generous people. My parents who owe you money are no longer here.
Besides, there's no way I can pay ¥156,804,000 back.
Don't sweat it. We're professional, as well.
Come with us, you'll go to a paradise in the south as a volunteer,
or we'll have you become a delivery man that travels across the world,
or it's not a bad idea to have you become a consultant that teaches traffic rules.
We can help you out a lot.
Where do you think you're going, kiddo?!
I managed to get away, but I never thought they'd go this far.
I can't believe my parents.
No matter how many times I read it, it says ¥156,804,000.
I guess I was abandoned by them.
But have faith.
The last one to smile is the diligent and earnest...
No!
In the end, the shrewd people are the winners.
There isn't a thing that I can gain from working diligently.
Nello from A Dog of Flanders died after being a good boy!
A Dog of Flanders (1872): Novel by English writer Marie Louise de la Ramée, about a poor Flemish boy named Nello and his dog Patrache
What is this machine?
It won't take credit cards?
It was the destined meeting of the boy and the girl.
Hayate no Gotoku!
Christmas.
We lost track of him.
What a fast kiddo.
Find him no matter what.
You two, as well. This is nowhere near enough.
Pay back everything by tomorrow,
or else you know what'll happen, don't you?!
Y-Yes.
Debt collectors like them will never let go of me.
Exactly.
You're doomed.
Just go to them and-
Hayate, you must not give up.
Since you were born a human,
you must keep working until the very end.
What can he possibly do now?
Let's kidnap that girl.
Huh?
You'll kidnap her and ask for a hundred-fifty million yen.
I see.
W-Wait, isn't that going a little overboard?
But thanks to the parents I have, my life is in danger now.
Yes. Some evil acts shall be overlooked. They have to be.
You shouldn't.
I'm sure Nello and Patrache are speaking to you from Heaven.
"Avenge us."
That's right. Even if I get arrested,
jail will have warm food and a bed.
Hey, don't touch me.
Hey, you're really cute.
You're all alone on Christmas Eve?
Let's go somewhere fun.
Don't flirt on the day Nello died.
Gaze on the painting of Rubens and reflect on your act, you fool!
Peter Paul Rubens: Flemish painter of the Late 16th and Early 17th Centuries
Hey.
I was never hit by my father, too.
We're sorry!
C-Crap, I jumped out instinctively.
Thank you.
I'm not really sure, but you saved me.
By the way, do you know what this is?
I want this "warm", but it won't come out even when I press the button.
Well, you have to put the money in.
Without this "warm", I'll freeze to death.
It's not good for a girl to catch a cold, so keep that on.
It's a cheap jacket.
It's made rough, and the fabric is heavy.
And it doesn't fit me.
But it's warm, so I like it.
Right, as a token of my thanks to this warmth, let me do something for you.
Thanks?
Anything will do. Say it.
Anything?
Are you sure?
Yup.
That's right; I have no choice but to do it.
The boy made up his mind.
He decided to have her become
the hostage to be held for ransom.
Then, I'll be really blunt.
Go out with me.
I want you!
This wrong choice of words made
the two's relationship really complicated.
Just because it's Christmas Eve...
D-Do you understand what you're saying?
I can't say things like this in jest.
I'm risking my life here.
The moment I saw you, I decided to take you away!
His seriousness passes on to her.
But correctly or not is another question.
F-Fine, but...
...never cheat on me, got it?!
Eh? Um...
Okay.
"Cheat"?
All right, then can you give me your guardian's number?
Sure.
Okay, wait for me here for a while.
My heart is still pounding.
But that man's strong and kind and cool!
Hayate.
Is this his name?
Haya-
It's time to ask for ransom money anonymously.
No one can stop me now.
Hello.
Hello, this is Ayasaki speaking.
What are you doing giving your identity out, kidnapper?
It's over.
My perfect plot...
And it hadn't even begun...
Daddy, Mommy, why is that person not wearing a coat in this cold weather?
Shh.
Yeah, this is how I'm supposed to end up.
Working diligently or trying to commit evil, neither works.
I'm tired now.
Will I die if I sleep like this?
So what if I do? It's only going to be painful even if I live on.
Not like anyone will care if I die.
Are you all right?
Oh no, you're so cold.
If you sleep in a place like this, you'll catch cold.
It was unexpected.
That kind smile was a quick remedy for the boy who was at the lowest point of his life.
Um, hello?
Patrache, I was wrong.
There's a very kind person like her in this world.
Yet, I was thinking of something as stupid as kidnapping.
What are you doing?
Don't make noise!
Hurry and get moving!
That's right; what am I doing?
Stop taking your time.
Hey-
Get in already.
Eh?
Oh no, she's getting kidnapped again.
Someone you know?
Yes. What should I do? Himegami-kun isn't around, either.
I'll borrow this for a while.
You call the police.
I will save her.
Save? But they're in a car.
Yes. This anime will never let any crimes go unpunished.
Kidnapping is not cool.
All right, we succeeded at kidnapping.
Now we can get loads of ransom money and pay our debt back.
Hey, two idiots.
You're contaminating the air, so stop breathing.
You're destroying nature.
Make sure you treat the Earth kindly.
Th-This brat!
You better not make us angry.
I told you not to breathe, you baldy!
If you don't stop acting like a snob, you'll really get it.
Don't come near me, pervert!
Come any closer, and I'll call someone over, you idiot!
You're the idiot, little one.
You think anyone can catch up to a car moving this fast?
Yes, there is.
He said he'll take me away even at the cost of his life.
So he'll come if I call him.
Then why not call him this very moment?
Hayate!
What?
Hayate.
Villains! Hand her back to me now!
Bro!
Shut up! It's his fault for jumping out in front.
How dare you two-
Can you give her back to me?
Y-Yes.
Hayate...
Get moving. Go.
Hey, how's your body?
Please don't worry; I train.
I'm really glad you're safe.
I need to repay you again.
Repay?
But I was about to-
What? Don't hesitate. Say anything you want.
Then, could you find me a new job?
Hey!
Are you really okay?
Hey, I see a red liquid coming out of you.
It's nothing. It's only a scratch on my head, body, and appendages that we can't put on the airwaves to broadcast.
Hayate!
Hey! Hayate.
Nagi.
Oh, Maria.
Perfect timing. Treat him now!
I have asked Klaus-san to come get us.
But this is...
And that pathetic looking jacket is?
Yes, it is a miserably cheap jacket,
but it's a jacket the person who saved my life gave to me.
If I don't take care of it, it'll defile the Sanzenin family's name.
The person who... saved your life?
Come to think of, the replacement for Himegami is still undecided, isn't it?
Let's put him there!
What?
Bring that injured man to this car!
Don't worry. He's taken care of.
I promised him that I'd find him a new job.
I need to show my gratitude, as well.
So I'll make him my, Sanzenin Nagi's, new butler!
Yes, it was the destined meeting.
From this day on, the boy's life takes a different turn.
But we'll save the details for another occasion.
We'll be fighting against the broadcasting code next week, too.
Hayate, you were looking for live-in work, weren't you?
Y-Yes.
Then be my butler here at the mansion.
But Hayate-kun, do you know what a butler does?
I'll do it!
No matter what happens,
I'll protect Milady, even at the cost of my own life!
What should we do about these two naturally empty minds?
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Sanzenin Nagi's Mansion and a New Start.
We meet again, kiddo.
Honestly, next week will be interesting and cool, too!