No one's home.
I'm pretending to be out.
Just leave already.
Now then...
Jeez!
This box is huge.
Enclosed merchandise must be delivered by 2/13
Qty     Item
Valentine's Day Gift
Oh, that's what it is.
Ooh.
I'm back!
Sasami-san!
I'm back home!
Would you like something to eat? Would you like to have a bath?
Or would you rather spend time with m—
The food.
Okay.
Today I've got some nice fresh mackerel.
So?
For dessert, I have jelly and...
...pudding.
Oh, you figured out I bought pudding too!
That's my Sasami-san!
There's nothing you don't know about me.
That just goes to show how much you love me!
Okay, go ahead and eat!
Feed it to me.
Such a spoiled child.
I'm starving here.
I guess I'll have to.
Open up!
Onii-chan!
What is it, Sasami-san?
Wash me.
Such a spoiled child.
Sasami-san...
Don't you think it's about time you went to school?
I can't.
You're still 16.
Your whole life's ahead of you.
Your future holds limitless possibilities.
There's nothing you can't do!
I can't.
You didn't enter high school
just to stay at home, did you?
Why not try spending some time having fun at school?
I said I can't!
My monotonous, boring, dull job as a teacher
would become simply marvelous if you'd come to school!
Don't expect anything from me.
Dry me.
Of course, Sasami-san!
Dress me.
Brush my teeth.
Of course, Sasami-san!
You're not going to bed yet, Sasami-san?
Staying up late is bad for your skin!
Shut up.
Call me if you need anything.
All right, see you tomorrow!
Oh, it's time for the late-night anime.
kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
From a god's fingertips
watashi no kisetsu tachi
My seasons are created
hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
A long dream that took me beyond the starry sky
nemuri wo yusaburu uta
Is disturbed by a song
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
I closed my ears and blended in with others
watashi ga kieta mitai datta
It made me feel like I vanished
kokoro wo enjiru ni wa
Putting on a front would be tough
zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otona ja nai
I'm not mature enough to handle the noise
deatta kouya no hana
I came across a wild flower
kowakute yasashikute
So scary but kind
fureta shunkan ni diorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touched it, even dioramas became reality
kamisama no itazura de egakareta
From a god's frivolity
watashi no mirai chizu
The course of my future is laid out
ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
A million tones will resonate
oikaketekuru ashita mo kowasu
Shattering the future coming after me
hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
Under the bright starlight, we're brought together
nukumori ga mieta yo
I caught sight of warmth
kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
As I struggle, a relationship is born
mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
The kind of relationship I want to keep
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Episode One
I'll Start Working Hard Tomorrow
Road Closed
From 2012/12/01 to 2013/05/05
Detour
Entire Road
Blocked Ahead
Detour
Open up!
I'll be heading to school now.
If you feel at all inclined, you should come too.
Onii-chan!
Take this.
A packed lunch.
For me, Sasami-san?
Ah, what a wonderful day!
I should make today a Sasami anniversary!
Actually, wow!
Today is February 14th!
Sasami-san
Licking Anniversary
Sasami-san's
Tender Anniversary
Sasami-san...
Sasami-san ...
cute, cute...
Sasami-san's
Squishy Anniversary
Calm Anniversary
Sasami-san
SASAMISAAAAAN
Eye Contact Anniversary
Sasami-san
Cream Puff Anniversary
Anniversary
Fluffy Sasami-san
Sasami-san
Suzuki Anniversary
Sasami-san's
Gobbling Anniversary
Staggering Anniversary
There's already the Sasami-san's Staggering Anniversary and
Sasami-san
Staggering Anniversary
I-love-you-big-brother
Dynamite Love Anniversary
Sasami-san
I-love-you-big-brother
Dynamite Love Anniversary
My Love for My Big Brother is as
Explosive as Dynamite Anniversary.
Oh, but it matters not.
I'll add "Sasami-san Packed a Lunch anniversary" to the list
and have a huge celebration for all three!
Don't!
It's a packed lunch.
You can't open it until lunchtime.
Oh, I see.
If you insist.
Okay, see you.
Yep! I'm off!
Big Brother Surveillance System...
activate!
And with that, I'm ready to roll.
TsukuyomilllllllllllKamiomi
Sasami
It's almost like Sasami-san and I are newlyweds.
Just go to school, already.
Hm?
Ribbit, ribbit!
I'm a cute and cheerful little frog!
Tama-san!
Paparin, morning!
What are you doing?
You'll catch a cold!
You see, the frogs...
are all gone.
So I'm being a frog instead!
Ribbit, ribbit!
The frogs are hibernating right now.
Hibernating?
What would you do if someone made a ruckus while you were sleeping?
I'd kill them!
So you should let them sleep.
You can play with them again when the spring comes.
Okay!
I won't disturb their sleep!
My stomach's growling.
Oh my. You're so helpless.
You can have this, then.
I was going to have it for lunch,
but I can buy something at school.
Onii-chan, you idiot.
This time...
I won't let it slide!
This again.
I...
can't do this.
Onii-chan...
I really...
can't handle this.
bleurgh
Vomiting
I knew it was no good.
Onii-chan, you idiot.
It was the first time I gave you chocolate.
I will give you my first time!
Tsurugi-sensei!
I don't think erotic games are
appropriate for the faculty lounge.
You owe me some barley tea.
Oh yeah, Tsukuyomi.
Did you get any chocolate?
No, not really.
I see.
Then have this.
D-Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm just showing some pity
because you're just too pathetic.
Pardon?
I'm saying...
the first person to give you Valentine's Day chocolate was...
lil' ol' me!
It should've been mine he got first.
How dare you do this to me, you loli-hag?!
bleurgh
Vomiting
Enough of this.
My life's an impossible game.
It's not worth the effort.
That's incredibly creepy, Sensei.
But I have nothing to do, Kagami-san!
I know, Kagami-san. Let's talk!
Please choose which topic you'd prefer:
"Sasami-san today," "Sasami-san yesterday,"
"Sasami-san's charms,"
"The day I argued with Sasami-san,"
and of course the popular
"Sasami-san's embarrassing incident"!
Let's talk about the world's
most interesting topic, Sasami-san,
all we want until we're blue in the face!
Huh?
I fell asleep.
Kagami-nee!
What's going on?
Tama-san?
P-Paparin!
Um, well, I certainly love you, Paparin,
but we should just be friends for now.
What should I do?!
Y-You're choking me.
Oh, hey! All three of us sisters are here.
N-Nee-san...
Tsurugi-nee!
I don't know what you're talking about, but don't leave me out!
Listen, Tsurugi-nee. The thing is...
Paparin proposed to me!
He what?
She must've misunderstood his intentions.
Valentine's Day?
Well, put simply,
it's a day when you give chocolate to someone you're fond of.
I-It is?!
Wow, no way! I can't believe it!
Sasami-san understands the world better than I do,
so I'm sure she knows about Valentine's Day.
But even though I'm sure Sasami-san loves me,
I haven't received any chocolate from her!
Oh, of course.
She must be planning to
give me some at the dinner table,
and say "I love you, Onii-chan!" while wearing a maid costume!
Like hell I will.
I have no time to waste here.
I must quickly go and buy a mountain of chocolate!
Still, that's a relief.
He just didn't know about Valentine's Day.
Oh well. I guess I'll buy him some more chocolate.
For the big brother you love:
Valentine's Day Chocolate Set
Valentine
Specials
Recommended for you
Love Between Angels
Cosmetic Gel
Comics
Beauty
Huh? I didn't know a new volume of this manga was out.
Product Details
Content
What happens in this volume:
Not honest to each other,
the couple gets into a fight
a first-class chocolatier
What happens in this volume:
Not honest to each other,
the couple gets into a fight
a first-class chocolatier
Let's see. "What happens in this volume:
Not being honest with each other, the couple gets into a fight.
But upon seeing Chiyoko's tears, Kakao
aims to become a first-class chocolatier"?
"Chocolate is everything. Chocolate is wonderful.
He doesn't care about Chiyoko anymore.
A shocking new development"?
That's too shocking!
Wasn't this called Love Between Angels?
Valentine
Specials
Chocolate Between Angels
A monumental work in choco-manga:
"Chocolate Between Angels"...
Where did the chocolate come from?!
Huh?
Choco, Choco, and Chocolate
(Limited Edition)
Blu-rays printing for Choco, Choco, and Chocolate?!
This one's only chocolate!
Where did the love and the election go?!
ChocolatelllllllSchoollllllSword/Magic
Product Details
Content
With the school festival right around the corner, the chocolate with the two is progressing rapidly!
"With the school festival right around the corner, the chocolate with the two is progressing rapidly"?!
Product Details
Content
A battle action series featuring swords,
magic, and chocolate!!
"A battle action series featuring swords, magic, and chocolate."
Product Details
Content
This work features violent imagery
and chocolate.
"This work features violent imagery and chocolate."
Product Details
Content
A chocolatey and heartrending chocotale about choco'ing the chocolate taken away by the chocolate.
As the couple chocolate each other and go choco,
they chocolatize.
"A chocolatey and heartrending chocotale about
choco'ing the chocolate taken away by the chocolate.
As the couple chocolate each other and go choco, they chocolatize."
I can't even understand what these mean anymore.
Oh yeah, I bet this is their Valentine's Day prank.
If I check out other sites...
Chief of the National Chocolate Agency Expresses Choco
"Chief of the National Chocolate Agency Expresses Choco."
Choco Chief
A real dilemma: I was told I wouldn't get promoted
unless I attend the choco meetings
"I was told I wouldn't get promoted unless I attend the chocolate meetings."
Choco Meeting
"Regarding the Chocoslovakia problem."
United Nations Security Council
Regarding the Chocoslovakia Problem
Chocos
Today's weather is generally chocolate, intermittently white chocolate,
macadamia nut chocolate for some regions
"Today's weather is generally chocolate,
intermittently white chocolate,
macadamia nut chocolate for some regions."
Choco Time
What the hell?!
Could it be...
Wow, there's such a variety of chocolate these days.
I should buy plenty and give it to Sasami-san so she'll go
"I can't eat it all. I'll share some with you too!
Don't get the wrong idea! I just don't
wanna get fat from eating too much!"
and act all coy like that!
That way, Sasami-san will still technically be giving me chocolate!
Oh no. A transformation...
This is just like in Hansel and Gretel.
Tama, you can eat all you want today!
Really?!
Now, bring it on!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Time to dig in!
Delicious!
Your attacks are too soft.
As soft as chocolate.
Don't think you've got me licked.
Licked like chocolate.
I'm gonna chew you up.
Like eating chocolate.
Moron!
You need to make a real bang with your boob missles!
What?
Don't give up just because they're small!
That's none of your business.
Choco-choco-chocolate!
All right, the target is Tsukuyomi's house!
You're nothing but a filthy demon!
Kagami, mirror the world.
Human world, return to the way you should be.
I'm home!
Sasami-san, I'm back!
I hear today's Valentine's Day!
Girls are supposed to give chocolate to boys,
but my love transcends age, gender, and blood relations,
so it's not a problem in the slightest!
S-Sasami-san!
I see.
This must mean...
"Eat me out," right?
Then I'll just help myself and lick, bite, and suck you.
I'm... I'm...
Cut that crap out...
right now!
Die!
I couldn't help it.
Okay?
Get out.
This is...
my home!
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
I'm tired.
That's the last time I ever try hard.
But hold on! You aren't getting off so easily, Sasami-san.
You're supposed to sing the ending theme every episode.
Here! Take the mic!
Please sing in a loud voice!
Bleugh!
What asshole decided I have to do something like that?
What a joke. I'll kill 'em.
Sasami-san, you've said a little too much.
Try to act a little more innocent, like a mewing kitty cat! Meow!
Don't tell me what to do.
Listen, the pre-recorded song is already playing.
Isn't that good enough?
Do I need to actually sing it every time?
I don't, do I?
Oh no, having your beautiful singing
voice broadcast out across the nation
is worth as much as the earth itself!
Wait, Sasami-san, are you listening?
Don't curl up in your blanket.
You look like you're about to go to sleep.
Be a little more involved!
Effort never betrays you!
Too bad. I couldn't get Sasami-san to get out of her bed at all.
However, I'm sure I'll deliver Sasami-san's sweet singing voice to you all next time!
Look forward to it!
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
Time for Lazy Horoscopes.
Lazy Horoscopes
Weekly Love Horoscope
Lazy Horoscope
Normal Capricorns who have a date
Weekly love horoscope.
For normal Capricorns who have a date:
Things go perfectly.
Value time with your lover like the normal people you are.
Light blue items bring good luck.
Something good might happen.
Lonely Capricorns
For you lonely Capricorns, there's nothing special.
Good things will happen if you keep on living...
probably.
Don't worry about it! Wipe away your tears.
Next time, episode two:
Next time, episode two
"Home Security Guard."
Home Security Guard