All right! I'm back!
Jeez, you made us worry.
Sorry, sorry.
It seems like she's fine.
Yeah.
You're having the sixth-graders play in overtime, right?
We agree, too.
We want to see you all at full power.
I don't like to admit it,
but this is for the best, considering your stamina and ability.
I guess we gotta go all out then.
U-Um...
Y-You say it first, Hii.
What? No, you go first, Tsuba.
What's wrong?
D-Do your best in overtime...
W-We're cheering you on.
Okay! Thanks!
Everyone! Gather around!
We need to decide on something before we start overtime.
That's it, right?
Yeah, I think that's the best thing to do.
Okay.
All right! Let's go all out!
Don't work so hard you hurt yourself again.
We need you out there.
One year ago I would have never imagined this happening.
Oh! We're all getting so much better at basketball!
I'm so happy!
Let's go! Let's show them our teamwork!
All the experience you've gathered up until now is your weapon!
No matter what happens in these next 3 minutes,
just go all out!
Okay!
Because You're Here, Tomoka
Thank's for waiting.
Let's continue what we've started.
Is your foot okay?
Oh? Are you worried about me?
Thanks.
Th-That's not what I—
Maho!
Okay!
Here I go then!
Airi!
Got it!
Hina-chan!
Oh!
Nice, Hina!
See? We're gonna keep scoring!
Hey, are you even trying?
H-Huh? Of course I am!
Then why are you acting like a scaredy-cat?
I seriously hope you aren't worried about my foot.
I just sprained it a little.
Th-That's not true...
If you don't go all out right now then you'll definitely regret it.
Don't hold back and come at me with all you've got!
I'll go all out, too!
Watch out! I'm gonna steal it from you!
I can't listen to your trash talk anymore.
I'll show you what I've got!
Nice shot, Rena.
That's the way.
Here I go!
See? I'm fine.
#13! Illegal use of hands!
Five fouls! You're out!
Did you see my true ability?
Yeah! That was some good defense!
I definitely won't foul the next time!
I'll learn how to play proper 5-on-5 basketball by next time.
I'm looking forward to that.
She should apologize to us.
We'll get much better the next time we play.
We need to show her how 5-on-5
basketball is supposed to be played!
Yep.
If I make both free throws, we'll be tied.
That should make it easier on everyone else.
This is bad. I'll end up...
My job is to give the team a boost in morale!
Nice shot, Maho!
Maho-chan has really improved.
Yeah.
Maho is the spark that gets the team going.
She's truly like "Fireworks".
But Maho isn't the only one.
okose big hareishon
Make them see that halation!
As a defender of Suzuridani, I won't let you pass!
ano hi no chikai wo hatasu tame
We'll carry out the oath we made that day.
Maho!
hirake new foumeeshon
Spread out, new formation!
Everyone knows how hard Hinata-chan has practiced.
shisen no aizu yobiau
We can see the signs as we call out for one another.
Her "Innocent Charm" makes
those around her play better!
kibou wo nosete hanate aachi
Place your hopes in it, shoot, and watch the arch!
Airi!
itsumo no doori ni ne shinjiteru
I believe in you, do it like you always do.
We've worked so hard to get here...
And we won't back down!
makasete
Leave it to me.
mune ni te wo atete hikiyoseta heijoushin
Put your hands on your chest, and calm yourself down.
The "Prismatic Bud".
Her talents have blossomed to their fullest.
kanaete kita koto sore zore ga oboeteru
I remember each and every granted wish,
Good one, Airi!
They're playing better and better.
ano hi hisokani naita koto mo
as well as that day I cried in secret.
Everyone! Stay on your marks!
onaji yume miteru no wa
We're not the only ones
Close down the spaces!
Okay!
watashitachi dake janain dayo ne
seeing these same dreams.
She's able to survey the entire
court at such a critical moment.
me no mae ni arawareta
The sparks in those unyielding eyes
The calmness of the "Ice Age" is the pillar of Keishin!
yuruganai hitomi hibana
that appeared in front of me,
chirashite
let them fly!
Over here!
okose big hareishon
Make them see that halation!
hiraku supeesu he hashirikome
Run into that open space!
daitan na forumeishon
It's a daring formation
As expected of Suzuridani. They can pull up from anywhere.
arata no rain umareru
Make a line that's never been seen before.
They're a really good team.
hibike edifikeishon
Your teachings resound
Their footwork and fundamentals are all solid.
michi no kanousei tsukami tore
they opened the path to our full potentials.
But we won't lose.
We still have our ace!
wazuka na senseishon senobi shiteita kinou he
This lingering sensation, looking back on those carefree days.
Here!
wakare wo tsugete hanate aachi
Tell me where you went, shoot, and watch the arch!
Saki!
Please, Tomo!
egao ga tookunaru yuugure
Your smile disappeared under the sunset
doushita no?
What happened?
kotoba ja nai mono ga afureru yo tomedonaku
Things we can't convey in words overflow endlessly.
I won't let you shoot!
nani mo kataranai gooru heto mukau ase
You wordlessly run to the hoop covered in sweat.
Yes!
sore ga kotae nano? to sagashita
Is that the answer you've been searching for?
Why are you smiling now?
I'm sorry, it's just that I'm having so much fun.
makenai! to tachitsukusu kimitachi mo onaji fuan no naka
You say you won't lose, but stand still in anxiety just like us.
If I hadn't met everyone at Keishin,
Subaru-san, and the girls on your team,
sore zore no kizuna heto
We're all reaching out
I wouldn't have realized how much fun basketball can be.
furueru te nobashi atte irunda ne
with shaking hands to the bonds we hold.
So, thank you.
todoke! high konekushon
Reach to our high connection!
kikoeteiru sa kokoro no koe
Can you hear my heart sing out?
I guess I should thank you a little bit, too.
kasaneta! forumeishon
It's our very own formation
You tried your best and are going to lose to us.
karamaru shisen yobi au
we communicate with not words but our eyes.
We won't let you have the sweet taste of victory.
koete! furastreishon
Overcome your frustration!
hitori ja nai koto no tsuyosa de
We're strong because we have each other.
I know I'm not the
only one who wants to win.
fukanzen na rileishon
An imperfect relation
chiisana ippo de chikazuku
take one small step at a time
Everybody else feels the same way!
"nakama" to chanto yoberu you ni
and we'll one day be true teammates.
Wow! That was amazing, Tomoka-chan!
Tomoka, you're my "Shiny Gift".
An irreplaceable treasure!
Aya! Over here!
Miyu-senpai!
Yes!
30 seconds left.
Crunch time.
Hina!
Saki!
Airi!
kimete kakenakuta
I ran my hardest up the court
I'm a part of Suzuridani, too! I'll fight till the end...
rain no mukou ni kimi ga ite
because you were waiting right by the line
...Airi-san!
miseta unifikeishon
You showed me true unification
shouri no megami hohoemu
The Goddess of Victory smiles on us.
okose big hareishon
Make them see that halation!
This ball...
hiraku supeesu he hashirikome
Run into that open space!
No one else will get it!
This is for our win!
daitan na forumeishon
It's a daring formation
The last shot!
arata no geemu hajimaru
that starts a brand new game.
hibike edifikeishon
Your teachings resound
Tomoka!
michi no kanousei tsukami tore
they opened the path to our full potentials.
wazuka na senseishon senobi shiteita kinou he
This lingering sensation, looking back on those carefree days.
Go! Tomoka!
wakare wo tsugetara egao wo tsunagete
After saying farewell, you smile with everyone else,
Not so fast!
She already got back?!
Suzuridani won't lose here!
yume mita basho he hanate aachi
aim for the place you dreamed of, shoot, and watch the arch!
No count! 50-51!
Suzuridani Girls' Academy wins!
You did it, Miyu!
We won!
Thank you very much!
I'm sorry.
I didn't shoot it in time.
You don't need to apologize.
Yeah! That was a fun match!
Yep!
Oh! That's right!
Hey...
Um...
Uh...
That was a lot of fun.
I had a lot of fun, too.
But I want to get a proper victory.
Let's play basketball through middle school, Tomoka.
Okay! I also want to play you again sometime!
Name
Ashihara Rena
Date of birth
Blood type
Class     Suzuridani Girls School
5th Year, Class 2
Height
\
Bust size
None - "They'll just get in the way."
Person she
respects
Herself.
I'll leave them to you, Aoi.
All right. I'll make sure to get them home safely.
I don't want to admit it, but the sixth-graders are amazing.
Yeah.
We need to train even harder.
Can we become as good as them?
We can! Someday, I'm sure we will.
Yes. I think we'll get even better than them.
Then let's talk about that together.
Okay!
Um, about Subaru...
Yeah. I'll take him home a bit later.
Thank you very much.
I don't think I could ever become a replacement for the bonds he has with those girls.
I'm sorry we lost again.
What are you saying, Subarun?
Boo! You aren't the reason we lost.
Your support gave us the courage to fight!
That's right!
That was the best game we've ever played!
They were just a little bit better.
Thanks.
But even so, this became your last official match.
I think this was the most fun we've ever had.
And...
And it's not the end yet.
That's right!
We can still keep on playing in middle school!
There's no way we'll stop
playing something so fun!
Please keep on teaching us!
Oh! We'll keep on getting
better in order to satisfy you!
Even when we become middle schoolers...
Even when we become high schoolers...
You'll always be our coach!
Everyone!
Jeez, why are you all crying?
You're all tears, too!
It's so weird! Even though we aren't sad at all!
Oh! I'm not sad, either!
I wonder why...
Me, too.
I want to keep on coaching you all in basketball!
As long as we have basketball, we will be together! I'm sure...
As long as we have basketball...
Subarun!
Onii-chan!
Subaru-san!
I'm sorry for being a bit selfish.
No, I don't mind at all.
Tomoka?
I-I have something... I want to ask you.
It's so pretty!
Yeah, it reminds me of that day.
I have a star I want to see.
I'm happy that you remembered.
So what was the star you were looking for?
It's probably that one.
It's there, inside those bunch of stars.
It feels just like our team.
Pleiades. The constellation of Taurus.
In Japanese, it's called "Subaru."
It's a star that's bright and far away.
Someone as small as me can't reach it.
But one day I'll reach it.
Me, along with everyone else, have worked so hard.
Under the guidance of a kind coach.
We learned how much fun basketball can be.
I wanted to tell you those feelings of mine.
I may not be able to play in any more matches as an elementary schooler,
but can I keep on feeling this way?
I should be the one asking you.
I want to keep on working hard, just like that shining star.
So...
Will you please stay by my side?
Yes!
Tomoka... is the best...
Subaru-kun! It's morning!
You're so cute!
G-Good morning!
Is that your middle school uniform?
Yes! I wanted to show you as soon as possible!
It fits you really well! It's really cute!
Th-Thank you very much!
I see. Their opening ceremony?
Must be tough on you.
My Airi has grown so much!
Yeah, we have to keep on moving, too.
That's right, Subaru!
The boy's basketball club has been reinstated!
We can start again next week!
R-Really?!
How?!
I spent summer vacation getting signatures and petitioning to the student council.
I'm the vice president now!
That's awesome, man!
Thanks, Kazunari!
That means it's time to practice!
Yeah!
As you progress into middle school, please keep on working hard at your studies and sports.
I look forward to your maturation into people who can contribute to society.
And please remember to
always live life to its fullest.
All right! We'll do our best today!
My, you seem quite hyper today.
This is the first practice we've had since starting middle school.
Oh!
Our first experience!
I'm looking forward to it!
The first time, huh?
It's been a long time since I started playing basketball.
Oh yeah, why did you start
playing basketball, Tomoka?
It was when I was very little. My mom and I—
Mokkan! Subarun! Hurry up!
Coming!
You promised you'd play with me...
Mom, you idiot.
Oh, it's open just like they said it'd be.
Yes! Only 99 more times!
Ah, were you using the hoop?
I see.
I thought you played basketball, too.
Basket... ball?
Yep, basketball.
Wow!
It's a sport where you shoot the ball into the basket.
Whoever scores the most wins.
Basket... ball...
Can I play it too?
Of course! It's a lot of fun!
Me, too...