“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Niekawa-san, how's your daughter?
You know about Niekawa?
Yeah, just the name.
Just who is Niekawa Haruna-san?
You don't say! Shizuo is much stronger than I am.
You're the guy who's been trolling the forums and chatrooms for the last half a year, right?
Run!
I really, really, really, really love you, Shizuo.
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Kadota. I need to borrow your door.
So, who's going to pay for the repairs on my door?
After I got home, I told Shinra the details about what happened,
and that it was all over.
Yet, it wasn't over. Instead, you could say it was just the beginning.
It turned out to be a very long night.
I left the unconscious man with Kadota and his friends,
and took the girl who had almost been attacked back home.
It was the girl who's always with Mikado and she asked me to show her if I really was headless...
So you did.
Just like Mikado, she wasn't surprised.
Are all kids like that today?
No, I don't think it has anything to do with how young they are.
Celty-san?
Who might you be?
It's nice to meet you, Sonohara-san.
I'm Niekawa Haruna.
Mutual Love
That said, about the Saika thing...
I know I asked you to look into it for me, but it's already over.
No problem. However, it all seems so anticlimactic,
or maybe I don't sense any closure.
Well now, what do we do with this guy?
Maybe we should call an ambulance.
For some reason,
it doesn't feel like this is over at all.
Why is that?
I'm going to quickly head over to Shinjuku and kill Izaya.
Hey! Shizu-chan totally likes Iza-Iza, doesn't he?
Are they men who happen to love each other like boys?
No way!
No, it isn't all–
Be quiet! Just the thought makes me nauseous.
Anyway, more importantly...
Don't touch it. It might have a curse on it.
This is Saika? It's just a carving knife.
I was surprised too, but the guy holding it really did have red eyes.
Plus, he was talking like a woman about love and stuff,
and stringing nonsense together.
Love?
I could tell I had seen him somewhere...
What do random stabbings have to do with love in the first place?
Is Saika a sadist?
No, it's a bit different from sadism.
Saika's goal is to love humans.
As it loves, and loves, and loves them,
it begins to love not just one, but all humans as a group.
All of us.
I don't get it.
If it loves them, why does it cut them?
Hey, Sonohara-san.
Do you know why I came to see you?
Is it about Nasujima-sensei?
I have nothing to do with him.
There are just some weird rumors going around.
That's right.
Still, I love Takashi.
All humans perform specific actions in order to show people they love them, right?
Actions?
Whether it's by talking, holding hands, embracing one another...
Were you seeing him?
It's not that I was seeing him.
We loved each other.
We were happy just knowing that the other felt the same way.
Yes. Forever, and ever, and ever.
However, one day he rejected me.
I was only trying to embody my love for Takashi.
To embody it? What do you mean?
She also wanted to express her love with some kind of action.
However, Saika is a demon sword. It doesn't have a body to love with.
And so it controlled its wielder...
And stabbed people to death.
Over and over and over. Just to confirm its love.
To give form to its love?
I was rejected by Takashi.
No, I'm not upset about that.
After all, I love Takashi.
No, I mean...
Even if Takashi will no longer accept me, even if he loves someone else,
I can forgive him.
However,
the one he loves, I can never forgive.
Never.
About five years ago, Saika disappeared for a while.
Of course, from what we've seen in the chat, it looks like it's still filled with love.
Wait, Shinra. I just remembered.
I have definitely met the man who was holding this knife.
It was the magazine reporter. His name was...
However, I can't use humans.
It just goes to show that if you want someone's love, you have to act on your own.
I thought Father could help me better than any child,
but it was no use.
That's why, by my hand, I'm going to put an end to all this.
To you, my rival in love.
T-That person was your father?
I'm pretty sure that the man who was stabbed in front of his house was Niekawa Shuji.
What could this mean?
Are you okay?
You don't feel like your mind's been cursed, do you?
No, it's all right. This isn't Saika.
Come on, take a look.
Why would a demon sword that's been written about for decades, have been made in 2009?
What's going on? I'm sure I...
You have to believe me.
I believe you, Celty. Have I ever doubted you?
Maybe that Niekawa guy knew about the legend of Saika,
and was just pretending. Or, maybe...
Anyway, if this isn't Saika...
Then there must be another Saika.
Even now, it's out there controlling someone, about to stab someone.
Hey, what about the chat? What's happening with the chat?
But I don't have feelings for Nasujima-sensei.
Sonohara-san, I don't care how you feel about Takashi.
I'm just doing the right thing for my love's sake.
I don't love you, but this girl, Saika, will love you just right.
Saika is multiplying. Into a million...
If you want me to analyze the situation, there's one theory I can give you.
Celty, think about it. If you love, and love, and love someone until you can't anymore, what do you want next?
I don't know. Isn't that enough?
Not for humans.
There's something they want to make together after they've loved each other the first time.
You don't mean...
That's right. Saika is going to make babies.
It's going to keep the babies in the souls of the humans it's stabbed.
Wait a second. One of us should watch the chat log.
You're going to find Shizuo-kun, right?
Izaya-kun!
Come out and pl–
What brings you here, Shizu-chan?
I'm here to clobber you, of course!
Why do you want to clobber me?
Because I'm irritated.
A man your age shouldn't speak such utter gianisms, Shizu-chan.
Shut up!
What part do you have in all this?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the slasher making trouble in my town.
That's a terrible accusation.
Well it doesn't make sense,
and you're involved in 99 percent of all malicious events!
Can you just believe in the other one percent this time?
You can't, can you?
I've looked up everything about you.
What a pathetic person.
Living like a groupie for a girl named Harima Mika ever since middle school,
making pretty eyes at every guy you see...
Oh, and I hear that both of your parents were killed by a burglar five years ago.
How can I get out of here?
You were in the same room with them, yet you didn't even think to try and stop him.
It's easy. Just drown everybody else out, like always.
Why is it that you were the only one who survived?
I know. You probably made those pretty eyes at the burglar.
Even though you were in elementary school.
I wonder if the criminal was a pedophile?
That's... right.
You're a parasite.
It must be nice to spend your life leeching off of others.
It isn't nice.
What?
It isn't nice... Depending on other people.
I think a parasite is a good comparison, too.
However, do you know how much you have to sacrifice in order to be a parasite without being chased away?
So you sacrificed yourself just like that so Takashi would like you?
No, Nasujima-sensei isn't worth that.
Is that so? Then, die.
A friend of yours?
Very well. I'll stab your friend before your eyes.
Then I'll finish you off.
Seriously?
My, oh my.
Celty, what is it?
What's this?
Is this a part of your plan, too?
If I could've planned on Celty showing up out of nowhere,
I would've dropped a meteorite on your house by now.
Really. For such a single-minded person, how is he so bright?
This is why I freaking hate Shizu-chan.
Niekawa.
Takashi!
Takashi! Takashi Takashi Takashi Takashi Takashi Takashi Takashi!
I don't have time to worry about you any more.
I'll let the others kill you.
Others?
Really, this isn't the time for all of them to be worrying about you.
They have more important business.
I love you... Shizuo... Shizuo... I love you...
Hey, Shinra. How many Saikas are there in South Ikebukuro Park?
I can't tell. However, Celty, one of those is the original Saika.
You should try to find that one.
Got it. That one's the "mother."
I've wanted to meet you, Heiwajima Shizuo-san.
How lovely. It's just like mother said.
We all know that you've killed our sisters. The Internet is very useful.
Is the mother not here?
Why?
At first it was difficult for us to even remember words,
but now we have an unclouded consciousness, just like our mother.
Now, Shizuo-san, show all of us your strength! Then we can all love each other!
We won't let anyone get in the way, not even that monster!
The police won't come! They're too busy right now,
because our sisters are off in other places making new sisters!
Can I ask you one thing?
What is it?
Why do you all like me this much?
Because you're strong.
That haphazard strength of yours, that's what we want.
So that we can love all humans.
It's just like humans wanting superior children.
Also, there's nobody who would love someone like you.
However, we can love you.
Get a grip, Shizuo.
If we can't take them, I want you to get out of here.
No, Celty. To tell you the truth, I'm happy.
I've always hated this strength, and there was nothing I could do about it.
I thought that there was no one who would ever accept me.
However, all of these... how many are there?
Well, there are a lot of them. So it's okay, right?
It's okay if I acknowledge my own existence. It's okay if I learn to love myself.
This power that I've always hated and wanted to get rid of...
It's okay if I let it all out, right?
By the way, you guys are not, at all,
not even the slightest bit, the type I'm into.
In fact, I hate you just about as much as I hate Izaya!
Shinra, there's something else I want to know.
You said Saika disappeared five years ago.
Why was that? What happened five years ago?
I don't think it went on vacation.
It's possible that someone, a person with a greater amount of power,
had stopped Saika.
A strong person?
I've been thinking of you all this time. And I know that you returned my love.
You used me to make money, and when you'd had enough you tried to get rid of me.
I accepted all of that, and forgave you, and I still loved you.
However, that wasn't enough. That just wasn't enough anymore.
Just then, Saika came and talked to me. Just like this...
When I gave her my blood, little by little...
Will you accept my love today?
Wait!
Niekawa-senpai, please stop.
Stop hurting people with that blade.
How did you get out of there?
Please stop.
Well, whatever. It looks like somebody saved you yet again.
However, Sonohara-san, I don't like you telling me that.
Someone like you, who was too weak to choose anything but a life as a parasite.
It's not true that I can't live without depending on others.
I choose to live that way. That's all.
Now you're quibbling.
I'd prefer it if you didn't judge whether somebody is strong or weak by the way they live!
Hey, Sonohara-san. Have you ever loved somebody?
I bet you can't. So there's no way you could understand me.
I control Saika here with the power of love.
With the power of love.
The first time Saika told me to stab Takashi, I desperately resisted.
However, when I listened to its voice, I understood.
That's why Saika and I have become the mother.
We are making lots and lots of Saika's children and conveying our love.
And through the power of our love, we may control all of mankind!
You're right. I can't love anybody.
I couldn't help fearing people after that day five years ago.
That's why I've lived depending on something else.
You don't mean...
Senpai, you've been stabbing people and making Saika's children,
however, that Saika of yours is just another one of its children.
This is the real thing.
I cannot love anyone. That is why I have lived my life depending,
no, relying on Saika to love them for me.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Durarara
Next time on
Shifts and Changes
It's false... It's true...
When a tragic past and existence are mixed together,
what she got was unrivaled power,
and an unrivaled everyday life.
Next Time: Shifts and Changes.