Time traveller Homura Akemi.
You repeated this one month countless times in multiple worlds,
changing the possibilities of the past and looking for the conclusion you wanted.
Your existence answered one question.
Why Madoka Kaname had such immense potential as a Puella Magi.
Now I can form a satisfactory hypothesis.
One's potential as a Puella Magi depends on the misfortune she's destined to carry.
It was incomprehensible to me why Madoka who had an ordinary life,
not one of a queen of a country or a savior, had such an amount of misfortune concentrated around her.
But Homura...
Could it be that she became such a powerful Puella Magi thanks to your repeating time over and over?
I thought so. You were the reason.
Or rather, the repeated use of your magic was.
What do you mean?
You rolled back time for one reason.
To save Madoka Kaname.
While you relived the same timeframe with the same purpose again and again,
you wound together numerous parallel universes.
All centered around the existence of Madoka Kaname.
As a result of that,
the fate lines of all those worlds that were never supposed to interact are now focused on Madoka.
By accepting that, we discover the origin of her immense magical power.
All the fate lines from the timelines you lived through are now wound tightly around Madoka Kaname.
That is the current situation.
You've done great, Homura. You've raised Madoka to become the most powerful witch ever.
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 11     The only remaining way
Sayaka Miki, second year student of the Mitagihara Middle School who has been missing since the 12th,
was been discovered dead in a local hotel.
As there were no signs of violence at the scene,
the police consider both accident and crime equally possible as they continue their investigation.
Next is the weather forecast.
Tonight, northwestern winds will get stronger and there will be rain.
Welcome home.
Hey Madoka.
You really don't know anything about Sayaka, do you?
Sayaka and Kyoko both died.
It is not an unexpected development.
The signs were there for a while.
Are you saying it doesn't matter? Even though they died because of you?!
Do you ever feel bad for cattle?
Do you ever think about how their meat ends up on your plate?
Stop!
That's an unreasonable reaction!
You're missing the true essence of the matter if you think it seems cruel.
To feed humans, they are protected from the wild and bred without natural selection.
The reproduction rate of livestock is overwhelmingly higher than that of wild animals.
You all live in a reasonable and mutually prosperous relationship.
Are you saying it's the same?
But rather than treating humanity as cattle, we actually make plenty of compromises with you.
We accept you as sentient beings and negotiate with you.
Can't you believe it?
Then, should I show you?
The past that Incubators and humans have shared.
You know, we have interacted with you since prehistoric times.
Countless girls have made contracts with Incubators and got their wishes fulfilled,
then devoted their bodies to despair.
What begins from a prayer ends in a curse.
It's the circle countless Puella Magi have repeated until now.
Some of them turned the tide of history and led society to a new stage.
Stop already!
They all believed you! They believed you and yet you betrayed them!
We didn't betray them, their own prayers did.
Every wish that does not fit within the bounds of reason gives birth to some kind of distortion.
It is an obvious conclusion that the outcome will be the worst.
If you consider that a betrayal, then making wishes is a mistake to begin with.
But I'm not saying that it's foolish.
Factually speaking, the history of humankind has gone on thanks to their sacrifices.
It was a plethora of tears from the past that laid foundation to your current easy life.
If you acknowledge that, then why do you consider just a few people special?
You felt nothing while watching over those girls?
You didn't even try to understand how hard it must've been for them?
We wouldn't have come to this planet to begin with if we could understand that.
In our culture, the phenomenon called emotion is only a mental disorder.
That's why we were surprised when we discovered you, humankind.
We couldn't even imagine a world where
every individual had their own feelings and yet managed to coexist.
If only... you hadn't come to this planet...
You'd still be living in caves, I think.
It's tough... To be separated from my students like this... It's tough.
Yeah...
And we don't even know what really happened.
A 3rd year student is missing too and the teachers are really worried.
So you don't know anything, either?
It seems Sayaka had love troubles with one of her friends.
She's having a hard time, too.
Usually it would become just a bittersweet memory,
but with her turning up dead...
The police are going to close the case after questioning the mourning.
There are no clues, either.
How is Madoka?
I don't know.
I feel like she knows something...
But she doesn't seem to be lying.
This is the first time I can't see through her.
I'm pathetic... She's my daughter!
This is getting to you, too.
I was thinking that it's strange.
She locked herself up in her room instead of coming to talk to me about it like usual.
I thought I could support her no matter what.
Kids her age grow up so suddenly.
It must be shocking for a parent.
So that's how it is?
You have no choice but to believe in her.
What Madoka needs the most is time to get her thoughts in order.
Just wait for a while.
It's tough... not being able to do anything.
You're still bad at that, huh?
Akemi Homura
May I come in?
This is Walpurgis Night... Kyoko told me about it.
You two were going to fight together to defeat a witch neither of you could defeat alone.
You've been preparing here this whole time, haven't you?
Will it be dangerous in the city?
Unlike the witches so far, this one doesn't need to hide and protect herself with a barrier.
Thousands will fall victim to her if she materializes even a single time.
Then she must be stopped no matter what, right?
Kyoko died too... You're the only Puella Magi who can still fight. Then...
I'm fine alone.
Even though it would be impossible for Kyoko Sakura, I can counter Walpurgis Night alone.
I wouldn't have needed Kyoko's help either. I just agreed so that she wouldn't lose face.
Really?
Somehow... I really want to believe what you're saying...
I don't want to think you'd lie to me...
I can't believe that it will be all right!
I can't believe that you're telling me the truth...
There's no way you could understand my feelings.
Homura?
Because... I live in a different time than you!
I came from the future.
I met you countless times... And I saw you die every time.
I looked for a way to save you; a way to change fate.
Trying again and again and again.
That's...
I'm sorry... You don't get it, right?
I'm weirding you out, right? It's been only a month since I transferred to the school and met you.
But for me...
But for me you are...
The more I repeated the circle, the more our timelines drifted apart.
Our feelings, too... And my words wouldn't reach you anymore.
I think I got lost a long time ago.
Homura...
The most important thing to me was saving you.
It was the only thing left showing me the way.
You don't have to understand.
I don't care if my words won't reach you.
But please!
Please, let me protect you!
Big clouds are gathering into a strong rotating updraft.
It's a blatant sign of a supercell formation!
Request an evacuation order immediately!
She's coming.
Camping? We're camping tonight?
Yeah, tonight we're all camping together!
Homura...
This time...
I'll finish you.
What's wrong, Madoka?
I'm just going to the bathroom.
Can Homura really do it by herself?
Would you believe me if I said she can't?
But I don't have to tell you.
You can see how poorly Homura Akemi will do
against Walpurgis Night with your own eyes.
Why does she keep on fighting?
Because she hasn't lost hope yet.
If she fails, she'll just negate this timeline and continue her battle.
Despite what has happened, she will continue this meaningless chain of events.
For her, stopping or giving up is out of the question by now.
The moment she realizes she can't change your fate,
Homura Akemi will despair and turn into a grief seed.
She knows that, too. So she has no choice.
She will fight even if it's hopeless.
You mean she can't be saved before her hope is restored?
Exactly.
She's just the same as any other Puella Magi.
Madoka, you've seen it too, right?
But... But... But...
Where are you going?
Mom?
I have to go and help a friend.
Leave it to the firefighters.
Us civilians should stay put.
It has to be me!
This isn't just your life!
Don't you feel anything when you think of what happened to Sayaka?
I...
I understand it, too.
I love you, Mom. And Dad.
I know how much you treasure me.
I know I mustn't throw my life away.
It's different...
Everyone's important and I have to protect you!
That's why there's a place I have to go to right now!
So you can't tell me why?
Then bring me along.
I can't. You should stay with Dad and Tatsuya and make sure they're safe.
You told me that you raised me up to be a good person.
I don't lie. I don't do bad things.
Will you believe in me now, too?
Will you think I'm doing the right thing?
Are you sure that you're not being tricked by someone?
Thank you, Mom.
If this goes any further...
I must do something...
And stop this right here...
That's...
Why?
Why can't I beat her, no matter how many times I try?
If I repeat this again... Madoka's fate will keep getting worse.
Everything I've done...
It's okay. It's okay now, Homura.
Madoka...
Madoka... you didn't?!
Homura... I'm sorry.
Artist Buriki
If someone tells me that it's wrong to hope,
I will tell them they're wrong every time.
I could tell them that countless times.
Episode 12     You were my best friend
You are my best friend.