You don't have to force yourself to show up anymore.
The Christmas event's only a week away, right?
I went to check on you guys,
but you were done for the day.
And just when I was about
to head home, I found you.
Right.
Was your car always like this?
Feels different from the one you had over the summer.
Oh, that was just a rental.
This, on the other hand,
is my beloved steed.
Hikigaya.
Mind if we take a little detour?
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something genuine
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
We're here.
Mihama
Bridge
l
v
I won't lose!
<3 Nakamura
Yuu & Saki
Celebrating 4 months together
We'll be together forever
Hikigaya.
You look kinda cool.
Well, I am trying to act cool.
So, how's it going?
Pretty bad.
And what's bad?
I'm not sure how to answer that.
Just give it a try.
Well...
The biggest problem is the lack of time.
I don't think we can turn things around in just one week.
Tamanawa and Isshiki are both scared.
They don't want to be the cause of failure,
so they're trying to make it a collective responsibility
by seeking out ideas and incorporating them all,
taking us directly into the impasse we're in now.
Not picking a leader,
someone who'd shoulder the most responsibility,
right off the bat was a huge mistake.
That's about where we stand, I guess.
You've got a keen eye.
You have quite the talent for
figuring out what people are thinking.
That's not—
However,
you don't understand how they feel.
People's thoughts don't
always mirror how they feel.
That's why they sometimes make decisions that seem nonsensical.
And that's why Yukinoshita, Yuigahama,
and you jump to the wrong conclusions.
Wait.
What do they have to do with anything?
I was asking about them. Not the event.
That said, I guess they both
boil down to the same thing.
The root cause of both problems is the same:
the human heart.
That's not something you can understand by thinking about it, though.
Is that so?
Then you need to think about it some more.
If all you can do is calculate,
take it all the way.
Come up with every possible solution and eliminate them one by one.
The last one remaining will be your answer.
I still don't think that'll help me understand.
Then you're either miscalculating or overlooking something.
Start again from the top.
You're insane.
Fool!
If feelings could be processed like that, they'd have been digitized long ago.
The last remaining answer—
the one you can't calculate—
that's human emotion.
Not that I'm one to talk.
I bet it's because I keep miscalculating things that I can't get married.
Just the other day, I went to a friend's wedding...
Nah, that's just cause nobody's
got any taste in women.
If I'd been born ten years earlier
and met her ten years earlier,
I'd probably have fallen head over heels for her.
There's no point in thinking about that now, though.
Wh-Where did that come from?
Whatever.
As thanks, I'll give you a hint.
Just this once.
When you think about something,
make sure you focus on the right point.
For example...
Instead of the Volunteers Club helping out Isshiki,
you took up her request personally.
Let's consider why you did this.
It was for the Volunteers Club—
or, well, for Yukinoshita.
Anybody could tell at a glance.
After the whole election thing went down,
Yukinoshita came to let me know.
She's not one to talk about herself,
but I could tell how she felt
by the way she was acting.
It was the same for you, I take it?
I-I'm not so sure about that.
If you did come to the same realization,
then it'd make sense for you to try to
avoid hurting them by pushing them away.
Maybe.
Just speaking hypothetically.
Yeah, I guess.
Hypothetically speaking.
But that's not what you should be thinking about.
It's why you don't want to hurt them.
And that answer should hit you immediately.
You don't want to hurt them because you care about them.
But you know what, Hikigaya?
It's impossible not to hurt others.
Whether they're aware of it or not, people hurt others just by existing.
They do it when they're alive, and they keep doing it long after they're dead.
They do it by getting involved with them,
and they might do it if they
try not to get involved, too.
But if it's someone you don't care about,
you won't even notice that you're hurting them.
What's important is being aware of the fact.
When you feel you're hurting somebody, it shows that you care about them.
That's what holding people dear is all about.
It means you're prepared to hurt them.
And that's all the hints you get.
Sometimes, people lose out on things
because they're looking out for each other.
But that's not something to feel sad about.
If anything, you should
consider it a source of pride.
That sounds awfully hard.
Yeah, it sure is.
But it's not impossible.
After all, I could do it.
But that doesn't mean everyone can.
You're being a little presumptuous.
You rebellious brat.
Fine.
Let me be honest.
Frankly, it probably doesn't
even have to be you.
Somewhere down the line,
Yukinoshita herself might change.
Or she might meet someone
who understands her someday.
Or there might be someone out there who can break through her shell.
That goes for Yuigahama, as well.
"Someday," huh?
I'm sure you guys feel like
the present means everything,
but that's not the least bit true.
The scales get balanced eventually.
That's how the world works.
However,
I want you to be the one.
I'm hoping you and Yuigahama can break through Yukinoshita's shell.
Uh...
That's easier said than done.
The present isn't everything,
but there are things you can only do now,
things you can only find here.
It's now, Hikigaya.
Now or never.
Think, writhe, struggle, and agonize.
If not, what you're going through isn't genuine.
But you can't call something genuine
just because it makes you suffer.
You really are a rebellious brat.
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
The biggest obstacle in the short-term
is of course the Christmas event.
Redial   Logs
And Isshiki Iroha's issues come with it.
Work Consulting on the Rise
Add to that Tsurumi Rumi's situation.
Students' Plea for Help
Diversifying Communication
There are unexpected dangers?
What's the optimal solution
for these three problems?
Dangers
I can't fix this alone.
HELP
Should I ask for help?
Discussion
HELP
Why am I trying to lean on others already?
Discussion
HELP
COMMUNICATION
Discussion
The bonds between people
have to be some kind of drug.
COMMUNICATION
Discussion
Before you know it,
you become dependent.
Back during the student council election,
I was given a reason.
"Do it for Komachi."
I used that as an excuse to act.
No, I had to.
I was probably mistaken at the time, and I still am now.
I need to act based on the answer—
the reason—I find for myself.
Yukinoshita and Yuigahama.
Why didn't I want them to be president?
Why did I make Komachi give me a excuse?
What was my real reason to act?
There was something I wanted.
Come in.
Hikki.
What's the matter?
You never knock.
I told you not to force yourself to show up.
There was something I needed to do here.
Wh-Why don't you take a seat?
Is something wrong?
You're not acting like yourself.
I want to make a request.
So you're finally gonna talk to us.
The Christmas event Isshiki was talking about
is going worse than I'd ever imagined.
I want your help.
But—
Look, I know what you're trying to say.
Yes, it's something I took up all by myself.
I even said it wouldn't help her in the long run.
But I'm the one who made her president.
Remember the grade schoolers
at Chiba Village?
That one girl's taking part, too.
Things haven't improved for her.
Oh, Rumi?
So I want to help her out, too.
I know that the stuff I've done is
the root cause of all these problems,
and I know I'm being presumptuous here,
but I'd still like your help.
So you're saying
it's all your fault?
Yeah. I can't deny it.
I see.
If this is all your doing, and yours alone,
then don't you think you
ought to resolve it yourself?
Right.
Sorry. Forget I asked.
Wait.
Don't give me that.
Why does it have to be like that?
That's just wrong.
No, it's not.
It's only natural that I'd have
to clean up after myself.
Yes.
No!
You've both got it all wrong!
Look, you're not the only one
responsible for this mess.
Sure, you may have come up with the ideas, and even carried them out yourself,
but we're just as responsible
for leaving it all up to you.
You know that's not true.
It is!
You're not the only one to blame for how things turned out.
I am, too, and...
You're being unfair, Yukinon.
You bring that up now?
Talk about playing dirty.
Hang on. That's not what I came to talk about.
You never said anything.
There's stuff others won't get unless you say it out loud.
You never said anything, either.
You kept talking as though nothing was wrong.
So I thought if that's what you—
if that's what you both wanted...
"Won't get it unless you say it out loud," huh?
But sometimes, you can't get through to people even if you spell it out.
That's...
I probably wouldn't accept anything anyone said at face value.
I'd fall back into my habit
of reading between the lines
and think they had ulterior motives.
Or selfish reasons for telling me.
Okay, but if they were
perfectly straight with you—
if we talk to you more, I...
That's not the point.
It's arrogant to think just saying things out loud is enough.
Self-gratifying on the part of the speaker,
and conceited on the part of the listener.
You won't always come to an
understanding by talking things out.
So it's not mere words that I want.
But...
If you don't say it, you'll never get through!
Yeah.
Expecting others to read your mind is delusional.
But...
I...
It's not empty words I'm after.
There was something else I desired all along.
Not mutual understanding,
friendship,
companionship,
or anything of the sort.
I don't care about being understood.
I simply wish to understand.
Understand, know,
and rest easy in that knowledge—
gain some peace of mind.
Wanting to know people inside-out
because being in the dark terrifies me
is an awfully self-indulgent,
egotistic,
and arrogant wish.
It's downright despicable and disgusting.
Having a desire like that
makes me sick to the stomach!
But if it's at all possible to share that desire—
if it's possible to have a relationship where you're free
to burden one another with
that repulsive self-gratification...
I know that it's out of the question!
I know that it's out of my reach!
Even so!
Even so,
I...
I want something genuine.
Hikki!
I don't understand.
I'm sorry.
Yukinon!
Hikki!
We have to go!
B-But...
Let's go after her!
She said she didn't understand.
She probably has no idea what to do.
I don't get it, either!
But we can't let things end this way!
It's now or never!
I've never seen Yukinon like that before!
So we have to go after her now...
I can walk just fine by myself.
Let's go.
'Kay!
Uh...
I wanted to call out to you, but...
Sorry, Iroha.
Save it for later.
We're taking the day off,
so I came to let you know.
A-Also—
Got it.
Hear me out, jeez.
Yukinoshita went upstairs.
Thanks. You're a lifesaver.
Yukinon!
I don't understand it.
What exactly do you mean by "genuine"?
Well...
Yukinon, it's all good.
What is?
Honestly, I didn't really get it either.
I'm sure we can understand it
better by talking to one another.
That probably won't be enough, though.
And then we'd spend our days
trying to figure it out.
But that's, like, something I can get behind.
Actually, yeah, I don't get it all.
But, you know,
I...
I hate the way things are right now!
Why are you crying?
You really do...
play dirty.
Hikigaya.
Yeah?
I accept your request.
Thanks.
I'll help too.
Even so, Hikigaya Hachiman.
You're lifesavers.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
And so, Yukinoshita Yukino.
Nothing beats a good beer!
I was so out of character in delivering that cool speech.
Way to go, me!
I'm a fine teacher!
Wait, a fine woman?
Why can't a fine woman like me get married?
Get me some chicken and wasabi, please!
And a husband while you're at it!
Just kidding.
Man, it's almost Christmas.
Makes me sick.
If only I didn't have to work.
If I didn't have to work,
I could party Christmas away!
I'd like a Highball, please!
I wanna get married...