In this world, everyone has something they haven't seen before.
It's all a lie.
This thing...
Mold
What? Why is there mold?
The mold was just removed a few days ago.
That's very kind, very sweet.
If it could be seen, everyone would probably want it too.
That's why the world hid that.
Not to let people get hold of it so easily.
Damn, it won't come off.
But...
However, someone will find it one day.
There will be one person, to find that.
That's what the thing is.
To
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
Tiger and Dragon
Eco, Eco, Eco, Ecology.
Parrot-chan, are you still sleeping?
It's morning.
I've caught you.
Ryuu-chan, you're so cold.
Didn't I say last night that I'm starting school today?
Whoa, the opening ceremony, eh?
Congratulations on that.
Is that the way to greet a new year of schooling?
Hey, this room is so dark, move the curtains.
It's open.
Eh?
Ah...
What a large condominium.
Takasu's home
I wonder what kind of a person lives inside there...
Ever since this was built, our sunlight was snatched away.
This
Now, things that were washed won't dry easily,
and everyday, everyday, there's mold, there's mold.
Ryuu-chan, that dark expression of yours looks the same as father's!
Looks just the same... Looks just the same...
Don't put me together with that...
Ah, so cool! More and more like your father.
Huh? Are you going already, Ryuu-chan?
What about my breakfast?
In the usual place.
That. Only that...
I didn't want to be told.
Just because of this expression that you praised,
I... I...
Hey, wait up!
Ta-Ta-Takasu-ke!
What have you done?
Eh, what?
Isn't it a good day today?
Here, please let us go!
Eh?
That's all we have right now.
It's true, we'll top you up next time!
Ah, no.
Sorry!
I...
Again? You're really find dropped wallets really often.
Yeah...
Hey, if only we're still in the same class.
Yeah.
There it is!
That's great, the same class.
Shoot, again.
Yo!
We're in the same class again, Takasu.
Kitamura.
Now, the opening ceremony officially ends.
Return to your respective classes and get ready for homeroom.
New class, need to start all over and clear the misunderstanding again, huh?
It's alright, at least it's not everyone, because I understand you.
Ah, thank you.
That's right, there's someone who understands me,
and he's in this class.
Yo, Kitamura-kun!
We're in the same class this year too.
Oh, Kushieda. You're in Class C too?
It's Takasu-kun, right?
Do you still remember me? I've appeared around Kitamura-kun several times.
K-Kushieda Minori, right?
Wow, you remembered my full name.
I'm glad.
Well then, let's experience the lively spring!
Yeah.
Y-Yeah...
That too didn't...
What's wrong, Takasu?
Uh, I have to go to the bathroom.
Is that so? Then I'll go back to class myself.
What?
A body so small,
just like a doll.
But, somehow...
Somehow I get the feeling she's a troublesome person,
and I'll be eaten up if I am careless.
Um, this is...
Ah, really? The delinquent and the palm-sized tiger.
Idiot!
With that ferocity
of a tiger
But being
too small
Palm-sized... tiger?
I see.
Palm-size-
What's that? She's exactly as described.
Okay, that's all for today.
Students who haven't handed in their career choice forms must come to the office later.
D-Did you hear me, Takasu-kun?
Y-Yes.
Are you alright, Taiga?
You came pretty late today too.
I've been sneezing, and have a runny nose.
Oh, the common cold. This is bad.
Palm-sized tiger, are she and Minori friends?
I'm obviously the one at fault.
Are you alright?
Pretty much.
But...
They're awesome. Aisaka-san and Takasu-kun.
The palm-sized tiger is powerful after all.
Takasu just appears scary, but isn't a delinquent in reality.
Is that so?
Looks like the misunderstanding will be cleared up soon.
Taiga.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
T-Takasu-kun, could it be that you're feeling lost over the path you're going to take in the future?
B-B-Besides you, everyone else has already handed in their forms.
Ah, sorry. I forgot.
Sorry, sorry!
It's because you're feeling lost about the future, that's why you don't want to talk much to others, is that right, is that right?
I don't know.
Ah, it's so late already.
It's almost the school's closing time.
A-Are you alright?
Um, bag... bag...
No matter what, don't bother her.
Hey! W-What are you doing, what are you doing?
What? Look, I'm here to get my bag.
Is that your bag? Isn't your seat by the side?
Could it be... Let... L-L-L-LET GO!
Why are you grabbing my bag?
Hey, that's enough...
Hey!
A-Aisaka.
Hey.
Idiot!
What a mess.
Daddy is in heaven.
He was a handsome man.
In order to protect against being stabbed by anyone, he hid thick magazines around his stomach.
How amazing!
Just like you, I'm having more trouble.
If it wasn't for this face, nobody would have to feel scared,
and I wouldn't have been bitten by the palm-sized tiger.
I've got to be more confident in myself.
Best Dryer Collection, Spring
With that...
Ah, career choice form.
Ah, what?
To Kitamura Yuusaku-sama.
Aisaka Taiga.
I see.
Was this misplaced?
Because I haven't seen it before, I can't think what's written inside.
Well, I'll return it to you.
Crap.
Stick it back.
That person, could it be...
Really absent-minded?
To
ra
do
!
www.aerosubs.net
I'll sleep.
Huh? Is it Yasuko?
No, it's not time for her to return home yet.
Alright! Drink to your heart's content!
Mirano-chan, Mirano-chan!
Hey.
The windows...
Ouch!
What's happening?
Huh? Where did I see someone of this size...
Aisaka!
Use a tissue!
What?
W-What?
Forget it.
Forget it...?
Ah, that letter!
Since someone found out about it, I can't live on.
I can only die!
If that's the case, then don't kill me!
But I don't want to die, so I can only kill you!
Failing that, make all of your memories disappear!
That's impossible!
Don't worry.
Just using this thing to split your head in half won't kill you.
But erasing your memories will not be of any problem.
Don't be rash!
Well, listen.
That letter...
Shut up.
Shut up, shut up!
You've seen it, right? You read it?
Like I've said, that...
I'm not listening.
Forget everything about that love letter!
It was empty!
Empty?
That's right. That's why the contents...
I should say that it's lucky it wasn't handed over to Kitamura.
There's no need to lose yourself.
H-Hey.
How many days have you not eaten?
I'm tired of the convenience store.
Convenience store?
Why, isn't there anyone to cook at home...
Everyone's family situation is different.
Here.
If you had obediently given me that bag,
things wouldn't have come to this.
Why did you snatch it from me?
There's rice left.
I'm not the kind of person who can eat Chaham fried rice.
Hey, look...
What part of a love letter is ridiculous?
Listen, there's no need to feel embarrassed over this kind of thing.
Wait here.
Take a look.
What are these?
Do you know what this is?
I bet you don't.
This is, for the sake of the girl I like,
the original plan for taking her to a music concert.
I gave it my all for her sake.
The music to play in the car while with her.
It's necessary, of course.
Variations for all seasons were prepared.
How is it, very disgusting?
With no courage to confess, I can only depend on these to imagine.
It's true that I'm pathetic.
Even so, I don't feel that this was embarrassing.
You can have full confidence.
That's because you didn't stop before communicating this to him, but have taken action already.
You have to look ahead.
Pure, witty.
To Kushieda Minori.
That's right, just like Kushieda Minori...
You like Minori too?
Eh, how conceited.
Really no self-awareness at all.
Shut up, you don't have the right to talk about others.
What? Didn't you say that you've forgotten-
Shut up, W-GO.
Sorry, Parrot-chan, for waking you up.
What did you show me? It's disgusting!
What did you say?
You're saying that about an important family member!
Oh, that's great, Parrot-chan.
The self-introduction to guests.
You remember how to say your own name today too!
No... Parrot-chan isn't in its best form today.
Eh, it's this time already?
Anyway, we are both in the same situation here.
Never tell anyone else about this.
Promise me, okay?
No.
Why?
And also I served you food! Hurry up and go back.
No, please go home.
My sick mother is coming home soon.
I don't want to!
I'm unable to believe you.
Moreover... Hey, what about the love letter?
Isn't it trendy nowadays?
What's with your shyness after all this?
Regarding love, I'll think it over with you.
But it's late today, how about tomorrow, okay?
Really? You will help me?
I will. I will, I will, I will.
I'll do anything.
Anything, right?
Obeying me just like a dog?
For my sake, you'll listen to anything?
I will, I swear.
So, let's say "Good" and move on now.
Okay? Okay?
How did she get in through the window?
See you.
Ah, I'll send you off.
No need, my house is close by. And I have a wooden sword too.
No, this is dangerous instead.
Hey, that hole...
Oh, that just needs some paper and glue.
This.
If possible, use this.
If there's still a need for money, I'll return and pay.
See you, Ryuuji.
Y-Yeah.
Wait, was I just called by my name?
Hello, Taka-
Hurry up and come-
Yes.
Did you hear it?
Hurry up and go where?
Eh?
I'm at the balcony.
Why?
Didn't you say that you'd do anything just like a dog?
W-Wait a minute...
What I said yesterday was about helping you and Kitamura...
Do you know what will happen if I were to get fired up?
I'll use this to make you understand.
No, that...
Give me ten minutes!
The rice will be ready in ten minutes.
Three?
Do you want some too?
How impressive.
Excuse me.
It's open?
What... is this smell?
Aisaka-san.
I'm coming in.
What a strong smell.
Aisaka!
Let me, please let me...
Let me clean up this house!
What?
She went back to sleep again.
Just like a custom-made...
The sleeping Aisaka really looks just like a doll.
A lifeless house.
Just like the set used when playing house.
But...
For a doll,
this house is a little too big.
About fifteen minutes, huh?
Okay!
What's this?
Yo.
I'm still in the midst of cleaning.
It's about done though.
Impressive?
The sink was full of rubbish, smelling so bad.
The water drainage was so clogged, full of hair. It was rotten to the extent of looking like hell.
The house was full of dust too...
Illegal intrusion.
Furthermore, cleaning by force.
What are you doing? You dog.
Dog?!
Ah, that's really rude towards a dog.
Being a dog, and you're a stupid dog.
Stupid dog!
What an ungrateful girl.
It wasn't easy for...
Hey.
You have to say "itadakimasu".
itadakimasu - "I'm digging in!" said by Japanese as of courtesy
To all the gods of rice, and all the labourers in production,
Itadakimasu!
You...
Eh?
Speaking of which, your runny nose is gone?
No, this is because it's cleaned up.
Ah, what did you just say?
Shut up!
VANIRA SORUTO de VANIRA
Vanilla Salt, Vanilla
amai dakenara
If there's sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
Though understanding me more than anyone else
shintte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
But still wanting to find me
demo dekinaino
But it cannot be done
genke NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Experience nothing, too much gluttony
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But it's an ordinary love
watashi ga moto meteiru monotoha chigau
A little different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If you say I'm white
kuro datteiichau
I will say it's black
sunamo ninare baii amanochaku
It will be good if you are a little more honest, but you are always rebellious
SWEET iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say I'm sweet, I will say I hate it most
ureshii noni nani ite iunara
Being happy obviously, what am I saying
amai VANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding the sweet vanilla salt
Ryuuji and Taiga
Meaningless argument.
The continuous misunderstandings.
The power that arises.
Taiga, you're an interesting kid.
Shut up, go and die.