What the heck's going on?
That castle...
It's Hope Kingdom's!
Whaaaa?!
Found ya, Princess Precures.
Let's take this power for a spin, 'kay?
Dyspairvil.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
To the Future!
The Culmination of Power, Princess Palace!
Fireworks!
Precure!
Scarlet Illusion!
Scarlet!
Are you unharmed?
Yeah, thanks!
It seems it is a Dyspairvil.
A massive one, at that!
Perf?
I feel the power of the Keys from inside it!
They Keys are caged within it!
The power of the Keys themselves
must have been turned into Dyspairvils.
Already?
You catch on too quick, 'kay?
Lock!
Give us back our Keys!
No chance, 'kay? I've got plans for those.
I need 'em to become the King of Despair.
The King of... Despair?
But that won't be any concern
of yours for much longer, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
Not on my watch!
With such strength, the school may be in danger!
If we take the Keys, we can stop that castle, right?
Are you saying you'll sneak in there?!
That's far too dangerous without the ability to transform!
But we have to do it!
Yeah. We made a promise.
To never despair!
What's this?
Something inside the castle is calling out to us!
Could it be that they're reacting?
Go forth! I shall stave him off!
Haruka!
Promise me you'll come back safe.
Yui...
I'll be waiting here.
Even if we're apart, I'm with you all in spirit.
But right now, you need to stop that castle as soon as possible, right?
Worry not. Yui shall have me to protect her.
Haruharu.
Haruka.
Let's go!
Good luck.
What?
Do not forget that I am your opponent!
Girls...
It's quiet.
Yeah.
I can feel the Keys from above!
Then let's climb those stairs!
There you are!
Lock!
This whole castle's a Dyspairvil, 'kay?
So get 'em!
Dyspairvil.
Whaaa?!
Not this way!
We've got bigger problems!
Fine, I'll handle them!
Bro!
Don't get so worked up, 'kay?
Why, you—
Aroma!
Leave this to me and go on ahead!
But we—
I'm your future butler!
Don't worry about me!
Now get going!
Dyspair...
Viiiil...
Is this it?
This is the king's throne!
The Keys!
It's reacting with this Key...
You got here quick, 'kay?
Pretty bold of ya, 'kay?
You're one to talk! I mean, stealing a whole castle?
Dyspear's really outdone herself this time!
Dyspear didn't.
This was all my idea!
Hiding herself in the forest gave me the perfect chance.
I'll replace Dyspear as the King of Dysdark!
And I'll make the world despair to the beat of my drum.
It won't be Dyspear's world, but mine.
And it's gonna be a lot of fun.
Fun only for you!
Can you try being less of a pain in our necks?
Not my problem, 'kay?
As future king, I'm gonna need you out of the picture.
Here's my chance, 'kay?
Scarlet!
Fighting for your friends now?
You've really changed, 'kay?
Indeed, I think so as well.
This'll end you, 'kay?!
You bit off more than you could chew by coming here, 'kay?
Just give up already.
I won't!
What a shame.
Haruka!
Haruharu! Minamin!
Nice dodge, 'kay?
He's totally messing with us!
The situation seems grim.
Girls...
are you ready?
Yeah!
Still got some fight left, 'kay?
Now's my chance!
Yeah, right, 'kay?
It's hopeless, 'kay?
Besides, even if you do reach the cage,
you girls have no way of opening...
A new Key...
Where did you get...
Oh, no matter.
I'll just help myself to those too, 'kay?
I'm going to help everyone just like my brother did!
Give me that Key, 'kay?!
Perf!
Haruka!
You go, girl!
Got it!
It's all on you!
N-No way...
Dyspairvil...
What's wrong, Dyspairvil?
That opening is all I need!
Phoenix!
Soar, O wings of flame!
Precure!
Phoenix Blaze!
Dyspaaair...
Does this mean the others...
Yes, it seems they've succeeded!
Haruharu!
You did it!
Yeah!
Our Keys!
Now transform!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
Heart Style!
The true battle begins here!
You seriously think you can beat me?
Don't make me laugh, 'kay?
Aroma!
Bro!
This is nothing...
How dare you hurt him!
This castle is still brimming with the power of despair.
And it'll all be mine!
What's happening?
He's absorbing the energy of despair!
No way...
It's this again...
Just like when we fought Close!
I'm just getting started, 'kay?
It's time to end you pests for good!
Mermaid! Twinkle!
Flora!
This is bad! We've gotta go all out!
Right!
Lily!
Bubble!
Shooting Star!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Explosion!
Girls!
You idiots!
The days when the legendary Precures used the Keys to seal Dyspear away are ancient history!
I've surpassed her in every way,
so the same trick won't work twice, 'kay?
But we...
Give up, 'kay?!
What a shame!
It's over for you, Precures!
Fireworks!
Scarlet!
You mustn't lose hope!
You girls were bestowed with more than just a Key!
That's right...
We have the hopes and dreams these Keys were imbued with!
That's not all!
We've had the help and support from countless others!
They gave us the strength to fight this far!
It would've been too much...
for us to take on alone.
Yes.
But we had to live up to their hopes
so that we could see tomorrow together!
Our hearts are one!
With these hands!
And these feet!
We'll pave our own future!
And that...
is what our strength is!
You really are pests!
Nobody cares about your stupid friendship or feelings!
I swear!
We swear!
To become King!
To never lose!
The Keys...
What?
Is that...
Whoah, we're falling!
No, we're floating...
Could that be...
I don't care about friendship...
and I don't need Dyspear!
Precures, you nuisances...
I've had enough!
Same here!
We didn't come all this way to lose!
It's reacting to the Keys!
It's absorbing all of your powers!
Let's go!
Right!
Mode Elegant!
Cherry Blossom!
Coral!
Galaxy!
Sun!
Dress Up Premium!
This is their power to fight for the future!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
I am not Dyspear's pawn!
I... I...
I am a kiiiiiiiiiiiing!
Adieu.
Girls!
Yui!
We're back!
You were amazing!
Is that Hope Kingdom's castle?
I believe so.
The unity of your hearts brought forth a new power!
A princess's castle can only be called the Princess Palace!
Princess Palace...
This is our...
strength for the future!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Flora!
Let the flower of yearning bloom
and fix your heart upon the land beyond the bounds
Never give in and never run away
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Flower arrangement is so hard!
Oh? Sure you just don't have the sense for it?
Gulp!
Still, the flowers my classmate, Hanae, arranges sure are splendid!
Oh no! Hanae's dream...
But how? Didn't we already defeat him?!
Why is he here again?!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Fall Semester!
A New Dream and a New Threat!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Okayama Prefecture - Rena (Age 11)
Saitama Prefecture - Nonoha (Age 5)