Ah...
Ryuuji?
It's morning, isn't it?
Yeah...
In the end, we couldn't sleep, could we?
Because that kind of thing happened...
What are you going to do?
For today's: "Scare Minorin, Her Shining Knight Appears!" strategy.
But as we're frightened ourselves,
is it even possible for us to scare her?
Shut up.
If you don't do it, the future is not going to change, you know.
Well, that's true, but...
What should we do then...
...to make Minorin scared?
What do you mean "to make Kushieda scared"?
Whoa! Ki...
Y-You're up early... Kitamura.
What kind of evil scheme are you guys planning this early in the morning?
W-What evil scheme...
Maybe, the ruckus that Kushieda made yesterday...
...was your fault?
I knew it.
Man, why did you guys do something like that?
Don't you guys feel bad for Kushieda?
T-That is...
A present.
A present?
M-Minorin actually likes horror more than her daily meals.
She said that she loves getting surprised and scared.
For summer memories...
Huh?
H-Hey, Kitamura.
I see.
No wonder, rather than being scared, she looked more excited.
Okay, count me in.
Huh?
Let's combine forces and give Kushieda a real scare!
N-No, that is...
Yeah, let's include Ami too.
Stupid Chihuahua too?
If it's her, she probably knows the area a lot better than we do.
Okay, let's strike while the iron is still hot.
Well... But what if she refuses?
Leave it to me,
I'll definitely convince her.
Don't worry about it!
W-What should we do, Ryuuji?
Even if you ask me...
I have no idea...
Seaweed...
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, yet complicated and mysterious
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
onkou tokujitsu ECCENTRIC na anata
You, who's gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PURE PARAATO
A naive preparation
atama no naka wa junjou PURE PAREEDO
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
Fireworks
Oh my, my...
I thought I'd make the breakfast,
but I'm too late, huh?
Good morning, Takasu-kun.
Y-Yeah.
Huh? What're you making?
Lunch boxes.
They said that we're going to play at the beach for a whole day today.
You woke up early for that?
This is not good.
Chef, please let this Kushieda help you.
Now, your orders, please.
Okay.
Then, can you please slice the onions?
Okay, onion-slicing. With pleasure.
What is the menu for the lunch boxes?
Egg sandwich and...
tuna sandwich.
Later, a soup made out of the leftover curry, perhaps.
Ooh... that's good.
You do that well, Kushieda.
Did you just compliment me? Yay.
You did a very good job with washing the dishes yesterday too.
Both of my parents work, you see.
When my younger brother was home,
there was a time when I made him lunch boxes.
You have a younger brother?
Just barely in the ninth-grade, Akechi-kun.
Ouch, it stings.
Hey, are you all right?
I screwed up.
Takasu-kun?
Ah... I have to peel some apples...
Takasu-kun is really good at cooking, huh?
Yesterday's curry was also superb.
I didn't do anything that special.
I think Takasu-kun's tidiness is a wonderful trait.
Other classmates don't know this side of Takasu-kun, right?
I'm going to guess,
that the girl that gets to be Takasu's bride will be extremely fortunate.
Kushieda!
What's up, Takasu-kyun?
It's about yesterday...
About that thing,
keep it a secret from the others, okay?
Eh?
I've never talked about it with anyone before.
How do you say it...
I was careless.
I let my guard down.
But, I'm glad it was you whom I was talking with.
Thanks for listening.
Whoa, the fire.
Hahaha, you klutz.
How cute!
D-Don't call me cute...
I kid, I kid. Anyway, Chef,
what should we do next?
Yeah, what should we do next...
Should we mix it? Should we mix it till it's messy?
Whoo!
Today, the sun is shining brightly too.
Beautiful angel!
Minorin is so spirited.
Okay, just follow the plan later.
Hm? How about Kawashima?
She is helping, right?
Yeah, with Ami as our guide,
we'll "attack" her in a nearby cave.
Then we can't do anything without her can we?
What's she doing?
Who knows?
I'll call her.
Taiga, hold on to this.
Huh? Whoa...
Hey, wait a sec...
Here, let me take it.
It's too heavy for a girl, right?
I-It's okay.
I'm fine...
Kawashima, are you there?
I'm here.
Everyone has gone already.
Man, what're you doing...
Charmed?
Takasu-kun, want to see it too?
You are so...
Hey, hey, isn't this a bit dangerous?
What do you think?
About this cleavage...
It's fine, isn't it?
That's it?
If it's a bikini, I've already shown it in school, huh...
That's not it.
But, this part can be taken off here.
Look.
Whoa! Put it back, put it back!
Eh? Then put it on for me.
I refuse!
How cold~
If you're going to have that kind of attitude,
I won't lend you a hand.
Eh? D-Don't say that...
Hey...
Why does Takasu-kun want to make Minori-chan happy?
Why? T-That is...
If you're not going to tell me, then I won't help.
In five seconds.
Five...
Four...
Three... Are you all right with this?
Two...
One...
Zero. I won't help you.
Taiga! Come and get me!
Go! Go!
It's cold!
Go! Go, Taiga!
What are they doing?
Hey, hey, why now?
Well, it's kinda dull.
If you're not coming, then no one will be familiar with the inside of the cave, right?
I drew you a map, right?
I'm sorry, but you have to do your best alone, Yuusaku.
Hey...
Don't complain.
It's Takasu-kun's choice after all.
I'm sorry Takasu, that Ami suddenly...
It's fine.
I'm coming with you,
it's hard doing it alone, isn't it?
But, if it's the both of us, it might look suspicious.
Don't worry, I'll handle it alone.
The ideas for scaring her, I've thought up three of them by myself.
Kushieda's fears will surely be half-chaotic.
I-Is that so...
Hey~ Kushieda, Aisaka.
What?
I'll be going to the toilet.
Well, it's delicious, isn't it?
Takasu-kun is a cooking genius.
No, that's because Kushieda helped in making it.
Eh? Minorin did?
That's right!
The one that mixed the egg in the egg sandwich was me.
Hm...
Oh, while I was gone, you started lunch without me?
What's wrong with you, Kitamura-kun?
Announcing loudly to girls that you'd be going to the toilet.
Sorry.
Where could you have gone during that time? It sure took you long.
The preparation is perfect.
O-Okay.
What? What? What are you guys talking about?
Oh, Kushieda.
Actually...
Hey, Minori-chan...
There's a really beautiful cave in the bay over there...
A cave?
A very special place for me.
Very special?!
Want to take a stroll there later?
A stroll?!
That's good. Let's go. Let's go. I can't wait.
Heh... is it here?
Ami's special... stroll...
I-It has a certain air about it...
Doesn't it?
Okay, why don't we go in?
B-But, doesn't it feel like 'it' is going to come out?
Oh... an encounter with an unknown creature, is it?
No, it's still fine if it's a living creature...
That's true. If it's possible, let's catch it alive.
Letting that guy in was the right choice, huh...
That way of speaking, so cool...
Okay!
Let's go, Kitamura Expedition Team.
Let's find that golden two-headed cobra!
It's dark! It's small! It's scary!
Haha. A phrase that I've heard somewhere.
It's unexpectedly big, isn't it?
Around here, perhaps...
Don't let your guard down,
it's not like we're doing any simple test of courage.
Do you understand?
Y-Yeah...
It's a bit narrow past here, be careful.
First, gateway number one...
What?
Fried tofu...
That's right.
Kitamura is smart but...
He's an idiot...
D-Don't speak bad about Kitamura-kun!
Hey, isn't it a bit cold around here?
Because we're going deep.
No, it's not because of that...
What's wrong?
I smell ketchup.
Huh?
Hey, what're you guys doing?
This is...
Blood... writing...?
"Gya~a~~a"...
This is the second...
I knew that guy was an idiot...
D-Don't speak bad about Kitamura-kun!
Don't sigh!
Ah, what?
This is...
Hey, what's wrong?
T-T-T-Takasu-kun, t-t-that is...
No, this is...
Ah! A woman's hair!
It's a curse of a woman who took a vacation, got lost, and died in this cave.
No! Let me out! Let me out of here!
Minorin, calm down.
Nice assist, Takasu.
Eh?
You made this one, didn't you?
No, this is...
The last trap I made is 50 metres from here.
Watch out for it!
Y-Yeah...
Hey! Kushieda, pull yourself together.
I knew that Kitamura-kun was capable.
Minorin is really scared.
It's not Kitamura...
Of course, it's not me either...
T-Then...
It wasn't faked...
Just like last night, it's real...
Minorin!
It's dangerous to be alone, let's hold hands.
For real? Let's hold, hold real hard...
Okay, now that our bodies are warm, let's continue.
U-Um...
Ah... ridiculous.
I'll take a short-cut home, okay?
H-Hey, Kawashima, where're you going?
Kitamura.
Kawashima.
Hey, Kitamura-kun, are we still going further inside?
This way is the exit.
Right, Ami?
Huh? Where's Ami and Takasu?
Wait a moment, Kawashima.
Do you really know the way?
Of course I do.
Do you feel so uneasy just by being separated from the others?
I'm not good with dark places...
Then...
What will happen if I leave Takasu-kun alone here?
Huh?
Scared?
Do you feel uneasy being separated from me?
Lonely?
Do you think that you don't want to be separated from me?
H-Hey...
Do you need me?
Th-That's not the problem here...
You want to return to Minori-chan as soon as possible?
That's why I said...
She's not your type.
I-It's not like...
The one that matches Takasu-kun is...
W-What?
Huh?
Eh?
Where is this?
Huh?!
No way! Are we lost?
You must be joking...
I am not joking at a time like this!
What should we do?
H-Hey...
I-It's gonna be fine!
I'm sure Kitamura and the others are going to look for us.
Don't be scared!
I'll be here with you.
I'm sorry.
No, you don't have to apologise.
I lied when I said that we're lost.
It's impossible for me to get lost.
You s-t-u-p-i-d.
Ouch, ouch!
Takasu-kun is so slippery.
This is not the time to laugh!
That's because Takasu-kun is like a kid.
I was really scared, that's why!
You're a bit...
...hopeless, aren't you?
Why you...
But, I don't hate that kind of thing.
I just said that Takasu-kun doesn't match Minori-chan, right?
I was serious about that.
That's because I like you.
What's with that?
Minori-chan is like the Sun.
If you get too close,
you'll only get yourself burned, I think.
I mean, Takasu-kun can't even talk to her face-to-face, right?
You adore her, yet can't be her equal.
The one that can be equal to you is a girl like me...
That was...
Kushieda's voice!
Wai... Takasu-kun!
Sorry.
I...
That's fine, let's hurry.
Y-Yeah...
Kushieda!
Ryuuji!
Takasu! Ami! So, you guys are all right.
Kitamura, Kushieda is...
What happened?
Well, that's...
Kushieda was... by something...
B-By what?
I don't know, but, there's something here.
Don't tell me, that thing did this to Kushieda...
The batteries died!
Takasu, lend me yours.
What is this sound?
Voice?
Kushieda!
I'm coming right now!
Hey, Kitamura...
Whoa!
Kitamura!
Kitamura-kun!
Kitamura-kun! Kitamura-kun!
What the hell is this?
Everyone, don't separate. Just calm down for now!
Anything goes, if it comes to this...
I'll do it!
Taiga?
Tai...
Kitamura-kun, an accident has occurred, proceed with Taiga's rescue!
Roger that!
Are you okay, Aisaka?
Kita... Ki-Kitamura-kun?
Kitamura?
You're late, Akechi-kun.
Kushieda?
That's right, I am Kushieda Minori.
Also called Minorin.
The criminal is ME!
And then, the accomplice is this guy.
The hair in Takasu-kun's room.
The scattered clothes in Taiga's room.
That and everything else was our doing!
We are sorry.
That's because both your methods of scaring people are half-baked, you see...
I felt like teaching some to you...
"This is how you scare people", or something like that.
Then, that means that you figured it out?
That's because the two of you were sneaking out all the time.
That's why I took Kitamura as my ally, and launched a counter-attack.
But, that was fun. Thank you.
You're not angry?
I'm not. That's because I like horror.
I used the "Manjuu-scare" method.
manjuu - steamed yeast bun with filling
When you say things like "Ghosts are scary", "Occult things are scary",
you're going to end up scaring someone, right?
That kind of thing is delicious to me.
Well, now that confession time is over...
It's on.
It's pretty.
It's been a really outrageous day, hasn't it?
That's true, it's really been troublesome.
About that conversation.
Because I haven't answered properly...
For me, if you're not there, I feel lonely, you know.
But then again, it's not whether I'm lonely or not,
it's whether you are lonely or not, right?
For me, I've never thought about whether I'm lonely or not.
Then think about it.
Properly.
That's difficult, isn't it?
If it's difficult, then just say it out loud.
That's because we're... um...
Equal, right?
Hey.
You know, Takasu-kun?
You can be really kind sometimes.
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
It's the last night.
Let's enjoy it.
Kushieda.
Hey, um...
Yeah?
Thank you.
I was completely tricked, and I was really scared, but,
it's always fun when I'm with you.
No matter when.
That's my line.
It was really fun for me too.
The curry was delicious too.
You listened to my strange conversation without laughing.
You really understood me.
I'm really sorry for scaring you.
Because you said you wanted to see a ghost,
I got too excited.
Because of me?
Hm. "I want to see a ghost", you said.
Eh? Ah...
Takasu-kun, why did you want to scare me?
Eh? T-That's because...
Taiga told me that you can't handle horror and stuff...
"Let's tease her". No, that's not it.
Takasu-kun is not the type of person that would do anything to displease others.
You always think of how to make others happy.
That kind of Takasu-kun, why did he do this?
I want to find that out.
I really thought that was strange.
Because I wanted to show you a ghost.
I wanted you to believe in ghosts.
"Just because you can't see it, it's too soon to give up."
That's what I thought.
I see.
Takasu-kun, let's search for UFOs next.
Not man-made satellites, but the real thing.
What's next after UFOs...
Tsuchinoko is good...
If I find what I seek, it changes my world, so then...
Kushieda!
It explodes... the UFO is...
Just like a dream...
I really saw it! I saw it!
The space wars are over! We shall protect the Earth!
The trip is not over until we reach home.
Everyone, don't get careless yet.
I suppose I should just go home.
Later then!
Why don't we stop by the supermarket and do some shopping?
I'm tired, so stop talking to me about all that house-wife stuff.
All right, all right.
Hey, there's this special sale going on...
Shut up, I say.
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru mono to wa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
Unable to be honest, I'm just rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
Oobashi High School Festival - Part 1
Culture Festival.
Getting heated up from the band's performance.
Getting thrilled by the cosplay cafe.
Warming friendships by the campfire.
Getting embarrassed by the Pro-Wrestling show...
You, you're plotting something, aren't you?