Richie.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
Be good to Ri'ko.
Take care.
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
Where are you goin' this early in the morning?
I knew you were acting strangely last night...
Looks like my suspicions were correct.
Hey, wait!
Wait, I said!
Let go of me!
Move!
I'm not moving, you idiot!
If I do, you're gone for good, aren't you?!
You're just gonna run away!
You're planning on just leaving everything and everyone behind?!
Sorry. I can't stay here anymore.
Since when did you become such a coward?!
Where's the guy who told me that nothing good comes out of being afraid?!
What the hell are you guys doing
this early in the morning?!
Richie-rich...
Are you okay?!
Bro?
So you two were fighting about the festival?
I understand that you're really into it, but...
I couldn't sleep last night.
The truth is I was scared, too...
Is something wrong?
Let me stay like this...
Just for a minute...
Ritsuko! Did you bring in today's paper?
Yeah!
I left it by the phone.
Oh, I see it!
I'm home.
It's Dad!
Welcome home, Dad!
Welcome home!
Did you bring us anything?!
Dad, your hair's turned gray!
Has it?
I suppose it has...
Did you bring presents?!
Yes, I bought you stuff.
Yay!
Let's have 'em!
Hey, at least let him set foot in the house first...
Welcome
Home
Dad
Everyone,
I'm sorry for being away all this time.
You look so cute!
Look, Bro!
That's great, Taichi.
And this
is for you, Sentaro.
Um... I don't know if you'll like it or not, though...
It's a fountain pen!
You're lucky, Bro!
Wow...
Something expensive like this is wasted on me...
C'mon now, a kid can't just turn down a present from his parent.
Oh, looks like everyone got a present.
Sachiko, pass these out.
Okay!
A kid...
His parent...
Are you coming to practice today?
Yeah.
Startin' today, I'm gonna practice my ass off for the festival.
You mean it?!
I mean it!
What the hell?
That how kids greet each other these days?
Me? At the festival?
Yes, I was hoping that you would play bass for us.
You're asking me out of the blue...
Adults have a lot of things on their plate, you know.
And there'd be so much to prepare...
You can't do it?
You're totally prepared!
Ain't no way we can lose now!
Hey, hey!
How's it goin' for you guys?
Oh...
Right now, we're in the middle of getting our costumes fitted.
There's no way we're gonna lose against you guys this year.
It's so flamboyant...
We, on the other hand...
We're plain. Way too plain...
We don't have any razzmatazz.
At this rate, we might not be able to beat 'em...
That stuff don't matter.
All we gotta do is put our music face-to-face against theirs.
I know!
I know that...
But this is our last school festival.
I just don't want to have any regrets...
Easy to say...
But appealing to people who have no interest in jazz is a tall order.
W-What are you saying?!
I can't sing!
Don't worry.
There are still ten days left. We'll work it out.
Ri'ko, if you're gonna refuse, now's the time.
'Cause if you decide to do it, we ain't gonna go easy on you.
If you don't wanna sing, tell us to shove off right now.
But I hope you don't turn us down...
I agree with Sen.
Won't you help us out?
All right.
I'll give it a try.
Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens...
Kit-tens...
No, you've got no swing!
Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens
Bright copper kettles and warm woolen mittens
Brown paper packages tied up with strings
These are a few of my favorite things
Cream colored ponies and crisp apple strudels
Doorbells and sleigh bells and schnitzel with noodles
Wild geese that fly with the moon on their wings
These are a few of my favorite things
Girls in white dresses with blue satin sashes
Snowflakes that stay on my nose and eyelashes
Silver white winters that melt into springs
These are a few of my favorite things
I simply remember my favorite things
And then I don't feel so bad
"My Favorite Things," huh?
My own favorite things are...
The footsteps of a certain person heading toward my house...
The sound of the piano and drums riffing in the basement...
The laughter of two boys...
Silly, I know...
Drums and watermelon and rice balls...
Those are a few of my favorite things...
What the heck is that, Sentaro?
Go on, Richie. Your turn!
Tell us your favorite things.
I don't have any!
Even before Ritsu said hers, I had something in mind.
My favorite thing is this moment in time... Right now.
Tomorrow's the day...
All that's left is playing our best at the festival.
Richie...
How about playin' "Moanin'" one more time?
Hmm...
Nah, let's save it for tomorrow.
If we started jamming now, we wouldn't stop.
I see. Yeah, you're right.
Well, see you tomorrow then. Don't be late.
Yeah!
He forget to take this...
Ah, well, you don't need a score for jazz.
An' I can just give it to him tomorrow.
Oh. Where are you going?
I'm gonna go deliver something he left behind.
But Kaoru left a while ago.
You might not be able to catch up.
I know, I know.
19th School        Festival
Sen's late...
Hey, hey!
It's almost time for our battle.
Huh? Where's your partner?
Don't tell me he's late?
No, uh...
Seiji, come on!
Okay!
Well, see you later!
Ritsu...
Sentaro...
He got into an accident on his motorbike last night...
He's in the hospital.
S-So... How is he?
I don't know!
What should I do?!
Kaoru...
Sentaro is...
Ritsu, calm down!
I'll go to the hospital to see how he is.
Stay here until I get back.
Dammit!
I've dashed down this slope countless times, but it's never felt this long...
Um, excuse me!
I'm looking for—
I'll help you when it's your turn, so please get in line.
Wait!
U-Um...
I heard there was an accident...
They've finished operating...
But there's serious head trauma...
Still hasn't regained consciousness...
No Visitors
Might never wake up again, the doctor said...
Don't talk like that!
But...
That's right!
Even when Sen is all bloody from a fight, he just laughs it off!
Um...
No, it's Sachiko who's in there.
I dunno what happened,
but she was riding on the back of Bro's motorbike last night...
Then they got hit by a car...
Well, how is he?
He's hurt, but not too bad.
He was sitting over here just a minute ago...
I see.
Thanks!
That's right!
The place he's most likely to go is...
Gotta be.
I've seen this angel before somewhere...
If you're gonna take somebody to Heaven, could you make it me an' not Sachiko, Mr. Angel?
Why do I end up hurting the ones I want to protect the most?
Why...
Why was I even born?
Richie? What's wrong?
Hey... What are you cryin' for?
This way, we don't have to see each other cry.
What's with the "we" stuff? I ain't—
It's okay to cry, Sen.
You've been keeping it bottled up all this time...
Sachi!
Thank goodness...
Huh? Sen?
At the time, it looked like he was just stepping out...
But he disappeared, and the festival was over before it even began.
And then...
Richie...
Kaoru...
Um, here. For whenever you're able to...
Do you know where Sen went off to?
He would normally never give me a ride on his bike.
But I twisted my ankle and kept complaining about it to him.
The accident was all my fault...
I have to apologize to him...
Sachi, right now you should focus on getting better.
Sentaro will come back soon!
You want to show him that you're healthy again, right?
Yeah.
I had to be strong in front of her, but the truth is...
Kaoru, what'll I do if Sentaro never comes back?
Ritsu...
It's Sen we're talkin' about.
I bet he'll turn up suddenly, when we least expect it.
Don't you think so?
Yeah.
You're right.
He'll come back, won't he?
Sure.
Kaoru...
Don't go anywhere on me, okay?
Um...
Excuse me...
Oh. I remember you. Richie, right?
Do I know where he might be?
No, I'm afraid I don't.
Um... Father,
he left this behind...
He once told me the reason he always wore the rosary as a necklace was because
he was afraid that if he lost it, he would be abandoned by the world...
Se—
I thought maybe Sen had come back.
Pops...
He's not coming back.
I'll never be able to practice with him again.
W-What are you talkin' about, Richie?
Never again...
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change