Haruka-chan, I'm gonna sweep over here.
Okay.
Then, I'll move the desks.
Is this the Underwear Appreciation Cub?
Mind if I join you?
Those panties are used for sex, right?
Amahara Kiyono-san...
She has always impressed me from the beginning.
But why would she join the Underwear Club?
Are you thinking about Amahara-san?
Yeah, I was thinking that she's a bit different from us.
You're right.
She is beautiful as well.
Nayu, Haruka!
Yako-chan?
What's wrong? Why are you breathing so heavily?
I knew it... She's...
Amahara Kiyono is...
Experienced!
Hey, look over there.
Nice view. Just a bit more.
Looks like you guys are pretty interested in the view up there.
N-Not really, right?
Y-Yeah, let's go.
Hold it!
You were trying to look under that girl's skirt, weren't you?
O-Of course not.
Don't lie! You can't fool me.
Hey...
Are you really interested in the view here?
Wait wait! Don't be so rash!
W-What happened next?
A teacher was passing by and the boys got scared, so it was avoided.
I was so nervous.
That Amahara girl is really shameless after all.
Your face is totally red, Yako-chan.
Anyone would turn red after seeing that...
You're right.
She is different from us after all...
Let's see...
I'm Hayama Nayu from first year.
I-I'm Shiraishi Haruka from the same class.
I'm Jinguji Yako, nice to meet you.
I don't have to introduce myself again, right?
More importantly, I'm surprised you are holding your meetings here.
Y-Yeah, Mizuno-sensei had it arranged by the school for us.
I was thinking about this yesterday but...
Why is our class representative here?
You're in the same class as Komachi-kun?!
That means you're of the same age.
Quite surprising.
I'm surprised as well.
So you were interested in these things as well...
These things?
Yes, for example...
Something like this.
A-Amahara-san!
Y-You are doing that again?
You've turned red.
K-Komachi-kun...
If he wants to take a look at it, he should just say so.
Too proud to admit it, like an idiot.
Right?
By the way, you three...
I assume you're wearing underwear,
since one would expect that from members of an Underwear Club, right?
Since one would expect?
Yes, for example...
W-Wait, my mother bought these for me by herself!
What's this? Pictures on the back... at this age?
Isn't that a little too childish?
The junior panties made by them are great, aren't they?
J-Junior?
The cotton makes them soft as well.
N-Nayu-chan, you're going off topic once again.
I won't ask you to wear a thong, but can't you wear something better than that?
No man would be happy with that underwear.
Well, I guess there might be some men who are into that.
How could you flip someone's skirt and insult them?
I can't take it anymore!
Seems like you're not that good after all.
L-Let me tell you, I joined this club just to learn what kind of underwear a "Real" woman should wear.
A "Real" woman?
For me, underwear is a weapon.
There's no point in wearing it if no one ever sees it.
You do talk big, but you're only wearing something like that!
What the hell are you doing?!
You're right, I'm wearing plain underwear today.
We have a meeting tomorrow as well, right? I take my leave then.
I don't intend to make an excuse to be present here,
but I've got my own reasons, remember that.
Do you think I don't have my own?
I wonder if Amahara-san is going to be okay using stairs.
I-I bet it's drafty.
We will be conducting a moral exam now.
Please be quiet! Attention everyone!
Your teachers shall be examining you now.
Your hair and uniform looks okay.
Next!
I was so nervous.
You're right, this was too sudden.
Even though I'm not breaking any rules, I don't like this.
This hair style... Isn't it like a perm?
This is my natural hair.
The examiners are really strict.
They check every inch of our bodies.
I wonder if this is how show dogs and cats feel.
I almost get what you're saying.
Go wash that off immediately.
Are you even listening to me, Amahara-san? You're too young for make-up.
I'm not young.
I've been a woman since the time I was born.
Besides, it's only foundation.
Amahara-san, come with me for a moment.
Amahara Kiyono... She's definitely a dangerous one alright.
Amahara-san...
She's a tough girl.
Good bye, Mizuno-sensei.
Okay, take care.
Geez... She doesn't listen to anyone.
Amahara, right?
Yes, how is she in class?
Her grades aren't bad at all, but she seems to keep her distance from other girls,
though there are quite a few boys who are interested in her.
Girls at her age starts to show their charm, eh?
She's caught my attention as well.
Then that makes wearing make-up at school even more unacceptable!
C-Calm down...
It's true that she's a difficult student to handle.
Difficult to handle... eh?
I've been a woman since the time I was born.
She sure is something.
I guess sunscreen and gloss aren't enough.
H-Hayama-san?
You didn't show up, so we came to get you.
What were you doing?
I-I was just fixing my hair.
I've brought back Mizuno-sensei.
Sorry for being late.
Seems like Komachi-kun is doing his best as well.
Oh, a new member?
A-Amahara-san? W-Why?
Is it a bad thing? I just joined the Underwear Club.
N-No, there's nothing wrong but...
Can we get started already? Look, our Class Rep is waiting.
Well, it seems like he's here without being certain whether he wants to see some underwear or not.
Listen you...
Hey, today I brought some materials for us to look at.
We'll be using these today.
What is this?
What do you think it is?
Actually, it's a part of a bra.
It's located here.
I didn't realize bras were made up of so many parts.
If you break them down into small pieces, they look something like this.
But you can divide those into four major sections.
Of course it depends on the type of bra, but there are some bras that have about 70 to 90 parts.
That's amazing.
You didn't know about this, Sensei?
Even after wearing such a large bra?
Amahara-san, many people don't know that.
So, are we gonna put these together today?
Yes, I thought you wouldn't be nervous doing stuff like this, rather than doing something womanly.
Learn to keep your mouth shut.
Well, I won't be nervous doing this, though.
Aren't you glad, Class rep? Now you can freely handle underwear.
Calm down...
Nayu-chan, what's this part for?
This is used to attach the cups together.
Nayu, what's this?
This is...
It looks like a plastic model.
That's boring.
I never expected to do this.
She's got long eyelashes and pale skin.
Of course boys would go crazy for her.
Then that makes wearing make-up at school even more unacceptable!
I think wearing make-up might be going too far.
What is it?
Um, about this morning...
Morning?
A-Actually Amahara-san, I personally don't think you should be wearing make-up yet.
You're still young, and you'd look much better the way you are... That's why-
Looks like a -30.
What?
What do you mean by -30?
Isn't it obvious? I mean Femininity.
Your eyebrows are plain.
Your sloppy braid...
Your faded jersey...
No self respecting woman would ever let anyone see her like this.
"No self respecting woman."
Y-You have some awesome womanly features as well, Mizuno-sensei.
For example, the shape of your breasts and the curve of your hips.
Hayama-san!
Sensei, you're wearing the wrong size bra again.
I-I've been pretty busy lately.
My laundry was starting to pile up, so I found one and thought it would be fine to wear it.
You shouldn't do that! You shouldn't wear the same bras forever!
Besides, sometimes their size change over time!
I knew it! This bra is way too tight.
H-Hey!
And it's about to come out from the side as well.
The area is expressed in square meters.
In other words, when the area is expressed in meters x meters,
the value can be determined by multiplying the length and the width.
The value of "pi" can be determined by dividing the circumference by the diameter.
As an irrational number, "pi" contains an infinite number of digits,
and is therefore more commonly denoted by the symbol "π".
P-Pi?
Excuse me.
P-Pi... pi, pi, pi...
Unbelievable.
I can't believe it.
Amahara-san?
You've got such great breasts...
But you're wearing an ugly old ragged lace bra!
I-I thought I could still wear it.
You're going too far!
Sensei, do you have a boyfriend?
That's out of the blue.
Then let me rephrase it.
Are you in love with someone?
Huh? Uh, well...
I know who it is.
What? You know who Sensei likes?
Of course I do.
I want to know as well.
Have we met him before?
You see him every-
Wai- What are you doing, Jinguji-san?
T-That's just admiration- That's not it!
Well well, Sensei? Who are you talking about?
Yoko-san used to say that underwear and love are inseparable.
Underwear and love...
Will my perception of underwear change when I fall in love?
I believe every woman has a responsibility to groom herself to look presentable to whom she loves.
I joined this club to become a true woman.
Femininity is all about understanding underwear.
A true woman...
Take a look.
What are these?
Catalogues of imported products.
What are these extremely revealing small bras?
Why are you imagining that on me?
But this one's kinda cute.
This one's a little risky, but it's still great.
Look at that black lace.
Sensei, I didn't know you liked flashy underwear.
That's not why I...
So, don't you prefer cute underwear like those?
I don't care.
In any case, please study more, Sensei!
You need to spend a lot more time on your make-up and underwear to create a womanly appeal.
After all, we are women.
Truly, these bras are cute...
but they don't provide any support.
The lace on these panties seem to be made of materials that would damage your skin.
Underwear should be...
Shut up.
B-But good materials and proper design are essential since we wear this on our skin.
Moreover, underwear fulfills an important role in protecting our bodies.
To protect... To protect...
Companies make some underwear in favor of design too, no?
Functionality is secondary.
T-That's outrageous!
Outrageous?
I guess a little K-I-D like you will never understand.
E-Even a child can identify underwear that are comfortable.
I'm sure even you've fallen in love once.
That's... well, um... I'm not really sure.
You may think of underwear as something that protects you...
But for me, underwear is a weapon.
Everything I do, is to look best for the man I love.
If he doesn't care about you, then there's no point.
Then, are you...
In love with someone?
I'm not in love with anyone.
Don't you guys get hungry after school?
I brought some snacks today.
Dorayaki!
I made some for my brothers yesterday.
They look delicious.
Maybe I'll treat you all with herbal tea that I bought for lunch.
Yay~!
Here, Nayu-chan.
Okay.
I don't eat sweets since I'm on diet,
but I will make an exception today.
Amahara-san, could you give me some beauty tips sometime?
On a day off, of course.
I'm kinda interested as well.
Even though I'm an adult, there's a lot I don't know.
I don't have anything to teach to busty women.
Women have a lot going on.
Western underwear gained popularity in Japan after a department store caught fire in 1936...
When some women who weren't wearing underwear were unable to escape in time.
There's nothing funny about that.
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!