The low sky looks like it's about to cry.
I spit a mixture of saliva and agitation on the sidewalk.
I cower at the thought of tomorrow,
Worrying that everything might fall apart.
In my heart, I know that looking ahead
To the day after tomorrow won't give me a single answer.
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
The head of the Dollars is your beloved best friend, Ryuugamine Mikado.
Take me to that meeting.
If you're looking for a fight, you'll find one.
If there's a group, within the Dollars, working with the Black Rider,
and they're attacking the Yellow Scarves...
It could be a real gang war.
There'll be nothing left after we're done with you!
We, the Yellow Scarves!
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
Young Men Arrested for Vandalism
I heard it was the Dollars.
They took my money!
Same here!
The Dollars made me buy an expensive ring!
I saw a "Dollars Were Here" tag on a wall!
That time... I couldn't stop.
Dollars
That time... Why couldn't I?
Everything Covered in Fog
Masaomi... Did he say anything?
Kida?
He hasn't come by.
It's not like I think it was you or anything.
The fact that I was in the Dollars... you didn't tell anyone right?
Right.
Then it's not your fault.
I'm leaving the Dollars.
We're not invisible anymore...
I see...
I was thinking. Are you part of the Dollars...
No!
Okay.
That day, he said...
But once you're on the other side, three days of that, and it's the new normal.
If you really want to escape the everyday, you must constantly evolve.
I decided I'd evolve.
But...
The Sky Has Fallen
This is the result.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Ryuugamine Mikado
So, you didn't hear me?
I told you, no little fights.
But-
I did say that, didn't I?
G-General!
You're okay with this?
We're sure that the Headless Rider belongs to the Dollars!
We're just supposed to sit here and let them mess with us?!
And if we keep this up, the leader of the Dollars might just show himself.
Ryuugamine Mikado
I'll look into the leader of the Dollars myself.
Until I know for sure, you guys stay put.
Got it?
Either way, it's too late to stop.
I know you're concerned,
but there's no reason to be so worried.
Even if you hadn't done anything, this might have still happened.
Really?
Fights are commonplace in this town.
It's nobody's fault that someone from your school was attacked.
So don't worry about it.
You're with the Dollars, right?
Aren't you?
<Setton> Got it?
Then I'll close this chat window.
Okay?
<Saika>
Hey! Are you gonna run into me without saying anything?
Huh?
Heiwajima...
Shizu-
Huh?
-o...
Huh?!
Man, the weather's sure nice today!
Hey, Shizuo.
Yo.
I hear he's part of the Dollars.
He was at the meeting six months ago.
Idiot!
You don't mess with Heiwajima Shizuo or the black dude at Russia Sushi.
Not unless you have a death wish.
Yo.
Hello.
Are you alone?
Kida's not with you?
Did something happen with him?
No.
It's dangerous to be out alone.
A student from Raira got attacked.
Did you know him?
I see.
Thank you.
Since the Slasher attacks, things have been crazy.
I heard the Yellow Scarves are going after the Dollars.
The Dollars haven't returned fire.
The boss hasn't given any orders.
A lot of people seem unhappy with that.
Those are just rumors, though.
Are you in the Dollars, Kadota?
Why do you ask?
I was wondering if it's really okay for the Dollars to exist.
Are they really needed?
Who knows?
I can't go to Ikebukuro.
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
I can't go to Ikebukuro.
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
I can't go to Ikebukuro.
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
I can't go to Ikebukuro.
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is our leader doing?
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is our leader doing?
The Slasher's part of the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is our leader doing?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is our leader doing?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is our leader doing?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is our leader doing?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is our leader doing?
Isn't a leader for times like these?
We're just gonna let the Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is our leader doing?
Isn't a leader for times like these?
A
I don't think violence
is the answer.
Shouldn't we wait for things
to calm down?
Sending
I got an e-mail just now!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
I got an e-mail just now!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
I got an e-mail just now!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Have fun!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Have fun!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Have fun!
Who the heck? Is it the leader?
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Have fun!
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Have fun!
He wants us to do nothing?
Then go work things out with the Yellow Scarves!
Have fun!
And now Mikado... Now?
I see.
You were Saika, having a private messaging session with Sonohara Anri.
But no matter how much you typed, you got no response.
You thought that, all things considered, she must be really depressed.
But...
But yeah...
Are there lots of fights?
You think so?
This town's in big trouble.
What should I do?
You can't call her?
Um, you know...
You're using the PM
mode wrong, Saika-san.
Um, you know...
You're using the PM mode wrong, Saika-san.
She turned it off.
Eh
You talking about Ikebukro?
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
What's wrong with Kanra?
He's just scaring her!
You talking about Ikebukro?
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
You talking about Ikebukro?
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
You talking about Ikebukro?
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
You talking about Ikebukro?
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
It's really bad.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
People are getting hurt every day.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
They won't be happy till they've hit the Dollar's leader, and hit him hard.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
They won't be happy till they've hit the Dollar's leader, and hit him hard.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
They won't be happy till they've hit the Dollar's leader, and hit him hard.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
They won't be happy till they've hit the Dollar's leader, and hit him hard.
It probably won't calm down until either the Yellow Scarves or the Dollars disappear.
Really?
That's what the Yellow Scarves think, anyway.
They won't be happy till they've hit the Dollar's leader, and hit him hard.
Sorry. I've gotta go.
Anri was that girl at Sonoharadou, right?
Yeah.
The antique store where my dad sold Saika...
So the leader of the Dollars is a classmate,
and she has friends in the Yellow Scarves, too.
Anri doesn't know that Mikado leads the Dollars.
The three of them are friends, and none of them know about the others.
I think so.
I don't know the details, either.
I'm sorry.
Please don't ask anything.
A love triangle, indeed.
So what will you do?
I can't say anything if Anri doesn't want me to.
I can only pray that they'll be okay.
<Kanra> Yoohoo — — — — — ヽ (    ´ ∀ ` ) ノ — — — —
It's Kanra!
Oh hey look, no one's here!
Don't tell me, having fun without me, aren't you~?
Pfffffft
But it's okay!
I'm having a great time toooooooo
The game's getting good, so I'm out!
Byebye — — — — ✰
<Kanra has left the channel>
<There is no one in the channel>
It's been several days.
I haven't checked the Dollars site for this entire time.
Things keep getting worse in the city.
But my life here hasn't changed.
Takiguchi left the hospital.
I can be at peace here.
This is my everyday life.
But...
Kida already went home.
Thanks for coming to see me.
Um...
I'll be... Here will be fine for today.
I see.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
You're part of the Dollars, right?
N-No!
Of course you are!
Get out of here while you can.
What are you doing?
Are you betraying us?
Mother told us to.
Mother told us to stop you.
If the Yellow Scarves are about to attack the Dollars, please stop them.
Yes. Understood,
Mother.
Thank you.
I'm counting on you.
It's my fault.
It's my fault Kida...
Can anyone in the Yellow Scarves hear my voice?
Anyone?
I have to do something.
I have to do something...
Hello?
Queen to C6.
Black to G6.
Good, good.
This is getting good.
Out with it!
I-I don't know what you're talking about. Honestly...
I can't hear you.
You can't remember?
Screw you!
It's true! I swear!
That's enough.
But we need to make an example...
You really don't remember anything?
Next thing I knew, everyone was mad...
It's true!
It's true...
Hypnosis or something?
You're getting sleepy... Very sleepy!
Like that?
Actually, it may be that.
'Cause... Yeah.
The Dollars have a Headless Rider. Why wouldn't they have a hypnotist?
Um...
What?
Yes, sir.
I saw them with a girl.
A girl?
Ah, come to think of it...
So did I.
I think they only started acting crazy after they saw the girl.
What kind of girl?
She was wearing a Raira uniform, glasses, and I think she had big breasts.
The girl with the Headless Rider had glasses, too.
No, it's impossible.
She had big tits, too.
I'm amazed you noticed that, during the fight.
Okay!
We'll catch her and-
No!
I told you. No fights!
But if we grab her-
The rest of you get it, right?
No one does anything without my orders.
It can't be.
It can't be...
'Cause...
'Cause she...
Anri...
Really?
Then I'll show you my notes.
They'd be useless!
Huh? What is it?
Something's wrong?
I know.
Masaomi and Sonohara are gone.
When you're alone, you remember how big this town really is.
The first time I was here, I remember wanting to go home.
But when Masaomi took me around, I met lots of people,
and I experienced lots of things.
And it felt like the town was mine.
But I'm sure some of them belong to the Dollars.
Ryuugamine?
Good timing!
Hey, we'd like to talk to you.
U-Um, Harima?
What did you want to talk to me about?
Oh, yeah.
About Anri.
What's going on with her?
What do you mean...
You haven't noticed?
Noticed what?
She's been worried about something.
I was concerned about her, so I asked,
and she insisted she was fine.
She's always been like that.
I hadn't noticed at all...
I was worried.
So I was wondering if you'd heard anything.
No, I haven't heard anything.
Okay, then.
I'll ask for you.
Okay!
If you learn anything, let me know.
All right.
That's all.
Let's go, Seiji!
Ryuugamine.
You like Sonohara, don't you?
Wh-What now?
Don't try to fool me.
I can tell by just looking.
If you really do love her, don't look away, no matter what happens.
No matter what you see, no matter what you learn about her,
don't look away.
Once you've got her in your embrace, don't let go.
Once you decide you love someone, it's your responsibility.
Goodbye.
I'll fulfill my responsibility to love you, too!
Yagiri 's a weird guy.
But I thought he was kind of cool.
Damn, what's with that bastard?
Stupid little kid, acting all tough...
It's kind of weird, isn't it?
Horoda!
Over there.
A Raira uniform...
Glasses...
No matter what I learn, no matter what I see, don't look away.
Responsibility...
I didn't notice she was worried about something.
Masaomi... Did Masaomi notice?
I was probably so worried about my own problems, I didn't notice.
Neither about Sonohara nor the Dollars.
What do I know about the Dollars?
Why didn't I quit the Dollars then?
I'm quitting the Dollars.
People, stop writing that.
I'll kill the Yellow Scarves.
Do something, leader.
Who is the leader, anyway?
Do you think the Dollars should exist?
There's no need for them anymore.
I'm quitting, I said.
Stop writing that.
I don't want them to disappear.
I want the leader to do something.
He created the Dollars, so he should take responsibility.
What does that mean?
There's no hierarchy. Everyone's free. That's what the Dollars are, right?
Don't rely on the boss when things get bad.
I remember seeing a post like this once,
"Why don't we make the Dollars a good group?"
"There are some bad members, but don't worry about them."
It's a gathering of shit after all
Not really
Some people may be bad.
But there should as well be a lot of people who aren't.
Why don't we make the Dollars a good group?
Like, maybe do enough good things to negate
the bad impressions those others leave?
The leader's got nothing to do with it.
That's right. The Dollars doesn't belong to one person.
It's everyone's!
Losers.
We should just do what we can.
Die.
Agreed! Let's all protect the city from the Yellow Scarves!
We should all make rounds or something?
We're invisible. They don't know who we are...
That's right.
That's right!
Back then, too...
A girl's being attacked by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
A girl's being attacked by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
A girl's being attacked by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
A girl's being attacked by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
A girl's being attacked by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
A girl's being attacked by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
A girl's being attacked by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
A girl's being attacked by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
I think it's a Raira uniform?
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
I think it's a Raira uniform?
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
I think it's a Raira uniform?
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
I think it's a Raira uniform?
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
I think it's a Raira uniform?
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
I think it's a Raira uniform?
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
Where?
In front of Veloce. They're taking her somewhere.
What kind of girl?
I think it's a Raira uniform?
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
Huge knockers.
She has big breasts
I think that's a Raira uniform...
Raira... Glasses... Knockers...
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
And huge knockers.
It can't be!
Sonohara...
The queen's been surrounded by black pieces.
No way...
It can't be. It just can't...
"Do dreams exist at a time like this?"
I've gotten tired of speaking like that.
I've been walking this entire time,
but recently, even that seems fruitless and in vain.
"I want to see you."
An irrelevant phrase
often heard sung round and round the city.
Something like that
No, something like that
isn't enough to satisfy me.
I know exactly how I feel.
We're free. We pray that all dreams eventually come true.
Just like that,
everyone searches for their true selves.
What we find after a long journey
is the answer.
We're free. We seek the light.
We float freely like butterflies.
Our hearts reflect the great blue sky.
Even if we happen to lose our freedom amidst a strong wind,
we never want to feel regret.
We're free. We seek the light.
We're free. We long to reach a new height.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Next Time
Dullalala!!
Declaration of Disbandment
Is this a dream?
It wasn't. His hands told me so.
When you realize something is important to you, why is it already gone?
Next time:
Declaration of Disbandment