-OP-
-ED-
Early Summer, 1958
Next Day
Closed
Azumada Hospital
Several Days Later
Doctor's Office
World Champion
Azumada Hospital
In Use
Minakami Mario (Debut)
World Champion
JGSDF First District Headquarters
Satake Wukipedia
NTV Anime Information!
I hope to see you again!
Early Summer, 1958
Man, that's good!
Gotta say, you look pretty beat.
You okay?
You bet!
Those gorilla-like wrestlers pound you round after round.
I don't see how you survive.
It was all really painful at first...
but lately, there's more to it.
Being surrounded by lights in the wrestling ring...
Standing up to the cheers of the crowd...
I mean, I still don't like pain or fighting,
but...
it feels great to be inside the ring.
I'm going to get much stronger and become the main event!
I see.
Then you'd better thank Mr. Arito for introducing you to wrestling.
Yeah, no kidding.
Welcome.
Jeffrey.
Next Day
Hey, what's going on?
Why'd you call me here?
Hey, does anyone here speak Japanese?
I'm Jimmy Brown.
You... know Japanese?
Put on some gloves, and get in the ring.
Good!
Now, with your right!
Your right, dammit!
I've trained many boxing champions.
I can tell everything about a boxer with just a glance.
I can see that you train every day.
You also have talent,
but...
I know.
I know I can't box with this busted hand.
Now I can finally give up on my dream.
You went beyond the call of duty.
Thanks, Jeffrey.
"I want to box inside the ring,
under the glare of the bright lights."
Mario had been training aimlessly with that single wish in mind.
Mario's heart was like dynamite that had never fully exploded.
Bro, I don't know where to run anymore.
See ya!
If...
If your right could be fixed,
what would you do, Minakami Mario?
My right can be fixed?
I can't guarantee it, but I know a very good doctor.
If you still want to box, I'll introduce you to him.
What, surgery?
Yeah.
I want to get an operation so that I can box again.
But can that doctor really do it?
He used to be a first-rate surgeon in America, and he's fixed a lot of broken hands.
I see.
You're gonna box.
So it all depends on the doctor.
Several Days Later
You broke your right hand three years ago.
You've never had treatment,
and you still can't grip tightly with it.
Is that right?
Yes.
Well, let's take a look.
In my professional opinion,
I don't think you should have the operation.
The risk is too great.
Frankly, I've never fixed a hand as badly injured as yours.
It's unbelievable that you've been able to use it normally.
Well, do something about it, old man!
Can you perform the operation or not?
The probability that I can fix it is...
thirty percent.
No, it may be even less.
If the operation fails, you won't be able to box,
and you may have to live as a cripple.
Don't think about the probabilities.
The smallest chance will take us a long way.
It's not like we have anything to lose.
Even one percent is enough.
Please operate on me.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Just shut it.
Leave the rest to us.
What are you guys thinking?
Don't you have somewhere to go?
Yeah, go tell him the news.
That's right!
Well, I guess...
This is all we have right now,
but we'll definitely pay the rest if it's not enough.
But if the operation fails, you're not getting anything!
That's right, you'd better fix his fist!
If you screw it up, you're gonna pay.
I'll take your lunch, every day.
Well, guys,
does he love boxing that much?
I don't know.
Beats me.
That's a good question.
I really don't know.
You're kidding.
Well, Doctor...
We don't really know, but we're certain of one thing:
he's serious about making Bro's dream come true.
He may be selfless or just stupid,
but he can't focus on more than one thing.
Yeah!
He even wished for everyone else's happiness on that tree.
Yeah, he's just an idiot.
Basically, we have to make sure the operation goes well.
I see that you're all quite serious about this.
Okay, I'll make you a promise.
I'll put my heart and soul into the surgery.
All right!
Bro, I'm going to give it another try.
Sign: To be the world champ
I'm going to make your dream come true.
Hello?
Are you...
Time really flies.
It's already been two and a half years since he died.
Yeah.
I've always wanted to meet you.
You're the one who comes to visit him every month, aren't you?
Thank you so much.
Bro...
Rokurouta took extremely good care of us.
I came today to tell him something.
Oh, so you're also a boxer?
Yes.
Bro taught me how to box.
He really loved boxing.
I could never tell if he was serious or not,
but he always said,
"I'm going to be a world champ and let you live in luxury."
Oh, yes!
Would you excuse me for a moment?
Uh, sure.
Here, will you use these?
They were originally my son's,
but he never got the opportunity to wear them in a boxing ring.
I can't possibly take them.
Of course you can.
I'm sure he'd love to see you in them.
I don't think Bro was joking.
He was going to be a world champ and let you live in luxury.
We heard it straight from his lips.
So...
I'm sure he sincerely felt that way.
I'll use these shoes with gratitude.
Sign: Azumada Hospital
It may take a while...
but watch me patiently, Bro.
I'll definitely...
definitely be a professional boxer.
The winner is Doi Masahiro in the red corner!
Finally.
Mario's up next.
I've been waiting for this.
His right had better work.
The operation was a success.
The problem is whether or not he can use it in a real fight.
Let's go, Mario.
Now it's time for the lightweight four-round bout.
In the blue corner, we have Minakami Mario from Kaneda Boxing Club!
Is... that really Mario?
Y-Yeah.
I mistook him for Bro.
He's Bro's spitting image.
Listen, Mario.
No matter how tired you are,
or how much punishment you take,
look into his eyes; never look down.
I know, Jimmy.
Seconds out!
Bro...
I'm finally here.
I'm in the ring you wanted to...
should've stood in.
The professional ring.
Let's go, Bro!
What are you doing, Mario?!
That asshole had better not be nervous!
Throw some punches, Mario!
Shit!
Mario, throw your right!
Throw the right!
Well, look at that.
He's having a lot of fun.
Look closely at his face.
He's smiling.
Let's see it, Mario!
He countered the punch!
Nice!
Now turn and...
Throw the right!
He did it.
He used his right.
You're the best, Mario!
Looks like he's doing fine.
Even when people recover, their fear usually keeps them from using their full strength,
but I guess I had nothing to worry about.
Well, of course not.
Mario worked really hard.
He stopped smoking and drinking,
and he endured the toughest training day after day.
Right, Mario?
Take him down, Mario!
Turn him into a meatball!
Bro, did you see my match?
Sign: To be the world champ
Did I make you smile a little?
A lot has happened since you died,
but everyone's doing their best.
Sign: To be a star singer
Joe met his sister.
Her name's Meg, and she's really beautiful and nice.
Joe hasn't given up on singing either.
He's only getting offers for small gigs at the U.S. base,
but I'm sure he'll hit it big eventually.
Sign: To eat lost of tasty things
And Cabbage...
He's taken all of us by surprise.
What do you think he does?
He's a pro wrestler.
He hates fighting, but he's wrestling. Unbelievable.
Sign: To get rich
Uncovered learned quite a hard lesson from his first love,
but now he's studying really hard to be a lawyer.
Sign: To have a harem
Turtle...
That idiot made us worry when we found him lying in his room, but he's fine now.
He got out of the black market, and he's a moneylender now.
He's raking it in, too.
He's an entrepreneur to his very core.
Sign: To be an officer
And Soldier...
Sign: JGSDF First District Headquarters
His only ambition was to be in the SDF.
He has a strong heart, and it helps him persevere.
He's the ultimate soldier.
Anyway, they're all doing great.
So rest in peace.
What about...
What about you,
Mario?
Sign: I'm happy if everyone's wishes come true
Me?
You know my dream.
I'll make your dream come true!
The survivors of cell 2-6 walk their own paths, bound by deep friendship.
Muddy paths, steep hills, winding roads...
Nothing scares them.
Their strong wills and Bro's words support them on their journeys.
A life without happiness is a terrible thing.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
So, how did you like the season finale of RAINBOW: The Criminal Seven of Compound Two, Cell Six?
The importance of pursuing your dreams, and the beauty of lasting friendship, truly touched my heart.
Wouldn't you love to find out what happens to the 2-6 gang?
Find out by reading the manga!
That's all, folks.
I hope to see you again!
Bye-bye!
Uki-Uki!