At that time, I couldn't understand the feeling of being in touch with people.
At that time, I couldn't understand the feeling of being alone.
Hey, Chihiro, let's go.
Yeah.
L-e-t's play!
Let's go.
E-Eh? Where are we going?
Our place.
W-Wait a second!
That small encounter totally changed the path I was walking.
I believed that the happy times would continue forever.
But...
Hey.
Something is on my head.
It's a present.
Present?
Sorry about the day before yesterday.
I broke our promise.
Ah, it seems that way, though...
Though?
The truth is, I don't really remember what happened back then.
Oh...
But thank you very much.
Pya?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
It's cute. Thank you very much.
Is your cold better?
Yes, it's fine.
I see. I'm glad that you've recovered.
Say.
What is it?
There's something I want to talk to you about.
Do you want to write a novel with me?
Eh?
Why did you ask that?
"Why...?"
Doesn't it sound fun? Let's try to write one.
It's impossible.
There's no way I can do it.
Why?
"Why?"
You know that my memory doesn't last more than thirteen hours, right?
Yeah.
But I'll help you too...
I don't want to write one.
No way...
Why did you say something so mean?
Mean? Me?
Yes. You're usually a much kinder person.
I want to try writing a novel for your sake.
Why is it for my sake?
Because you said it was your dream to write stories.
That was the me from a week ago.
You are you, whether from a week ago or now.
A dream is a dream.
I'm going home.
Chihiro!
Somehow I don't understand you anymore.
That's natural.
Even I don't understand myself anymore.
You broke your promise to me because you met Miyamura-senpai?
Idiot.
Ah, Kei-senpai?
Let's trade this month's manga.
Ah, sorry. I haven't bought mine yet.
Eh?!
You're in charge of getting the monthly magazine, MIMI.
Sorry. You can go ahead and read it first, so you buy it.
I'm out of money already for the month.
I lent some to Hiro-senpai the other day too.
Eh?
Why did Onii-chan borrow money from you?
Because Hiro-senpai was dumped by Miyamura-senpai.
Huh?
Hiro-senpai was penniless, so I paid the bill for him.
I don't understand what you're talking about at all.
In other words, Miyamura-senpai was supposed to treat Hiro-senpai the day before yesterday.
Hiro-senpai made her mad, and she went home early.
Then Onii-chan is...
Hiro-senpai is as clumsy in relationships with girls as he seems.
I see.
It flies pretty well, because it's light.
Can't I get paid soon?
Miyamura?
Ah, erm... Miyako-san.
Don't add "san" either.
Next time I won't answer you.
Okay.
Good.
Because of your obedience, I guess I'll make an exception and forgive you this time.
Forgive? Did I do something that bad?
Hirono-kun, what's that?
I know. It's some extraordinary food prepared for our reunion.
That's right. My credit is always in an extraordinary state at the end of the month.
Poor you.
That's right.
This time I'll treat you for real, so let's go and eat something.
I can't just go strolling around every day.
I have work to do.
Even though it's Sunday?
That doesn't matter.
I see.
Well then...
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Your place of course.
Huh?
I'm sure he doesn't have anything good to eat, since it's the end of the month.
All right.
If I remember correctly, that girl is Hirono's...
So it was her.
Heh, you live in quite a nice place.
Shouldn't you be a little more cautious?
Eh? Why?
You're a girl after all.
You shouldn't just go to a guy's room like it's nothing.
It's okay. I know.
What?
That you'll be nice to me.
Your thinking is too naive.
That response doesn't sound right.
With someone you don't know well, there's no way you could know.
I know what kind of person he is and what he's thinking.
Liar.
I'm not bragging, but I have a good eye for people.
Because, I...
What?
Ah! I found an ecchi book!
Heh, so that's what you're into.
This is drawing material.
Oh, like that sounds plausible.
I want to do my work soon.
Ah, go ahead. Don't mind me.
I'll observe quietly.
Listen, I can't let others see my drafts before they're published.
Then show me some that have already been published.
Lend me the manga that you drew.
If you do that, I'll go home immediately.
Why do I have to make a deal with you?
S-h-o-w me.
I guess I have no choice.
This is a short story I wrote before my works were serialized.
It hasn't been published as a book yet, so I only have copies of it.
That's great.
Then I'm borrowing it.
Kyosuke.
Sorry, President. I'm taking my camera.
I see.
Let me know if you're short of equipment.
Thank you. I think I'll probably ask you before the next production.
The Cinema Festival.
The guys were bragging about it, so they'll definitely win.
What about you? Are you going to make one by yourself?
Yeah. There's a film I want to make no matter what.
How is it, Mizuki? Is it good?
That's quite an arrogant question.
This isn't about deliciousness. It's about whether eating it will be harmful or not.
Is it that bad?
How on Earth can you make such bad food?
You don't need to put it like that.
Even though it's just one, you shouldn't waste rice like this.
It's not one. It's three.
Yes?
I made three. This is the rice ball that got finished.
Where are the other two?
They stuck to my hands while I was molding them.
You shouldn't cook, ever again!
Don't be so mad.
Anyway, what happened all of a sudden?
It's not like you to cook.
Because... I'm responsible for it too.
Hah?
Nah, it's nothing.
It's also partly my fault that Onii-chan is working so hard now.
A
This is a parody of an erotic literature's title of the same pronounciation (花と蛇), written by Dan Oniroku.
Onii-chan, look! This one is interesting too. Read it.
A
This is another parody of a martial art manga of the same pronounciation (マスカレード) drawn by Itagaki Masaya.
Okay. Ah, wait a second.
Amazing!
Wow. It looks exactly the same.
Hey, draw more.
All right.
You might be a genius.
I... wonder.
Amazing.
At that time, I was happy to be with Onii-chan.
At that time, I was happy to see them happy.
But, now...
What am I seeking now?
I'm searching for the color that's missing from the world I see. I...
Hirono-kun.
When did you come in?
More importantly, Hirono-kun. Manga.
Huh? I'm drawing it right now.
Not that one. The others.
Do you have any other manga that you drew?
Yeah. I still have three more short stories, and the ones that were serialized already.
Lend me those. Right now.
"Right now"...? Is my manga that interesting?
Eh? Hmm...
Hirono-kun, you're being nervous.
Shut up!
Well, they were really interesting.
You might be a genius.
Hi. Hello.
Ah, Mizuki. The pork cutlet is still raw inside, even though the outside is burned black.
Is it the pan's fault?
It's your fault.
Don't be mean to me. Teach me.
Listen, Senpai. For fried food, the temperature of the oil...
Ah, fire! Fire!
The pan is burning!
Water! Water! Water!
Nah, don't use water! Absolutely not! The fire will only get stronger!
Then what should I do?
Mayonnaise. Please put mayonnaise on it.
Pour a whole ton of it into the pan.
A whole ton of it...? H-Hold on a second.
Senpai? Senpai?
The fire is out.
The fire is out, Mizuki! You're an amazing genius!
I'm not an amazing genius!
Ah, a new record.
Welcome back.
It's not "welcome back."
It'd be better if you stopped hiding the duplicate key under the flowerpot.
What are you doing?
I'm thinking of making you dinner to thank you for the manga.
Go home, you.
Why?
Do you know that humans can't digest raw starch?
Yes?
Do you know that an excessive intake of chemical seasonings makes your hands and feet go numb?
What's that already?
I decided I wouldn't eat a girl's home cooking as long as I lived.
It seems you have some kind of dark past.
It's fine. It's none of your business.
The only food that my heart allows are these!
All right, Miyako's specially-made rice with wild herbs is ready!
So? Are you going to try it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
Delicious?
Yeah, it's good.
See?
Damn it. She's the only one I didn't want to flatter.
It's some compensation if you say it's delicious.
It's not worth making if I'm eating alone.
Alone...? What about your family?
You shouldn't, Hirono-kun.
The way you hold your chopsticks is weird.
Since you're Japanese, you have to hold chopsticks properly.
I have tendonitis. In my right hand.
Sorry, I didn't know.
Don't worry about it. It's something like an occupational hazard.
Is it serious?
It's a light case.
There are people who only draw when the pain abates, but I'm not that badly off.
Hmm, that's terrible.
How should I put it?
It is terrible. Not sleeping, not eating. Can't have fun, and can't go to school.
That's...
What do you think?
"What do I think?"
Do I look like an idiot who's forcing himself to do the impossible?
That's not true.
Just doing your best makes it worthwhile.
Hirono-kun's not an idiot.
What are you doing?
You can't hold the chopsticks, right?
It's okay. I can eat by myself.
No.
If you want to do your work, you have to let your hand rest a bit.
Here. Ah.
Stop it. It's fine.
It's not. Ah.
What're you doing?
Kei.
Kei...
A
The furigana next to it says "Yume," which means "Dream."
Wait, Chihiro. Why not?
Give the novel a try.
Didn't you say it's your dream?
Eh?
Didn't you say there are stories you want to write?
I'll help you too.
Do you think you're saying something nice?
Do you think you're saying something cool?
Since I'm a person who's come to a dead end,
since there's nothing I want to or can do,
that's why it's okay if my dream comes true.
Such a simple...
You're right.
Chihiro...
You're the one who's right. I'm the one who's wrong.
But even so, what do you want me to do?
Help me.
Why?
Why does someone else know me better than I know myself?!
I want to write.
To tell you the truth, I want to write.
That's the only dream left before my memory disappears.
But I really don't want to.
Why?
I'm scared.
If even that doesn't work out, then I really will have nothing left, won't I?
I see. Sorry.
Yeah.
Erm, can I kiss you?
Kissing is something lovers do.
Can't we become lovers?
You're mean today, so no.
I see.
Yesterday, I would've been glad to.
I felt really lonely sleeping by myself last night.
I wanted to see you, and... I loved you.
The me from yesterday wrote that in my diary.
Really? That's a pity.
I dislike today's you. But I don't hate you.
Please hug me for a bit longer.
Hug?
Yes. It's warm.
Chihiro.
Yes.
What kind of story do you want to write?
Geez, you're persistent.
Tell me.
What I'm thinking about writing is...
a story about a girl who's the only survivor in a world where everything's been destroyed.
Kei-senpai!
What are you doing, Senpai?
Nothing.
What's wrong with that?
Can I have one?
Geez, this is no good, Senpai.
If you don't put something on it,
the bread becomes soggy after absorbing water from the vegetables...
Senpai?
It's nothing.
The woven story is a lonely one.
Next episode, ef - a tale of memories:
Outline.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?