Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
oshitari? hiitari?
Pushing? Pulling?
sakusen!! doushiyou?!
Which strategy should I use?
oh! what a night! tomaranai
Oh, what a night! Don't let it end,
risou to mousou bousou BATORU
This out of control battle of dream and delusion
mekuru meku sekai jinsei kore deai
This amazing world!  For life to encounter this..
ikenai? demo mitai nee motto motto
I shouldn't, but I want to see!  It'll make me more and
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
More and more and more and more and
shichaundeshou?
More excited, won’t it?
iijan iijan iijan iijan isshoumon no yuujou
It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! Lifelong friendship!
HIIROO mitai ja nai kedo guttokichaimasu
He doesn't look like a hero, but he'll come running to
kimi boku dare? sore are kare dare de mo OK! donna basho de mo
You, Me, Who? This, that, him, whoever, OK! Wherever we are!
minna to ireba saikou no hoshi nan desu
If we’re together it’s the best planet ever!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
It'd be nice if they're selling...
Najimi? Najimi?
Ahh, that's right.
You're out of it.
Ah, are you having naughty thoughts again?
Yeah...
Wait,  no I'm not!
It was all so sudden, you know?
You should be glad everything's going well.
Well, yeah...
Say, Tsuyuri and Justice,
have either of you had the chance to debut as a professional artist?
I have.
Yeah, a couple times, even.
So, why haven't you debuted then?
What a waste.
I want to do things at my own pace.
That's right...
The things I want to passionately express aren't widely accepted in the industry.
For example, like this.
Whoa, totally perverted!
Or this...
Err, where's your sense of morals?
How about this caption?
That's way too extreme!
But Najimi, it should be good for you to take this chance.
Yeah, Najimi, you'll do fine.
I'm happy as long as Najimi's happy.
Well, we don't know the results.
So I don't want to get my hopes up!
True.  It's unlikely a hundred of your books will sell in three days.
Just you wait!
I'll sell one hundred books just like that and head straight down the road to professional success!
And I'll live in a luxurious designer condo.
I'll have a chauffeur drive me around in my roll-cabbage?
Rolls-Royce.
...in my Rolls-Royce!
Goodbye to this train!
Wow, they're really selling mine!
And in the center of attention, at that.
But...
No one's buying it.
Well, that's expected.
It's only the first day, nothing to worry about.
Go buy one.
Me?
Yes, you.
But, that's kinda cheating.
If you miss this chance, you might lose your road to success.
W-what are you saying?
You're going to drive a Rolls-Royce, right?
Welcome.
Will that be all?
Y-yes!
Why are you dressed like that?
I don't want people to see me buying my own book.
I doubt anyone knows that you're the one who made that book.
Even so, it's porn.
You made it.
Shut up!
Umm.
Yes?
You're not working today, right, Najimi-san?
Hoshi-kun told me all about it.
I hope it sells well.
Yes...
My cover's blown...
Thank you very much.
Najimi-san!
Be excited!
We sold two copies yesterday.
Really?
I was so worried, I bought a copy yesterday.
Eh, you did?
I guess I was worried for nothing that it wouldn't sell.
I guess.
Well, keep up the good work.
Ah, yes!
So her copy and your copy.
Two sales, eh?
But wait, how come you guys didn't buy any?
Because I'm not of age.
Because you gave me a copy.
Just because.
Traitors!
How about you, Nidou-san?
It's the 21st century, don't stick your tongue out at me.
Are you still jealous?
Won't you cheer me on?
You're wrong.
I'm not jealous.
Then what is it?
You really don't want to debut professionally.
That's an original theory.
It is.
That's not the case!
It is the case!
Nidou-san, you don't understand how I feel.
I do, too.
No you don't.
I do, too!
Kaneru-chan.
Stupid!
STUPID STUPID STUPID STUPID STUPID STUPID
STUPID!
Oh my...
It's the fateful day.
How about this?
Limited edition sale ends today!
It's totally pervy!
Highly recommended.
I understand how you feel, but you're making it difficult to buy.
You're right...
What's this?
I'd like this, please.
Welcome!
That's...
Nidou-san.
You have good taste, miss!
This is done by Beauty Love-sensei.
She is a rising star and we have the privilege to distribute a limited quantity before her actual debut.
Isn't that Justice-san?
It's Justice!
It really is!
He's buying that manga...
I'll buy one too, then.
Thank you very much!
Amazing, you sold every copy.
Ah, thank you very much.
But, I didn't have much time...
I just got the text.
Every copy really sold, Najimi-san.
But I hear everyone followed suit after Justice bought one.
It kinda feels awkward...
Hey now, you're going to debut now.
You're right, I shouldn't think like that.
May I take a look at your manuscipt?
Ah, sure.
It was my first time not drawing ero.
It was refreshing.
I-I think my lifeline just became shorter...
Ah, It's good! Very well done.
We did it!
Take a look over the contract, and stamp right here.
Its our company policy.
Right.
Let's see... Hmm...
Well...
Like it says there...
You'll have to quit doujin work once you've gone pro.
I'll make you feel much better.
I'm happy as long as Najimi's happy.
You're going far away!
Najimi-san, you're going far away!
Is something wrong?
Najimi-san?
Umm...  Dreams should be...
SLAMMED onto you!
Congratulations on your debut, farewell!
Wait!
Najimi!
Wait!  Let me think it over!
There's nothing to reconsider!
You're a pro!
This is what you wanted!
That may be true but...
I still...
I still want to shamefully buy erotic games!
And run into friends and feel awkward!
And want to draw manga with my crappy drawings...
To be tossed around in a crowded train after an all nighter...
To become ecstatic with every small sale...
I want to...
Hand my book to each and every customer!
Foolish!
Yes, it may be foolish!
But..  I want it to stay that way.
Well said, Najimi!
Brother!
It's you, good timing.
Hold down the hard-headed fools.
Ok!
Well then...
Idiot! Not me!
You're the one who recommended that girl.
Sorry, something was wrong with me.
The manuscript!
Leave it to me, kuma!
Nidou-san!
I am Aiorusu.
A brave warrior, kuma!
I don't like to fight, kuma!
Hoshi-kun!
Damn it!
H-he's going to kill me!
Construction?
Brother, take this.
Jump to the left.
You couldn't press the stamp to close the deal on your own.
Your mouth says one thing, but your body is honest.
Hoshi-kun, I'm sorry about the big chance.
What're you saying?
Najimi-san, you've sold out twice already.
That's an amazing feat.
Oh yeah. Now that you mention it...
Welcome back, Najimi-san.
Yeah, we're all together again.
This is the application to the next comic festival.
The deadline's tomorrow.
Count me in!
Najimi looks so happy.
What should I tell the company?
I'm still far from making my fortune.
I, Najimi Osana, have returned here for my friends, and rival.
As well as my fans!
Nah, actually...
I've returned here for myself!
That's right...
Dreams shouldn't come true that easily...
Probably.
But god...
Please give me another chance after some time.
Until then, I'll dawdle along.
Because right now that's my no-good-at-all but really fun...
Doujin Work!
fushigi itsu no ma ni ka
It's strange
hajime no ippo fumidaseba
Before I noticed
maru de yosou gai de
After taking the first step, despite my predictions
iya mo iya mo suki ni naru
It might be icky, but I'm starting to like it,
hontou no watashi ga mezamechatta!?
Has the real me woken up?
mufufu miryoku kamo ne
Hah ha ha! It might be charming,
jinsei kake masshigura
To live life fast and free.
sora wa PINKU iro de
The sky has turned pink,
BURUMA mo BYUtto tonde iku
Even bloomers fly through the air,
mitaiken na ERIA saa susumou!!
An area I haven't experienced! Now, forward!
yume miru otome wa SUI SUI CHAO!
Girls who dream can do anything smoothly,
kewashii michi mo hiraoyogi
Swim through even the hardest path,
mizutamamoyou no ashita ni naare
Get used to a polka dot future,
dakara ganbaccha Oh!
So then, let's give it our all!