"Minami, do you wanna stay in Germany?"
"If you wanna stay at any cost,
I'll make arrangements for you, but..."
"Big Sis..."
"You're not coming with us?"
"I am."
"I'm coming with you, Haduki."
I'm going, too... to Japan.
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
"Episode 8
Me, Japan, and Unknown Words!"
It was on the day of the
entrance ceremony a year ago.
It was right after I came to Japan
so I couldn't understand Japanese well.
Nice to meet you.
"Whether I can fit in at a Japanese school or not
all depends on the first impression I make.
I have to be careful not to do weird stuff."
That's what was going through my mind
while I nervously awaited my
turn to introduce myself to the class.
Next... Minami Shimada.
"Shima"
"da"
I'm Minami Shimada.
Pleased to meet you.
Hm? Did I do something weird?
Well, I heard that Shimada is a
returnee student from Germany.
Since she came back to Japan recently,
there are a lot of things she doesn't know.
Everyone, please help her out.
Don't worry, Shimada.
You can learn kanji
characters little by little.
Kanji characters?
"Shimada"
"Mikare"
"kare"
Ah!
Pleased to meet you.
I wish they had told
me that I made a mistake.
How underhanded of them to
not tell me about it and then laugh.
Dad told me that Japanese people are all kind,
but I was starting to
feel uneasy about this class.
I'm Yuuji Sakamoto
from Kannaduki Junior High.
So that's the guy who's rumored to
be the demon of Kannaduki Junior High...
Oh shoot... I'm in the same class...
"Yuuji Sakamoto"
Is someone like that common in Japan?
No... Dad said that Japan is
an exceptionally safe country.
So it must just be his appearance.
I'm Hideyoshi Kinoshita.
Nice to meet you.
I wonder why that girl's
wearing a guy's uniform.
It's just that she isn't
used to wearing a skirt, right?
This is nothing strange, right?
Dad said that there are no scary
or strange things in Japan, so...
I'm Kouta Tsuchiya. My hobby is taking
secret pho-- I mean, I have no hobbies.
My special skill is wireta--
I mean, I have none.
Ah... You dropped this.
Forget what you just saw.
Th-That's normal, right?
He uses it to record classes, right?
It's okay to believe what Dad told me, right?
I'm Akihisa Yoshii from Nagatsuki
Junior High. Nice to meet you all!
"Akihisa Yoshii"
He lied... Dad lied to me!
So you're a returnee student, Shimada?
When did you come to Japan?
Were you born abroad?
It seemed that they weren't
used to seeing a returnee student,
so they all looked at me with prying eyes.
Are you good at English?
Aren't you gonna join a club?
Do you have a boyfriend
where you came from?
What am I gonna do?
If they talk to me all at once when
I don't even understand Japanese well...
How do I say "please be quiet" in Japanese?
What's your hobby?
What's your favorite food?
What's your breast size?
Oh yeah...
The girl I saw this morning shut
everyone up by just saying a phrase.
So I just have to use those words.
Da...
Da...?
Damn pigs, shut your traps!
H-Huh?
I already made a mistake on my first day.
I asked Dad about it later. He told
me that was really abusive language.
Since then, no one
tried to get closer to me...
...except for one person.
Uhm, Shimada, was it?
Yes!
Sigh...
Huh? What?
Why are your clothes...
Oh, these? This is because... uhm...
...I overslept this morning... and rushed out.
Do Japanese students wear a sailor
school uniform when they're in a rush?
I somehow feel like you'd
need a Ph.D. to figure this out.
Hey, stupid. Don't block the exit
while you're making mindless chatter.
Stop it, Sakamoto.
Shimada isn't used to Japan yet,
that's all. Don't call her stupid.
I meant you, Yoshii!
Which part of me are you calling stupid?!
Your getup, words, and actions!
What?! Don't judge people just
from their outsides and their insides!
What more do we need to judge people?!
You say that, but you
are stupid, too, Sakamoto!
To think that you ignored such a pretty
girl when she talked to you this morning!
She has nothing to do with you!
I didn't like your stupid look
from the first time I met you!
That's my line!
To think you called someone you met
for the first time stupid...! How rude!
I don't wanna get
lectured on manners by a guy
who attended his entrance
ceremony in a sailor school uniform!
--You have no idea how I feel!
--W-Well then, good-bye.
I didn't know what they were saying,
but I realized intuitively then
that I'd better stay clear of them
or I'd never be able to go
back to an ordinary school life.
I wonder if I can get
along okay at this school...
I wanted to be with my
little sister, Haduki, for her sake
so I came to Japan when
Dad got his job transfer...
I was feeling really uneasy.
So the ladies' room is blue and
the men's room is pink in Japan, huh?
I'd better be careful.
I almost embarrassed myself.
What the hell are two girls doing in here?!
Wait! I'm not a girl!
Gehen mal hier, Kinoshita!
You're getting it wrong!
Why do I have to run away?
Wie dumm! Was machst du?
Hier ist die toilette für die männer!
What?! Why are you upset?!
I am a guy and I did
nothing wro-- Hey, Shimada!
"Shimada"
I still don't get Japan well.
But this was just the first day. As time goes on,
I'll probably come to understand
many things little by little.
Until then, I won't get hasty
and will live here with my fami--
A-Almost...
Yeah, I really don't get Japan.
"How was the Japanese school?"
"Did something happen?"
"No, nothing happened."
"There are many distinctive, strange people."
There were only strange people.
"I see. It sounds like you had fun. I'm glad."
"I hope you'll make lots of friends, Big Sis."
"Y-Yeah."
Friends... huh?
Idiot Test.
About a week later...
...the classes had already started in full swing.
I wasn't used to Japanese yet,
so I couldn't understand the
modern Japanese class at all.
And when it came to the
classics, it was just gibberish.
Well then, Yoshii. In this case,
what's the conjugation of "haberi"?
Yes. It's "hannari."
To think that you answered
a word in the Kyoto dialect
when I asked you the conjugation
of a classic Japanese word...
It's so irrelevant that it's even refreshing.
What? H-Huh?
Well then, please review what
you learned today for the next class.
It's finally over.
Just when I thought I'd finally
be free of this tortuous boredom...
Ah, Shimada, where're you going?
What is it?
W-Well...
Watashi wa kaerimasu.
[I'm going home.]
Huh? "What a sea"?
Wa-ta-shi!
Oh, I see. You said, "I'm going home."
I'm sorry, I couldn't hear you well.
Since you came from abroad recently,
I just assumed that you were
speaking in a foreign language.
What?
Since I wasn't used to Japanese,
I couldn't follow his rapid talking.
I tried hard to understand him,
but my head couldn't follow it.
I felt like it was going to burst.
It's a pain and I wanna go home,
too, but you can't go home yet
because we have homeroom after this.
What? Er...
So don't go home yet. Wait a little longer.
--And after the homeroom, we'll
all get together after school and...
--What is he smiling about?
--And after the homeroom,
--Is it that funny that I can't speak Japanese?
--we'll all get together after school and...
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
Huh?
Uhm... Is he saying, "What club did
you belong to in junior high, Minami?"
Well, this isn't the right
time for that question, right?
To start with, is his
Japanese grammatically correct?
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
Uhm, tu ne voudrais...
I don't understand!
Ah...
What can I do?
Why doesn't anyone understand me?
I'm trying this hard and yet...
"Ah..."
"Welcome home, Big Sis!"
Could it be that everyone hates me?
"How was your day at school?"
"It was a lot of fun!"
In fact, I wonder if I shouldn't be here...
"Did you make friends?"
"Yep! I made lots of very nice friends."
"Really?"
I...
"Yep! Japan is a nice place."
"I'm happy for you!"
I still couldn't get along in the class.
Since I couldn't understand
Japanese, I couldn't make friends
and so I didn't have anyone to talk to.
It was a bad cycle.
It was because my first
impression on the first day was bad.
From the time I made a mistake
in writing my name on that day...
"kare"
"Minami Shimada"
Ah...
Huh?
I'm sure I didn't correct it... Why?
Hey, Akihisa. The guys from
Akebono Junior High suggested that
we play basketball for bread from
the school store. What do you wanna do?
I'll do it! I'll do it! My food
budget for this month is tight, so...
I'll help you.
Let me join you guys, too. It looks fun.
--Okay. Now we're four.
--I wonder when they became close.
--Do you know one more person who might join us?
Let's see...
Leave it to me.
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
Ah...
What's with him?
He's talking gibberish again.
I don't understand Japanese!
To start with, what's "Monamie"?
I'm "Minami," not "Monamie."
Don't get fresh with me when you
can't even remember my name correctly!
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
Tu ne...
Hanashi kakeruna baka!
[Don't talk to me, you idiot!]
What? "Nashi o keruna"?
[Don't kick the pear.]
What a shit man you are!
"Watashi wa man, you wa"?
[I'm a man, you are...?]
I'm a man, too, but...
What? Then you're a man?!
He doesn't even understand English?
"What a shit man you are."
It means "you piss me off."
What? Is that right?
To see you called an upset girl a guy...
What guts you have, Akihisa.
D-Don't get me wrong, Shimada!
It's not that I thought you were a
guy because you have small breasts,
but my elbow joint hurts
as if it's being smashed!
Although I don't understand Japanese,
for some reason, I clearly heard
just the "You have small breasts" part.
What a shit man you are!
Terrible... This is really terrible...
I shouldn't have come to Japan.
Hey, Shimada.
Since I came to know him just
recently, I don't know him well,
but that baka [idiot] may
be quite an interesting guy.
Baka?
Check what he said.
"Idiot"
Oh, it means "idiot," huh?
I already knew he was.
"Idiot"
"Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie"...
What on earth does it mean?
Well, whatever it is,
I bet he's making fun of me.
I'm gonna look up what it means
and make fun of him in return.
Tu ne voudrais pas... Tu ne voudrais pas...
Tu ne voudrais pas...
I can't find those words.
I wonder what he said...
Is that even correct Japanese?
He didn't even say my name correctly.
My name is "Minami," not "Monamie."
"Monamie"?
"Mon amie"
"Why are they calling my name?"
"It's not your name."
"They're not saying 'Minami,' but 'mon amie.'"
Here it is.
France...
"Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie"...
So it's not Japanese.
Not to mention, it's not German, either.
He checked French by mistake.
He really is stupid.
There was no French-German
dictionary in the library.
I had to translate it into
English first and then into German.
I didn't know the spellings or
if the pronunciation was correct.
But...
"Tu ne voudrais pas" is
second-person, like "could you" in English.
"Devenir" is equivalent to "become."
"Mon amie" isn't "Minami."
It's "mon amie" and it
means "my friend" in English.
If I translate the whole thing together...
"Could you become my friend?"
it means "Could you become my friend?"
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
He must've looked it up like this, too...
...even though it was unknown
words from an unknown country...
...even when he's having a hard time in
the classics class of his own country...
"Akihisa Yoshii"
...when he's stupid...
...even when he's stupid...
"Idiot"
...when he's stupid...
Could you... become... my friend?
"Could you..."
Could you...
"Minami"
"Shimada - Older Sister"
Good morning, Yoshii!
Ah, yeah... good morning, Shimada.
Huh? Wh-What is it, Shimada?
Say, Yoshii...
Y-Yeah...
Watashi...
[I...]
"What a shit"?
I'm sorry. Did I do
something to upset you again?
No... Watashi wa... [I...] Ah...
Say, Yoshii...
"Uchi wa..."
[I...]
...uchi wa... [I...]
Flash! Shine! Light bulb, shiny flash!
I'm not making progress.
Someone's interfering... No, no!
The issue is, I don't have
enough common multiples
Okay, I basically get it.
What is the truth... Baby?
If you see this, draw a
diagram and explain it, Baby!
No word or number can describe you
My heart is being shocked by
the magnetic force between S and N
(S! S! Super! Sticking together,
Number! I say No.1 boy!)
Congratulations! From here on
out you're My, ma-my "treasure"
You're special to me,
no matter what happens
I'll hold you ever so
tight and never let you go
I want to be in love, in a
dream you can forget about limits
It's special, right? After all,
we came to know each other
Forgive me for being like this
Flashed! Shined! Right answer, perfect match!
Question 9.
What do you call the actions by
groups that reach out to politicians
in order to influence policies?
Matchmaking party?
Who's the king?
Next episode!
"Me, Romance, and Negotiation Skills!"
This will be on the test.