- ( water splashing )
- Fukuhara: SUMMERTIME...
FUMIZUKI ACADEMY IS BATHED
IN GOLDEN BLISS.
LAUGHTER CAN BE HEARD EVERYWHERE
AS SPLASHING WATER
GLISTENS IN THE SUN.
- ( girls giggling )
- ( gasps )
- Fukuhara: ALSO, THERE IS
SCREAMING AND SPURTING BLOOD.
- ( theme song playing )
- Akihisa: OH THAT'S RIGHT.
YUUJI.
- HUH?
( screaming )
- THE GAS HAS BEEN SHUT OFF,
SO THERE'S NO HOT WATER.
- HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
TAKE A SHOWER?
- WELL IF YOU START BY KINDA
NUMBING UP YOUR ARMS AND LEGS
EVENTUALLY YOU CAN
WASH YOUR HEAD
AND ALL YOUR IMPORTANT JUNK.
- THAT WASN'T A
REAL QUESTION, YOU MORON,
IT WAS
A HYPODERMIC ONE!
- I DON'T THINK YOU'RE USING
THAT WORD RIGHT. I KNOW.
WHY NOT TAKE A SHOWER TO
CLEAR YOUR HEAD?
- I'M NOT FREEZING MY BUTT OFF
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
A GASLESS TOOL!
SERIOUSLY, MAN, YOU'VE GOT NO
HOT WATER, NO FOOD.
HOW CAN YOU LIVE LIKE THIS?
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
- DON'T BE SUCH A JERK. IT'S NOT
LIKE I'M SURVIVING ON NOTHING.
I'VE GOT STUFF TO EAT.
- I LIKE TO START MY DAY WITH A
NICE GLASS OF OLIVE OIL.
HOW MUCH YOU WANNA BET THERE'S
NOTHING IN YOUR FRIDGE.
- SHOWS WHAT YOU KNOW, I'VE GOT
STUFF IN THERE.
- OH THANK GOD, THERE'S A
GREEN BAG OF FUNK.
- SO, YUUJI, WHAT'RE YOU
GONNA HAVE TO EAT?
- EVERYTHING YOU SEE HERE,
MINUS THE CHOPSTICKS.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THE ONLY THING YOU'RE LEAVING ME
TO EAT ARE THE CHOPSTICKS?
- YOU WOULDN'T SERIOUSLY
EAT THOSE THINGS?
- WELL, IT'S BETTER THAN
EATING THE PLASTIC BAG.
AT LEAST THE WOOD IS ORGANIC.
- I CAN'T LET YOU EAT WOOD
FOR LUNCH.
BESIDES, I DON'T WANT TO USE
MY FINGERS FOR THE NOODLES.
BUT DON'T WORRY, I GOT
SOMETHING FOR YOU, TOO.
DIET COLA, DIET GELATIN
AND DIET NOODLES.
- I DON'T NEED TO GO ON A DIET!
- I'M TRYING TO KEEP YOU HEALTHY
AFTER ALL THAT JUNK YOU'VE
BEEN EATING.
- MAYBE YOU DON'T REMEMBER US
TALKING 10 SECONDS AGO
BUT I HAVE NO FOOD!
- YOU SHOULD KNOW A DIET OF OIL
AND SUGAR IS BAD FOR YOU.
- WORSE THAN STARVING?
I'M GONNA SHOVE THAT DIET
CRAP UP YOUR NOSE.
- BIG TALK, YOU WANNA GO?
- HECK YEAH. GOTTA SAY I'VE BEEN
DREAMING ABOUT TAKING YOU DOWN
FOR A WHILE NOW, YUUJI.
- THAT'S FINE.
GIVE IT YOUR BEST SHOT.
- ( grunting )
- ( both screaming )
- YOU'VE GOT PRETTY GOOD AIM.
- COULD SAY THE SAME THING
ABOUT YOU.
- WATCH OUT. I'M DONE SCREWING
AROUND, YOU PANSY!
- GO AHEAD, BIG MAN,
BRING IT ON!
- WHAT EXACTLY DO WE GET OUT OF
CRACKING EACH OTHER'S SKULLS?
- NOTHING...
I'M ALL STICKY. I BETTER TAKE
A SHOWER SOON.
BUT YOU CAN GO FIRST
IF YOU WANT TO.
- I'M NOT TAKING A SHOWER HERE.
- WHERE YOU GONNA GO THEN?
- SOMEPLACE WHERE THEY'VE
HEARD OF A LITTLE THING
CALLED HOT WATER.
- OKAY FINE.
YOU HOPPED THE FENCE TO TAKE A
SHOWER IN THE LOCKER ROOM,
BUT THEN THOUGHT
SINCE YOU WERE HERE
YOU MIGHT AS WELL GO SWIMMING IN
YOUR UNDERPANTS
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
TO SAY FOR YOURSELVES?
- Both: IT WAS ALL HIS FAULT!
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO COULDN'T
STAND A LITTLE COLD WATER.
- WE WOULDN'T BE HERE IF YOU
COULD PAY YOUR STUPID GAS BILL.
- IT'S BETTER THAN NO WATER!
- YOU'RE LIKE A HOMELESS DUDE!
- I'VE HEARD ENOUGH EXCUSES,
I THINK I GOT IT.
- SEE? IT'S NOT MY FAULT, RIGHT?
- I DON'T THINK EITHER OF YOU
WOULD CHOOSE TO BE THIS STUPID
IF YOU COULD HELP IT.
BUT MAYBE CLEANING THE POOL NEXT
WEEKEND AS PUNISHMENT
WILL MAKE YOU THINK A LITTLE!
- Both: YES, SIR...
- HE REALLY PICKED YOU UP
BY YOUR FACE?
- YEAH AND NOW WE HAVE TO
CLEAN THAT GINORMOUS POOL
ALL BY OURSELVES.
- CHEER UP, PAL.
WE GOT AN ALL-ACCESS PASS TO
USE THE POOL
AS LONG AS WE CLEAN
THE STUPID THING.
YOU WANNA COME
HANG WITH US, KOUTA?
- NO THANKS.
- NOT THAT IT MATTERS,
BUT I'M INVITING MINAMI
AND MIZUKI TO COME WITH US TOO.
- WHERE'S MY BRUSH AND
WHEN DO I CLEAN?
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
WOULD IT BE ALRIGHT WITH
YOU IF I ASSISTED
IN YOUR CLEANING
EFFORTS AT THE POOL?
- HECK YEAH, MAN!
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- KEEPING OUT OF TROUBLE?
- GOTTA CLEAN THE POOL
THIS WEEKEND,
BUT WE WERE THINKING
OF SWIMMING.
YOU LADIES WANNA
JOIN US?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MIGHT NOT HAVE A SUIT.
- YEAH ME TOO.
NOT SURE MINE FITS.
- I BET AKIHISA CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE HIDEYOSHI'S SWIMSUIT.
- I'VE GOT MY SWIMSUIT.
- NO FAIR MAKING THE REST
OF US LOOK BAD
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE SUPER HOT.
- THAT'S RIGHT. DO YOU HAVE TO
MAKE EVERYTHING SO DIFFICULT!
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU TWO ARE TALKING ABOUT.
- SO, YOU COMING WITH
OR WHAT, GIRLS?
- I'M COMING.
- YOU BET I AM.
- I HAVE TO START GETTING READY.
- OH YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT. WE
CAN'T SHOW UP THERE LIKE THIS.
I HAVE TO STOP EATING SO I CAN
LOOK GOOD AT THE POOL.
- OKAY. I JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE
SHOUKO CAN GO, THEN WE'RE SET.
- YOU'RE ASKING HER?
I GUESS YOU'RE STARTING TO
GET INTO SHOUKO A BIT, HUH?
- AKIHISA, IF SHE
FINDS OUT LATER
THAT I DIDN'T INVITE HER
ALONG WITH THE REST OF US,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
SHE'LL DO TO ME?
- I'M SORRY.
- GOOD MORNING, EVERYONE!
- WELL SOMEBODY'S IN A
GOOD MOOD TODAY.
REALLY LUCKED OUT WITH
BEAUTIFUL WEATHER DIDN'T WE?
- I WENT OUT AND BOUGHT A NEW
SWIMSUIT ESPECIALLY FOR TODAY.
- REALLY? WHAT KIND IS IT?
- I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE.
- EH, JUST SOME BORING TRUNKS.
- BUT THAT'S A MEN'S SWIMSUIT.
- YOU'RE TOYING
WITH ME, HIDEYOSHI!
DON'T YOU LIKE ME ANYMORE?
- I REALLY DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT
ALL THE FUSS IS ABOUT.
- HEY THERE, BIG STUPID HEAD!
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
- HI, HAZUKI.
- SHE KEPT FREAKING
OUT ABOUT COMING
SO I FELT BAD AND SAID 'YES'.
- WELL, THIS IS EVERYONE.
LET'S ALL GO GET CHANGED IN
THE LOCKER ROOMS
AND THEN MEET UP POOLSIDE
IN A FEW.
- YAY!
- HOLD UP KID. THIS IS THE WAY
TO THE GUY'S LOCKER ROOM.
YOU AND HIDEYOSHI HAVE TO
GO THAT WAY.
- ( laughing )
I'M JUST JOKING.
- MY CHOICE OF LOCKER ROOM
IS NOT A JOKE.
- OKAY, YOU'VE HAD
YOUR FUN, YOU TWO,
YOU CAN'T CHANGE
WITH ALL THE BOYS.
- DON'T AGREE WITH HIM!
I CAN'T GO WITH YOU, THEN I'D
BE CHANGING ALONE
IN FRONT OF A BUNCH OF GIRLS,
WHICH IS HARDLY APPROPRIATE.
- YOU'LL HAVE TO CHANGE
WITH YUUJI.
- I'M OKAY WITH THAT.
- DON'T SWEAT IT, HIDEYOSHI.
CHECK IT.
- SO, IS HIDEYOSHI
A NEW GENDER?
- HEY SILLY BOYS!
THANKS FOR WAITING FOR ME!
- OF COURSE, HAZUKI WE...
( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- WE COULD GET ARRESTED
FOR WHAT WE'RE THINKING.
- I THINK I NEED TO CALL
MY LAWYER.
- PULL YOURSELVES TOGETHER,
GUYS. QUIT BEING OVER DRAMATIC.
- HAZUKI, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
BE WEARING THAT! GIVE IT BACK!
I HAVE TO USE IT TO
KEEP MY BIKINI TOP ON.
- THESE?
THEY COME RIGHT OUT, CHILL.
- THIS ISN'T A TOY TO PLAY WITH!
THEY COST A LOT OF
MONEY, YOU KNOW!
- SO THOSE ARE YOUR BOOBIES?
- YOU EVER MENTION THIS AGAIN,
I'LL TWIST YOU INTO
NEXT TUESDAY.
- MENTION WHAT?
I ALREADY FORGOT! SEE?
- ALMOST... ALMOST...
- ( screaming )
PLEASE, SOMEONE,
TAKE A PICTURE.
- STUPID HAZUKI RUINED THE WHOLE
ILLUSION I WAS TRYING TO CREATE.
- ( laughing )
- WHAT'RE YOU GRINNING AT?
IS THERE SOMETHING FUNNY HERE?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
I THINK YOU LOOK REALLY GOOD.
- REALLY?
- SURE.
IN THAT SUIT YOUR BOOBS...
UH BUST... I MEAN BREASTS...
THEY LOOK SAME FROM ANY SIDE
LIKE... MY FOOT BEING CRUSHED!
( crying in pain )
- MY BODY DOES NOT LOOK THE SAME
FROM ANY SIDE, GOT IT?
- NOW DON'T GET UPSET.
THAT'S HIS OWN STUPID WAY OF
HIDING THE FACT
THAT HE'S CHECKING YOU OUT
IN YOUR SWIMSUIT.
- GEE, AKI YOU'RE SO SWEET.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HIDE YOUR LOVE
BEHIND STUPID COMMENTS.
- COOL. YOUR MICRO-BREASTS
ARE HOT.
- AND NOW I GOUGE OUT YOUR EYES.
-MY EYES! I'M BLIND.
SHE STABBED MY FREAKIN' EYES!
- YUUJI. NOW YOU WON'T
LOOK AT OTHER GIRLS.
- OH WOW. YOU'RE SO PRETTY.
- THAT'S VERY SWEET. I BLUSH.
- OKAY STUD.
ISN'T THERE A LITTLE SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO SAY TO SHOUKO NOW ?
- SHOUKO...
YOU GOT A RAG? MY EYES
FEEL LIKE THEY'RE BLEEDING.
- TELL HER HOW YOU
LIKE HER SWIMSUIT.
- HOW CAN I,
WHEN I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING?
- AH, MAN YUUJI'S TURNING
INTO A WUSS.
AM I RIGHT, KOUTA? KOUTA?
KOUTA!
- I'M SORRY BUT MY TIME HERE
IS FINISHED.
- OH NO. NOT YET.
WHO DARES ATTACK MY FRIEND
KOUTA LIKE THIS!
- I'M SORRY!
IT TOOK ME A WHILE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO TIE MY STRINGS IN
THE BACK ALL BY MYSELF.
- ( screaming )
SWEET DEATH EMBRACE ME!
IT'S LIKE A WEAPON
OF MASS DESTRUCTION!
- YOSHII! WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- ( speaking in
foreign language )
- MINAMI, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S WEIRD, BUT SOMETIMES
WHEN MINAMI GETS UPSET,
GERMAN IS THE ONLY
THING SHE CAN SPEAK.
- OH MAN, WHAT THE
HECK'S GOING ON?
- ( punching )
- ( groaning in pain )
- YOU CANNOT LOOK AT HER.
- SO IS THIS EVERYBODY?
- NO. HIDEYOSHI HASN'T
MADE IT YET.
- WHAT'S HIS SWIMSUIT AGAIN?
- A PAIR OF TRUNKS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU ALL WAITING.
- MY NOSE DIDN'T EXPLODE.
- IT'S DRIED UP.
- DID EVERYBODY MAKE IT?
- THANKS HIDEYOSHI,
WAY TO GO MAKE US LOOK LIKE
WE'RE NOT EVEN TRYING!
- BIG FAKER. PRETEND YOU'RE
GOING TO COME HERE IN TRUNKS
AND THEN
SHOW UP LIKE THAT.
- I THINK YOU'RE THE PRETTIEST
GIRL I'VE EVER SEEN.
- I WOULD THANK YOU EXCEPT THAT
I'M ACTUALLY A GUY.
- THEN WHY DID YOU COME HERE
WEARING A GIRLS SWIMSUIT?
- I TOLD THE STUPID SALESPERSON
I REQUIRED REGULAR
FASHION FOR A POOL.
- TO BE FAIR TO THE SALESPERSON,
IT WOULD BE REGULAR FASHION IF
YOU WERE A PRETTY PRINCESS.
- POOR YUUJI... ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
- YEAH, DON'T WORRY.
EVENTUALLY I'LL START...
- ( screaming in pain )
KILL ME ALREADY!
- LOVE HURTS. BUT IT CAN
HURT WORSE
IF YOU ALLOW YOUR EYES
TO WANDER.
- Hideyoshi: BAKA AND TEST
- ( laughing ) THERE!
- ( muffled )
SHOUKO? SHOUKO?
- HEY, YOSHII, LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
A PRETTY GOOD SWIMMER.
- YOU'RE NOT GOING IN MIZUKI?
- ACTUALLY, THE ONLY THING I DO
IN WATER IS FLOAT.
NOBODY EVER TAUGHT ME
HOW TO SWIM BEFORE.
- I CAN TEACH YOU HOW TO SWIM
IF YOU'RE UP FOR IT.
I'M A REALLY GOOD SWIMMER.
- THAT IS SO SWEET OF YOU,
I WOULD LOVE THAT.
- IT'S LIKE THEY'VE
SWITCHED ROLES.
MIZUKI THE A STUDENT IS BEING
HELPED BY MINAMI THE F STUDENT.
THINGS ARE BACKWARDS...
MIZUKI'S GOT F'S
AND MINAMI'S GOT A'S.
- WITH DUCT TAPE AND THE RIGHT
LIGHTING I'M AT LEAST A B.
- IN CASE YOU'RE CURIOUS
YUUJI I'M RANKED A STRAIGHT C.
- ( muffled ) I HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
- HEY DORKFACE!
ME AND YOU SHOULD PLAY
UNDERWATER DEMON!
- UNDERWATER DEMON?
IS THAT ANYTHING LIKE SHARKS
AND MINNOWS?
- NO. IN UNDERWATER DEMON,
THE PERSON BEING THE DEMON
CHASES AFTER EVERYBODY ELSE.
AS SOON AS HE IS ABLE TO DRAG
SOMEONE INTO THE WATER
AND DROWN THEM HE'S THE WINNER.
- THAT ISN'T A GAME,
THAT'S PSYOCHOTIC!
- LISTEN, HAZUKI...
THAT GAME IS TOO DANGEROUS
FOR YOU TO PLAY, OKAY?
- OKAY. JUST SOUNDED LIKE FUN.
- CHECK IT OUT. HEY SHOUKO!
- YOU RANG?
- I'M GOING TO TEACH YOU
AN AWESOME POOL GAME
TO PLAY WITH YUUJI.
IT'S PRETTY SIMPLE.
YOU DRAG YUUJI INTO THE WATER.
AFTER HE DROWNS, YOU
PERFORM CPR ON HIM
AND THAT'LL MAKE YOU A WINNER.
- ( screaming )
- ( water splashing )
- HELP! I CAN'T...
PLEASE! SOMEONE... HELP!
- SEE? NOT MUCH FUN.
- ( water bubbling )
- YOU DID THIS, DIDN'T YOU?
- YUUJI, IT'S ONLY A GAME.
- ( muffled ) GET OFF OF ME!
WHY DO YOU HATE ME SO MUCH?
- SHOUKO... WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HEY, AIKO.
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE AIKO?
GOT SWIMMING CLASS?
- I'VE GOT A MEMBERSHIP
TO THE POOL HERE.
A BUNCH OF US DO ACTUALLY.
- THERE'S MY HONEY!
- NOW WHY WOULD YOU PLAN A
NEAR NAKED TRIP TO THE POOL
WITHOUT TELLING YOUR
SWEET GIRLFRIEND?
- WHY ARE YOU HERE, MIHARU?
- I HAVE SPIES AND THEY'RE
ALWAYS KEEPING ME UP TO DATE
SO I CAN PROTECT YOU FROM
THE CRAZIES AROUND HERE.
- WELL, I'M GOING TO GO
GET MY SUIT ON.
BY THE WAY, BOYS, IF YOU'RE
GONNA CHECK ME OUT,
DON'T LET ME CATCH YOU.
- OH CRAP. SHE JUST TOTALLY
GAVE ME PERMISSION.
THEN MY MANHOOD REQUIRES
THAT I GO.
- BETTER THINK TWICE BEFORE
FOLLOWING YOUR MANHOOD, YOSHII.
IT'LL ONLY LEAD YOU TO TROUBLE
IN THE END.
- YOU DO WANT TO LIVE TO SEE
ANOTHER TOMORROW, DON'T YOU AKI?
- ( screaming in pain )
- THIS IS THE CREEPIEST
POOL EVER.
MY ONLY HOPE NOW
IS THAT KOUTA'S CAMERA
WILL BE ABLE TO FIND ITS MARK.
- NO!
- OH MAN, SWIMMING REALLY
MAKES ME HUNGRY, YOU KNOW?
- THEN I'VE GOT THE
PERFECT TREAT FOR YOU.
- I BROUGHT ALONG SOME SNACKS.
I DIDN'T MAKE ENOUGH
FOR EVERYONE
SO I WASN'T GOING TO MENTION IT.
- ( all gasping )
- I ONLY HAVE THREE WAFFLES BUT
THEY'RE REALLY CUTE.
- WE HAVE TO DO IT!
- A WINNER-EAT-NONE
CHAMPIONSHIP.
- Both: SUDDEN DEATH
SWIMMING CONTEST!
- YEAH!
- THE RULES ARE SIMPLE. THE
FIRST ONE TO REACH THE END
AFTER MAKING A
LAP IS THE WINNER!
- Fukuhara: MIZUKI MADE THREE
WAFFLES OF DEATH.
THERE ARE FOUR BOYS
TO FEED THEM TO,
WHICH MEANS WHOEVER WINS THIS
RACE HAS THE RIGHT TO REFUSE
EATING AND LIVE TO
FIGHT ANOTHER DAY.
- READY EVERYBODY?
ON YOUR MARK!
- KOUTA'S WEAK BECAUSE
HE'S A BLEEDER.
HIDEYOSHI'S HOT BUT
I'M TOTALLY STRONGER.
- SET!
- WHICH MEANS...
IT'S JUST BETWEEN
THE TWO OF US.
- GO!
- DROP DEAD!
- YOU PLAY DIRTY!
-
WHATEVER GET'S ME THROUGH
THE DAY, WAFFLE EATER!
- NOT BAD, AKIHISA.
- IS THAT ALL YOU GOT FOR ME,
TOUGH GUY?
- YOU GUYS CAN FIGHT
ALL YOU WANT,
BUT THEY'RE AT THE TURN ALREADY.
- WHAT?
- THIS IS BAD.
THEY'RE GOING TO BEAT US.
- NOT IF WE CAN HELP IT!
I'M GONNA TAKE KOUTA
OUT OF THE RACE,
WHILE YOU GO AFTER HIDEYOSHI!
- OKAY!
HIDEYOSHI! YOU SHALL NOT PASS!
WHAT?
WHAT'S THIS?
- AKI!
- WHY ON EARTH WOULD YOU DO THAT
TO HIDEYOSHI? WHY?
- WHAT DID I DO?
WAIT!
DON'T TELL ME I ACCIDENTALLY
SNAGGED HIS...
- HEY! WHAT DID YOU DO
THAT FOR?
- Mizuki: YOSHII!
- Minami: AKI!
HIDEYOSHI, COVER YOURSELF.
QUICK!
- BUT WHY?
I'M JUST A REGULAR GUY.
- I'M A GONER,
BUT I HAVE NO REGRETS.
- ( laughing )
I WONDER HOW YOU GET BLOOD
OUT OF A POOL.
- THAT WAS A LOT OF FUN,
WASN'T IT?
- YEAH.
- I AM TOTALLY BEAT THOUGH.
- IT MIGHT BE ALL THE
BLOOD LOSS, DON'T YOU THINK?
- HERE'S AN IDEA. WHAT DO YOU
SAY WE ALL HIT THE BATHHOUSE?
- OKAY!
- HOLD UP, KID. THIS IS THE WAY
TO THE MEN'S BATH.
YOU AND HIDEYOSHI
HAVE TO GO THAT WAY.
- ( laughing )
I'M JUST JOKING.
- MY CHOICE OF BATH
IS ALSO NOT A JOKE.
- OKAY, YOU'VE HAD
YOUR FUN, YOU TWO,
YOU CAN'T BATHE
WITH ALL THE BOYS.
- NOT AGAIN! I TOLD YOU BEFORE.
IT'S TOTALLY INAPPROPRIATE FOR
ME TO GO WITH THE GIRLS.
- DON'T SWEAT IT, HIDEYOSHI.
CHECK IT.
- SO IT'S ACKNOWLEDGED
BY SOCIETY.
- SO SWEET.
- SOOTHES THE BONES.
WHAT'S YOUR DEAL, KOUTA?
- NAKED GIRLS ARE
RIGHT OVER THERE.
- WHAT?
- ( girls giggling )
- HEY! WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
- IT'S JUST WASHING.
- I'M PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF
SOAPING MYSELF, THANK YOU!
- IT DOESN'T MAKE YOU WEIRD
OR ANYTHING.
- WOULD SOMEBODY PLEASE
SAVE ME FROM HER!
- ( grunting )
- ( humming )
- ( screaming )
- OH THESE?
YOU KNOW THEY'RE REALLY NOT AS
FUN AS EVERYONE THINKS.
YOU GET THESE BACKACHES
AND JOGGING'S A TOTAL PAIN.
- THAT'S THE LIE ALL YOU
HUGE BOOBERS TELL US.
- AKIHISA, SHAMPOO.
- SURE, HERE.
- SAID SHAMPOO, THIS IS SOAP
THAT I BOUGHT.
- ALL YOU NEED TO
CLEAN HAIR IS BUBBLES
SO I JUST RUBBED IT ON MY HEAD.
- WHY THE HELL DID I BOTHER
ASKING YOU TO GET SHAMPOO?
- HEY, SHOUKO, CAN I BORROW
YOUR SHAMPOO?
THANKS!
- YUUJI, I NEED SOME SOAP.
- CATCH.
- Mizuki: YOU TWO ARE ACTING
LIKE A MARRIED COUPLE ALREADY.
- MIZUKI, BITE YOUR TONGUE!
SAYING CRAP LIKE THAT ONLY
STRENGTHENS HER DELUSIONS.
IF YOU START BUYING INTO IT
SHE'LL ONLY TRAP ME...
- ( humming )
- I DON'T THINK THEY CHANGE SIZE
IN ZERO GRAVITY...
- DON'T YOU KNOW THAT
IT'S BAD MANNERS
TO TRY AND STAY COVERED UP
IN A SPA LIKE THIS.
YOU HAVE TO SET YOURSELF FREE
AND LET US BE TOGETHER AS
NATURE INTENDED!
- WHY CAN'T SHE JUST
LEAVE ME ALONE?
- ( humming )
- HEY, DID YOU KNOW?
THE MEN'S AND WOMEN'S SIDES OF
THE BATH ARE TOTALLY CONNECTED.
- YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO
SEE STUFF UNDERWATER.
- Both: DIVE CHALLENGE!
- HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT!
- THEY KEEP US SEPARATE
BY SUPPLYING ALL THE HOT
WATER RIGHT THERE!
- LET'S FREEZE OUR HEADS
AND THEN WE CAN TAKE THE PAIN!
- Both: DIVE CHALLENGE
NUMBER TWO!
- MY EYES! THE PAIN! OW! PAIN!
PAIN, PAIN, PAIN!
- ( laughing ) LOOKS LIKE IT
DIDN'T WORK, DID IT?
- WE CAN'T LET THAT WENCH JUST
MOCK US LIKE THAT.
- IT'S GAME TIME.
- TIME TO PULL OUT THE BIG GUNS.
- Fukuhara: THE IRON BRACELET
ALLOWS AKIHISA
TO SUMMON HIS AVATAR
WITHOUT THE NEED
OF TEACHER APPROVAL.
- AWAKEN!
I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR. SUMMON!
OKAY, GO!
- YOSHII'S STUPID AVATAR IS
GETTING ALL CREEPY!
- CAN YOU SEE?
- MY AVATAR CAN SEE THEM
BUT IT'S JUST MAKING MY BRAIN
EXPLODE INSIDE!
- TRY PLAN B. HERE.
- AWESOME! MY AVATAR CAN
DEFINITELY TAKE SOME PICTURES.
- Girls: I'M
SUMMONING MY AVATAR!
- SUMMON!
- WE'RE NOT GONNA LET YOU USE
YOUR AVATAR AS A PEEPING TOM!
- I DON'T THINK THAT
LITTLE THING
HAS WHAT IT TAKES
TO GET PAST US.
- IT'S NOT THE SIZE OF THE SHIP
BUT THE MOTION OF THE OCEAN!
- ( screaming )
- THOSE WHO DIED, MEET ME IN THE
REMEDIAL CLASSROOM!
- WHAT? WHERE DID HE COME FROM?
HELP ME!
- HE REALLY HASN'T EVEN THE
SLIGHTEST BIT OF LUCK.
- LOOK AT THAT, I WON!
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION SEVEN,
WHAT IS THE MARRIAGEABLE AGE IN
JAPANESE CIVIL LAW?
- Akihisa: THE DIFFERENCE IN
AGE DOESN'T MATTER
AS LONG AS THERE'S LOVE.
- Fukuhara: THANK YOU FOR THE
HOPES AND DREAMS.
- Akihisa: NEXT EPISODE! ME,
SHOUKO, AND KISARAGI GRAND PARK
- Fukuhara: THIS WILL BE
ON THE TEST.