Good morning, Run-chan.
Morning.
Got your panties?
Of course! I'm awake and alert this time!
Come on! Let's go!
Run-chan...
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
ふわふわ　浮遊して
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
きらめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
一つになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
私の行方は彼方
Let's go together.
issho ni ikou
一緒に行こう
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
セカイのSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　集まるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
おはようと　さよならの　間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
私たちだけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
生まれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ち合わせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振る君へと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
取って置きの今日を渡そう
And we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
おしゃべりが始まる
There's nothing like a fizzy drink to wake you up!
Don't people usually drink coffee?
Really?
Soda goes all fwoosh and makes your eyes flutter,
so you wake up right away!
Is that how it goes?
Nice shot.
Come to think of it, I haven't seen Tooru yet today.
She has cleaning duty today,
so she said she'd be busy this morning.
Really?
It feels like we're always together,
so it's lonely when she's not around.
You're right.
But if she's on duty, there's no helping it.
That's right.
What is it, Nagi?
Say,
want to go take a look?
At what?
First-year student, Tooru!
Classmates
Look at this graffiti!
It's still there.
It's carved in, so it'll probably stay.
Anyway, let's get a move on.
Wait for me!
Seeing the first-year rooms brings back memories.
It hasn't been all that long, though.
Ah, isn't that Tooru's classroom?
I wonder what Tooru's like in class?
Maybe everyone's afraid of her?
Surprisingly, Tooru's an honor student!
No way!
I thought she'd be a delinquent!
That's right!
S-Swinging around that bat, staining the room with blood...
No, I don't think so...
Sensei, we're done with these.
Ah, thanks as always.
Um, there was a mistake in the number of boys written here,
so I corrected it.
Is that okay?
Oh my, you're right.
That must have been my mistake.
Thank you! You were a big help.
No, it was nothing.
To-o-ru!
"It was nothing," she says.
What a good girl!
So reliable. Nudge nudge.
Why are
they here...
Umm...
I forgot my textbook,
so can I look on with you?
Sure.
Thank you so much!
Sorry.
I forgot my contacts today, too.
I-I see.
Ah, I can't see...
Too close...
Thank you very much!
You saved me there!
Don't mention it.
My name is Yutaka!
I've actually been meaning to talk with you!
I just never had the opportunity.
I-I see...
Let's be friends, please!
TOORUN
Toorun!
Huh?!
As a sign of our friendship,
let me buy you a juice!
Wait!
What did you just-
Huh? Tooru?
What's wrong?
What is it?
This is unusual.
Are you squeezing me or something?
Ow-ow-ow-ow!
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow...
What's up with Tooru?
Dunno.
Thanks for waiting, Toorun!
I bought some more!
Huh? Toorun?
Where did you go?
Toorun!
Can I have a moment?
Yes?
You have a beautiful forehead.
Run's talking with a strange man...
It's very nice.
Ah, thanks.
And plus, what's with the design on that shirt?
By the way, where is the nurse's office?
It's over there.
I see. Thank you.
Well, see you, then.
Nagi-chan!
H-Hey, who was that?
He says he's the new nurse.
Seems like he got lost.
So that's who he was.
I thought he was someone suspicious at first.
Also, he complimented me,
saying, "Your forehead is beautiful. It's very nice"!
And you didn't find that... strange?
Really? We have a new school nurse?
Special Ed Teacher
Satou-sensei
He looks really shady, though.
I bet the girls will like him, though.
And there he is again!
Thanks for before.
You really helped me out.
Oh no, no need to thank me.
Ah, yes.
You should drop by the nurse's office one of these days.
I'll have a special bed prepared for you.
Sensei, you're funny!
Come whenever you like.
Something's been moving around for a while...
You are...
Don't act so friendly with Run-chan!
I see. So you're called Run-chan.
May I call you Run-chan as well?
Sure!
I see. Run-chan.
How adorable. Run-chan.
You look like a sea urchin,
so you'll be Uni-chan.
She looks depressed.
He's sure being infuriatingly nice.
Ah, but Run-chan, your forehead really is adorable.
Thank you very much.
That's right... it really is...
Really...
Get away from Run-chan!
E-Excuse me.
It's time for my medicine.
Ah, so his body is weak.
Oh yeah!
Look at this!
Ta-dah!
No music, no life!
You got the limited edition color one!
Oh. I did?
Aw, man, I want one so bad.
How very high-tech.
What sort of music do you listen to, Run?
Umm...
I'm still living a No Music Life.
You couldn't put anything on this?
I tried a bunch of different ways,
but I couldn't get any music on it, so I thought it was broken.
I tried that...
Minidisk Compo
It won't connect...
and this...
Cassette
It won't connect...
and that...
Just like with a TV
Hit at a 45
degree angle
Yeah...
But it just wouldn't work.
What was the last one there? The last one!
You took it apart?!
Well, I thought it was broken.
And you thought an amateur could fix it?!
You could have sent it back to the manufacturer or something!
Calm down!
Nagi, it's not like it was yours.
If it were mine, I'd have taken you apart!
Don't worry!
I'm not broken, so you don't have to.
That's not what I meant!
It's on!
Ah, thank goodness!
Run, to put music on this,
you have to use a computer.
Huh?
I don't have one.
So why'd you buy that?
Um, where do you go off to every break?
I won't let go 'till you tell me~
I was kidding!
Toorun, wait!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Are you angry?
I'm not.
It got so stretched...
It'll go back when I wash it, so don't worry.
No! This is useful in its own way!
Now, where are we headed?
Yutaka shall pull you there!
Run-chan?
I see.
They have gym next.
We're so close, yet so far.
What do I need? What am I missing?
Even if I don't look, the truth is, I know:
It's just a bit of courage and toughness.
(I miss you) If I call you, then right away,
(do you hear me) I can meet you, in voice,
(hold me real tight) but I want you to hug me
(don't you feel me) so tight that I'll break.
(I miss you) I want to see you right now.
(this ain't right) It's not really romantic love,
but if you aren't here for me, it's meaningless.
So I want you to hug me close. (never get enough)
Run-chan.
In the end, it was Tooru's
job to upload the music.
In use
But man,
I can't believe we're still wearing bloomers.
That's for sure.
They wear shorts in other schools.
Bloomers are practically panties.
And we're already wearing panties underneath...
It's panties-on-panties.
Nagi?
There's something wrong with a class where we wear panties.
"They're not panties, so it's not embarassing"?!
It sure as heck is!
Nagi, you're being way more embarassing than the bloomers!
The way you keep saying that makes it sound like you like it.
Start warming up!
Hup.
Hey.
What is it, Yuuko-chan?
Do we pull for this?
I thought we push.
Oh, really?
Then let's do it on "go".
All right!
Ready, go!
What are those two doing?
Hup!
I guess we were supposed to pull on the last one.
Guess we were, Yuuko-chan.
We got this one right!
Looks like you're enjoying yourselves.
If you keep goofing off,
you're going to hurt yourselves.
We'll be okay!
Huh?
What's wrong, Nagi-chan?
N-Nothing!
Okay! On to the next question.
Toorun, you looking at Yutaka?
No mistake about it!
Can Yutaka help you?
Outta the way.
Okay! Who can solve this problem?
My, a volunteer.
You mean Yutaka?
Of course.
Go on, come to the front.
Toorun!
In use
Yuuko-chan!
Try leaving that out instead of tucking it in!
You mean my gym uniform?
Mm-hmm. Not wearing any.
Nagi-chan, look quick!
Yuuko-chan's not wearing anything below! Nothing!
Run, don't shout so loud!
... is what happened.
Tooru, you're in your gym uniform, too.
You want me to untuck it?
I'm afraid it won't meet your expectations.
Ah! This is...
just a one-piece dress!
You sure tuck that in well!
She complimented me!
Toorun.
That's...
Okay! Let's get started!
We'll be doing warm-ups,
so get into pairs.
Tooruuun!
Please partner with Yutaka!
Ah. Miporin.
Yutaka, you'll be my partner, right?
Uh? Yutaka wants to partner with Toorun-
With me, right?
Then let's go over here.
Miporin...
Hey, Yuuko.
Got any band-aids?
Why? Are you hurt?
Well, when I fell down in gym earlier,
I scraped my knee.
Oh no! You'd better put on some disinfectant.
Let's go to the nurse's office.
Huh? A rinse and a band-aid should be good enough.
That's no good!
If it gets infected, you'll regret it!
I'm telling you, it's fine.
Besides, class is about to start.
Forget that, come on!
Hold on!
I told you, I'm fine!
And I say no!
Wonder what happened?
Excuse u...
Yuuko-chan?
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!
I didn't expect you'd be down there...
Ah, I just had a seizure and collapsed.
Thanks.
Yuuko-chan?
What happen-
...ed? Huh?
Sensei, I'm so sorry.
I didn't see you.
No, don't be.
In fact, I'm honored to have been stepped on by you.
Um,
Satou-sensei, you seem to like Run.
What do you like about her?
The candid way she talks,
and how she's exactly how she seems...
That's for sure.
Plus, she seems like a natural dominatrix.
Plus her forehead is beautiful.
Plus the wideness of her forehead is perfect.
Plus her forehead...
Th-This teacher...
Excuse us.
Come by again any time.
Class already started.
Sorry for dragging you two along.
No worries. You can't underestimate a scrape.
I got it. I'll be careful.
I wonder if that Satou-sensei will be all right, though.
How so?
He was collapsed earlier, wasn't he?
Can we just leave him alone?
I guess I'm a bit worried.
That's right!
That teacher's bad news waiting to happen!
Bad news in what way?
That teacher...
h-has some weird tastes.
Ah, that's what you meant.
He told me my forehead was pretty!
That's certainly bad news.
Right?
Hmm... well, whatever.
Toorun,
could you explain this part to me?
Sure. What don't you get?
All of it!
Then let's start from the beginning.
Got it!
Tooru-san's nice, isn't she?
Yep!
Why don't you get it?!
I've explained this so many times!
I'm sorry! This goes like this, right?
No, I told you that's wrong!
You do it like this!
Meaning here goes like this?
I would have given up by now.
No, you do it like this!
I agree.
Understand?
Not at all.
Yutaka!
Oh, Miporin.
Yutaka, you've been bothering Tooru-san too much lately.
Eh?
Sorry, Tooru-san.
You don't have to put up with her.
She's a pain in the rear, isn't she?
Come on, let's go.
Look at the trouble you gave Tooru-san!
If you just can't understand, ask me first, 'kay?
It's lonely when she's not around...
... is not what I'm thinking! It's not!
Tooru!
Tooru! Wait!
No! I can't- Please, stop!
What's up with Tooru?
Dunno.
I give in! Give! Give! Give! Give...
Because I'm not lonely.
The hats hanging from the tall rack
akane ni narabu
あかねに並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kakeboushi
背高かけ帽子
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
楽しい一日の終わり
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　おしゃべり
Our chatter goes on and on,
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigatou
いつもありがとう
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれてよかったな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
るるるん
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風と　心ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
次の角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Next time
And so,
Yutaka and Miporin got a lot of screen time!
By the way, it's summer already, isn't it?
Huh? Summer already?
Isn't it a bit early?
And that means all sorts of things!
You know, like swimsuit and hot springs.
Well, I dunno about the hot springs.
But before you get in your swimsuit,
a fearful barrier awaits!
Next time on A-Channel!
"Kilogram"!
Diet, huh?
With a nice body like Yutaka's, that word has no meaning!
See you next week!