I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but then a small incident happened.
What I received was a courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
Our tumultuous encounters...
...are filled with feelings and words that
we can't express to each other.
Because I believed I wanted to understand
your wishes and sadness...
...I'm filled with feelings that
I want to pass along to you.
Only to you, and your heart.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
And so...
...as of today, each crew member's new mission
involves the search and recovery...
...of the remaining Lost Logia... the Jewel Seeds.
Due to the extensive scope and
difficulty of this mission...
...we have enlisted the one who discovered the Lost
Logia, who is also a mage skilled with barriers...
Yes. My name is Yuuno Scrya.
And also a resident mage of the world
the Seeds fell to, working with him...
I-I'm Takamachi Nanoha.
While in the care of the Civil Affairs Bureau,
these two have been assigned to us.
Please take good care of us.
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean!
From now on, we'll be pinpointing
the Jewel Seeds from here.
Once we locate them, we'll send
you two to the scene right away.
Yes, sir!
Captain, I've brought you some tea.
Thank you.
Now that I think of it, Nanoha-san...
will you be okay missing school for a while?
Ah, yes. I came up with an explanation
for my family and friends, so...
It appears that Takamachi-san will be absent
from school due to family circumstances.
But she's not out because she's sick or anything
serious, so there's no need to worry.
While Takamachi-san is absent, would someone
gather hand-outs and take notes for h-
Yes! I will.
In that case, I'm counting on you, Alisa-san.
Yes!
Now then, shall we begin homeroom?
Stand.
Bow.
Nanoha-chan... I wonder how you're doing...
Sit.
I got it, Nanoha!
Yeah!
Sealing Mode. Set up.
Stand by. Ready.
Lyrical Magical! Jewel Seed Serial VIII.
Seal!
Sealing.
Receipt Number VIII.
The situation is under control.
Jewel Seed VIII safely secured.
Good job down there, Nanoha-chan, Yuuno-kun.
Yep!
I'll create a gate for you two now.
Just wait there for a second.
Hmm... those two sure are impressive.
At the rate they're going, I might
really want them to stay with us.
The black-clad girl... her name is Fate, right?
Fate Testarossa... there was once a great
mage with the same family name.
Huh? Really?
It's an old story now, though...
A great mage from Central Midchilda... in the
middle of one of her magical experiments...
...she had an accident that formed a great dimensional
interference, and was exiled because of it.
Could this girl be related to her?
I don't know... names don't mean anything.
Ah... as I thought, it's no good. I can't find her.
Fate-chan appears to be using a strong,
complicated barrier to block us.
Her dog familiar...
It's probably supporting her.
Thanks to that, they've already stolen two
Jewel Seeds we've managed to locate.
Perform a very thorough search, and locate her.
We're really counting on you for this.
Yes, yes...
Doesn't look like Fate-chan will be showing
herself anytime soon, huh...
Yeah... though it looks like she's been
capturing Jewel Seeds, too...
Yeah...
Fate, it's no good. It's looking like this is all in vain.
I see...
Really... it's pretty difficult to hide and search
for the Jewel Seeds at the same time...
Yeah... but let's try our best a little longer.
It's been ten days since we were
brought on board the Asura.
We've managed to get Jewel Seeds
VII, IX, and XII... only those three.
Fate-chan and Arf have managed to get
two themselves... Serials II and V...
Six more, huh?
The remaining six... we just can't seem to locate them...
We're increasing the scope of the
search beyond landmasses.
Since the ocean is nearby, there's
a chance they may be there.
Amy is searching there right now, in addition
to searching for that black-clad girl.
I see.
Today was another swing and a miss, huh?
Yeah... it's possible this could end up
taking an extended period of time...
Nanoha... I'm sorry.
Aren't you lonely?
Not really... I'm not the least bit lonely at all.
After all, I'm with you, Yuuno-kun,
and I'm pretty used to being alone as it is.
Because ever since I was little,
I've been left alone a lot.
You see... in my house, when I was still really young...
...Dad hurt himself on a job, and for a time
he couldn't leave his hospital bed.
We had just opened our coffee shop,
and it wasn't as popular as it is now...
...so Mom and my brother were
always really busy there...
And Sis was always together with Dad, to nurse him.
So... until recently, I've been home
by myself most of the time.
So I'm pretty used to it.
I see...
Now that I think about it, I don't know too
much about your family, Yuuno-kun.
Ah... I've always been alone from the start.
Huh? Really?
I didn't have parents, so I was raised
by everyone else in my tribe.
That's why I consider everyone in
the Scrya tribe to be my family.
I see...
Yuuno-kun, once we finish this mess,
let's have more talks like this, okay?
Yeah. Once everything's cleaned up.
Once all of this is cleaned up, once this
Jewel Seed problem settles down...
Yeah... after that, I'm sure we'll...
Emergency! A large magical reaction has been
detected within the search parameters.
W-What are those kids doing down there?!
Arukas, Krutas, Eygias...
Heavenly gods who shine over all,
descend upon us now as I guide you.
Baruel, Zaluel, Browzel...
The Jewel Seeds are probably in the ocean...
So she's going to release electrical power into it,
and force activations to locate them all at once.
That much isn't wrong, but... Fate...!
Strike with lightning and roar with resonant thunder...
Arukas, Krutas, Eygias...
I found them... the remaining six...
Attacking with this much magical power... and to try
to seal all of them with her remaining strength...
Something like this will definitely push Fate
beyond her limits, even for her magical skill!
Arf, please support me with spatial barriers.
Yeah! Leave it to me!
So... no matter who comes, and no matter
what happens, I will definitely protect her!
Let's go, Bardiche. Let's give it all we've got.
This girl is so reckless, it's outrageous!
Thoughtless, indeed. She'll doubtlessly
end up destroying herself out there.
She's going way beyond the limits
of her magical power throughput.
Fate-chan!
I'll go there right away!
There's no need. If we leave her alone
long enough, she'll finish herself off.
Even if she doesn't kill herself out there...
...we can make our move once
she's used up all her power.
But...!
Start making preparations to capture the Seeds.
Understood.
Fate! Fate!
Now that we've finally found the last of them,
we can't afford to lose them now.
It may seem cruel, but this is the reality of the matter.
But...
Go.
Nanoha, go!
I'll open the gate for you, so go to that girl.
But Yuuno-kun, the reason I want to talk to her...
The reason I want to talk to Fate...
doesn't have anything to do with you...
That may be, but...
Nanoha, if you're ever in a bad situation,
I want to be your strength.
Just like how you were for me.
You're...!
I'm sorry. Takamachi Nanoha is ignoring
orders and taking selfish actions!
Transferring you into that girl's barrier!
Let's go, Raising Heart.
Wind in the sky, stars in the heavens.
The bright, shining light is within my arms.
And a resolute heart beats within my chest!
Raising Heart! Set up!
Stand by. Ready.
Don't you dare... get in Fate's way!
You're wrong! We didn't come here to fight you!
Yuuno-kun!
I don't believe this! What are you two doing?!
I'm sorry. I'll apologize later for ignoring your orders.
But I just can't leave her alone!
She's all alone! And I can understand some the
sadness someone feels when she's all alone!
First, we have to stop the Jewel Seeds before
this turns into something much worse!
So for now, let's support hem as they seal them!
Fate-chan!
Let's help each other and stop these Jewel Seeds!
Power Charge.
Supplying Complete.
We'll each take care of half of them!
Yuuno-kun and Arf-san are stopping
them for us! Now's our chance!
On the count of three, we'll seal
them all at the same time!
Shooting Mode.
The thing you want most when
you're feeling alone and sad...
...isn't to hear, "Everything's all right,"
or the kindness of others, but rather...
Sealing Form. Set up.
Bardiche...
Divine Buster... Full Power.
You can do it, right?
All right, my master.
One, two...!
Thunder...!
Divine...!
Rage!
Buster!
The remaining six Jewel Seeds have
been confirmed as sealed!
W-What an unsystematic...
But that was amazing...
Being able to understand each
other with the same feelings...
With sad feelings and lonely feelings,
being able to stop half of them each...
Ah, that's it... I finally understand.
I want to share my time with her.
I want us to be friends.
Dimensional interference?!
A wide-area magical attack from another dimension
is heading straight for them and us!
Ah! Only six seconds until impact!
Mother?!
Fate-chan!
Get out of...
...our way!
There's only three!
They'll start running wild again! Hurry and seize them!
It's no good! The dimensional attack disabled
the functionality of our ship's tools!
25 seconds remaining before functionality returns!
We can't trace the source of the attack!
Until functionality fully returns, transfer all
power into our magical defense systems.
Yes, ma'am!
And also... retrieve Nanoha-san,
Yuuno-kun, and Chrono.
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
Next time, we'll finally
be at our final scene!
In order to withstand the final
storm, everyone makes a vow within their heart.
And I tell my feelings to Fate.
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Ten: Everybody's
Separate Heart-felt Vows
Lyrical Magical!
So I can start anew as the true me!