Th-That's... impossible.
She's dead... I killed her.
And yet I thought she might still be alive.
To think that I hold onto such hope...
and try to gain her forgiveness...
Elen...
Reunion
Tell me what this is all about.
Four in the previous deal and another one today...
Muroto, the one killed today, was a man whom I had looked after since he was a kid.
What's going on, huh?!
Depending on your response...
Shiga, you can shoot.
Yes sir.
Lizzie...
Please be rational, Mr. Godo.
Shooting each other here...
will only serve to make Mr. Muroto's killer happy.
Wasn't that your order?
If you're suspicious of me, that's fine.
However, if you want to shoot, you should also prepare yourself.
Claudia, this is you we're talking about.
I bet you've got another option besides shooting each other.
If you calm things down here and do as I suggest,
three days from now, I'll smoke the ringleader out and present him to you.
Let's see how Inferno takes responsibility.
Counter snipe?
Right.
Reckless.
The day after tomorrow, the Godo Family
will be invited to the meeting among Inferno's senior members.
There they will be officially approved to join Inferno.
Once that happens, even Wisemel can't touch them.
So this'll be his last chance.
Then you're still suspicious of Wisemel?
The shootings from the other day...
Muroto's murder...
He's the only one who benefits from them.
The meeting will be held on the fifth floor of the Atrium Hotel.
It'll be held in a conference room with a glass wall.
So the prey will be put on display, huh?
And you'll lie in ambush.
You're really going to continue to use the Godo Family as a bait?
If it's successful, everything will work out fine.
Of course, this is a risky gamble that doesn't work without you... Phantom.
Ah! He's home!
Welcome home!
Hi, I'm back.
Hold on a sec. I'll reheat the soup right away.
Cal.
I found this when I was cleaning.
Did you disassemble it?
Sorry. I'll fix it right away.
Are you good with machines and stuff?
I often played with whatever we had at home by disassembling them.
I wanted to know how they worked.
Okay, it's done!
Put it back where you found it, okay?
Okay!
Work?
Yeah. Do you want to think about it with me?
Yes! I'll do it! I'll do it! So what is it?
The target is... on the fifth floor of this building.
Suppose the sniper is shooting from this side.
Are you the sniper?
No, it's not me. A different sniper.
We have to guess where he'll be shooting from.
Hmm...
It's not like he can shoot from anywhere...
He'll choose the best place that meets the criteria.
Criteria...
A place high enough but still inconspicuous would be good.
Like the rooftop of a building?
Yeah.
Then how about here?
No, it's too close.
It's all over if the target finds out.
It has to be at least 400 yards away.
At least 400 yards?! He can still hit the target from that far away?!
Depending on his equipment and skills, even 800 yards is still within the range.
Whoa...
But then that would be too broad... to identify the place.
Yeah, you have a whole bunch of places to choose from.
Hmmm...
It's homework, to be done before you go to bed. Let's eat now.
What's going on with that thing?
Everything is ready. Please leave it to me.
Don't fail. If things go wrong, you're dead meat.
Yes sir.
What's the matter?
Say, Reiji...
Don't you somehow feel reluctant to aim from a higher place?
Why?
When shooting a gun, aiming downward feels, how should I say, uncomfortable.
Am I saying something weird?
No, you're right. It's true that it's hard to shoot that way.
Which means that we can ignore places that are too high, doesn't it?
A place as horizontal as possible with the target.
Then we just need to worry about a clear line of sight.
If we narrow it down that way,
the number of places is rather limited, don't you think?
That's a good answer.
Am I correct?!
Yes, you are, so far.
All right!
We'll do the rest tomorrow at the site. You'll come with me.
What?! I can come along?!
I'm going somewhere with Reiji!
This isn't for fun.
Okay!
Excuse me.
Muroto's body went back to Japan on the flight earlier.
Tsuzuki and Kakinuma are on their way here with their men to take his place.
What about things like guns?
I had Giuseppe obtain them. We'll probably have them by tomorrow.
That German guy?
Drinking to say goodbye to Muroto?
Yeah... You have a drink, too.
Thank you.
It's not just him. Since we came here, Hamura and Shinjou, too...
I let five of my men die in a foreign land like this.
Millions of dollars are involved.
It's just natural for the situation to become a war.
I'm sure they understand it all.
That's exactly why...
I'm upset with myself for not being able to give a gun to Muroto.
Of course, I'll make Inferno take responsibility for this.
Regarding that matter, I'm suspicious of that Claudia woman.
I'm listening.
We know everything about that plot she set up.
If push comes to shove, she'll probably want to break things off with us.
Shiga...
In this case, she's innocent.
Do you have any proof?
Proof?
Shiga, what's the drawing on my back?
Five colored spheres and a rising dragon.
The dragon on my back feels it...
That woman is also carrying the same dragon on her back.
She has the same kind of mettle I have.
A dragon that gains control of heaven by obtaining spheres.
She's got that kind of dragon too.
Since we're alike, I know...
that I should leave the matter to her for now.
This isn't something I can explain with words.
Shiga, I'm counting on your wisdom.
So you trust my mettle.
If you insist that much...
I'll just protect your back.
Thanks for coming.
Now, what're you going to do, Inferno?
We've got to go!
Sorry! I'm coming.
This is a special occasion, so...
Shall we go, then?
Yep!
That's the target building.
We narrow down the places that meet the criteria we talked about yesterday,
and then walk around and identify the place.
How?
We'll look for a weather vane.
A weather vane?
Even a pro can't do difficult sniping without any preparation...
especially in an area full of big buildings like this.
Wind...
That's right. A strong wind will cause a margin of error when sniping.
The sniper has to watch the wind when he shoots.
You can't see wind.
Ah, that's right!
Snipers often have this sort of weather vane set up at each point.
Then we'll look for places where such a cloth or flag is put in an unusual way.
That's correct.
Cal...
Ah, sorry. I didn't find anything.
Me, neither.
Then, let's go to the next area.
I guess this is it for today.
Wait, Reiji.
This place seems strange.
Strange?
Look at that.
Good catch, Cal.
Bingo?!
Yeah.
There's no mistake about it. The sniping point is over there.
Say... are you going to shoot the sniper from here?
Yeah.
Could it be that he's Judy's killer?
He probably is.
At least he's one of those who were responsible.
Please let me be by your side.
Please let me see it... when you shoot him!
You shouldn't see someone die.
Judy was...
killed before my own eyes.
Normally, it's ideal to work as a two person team in a sniping mission.
In that case, the sniper is accompanied by his assistant.
Huh?
By using a different telescope,
the assistant keeps an eye on the target and its surrounding...
in order to support the sniper.
That's the observer.
His job is to watch everything to the end.
Can you do it?
Yes!
Cal, give me your hand.
Hm? What?
Your compensation for today.
This is...
Thank you, Reiji!
I'll take good care of it.
I'll take good care of it... always.
Our enemy will be there and the sun is at our backs.
He won't be able to see us due to the sunlight.
That's right.
Clo... Wisemel has arrived.
Okay.
Randy Weber isn't with him.
It's unnatural for Wisemel
not to be accompanied by his right hand man on this important occasion.
Don't you think they are going to try something?
Today is the promised day.
I can't wait to see what that woman will do.
A white suit and a gun.
It's a suitable appearance to jump into hell.
Let's go, Shiga.
Yes sir. I'll follow you wherever you go.
There's no one there, Reiji.
Could it possibly be a different place?
Calm down. It's still early.
Welcome... to Inferno...
There he is! There's someone behind the water tower!
I see him. Can you see his face?
The face is hidden and I can't see it. A man... or maybe a woman.
This is bad, Reiji! He's going to shoot! Hurry!
No...
It can't be her.
Reiji?
She's... dead...
I... killed her...
Elen...
Reiji! Shoot!
Show...
Reiji?!
your face!
He's out!
Reiji!
Were you shot?! Did it hit you?!
No, it's just a scratch.
Stupid Reiji!
Why did you do such a reckless thing?!
I wanted to see his face at any cost.
You dummy.
You did a good job, observer.
He was Judy's killer.
You avenged her.
Yeah.
Now it's clear who was pulling the strings.
The rest is...
You bastards!
What was that?! What happened?!
There's... one more.
What?!
Can't be...
No way...
Mission completed.
Can't be...
Yes...
Master.
Next episode
Confession
I don't want to be separated from him.
I want to be with him forever.
I want to be of help to Reiji so that he'll think that he needs me.