It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Decision
The date changes at the stroke of midnight.
Here's some new shampoo, Miss Nagumo.
Ah, thank you.
MIss Nagumo.
Shinpei and I saw a memory from 14 years ago.
From when Haine and ya first met.
Yes, I heard.
Y'were...
a real washboard then! So how?
Can I touch 'em for a sec?
I don't particularly mind.
Whoa, they're heavy.
Don't yer shoulders get sore?
They do.
Why do ya think
Haine turned out the way she did?
When the two of ya were hangin' out, she seemed human.
Like a regular, cute little girl.
Well.
It was due to my own foolishness.
I shouldn't have gotten involved just to sate my curiosity.
I think this body of mine was born from Haine.
The moment Ryuunosuke was killed, a section of her split off. That was me.
I'm scared.
Won't I eventually go crazy like her?
Don't worry.
If that happens, I'll kill you myself.
Mio.
Oh, it's just me.
Whaddya want?
How very cold.
But I get it.
I hate myself after all, don't I?
Wh-What are you...
My shallow nose, my stubby fingers,
my hairiness,
my sweatiness.
Stop...
I hate it all.
Because I'm the complete opposite of Sis.
But it doesn't stop at just looks.
My grades, my personality...
I said stop it!
You're Sis's real shadow.
How long do ya think ya can keep this up?
At least tell Shin how you feel.
If ya don't hurry up, I'll do it for ya.
Ya can't!
Ya just can't.
These are your mother's ashes.
I couldn't allow her to end up as food for Haine.
She passed on January 3, 2013.
Cause of death was heart failure.
So that stuff about finding a donor was all a lie?
She was dead way before the day of the surgery?
Ya should've told us something so important.
The Hishigatas have been involved with the Shadows for 300 years.
This secret, too, was part and parcel.
But there was only one successor.
It was passed on only to me, not my father nor my brothers.
I thought it would be too much for you to bear.
Sou.
Human life is valuable to you, isn't it?
Yer damn right it is!
That's exactly why I thought it impossible.
I'm sorry.
If yer gonna apologize to someone, do it to Tokiko.
It's weird.
I can't really think of Dr. Hishigata as a bad guy.
He was just forced into this situation trying to save the people he loves, right?
I dunno if I could do that if I were in the same position.
But as a result,
he helped bring about the revival ritual—that mass murder.
Once the sacrifices are turned into Shadows,
they lose their memory of being killed.
No one would be the wiser.
Yer dad's plan seemed to go further beyond that, though.
Yes.
Ushio is Ushio even as a Shadow.
And Chitose still acted like Chitose.
I really don't think I could do it.
You're very kind.
Shinpei.
When was the last time ya slept?
Yer mind's been conscious through all of the loops, right?
Ya've got huge bags under yer eyes.
Ya have a point.
I think I've been awake a long time.
See? Don't push yourself too hard.
Right.
Everyone's here, so at least get some sleep tonight.
Toki is right.
This might be my last chance to catch some shut-eye.
Hishigata Clinic
Thanks.
Where do ya think yer goin'?
Ushio, eh?
It's dangerous to go alone.
I told y'all to tell me if yer goin' to the bathroom.
Let me go home.
Go home? Alone?!
Absolutely not! What're ya think—
Keep it down!
Did ya forget something?
Somethin' like that.
And ya won't change yer mind?
Well...
Then why don't I come with ya?
If ya insist, then let's compromise.
Fine, then.
Come along.
Nezu
I'll be right back.
Wait out here.
Who told ya to waltz right in?!
I came in because I sensed a Shadow.
Don't worry.
It can't move.
I'm home.
Is... Is it your...
Yeah.
It's a Shadow of my wife.
It was just two months ago.
She went out to the farm by herself and came back as a Shadow.
There was a bright flash of light, and it suddenly came back to me.
The day Ryuunosuke was killed 14 years ago.
It tried to copy me, but I had immunity.
What's going on?
It's acting weird.
This has never happened before.
It's the same telepathy Haine did to drive Chitose crazy.
She also sent it to your wife's Shadow.
I see.
Nezu, wait!
Sorry, but can ya leave us alone?
Hold on a sec!
If I hack her, I may be able to bring her back to the way she was before!
Even if it works, it'll still be a Shadow.
And it's different from you or Hishigata.
It killed my wife and transformed.
It's my wife's enemy, isn't it?
But!
I just couldn't bring myself to kill it.
I was all about wiping out the Shadows.
But I've let my biggest enemy live for too long.
I don't need any more time.
Please let me have some closure.
Please.
Sorry, Kaoru.
I'll follow ya soon.
I'd expect no less from you, Negoro.
You gave the perfect treatment.
Summer Time Rendering
Hishigata Clinic
The long night has broken.
It's morning.
Hey, man, you okay?
You were totally zonked out.
Present
Limit
Thank goodness.
The edge of time that had been drawing closer is farther away now.
Now I have a bit of leeway with the number of loops left.
And yet, the pain in the back of my eye hasn't gone away yet.
My headache's gotten worse too.
Is everyone else safe?
Oh, right!
Mornin'.
M-Morning.
All of us safely made it to the morning of the 23rd.
Today, the 23rd, will be the day of the hunt.
With the big battle coming, we're going to try and thin the Shadows' numbers as much as possible before tomorrow.
First, there's the Shadows that Miss Nagumo spotted at the funeral.
Team Nagumo's target were the Kogaitos.
The rest of us on Team Ushio were to investigate the Hitobuchis.
Bistro Kofune
Before that, Team Ushio stopped at Kofune's for a bit.
Alan was preparing to open the restaurant.
We were sure he'd be mad when we came home.
But he wasn't. He simply said "Welcome back" gently.
We relieved Ros and Guil of their post and let them return to Toki after watching Kofune's all night.
Mio will help Alan with the restaurant.
Shadow Mio will be left behind as a bodyguard.
And I also had Sou stay at Kofune's as well.
So it's just gonna be the two of ya today?
Huh? Oh, I guess.
Lucky.
Right, Mio?
Huh?!
I've got Sou, so I'm fine.
Right?
Y-Yeah.
Sis and Shin, be careful.
And take this.
They're strands of yer hair from yer real body.
Whuzzat for?
Oh, I get it!
I gathered them up from the bathroom and yer room.
These have yer original's data, right?
It's only a few strands, but maybe it can be like a small healing potion?
Mio!
Yer a genius!
Hair regenerated!
Okay, time to go.
Ready!
Sou, look after Mio.
Leave it to me.
And don't y'all die, either!
Shin.
I have something to talk about later.
So swear you'll come back safely.
Sure.
Call right away if anything happens.
Okay.
Hitobuchi
I don't sense 'em.
They ain't here no more.
It's just like Miss Nagumo said.
The Hitobuchis were all killed.
One of the Shadows Miss Nagumo discovered at the funeral was Hitobuchi Kanae, my old teacher.
We called her Bucchi.
Naturally, I, Ushio, and even Miss Nagumo were taught by her.
She taught every kid who grew up on this island.
There she is!
Hey, check it out!
She's got blonde hair!
And her eyes are blue!
Weird!
A foreigner! She's a foreigner!
Foreigner! Foreigner!
Hey!
Die!
Ushio!
Get back here!
Hey!
Whaddya think yer doing?!
Bucchi!
Nurse's Office
It ain't my fault.
I didn't do nothin' wrong.
Right, ya didn't.
Must be tough.
It ain't.
All those twerps can do is bully the weak.
'Cause they're weak too.
But I ain't weak.
I was just teachin' them a lesson.
Ya certainly are strong, Ushio.
But violence ain't the answer.
Those who are truly strong don't hurt others.
What the heck? That makes no sense.
Yer hands weren't made to hurt others.
They're for holding others' hands,
for stroking their head,
and for holding them tight.
Ya want me to hold hands with 'em?
Heck no!
Shinpei.
Y-Yes?
Please continue to look out for Ushio.
I'm counting on ya.
I will.
Next time, before ya clench yer fist,
I want ya to think a bit.
I can't make that promise.
I always hit back.
You do.
And that honest side of yours is what I love so much about ya!
Bucchi...
She was so kind.
Yeah.
But she was scary when she got angry.
Only we can avenge her.
We followed the presence of Shadows to the depths of the forest in Mt. Takanosu.
Well, sense any nearby?
Yeah, we're getting closer.
Still, be careful.
They're probably onto me by now.
Yeah, I know.
Are ya nervous, Shinpei?
Well, yeah, it's just us two.
Don't worry, ya got me!
Just be all aloof and objective like usual.
Shinpei, get on!
Get back!
Stay back!
My, aren't we raring to go, Hamaji.
You'll make a fine meal.
Ushio?!
I missed one!
Shinpei, it's behind the kids!
Ya sure grew up, Shinpei.
Have ya been well?
I have, Miss Hitobuchi.
So, basically, there's a battle between good and bad Shadows.
And yer a good Shadow, Ushio?
Yup! Totally correct, Toudai!
Don't worry.
We'll take out all the bad Shadows, okay?
Right, Shinpei?
Precisely!
How long are ya gonna be up there?
I-I can't get down!
You're the one who put me up here!
Shinpei's whipped.
Yeah, it's like they're married!
It ain't like that!
Listen, we're on a top-secret mission.
Ya can't tell any adults, got it?
Sir, yes, sir!
That's pretty cool!
I couldn't bring myself to tell them that the real Bucchi is dead.
That's fine.
There's no need to scare them.
I wonder if they'll keep quiet about the Shadows.
Don't worry. No one'll believe 'em anyway.
Shinpei, there's blood.
And it's still fresh.
Must've been Bucchi's doing.
34 years old, female, not an islander.
She's from Osaka, so maybe a tourist?
From what I can tell, there's no human-shaped stain.
This tourist must've been taken away.
Damn it!
Haine is consuming more people than normal to heal her wounds from yesterday.
The fool.
She'll never heal by eating others.
Kobayakawa Shiori and Haine no longer exist.
Their original bodies are gone.
Ushio?
Huh?
Did I say something just now?
Hold on.
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
It's Miss Nagumo.
Let's meet up with the others, like planned.
We can leave the kids at Kofune's.
That'll be the safest.
The teams met back up and updated each other.
Getting down to brass tacks, we took down the Shadows of Miss Hitobuchi and the two kids.
Meanwhile, only stains were left at the Kogaitos'.
The team was unable to find any Shadows.
After that, Totsumura led an investigation of the houses of the Shadows we defeated at the gym.
They'd told their neighbors they were going on vacation,
so their absence wasn't suspicious to them.
For the Kobayakawas, apparently people think that
Shiori is resting in Kainan, and Asako is visiting her brother.
By the way, I called her brother and he said that wasn't true.
During the first loop, yer Shadow said they ran away during the night to escape debt.
Debt?!
These excuses mean even if we erase their Shadows,
no one will raise a fuss.
It must be to ensure the festival goes off without a hitch tomorrow.
They don't seem to be readying to attack us.
Perhaps they're afraid of being hacked by Ushio.
Damn cowards.
They're probably hiding out till the big night.
So their biggest priority is the festival, huh?
Maybe if we could stop it somehow...
To do that,
we'll need to go see him.
Thinking back on it, from the very start, I was trying to meet with him.
This is the place where I was first killed.
Hiruko, where everything began.
Hello.
Well, hello there.
I need to speak with you, Karikiri.
Do you have some time?
Yes, that's just fine.
But let's have a seat first.
Come inside.
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time
Face-to-Face