Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
We've not seen each other
for a long time. It's Layla.
Did you see the legendary great
maneuver that I did with Sora?
I bet everything on that show.
Both my own fate and my
bond with my best partner.
I can no longer appear on
Kaleido Stage, but I have no regrets.
Because I found a new dream.
Sora, follow me.
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa
aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Wow, we've got a vacation! A whole week too!
It's all thanks to regular maintenance.
I'm gonna take this chance to really
make the rounds of the comedy theatres!
I'll plan new productions
like crazy at the library.
I'm going to spend day and
night on special trapeze training.
Sora, would you mind joining me...
Everyone's so motivated.
You will be Mina Murray.
Yes.
If I stay like this, I can
never be a real Kaleido Star.
Is something wrong?
What? Oh...
It's nothing. It's nothing. It's nothing.
Sora, when you've changed your clothes,
go to the Boss's office right away.
He has a surprise for you.
What?
Somehow... I have a bad feeling about this.
I think it's a conditioned reflex.
I remember there was that time
you had to work during your time off.
Just in case, you should go there
expecting the worst case scenario.
The shock will be less that way.
Go for it, Sora!
Okay.
What?
I'm going to make a guest
appearance on stage with Miss Layla?!
It seems Layla's recommended you.
But if you don't like it, do you
want to me to decline the offer?
Of course I'm going!
I'll go to the North Pole,
the South Pole, anywhere!
Sora's going to appear
on stage with Miss Layla?
I'm going to see Miss Layla.
Miss Layla...
"The Ever Amazing Miss Layla."
Well... Please take me to off-Broadway.
Follow that car.
Miss Layla...
Sora!
It's been a long time, hasn't it, Sora?
Miss Layla!
Sora?
Sora!
Charlotte... Julie?
We're working as Miss Layla's
personal assistants now.
Sora, you, like, haven't changed at all.
This is Sora Naegino from Kaleido Stage.
This is the producer, Mike Abbott.
Welcome.
I look forward to working
with you for the next week.
under your supervision.
And this is the writer and the
director of this show, Cathy Taymor.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Okay...
I guess I don't need to alter costumes.
Layla fired the previous performer, you see.
Fired?
She was a professional
performer with a decent career,
but it seems Layla didn't like her.
In the middle of the season, without
consulting the producer or the director!
Is that the kind of thing people normally do?
Well...
No! Normally they don't!
I just don't want to appear on stage
with someone who doesn't have any zeal.
This is why I don't like spoiled rich girls.
Her schedule happened
to be open, so we're okay,
but what were you going to do
--if we couldn't find a replacement?
--Oh... well... er...
Thank you for coming, Sora.
Oh, you're welcome.
But I can't be away
from Kaleido Stage for more than a week.
That's enough.
We'll figure the rest out, so don't worry.
Right.
You're only going to appear in one scene,
but it's a very important scene.
That scene is Salome's dance,
which will be in the latter half of the show.
Yes.
Anger and sorrow.
Love and hate.
All of Salome's passion
is poured into that scene.
I want you to fire up the scene with an acrobatic
performance as a shadow of my character,
and raise the temperature of the stage.
Raise the temperature of the stage?
Once we've set up the
rough outline of how it will go,
how you want to perform is all up to you.
In other words, do it ad lib.
Ad lib?!
Let's run through the basic outline.
Yes.
Please wait!
That voice is...
May!
Who are you?
I'm May Wong.
I was inspired by you,
and joined Kaleido Stage this year
with the top score for new entrants.
May, why?
Please accept this.
Thank you.
So you're the newcomer who's playing
the leading role in the new production.
Yes. I'm more talented than Sora.
Instead of Sora, please
let me be in the show!
What?!
Rolling Flower!
May found out that I was
invited by Miss Layla
and came to New York planning to do this?
Shining Flower!
Miracle Great!
Stop, May! Stop it!
What!
I'm the one who was invited by Miss Layla!
Get off this stage right now!
Miss Layla invited you
because she didn't know about me.
It's like, "A super powerful
newcomer appears."
Sora, like, doesn't seem like she can win.
This is interesting.
Why don't we put them both on, Layla?
Those were my thoughts exactly.
Then, let's start rehearsal.
Yeah. I want to put in an
emergency order for another costume.
What do you think?
I think maybe I want one more
idea in there to make it fly...
Well, let's put that in tomorrow.
I'll take you to the hotel, then.
I booked a room at the
Century Hotel, which is close to here.
Please don't tell me that you're going
to put me in the same room with Sora!
Uh... Yeah...
I refuse!
May, don't be so selfish!
I'd rather sleep outside
than stay in a room with you!
Me too! Who wants to
be with someone like you?!
Quit your whining!
Save that energy for tomorrow's show!
Uh... yes, ma'am.
Say, if the two of you don't mind, why not cancel
your hotel reservation and come to my place?
Here we are.
Wow...
Amazing...
That's New York for you.
Beautiful.
I'll try to make coffee now.
So make yourselves at home.
"Try to make"?
Miss Layla, that's where you put the water.
And the coffee beans should be ground first.
Really? Sorry.
You seldom drink coffee...
Having you really helps me out.
Oh, I'm honored to be of use to you, Miss!
Miss Layla's already
started her new life here.
I guess the legendary great
maneuver is already part of her past.
This is interesting.
Why don't we put them both on, Layla?
Those were my thoughts exactly.
I'm not the only one she has hopes for.
Would you quit moping already?
Moping?
Now that we know both
of us will be in the show,
if you don't pull yourself together,
Miss Layla will be the one who's embarrassed.
I had so many things I wanted to talk with
Miss Layla about. I haven't seen her for so long.
But, because of you...
Miss Layla isn't yours.
I also want to talk with Miss Layla.
It was my dream to
appear on the stage with her.
I came here to have Miss Layla
recognize me as better than you.
You're the one who injured Miss Layla...
You alone I won't lose to!
Wait a second.
Did you say that Sora injured me?
If you hadn't paired with Sora to
perform the legendary great maneuver,
I'm sure you never would have been injured!
Why don't you two have a seat?
I hurt myself because my mind
wasn't fully where it needed to be.
I still ventured to do the
legendary great maneuver
even if it meant smashing my shoulder.
I did it of my own will.
So it's wrong to put the
blame on Sora for that.
I can no longer do that kind of performance,
but thanks to my injuries,
I think I have new opportunities.
But, if you hadn't injured your shoulder,
right now you would be in
an even larger-scale show...
I chose that show.
After I performed the
legendary great maneuver,
when people heard that I would
not go back to Kaleido Stage anymore,
I got a lot of job offers to be
in movies, plays, and TV shows.
But, after having accomplished
the legendary great maneuver,
none of them appealed to me.
And then...
You have a guest.
Okay, now...
Here you go. A script.
So how's the injury? When will it be healed?
To recover to the point
where I can live a normal life,
it will take about a month, maybe.
It'd be great if you could
recover faster than that,
but I guess there's nothing you can do.
Why don't we do this together?
You won't regret it.
"Salome in Vegas"...
Everything about it was fresh.
There were some people who
murmured that I'd come down in the world
because I appeared off-Broadway in
a show that wasn't even all that big.
But that didn't bother me at all.
Because there was something
there that motivated me again.
I thought, "This is my new stage."
And Cathy is my new partner.
Your new partner...
That's right.
Miss Layla, I will do my best.
So that I'll also be considered your partner.
It was my dream to be able to appear
on the same stage with you, Miss Layla.
What is your dream after that?
What?
After that?
After all, your current
dream will come true tomorrow.
Oh... well... er...
I beat Sora and... No...
So, Miss Layla's current dream is here, huh?
Sora...
That's right.
I went and brewed coffee for
both of you, and you didn't...
It's bitter.
And Cathy is my new partner.
I'm no longer Miss Layla's partner.
I know that.
We're walking down different
paths, so that's natural.
I know that, but...
I never expected to hear it so clearly,
straight out of Miss Layla's mouth like that.
I never expected to feel so lonely
just hearing one word from Miss Layla.
In the end, I can't stand on my own at all.
It's pathetic...
This is not good.
I won't be able to perform
tomorrow the way I feel now.
I have to pull myself together.
Layla's constellation, Leo,
which emits a blindingly bright light.
And standing motionless in
its shadow, Sora's Sagittarius,
who's lost sight of the target
it should be aiming its arrows at.
Anyway, don't worry about anything.
Just perform the way you feel like doing.
Yes.
Stop looking at me with puppy eyes.
Get on the stage with enough spirit
to steal the part of Salome from me.
Salome, please dance for me.
I don't want to dance right now, Herron.
My heart might be the only
thing in this country
that doesn't always do as you please.
Salome...
Johann, your skin is as
white as new fallen snow.
And your lips are...
Salome, don't touch me!
Johann!
Johann...
I love you.
Get on the stage with enough spirit
to steal the part of Salome from me.
Stand by!
Herron, I will dance for you.
In return, I want you to grant my wish.
Now the match begins, you two.
Attract the audience's eyes. Upstage me.
In order to meet Miss Layla's expectations...
I have to do a performance
which exceeds Miss Layla's.
Miss Layla!
I want to be acknowledged.
I will not beaten by May.
I will not beaten by Sora.
I'm going to win no matter what!
I will make sure I win.
Looking good.
But...
I cannot beat Miss Layla.
Ask me for anything you want, Salome.
There's only one thing I want.
So, this is all right with you?
Yes.
Miss Layla's shining
supremely on this stage too.
But still...
I can't catch up with her at all.
We couldn't match Miss Layla.
I know.
Thank you very much for this week.
Thanks to you, I was able
to create a satisfying show.
Really?
Really.
Thanks to you,
Cathy understood what I meant when I said
we didn't have enough temperature on stage.
Then that's why you invited me here?
Yes.
I thought I could show her what a
heated stage was really like if I was with you.
But, Sora...
Back when I was still at Kaleido Stage,
I was afraid that you would
overtake me from behind.
But I wasn't able to feel
that edge from you this time.
When you're having a hard time,
you're the only person who can save yourself.
What you're aiming at,
what you want to grasp,
the only person who knows
those things is you.
All the answers are inside you.
My current dream is on this stage.
But, the dream I told you about on that day
is also my important dream.
Please be my dream, Sora.
I know you can become a true Kaleido Star.
Miss Layla...
Keep going after your
dream without being lost.
If you do that, I'm sure the road to
being a real Kaleido Star will open for you.
Going after my dream...
That's right.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Please say hello to
everyone at Kaleido Stage.
--Yes.
--Yes! Don't worry. I'll take care of it for you!
I still can see Fool?
I'll admit that I misunderstood
you about Miss Layla.
But it doesn't mean I'm
giving up competing with you.
Yeah, I know.
I wonder what I want to do now.
The answer is inside of me...
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (Here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
I don't want to see Dad
looking sad like that.
And so, we decided to do a
Kids' Stage for the children.
Wow, Marion is really good at the trampoline!
I'm not doing the trampoline.
Are you going to bury your dream
along with your mother's memories?
I want to bring the smile back to
Marion's face. I want to! I want to!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Marion's Amazing Debut."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...