[heavy metal music playing]
EXPELLED FROM PARADISE
[narrator] In the aftermath
of the carnage,
Ares attempted to make sense
of the phenomenon he had just witnessed.
I'm not proud to say this,
so allow me to be direct.
Not to sound arrogant,
but I am the god of war.
I've seen my fair share of fights.
When it comes to moves like the Meteor Jab
or the Divine Axe,
they're so swift that lesser gods
fail to glimpse even a shadow of the fray.
That was hardly an issue for me,
of course.
I saw them.
Except...
All right.
Let's see if you can copy this one.
Brace yourself!
I was alert.
Understand?
On the blessed names of the gods,
my gaze never strayed once.
Not even for a slight
fraction of a second.
But in one moment,
I saw my father
shape his hand into a fist,
and in the next instant, it was all over.
Before I knew it,
his skull was facing
in the wrong direction.
Huh? Huh!? What in the realm is going on?
The lord of the heavens,
the creator of the universe,
the indomitable Zeus
has crumpled to the ground!
Wait. But, how?
This turn of events, it's unprecedented.
I don't understand what happened.
What is the meaning of this madness?
I was looking right at them,
but I didn't see anything.
How interesting.
The human's powers are impressive.
Perhaps his strength is more formidable
than we initially thought.
Uh...
It went like this.
Master Zeus closed in
to perform his final attack.
Still, Adam was undeterred.
He replicated those movements
at the same time.
[shimmering]
He managed to dodge
the oncoming blow by a whisker.
Like so.
[slamming]
Then he threw his own punch.
Wait a second.
Are you saying
you're able to see everything?
In spite of the fact that I,
the god of war,
could not perceive what you described?
What? No. It's merely a casual hypothesis,
and nothing more, dear brother.
Huh?
[grumbling]
[Ares] In any case,
I was none the wiser about what had
transpired before my very eyes.
And yet, I was unshakably
certain about one thing at least.
In the end,
even if I were to train for 1,000 years,
I would never outpace Adam.
You can't say I didn't warn you.
I told you you'd regret this, right?
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my goodness, folks!
I can hardly believe it,
but as you can see...
the mighty boss god is down!
Down for the count!
We are witnessing the first true miracle
since the birth of the cosmos!
[humans cheering wildly]
[crows cawing]
Well, not too bad.
The boy has some talent.
What are you doing, old man?
Quit messing around and get up!
He's amazing.
That human is way too strong.
I get that his special power is
the ability to mimic the god's attacks,
but being able to surpass them
is on a whole other level.
Like, what is this Adam guy made of
that makes him so unbreakable?
Didn't I tell you already?
The source of that man's strength lies in
his relentless will and firm conviction.
- That's why he's strong?
- Oh yes.
He loathes the gods with all his heart.
He hates them?
[birds chirping]
[calming Gregorian chant playing]
[Brünnhilde] Once upon a time, ages ago,
Adam lived his days
in the paradise of Eden,
among the animals.
He enjoyed a life of comfort
basking in the endless bounty of nature.
But these days would soon end.
[gavel hammering]
[woman] No, it isn't true!
I swear to the gods, I didn't do it.
Please believe me.
I never partook
from the Tree of Knowledge.
EVE
ADAM'S WIFE
Objection! I witnessed
her doing it right in front of me.
I watched you sink your teeth
into that forbidden fruit myself!
THE SERPENT
That's not true!
[laughing]
[Brünnhilde] The truth
was far more sinister.
[Eve struggling] No!
I'm telling you to stop!
- [Serpent laughing]
- Someone help me!
I'm afraid that
no one's coming to save you.
- [crying]
- Quit struggling.
Adam!
[Serpent laughing]
[pecking]
[grunting]
[growling]
[grumbling]
You simpering whore!
[Brünnhilde] The Serpent had tried
to take the woman for himself,
but Eve remained true to her beloved Adam,
and his test of faith only met resentment.
How dare you try to make a fool out of me.
Learn the consequences
of messing with the wrong deity!
You want proof of her wrongdoing?
I have the very apple she bit into!
- [gasping]
-[Brünnhilde] The accusations were false!
However, everyone was a god,
from the prosecutor, to the judge,
and the whole jury.
The gods had complete
autonomy over paradise,
making the likelihood of a guilty verdict
99.99999%.
[all clamoring]
Eve was sentenced to banishment.
The gates to paradise were closed shut.
[crying]
No, this is unbearable.
My dear husband...
This means I won't be able
to see my beloved Adam ever again.
[sobbing]
[Serpent] Since you refuse to submit to
me, there's simply no place for you here.
Have fun fending for yourself in
the outside world, you disgraceful harlot.
[laughing]
- [creaking]
- Huh?
[crowd murmuring]
Why are you interrupting?
Can't you see court's still in session?
- [all gasping]
- [male god 1] He fell flat on his face!
Uh, what is the meaning of this?
[crowd gasping]
Adam, you're here!
[gods murmuring]
[male god 1] He's coming in here
with some fruit. Why?
- [male god 2] Wait, are those...
- [male god 3] Those are the apples!
Don't tell me he's harvested
every last one!
Deplorable crime.
Each one he's picked represents a sin!
[Serpent] Trespasser,
why have you disturbed us?
You came for me.
Be aware,
this is a holy place of judgment.
The likes of you are not welcome here.
[crunching]
[all gasping]
This brute actually ate it!
So sour.
[exclaiming in horror]
What? He just spit it out?
[spitting]
[all murmuring]
[crunching and spitting continues]
Ahhh...
Now you listen, boy.
I won't allow you to come in here
and make a mockery of this court.
Hey.
Ah.
If you're going someplace else,
I'll go with you.
- Oh, Adam!
- Uh... Whoop.
Thank you.
What's with the waterworks, Eve?
Why'd you start crying all of the sudden?
Ah! Fools, you think this is a joke,
or a fairy tale?
[both] Huh?
[straining]
[growling]
If you thought you could disrespect
the gods, then you're mistaken.
You won't get your happy ending!
You know, some little birds
told me about everything you did.
They said that you made Eve start crying.
What does it matter, you filthy worm?
I'll slice you into pieces,
and send both of you brats back to dust.
DIVINE REFLECTION
EMULATION
[gasping]
[cackling]
Yes, that's right. I'll chop you up.
Wait!
Ah... Ah! Ah!
[screaming]
[crashing]
[coughing]
Just save it.
Your trouble-making days are over.
[exclaiming in shock]
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry for making you do this.
Good thing I was doing it for us.
You charmer.
Are you ready to get out of here?
'Cause I'm ready to start over.
Let's build a brand new Eden of our own.
[Brünnhilde] Thus, Adam left the heavens
for an earthly life with Eve.
And they lived happily ever after.
[humans celebrating]
[woman] Great job, sweetie!
I knew you could do it.
Congratulations, darling!
Beautiful! A second Renaissance!
See that, Mom? Dad is totally
cleaning up out there, isn't he?
- He sure is.
- [giggling]
He actually KO'd a god!
[Heimdall] With this,
revenge has been served.
Adam has finally turned the pain
of his exile back against the creators.
He's rubbing it in their faces.
We did lose the last fight,
but now we're even again!
Ragnarok round two is a complete victory!
Honestly, I felt nervous when Zeus
chose to barge in uninvited.
But he was the perfect opponent.
All's well that ends well.
Whatever.
I'm just happy that the human
found a strategy to hang
that old geezer out to dry!
It's too good!
Oh no, I can't hold it in!
- [laughing hysterically]
- Ah!
- Amazing work!
- Get him, Adam. That's right.
They'll regret ever wanting to ban you
from paradise in the first place.
[humans cheering]
[Heimdall] Okay,
it's time to call this fight.
Round two of Ragnarok
winds down to an official end.
And our winner is, Adam,
the father of human--
Hm?
[gasping]
[Heimdall straining]
Sorry, I'm not done.
[gasping]
[Heimdall struggling]
[Zeus straining]
[cracking]
He just twisted it back!
[gods cheering]
Looks like father caught his second wind.
I knew my old man
had some fight left in him.
- There's still cause for concern.
- Huh?
He took quite a beating.
[panting]
Come on, gramps. You shouldn't
be pushing yourself this hard.
I understand now.
I'm beginning to realize that all that
big talk wasn't just for show.
I'm getting a better idea
of what's beneath the leaf.
But there's still one thing
that this withered noggin
of mine can't make sense of.
They say no one hates us more than you do.
When I look at you, I don't see
even a single ounce of resentment.
So if you'd be so kind to indulge me.
What's the reason you want to
go toe-to-toe against the gods?
[sighing]
Everybody's always
asking me that question.
And it seems now you are too.
Is it hatred?
Or revenge?
Why does it matter?
That's irrelevant.
Is there any man alive who needs a reason...
to protect his very own children?
[uplifting Gregorian chant music playing]
Well said.
Always with the mushy stuff.
You can say that again.
[narrator] Upon hearing this,
humanity trembled.
The children of Adam,
awestruck by the compassion
of their father's benevolent words,
felt a shiver of emotion.
Without any prompt,
the people began to take action.
And for the first time in history,
the entire human race united as one.
They prayed for humanity.
They prayed for victory for their father.
Uh, it appears that mankind has
spontaneously achieved consensus!
[scoffing] Feels like it should
have been me fighting out there.
In spite of my better judgment,
I believe the young man is growing on me.
[crying] What a hero! That naked guy
is so cool I can barely stand it!
It appears I underestimated
the quality of his moral character.
He really is the paragon of mankind.
My, you've charmed the whole arena.
What an inspiring spectacle. [chuckling]
Nice work, pretty boy.
[sighing]
It would have been better for you
if you'd stayed on the ground.
Careful, this next one will kill you.
[chuckling]
I can tell you aren't bluffing
by the sound of it.
Though it pains me to say it,
I admit you're a tough contender.
- If you want to surrender, then maybe--
- I didn't say I was finished.
I thought I could do away with you
using the usual technique.
But that was rather naive of me.
I didn't want to resort to this
since it's so draining,
but I'm left with no other choice!
[Hermes sighing]
It's my only option.
[yelling]
[gasping]
[screaming in pain]
What's going on?
Master Zeus is contorting his body.
- He's all flesh.
- Disgusting.
What is he doing?
My, he's so repulsive.
Well, well, what do we have here?
What's he trying to accomplish?
I say the so-called maker of the universe
has gone senile.
[male god] You two have it twisted.
Huh?
[ravens cawing]
I should devour you birdbrains whole!
- Unhand me, you maniac.
- Please, have mercy.
Didn't I warn you?
Don't ever transform into my son again.
[laughing] Hey, I was joking.
There's nothing wrong with a little prank.
Oh, my bad. I forgot.
You don't have a sense of humor.
[screaming] Who are you?
I respect you too much to ever
eat your precious pet birds, Uncle Odin.
LOKI
GOD OF DECEIT
Hmm.
The first time I've seen him
go beast-mode in, like, a billion years.
It's a bona fide spectacle
on the rare occasion he does it.
That human's making me turn
green with envy.
All of it's totally unfair.
Huh? In what way?
I'll say this. It's extremely difficult
getting the old man to fight for real.
Thinking about it makes me so jealous,
I could...
[screaming]
[exhaling deeply]
Hmm.
He looks different. Something's happening.
Master Zeus, he's transforming.
[ominous music playing]
What a sight. He's writhing
in agony while reshaping himself.
[shuddering]
[moaning]
[screaming]
[gasping]
Is that Master Zeus?
- [gods murmuring]
- [male god] Zeus?
[woman] What is that monstrosity?
[Göll] Wait, what's happening?
Why are my hands trembling?
I can't seem to stop it.
It feels so weird.
Why do I-- Ah!
I'm not sure either.
It might be our instincts kicking in.
- Or something.
- Instincts?
It's the gut feeling you get,
when you're in unspeakable danger.
Mm-hm. I've never seen
anything more beautiful.
The glory of grandfather's ultimate form.
ADAMAS
[giggling]
[Japanese pop ballad playing]