Yurika!
Why... Why are you doing this!?
You all are trying to protect
too many things at once.
That's why you can't protect anything.
I won't let you lay another finger on Yurika.
That's if you can win.
Then I'll do just that.
I will win!
That white magic again?
Koutarou-sama.
Sakuraba-senpai!?
E-Even Sakuraba Harumi can use magic?
This is your sword.
I understand.
I wish you luck.
Sakuraba-senpai!
Looks like she's okay!
I'm surprised.
So that's your true power?
I'm surprised too.
You're like a freak of nature.
But I can at least test
that power of yours!
Double Cast!
Force Field! Thunder Lance!
What!?
What power!
At this rate...
Quick Cast! Fog Cloud!
Modifier: effective area colossal!
Yurika!
How dare you, Satomi Koutarou!
In order to defeat him, I'll have to
get the power residing in room 106.
dare no koto o kangaeteru no
Who is it that you're thinking of?
haato no supeesu soudatsusen
It's a game for a space in your heart!
senkyouteki ni isshin ittai de
It's an advancing and retreating invasion
yudan naranai na
I still can't let my guard down
a
no
ano ne ima no koto
ne
You see, right now,
honno suu paasento shika
I only have a few percent
aitsu no kokoro ni
tsu
of the space
ibasho ga nainda
in his heart
true
intentions
peek
out
seifuku no poketto
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
true
intentions
out
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
peek
out
My
from
my
uniform's
pocket
honne o shinobasete
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
pocket
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
I
calmly fix
my collar
sotto eri o tadasu
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
my c
calmly fix
Simply revealing all the tricks up my sleeve
sonna kantan ni wa
te no uchi akasenai
would be no good
So I guess I'll just have to wait and see
akumade mada yousumi no dankai
dakedo hontou wa ne
But you see, the truth is
miyabutte hoshii no
I want you to realize it
awai kitai ni mune tokimekashite
My heart throbs from this bubbly expectation
chirachira to miteru
I shyly take a glance at you
onna no ko no daiji na mono
What girls value as important
i
ijiwaru de
a bit mean
ji
wa
ru
de
otoko no ko no daiji na koto
and what guys value as important
mukatsuku
mu
and annoying
ka
tsu
ku
hiku ni hikenai sorezore no jijou
tug back and forth with each other
hoka ni nani mo kangaerannai
My mind stutters, I can't think at all
ma
massugu de
so direct
s
su
gu
de
isshun datte yosomi dekinai
I can't take my eyes off you for a second
ni
nibui ne
yet so dull
bu
i
ne
juujitsukan afureru hodo ni
I'll fill you up with this sense of contentment
mitashite ageru yo
until you can't receive it anymore
jo
u
jouken chiratsukase
ken
Add requirements
yousu ukagatte miteru
See how things go
otagai win-win na
ga
I think we can both win here
i
win-
win
na
to
ri
torihiki shiyou yo
hi
so let's make a deal
ki
shi
yo
u
The Sun and a Rainbow
Huh? I...
Are you awake now?
Koutarou-sama...
Satomi-kun!
Oh, right.
Is Yurika-san okay?
Yurika-san!
Calm down, Sakuraba-senpai.
She's just unconscious.
B-But...
It'll be okay.
Just relax.
Right.
I'm sorry.
So what happened?
I don't remember anything
after Yurika-san was defeated.
You don't remember?
No, not a thing.
I see. I guess that's fine.
Yurika!
Yurika-san!
Satomi-san...
Sakuraba-senpai...
They still haven't come back.
Luckily for them,
fifth period was just study hall.
I guess I'll try to contact them.
I tried to call them,
but they were out of the service area.
If you're worried,
we can go look for them.
I'm not worried at all!
Anyway, I have to go work on the play.
Don't bother me!
The problem is the ending.
It's true that the Silver Princess loved the Blue Knight,
but did the Blue Knight...
They kiss
I imagine if they loved
each other, they'd kiss...
No, no!
The Blue Knight and the
Silver Princess would kiss!
Wh-Why would I kiss someone as ill-mannered as him?
They kiss
B-But...
I have to direct him...
They kiss
S-So that means I just have to...
you know, do like a couple would...
Share one of those breathtaking,
passionate kisses...
Your Highness! What's wrong?
A kiss...
Huh?
Guys, come quick!
Sanae?
I see.
Maki-chan...
Yeah, she got away.
I had Sanae fly to go get everyone.
Wait until-
We don't have time for that.
Yurika-san, you can't push yourself.
I'm fine.
I'm a magical girl who
represents love and courage.
But...
Maki-chan is at room 106, no doubt about it.
We need to head over there.
You can't fight in your condition.
Wait here a bit longer
until you feel better.
But...
I'll fight with you.
But we won't be able to win if you don't get your strength back.
Also, there's something I want to ask.
About your magic, I mean.
I understand.
I see.
That sword was created by controlling some of the magic that's pooled here.
It was strong for how little of it was used.
If I read the magic Satomi Koutarou was using,
and control this energy myself,
I'll be able to gain the advantage.
I had the potential to use magic,
but one day, I was attacked by a beast
that sensed that magic within me.
Magical Girl Nana-san saved me.
She saved your life?
Yes.
I wanted to repay Nana-san
for what she had done.
So I started helping her out.
She wouldn't let me fight alongside her,
but I'd prepare meals
and help her with research.
Nana-san was a Forsarrian,
so she didn't have any citizenship papers.
There was a lot for me to do.
Forsarrian?
The name for magical kingdom residents.
Nana-san was one of the Archwizards for
the Magical Kingdom Forsarria Army,
Rainbow Heart,
and was a genius mage.
If there are other mages around,
why are you fighting, Yurika-san?
Well...
Nana-san lost her magic because of me.
Eight months ago, I was held hostage by
Maki-chan's group, Darkness Rainbow.
Nana-san was badly hurt protecting me
and released all of the magic within herself to defeat Maki-chan and the others.
Once you do that,
you're no longer able to use magic.
But Nana-san did it to protect me.
I see.
So you took her place after that.
Yes.
This costume and this staff
originally belonged to Nana-san.
I have to do what she
was supposed to do.
Yurika-san...
I'm okay now.
Let me go, Satomi-san,
Sakuraba-senpai.
This is troublesome.
I never would've thought I'd see old Forsarrian magic here.
Satomi Koutarou... Just who are you?
He's so warm.
I think I understand how Sanae-chan
feels since she's always back here.
Yurika.
You really are a magical girl, aren't you?
Huh?
I know I said this yesterday,
but I'm surrounded by many types of people, right?
Yeah.
But I thought of you as a normal girl.
Just another normal person like me.
Messing around with everyone from class... Joking around...
I thought we'd go through school together without anything special happening.
It wasn't fair of me to think that.
I think I just wanted you to be a normal classmate of mine.
A normal classmate with a hobby
a little different than everyone else's.
Fighting doesn't suit you.
Satomi-san...
Yurika.
Yes?
I'm sorry for not believing you.
Pretending to be a cosplayer for
these last six months wasn't so bad.
I see.
Hello?
Koutarou!?
Where are you!?
Why'd you leave without saying anything!?
I did it.
I managed to gain control.
This is some serious magic,
even if it's just a small portion.
Now Satomi Koutarou can't
use that crazy magic of his.
I'm going to take him out.
You're here.
You're giving this room back.
You want to fight here?
Wait!
You're pretty good, Satomi Koutarou.
You're not bad yourself, Maki-san!
Mind Flare!
How about this!?
Quick Cast! Force Field!
Not too shabby.
Sonic Impact.
Modifier: Touch Trigger!
Quick Double Cast!
Acceleration! Tiny Memory Flash! Modifier: Touch Trigger!
Watch out for her staff!
If you touch it,
you'll lose your memories for a few seconds!
What was that!?
I can't get close!
Control Plant.
Modifier: Extend Length Four Times!
Yurika!
Now, Satomi-san!
Leave it to me!
Looks like I'll have to use this.
Wh-What's going on?
Surprised?
This is your power.
Satomi-san, run!
Maki-chan is controlling the power from room 106!
You need to hurry!
What!?
It's too late now!
Return to the dust whence you came,
Satomi Koutarou!
Lightning Lance!
Modifier: Change Element Darkness and High Concentration!
This is bad!
You're finished, Satomi Koutarou!
Quick Cast! Anti-Magic Shield!
Modifier: Maximize!
I didn't expect you to live through that.
I'm glad.
S-Satomi-san, run away.
Damn it...
Looks like it's time to say farewell,
Nijino Yurika and...
Satomi Koutarou.
Karama, Koroma!
Right!
What!?
Expand an etheric field in front of us!
Time to show our stuff!
Let's go, Brother!
Damn...
Kiriha-san... Everyone else...
How did you...
I opened a hole in Maki-chan's barrier.
Give it up, Maki-chan.
A bunch of weirdos banding together.
You think you've won because you managed to block that one attack?
I agree.
You can't win a battle without attacking.
Blue Knight.
Fire the ships' high convergence lasers.
Obliterate my enemy.
As you wish, My Princess.
Quick Cast! Force Field!
Modifier: Maximize!
Your Highness, isn't this a bit too much—
I'm punishing her for hurting my knight.
Wh-What's going on?
I can only defend against it by
pouring all the room's magic into this.
Oh? You're still standing?
Well, this is the end.
Blue Knight, attack with the main cannon.
Your Highness!
Koutarou must be in the play with me.
We'll scream at each other and laugh.
The play will be great!
But this girl hurt him!
I won't forgive her!
Yes, but you can't blow away
Corona Apartments along with her!
Say, I wanted to ask you all something.
Y-Yes?
Who did that?
U-Um, it was Maki-chan.
I see.
What—
Who are these people?
It's not just Koutarou Satomi,
but all of them...
Now, are you going to give up?
We won't hold back next time.
Take our advice. Surrender.
Thanks for everything, Twilight Wing.
Sacrifice Twilight Wing!
Pre-cast Spell! Release!
Maki-chan!?
She got away.
Is everybody okay?
Cosplaying again, Yurika?
Huh?
I told you not to go around
the neighborhood like that.
Keep that stuff between you and your club.
Hey, Ruth, when did we get back from school?
I don't know.
I feel like we were in class
until just a second ago.
It feels like time just flew by.
That's weird.
Very weird.
That's not possible.
My roof is broken!
Who did it?
I won't forgive them!
I-It wasn't me!
What?
What!?
I see. Rainbow Yurika has allies?
Yes.
But we need to be most
wary of Satomi Koutarou.
Huh, you in love?
Stop with the bad jokes!
At any rate,
we were able to make progress
on deciphering that room's spell
and got information on the enemy.
You did the best you could,
given that we can't act yet.
Yeah, but I sacrificed Twilight Wing
in exchange for their memories.
I need to make another staff.
And get more information
without attracting attention.
We're counting on you, Maki.
I know.
Satomi Koutarou...
I'll take you down myself.
What is this, Satomi-kun?
A sea urchin.
It's small.
Don't laugh at me.
Why?
That's not nice, Satomi-kun.
Kou's such a kid.
Yeah.
I'm glad.
Sakuraba-senpai was able to
ask Satomi-san on that date.
It feels a bit different from usual too.
But...
Yurika, what's with you lately?
You seem unhappy.
You're sighing too.
I had some people that
I felt finally understood me,
but now they don't all over again.
I see.
That's too bad.
Satomi-san,
what do you think I'd have to do to
get you to believe I'm a magical girl?
Hm... Well...
I don't think you'd have to do anything.
Huh?
Lately, I've been feeling like I don't really care if you're a magical girl or a cosplayer.
What do you mean, "you don't care"?
I keep telling you to believe me!
I do believe you.
That's precisely the reason.
You protected Sakuraba-senpai
and got hurt because of it, right?
I can't really remember when that was.
After I saw that, I stopped caring
whether or not you're really a magical girl.
No matter who you are,
you're a good person who helps other people.
There's not many people who'd throw
away their own life to protect another,
whether they're a magical girl or a cosplayer.
That's why if you say you're a magical girl,
it's enough for me.
You can do things worthy of that name.
Satomi-san...
That's right.
That's why I looked up to Sakuraba-senpai.
Even if I couldn't be like Nana-san,
if I could be a magical girl
like Sakuraba-senpai...
I am a little worried about
having you use magic, though.
It might be better for you to be a cosplayer.
Sun and rainbows suit you better.
You're so mean, Satomi-san.
So who should I consider you from now on?
I'm Nijino Yurika.
Your classmate and someone who stays at your place for free.
akogarete iru no you
I always wanted
anata to sukyandaru
to have a scandal with you
itomenai no kokoro
My heart wants to win you over
ano koyori mo hayaku
before that other girl does
hito wa
Why do people
nande nande
Why, oh, why?
nando
Even though each and every time
kizutsuitemo
I end up feeling hurt
koi ni
It's love
koi ni ochiru
I fall helplessly in love
ikimono nano
Ah, but such is life
marude marude mirukutii
Just like a milk tea
betsubetsu no tokoro de umareta futari
Our hearts lie in separate places
amai amai no mirukutii
Just like this sweet, sweet milk tea
atsu atsu yo ima sugu kyun to nomihoshite
It's steaming hot, so I want you to drink it up in one go
marude marude mirukutii
Just like milk tea
zetsumyou na kaken ga wakaranai no ne
I can't make sense of this breathtaking feeling
torotorokeru mirukutii
It's liquid velvet, just like milk tea
saigo dake chotto dake horori tii tongai
Even though it tastes slightly bitter at the end
No Fear
Hey, Kou, let's play a trading card game!
What's that, Matsudaira-sama?
Well, you battle with them!
Rhinoceros
Beetle Man
No Fear
Rhinoceros
Beetle Man
Look at this, I finally got—
Makkenji never learns, does he?
The Earth Empire vs. The Sun Squad!?
Next Episode