Sho good!
It tastes even more delicious than usual!
Life has a way of doing that! When it treats you well, everything seems that much sharper to the taste buds.
And it really has treated us well as of late!
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Now that the four of them have united their hearts and powers as one,
we've unlocked a new power to call upon!
They're all sho cool!
And we've gathered a ton of Heart Seeds too!
The Great Heart Tree's starting to look really vibrant again!
All thanks to our Precure!
I wonder what I can do to thank Tsubomi, though.
Oh! I wanna thank Ichuki for what she's done too!
Give thanks?
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
I wonder what'd be a nice surprise for Erika...
I really need your help!
Wh-What's wrong?!
I've gotta transform!
On it!
Go, Seed of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
Have the Desert Apostles invaded your house?!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
Marine! Where's the Desert Apostle?!
Desert Apostle?
What?
Huh?!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Now wait just one second!
Huh?
Are you telling me there is no Desert Apostle?!
Then what'd you transform for?!
Well, our Tacts have the power to purify Desertrians, right?
So I figure they'd be able to clean my room for me too!
Clean your room?!
Erika's in Trouble!
Someone Stole Her Marine Tact!
Well, you know, I've been feeling oddly productive lately...
But Mom says if I don't clean up
afterward, I can't have any snacks!
And that's a fate worse than death!
So here goes!
Flowers, glitter bright!
You can't just go using your Tact for chores like that!
Don't be so stingy, jeez!
It's not just a magic wand to solve all your problems with! It exists to save people from the depths of—
Whaaat?!
Aww, come on. It's not that big a deal.
It's not a massager either, you know!
Oh, that a fact?
All that floral power's doing wonders for my fur...
Wait, no!
Floral power doesn't do that!
Anyway, you can tidy your room yourself!
You can do it for me, right, Coffret?
You can clean up your own mess, Erika!
I don't see why I should do it!
Well, we're partners, right?
I'll leave it to you, 'kay?
Erika!
You can't just leave your Tact lying around like that!
I've... I've...
I've had it up to here with this!
I put up with a lot from you,
Erika, but this is the last straw!
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
This is goodbye!
Chypre! I need someone to talk to right now!
Chyp—
We're out here, Coffret!
What're you doing?
Tsubomi and I are planting these bulbs!
I'm glad Chypre's helping out.
It's making light work of it, really.
Thank you so much.
No need to thank me!
Courtesy costs nothing, as they say!
You deserve whatever thanks I can give you.
Well then, thank you for always
being there to help me, Tsubomi!
I bet even if I did clean her room for her, Erika wouldn't bother to thank me!
No way am I gonna help her!
Coffret?
Huh?
Hey there.
Hrm?
Isn't Erika with you?
I-I'm just out for a float on my own, that's all!
Are you going somewhere, Itsuki?
Yeah, I'm participating in a martial arts tournament.
And I'm gonna cheer her on every shtep of the way!
Hooray! Hooray! I-chu-ki!
Show 'em whose bosh, Ichuki!
You're all the support I could ever need, Potpourri!
I'll be shure to cheer you on all the way!
Just make sure that nobody else sees you, okay?
Shure thing!
Hey, Coffret, why don't you...
Huh?
Coffret?
Itsuki manages to juggle everything in her life just fine,
but Erika can't even find time to clean her room!
She's an idle, lazy, slacking layabout!
Who's there?
Sorry. It's just me.
You're all dirty. Look.
Alone, I take it?
Yeah...
There we go. All clean again.
Thank you!
You're very welcome!
Why were you staring at the Heart Pot like that, Yuri?
I suppose I rather consider it a
memento of my time with Cologne.
Sometimes I get lost in it.
You still really care for Cologne, don't you, Yuri?
Of course I do.
Huh?
I'd be fine if Erika was even half as considerate as Yuri is!
Hm?
It wasn't just me, was it?
I wish Erika took after her friends a bit more.
Maybe then she'd actually care about her partner.
Coffret!
Down here!
Rumi! Haruka!
What're you doing?
Not telling!
What?
We're staying firmly here at base today, thank you.
I am planning, thank you very much!
Come back some other time.
Oh? You've been training, have you?
And you think that'll make a difference? You've never been competent before!
What am I watching here, exactly?
Ugh, I feel sweaty just watching this!
Yes, yes, I am watching!
Looks like he got busted.
Must be nice, being able to patch up that easily.
You don't seriously think you can beat them, do you?
We have the Desert Devils if we need troops!
You guys can go take a hike!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
You got me...
Hooray, I won!
I get to be Blossom now, right?
Rumi! Haruka!
Don't go swinging the Tact around too hard, okay?
Thanks, Coffret!
I mean, this is really important to the Precure, isn't it?
It's so cool we got to play with the real thing!
At least you two understand
how important the Tacts are!
Snackies!
What are you doing?!
Rumi, Haruka, you have to get out of here!
R-Right.
You come too, Coffret!
No! I have to get the Tact back!
Snacky!
Give me back that Tact!
This belongs to the Precure, not you!
Get back!
Coffret...
Rumi! Haruka!
Let's do this, Coffret!
Come on, Coffret! We haven't got all day!
O-On it!
Rumi, Haruka! Promise me you won't look!
Okay!
Go, Seed of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
Just Snackies to worry about, huh?
I think I can take these guys, no sweat!
I was so looking forward to my day off, and then you just had to go run off somewhere, Coffret.
Well excuse me!
I don't remember asking you to come look for me, though!
Oh, that's nice! Maybe I won't bother saving you next time!
I don't think you even care about me, Marine!
Where's this coming from?
I want an answer!
Do you care about me or not?!
I could ask you the same thing!
If you weren't so selfish, and demanding, and lazy...
Excuse me?! You're making me sound really awful!
Well you've gotta be pretty awful if
you can't even clean your own room!
And you're pretty awful if you won't even help me!
Coffret.
Fine.
We'll have this conversation after we've dealt with those Snackies!
Marine Shoot!
They don't give up, do they?
Snackies might be weak, but they're tough!
Maybe you should give them more credit!
Fine then!
Marine Impact!
Impact!
They can tape themselves up?
You learn something new every day.
Coffret, let's use the Mirage!
We can't! The Mirage needs all four of you
using it to power the HeartCatch Orchestra!
Wait, really?!
Behind you, Marine!
Huh?
Why are they so heavy?!
Hey, lemme go, dang it!
What?
Isn't that my Tact?!
Only Precure can use the power of the Tacts, you doof!
Isn't he?
Hmph!
I've had enough of this!
Get back here!
Marine...
Taking hostages now? You coward!
Help has arrived!
Nice timing!
Gotcha!
Now you've done it...
How dare you hurt my partner like that?!
I'm gonna make you pay!
Nobody hurts my Coffret.
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
Thanks for saving us!
You were so cool...
Blossom!
Don't I get any thanks?!
Maybe if you hadn't fought with Coffret.
But we don't like people who don't care for their Tacts!
Do we?
Coffret?
Erika was really worried about you, you know?
No matter what you think, she really does care about you an awful lot.
But I think you know that too, deep down.
Erika.
Is there anything you'd like me to do or get for you?
Erika?
Oh, yeah, sure!
You can clean my room and do my homework!
And you can get me...
Clothes!
Accessories!
And new shoes!
I shouldn't've asked.
Just kidding!
I think I'd be fine with...
you just being there for me, Coffret.
Brrr, it's cold.
Sheesh.
Maybe you should remember to wear a coat in the future!
You're so warm!
Like a fluffy little hot water bottle!
I suppose they fight so much because they worry about each other.
Maybe so!
Besides, the cold won't bother you, Erika!
Why not?
You're too daft to notice it!
Hey, you!
Well, see, I figured I must've put the Tact somewhere, so I turned the place over a bit...
You'll help me clean it up though, right?
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
he hehappy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
All this talk of friends, hearts,
and Precure! It's rubbish, all of it!
But once I tap into my true power, I won't have to hear you prattle ever again!
Why're you so adamant about destroying our world?
There's so much kindness and beauty here.
And so many wonders all around!
Not interested!
Don't worry, the HeartCatch Mirage will erase all your bitterness and regret!
HeartCatch Precure:
Farewell, Sasorina...
The Flower of Your Heart is a Desert Bloom!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!