Gosh! Why is Mitsuki so worried
about Madoka Wakamatsu?!
She says she can't let her be
and starts chasing after her,
and she even ends up
getting soaked!
Not only that, she encourages
the disheartened Madoka to sing again!
She's such a simple,
good-natured person.
So, I wonder what's
going to happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Okay, we're going to
decide the groups.
Draw a lot from this box
one person at a time!
Mitsuki, I hope we're
in the same group.
Yeah!
Whoa, my heart's racing!
I'm Group F.
What about you, Mitsuki?
Group F!
We're together!
All right, Mitsuki!
Over here, over here!
Group F is over here!
Emi's with us too?
Looks like it!
Oh...
What about Machida?
Well, actually...
Hey, Group B is over here!
Oh! Me, me!
It's too bad that Machida
isn't in our group.
Yeah... I guess.
But we'll be on the bus—
Are you okay?!
Yeah.
It's nothing new.
I'm fine.
See?
Thank you very much for coming
to the appreciation party
for the success of "Eternal Snow."
With everyone's help, we were able to
get into the top ten this time as well.
Now then, we will have a few words
of greeting from Full Moon.
Thank you for taking
the time to come here today!
Oh, Dr. Wakaoji!
- Shall we go?
- Yes!
You're still going to eat?
Why?
No, it's nothing.
Why don't you eat too, Takuto?
You have to fill up in autumn!
Well, the recording was fun.
I hope we get to record together again.
Yeah.
Thank you for
the wonderful performance.
Next time we're going to have
a secret session in the studio.
You should come, Wakaoji.
Sure.
If you'd like,
why don't you join us?
What?! Is it okay?!
Yes, I'll go!
Oh, I should tell Dr. Wakaoji about
what happened with my throat today.
It'll be late at night,
so we can't invite Full Moon!
She'll be on her school trip anyways.
Umm...
Hmm? What is it?
Oh... Nothing.
Umm... Please look forward to
a souvenir from my school trip, okay?
You don't have to get me anything.
School trip, huh? How nice.
Right in the prime of youth!
What's with you?
You sound like an old man!
You don't have to say it like that!
Oh well! It wouldn't be good to
make him worry over that little cough.
I ate a lot! No more will fit!
Of course!
If you ate as much as you did...
I don't feel good.
Maybe I'll take some stomach medicine!
You shouldn't put anything else
in your stomach.
I wasn't able to tell Dr. Wakaoji
about my throat,
but I don't want to
miss the school trip.
Well, I'll be fine.
This is par for the course.
What're you doing?
Hmm? Oh, it's information
about my school trip.
Oh...
What? Isn't this your new song?
Yeah! We're going to sing it on
the bus and the bullet train!
Hmm?
You can't have a school trip without...
Ghost stories!
Wrong, wrong!
Then, being lectured by the teacher!
Wrong again!
You can't have a school trip without...
Wooden sword souvenirs?
Pillow fights!
Hey, now you've done it!
Eat this!
Be quiet—
Jeez, don't bother me!
I said no!
Goodness...
What's she doing making
a ruckus by herself?
Her school trip is near,
so I'm sure Mitsuki is just very excited.
No more!
WELCOME TO KYOTO!
MAP OF KYOTO'S TEMPLES
How's it going?
Were you able to find places your group
wants to go on the school trip?
When you think of Kyoto,
you think of maiko, the apprentice geishas.
Where can you find maiko?
Mount Hiei? Kiyomizu Temple?
Really? Mitsuki, search!
Okay!
Ma...i...ko...
LIFESTYLE AND CULTURE
PLACES TO EAT
PLACES TO STAY
Let me see... Shi...
Shien?
You don't read it Shien. It's Gion!
Huh?!
You said Shien! How embarrassing!
Shut up!
Mitsuki!
Are you okay?
I-It hurts.
Mr. Yamane! Mitsuki is...
Mitsuki! Mitsuki!
I see... She was really
looking forward to it, but...
We will pay careful attention,
so could you please let her...
No.
If something should happen on the trip,
it would cause trouble.
So she will not be going
on the school trip.
What?!
It's in the interest
of your health!
And you must not cause
trouble for everyone.
But...
What?
There's only one school trip.
It's not just your problem.
Give it up!
I tried to tell Dr. Wakaoji, but he's off
today and tomorrow for something.
So I'll try consulting with him
early next week.
Okay.
What?! No way!
We can't go on the school trip?
Man, I was really looking forward to it!
This isn't the time for that!
Huh?
You're right. The one who's
the most upset is Mitsuki, huh?
And she has to worry
about her throat too.
Remember Dr. Wakaoji's conditions
when he came on as producer.
First, that you'll undergo
regular checkups for your throat.
And second,
when push comes to shove,
you will follow my instructions,
including undergoing surgery, okay?
Th-That's bad!
Right?!
I'll have the checkup in her place!
That'd be totally obvious.
Th-Then how about
manipulating the X-rays?!
Even if you were to cover it up
with a quick fix...
This isn't the time for you
to be all downcast, right?
From now...
W-What is it?!
Calm down!
Put yourself in her position!
Then what do we do?! If she gets surgery,
she might not be able to sing anymore!
And things will get messy if she has
the surgery and ends up living longer.
What should we do?!
Have a good trip!
Mitsuki, we'll be back with souvenirs!
I'll send you a postcard too!
Okay! Take care!
Hey!
I'm okay!
I just choked on the fumes.
If you say so.
Mitsuki is in Kyoto about now, huh?
I hope it doesn't rain.
Yeah. I hope she
creates nice memories.
Yes.
We're going to sing on the bus,
there and back!
How long has it been
since I fell in love with you?
My feelings keep
getting stronger.
- They're silent like—
- ...like the snow.
Takuto!
Don't stop. I've gone to
the trouble of singing with you.
Okay!
- They're silent like the snow.
- ...silent like the snow.
- But they keep building up.
- Hold me tight.
- If loving someone...
- was going to feel like this...
I wish I never
found out about love.
- I love you.
Mitsuki!
Meroko! Water!
Right!
I-I'm okay. I can get it.
Mitsuki!
What does this mean?
In my opinion,
she should have surgery.
S-Surgery?!
Dr. Wakaoji didn't say anything about that.
Where is Dr. Wakaoji now?
He's off today.
Off?
Wakaoji is part-time now.
You hadn't heard?
No.
H-Hey.
This could turn into something bad!
Everyone was saying he would be the
next chief physician for sure.
He has no ambition.
He said he wanted to play music again
like he used to long ago. And so...
Why?
Jeez! Don't say any more!
Music?
Dr. Wakaoji...is playing music?
Oh no. Now she knows!
You still haven't been
able to contact Wakaoji?
No... I get his voicemail
on his cell phone.
I see. Then it can't be helped.
I have no other idea.
Dr. Wakaoji said that it could
be controlled with medicine.
What about that?
Oh? Let me see...
If nothing else, the progression
of the sickness will be curbed.
If nothing else?
Doctor, please operate!
N-No way!
N-No, that's something
for Wakaoji to decide.
No, please do it!
Mitsuki?
Where am I?
The hospital. You're okay now.
Surgery?!
The old lady did something
she shouldn't have again!
I know!
She outright asked for the surgery!
What should we do?!
That puts her voice in jeopardy too.
Mitsuki, you mustn't in your condition!
Mitsuki!
Well, that was fun.
We haven't had a blast
like that in a while, eh?
Ms. Oshige, let's do it again.
What? Really?!
What?!
Please arrange for
the surgery immediately!
W-Well, I must ask Wakaoji.
It'll be fine if I sign
a letter of consent, right?
Hey, you...
Grandma!
Mitsuki!
Umm... I'm okay now.
What's with you?!
Go back to your hospital room!
B-But...
Relax, Mitsuki.
Just say you don't want to.
Say it! Say you don't
want to have surgery!
Jeez, this is irritating.
Meroko!
But...
Is it okay with you
if you lose your voice?
You get healthy if
you transform into Full Moon,
but if you lose your voice,
you lose it as Full Moon too!
What?
Umm...
Jeez! What's Wakaoji doing?!
Surgery?! When did it get that bad?
I don't know!
I didn't find anything unusual
at her last checkup!
Anyway, do the surgery
as quickly as possible!
As I've said many times,
I'm not authorized to.
That's enough.
I'll try asking another hospital.
Ms. Koyama!
Sorry I'm late!
Wakaoji...
Mitsuki!
When did you start coughing?
On the day of the party...
Why didn't you tell me then?!
I-I'm sorry!
Dr. Wakaoji!
Thank you for taking the time
to come on your day off.
Sure. I apologize for how I look.
Why didn't you tell me that
you had become part-time?
I'm sorry. I judged that it
wasn't necessary to tell you.
And that you're playing music.
Well...
It's okay.
She doesn't know that
he's Full Moon's producer.
I think mutual trust is
important for a doctor.
Grandma! It's not his fault!
I forced him to.
Forced him to?! What?
M-Music...
Excuse me!
If it's that,
then I'm accountable!
Who are you?
Oh, Ms. Oshige is Wakaoji's fiancée.
Oh, no, you have it all wrong!
Then please be quiet!
O-Okay.
Let's talk about that later.
Anyway, let me examine her!
Okay then, Mitsuki.
Yes.
Okay, we're done.
H-How is she, Wakaoji?
Yes... She's indeed getting worse.
I think surgery...
will be a last resort,
and it should be okay to treat you
with medicine for a while.
A different opinion
than this doctor, huh?
Who should we believe?
I'm the physician in charge.
Believe me.
Oh, I also think that would be best.
But, earlier you said...
Well, that was my individual opinion.
And Wakaoji's opinion
is not wrong, so...
But we should ultimately
choose which.
Please, Grandma.
If it's about the school trip or other things,
I'll do as you say. But...
Please at least let me decide
to whom I entrust my life.
Ma'am?!
Ma'am!
Ms. Koyama!
Grandma!
Do as you like.
Okay, here.
It's stronger medicine than before,
but hang in there, okay?
O-Okay.
Has the matter somehow
been settled?
But we have to hurry before her condition
gets any worse and find Eichi.
Why?! Why?!
Huh? What happened?
No way! That can't be, right?
I said, what happened?
No! I can't believe it!
I said, what happened?!
On her way to school, she ran into
an old man who can see us Death Spirits!
What?!
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Gentleman on the Swing."
- Look forward to it!