Who are you?
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Recover Your Love!
The Precure's Five Vows!
Cure... Ace?
I've never seen her before!
Who is she?
Just looking at her makes me sick to my stomach!
Get out of my sight!
Just where were you aiming?
She's fast!
I shall end this fight in one blow!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Regina!
Cure Ace, was it?
I'll remember that name.
Wait, don't take Regina away!
Regina...
Precures...
I'll never forgive you!
Precures!
Regina!
Mana!
Do you think your tears will bring her back?
Now stand.
You have no time to waste.
Now hold on!
You don't know how strongly Mana felt for Regina!
I may not know who you are or where you came from,
but I will not allow someone to disrespect Mana's feelings!
The Precure's Five Vows!
First!
A Precure must always hold her head high and persevere!
Now, gather your strength.
I can't...
That was all the strength I had!
You leave me no choice.
Until you recover your love,
I shall take hold of this.
A fair deal, no?
Adieu.
W-Wait!
She left...
I'm sorry, girls...
She was completely right...
I don't deserve to be a Precure!
Mana...
Mana, it's not your fault!
So please, don't cry!
Oh, poor daughter of mine,
slumber for now.
Deeply... ever so deeply.
And who was that Cure Ace?
We do not know.
But she is a fierce opponent.
Seems she's a bit too much for you to handle, Belly.
I told you never to call me that, Leva!
You mean to tell me that you lot have yet to conquer a single world?
We've already led three worlds to their doom!
Gula!
Doesn't mean much when all three of 'em were ape-infested boonies.
My, you've got quite the mouth!
How about I gobble you up head first?
Go ahead and try, fatso!
Cease your foolishness!
Leva, and Gula as well,
I task you with the annihilation of the Precures!
Yes sir!
Oogai Shopping District Festival
Frankfurters
Hello!
Welcome!
Ooh, that smells good!
Want a taste?
Don't mind if we do.
Um, about Mana...
She hasn't left her room since yesterday.
She didn't eat breakfast, either.
I see...
Did something happen?
Huh?
What kind of something?
I've never seen Mana be so down in the dumps.
I thought that maybe she got into a spat with Regina.
Well, it wasn't what I'd call a spat...
Don't worry.
She may be in pain right now,
but Mana will be back on her feet soon enough.
You're right.
Mana's got some good friends, huh?
It seems Mana's depressed.
I can't blame her.
Not only did Regina get taken away...
But her Lovies was confiscated, too.
Just who was that Cure Ace?
About that...
We have been searching for Cure Ace's location,
but we have yet to retrieve any useful data.
She's as stubborn as she is strong!
Hmm?
Mana's grandfather?
Hello!
Oh, hello.
What are those boxes for?
I'm runnin' a garage sale at the festival.
Mana said she'd help, but...
We can help, if you'd like.
You sure?
Why, absolutely!
Um...
I'll help too!
Welcome!
Makopi, I'd like this!
100 yen!
I'm a huge fan!
Keep doing your thing!
Thank you very much!
Weren't we running a garage sale?
Being busy is hardly a bad thing.
Yeah, it gets lively when people get together.
And lively towns mean happy people.
Let us liven up this festival in Mana's stead.
Sounds good.
Mana...
Mana!
It's you and me!
It looks just like us!
Look, it's your old backpack!
It looks great on me!
This pillow smells like you!
Regina...
Precures...
I'll never forgive you!
Mana, it's unhealthy if you don't eat.
I don't wanna.
Keep it together!
You're a Precure, a legendary warrior!
Not anymore...
Kyupirappa!
Cha-what?
W-What?
What was that?
Yes?
It's getting busy out front,
so could you look after Ai for a bit?
Huh?!
Ai, what are you doing here?
Well, where else would your baby sister be?
S-Sister?!
Thanks for the help.
Then that means...
I think that magic earlier...
made my parents think Ai was my sister.
Huuuuuh?!
Mana.
Ai, did you just call me "Mana?"
Ai! Mana!
Us!
Ai...
A Nurture Lovies?
You want me to use this?
Mana, happy, happy!
Are you trying to cheer me up?
Ai...
You were the one who nurtured me...
Thank you, Ai.
This is a pretty busy festival.
I'm sure Regina would love it here.
Of course it wasn't her...
How long do you intend to mope around?
Wait, Ai!
If you don't change your attitude soon, you'll lose what you hold most dear,
Aida Mana.
Can you sign this?
Sorry, but this is a private function, so autographs are...
Aw, come on!
Oh well.
It's enough to see Makopi in person.
There's no need to hold back.
I shall grant your desire!
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Selfish!
Sign this!
If you'd please!
Everyone, please escape!
Girls, let's go!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
We'll have to make up for Mana while she can't transform!
Right!
Oh my, aren't you lot on the scene quick?
Who are you?
I am Leva.
And I'm Gula.
Pleased to make your acquaintance!
Huh?
Losing focus will get you eaten!
Sign these!
If you'd please!
Selfy selfy selfy!
Are you...
Mana, I heard a dark heartbeat!
The Sparkle Sword isn't working!
It's time to finish this.
Let's go to them, Charles.
But you can't transform!
We're going anyway.
Thank you very much.
I couldn't stop thinking about how Regina was gone,
so I lost sight of what really mattered.
But it's not about what's most dear.
I just want to protect everyone's smiles.
That includes my friends', and Regina's, too.
I'll protect them all!
Sign this!
If you'd please!
An excellent silhouette - or perhaps a Curouette?
Self?
You still fight?
Losing is not an option for us!
To make up for Mana, we have no choice...
but to defend this town and the smiles of its people!
What a nuisance.
Selfish!
Self!
Stop right there!
Mana!
You must stay back!
You can't transform!
I won't run away anymore!
I'll keep fighting to protect those I love!
Selfiiiiish!
No cigar!
Watch it!
What was that for?!
You hit me!
Nuh-uh, you did!
It worked!
Good thinking!
Mana...
Excellent work, Aida Mana.
No, Cure Heart!
The Precure's Five Vows!
First!
A Precure must always hold her head high and persevere!
Could she be...
It seems you've recovered your love.
Now, let's fight together!
Yeah!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Oh poor pen and paper who have lost their love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your hearts race once more!
Cure Heart!
End her by dying her in black!
If you can, that is.
Self?
Ai, let's go!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Beauty is the mark of the righteous!
With a single wink,
I shall pierce your heart!
Huh?!
Let's go.
Right!
Sign these!
If you'd please!
Please!
Self?
Seeelf?
Self!
Seeelf!
Are you ready?
You bet!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Love love loooove!
Precure Heart Shoot!
Huh?
Cure Ace...
We'll show no mercy next time.
Cure Heart!
Thank goodness!
I'm so glad!
Sorry for making you worry.
Don't worry, as long as you're back to normal.
Yes, indeed.
You've no time for celebration.
Your tribulations have only begun.
You must continue to climb until you reach my stage.
I shall be waiting.
Adieu.
Cure Ace...
Who was that woman?
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
I'm going to quit being an idol.
So I won't sing anymore.
What?! Makopi, you can't stop singing!
Time for Operation "Make Her Want to Sing!"
I shall prepare a splendid full orchestra!
That'd make it kinda hard to sing...
If the princess asked her to sing, she wouldn't refuse!
Huh? "Princess?" What are you planning?
Dokidoki Precure:
Shocker!
Makopi Announces Her Retirement!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!