"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Hey, what in the world is this line for?
Do you know, Yuki-chan?
I have no idea...
Now, now...
"Sorry, not a winner" "Performance of Haruhi
Suzumiya advanced ticket sales lottery"
So that's what this is about.
Sorry to say, I didn't win either.
Um... It seems that I have won.
Me too!
"Winner"
My friends from the heart!
What about me?
♪ I'll follow you ♪
♪ Even in the toughest of all
the shadows of the world ♪
I can't see at all...
Here.
♪ Making sure the soul doesn't
break from its frailness ♪
That was amazing!
I was so touched!
The guy that came out in the
beginning was really attractive!
Eh?! That guy?!
He was a no-go?
There's a need for someone like him?
Konata, you haven't spoken
a word for a while now.
Oh, yeah...
You seem to be down from using
too much energy at the festival.
Well, it's true that I was
touched by all of it too.
Yeah...
I wonder what this feeling is.
"I Can't Suddenly Change"
What are you doing?
Come on, let's go.
Kagami, you're active in
all the strange places.
Well, we had to come watch the flowers today,
or we'd miss the full bloom.
When you think, "Maybe tomorrow...
or maybe the day after tomorrow,"
it usually starts raining and all
the petals start falling off.
Come to think of it, what
happened to the goldfish
you caught at the summer festival?
Actually...
It seems like I gave it too
much food, and it's this big.
That's huge! Like, a Shogun?
I pampered it a little too much.
Wait just a minute.
Maybe you need to check your curriculum?
That's not a goldfish anymore.
All I can do is pray that it's
gotten fat from happiness.
Maybe you're going to eat it?
Like I would eat it!
There was an anime where the pet
that was pampered by its owners
came back as a human and did the
"Welcome home, my master" bit...
There you go again, always
referring to the hard-core stuff.
Maybe I'll make it go on
a little diet after all.
You know, Kagami...
You aren't thinking about fishing up
a replacement to take over, are you?
It's getting pretty cold now.
I guess we'll call it a day soon.
When you're out to see
cherry blossoms at night,
it gets really cold in
your afternoon outfits.
Your butt gets cold while
you're sitting down, too.
I've heard somewhere that the
average temperature in March
is basically the average
temperature in December,
and that of April is similar
to that of November.
Oh, if it's November or December,
I'd definitely be putting more clothes on.
When you think March or April,
you somehow wear less clothing.
Isn't it because you're getting
tired of wearing winter clothes?
Perhaps it is a show of emotions after all,
that you want spring to arrive soon.
Kagami, you're in high spirits.
You can't be wearing wool...
"Long-wave infrared radiation effect"
...are you fully prepared?
I'm wearing no such thing!
That's all you get today, Gyopi.
If this thing were to
show up as my boyfriend,
and he was into domestic
violence, I'd be in a bind...
Just kidding.
I wonder what's wrong with Sis?
It's so irritated! My
skin is rather delicate.
This season is always so tough on me.
It must be a pain.
I'm home most of the time, too.
They seem to have all sorts
of stuff for hay fever now,
so why don't you buy some?
I see...
Transformation!
I see, it's good! I'm cutting
out 99% of the pollen!
Now you're suspicious inside and out.
Please, make sure you don't
end up in police custody.
I'm gonna do a little shopping now.
Take care.
Want to come with?
I'm not going.
Or rather, Dad, are you going
to go shopping like that?
Of course.
There's no point to this gear
if I don't go out in it.
Our next news story.
Last night, around 11 o'clock, a
woman barged into a convenience store
and tried to take that day's earnings.
You know, Yu-chan...
What?
During this season, are there
more convenience-store robbers
just pretending to have hay fever?
You'd think that there are some like that.
Freeze!
Why does it end up that way?
Oh, tomorrow? That's fine.
Let's go have fun for the
first time in a while!
That's true. My homework is done too.
Huh? What did you just say?
That your homework is done?
Really? I don't believe it!
I'm sorry. I lied.
You know, don't you feel like
telling a lie on April Fool's Day?
It's a good thing I remembered.
No, you really show zero effort
in trying to do it yourself.
You bored person, you...
You're about the only one who'd
call this late just to tell a lie.
Anyway, see you tomorrow.
Yes, Izumi residence.
My name is Kuroi... Is
this the Izumi household?
Oh, ma'am.
Hey, Izumi, it's me. I'm sorry,
the game you lent me...
I accidentally saved over your data.
What?!
Just kidding! Serves you
right, you fell for it!
Today is April Fool's Day!
I found one more bored person right here.
Ma'am?
Oh, what is it?
The other day, Miyuki-san...
Teaching must be an easy job,
if even someone like Miss
Kuroi can keep at it...
That was what she said.
Oh... That brat. She was
faking her niceness, huh...
Um, ma'am? It's a lie, okay?
Konata called just so that
she could tell a lie. Sheesh.
Did you tell a lie to someone today, Tsukasa?
Yeah.
That's unusual. What kind of lie?
Just now, when I said I
told a lie, that was a lie.
That's so hard to follow!
Or rather, you don't have to force
yourself into telling a lie, okay?
What kind of a lie did Kona-chan tell?
Oh, it was something like she
did all her homework by herself.
When you think about it,
I was dumb for falling for it, too.
It's just plain impossible.
If it's a lie, she hasn't
done her homework yet, right?
Well, knowing her, I'm positive
that she hasn't done it yet.
I see...
You just thought, "I'm glad someone
is in the same boat as me," right?
Well...
Konata, can I have a minute?
Sure.
Is it interesting?
Unique.
I see...
Konata... Actually, I'm thinking
about getting married again.
I see.
No, it's normal for you to be against it.
It's true that Kanata alone is your moth--
"I see?"
"I see?" So, Konata, you're
fine if I get married again?
Isn't it all right?
But, you know, for you, it means
that you'll have a new mom.
What kind of a person is this new mom?
Well... Um, uh...
It's a problem for you to
take it so seriously...
Now, the next problem! What is
the modest-polite form of "yuku"?
That would have to be
"ukagau"... That's so easy!
Oh, you're right, it has to be "ukagau".
Yeah, that would be right.
Oh, come to think of it,
I think that's right.
The correct answer is "mairu"!
Come to think of it, that's true.
Yeah, actually...
Your mom fell for it too.
What is with this strange atmosphere?
It's because someone so confident
in their answer made a mistake...
First multiple-choice question:
Which prefecture does not face the ocean?
A: Ibaraki Prefecture.
B: Tochigi Prefecture.
C: Kyoto Prefecture.
It's B.
It's B, right?
This is so simple.
The answer was B!
Next question.
What is the famous theorem that
has been known for ages as
one of the most difficult questions
in the world of mathematics,
only to be proven in 1994 by Prof.
Wiles of Princeton University?
A: Pythagorean theorem.
B: Taylor's theorem.
C: Fermat's theorem.
Why do they all blurt it
out when they know it,
yet when they're not so
confident, they all shut up?
Since we have the opportunity,
let's all go visit Miyuki-san's
place during spring break.
Oh, that sounds good.
Since it's pretty far away, we've
never had the chance to go.
Miyuki-san lives in a well-to-do household...
I wonder what it's like.
Maybe there's a pool in the yard!
No, no, maybe there are security
guards around the house!
No, I'm sure it's more normal.
Oh, she seems like she'd
have a pet or something!
The image I have of her says a
ferret or something. A white one!
No, no, it's got to be
a dog. A big white dog.
And in the big yard, she's
got a white parasol!
Maybe there really is a dog.
And so, our conversation really took off.
You're all welcome to come, but
please don't expect anything.
I'm sorry that we don't have any pets.
Oh, though we don't have a
big white dog nor a parasol,
there is a house in our
neighborhood that is like that.
I see...
And I hear that someone from that house
is going to start attending Ryouou this year.
I see...
We'll invite her over, and you
can come with us, Yu-chan.
One of my friends has a cousin
that will be attending Ryouou
starting this spring.
The world is a rather small place.
Small world, isn't it?
Lucky Star!
I'm so sleepy...
Sheesh, it's because you always
sleep into the afternoon.
It's Konata.
Heya!
What? Did you get into the
habit of sleeping in too?
I've been up for three nights,
more or less, playing games.
I think I'm going to die soon.
These two are just alike in their laziness!
"Miyuki Takara" "Konata Izumi"
"Tsukasa Hiiragi" "Minoru Shiraishi"
We're in the same class again!
You're right! I'm so glad!
Good morning.
Oh, Yuki-chan, good morning.
Morning! Miyuki-san, you're in our class too!
Oh, you're right. I'm so glad.
My regards for the upcoming year.
My regards!
"Minami Iwasaki" "Yutaka Kobayakawa"
We're in the same class!
Yeah...
Oh... My regards for the upcoming year!
My regards...
Kagami's the only one in
a different class again.
I already have so many
chances to see you as it is.
I'd get too tired unless I was
at least in a different class!
It's a shame.
Sis...
Not really. It's always like this, right?
Besides, someone like Konata will come see me
to borrow notes or textbooks anyway.
She's read me...
So you guys go on ahead.
Yeah, see you later.
See ya.
S'up, Hiiragi! What class are you in?
Hey, we're in the same class again!
Counting junior high, does that
make it five years in a row?
My regards once again.
Huh?
There are people like that...
Cold-hearted ones that see nothing
but their main objectives.
Now, now.
It's like we're just scenery.
How do you think they decide
how to split up the classes?
I've heard that they try to
average out the test scores,
or that they try to split up
relatives as best they can,
or that they split up all
the problem students.
I heard that it depends
on the school, though.
In dramas and stuff,
all the problem kids get bundled
up in one class, don't they?
That livens the show up too.
But in high school, everyone
should be at the same level,
so there probably aren't
that many problematic cases.
That's true...
Miyuki...
You can come back with
"Understand that you are one of
the problem students," you know?
You wouldn't want to be put in
the same boat as her, right?
Oh no, it's not like that...
The bell rang. Our teacher's late.
Come to think of it, you're right.
All to your seats!
Close call. Just barely safe!
That's an out.
Well, I'm your homeroom teacher, Kuroi.
All of you, now that you've moved up a grade,
you can't be in vacation-mode forever.
Have a change of heart, and
make sure to do your best!
That's so unconvincing!
"Responsibilities for first
half of the trimester"
"Class representative"
"Library representative"
Well, I won't yak on about
how you guys need to study,
but since this is your last year in
high school, spend your days wisely!
Now, we'll move on to splitting
up responsibilities...
Takara, can I ask you to be the
class rep for the first half?
Yes.
Class reps and stuff like
that, once you do it,
the character image lingers
on, and you keep doing it...
That's true... Though it's not
a chore for me, so it's fine.
And the teachers usually decide who
it will be during the first trimester.
Since there are so many
people that we don't know,
it's hard to nominate someone.
But in Miss Kuroi's case, isn't
it more like it's easy for her
to make you do everything, Miyuki-san?
I heard that!
Our teacher's hair was a mess!
But I think this will be a fun
class with Miss Kuroi again.
Well, she's got a fun groove...
The class "color" usually depends
on the teacher in charge.
I see, that's it!
The fact that both of you are so
slovenly is similar to your teacher!
I heard that!
I'm Iwasaki... Nice to meet you.
That girl is pretty cute.
I was in the same junior high with
her, but she doesn't talk at all.
She's rather dull, and since
she reads books all the time,
she's kinda creepy.
She's actually a really nice girl.
So I'm the only one that knows! I
feel like I've got an advantage!
Next.
Yes!
The beginning is the most important
part in stuff like this!
I have to act bright and cheerful.
I'm Yutaka Kobayakawa.
I'm short like this,
but I'm not a grade-school girl
that skipped grades or anything!
Just kidding.
Skipped grades?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Maybe I've been influenced by Sis too much,
and gotten a bit on the maniac side...
Now, I'd like to delegate
all the responsibilities.
Anyone volunteering to be
the class representative?
Nobody, huh.
Iwasaki, since you were class
rep in junior high, you do it!
If that's the case,
Iwasaki, can I ask you to?
I'm sorry, I'd like to take another position.
Someone who's done it before is
best suited for the position...
What position do you want? The library rep?
The health rep.
I'll be the class rep, sir!
She really is a good person!
Spring...
Something is about to begin.
Such a premonition...
A new introduction...
"Konata Izumi"
A new life...
A new...
...love!
With that childhood friend...
With that upperclassman that
you've always admired...
Or with an exchange student
that you find unfamiliar...
A small bit of worry and
lots of expectations...
Five seconds before seriously
falling in love, MK5!
That's the refreshing image I have,
but since you're starting from square
one with people you don't know,
it's actually rather depressing.
I'm used to it already.
You're better off than I am!
Sis!
Oh, Yu-chan. Haven't seen you since morning!
That's true, I haven't
seen you since morning.
That's right!
This is the person that helped me
out, the one I mentioned before!
Oh, so you got to see her. Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you.
See, it's just like what I said, right?
That she'd definitely get in.
Yeah, yeah. But Yu-chan, you
overlooked the possibility that
she might not have decided to
attend here even if she got in.
But it was all right in
the end, so it's okay!
By the way, Yu-chan, what
were you guys doing?
We thought we'd check where
the nurse's office was.
I'm sure I'll be seeing a lot of it, anyway.
I see.
Oh, Sis, show us where it is!
All right, leave it to your big sister!
Where was the nurse's office?
"Nurse's Office"
I don't know, because
I've never had to use it.
Come on, you've been here for two years
and you still don't know
where the nurse's office is?
Well, it just means that I spent
two years completely healthy.
No, you've gone to the
physical exams held there.
Come to think of it, I've
never gone to the art room.
You don't have a chance to go when
you choose music instead of art.
I myself have not set foot
inside the judo room.
Until recently, I didn't even know
of the existence of a tea room.
Even if you go to the same
school for three years,
it's true that you only go to
places you have a need to go to.
I don't go to study hall much, either.
I go to the study hall a lot.
Oh, that's unexpected.
That quiet room is perfect for sleeping.
I see.
Oh, Yu-chan came by with the
girl that helped her out
during the entrance exams to see
where the nurse's office was,
but she said they were in the
same class. It's a miracle!
But, when I think about it,
I think it's a miracle for me
that I met people like Kona-chan
and Yuki-chan in this school,
and got to be friends.
Well, yeah.
I only have one more year
of spending my days together
with all of you like this...
But Kagami was in a different
class for all of it.
Don't say that.
The answer is B, the poisoned carrot.
This will be on the exam,
so make sure to remember it.
Hey, Izumi, wake up!
Potemkin?!
What were you dreaming about?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm doing my best to concentrate
so that I don't fall asleep.
Oh?
But, ma'am, they keep coming!
The monsters called sleepiness!
They come so suddenly! And
I can't dodge the attack!
It's absolute destiny!
Even though you just made such a
bold explanation to a teacher...
That should wake you up a bit.
Miyuki-san, you never fall asleep in class.
Is there some trick to it or something?
It's not much of a trick, but...
I'm one that can't go without sleep,
so I go to sleep around
11 o'clock at the latest.
Until last year, I used to be in bed by 10.
No good... I'd feel like I'm losing
out on life, so I can't mimic that!
I remember jotting memos on
my notes earlier during class,
because I thought I needed to
remember it, since it was important,
but since I was half asleep, I
don't know what I wrote down.
I can't tell.
But, when I look at this, I
feel so proud of myself...
It's a show of strong will
that I want to study. Yeah.
But honestly, what did I write down?
Yeah...
Isn't that a mathematical equation?
Miss Kuroi...
Amazing! You can read this
strange manuscript, ma'am?
Well, yeah.
But that means that Izumi, in your dreams,
you weren't in world history class.
Okay!
Sis, are you still up?
So it smells after all.
Oh, no. It's already that time.
Maybe someone will be on by now?
You really have no self-awareness, do you?
I'm looking forward to tomorrow, you know?
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
This is Lucky Channel, rumored to
be helping to achieve world peace!
I'm Akira "Pretty" Kogami, the navigator!
Likewise, I'm Minoru
Shiraishi, the assistant.
Time passes by so quickly, and Lucky
Channel is already on episode 15!
Wait, today is the 15th episode?
That's right.
Then you're done for after today's episode.
Huh?
Goodbye.
Didn't you hear? The producer
told me that starting episode 16,
they decided that Akira Kogami
will be doing the segment alone.
He gave his regards to me.
I see, but, wait, that's...
Hah! You fell for it, you fell for it!
April Fool's!
Oh... I see, so that's what it was.
That's right...
Come to think of it, it
seems to have been a riot.
"The Performance of Haruhi Suzumiya," was it?
Nyoron!
It looked like someone resembling
you was hosting the show.
Really? That shouldn't be...
So, when is my live event again?
Eh? Um, I don't know...
I need advance notice and stuff,
as my schedule is filled up
way in advance, you know?!
I'll check right away!
Behold!
Hurry!
The eastern skies are burning red!
Hurry up!
It's a go? Producer? Okay?
Wha... Next episode? Understood!
Next episode, during this segment,
we're going to have a live
event featuring Akira Kogami!
Eh? Eh?!
Next episode?!
A-A-Are you serious?!
You have the arena booked?
Yes. Looks like they
twisted a couple of arms.
Bend!
Amazing! All right!
Way to go, Itoh!
Oh, I'm so looking forward
to Akira-sama singing!
Oh, no, you're serious? Really? Serious?
Oh, please leave hosting the show to me.
Wow, I'm honestly enthused
about this! I'm gonna do it!
I may look like this, but I've
gotten good reviews as a host!
So that's how it goes, everyone!
Next episode, we're going
to go all-out and have fun!
Then, see you next week! Bye-nee!
That's right... Will Minoru Shiraishi
really be here again next week?
I'm a Lieutenant.
Well then, please listen.
Hey, what are you going to sing first?
The first song isn't Hare Hare, is it?
Legend of Lovely Minoru
(Koi no Minoru Densetsu)!
One, two, three, four!
He's already going off.
♪ Min-min Miracle, Minorun-run! ♪
♪ Min-min Miracle-- ♪
It's not Hare Hare!
There's a huge audience over there!
So what's the first song?
Well, then, how about Legend
of Lovely Minoru for now?
Okay.
Then, we'll go with that.
Go at your own pace...
Go at your own pace!
Well then, please listen.
Legend of Lovely Minoru!
One, two, three, four!
♪ Min-min Miracle, Minorun-run!
Min-min Miracle, Minorun-run! ♪
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
I'm Inori.
I'm Matsuri.
I'm Miki.
I'm Tadao.
Next Episode: Ring.
Please look forward to it!