Ready your blades.
If we see it, it'll only be for a split second.
Go!
Damn it's fast!
In these trees, it's impossible to predict and evade its attacks!
It'll get us!
Corporal, let's engage with Multiaxial Maneuvers!
Corporal!
Gotchya!
Reinforcements from the rear!
Corporal! Orders?!
Let's go for it!
That thing's deadly.
We have to kill it!
At this rate, we'll never survive!
We kill it here!
That's why we're in this forest!
Isn't that right, Corporal?!
Corporal, your orders!
All troops. Please cover your ears.
O, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
O, my friend!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel
We will kill
The enemy is huge
We will jump
In our hands we hold blades of glory
We sing of victory
On our backs we have wings of freedom
We put our iron determination into our hearts
We slash apart the circle of idiocy
We fly through the endless blue
on wings of freedom
the eotena onslaught
Worry
57th Sortie Beyond the Walls ( 3 )
A sonic flare?
What is your job?
To follow your instincts and attack unthinkingly?
I don't think so.
Your job
is to keep this mewling brat safe from all harm.
Even if it costs you your lives.
They aren't here to keep me in check?
We remain mounted. Got it?
Yes, sir!
Keep going? How far?
That thing's right on top of us.
Again?
More reinforcements!
If we don't help, she'll kill them again!
Eren, eyes in front!
Sir!
Do not slack your pace.
Remain at top speed!
But sir...
Why?!
If Squad Levi won't take that bitch out, who will?
Another man down.
And we could've saved him!
One's fighting on.
We can still help him!
Eren! Look ahead and do not falter!
You're ordering me to avert my eyes?
To forsake my comrades and run away?!
Yes, that's right!
Obey the Corporal's orders!
I can't understand why we're leaving them to die!
Or why he won't explain his commands!
Why?!
Because the Corporal judged his intent should not be revealed.
Your refusal to understand only betrays your inexperience!
Got it? Now shut up and follow orders!
No.
I can fight alone.
Why am I depending on others?
I can just fight my own fight.
What do you think you're doing, Eren?
That's only permitted if your life is in danger.
Didn't you promise us?
Eren!
You aren't in the wrong.
If you wanna do it, do it.
I can tell.
This kid's the real monster.
And not because of that ridiculous power.
No force of coercion can suppress him.
No cage is strong enough to hold him.
He will never submit. Not to anyone.
I just want to exterminate every last Eoten!
Eren, the difference between your thought process and ours is experience.
But you don't have to trust in our experience.
Decide.
Believe in yourself.
Or believe in the Legion and in me.
I don't know the right answer.
I never have.
I can only decide to trust in my own abilities
or the judgment of those I trust.
But no one ever knows how it'll turn out.
So make your call.
Make a choice you'll regret the least.
Eren!
Have faith.
I've come up with a way to half-kill you.
Sir?
I once said I could only stop your Eotenes form if I killed you.
But this tactic requires only grievous bodily injury.
Of course, everything depends on the squad's skill.
The idea is to cut you right out of the Eotenes' neck.
'Course we'd slice most of your arms and legs off,
but you grow everything back like a damn lizard.
Fucking creep.
Wait a second.
I don't actually know how they'd grow back.
Isn't there any other way...?
So you want to avoid any danger or self-sacrifice?
N-No.
Then just steel your resolve.
We'll do the same.
For us, the danger is death at your hands.
So rest easy.
Yes. Understood.
S-So... I can try a little experiment?
It's very risky.
But that doesn't mean we can't get some info out of him.
So I have full authority to plan this test?
Eren, if there's something you don't know,
learn it.
Knowledge is worth even mortal danger.
All set, Eren?
When everything's ready, I'll use the smoke round to letchya know.
After that, any decisions are in your hands.
Roger!
I'm sure this dry well could restrain even a mindless Eoten.
Probably!
That's the signal.
I haven't tried to transform since I sealed the wall.
If I lose control, Squad Levi could kill me.
Did he miss the signal?
No.
It's just that his power isn't that reliable.
Hey, Eren! Give it up for now.
Anything amiss?
Hanji...
I can't transform into an Eoten.
So the self-inflicted bite wounds on your hands aren't healing, either?
They're not.
If you can't transform into an Eoten,
we can't achieve our goal of sealing Wall Maria.
This is an order.
Do something about this.
Yes, sir.
Don't let it get you down, Eren.
But...
Well, this just means you're more human than we thought.
Failing now is better than rushing into battle and getting killed.
This experiment isn't meaningless.
Yeah.
We can't be too cautious.
Why's everyone so calm about this?
Do they really not mind that I can't transform?
You okay?
Sure.
Whoah!
What was that?
An explosion?
Why now?!
Stay calm.
Corporal Levi!
This is—
I said to stay calm.
All of you.
Smoke Rounds ( 1 )
Gunpower-propelled signal rounds fired by small handguns.
The entire tube-shaped cartridge is replaced for each signal.
Smoke Rounds ( 1 )
Gunpower-propelled signal rounds fired by small handguns.
The entire tube-shaped cartridge is replaced for each signal.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Smoke Rounds ( 2 )
The color of the signal conveys its message.
Red... Eoten sighted.
Green... Alter course.
Black... Abnormal Eoten sighted.
Smoke Rounds ( 2 )
The color of the signal conveys its message.
Red... Eoten sighted.
Green... Alter course.
Black... Abnormal Eoten sighted.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
What? What was that sound?
Eren.
What is the meaning of this?!
Sir?
Why now, without authorization?
Answer me!
Elad, wait.
Answer him, Eren!
What are you up to?
No, questions can wait.
Prove you're not our—Mankind's—enemy!
Give us proof! Now!
This is your duty!
Just you try making a move with that arm!
I'll slash off your head!
I can do it! For real!
Wanna try me?
Orlo!
I told you to stay calm.
Corporal, keep away from Eren!
You're too close!
No, you're the ones who should keep away.
Get back.
Why?!
A feeling I've got.
What's wrong, Eren?
Say something!
Like I said...
No sudden movements!
Prove yourself, Eren!
I said I don't understand.
Answer us! You think we can't kill you?
I'm serious!
Do it now!
Are you listening to me?
Okay, let's get it on!
Are you humanity's—
Could you all please just shut up?!
Eren!
Can I touch that arm?!
'Sall good, right? Right?
Juss' wanna touch it!
Hanji!
Wait a second!
So... hot!
When it's naked, it's so damn hot!
Unbe-fucking-lievably hot!
Squad Leader!
Please control yourself!
Hey, ain'tchya gettin' hot too, Eren?
How d'ya feel right where the that arm connects?
I juss' gotta see!
That's it.
If I just pull my right hand out...
This damn thing!
Hey, Eren.
Don't do anything rash!
What?!
Come on, Eren! That was way too fast!
I wasn't even close to—
Corporal.
How do you feel?
Not... Not so great.
Until I saw them standing there, ready to kill me,
I didn't understand.
I didn't understand that they doubted me so deeply.
But of course they do.
That's why I chose them.
People say you only become a real member of the Legion
after you've survived a mission.
But every time you engage the Eotenas, you lack information.
There are just too many situations you can't anticipate, no matter your skill.
They've had to cultivate their abilities to take decisive action
and to make impassive decisions based on the worst-case scenario.
But that doesn't mean they've become heartless.
I'm sure they felt compassion even as they drew their blades on you.
Corporal Levi.
Squad Leader Hanji is asking for you.
Spend too long on the shitter?
Nah. I'm was done in a twinkling.
I just wasn't sure what to tell the brass.
Well, first off...
Check this out.
A teaspoon?
Yes.
That strange Eotenes hand Eren generated was holding this.
Like so, between index finger and thumb.
I just can't figure that for an accident.
And what's more,
the spoon wasn't the slightest bit warped by heat or pressure.
Any clue why?
I was trying to pick it up.
I transformed in that moment.
That so?
This might explain why you couldn't transform earlier.
"Exterminate the Eotenas."
"Stop the cannon shell."
"Lift the boulder."
During every event, your transformation has had a clear goal.
I'd wager that self-inflicted injury isn't the sole trigger.
It seems you need a sense of purpose as well.
True, this transformation was a lot like the one I used to block that cannon shell.
But...
I turned into an Eoten to pick up a spoon?
What in the hell is this?
So you're saying you didn't transform deliberately?
No, sir.
Eh? Whuuh?
Wait, what are you up to?
Man, that hurts.
This isn't easy.
Eren, I'm impressed you can bite clean through.
We made a bad call.
This is a small price to pay.
Not that it justifies our actions.
Keeping you in check is our job.
Nothing wrong with doing our job.
So don't get too full of yourself!
Forgive us, Eren.
We've been awfully jumpy.
I'm sure we seem pretty silly.
But, no matter how silly we are...
We're depending on you. And we want you to depend on us.
So please.
Trust us.
Have faith.
Eren!
Just make up your damn mind!
I'll continue on!
Let me go!
I'm so sorry!
Target is accelerating!
Go!
At this rate we'll outrun it.
There's absolutely no way.
If we try to run away, it'll just stomp us all flat!
But...
Even if it cost our lives,
everyone's chosen to continue on.
Even if we have to abandon our comrades.
Corporal Levi has kept his eyes forward this whole time.
And the rest of the squad—
they believe in him. They place all their trust in him.
I'll believe in them, too.
Just like they
believed in me!
Fire!
Move a bit farther away, tether the horses, and switch to Multiaxial Maneuvers.
You will be acting independently.
Squad leader will be Elad.
Once you're a good distance away from the Eoten, get Eren under cover.
Take my horse.
No way.
He wants to take that Eoten alive?
Well, Eren? You see that?
We caught that Eoten!
This is the power of the mighty Reconnaissance Legion!
Don't underestimate us, you fuckwit.
Well? Now do you get it?
Yes!
Looks like it's stopped moving.
We still can't lower our guard.
But you did very well to lead it here.
Many troops from the rearguard died to give us the time we needed.
We couldn't have made it without them.
Is that so?
It is.
Thanks to their sacrifice, we'll be able to see who's inside this bitch.
Let's just hope she's not full of terror piss.
If we assume that I am not truly who I think I am,
then how can you claim that you are yourself?
A castle of sand guarded your heart, and it fell apart
Can you gather the pieces and repair yourself?
The voices of others calling you
are just a ringing in your ear now
It's like time has stopped
Now, wake up
I want to escape the darkness
I want to flee like a raging storm
We lived like corpses, as though already dead
Let us meet again
outside the walls
where maps reach terra incognita
Erwin Smith's secret plan was to capture the Eoten Fatale.
The champions of the Reconnaissance Legion attempt to uncover its true identity, but...
Erwin Smith
57th Sortie Beyond the Walls ( 4 )