No!
Summer Time Rendering
Although it's her original hair,
it's not enough fer her to recover.
She's turning into a child.
She's in bad shape.
Shide.
Her nerves and muscles are worn out.
Ushio can't fight anymore.
Damn it.
If only I had the power to erase him.
Ryuunosuke, can you get into Shide's armor?
What?
No, that's too much to ask.
But it's the only option I see.
Don't turn around, Ryuu.
Shide can't hear our thoughts.
Both of y'all, listen to me.
I'll put all of myself into the shotgun shells and turn them into hacking bullets.
But it'll take two minutes to print 'em.
I need ya to buy me that time.
Having a secret strategy meeting?
Let me join ya.
It's fine.
Shide can't read memories.
He only had weapons because Hiruko was beside him.
You've changed, Haine.
I never expected ya to betray me.
Yer the one who changed!
Everything went wrong after that whale washed ashore!
I haven't changed at all.
I just became enlightened.
I realized that I must be faithful to my own desire to live!
In the beginning, I just wanted us to be together.
That's all.
Two minutes, Shinpei.
Give it yer all fer just two minutes.
There's no going back.
I'll give him all I've got!
He's just rushing at us.
That's fine.
Let him think that the shotgun is worthless.
Crap! The shotgun won't stop him!
Ushio, change weapons!
Good thing I like to copy everything.
Even Hizuru's sledgehammer!
Thanks.
Now we can still fight.
Everything ends if ya die.
Ya can't use foresight or loop.
Ya gotta give the last boss a chance.
One more minute.
I see.
Both are right-handed.
It's hard to use.
The first hammer blow came back.
This is his echo!
Shide's left arm...
It grew back!
He just copied his right arm to make his left.
My erasing is working.
Keep it up, Ryuu.
Yes!
If I attack, it echoes back.
But if I stop, Shide will go fer Ushio.
Attack!
Keep attacking!
Don't give him room to breathe!
Shit!
I could only punch him!
Bad time for a bullet!
Ryuu, no!
Behind ya!
This is bad! I can't dodge—
Take a bird's-eye view.
Take a bird's-eye view!
Those are shell casings.
They haven't hit the ground.
Is this how shadows perceive time?
One second is so long.
It feels like forever.
How many more blows can I take?
Will I be able to shoot the bullets by the time they're ready?
Dammit.
Ushio even cut off one of his arms.
He's too good.
Much stronger than other shadows.
I'm the only one who can shoot!
I'm... the only one!
There's an advantage to being old, Ryuunosuke.
We can both fight like shadows,
but I've got many years on ya.
I'm sorry, Ushio.
Even if ya finish the hacking bullet, no one can shoot it.
Ryuu!
Don't give up, Ryuunosuke.
There's still a way.
It's time for the comeback story of the ages.
Ushio, I'll shoot the hacking bullet!
Ryuunosuke, you're good at possessing people, right?
Can you take over Shide's armor and stop him from moving?
We just need a few seconds for the bullets to be ready.
It should be easy since it's empty inside.
Wait!
Ya can't survive without Ryuu's support!
I know.
We can keep dodging him, but my body won't last five seconds.
To do that, I need to touch the armor.
Can I get that close without dying?
Be more confident.
I know you can do it.
Odd.
Okay!
Even without the foresight, he escapes fatal blows.
I'll try it, Shinpei!
Listen.
You can replicate any movement that you see.
Nezu will show you how to shoot.
I'm relying on you, Ryuunosuke.
I'll detect everything!
I'll weave past a fatal attack!
I can do it!
He's in!
Good work, Ryuunosuke.
Are ya trying to control my armor?
Ya got it wrong, ya bastard!
I'll never let go of ya, but I hate ya more than anything else!
Good. Just stop his movement.
This is bad.
I almost passed out.
Is this the pain that Ryuunosuke held back?
Hang in there, Shinpei!
Just a while longer!
Right, Ushio.
Your voice relieves my pain.
I can move a little more.
Well, well.
Yer hate makes me sad.
I like ya,
Ryuunosuke.
Ryuu!
Did ya intend fer Ryuunosuke to destroy my armor?
Not a terrible idea.
However,
I took it upon myself to separate Ryuunosuke from you.
Ya can prepare if ya know beforehand.
Ya often did that yerself.
What?
What do you mean, "If ya know"?
Ya didn't see the battle at Torajima.
Ya made it like it never existed,
but Hizuru tried to use the same exact strategy.
I gotta admit it.
I love loops!
The shotgun is two meters away.
Only three steps, but can a human like me reach it faster than Shide?
Yer body is starting to break apart!
Dammit!
Goddammit!
It's nice to just watch ya fall apart,
but before I take the eye from Ushio,
I should kill ya myself.
That sounds so much more satisfying.
Ya won't get Ushio's eye!
She'll give me her eye.
The fact that I still have this eye is
proof that the ending is set in stone!
Ushio will win in the end!
In the end?
I just want to live forever.
That's all.
I want to see this world. The future. The end of man.
The ending of everything.
That was possible with Haine.
I've lived fer 326 years and 24 days by switching bodies.
However, Haine got weaker.
When I learned my life would end with Masahito,
I was filled with despair.
Ya can't possibly imagine.
But I changed my thinking a few months ago.
If I can't see the end, I should just end the world with me!
If the world ended, I could see the ending of this world!
If I could revive Hiruko's eye fer even a little while,
I could steal that and erase the world.
I know how to turn off the power from the game console.
I'm the final boss after all, Shinpei.
Even if ya know that, ya can't change the ending!
I'll steal the eye and overwrite the future!
I shall reach the ending!
It's done!
Locked and loaded!
Go get it, Shinpei!
Wait for me, Ushio.
Here I come!
Don't waste yer effort, Shinpei!
Everything you've done is in vain!
No use, huh?
Ya won't make it.
Move.
Move!
Move, please!
Just a little is fine!
Get closer to Shinpei!
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
He reached it!
Haine!
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Yer the best!
Shinpei's right eye has Shide in its sight.
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
When he takes a bird's-eye view,
he syncs with shadow movements.
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Since I'd been moving him, his nervous system is active.
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
He just needs to move his body!
Illuminated by the moon
Ya can do it, Shinpei!
Your figure casts a shadow
You've come this far!
I know ya can!
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That's right, Ryuunosuke.
That happens to be my cue
Nothing's in vain.
Everyone helped to get me here.
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
No one was meaningless.
I won't let their sacrifice mean nothing.
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
He fell.
No, he evaded me!
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
You all brought me this far.
Amidst pain and sorrow
Now I'm here!
I-It's like Sis said.
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
The one who will save everyone...
Or perhaps god's algorithm
is Shinpei!
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Th-That bullet...
Yer so stubborn... U-Ushio...
This is the end, Shide.
We'll keep on living.
S-Stop...
After ya disappear, the world will continue on like normal.
If Hiruko is erased, my armor will disappear.
I can't move. I can't see.
No.
No!
Haine...
Oh...
This is my ending.
Summer Time Rendering
Shinpei...
Y-Ya did it.
Yeah...
Everyone will survive now...
Ow... It hurts...
I'll end it, Hiruko.
My body...
Shinpei, look behind ya.
Wh-What is this place?
This is...
the real world.
But...
from 300 years ago.
Wait, 300—
Hiruko must've connected the exit
of the endless night with this beach.
Our bodies are far away.
Only our data is here.
I could sometimes see the past during loops.
Is this the same as that?
That girl...
It's the real me.
I see.
Ushio, please erase Hiruko now!
That whale is Hiruko from the past.
She wants to move her data back and start everything again.
Wait! Stay away from the whale!
You'll be killed!
I can't touch her.
What?
Don't touch the god.
Go get a grown-up.
It's a ghost!
Guess I scared her.
Amazing. Ya touched the past.
The awakened power in that eye changed the past.
Oh, okay.
Please take the little one.
What are ya doing, Ushio?
As long as this thing washes ashore here,
the same thing will happen even if I erase her.
I need to erase this Hiruko.
She didn't want to redo it.
She called me here to end it.
Thank... you...
Goodnight.
Bye.
Thank you.
Thanks, Ushio.
Thanks, Shinpei.
Haine.
Hey, Ryuunosuke.
If I'm reborn,
can we be friends instead?
Yeah!
Of course!
I'll bring plenty of snacks!
I'm sure Sis would also...
Ushio.
I guess this is goodbye, Shinpei.
W-Wait!
Wait a sec.
I'll come with ya.
We can be together.
With Hiruko gone, all the shadows will disappear.
My right eye is normal now.
I'll die once I return to my body.
I want to disappear alongside ya.
Dummy.
Yer giving me second thoughts.
Ya gotta go back!
Everyone's waiting!
Don't worry.
I'll send ya back to 2018.
These three days were really scary and stressful.
But more than that, I was happy to spend time with ya!
Well?
Whaddya say?
Me... Me too.
I'm glad I could see ya!
I was so happy, Ushio.
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
The power to cross time.
I finally figured it out.
But even now I still see visions of you
This wasn't a coincidence.
That strong desire to see someone again linked Haine and me.
In reality I only have vivid memories
With the power given to me,
I'll jump back and rewrite that summer!
To play in my head over and over again
I gotta hurry!
Before this body disappears!
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
Recording
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
So if I could just talk to my past self
I'd tell her not to give up even if it hurts
So please, don't let go of that hand
Make sure to find me.
Never let it go
Take good care of Mio.
But it's too late for that
I have to go now.
Come to this ending.
Everyone is waiting fer ya at the end.
I'm waiting fer ya!
Ushio!
Huh?
Next time
"I'm Home"