One morning I suddenly realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
✩Ah✩
Nothing good can come from cuddling you all the time
Cuddle,
cuddle,
cuddle
The scent of my feelings might stick
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Tell me, is this "love"?
That's a secret beyond all secrets, you know?
Yeah!
That's a secret beyond all secrets, isn't it? ♡
Changing World
Good morning, Manabe!
Morning.
Hey, Manabe!
Yo.
Morning.
'Sup?
So there's this new ramen place by the station.
I wanna go check it out, but...
Hey!
Uh, nothing.
But I've heard those frauds make their so-called "miso butter ramen" with margarine!
Are you serious?
Yeah, that's just wrong!
Manabe's totally back to normal.
Isn't that a relief, Moritani?
Yeah...
Hey, think this might be your chance?
Yeah! There's no one to get in the way now.
It's been a week since Kotoura vanished.
Life goes on, completely unchanged.
It's just as if the girl named Kotoura Haruka
had never been.
Kotoura Haruka
Dialing...
The number you have dialed is not currently in service.
Not a care in the world, eh, Manabe?
Aww, so close, yet so far.
Y'know, you might as well come a tiny bit closer.
You can't even be bothered to move your head?
Whatever. Just come along to the club room.
I don't need to participate in the club anymore, do I?
I was just part of the Kotoura Bundle Pack for you anyway.
Shut your mouth and come on!
Hey hey hey—whoa! That hurts!
Stairs! Stairs!
So grit your teeth!
Wait, hadn't you already recovered?
Sure, until she came along.
Man up!
Honestly. I misjudged you.
I didn't believe you'd give up on Kotoura so easily.
What am I supposed to do?!
Her apartment was stripped bare,
and I can't reach her cell.
Not even the teachers can tell me where she moved or transferred.
I really tried my best, but I just can't keep it up.
Seriously, I've got nothing left.
I'm so pathetic, it's actually funny.
I don't even have a single picture of us together.
Is there really nothing left?
Not all the things we leave behind are tangible, after all.
What does that mean?
Oh, for crying out loud!
You should be asking yourself that question!
Manabe!
Well?
I'm surprised.
You're exactly right.
She walked into my life without warning.
We were together for all too short a time.
But in the end, she left me with something truly incredible.
What would that be?
That would be...
my blazing rage!
How dare that little vixen just up and leave me?!
I'll find her if it kills me,
and I will give her the soundest spanking of her life!
You really are a funny guy.
Huh?
Well said, Manabe!
The very words I was waiting for!
We, the ESP Society, shall sortie forth
to retrieve our lost Kotoura!
Yes!
Wait, retrieve her?
Yeah.
We've already worked out where she's most likely hiding.
What?!
Why so surprised?
I simply took a little peek at some data from train station security cameras.
I've all but pinned down Kotoura's escape route.
Um, isn't that a crime?
Wait. Forget I asked.
And so, this weekend's ESP Society activity will be field work!
Phew. It really took forever to get here.
The sun's already going down.
This place is totally dead.
Is Kotoura really here?
Yes.
There's no doubt that this station was her final stop.
All that's left is—
I-It's p-pretty cold for May.
I've been wondering for a while:
Why exactly didn't you bring a jacket?
When we set out, I was kind of counting on the flame of my passion to keep me warm.
Ask a stupid question...
So what do we do now?
We start asking around to see if we can deduce Kotoura's location.
Fortunately this isn't a big town.
Someone must have seen her.
Okay! Then let's rest up for tonight
and begin gathering info first thing tomorrow.
Right. Establishing a command post comes first.
So where are we staying?
Where are we staying?
You didn't make any reservations?
I thought that was your job!
A heck of a vice-president you are, Muroto, always screwing up right when it counts!
Says the president! The club's your responsibility!
Woah, guys, chill out.
You kids have no place to stay tonight?
Man, we're saved!
Can you believe this temple will let us crash for the night?
Pure dumb luck.
Next time, Muroto, do your job!
Yeah, yeah.
Ah, come on in.
The station attendant told me about you.
I can't offer much, but you're welcome to what I have.
Thank you very much!
At last I can take a breather.
We were swaying back and forth on that train all day.
You're both being rude.
Goodness no. Please do make yourselves at home.
So tell me, what brought you three out here?
It's sort of a club field trip.
Oh? What kind of club?
A secret society dedicated to proving the existence of psychic powers, and to protecting those who have them.
The ESP Research Society!
ESP, you say?
Oh boy do I love that kinda stuff!
Hail, fellow fanatic!
Shall we swap supernatural stories 'til sunup?
Abso-friggin'-lutely!
Oh-ho! You'll get no sleep tonight!
There's a reason why I took an interest in strange phenomena.
About ten years ago, I met a certain little girl.
Something evil has possessed my daughter!
Please, can't you exorcise it?
Here we are.
Please, come in.
Wow, check this out!
Are all these texts about the occult?
That girl's strange power was bringing her great pain.
I wanted to help her if I could,
but once I started collecting books I couldn't stop.
A girl with a power that brought her pain?
That sounds like...
What on Earth is it?!
Look at that!
At what?
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
Haruka, it isn't your fault.
Please don't blame yourself.
But sir, how can I get my parents and my friends to stay with me?
How can I get them to give me a smile?
I couldn't do anything for her.
But I feel better now. After all, you're her...
Why is she always shouldering everything herself?
You...
Please! Tell me where Kotoura is!
I promised I'd stay with her!
That no matter what happened, I wouldn't leave her!
And so help me, I will keep that promise!
Her family's home is on the other side of the mountain.
I'll show you the way tomorrow.
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Haruka, it looks like you found some truly good friends.
You won't get away this time, Kotoura!
Remember, we strike from behind and take her down!
The capture net is prepped.
Okay, let's practice until bathtime!
Truly... good... friends.
Once she's caught, let me tie her up.
Grandfather.
Um. Have you found a new school for me yet?
A new school?
You don't have to force yourself to go, you know.
No, I should at least do that much.
I'm causing you enough trouble as it is.
Don't worry. I'm looking.
I'm sorry to impose on you for so much.
You not only find me new schools,
you take care of all my rent and other living expenses.
I...
Don't worry your head about all that.
Just come sit on your grandpa's lap once in a while.
Welcome, dear granddaughter!
Look, I'm in high school now.
I forget things so easily these days...
Was I looking for... a school...?
If only I could feel my granddaughter's gentle touch,
I might be able to remember...
Fine.
Now, this brings back memories.
You really have grown up.
Grandfather.
Oh, Grandfather!
Oh, the transcendent touch of my granddaughter's ass!
The spoils of a long life are mine!
Are you actually cackling out loud?
You ought to know that I can hear your thoughts.
Sheesh, you're just like Manabe.
What?!
There's another despicably fortunate man capable of imagining you like this? What is this blasphemy?!
Please, Grandfather, just calm down.
My granddaughter's ass and thighs are mine!
All mine! No other man shall touch them!
Actually, you filthy old lecher, they're mine.
Right.
I can hardly believe there's actually a house here.
I can't even see any buildings from the gate.
How big is this place?
I guess she really is stinking rich.
These are precisely the kind of environs in which we're likely to find a Kotoura or two!
What is she, a cockroach?
Her grandfather says he'll see you.
But he seems to know you somehow, Manabe.
His exact words were, "Manabe's here?!"
Huh?
So, Zenzou, these are the friends of Haruka I told you about last night.
Yeah. Looks like they made it.
Is he mad at us?
Hurry up and apologize, Manabe.
Why do you assume it's my fault?
So you are this "Manabe"?
Yes sir, I am.
I'll ask you straight.
Exactly how have you been
molesting my granddaughter?!
By making her the star of all my lustful fantasies, and getting off on her embarrassment.
Oh, is that all?
You're still quite the novice, aren't you, boy?
Why, I experienced direct contact with her ass and thighs only just this morning!
Well I think there's a far more subtle pleasure in a face flushed with shame than in crass physical groping!
Oh, so your aesthetic tastes are so refined you don't even care
to feel for yourself the shape
of her tiny little breasts?
Of course I do!
Grandfather, I heard the head priest was... here...
Kotoura!
Get her!
Roger!
Wait!
Interesting bunch of kids.
They seem to be enjoying themselves.
Why? Why are they all here?
Wait!
Waaait!
I'm scared! I'm so scared!
Damnit, she gave us the slip!
We're in trouble. This house is too big.
We'll have to split up to hunt her down.
Come on! Why are you hiding from us?!
I'm sorry. I abandoned everything and ran away.
Now I'm too ashamed even to face you.
But what a relief. You look well.
Your injuries have healed.
I'd like to come out and talk,
but I'm sure you'd just get angry.
I'm sorry.
Kotoura, I'm sorry.
Why? It was my fault!
I couldn't... I couldn't protect you.
That's not true!
You did more than I ever deserved.
I promised that I'd stay with you.
That I'd never leave you no matter what.
No.
It's not about the promise!
I just want to be with you.
I just don't want to be apart!
I want to see you, Kotoura.
I've finally found you.
Please, let's go home. Let's be together.
Let's...
Kotoura!
Manabe. Manabe!
I want to see you.
I want to see you!
Mana—
Crap. Now I'm getting pissed again.
I guess I'll have to give her a spanking after all.
A spanking. A spanking! A spanking!
It's the only way to atone for making me worry so much!
But I am not without compassion.
How gently shall I stroke your swollen red buttocks!
Kotoura!
Gotchya!
Let me go!
No!
Now, how about you explain yourself?
Why did you just disappear like that?
Because you got hurt, and it was all my fault.
I thought if I left,
you could go back to your normal life.
Oh?
Hmm.
I see.
Are you stupid?
It's your fault I was attacked?
Don't give me that bull!
Besides, you already are my normal life!
In other words, you're saying you'd die without her?
That's not what I meant!
But she was just being so stupid, I had to say something.
I'm sorry. Please don't spank me.
So you did hear me!
And after I tried to fool you by being all serious!
Looks like this whole thing is Haruka's fault.
Grandfather.
But could you forgive her anyway?
She hasn't had friends in so long
that she just doesn't know how to interact with them.
That's why she tried to run away.
Still, it seems I can start the
re-enrollment process at your old school.
I'm not going back! I'm not!
I do apologize for leaving without saying anything.
But I can't let anyone else get hurt because of me.
Please just let me be.
Go, Manabe.
Just show her that noble martyrdom
doesn't move idiots.
Right!
Hold up!
Let me go!
No way.
If I leave you alone you'll just lock yourself up again
and wallow in your misery.
What choice do I have?
If people get hurt on my account, I...
What are you two doing?
Moritani?
What are you doing here, Manabe?
I should be asking you that!
What do you want with us?!
Just... just to apologize.
I had a detective track you down.
Moritani?
I'm sorry.
My stupid jealousy created this whole mess.
I was so blind, I even let Manabe be attacked.
What?!
Huh? You still didn't know?
That was your fault?!
Why didn't you tell him?
You really are too good to be true.
And precisely why would you have someone attack your classmate?
Are you into that stuff? A little deviant, aren't we?
Oh, shut up! That's why I'm standing here apologizing!
You haven't apologized!
Or rather, you apologized to her,
and then completely ignored me!
Isn't that how you treat me every day?!
Moritani did apologize, over and over.
Wh—
She just couldn't say it out loud because she didn't have the right words.
Please don't tell him that!
But it's just like she said.
How can I apologize to you after what I did?
When she left, and you started acting all weird,
I thought if I brought her back, I might be able to tell you I was sorry.
But you're here, now, and I... I...
Oh, screw it. You're just grossing me out.
It's okay. It's okay!
He's such an awful person, isn't he?
Absolutely despicable. The most contemptible man alive.
Wait, how am I the bad guy now?
Don't let it bother you, Moritani. Okay?
Wasn't I the victim?
Separated
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It's funny. I came for forgiveness.
How did I wind up leaving in tears?
Pretty pathetic, huh?
So while I'm embarrassing myself, let me say this:
You've helped me see myself so much more clearly.
I think I can change now.
Thank you, Kotoura.
How do you stand again when something trips you up?
Why did she come here anyway?
She thanked me.
Then she said, "I'll see you at school."
Can truth be found by thinking about the days to come?
Kotoura!
I want to go home.
With you, and with everyone.
We all come into this world alone when we are born,
Yeah! We're going home!
Yes!
H-Hey! Manabe-kun!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah...!
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Geez!
I guess I was thinking like a child.
I thought I could understand people's hearts
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
just because I could hear their thoughts.
But people can change.
Something that simple never even occurred to me.
and I embrace it with all my heart
I had turned my back on the world. On myself.
So that in all things around us the flower of hope may bloom,
I was a hopeless coward, trapped in my own misery.
we start our days together here
But now I believe I can change, however slowly.
We start our days together here
Change myself, and change my world.
Because I'm not alone anymore.
After all that,
it looks like we got everything back to normal.
That's not true.
No matter how little,
things have changed.
Ungh!
Oh!
Hi-yah!
Eep!
Fwap!
Eek!
Fwa-fwap!
No!
What is this? Seeing Kotoura cowering before my spanking is sexier than I can bear!
Something's seriously wrong with you, lecher!
Episode 5
School Paradise?