Looks like the first piece
will be moving soon.
Question: do you desire the
destruction of the Imanity?
Or have you finally decided to act?
Spying on people isn't a very
commendable hobby, you know.
Question: an event fluctuation was detected
just before the new Imanity king was crowned.
We assume this heralds your intent
to join the battle: yes or no?
You guys are so boring.
The fallen gods,
first in the ranks of
the Exceed: the Old Deus.
I'm on no one's side.
So you can keep playing
your idle games.
They're on their way.
And they're heading
straight for the top.
There was a time when I thought
that those two could save Elkia.
...But now...
Ever since they took the throne, they've dumped
all the work on me and the ministers,
and now they spend
all day playing games.
We're moving.
If you need something done, ask Steph.
...Today's the day...
Sora and Shiro's House
Today's the day I put a stop to this!
...Hi—
mawaritsuzukeru haguruma ni wa narisagaranai
I never wanted to become just another cog in the machine
heikin enjiru kanjou kara hajimatta jigoku
My life had become hell because I was pretending to be average
asobihanbun de kami ga michibiita
But then God frivolously took me to a new stage
danjou no sekai no no no game no life
To the world of no game no life
nurui heion wo bassari kirisutete
Where I can do away with my boring everyday life
eikou e no kaidan ni sonzai kizamunda
And engrave my name on the stairway to glory
me ni utsuru no wa kanzen shouri no unmei
I now see a destiny of flawless victory for myself
nani mo kamo keisan doori kaete yaru
I'll change everything precisely the way I want
somaranai kuuhaku de
As an untainted blank
riaru made ni kyuusai nante iranai
I no longer care about salvation in my real life
donna michi osotte mo kateba ii dake no hanashi nara
I don't know what the future holds, but if all that matters is to win
kakehiki to sainou ga muhai izanau
Then I'll put my strategy and talent to work and stay undefeated
umarenaoshita inochi de tanoshimu sa
I'm enjoying my new life to the fullest
jibun dake wa jibun shinjiteru
Believing in myself
Hi-yah!
My eyes! My eyes!
Wake up, you two.
Weak Square
It's time for you to
do your jobs as rulers.
Weak Square
How could this happen? This room was
perfectly shielded from the morning sunlight!
Weak Square
It's already afternoon.
It's 36:00. The middle of the night.
What kind of clock do you follow?!
And look, you've left these
precious books all over the place.
Go ahead and take them
back to your grandpa's room.
It's your room now.
That's been the king's room for
generations. You can't just move out!
The bed's tilted, though.
It's hard to sleep on.
Can't beat the humble futon.
What are you going back to sleep for?
It's mortifying to think that you have the
lives of three million Imanity in your hands!
Mortifying?
If that's how you see it, sure.
That's just your opinion.
But be it our old world or any other,
never will Blank take up work!
Don't underestimate humanity!
Humanity
I'd rather see humanity die out
than grow as lazy as you two!
My patience has
finally reached its limits!
Sora!
I challenge you!
So you want to play a game with me?
Th-That's right.
Commandment Five:
The challenged party has the right
to decide how the game is played.
Commandment Five:
The challenged party has the right
to decide how the game is played.
Commandment five: The challenged party
has the right to decide how the game is played.
Are you sure?
...Yes...
B-But I'm sure that the best gamer in the history of
mankind wouldn't need to deliberately pick a game
that gives him an advantage
over someone like me, right?
Fine.
Pick whichever game you'd like.
So what are we wagering?
If I win, you'll become a decent person!
Decent Person
...U-Um...
Of course!
The ten commandments are absolute!
Such wishes are well within their capability!
...Then...
Please, Steph!
Don't make me a decent person.
Make me popular!
Popular?
Who cares about
being decent? I want girls!
Let's do it right now!
I'll do everything I can to lose!
You're not allowed to
lose to anyone except me.
Sis, would you stand between
your brother and popularity?!
Blank must never lose.
No!
There's no way I could possibly
lose to Steph fair and square.
Hey!
Steph!
Y-Yes?!
I'll bet on the one-in-a-million chance—
no, the chance that can only be described
with imaginary numbers—that you'll win!
Now you've done it.
...The game we'll play is...
Blackjack?
How about I be the dealer,
and you be the player?
What's with that despairing sigh?
And she's not even
interested anymore!
Look, blackjack is
purely a game of chance!
Your tricks and cheating
won't help you here!
Now get ready! Aschente!
Aschente.
You fell for it.
A game of chance?
Not if I can help it.
After all, it's okay to cheat
as long as you're not found out.
I've been practicing
this trick in secret!
Today's the day I knock
you down a peg or two!
My granddaughter, the weak must
use their wisdom to defeat the strong.
That's the hope of humanity.
...Humanity... Humanity...
This is humanity's true potential, which my
grandfather believed in and Sora showed me!
Hit.
Stand.
Twenty-one.
Nineteen.
I'm just getting started.
Okay. This is the final round.
I think we know who's
going to win, though.
Blackjack is one of the few casino games
where the player has an advantage.
What do you mean?
Player
Dealer
The dealer has to draw another card
whenever she's below seventeen,
so she has a high chance of going bust.
But that hasn't happened once to you.
Pretty impressive luck.
Stand.
Has he just given up?
He didn't even look at his cards.
Looks like the game's over.
Yeah, it's over all right.
With a natural blackjack, you get back
two and a half times what you bet.
I win.
...No...
...Humanity's true potential...
...Steph, my granddaughter...
Grandfather!
However, if you should face
another human, I guess you're screwed.
...Screwed... Screwed...
...Wha— Grandfather?!
Grandfather!
What a hollow victory.
Popular people are just
an urban legend anyway.
I refuse to accept this!
How did I lose?
Oh? Didn't you say blackjack
was purely a game of chance?
Card counting.
Card coun— What is that?
You count the cards
according to their face value.
Cards between two and six are +1,
ten and above are -1,
and seven through nine are 0.
You tally up the cards that
have already been played
to mathematically determine the
probability of what will be played next.
So you used math to win a game?
Scales
I didn't know that was possible.
Wait, isn't that cheating?
No. Cheating would be, for instance,
that false shuffle you were doing.
You noticed?
It made counting much easier.
He used my own trick to beat me?
Whoa, where are you going?
Back to work.
Remember those policies
you proposed yesterday?
I have to meet with the
nobles who oppose them now.
That took longer than I thought.
I guess I'll go act like
a king for once, then.
I'll get you for this!
Don't think you can get away
with such tyranny against nobles!
Former nobles.
Your titles, your land,
...your money, your holdings...
You lost them all.
Well, after a quick reformation like this,
people like them were bound to show up.
If anything, I'm surprised
it took this long.
Still, the way you dealt
with them was just mean.
I'd worked so hard to keep them
under control peacefully.
Huh? Keep them under control?
I used data from the large-scale experiments we'd
conducted on the lands belonging to the royal family
to distribute the commercial rights to
the major noble factions that backed us.
I used those successes to keep
the other major nobles in check
and quietly split off the smaller groups to
slowly whittle down the power of the opposition.
If I'd won over those last
few guys that showed up,
we could've had a complete, bloodless
victory over the entire opposition.
Wait, what's wrong?
I-I didn't think this was possible,
...but Steph, are you actually...
not an idiot?
What did you think I was?!
But you're a Steph. A total Steph!
Have you turned my name into a
derogatory term, or am I imagining it?
Am I imagining it?!
Shut up. What would
a Steph like you know?
That is possibly the most
unfair insult in history!
I'll have you know I graduated top of my class
from the most prestigious academy in the country,
and I have connections with every
major family through my former classmates.
She graduated high school
...and has lots of friends...
And when you think about it,
...she's a princess, and a rich one at that...
...And she has big boobs...
S-Sora? Shiro?
We didn't decide what we were going to
make you do for that last game, did we?
We're doing it now, Steph. No mercy.
...W-Wait—
No!
Th-There are t-too many people!
Shiro, no matter what,
don't let go of my hand!
D-Don't let go of me either!
It was your idea to come to
town, Sora. What's going on?
W-We've got something
we need to do.
Wait, why is everyone
looking at us funny?
...Probably because...
You made me wear this!
Why wouldn't they be?!
Wow.
Couldn't you have come up with
something a bit more reasonable?
Steph, paw.
Woof!
I can't disobey!
That's the rule.
As per the commandments,
you're our dog for the day.
She's a Dog for a Day
True, your outfit is unusual,
but they seem more scared
than anything else.
That's because the rulers of Elkia are walking
around with someone dressed as a Werebeast, woof!
Hold on.
You're dressed like a Werebeast?
"Ranked fourteenth among the Exceed,
they hail from the Eastern Federation,
one of the three largest nations.
They possess enhanced
senses and physical abilities,
as well as a sixth sense that
!allows them to read minds!"
In other words,
...the Eastern Federation...
is an Eden composed entirely
of hot girls with animal ears?!
...No, there are men and elders too...
Okay! That's it! That Arcadia is mine!
We're going after the animal girls!
...Right...
now.
Wait! They're one of the three
biggest countries in the world!
Take control of the animal girl kingdom #conquesttime
Silence!
You and your false ears shall not stand
between me and the real deal!
The animal girl kingdom
is waiting for me.
...Before that...
Oh, right.
Okay, let's go.
Let's.
...Wait a sec—
You're leaving me here?
We haven't found anything.
This country is weird.
That's for sure.
These aren't that good.
There's a shortage
of goods like sugar.
So Steph's cookies were good because she
was able to make the best of what she had.
Found you!
Oh, Steph.
Where did you go?
"Oh"? You serious? "Oh"?!
You made me dress as a dog, tied me up
in the middle of town, and forgot about me?!
Forgive me, Steph.
Sit.
You tell me to forgive you then order
me to sit? That's basically brute force!
This is no good.
I need to do something
about these two.
But if I'm going to
beat them in a game,
it needs to be a game
that really is pure chance,
where not even math plays a part.
...So...
Sora! One more game!
Beg.
Seriously? What are we wagering now?
For the sake of the country,
I'll wager the same thing I did this morning,
and make you popular!
...Steph, I knew you'd—
I will accept on behalf of Blank.
If you lose, you must
follow one order of mine.
...No, Sis, don't...
That's fine.
For our game,
we'll take turns guessing whether the
next person to pass by is male or female!
Best out of ten.
Aschente!
Aschente (I swear by the commandments)
vs
This doesn't make sense!
Did you really think people randomly wander
down the street with no purpose in mind?
Shiro applied the data on
time-based sex ratios, occupations,
and employment rate for this area
to the general trends I observed.
Victory.
Do you always take
these things so seriously?
What a silly question.
...When it comes to games...
We're always serious.
And so,
I'm taking your panties.
I'm really ruined
forever now, aren't I?
Hey, Shiro.
This is actually kinda disturbing.
I'm only eleven years old.
I'm just a kid,
so I don't understand.
You seem like you're in a bad mood,
what with how badly
you're treating Steph.
I am not.
I'm just getting started!
You've seen nothing yet!
I think we've seen
more than enough already.
Here I go!
Aschente (I swear by the commandments)
Aschente!
Ghost Leg
And she bet...
Her shawl
Super-Spicy Russian Takoyaki Roulette
And she bet...
Her shoes
The Game of Life
And she bet...
Her bra
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
And she bet...
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
And she bet...
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Rock-
Paper-
Scissors
Glasses Steph with Animal Ears
Glasses
O-One more... one more game!
You don't have much left to lose.
A temporary defeat is nothing
if it leads to ultimate victory!
I'm starting to understand
how Elkia got screwed over so badly.
This time it'll be pure,
one-hundred-percent chance!
How many seconds
before those birds take off?
Fine. I'll let you go first.
Aschente.
How many seconds?
Aschente... Okay, thirty seconds!
I'll say... three seconds!
Hey! That's against the rules!
You never set any rules, did you?
Steph, give it up.
Why?
Why can't I win?
I'm doing this for Elkia,
...for the Imanity...
Why can't I even win by chance?
...Steph...
There is no such thing
as luck in this world.
Rules, prerequisites,
...psychological states...
There are any number of invisible factors that combine
to produce an unpredictable but inevitable result.
The winner of each game is
decided before it even begins.
Chance is never a factor.
For example,
what's the probability of drawing the
ace of spades from a deck with no jokers?
It's one in fifty-two, right?
You'd think so, yes.
Brand
New
But what if it's a brand new deck?
Brand
New
The cards in a new deck are
generally arranged in a preset order.
Brand
New
If you take out the jokers
...and draw the very bottom card...
it'll be the ace of spades
almost every time.
...B-But...
Yeah, I didn't say anything
about it being a new deck,
so you'd have no way
of knowing, right?
That knowledge changes the
probability from 1.92% to 100%.
Basically, the person with that
knowledge is the inevitable victor.
That's why you and
the Imanity keep losing,
and why we're at a
loss as to what to do.
At a loss?
We don't have enough information.
Before we can invade
the animal girl kingdom,
we've gotta deal with the fact
that we don't know their weakness.
All we know is that they've
got a sharp sixth sense.
They can read minds.
If that's true, then bluffs
and strategy are useless.
It's not even a game anymore.
I've read every book and paper
in the palace and found nothing,
and there's not a single
bookstore or library in this town.
Does this nation even care?
Has he been looking for information
about this world ever since he was coronated?
Only an idiot starts
a fight they can't win.
But we have to do something
or we'll get nowhere!
Even if it means sacrificing ourselves, we need
to do what we can for Elkia as soon as possible!
One screw-up and it's all over.
This country, and the Imanity
themselves, are on their last legs.
Don't forget that.
They weren't just playing
around without thinking.
They were taking the lives of three
...million Imanity onto their shoulders...
and I didn't even realize it.
Well, I guess you were able to keep things
from breaking down completely, Steph.
I was wondering why there was
so little resistance to our reforms.
I guess you were keeping it in check.
You're a smart girl, Steph.
That really helped us out.
Thanks.
Sora! Shiro!
...Well, you know...
I hope we can keep
working together, Steph.
Right! I agree, woof!
But that doesn't change
the fact that we're stuck,
and we lack the key to the
one door out that I can see.
What? It got dark all of a sudden.
Wow.
Laputa really exists!
That's Avant Heim,
one of the Phantasma.
The second-ranked Exceed?
Phantasma:
Exceed Rank 2
How the hell am I supposed
to play a game with that?
Brother, look up there.
Yeah, the best thing would be to bring those
...Flugel in that flying city around to our side...
But how do we get there?
Balse!
*
It didn't fall.
The servers here are
better than in our world.
If you're looking for a Flugel,
there's one near here.
About five years ago, it showed up
in the National Elkia Library.
It beat my grandfather in a game and
won the library, along with everything in it.
Oh, you had a library?
You bet your knowledge?
Are you retarded?!
That's humanity's only weapon!
Steph, sit.
Stay.
No, please! People are watching!
The Flugel.
Ranked sixth among the Exceed.
Created during the ancient war as a
front-line weapon designed to kill gods.
I can't believe there was one so close.
Sora, are you really going to
challenge a monster like that?
That god-slayer's worldly
knowledge is the only lead we have.
You don't have to come
if you don't want to.
dare ni mo mienai
With a loneliness
I-I'm coming!
Steph, the Flugel traditionally
only play one game, right?
kodoku wo kakaeta mama hitori de naiteta
That no one else could see, I was crying all alone
Yes, according to records.
dare ni mo jouzu ni waraenai bokura
We could never bring ourselves to smile
That's fine.
Well, then.
It's time to start
conquering the world.
futari deatte waratta
But the moment we met, we smiled
mayonaka sugi ni souzou no oku ni
In the dead of the night, we delved into our imagination
dou shiyou mo nai kimochi wo tada oshieatte
And shared all the feelings we didn't know what to do with
sayonara bokura kitto umarekawareru kara
"We'll be starting our life anew, so farewell"
kanashimi ni te wo furu deshou
We waved goodbye to sadness
soshite itsuka
And someday
karappo no mama no kokoro ni akari wo tomosu you ni
We'll light up our empty hearts
togire togire no kotoba wo sagashite tsunagitometa
By piecing together the fragments of expressions we find
sore demo tatta futari no sekai wa tsuzuitekun da
Our own little world will never end
sora ni inoru you ni
Like we're praying to the sky
tobou eien ni
Let's soar high into eternity
Wow.
Now, where's our angel?
I take it back. She's no angel at all.
...She's...
death itself.
Excusing me, persons in there!
What do you wanting in my's library?
...Oh...
That ruined it.
Interesting
Death should not have taken thee, Steph.