Home at last...
Hey, Waver!
What are you looking at?
Over here!
G-Grandpa?
What's going on?
Never mind that...
Come on up.
I wanna talk to you.
Why does it have to be on the roof again?
Grandpa, could we talk later?
Oh, come on...
He likes you, boy.
That's just because I hypnotized him—
Oh, go on...
That old fellow seems like
he really wants to talk.
I'll hang around and keep
an eye on things, so relax.
No need to be shy.
It's not about being shy...
This here...
...is the best spot to watch the sun rise.
Have a seat.
I made coffee,
so warm yourself up.
Grandpa, how long have you been up here?
I woke up early in the morning
and you still hadn't come home,
so I thought I'd watch the sky
and wait for my grandson to come home.
We used to stargaze
this way all the time when you were little...
Do you remember?
Yeah, I do.
When Martha and I decided to live in Japan,
we built our house here on Miyama Hill
and made sure to include a skylight
that allowed access to the roof.
And all so we could sit out here,
like we're doing now.
That was our old dream, to stargaze on the roof,
next to our grandchildren.
Never thought it'd come true, though.
Our real grandchildren
never once came up here with me.
I've always watched the stars all by myself.
Waver...
You aren't our real grandson, are you?
I'm not exactly sure why
Martha and I were so convinced you were.
Honestly, you've always been a bit
too nice to be one of ours.
Are you angry?
I guess I have the right to be.
But lately, I've been seeing
Martha smiling cheerfully.
I never would've imagined it.
Honestly, I'm grateful to you two.
Besides, I can tell from the look of you
that you don't mean us any harm by living here.
How about it?
I'd like it if you could stick
around for a while longer.
I'm sorry...
But I can't promise that.
There's no guarantee I'll even
make it back alive again.
So, the two of you are risking your lives?
Yes.
Well, I don't know what
could be so important
that you'd be willing to die for it.
But when you've lived as long as I have,
and you take a moment to consider your life,
you realize that really, nothing out
there is worth more than it.
Enzousan
Forty hours since I last slept.
To win the war and call forth the Grail,
the ceremony must be
performed at one of Fuyuki's
four major spiritual ley lines.
Two of them
are the Tohsaka estate and
the Fuyuki City church,
and there was no sign of Kotomine Kirei at either.
That leaves two places.
Enzousan and the Fuyuki City civic center.
In terms of spiritual energy,
this location is the obvious choice.
On the off-chance he selects the civic center,
I need only mount a direct assault.
If Maiya were still alive,
I'd have stationed her there.
But I'm alone again.
Actually,
I've never thought to count her.
Since last night, I have scoured
every inch of the city,
looking for Irisviel.
But I have found nothing.
I am very sorry.
Should anything happen,
please summon me
with the Command Spells, as you did before.
Woman.
Can you hear me, woman?
Kotomine Kirei...
This is the place where
Caster's Master once hid.
Emiya Kiritsugu never managed to find it.
The Holy Grail War will soon be over.
It appears that I will be given the opportunity
to grant the Einzbern family wish.
Are you upset that it would be me?
I would only relinquish the
Holy Grail to one man...
And that is not you, Executor.
Emiya Kiritsugu sees right through you.
He knows you are the opponent to fear most.
Be ready.
That is good news indeed.
Emiya Kiritsugu is exactly
the man I thought him to be.
Ridiculous...
You are further from him than anyone.
What was that?
Kiritsugu can see through you,
but you can never say the same.
Your heart has none of the things
that he carries within his.
Why do you speak about me?
I admit it...
I am an empty man.
How are he and I different?
He's subjected himself to fighting endless,
pointless battles,
doing nothing but slaughtering
others again and again...
To live so aimlessly, wasting so much!
What are we, if not lost?!
Tell me...
What will Emiya Kiritsugu
ask of the Holy Grail?
What wish will he entrust to the
sole device that can grant it?
Fine...
I'll tell you.
Emiya Kiritsugu's wish
is for humanity's salvation.
An end to war and bloodshed.
Forever.
World peace.
What is that?
You will never understand.
And that is how you two differ...
He has convictions.
Human nature is conflict.
To reject that is to reject humanity itself.
It is a baseless ideal.
Like the idle wish of a child!
And that is why he knows
only a miracle can make it happen.
He's been forced to discard
everyone he's ever loved,
in order to make his ideals reality...
That's right...
Kiritsugu is too kind for his ideals.
Even though he knows he will lose them,
he cannot stop loving others...
I understand.
I understand completely.
So that is who Emiya Kiritsugu is.
Finally, I have a reason to fight!
Emiya Kiritsugu...
I shall destroy
the Holy Grail before your eyes.
And with it, your ideals.
Oh, you're awake, boy?
I told you to wake me at nightfall.
What are you doing?
Sorry, sorry.
I thought tonight we'd be better off
staying calm and fully preparing ourselves.
How come?
It's just a feeling.
But my gut says that everything
will be decided tonight.
Yeah, the night air feels too still.
Is it because there are fewer of us left?
From here on out, it will be only
the powerful adversaries.
W-What was that?
A strange mana burst.
I've felt something similar before.
That pattern...
What is it?
Some manner of code?
Four of one color, seven of another...
"Achieved" and "victory."
The signal is pretty clear...
Does that mean the Holy Grail
War's already been decided?
No, the church is in the complete opposite direction.
Then the church didn't fire those...
Sounds to me
like someone's getting ahead of themselves.
"If you don't like it,
show yourself."
We're being challenged.
This is the beginning of the end.
Yeah...
So, this is it.
Indeed!
Now...
If our battlefield has been decided,
I must comport myself so as not to
bring shame upon the Rider class!
Come forth,
my faithful steed!
Okay, boy.
It will be a rougher ride than the chariot...
What are you waiting for?
Get on.
Only the powerful can continue...
My Servant...
I, Waver Velvet, order you
with this Command Spell...
Rider, you must be victorious.
With this Command Spell, I order you...
Rider, you must obtain the Holy Grail.
And by my Command Spell, I order you...
Rider, you must conquer this world.
Failure will not be tolerated.
There, I'm no longer your Master.
Get moving.
Go wherever you please.
You're just...
I shall go in a moment.
But after issuing all those long-winded orders,
surely you're prepared to watch
me carry them out.
No, no, no, you idiot!
Look, I have no Command Spells.
I quit being a Master!
Why would you take me?
I...
You may no longer be my Master,
but you are certainly my friend.
I-I am...
You really don't mind a kid like me?
You'd let me come with you?
After all the battles we have fought
together, how can you ask that?
Idiot.
We have faced every enemy as partners.
You are my friend!
Stand tall, and consider yourself
my equal.
Now then, I shall begin with your first order.
Watch closely and I shall fulfill it!
Go get them...
I'll be watching!
He chose the worst possible
site for the ceremony,
to control when and where
the fights commence.
In other words, he doesn't
want the Holy Grail.
He wants to use it as bait, to lure and kill
the other Masters and me.
That makes things simple.
If that's the best he can come up with,
I must make it quick.
Kotomine Kirei...
You do look especially ferocious tonight,
Kirei.
What do you plan?
Shall I stay here and wait?
Unleashing your power at close range
would put the ceremony at risk.
If you wish to fight at full strength,
then go out and welcome them.
Very well.
But what if you're attacked while I'm away?
I will summon you with a Command Spell,
if you would indulge me.
That would be fine.
But I make no guarantees
for the Grail's safety.
Tonight, I shall not hold back.
That is the worst-case scenario,
but if it happens, then that is fate.
Kirei, you seem to have found
your reason to fight.
Even so, have you still no
prayer to offer the Grail?
No, I cannot think of anything.
If forced, I would say I wish for no one
to interfere with this fight.
Really, now...
As I thought, the only thing to do
is to let the Grail draw out
what you have hidden in your heart.
If it seems that Saber will
arrive before I return,
let Berserker keep her occupied.
Understood.
Speaking of Saber,
what became of the puppet she
protected so desperately?
Is not the Holy Grail's vessel inside of it?
I killed her.
There was no reason to let her live.
Are you crying,
Mother?
Mother, I had a bad dream.
I dreamed I turned into a cup...
And inside me
were these big lumps, seven of them...
It's okay, it's okay...
I'll never let that happen.
I promise that it won't happen, Ilya.
I know that you'll be freed
from the bonds of fate.
Where...
Inside the Holy Grail?
It can't be!
Then...
Who am I here?
Of course...
I'm inside the Holy Grail.
The omnipotent wish-granting artifact that
will wash away the world's sorrows,
and end its suffering.
I will have the power to
make that all come true.
The end...
is close at hand.
Episode 22:
All the Evil in the World
Our opponent is the mighty
King of Heroes,
a truly worthy foe.
Let us show him where our
path of conquest leads!
King of Conquerors, I shall wake
you from your endless dream.
I shall see to it personally.
Next Time:
The Ocean at the End of the World