7th Street
Lovers' Midnight Dash
Let us compare love to Western food.
Love is like a napolitan.
An ordinary dish, but everyone has their own special preferences.
Love is like a rice omelette.
You find yourself captivated by the outer layer of egg,
but you musn't make light of the chicken and rice underneath.
Love is like curry.
It’s almost as if both become sweeter with age.
What a disgusting sight.
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Lover's Elopement (From Vol. 1 Ch. 5)
Here's today's blood type fortune!
Type As are number one today.
If you take a little trip, you might close the gap between you and your beloved!
Where the hell am I supposed to go on a weekday?
Later, dad.
So now you've started talking back to the TV.
Going senile already, huh?
I wasn't even paying attention to it, cue-ball.
You've got some balls calling your own dad a cue-ball!
Besides, crab for breakfast? Are you serious?
Crab first thing in the morning is one of life's little nuggets of joy.
How the heck does crab and bread count as a nugget of joy?
I think I just invented crab bread!
Oh, it's just you, Arashiyama.
How come you look so disheveled?
Morning...
Normally you barely make it on time,
but you're awful early today.
I was late by a hair yesterday.
I'm gonna be late 'cause the stupid bus caught every red light!
Well, no shit!
Maybe I should just give up.
Don't give up, Arashiyama. Let's make one last sprint!
Wajima...
Isawa.
Here.
Mori.
Yamakawa.
Present.
Wajima.
Here!
Please be seated.
Safe!
Arashiyama, you're late.
Go stand in the hall until homeroom's over.
No way! That's so not fair!
Wajima was only safe ‘cause the thing’s sorted alphabetically.
Our last names are the difference between heaven and hell!
If my name was Warashiyama, I would have been safe.
Boo-hoo...
Hoo... what hoorible luck.
Ba-dum-tish!
If you won't take this seriously, I'll mark you absent.
Whaaaat!?
So that's why you got up early today.
That's admirable of you.
No, that's not it.
I was up all night finishing this.
Another detective novel, huh?
You can borrow it.
So, who's the culprit?
The wife.
Nevermind.
Who cares who did it?
It's really good so just read it!
She's acting like a drunk person.
Thank God!
Thank you so much, God!
The next stop is Oya High School.
How cruel!
Neither God nor the Buddha exist in this world!
Such supreme bliss...
Why must I suffer the torture of ending it with a single push of my finger!?
Here's today's blood type fortune!
Type As are number one today.
If you take a little trip, you might close the gap between you and your beloved!
A true man wouldn't get off of this bus!
I'll stay on ‘til the bitter end!
Umm, where are we?
End of the line.
I gained 2 kilos in one day.
Aw, crud! First period's already started.
S-Sorry about that.
I uh... dozed off as well.
Doesn't the bus just go round 'n round in circles all day?
I thought so too, but I guess not.
Our world holds lots of secrets.
Next bus arrives in about... 20 minutes.
Even if we hurried, second period would already be half over.
Sure is nice out.
We don't have gym class today, right?
Kind of a waste being cooped up in the classroom all day.
Why don't we just take the day off?
Just kidding.
You think so?
Eating ramen after barbecue makes your tummy hurt.
It's a whole new town!
She sure changes gears quickly.
Yeah, there are people living outside our tiny little reality too.
It's a strangely comforting, but vexing feeling...
Right?
Yeah...
Okay! Let's blaze a trail, Sanada!
You sure are excited.
Oh, sorry about that.
I have two really young siblings, so it's just a habit.
You don't wanna?
Don't be silly!
There's not a single particle of me that doesn't want to!
But!
A high school girl holding hands with just anyone is kind of...
Well, it's not like I don't get to pick whose hand I hold.
I, Hiroyuki Sanada, am truly proud to have been chosen!
Thank you so much for all your support!
5 seconds
20 seconds
35 seconds
I can't hold on anymore!
This has exhausted my lifetime's remaining happy reserves!
Hey, there's a river!
It's the Tamakawa!
You think if we follow the river, we can get home?
Yeah, but your legs will be worn down to stumps by then.
We're actually cutting class...
Don't start regretting it now.
Once in a while doesn't hurt.
Yeah, you're right.
School isn't the only important thing in life, right?
But what if I get called into the teacher's lounge tomorrow?
We're partners in crime.
If you get called in, then so will I.
Feels like it's been forever since we played together like this.
Yeah...
We used to play all the time as kids.
I wonder why we stopped...
Huh?
You don't remember?
It's ‘cause you said,
Who wants to play with a stupid girl?
…remember?
I think I do.
I'm really sorry.
It's not that big of a deal.
I was going to tell you one of these days, anyway.
I'm home.
Don't wanna forget that emotional rollercoaster today,
so I guess I oughta put it in my diary.
Umm, today... today, I...
Today, I skipped school with Arashiyama and we hung out.
Huh? Was that all?
‘Guess I'll read a bit to improve my vocabulary.
I already know the culprit, though.
1/4 Bloodlust
Let us compare love to drinks.
Love is like a delicious blend...
Its bitterness can lead to sleepless nights,
yet it also grants us irresistible comfort and tranquility.
Arashiyama, a cup of cold coffee please.
Hmm?
And it's recipe contains misunderstandings and false assumptions.
Hey, who the heck's Cuprice?
Did you somehow forget your childhood friend's name!?
J-Just calm down, Arashiyama! I said a cup of cold coff-
And I said who the heck is that?
You sure have an old fashioned way of speaking, Sanada.
GET OUT!
I used to be quite the troublemaker way back when.
Night Walker (From Vol. 2 Ch. 16)
Can't sleep...
I bet it's ‘cause of that.
A little early, but I think I'll visit the potty and call it a night.
It's a ghost!
That's awfully considerate of you to muffle your scream like that.
Oh, it's just Takeru.
What are you doing up so late?
Good little boys go to bed at 9 and get up at 6.
I can't sleep.
If I could, why would I go to your stupid room?
What the heck is that supposed to mean?
This is partially your fault too, sis.
4 hours ago
Hey, have you seen a bottle of about this size?
I'm need it for a project.
Here.
Relieves muscle tension and replenishes vital nutrients: Napovitan C!
There should be an empty bottle in there, though...
It had a pretty wicked taste,
but I didn't wanna waste it, so I drank the rest.
And I'm still wide awake.
Half is plenty for me, but for someone your age to down the whole thing...
But thanks to that, I was able to make a really cool castle.
All right, fine.
How about a half-hour stroll to diffuse all that extra energy?
Really? For real?
Is it cool? Totally cool?
Aren't you just a wee bit excited?
Well, late night to a kid is like evening time for me.
I'll give you a shoulder to cry on.
How come we're going out the back door?
The front door has a chime, so mom would hear us.
What's with the backpack?
Travel preparations.
All the strong monsters come out at night!
Where’s that from? A game or something?
Safety's about all this town has going for it.
Huh? Seaside's still lit up.
Are they still open?
You don't wanna go near there at night.
Look.
It becomes a hangout for seedy middle-aged guys.
Please don't grow up to be like them.
But they look like they're having fun.
When I grow up, mom said I should be a lawyer so I can defend you-
I'll be just fine, thank you!
Carbonation makes me feel a little warm and fuzzy inside.
Wow, the market's almost a ghost town!
Now then, where to?
Sanada Fresh Fish
He's still awake, huh?
Maybe I'll recruit him as a bodyguard.
Huh? Rats, I forgot my phone.
Hey sis...
Oh, you got something handy in there?
Looks like nothing but junk.
S.S.
Ess ess?
Here you go.
What am I supposed to do with these?
That's not it?
There's nothing else that looks like S.S., though.
Jeez, I'll get it myself!
S.S. is short for “slingshot”, duh.
How would I know, stupid?
Go tell them that at the panchinko joint!
The season's over, so I've only got two D.D. left.
D.D.... Dehesa duds, huh?
I get the idea now.
Grade schoolers are so simple-minded.
I missed! There goes my precious acorn.
Don't you mean D.D.?
If you pull too hard, it'll break!
I swear I can hear people outside...
All right, who's the dead man?
Come out and take your licks!
Oh, crap! He's gone from  self-defense to offense.
One word can totally change the meaning!
If you’d just apologize, he'd probably forgive you.
Those eyes don't give the impression that he'd be willing to talk!
Yeah, but I think Sanada likes-
Ah, nevermind.
What'd you say?
Oh, nothing.
I'll apologize to him next year.
You hungry, Takeru?
Yeah, I guess, now that you mention it.
Maybe by the station...
Nah, I don't wanna teach you bad habits like that.
Well, there is a ramen stand by the station.
Wow, this late at night? No way!
Doesn't take much to amuse you.
I’m so sweepy, my eyes are spinning.
Ah, but I wonder if that'll make me fat...
My tummy's telling me a little bit is okay.
Oh, Hotori!
What are you doing out at this time of night?
Did you just mention a delinquent's name?
Well, pops?
N-No, I didn't say anything!
Just "these noodles are taking a really long time!" is all.
See?
"These noodles are taking a long time...”
What part of that includes Hotori?
That was such a lame excuse!
Oh good, just my imagination.
‘Thought I'd almost caught her.
Why the heck is he having ramen!?
Cops should just be chased off with fish cake scraps!
Don't you dare get caught before I find you!
What, no comeback?
Who am I, Lupin?
Sis looks pretty upset.
Can't hear a thing. Must really not be there.
I have a feeling that I'll bust you one of these days.
Takeru, maybe I'd like you to become a lawyer after all.
Green-Mart
Convenience Store
I guess convenience stores are the only sure places we could go to, huh?
That's where the youngsters tend to gather.
It's pitch black outside the store!
Yet again, the weirdest things amaze you.
Well, it's true that normally you don't go out after dinner.
This is a midnight reminder from Yamamura Cameras.
Takeru.
It is now the 1st of May.
Night Head Radio is brought to you commercial-free by "Amigo Kirihara".
Huh? Midnight, as in zero o'clock?
Yup. That's right.
Zero o'clock?
Zero o'clock!?
Zero means nothing, so how can it be a time?
I'm scared!
Just mere seconds ago, it was April 30th,
but now it's May 1st.
You've just crossed the gap between yesterday and today.
Whaaaat!?
It was just tomorrow, but now it's today...
It was just today, but now it's yesterday...
Yup. You've just witnessed firsthand one of the world's secrets.
I wonder when it was I first watched the date change.
Wish I had written it down or something.
Make sure you put your shoes back by the entrance, or we'll get caught.
Ah, right!
It was colder out there than I thought.
Since we're cold, we should hop in the bath.
And just cover it with a towel...
Think you can sleep now?
Probably.
Hey, sis?
Hmm?
You sneak out at night pretty often, don't you?
W-What makes you say that?
You know quite a few tricks to not getting caught.
Today wasn't the first time, was it?
I think you'd make a better prosecutor than a lawyer.
Umm, I figured out who the culprit is.
Let us compare love to snacks.
I've figured out how to pull off the perfect crime!
Love is like a banana.
With its popularity and abundance of nutrients,
the banana is the ideal foodstuffs for powering our everyday lives.
Kill the victim by hitting them with a frozen banana.
...and eat it!
Yes... no weapons, only the banana peel remains!
Then just make it look like they slipped and fell from the banana peel,
and it's the perfect cover up!
Even the police wouldn't solve the case!
I wouldn't want to eat a banana I just used to whack someone.
Ah! W-Well yeah, me neither!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
Living for rock!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living alone, blasting my music.
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
but my beloved has yet to confess to me.
Kyou mo kare ni wa naze ka kokurezu
We devote our beings to table tennis,
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
so we build our endurance by playing the drums.
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
We're the Maids, yeah!
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
Seaside's the best maid cafe around!
Shisaido wa zessan eigyouchuu
Thank you very maid for coming!
Next Episode
We live in the 21st century!
Behold the pinnacle of convenience: the fully automatic washer and dryer!
No need to worry about forgetting to hang wet clothing.
No fears that your clothes will smell sour!
BUT WAIT!!!
We still have to fold our clothes and put them away.
It's still yet ages before we can truly call it fully-automatic.
Next time: Eighth Street.
Cafe Seaside
Full-auto Orchestra.
It keeps turning nihilistically.