Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
Student Council Room
It seems like our finances won't cover everything.
Student Council
President
It's quite regrettable, but we won't be able to do anything for the third-years..
Student Council
It does seem that way.
And they've helped us so much, too.
I wonder if anyone might be willing to help us.
One of my friends said she'd like to hold a graduation party.
Want me to introduce her to you,
President Sumisumi?
Why are you addressing me as Student Council President Sumisumi?
She got angry.
Smirk
The President is Sumisumi!
President Mitsuki's Farewell Party (Working title)
What the President likes
Green tea
When it comes to things that President Mitsuki likes,
President Mitsuki's Farewell Party (Working title)
What the President likes
Green tea
the only thing I know is that she likes green tea, just like Yuu-chan.
What should I do?
And she's probably busy this time of the year, too.
What's wrong, Yuu-chan?
You have me, you know!
Ah, that's right!
How has President Mitsuki been lately?
Let's see...
We've been bathing together recently, which is unusual.
I wonder if she smells suspicious.
And she's been sleeping with me too, which is also quite strange.
I wonder if there are any suspicious marks.
How lucky!
Rattle
What else have you done with President Mitsuki?
Hey, Haruka!
You know,
this is the new Student Council President, Otokawa Sumi-san.
There's something she'd like to ask you.
Huh?
Mitsuki-senpai!
What's with your hair?!
You shrunk?
And your glasses...!
What's going on?!
I'm her little sister!
Oh!
I do seem to recall her mentioning
something about having a little sister.
So you're Haruka, her sister?
This is Haruka.
I'm the little sister, Yuu.
That's right, I'm Haruka.
I haven't seen you before!
So they elected a first-year this time?
Nice to meet you!
I'm not a first-year.
Huh?
I thought we weren't second-years until April.
That would be for you blokes.
Ah!
I'm sorry!
I forgot that Misato West isn't accepting any new students!
I'm in my second year!
I'll be a third-year next year!
What?!
You're a year older than us?!
What's so surprising?
This is hardly a joking matter.
That's a odd way of speaking.
Wha-
Yuzu, you shouldn't be acting like that towards upperclassman.
You're one to talk,
after calling me Sumisumi and whatnot!
Well, so be it.
I am the Student Council President,
so I shall be kind to all those beneath me.
Let me explain why I articulate my sentences the way I do.
My grandfather is an exceedingly dignified man.
And as his grandchild, speaking as such comes naturally to me.
It's quite strange, isn't it?!
I wouldn't expect anything less from you, President Sumisumi!
It's great!
Don't call me President Sumisumi!
President Sumisumi, your way of speaking is slipping.
Oh no!
Did she do that on purpose?
So, what do you need Haruka for, President Sumisumi?
Do stop with the Sumisumi!
I beg of you!
I had been notified that you're planning a farewell party for the third-years.
Third-years... or more like just President Mitsuki.
Big
Sister
Solely for President Mitsuki?
Yep, just President Mitsuki.
Big
Sister
I-I think Haruka-san just called out to me.
It couldn't be, I just happened to be passing by.
Ex-Vice President
How about including Vice President Sekai Rina in your farewell party?
Ah, she is friends with President Mitsuki!
They were always there for me.
You could say that more clearly.
O-Okay!
It'll be okay, Sumi-chan.
Calm down.
Thanks to them, I finally started to enjoy the secretary work I used to hate.
I want President Mitsuki and Vice President Rina to be happy that they came to this school!
Your words...
...weren't very fancy there.
Whisper
Blush
Do stop that, I was being serious!
Even if we had but little money, she planned a ball games tournament for all of us to enjoy.
So I thought it would be splendid to do something similar for them.
Let's do it!
A sports tournament! With Vice President Sakai, too!
Yuu-chan, do you know what President Mitsuki's favourite sport is?
Onee-chan's not good at sports.
Collapse
Back to the               drawing board!
Back to the drawing board!
I thought Sonoda Yuu would lead the cheerleading squad!
Just for you?
Don't forget that we're doing this for the presidents.
Aside from sports, what do President Mitsuki and Vice President Rina like?
That's right!
We don't have to limit ouselves to just sports!
Hey, Yuu-chan,
what kinds of things does President Mitsuki like?
Other than green tea.
Onee-chan likes the same things I do, so...
Red bean soup with lots of red bean...
...or dumplings covered in brown sugar syrup and soy!
Not good enough.
How about something other than food!
Instead of just one thing, how about an
all-girls get together for Japanese sweets?
That even sounds sweet.
Yuzu-chan only thinks about yakisoba and can't understand the appeal of sweets!
Don't make light of yakisoba bread!
Snarl
President Sumisumi, do you know anything about the presidents?
To be honest, I was never very personable with President Mitsuki.
I only watched her from a distance.
Vice President Rina often watched
President Mitsuki from a distance, too.
I do believe she loved her very much.
We couldn't help learning about who Vice President Sakai loves, could we?
That made her happy?
I-I'm sorry!
So, Yuu-chan, do you know anything else?
Why don't we visit the third years'
classroom and ask them what's popular?
Way to go, Shizuku-chan!
Pat
Such a good girl!
Let's go, Yuu-chan!
I'm coming too!
Going to the third years' classrooms is so nerve-racking since we almost never go there.
Is that so?
They even have coloured shoelaces!
You'll probably do the same thing after your first year.
Since it's exam season,
most of them are studying.
Come to think of it,
we don't really know any third-years other than President Mitsuki and Vice President Sakai.
True.
If you were in a club, that likely wouldn't be the case.
Excuse us.
Ah, we're sorry!
They act really mature, don't they?
Yeah.
You could go as far as calling them refined.
But...
Your breasts are bigger, Haruka.
Glomp
Don't say something so unnecessary!
Huh?
For some reason...
...everyone's suddenly...
...eating pudding!
They were all eating pudding, weren't they?
Yes, they were!
Why? Is it some kind of boom among the third-years?
Green tea bucket pudding.
That's it!
A green tea bucket pudding party would be splendid, no?
I agree!
It would be even better with red bean paste!
Mitsuki-senpai and the others would surely enjoy it!
I'm suddenly looking forward to it!
President Sumisumi,
are you oka-
S-So soft!
Amazin!
They're D's, aren't they?
Squish
Can I touch them some more?
You sound like a pervert with that tone!
Squish
Grope
What are you saying?
Haruka's a C!
Grope
Yuu-chan, you too?!
See, they're C's!
Grope
They feel like D's!
S-Sto-
You have nice boobs, Haruka.
I shall now return to my classroom!
Let's go over the details later!
President Sumisumi is a peculiar one, isn't she?
Yuu-chan...
You know I don't like people touching my chest, don't you?
But I wanted to touch it!
Would you do anything to touch breasts?
Are my breasts what you really love?
Answer.
I love...
You can't say it out loud?
I'd like to hear...
...what comes next.
No.
Tell me...
...what comes next.
Do it already!
You're being unfair.
You're assertive today, Yuu-chan.
D-Don't say that!
Tehehe
Big
Sister
Let's head back already!
Got it!
Freeze
Big
Sister
Little
The President is Sumisumi!                   The End
Good afternoon, everybody!
I'm Takayama Haruka.
My best friend Sonoda Yuu and I...
...have a special relationship that we don't have with other girls.
Peek
Those hair ornaments!
Yuu-chan!
Then suddenly...
Morning, Haruka-san.
I can't kiss Yuu-chan anymore!
Recollection
We happened to run into President Mitsuki yesterday, and now...
What were you two just doing?
What do you think you saw, Rina?
W-Well, it might have been a k-kiss.
It's not something you should be doing at school,
much less something that two girls should be doing.
Moreover, it looks like this wasn't the first time.
Who started it?
It was Haruka.
It was Yuu-chan!
Which is it?
Have you said that you love each other?
I won't tell anybody about this.
Haruka-san, you need to open your eyes.
For me, Yuu... my little sister is important!
And as such, you're not allowed to kiss her anymore!
No way
The Sakura-coloured Truth
Today's subjects
Dance production
Light warming-up
Dance practice in pairs
Decide the theme for next week's presentation
W-What should I do?
Harupoppo, are you worried?
Y-Yeah.
You'll be fine.
I'm sure you can dance, Haruka-chan.
No, that's not it...
Though, maybe Kotone-chan will understand.
I'd like you to keep this a secret, but...
You're going to kiss me?
That's a problem!
No! I won't!
That hit too close to home to ask her now.
If there was something that you and
Shizuku-chan wanted to keep secret,
but a third person found out and told you not to do it any longer,
what would you do?
I wouldn't stop.
Huh?
Since it was a secret,
if you can make it a secret again, you won't have anything to worry about.
So it's fine as long as they don't find out.
Haruka!
Yes?
President Mitsuki asked me to observe you.
What in the world did you do?
Why does she want me to keep an eye on you?
No waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
And there!
Ta-da!
What did you think of my turn?!
Did President Mitsuki seem angry?
I wouldn't say that.
Hey, nobody's watching!
Watch me!
I saw it!
You're a good dancer, Yuzu-chan.
Thank you, Shizuku-chan!
She's sweaty...
Okay, everyone!
Next we'll rehearse for our dance recital!
I haven't been able to talk with Yuu-chan at all today.
I don't have a sense of rhythm, so dancing is hard for me.
What?
But isn't it fun?
Pair up with who you were paired up with last time.
...which means!
I'll get to lawfully pair up with Yuu-chan!
Haruka!
Hey, Yuu-chan.
It'd be best if we don't kiss anymore, huh?
Yeah...
Trip
S-Sorry, Haruka!
That wasn't on purpose!
I really tripped!
I know.
Yuu-chan, you have to be more careful.
It's fine, just look!
There are others around.
Yeah, that's nice!
Also, Kaede-chan's keeping an eye on me.
Hey, Yuzu, I can't see!
Whoops, here we go!
You can't see?
I'll show you once more!
Tee-hee
I accidentally bumped into you!
Wa-
Haruka, that was on purpose, wasn't it?
Totally awesome.
She said we shouldn't do this.
It was an accident.
No...
Stop it!
Angry
I'll just have to use your weak points.
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
All right!
I have to protect my little sister!
Are you going to Yuu-chan's class?
Yes!
I can't leave them alone even during lunch break!
I absolutely won't let them kiss!
They already did
They already did!
That's right.
I could go buy something for Yuu at the school store.
Green Tea Pudding
I found our usual green tea pudding!
Mitsuki-senpai, you're getting pudding too?!
Shock
Why is pudding so popular among third-years?
Oh, it's just Sumi.
What are you doing?
I'm investigating pudding sales.
1st year          2nd year           3rd year
6             10             42
As it stands, third-year students have bought the largest share.
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
Why?
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
What's behind it?!
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
Why is it?
What is
behind it?
Well...
Well?!
Big
Sister
I told Rina quite some time ago that eating pudding would help them study faster.
Big
Sister
The rumour spread before I realised.
To my surprise, everybody took it seriously.
Though, if it gives them peace of mind, there's no real harm done.
So you're the culprit behind the pudding boom, Mitsuki-senpai?!
Pudding    Boom
Culprit
President Mitsuki is
the culprit behind
the Pudding Boom!!
By the way, Mitsuki-senpai,
where are you planning on eating lunch?
I would enjoy eating with you!
Please do.
I'll be in 1-A.
Those upperclassmen with coloured shoelaces are buying pudding too.
So even they study.
Of course.
They're very serious.
Let's go, then.
Eventually we will...
...have breasts as big as Mitsuki!
Surely, if we eat the same thing as her...!
Sheesh.
Don't judge a book by its cover, Sumi.
Got it.
I will carve that in my heart.
Mitsuki-senpai, unlike me, you're easy to read.
What? I am?!
I love how you're always so earnest!
A-Ah, is that so?
Rub
I also love how you're so soft here!
She's something else.
T-They're even bigger than Haruka's!
Hey, you...
Sumi, you know Haruka-san?
Kaede introduced us.
Ah, I see.
Huh?
So you're saying you touched Haruka-san's chest?!
No!
Why are you angry?
I have no idea.
Is it my fault?
N-No, that's not it...
There's something I want Haruka-san to reflect on.
That might be what I'm upset about.
Oh?
Mitsuki-senpai, is there something else you want to tell her?
Huh?
You should just ask if you can touch hers!
I wasn't thinking about touching anything!
Are you thinking about something related to Haruka though?
There are many things that you cannot see from my facial expressions alone,
so I express them through my words.
Now that you mention it,
you've changed a lot since I first met you.
Past
Your manner of speaking was more normal at first.
Got it!
I'll do it, President Mitsuki!
Let's forget my dark past!
But how you speak now is...
Indubitably!
Certainly!
Ah
My lunchbox is forgotten in my classroom!
Why don't you go and get it?
I will!
Something I want to tell Haruka-san?
I just want her and Yuu to be normal friends...
Come to think of it, I'm always thinking...
...that Haruka-san and I would...
...become lovers!
H-Hey, what did I just imagine?!
H-Hey, this is...
P-Perhaps...
Haruka-san, you need to open your eyes.
And I said such a thing...
I was the one that needed to open their eyes.
So Haruka-san's the one...
...I'm in love with?!
No, no!
How can I face her now?!
The bell...
Oh.
Big
Sister
The Sakura-coloured Truth                              The End
Yay
Won't you kiss
Kiss and love
futari dake no jikan ga
二人だけの時間が
Time for just the two of us
futari dake no himitsu ga
二人だけの秘密が
A secret for just the two of us
futari dake no yakusoku
二人だけの約束
A promise between just the two of us
aru kara ne
あるからね
We have all of them
yorokobi wakachiaete kanashimi wakeaetara
喜び分かち合えて 悲しみ分け合えたら
If we share our joys and split our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
一人より幸せに なれるように
We may be able to become happier than if we were alone
ashita mo omoide wo saa fuyasou
明日も思い出をさあ増やそう
Let's make more memories tomorrow as well
ippai ni shichaou ne
一杯にしちゃおうね
Let's make a lot of them!
Love you
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
この広い世界で 逢えた奇跡
I came across a miracle in this wide world
tokubetsu na no anata janai to dame dakara
特別なの あなたじゃないとだめだから
But it's no good if you're not special to me
futari janai to dekinai koto da yo
二人じゃないとできないことだよ
It's something we can't do if we're not together
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
いますぐに 大好き kiss and love
I love you now, kiss and love
Love
Preview
In the season of dancing sakura petals,
Yuu-chan and I became high school students.
After that, the days were filled with various people and events,
and while spending them together with our new friends,
they seemed to pass by in an instant.
And now that the season of falling sakura petals has come again,
I'll...
For the last time:
Pudding and Mitsuki's Decision
Sakura Trick
"Pudding and Mitsuki's Decision" and "Sakura Trick".
Please wait for it.