Yuu-chan...
Haruka?
Does your forehead still hurt?
Yeah...
A little bit.
My heart skipped a few beats there!
Yuu-chan!
Why didn't you sleep properly last night?
I've never seen you miss the ball like that before!
I was up late studying with Onee-chan.
Huh?
I thought I'd get a perfect score on our midterms to surprise you...
Geez, don't push yourself!
You made me worry, so I'm going to...
...punish you.
I-I think somebody's sleeping next to us!
Don't worry!
I'll be gentle.
Gentle.
Gently...
That wasn't enough...
I-I'm injured!
Is that not obvious?!
Yuu, is that you?
AH
If you're healthy enough to make that much noise, you should head back to class.
I'm exhausted because of you.
Sheesh...
Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
Okaa-san!
You have been invited to our wedding!
Morita  Kouichi      Takayama Megumi
Time
15th December
11:00 am
Location
Wedding Palace Pia
Megumi-san's wedding is next week, right?
What should I wear?
Anything should be fine as long as it isn't white.
Your school uniform would be fine.
I see.
By the way, your father will be on a business trip that day
Why don't you bring a friend in his place?
Can I?!
In that case, Yuu-chan!
And Shizuku-chan, Kotone-chan, Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan...
I don't think we can take that many with us.
I guess I'll ask Yuu-chan, then.
Wedding, huh?
One day it might be Haruka's turn.
What?!
I won't give Haruka to some man I don't know!
Thump
Darling, that was like a line from a TV drama.
So a girl would be fine!
Sakura-coloured Wedding
Hello!
Yuu-chan, were you sleeping?
No, I wasn't.
Do you have time for a wedding next week?
What?!
U-Um..
Aren't there some formalities that we skipped?!
Are your parents okay with it?!
Yeah, they are.
H-Haruka, if you're fine with it, I...
...I'm fine with it too.
Really?!
Thank you, Yuu-chan!
I'll call you later!
Haruka
I'm suddenly getting married to Haruka!
I wonder if Haruka's fine with rushing like this.
We're both girls,
so I don't know what we should do for a wedding!
Onee-cha-
Did something happen, Yuu?
Little
Sister
Nothing!
Really?
I can't ask her for help!
Even if I don't say anything, she'll find out sooner or later.
Haruka, this is too sudden!
A-All right!
Onee-chan...
What's been going on with you?
So... what if two girls-
My phone!
I didn't say anything unnecessary!
What is it, Haruka?
Haruka-san?!
Yuu-chan, you know,
about what I mentioned earlier,
will you wear your school uniform?
Otherwise, we could also rent formal wear.
So you can get married in your school uniform?
Since this is so special,
I'd rather rent something.
Okay!
Mother!
Yuu-chan wants a rental too.
What?
Your school uniforms are perfectly fine.
Even cheap rentals cost 5000 yen!
I'll take it off your allowance.
Allowance or party dresses?
Which one?!
Of course I want the dresses!
You really want it that much?
Sakura
One Week Later
We're about to get married, and I haven't even properly introduced myself to her parents yet.
I wonder if this is okay.
Yuu-chan, are you nervous?
You'll be fine, Yuu-chan.
You don't need to be so tense.
I may be incompetent, but I hope you'll treat me well.
Of course!
Welcome aboard.
Clothes Rental
Ohanaya
We're here!
This isn't a wedding location...
Haruka must have been joking.
What are we doing here?
Huh?
We're going to rent the dresses for the wedding here.
Haruka.
I'll go tell them we're here.
Okay!
We really are getting married!
Yuu-chan tensed up!
Yuu-chan, you're so cute!
H-Huh? It's deep blue...
Not pure white.
Did you want some other one?
But that one suits you!
I know!
Yuu-chan, have you ever put on makeup?
Nope.
Let's try it out, then!
Geez, I can do it myself!
Kiss
I painted my lips too.
Haruka, what is this about?
What?
What's wrong?
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
You kiss to seal the vow!
It's an important part!
There
You thought we're the ones taking the vows?
Huh...
We're going there to celebrate the newlyweds!
Why did you think that?
It's because you said it in a weird way!
Bam
Don't you want to marry me, Haruka?!
That...
Huh?
That was my vow to you.
This too.
And this.
They're all my vows to you.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Y-Yeah!
W-Well then, Yuu-chan, let's go.
O-Okay.
Auuuuugh
I'm so embarrassed...
...that I can't look her in the eye!
Auuuuugh
The bride and groom will now enter.
Please welcome them with a grand applause!
That'll probably happen to us, too.
He cries easily, doesn't he?
They will now cut the cake!
It's so big!
It would be even better with green tea in it!
Green tea!
Sniff
Sniff!
W-What's wrong, Yuu-chan?!
I'm just disappointed that you're still thinking
about cake during such an emotional occasion.
Wha?!
I'm worried.
I was moved!
Bouquet toss!
Everyone able to should participate.
Can I go too?
Let's go catch it together, Yuu-chan!
Yeah!
Go on!
Yuu-chan, it's coming this way!
It's coming!
Haruka, I caught it!
Mother!
I wonder how my life will turn out!
Sakura
Our turn . . .
Megumi-san, congratulations on your marriage!
Haruka-chan, thank you!
It may be your turn next.
Tenses
I don't think it's that far away!
Haruka!
My!
Have some petals.
A flower shower, huh?
This is my first time!
The bride was beautiful, wasn't she?
Yeah.
The chicken was delicious, wasn't it?
Wha?
The cake was delicious, too.
And the salad was delicious as well!
Geez
Geez!
Yuu-chan, weren't you moved?!
W-What now?!
Come to think of it...
My father said that I can marry anyone as long as it isn't a man he doesn't know.
He didn't
What are you doing all of a sudden?!
Sakura-coloured Wedding                     The End
Who could it be?
I was finally making some progress...
Yes?
President Mitsuki, good evening!
Doki
H-Haruka-san?!
Would you like to go see a light show tonight?
W-Why?!
Alone with Haruka-san?!
I'm not prepared for that!
Big
Sister
I-I can do that.
Great!
Please invite Yuu-chan, too.
Okay.
What was I thinking?
I've never even hung out with just Haruka-san before!
But that might have been the first time she called me.
Yuu was always the one inviting me until now.
Onee-chan, would you like to go to the pool with Haruka and the others?
Haru-
Now that she's inviting me directly, we're making progress, right?
Yeah, we are!
Wait, progress towards what?!
Wait, huh?
Why did she call me and not Yuu this time?
Sakura-coloured Christmas
Yuu!
Yeah?
I just got a call.
From who?
Haruka-san invited us to go see a light show with everyone.
Huh?
Got it.
I'll get ready.
Did you get a call from Haruka-san?
You did, didn't you?
Something's seems weird about her.
If Yuu didn't get a call from Haruka-san, could it mean...
...they're fighting?!
I'll go change!
It's bad to fight during winter vacation!
The longer you wait, the harder it is to find the right time to apologise.
Since Yuu wants to go, she wants to make up, right?
I'll have to help her apologise!
Yuu, listen to what I'm going to tell you.
Hm?
Yuu, sometimes you're stubborn and not honest about your feelings.
over
and
Right? Aren't you?
over
and
Not at all.
You can't just wait.
You can only deepen your relationships by meeting others halfway.
I'm sorry.
Got it?
No I didn't!
What's this all of a sudden?!
Just go with it!
The Sonoda sisters are here!
Yahoo!
Did you wait long?
Not at all.
Haruka-san really is keeping her distance.
I'll make sure they make up!
Anyway, it's really pretty here!
Wow!
There's no time to be captivated!
Get closer to Haruka-san!
Go, Yuu!
Are you all right, Yuu-chan?
Ah...
You have to be more careful!
Y-Yeah.
The distance just got bigger!
This is bad.
They're even further apart!
They must feel awkward being in each other's presence.
I already knew Yuu was,
but Haruka-san can be quite stubborn, too, can't she?
I learned something new about her.
It's nothing to giggle over!
Big
Sister
Now that it's come to this...
Geez, what's going on, President Mitsuki?
Doesn't it seem like Haruka-san and Yuu are fighting?
You think so?
It certainly looks like that!
Have you heard anything?
Nothing at all.
But, why?
A while back you were suspicious of their excessive physical contact too.
We're not going to talk about that now!
So bothersome...
Can we go to the general store?
Sure!
Welcome!
Oh wow!
Huh, that pendant looks like something Yuu would like.
Haruka-san!
Do you think this is good?
It looks like Yuu-chan might like it!
I'll go tell her!
It would suit you really well, President Mitsuki!
That makes me happy, but I didn't want to hear that!
It didn't work.
What should I do next?
President Mitsuki, are you interested in that?
Y-Yeah, it looks kind of cute...
Why don't you buy it, then?
I bought things for my little brother and sister, so I don't have much money this month.
Huh, is that so?
I'll have to ask Santa for it, then!
You're kidding, right?
Seven minutes until they start the show!
There's a lot of people here.
Should we be here?!
Calm down.
There are families and other groups of friends here too.
There are different forms of love.
I-I'll go check out the general store again!
I'll go to the store next door!
They're getting even further apart!
They could have went together since they're going the same way.
That was unnecessary...
No, that's wrong.
This is their chance!
All right!
There are fewer people on the other side, so it's probably be easier to see there.
Let's move over there!
Okay, let's join Haruka and Yuu-
I-I'll tell them!
Go on ahead!
Isn't it natural for the student council president to lead the students?
Puff
What is she talking about?
Let's go!
They're leaving.
President Mitsuki...
Where did everybody go?
You can probably see better from the other side, so...
That's right,
I need to go to the bathroom,
so would you wait for Yuu?
Okay...
Telling Haruka-san that I'm going to the bathroom...
Bear it, Mitsuki! There's no helping it!
Huh?
Shizuku-chan?!
Kotone-chan?!
What should I do? I can't find them.
Ah, Haruka!
Yuu-chan...
W-Where did everybody go?
Apparently there's a place with a better view on the other side, so they all went there.
So everyone went without us, huh?
They're in too much of a hurry, aren't they?
I was just about to call them, but then I found you.
Good timing, huh?
This feels weird!
Whenever I look at Haruka, I remember
what happened, and my heart starts racing.
I want to look into her eyes,
and talk with her like always.
Haruka...
Sparkle
It is 7 PM.
The light show is now starting.
Wow!
The pictures change!
Let's take a photo, Yuu-chan!
Yeah!
Why?
We were talking normally just now, too.
Haruka...
Yuu, sometimes you're stubborn and not honest about your feelings.
You can't just wait.
You can only deepen your relationships by meeting others halfway.
Haruka!
We'll get a better view over there.
Let's go!
I-I didn't mean to!
When I look at you, many things come to my mind.
I get nervous and confused.
I couldn't even call you earlier because I thought I'd get nervous again.
I...
I was thinking the same thing.
Isn't it okay for us to be happy together?
Let's get just as nervous as we were before.
Yuu-chan, somehow you're different from usual.
For once you're more excited than I am.
That's not true!
I have to be more excited so I can be with you.
Where did everyone go?!
Sakura-coloured Christmas                       The End
Big
Sister
kagayaku irumineeshon
輝くイルミネーション
Shining illuminations
mune ga tokimeku no
胸がときめくの
Excitement in my
tobikkiri kawaiku kigaete
とびっきりかわいく 着替えて
I change into the cutest clothes
dekake yo kurisumasu
出かけよクリスマス
to go out for Christmas
machijuu kirameku tonari ni minna no egao
街中きらめく 隣にみんなの笑顔
In the city, all the smiling faces around me are shining
afureru shiawase shiroi toiki ni naru
溢れる幸せ 白い吐息になる
Their overflowing happiness turns into white puffs
furihajimeta sakurairo no yuki
降り始めた桜色の雪
Sakura-coloured snow started falling
kimochi tsutaetai konya dake wa ne
気持ち 伝えたい 今夜だけはね
This is the night I want to tell you how I feel
kamisama toki wo tomete kirakira kagayaku
神さま時を止めて キラキラ輝く
God, stop time for this sparkling, special moment
tokubetsu na shunkan anata to
特別な瞬間 あなたと
The warmth that connects you and me
tsunagaru nukumori ne zutto gyutto
つながる温もり ねぇずっとぎゅっと
Forever tightly.
sakura christmas...
Preview
Kotone, you're the only one who addresses me without a honorific, aren't you?
Do you want me to use one?
I didn't mean it like that.
Yuzu-chan!
That's gross.
Yuzucchi!
That doesn't feel right!
Use diplomacy!
That has nothing to do with my name!
You're so selfish.
In that case,
Mikan-san!
Don't call me that!
Next time, Trick 9.
S.B.J.K's End-of-Year Debut
A Sour Plan Continued!?
"S.B.J.K's End-of-Year Debut" and "A Sour Plan Cont'd".
Look forward to it!
It's Harupoppo's debut!