When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Boyfriend?!
M-Mom, what's this all of a sudden?
Don't scare me.
But you're starting to reach the best days of your life.
I thought you'd like to spend
your birthday with someone you like.
It's got nothing to do with that!
Besides, I don't have anyone like that.
Oh, you don't?
Plus, we had decided to spend my birthday as a family.
It's been ten years since then, huh?
What? What's this?
You were so small, and look at how mature you've become.
Time flies.
S-Stop that. You're embarrassing me!
Boys won't leave a girl this cute alone.
I'm sure there's a wonderful boy out there who will come dashing to you if you call.
Someone who'll come if I call, huh?
Wh-Why is Hayate-kun coming to mind here?
Yes, he is a kind person, and I don't dislike him...
But he's nothing special!
Did you all know that there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
No! I swear it's not like that!
Good morning, Hinagiku-san.
G-Good morning!
Hinagiku-san?
What happened to Hinagiku?
Could I possibly have done something to make her mad at me again?
Hey, pull yourself together. Why are you depressed before even taking your exams?
Ah, right. Today is  the day of the final exam, isn't it?
Then what were you just depressed over?
Oh, nothing.
Geez. Because Mom said something like that last night, I ended up being anxious around him.
Th-This is...
No name.
Who could it be from?
Someone's got some courage to send me a love letter.
Could it be from Hayate-kun?
No, it can't be!
But he did say hello when we ran into each other.
Wh-What could it say?
I'll be waiting in front of the Kendo Dojo after school.
Please come.
What are you doing, Hayate?
N-N-Nothing! It's nothing.
If it's the Kendo Dojo, could this be from Hinagiku-san?
No, calm down, Hayate.
A youth love story event like this can't really be happening to you.
Besides, were there any events that made my rating with her increase?
Or wait! Was this morning's strange attitude because of this?
Here, Milady.
Thank you.
Stop, stop. If I fail this, then I'll have nothing left.
I must concentrate.
Like that, the final exam ended covered with pink-colored distress and H-game-like imaginations.
And now it's after school.
What?! This is wrong, as well?
God, I taught you that multiple times. How foolish can you be?
Crap, what should I do?
Nagi, you don't need to check Hayate-sama's answers?
No need for that. Hayate can do anything when he tries.
Right, Hayate?
O-Of course, Milady.
Honestly, because of this, I couldn't concentrate much.
But for now, I guess it's time for a study session for those who can't get it even when they try.
Who are you calling "those who can't get it even when they try"?
I'm not going over to your house!
Oh, what a waste. I was thinking of doing it at Isumi's place.
What?
A-At Isumi's place?
Sure. Let's all study together.
I-If you say so, then I guess I can come.
So, Hayate. Sorry, but can you head back to the mansion first?
Okay.
I've got some free time now.
I guess I'll go for the heck of it.
But I'm sure Hinagiku-san won't be the one waiting.
Um... Was there a Legendary Tree-like tree
in front of the Kendo Dojo?
And why a sakura tree in March?
Plus, the Legendary Tree isn't a sakura.
Forget about all those minor issues!
H-Hinagiku-san!
H-Hayate-kun.
Why are you here, Hinagiku-san?
Wh-Why? W-Well... because I'm here for my club activity, of course.
Why are you here, Hayate-kun?
Um, then could you be...
Could you be...
...the sender of this letter?
I've been waiting for you, Ayasaki!
You're mystery kendo club member A!
Who are you calling the kendo club member A?!
Don't treat me like a background character!
What are you doing here, Azumamiya-kun?
Katsura-san! Today, I shall defeat our enemy Ayasaki before your very eyes and show you my true ability!
Then, you sent me this letter?
How could you end it like this...
What's wrong, Ayasaki? Giving up once you found out that you have to face me?
What exactly is with this lovely challenge letter?
What kind of background character are you to write a heart in a challenge letter?
Don't call me a background character!
My name is-
I'm aware.
You showed up in episode 15 and declared your rivalry to me...
...but got beaten within seconds by Hinagiku-san in episode 16...
...and haven't gotten much screen time ever since.
In the popularity vote taken at Akiba,
you were ranked lower than Hata-sensei's mother.
Right, Azumamiya Koutarou-san?
Yes, you're right!
But forget all of that explanation!
Hayate-kun. Did you perhaps think that I wrote that letter?
Ah, no! Absolutely not!
Oh please. Why would I think that?
Hinagiku-san would never do something so girly.
What do you mean by that?
What did you mean when you said
I would never do something so girly?
It didn't have any deep meaning.
Then tell me what you meant.
Did I make her angry again?
Looks like even Katsura-san despises you.
Serves you right.
You don't have to worry about me. Why not deal with him?
Hina- Hinagiku-san?
You hear that, Ayasaki?
Even Katsura-san wants to see me beat you gallantly.
I ask of you a favor, too.
As his butler, I request that you have a match with him.
For the past two and a half seasons, he's fought through hard training.
And he finally opened his mind's eye for beating you!
All that so he can fight me?
Exactly.
It's very rare for the loser Azumamiya to come make a challenge on his own.
Wouldn't turning him down tarnish your manhood?
Y-You might have a point.
Plus, if you turn it down, I'll have to forward the bill for the flowers from the Azumamiyas to the Sanzenins.
Himuro. Do I need to keep going?
Keep it up, Sir Taiga. It'll be over soon.
Okay, fine. I will fight you, Azumamiya-san.
I'll do my best for you, Himuro.
That's what I like to hear, Ayasaki!
A secret technique he came up with just to defeat me.
What sort could it be?
Ready?
He threw away his shinai?
He's going to fight with his fists?
The secret technique I came up with...
It's this!
Huh?
My turn!
Come on!
Um, what is this about?
Can't you tell by looking at it? It's a cat's cradle battle!
Huh?
The secret technique Sir came up with after two and a half seasons.
It goes, "There's no chance of winning in kendo. Then I shall beat him in something I'm best at!"
Indeed, that's the Azumamiya boy.
What a loser choice.
You're such a Nob***-kun.
Well, Ayasaki? Giving up already?
Fine. I did accept your challenge.
Zo*** Genesis. Mur***** Liger!
What the heck is that?!
How did you even make that?
Nothing is impossible for butlers.
W-Why you...
I-I lost...
I just wasted thousands of pieces of yarn that I wore out for this day.
What kind of training did you do?
Sir!
Nonohara...
It's pitiful for you to give up after only one loss.
I've always taught you to keep rising with an adamant attitude until you win if you're a man!
That's right! I can't give up just because I lost once!
So you understand me.
Therefore...
Fight me, Oukouchi Taiga!
That's right, Sir.
How sharp of you to pick a fight with someone you have the best chance of winning against!
Hi-Himuro!
Interesting.
I don't want you to underestimate
our Sir Taiga's ability, Nonohara-kun.
Why are you taking it there?!
Um, may I go home now?
No one's listening to me.
Oh yeah, where did Hinagiku-san go?
God, God, God!
Why did I hope that the letter was from Hayate-kun?
It pisses me off!
It almost feels like I got dumped,
when I wasn't necessarily in love with him.
Wow, youth is so nice.
End of that. We'll forget about
Azumamiya vs Taiga and continue to the second half.
Ganbattan dakedo damedatta!
Ganbattan dakedo damedatta! = I tried my best but couldn't!
Tarutaru monku suishou shimasu.
Tarutaru monku suishou shimasu. = I recommend Tarutaru Monku.
It's no good. Why can't I concentrate on studying?
When you're feeling irritated,
it's best to go out to the city and change the mood.
Hey, what do you want for your birthday?
As long as Gin-tan's with me, I don't need anything else.
Yeah. After all, spending a birthday with your sweetheart and being all excited about it is the best.
Right, right. Spending a birthday alone is so lame.
Yeah, yeah. Just rub it in.
Who cares. It's got nothing to do with me.
If you're with your sweetheart or not for your birthday...
H-Hinagiku-san.
Hayate-kun.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to get another reference book.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wh-Why are you apologizing all of a sudden?
I'm not really sure myself.
It looks like I made you angry yesterday, too.
Are you really reflecting on your acts?
Then treat me to a drink.
Thank you for waiting.
Enjoy.
The cappuccino here is really good.
I see.
What happened to Hinagiku-san all of a sudden?
It's rare to see you in outside clothes.
R-Really?
Yeah. It looks good on you.
Thank you very much.
Um, you look very cute, too.
Wh-What are you saying all of a sudden?
No, I mean your clothes.
Your clothes are cute.
Oh, right. The clothes...
What's wrong, Hinagiku-san?
So, did you do all right on the exam?
No...
Hey, don't put on that sad face again.
Let's forget what's past and enjoy ourselves instead.
It's so cute!
It's so nice. I want it.
Watch me. I'll definitely get it.
I put in all the money I had, too.
Do you want that doll that bad?
I guess you have a girly side to you, too.
That's your second strike!
You said the same thing to me yesterday at school.
Something like I wouldn't possibly do anything girly.
No, that was...
Besides, I didn't hear a clear answer.
Spill it! You thought I wrote that letter, didn't you?
You did, didn't you?
No, I absolutely didn't.
Wh-What? So you still mean that I'm not like a girl?
Why do I keep messing things up?
I'm not seriously angry or anything.
I thought that letter was from Hayate-kun at first.
Idiot! Get out of here, Hayate-kun!
See you, bye!
Looks like I made Hinagiku-san mad again.
Why am I always like this?
What am I doing?
I was enjoying it, and then there I went destroying it myself.
Selfish and hates to lose...
I've never shown any of my girly sides in front of Hayate-kun.
A kitty!
Wh-What should I do? I can't get up to a place that high.
Actually, wasn't there a similar situation to this before?
What am I remembering at a time like this?
Don't go that way!
I'll get you down right away!
Mustn't look down!
I have to concentrate on what's above me.
Come over this way.
There, there, good kitty. You don't have to be afraid anymore.
Thank goodness. I'll take you to your mom right away.
Someone, help me.
I would have come to save you if you'd asked.
H-Hayate-kun...
I would come to save you.
Hayate-kun!
Are you all right, Hinagiku-san?
Hayate-kun?
I-I'm sorry.
I-It's fine. Thank you.
And... Um, here.
You got it for me?
You always end up helping me.
I told you that I would come to save you if you called.
Well, my house is this way.
Okay.
Thank you for accompanying me today.
It was really fun.
Oh, for me, too.
Um, if I call for you, would you come again?
Yes. Call me anytime.
I'm good at the UFO catcher.
I'll see you tomorrow, then.
Goodbye.
What's wrong, Hayate?
Oh boy...
What "Oh boy"?
Is the result of the exam that depressing?
No, that's not the case.
An unexpected expense emptied my wallet.
Nagi, what should we do for Hinagiku-san's birthday present?
I'll leave it to you to decide.
Um, is Hinagiku-san's birthday soon?
Yes. She was born on March 3rd.
R-Really...
Then I probably should get her something, too.
Why are you giving her a present?
Besides, you just said you don't have any money.
Besides, before you think about Hinagiku-
Oh, right...
Thank you, Hayate-kun.
Will Hinagiku be calling for
her special person on her special day?
That'll be for another episode.
You might get to see it on some other occasion.
Next week, we'll fight against a really normal story.
Yay! I won again!
I give up.
Wow, Sir Taiga is strong.
Oh no. The Azumamiya boy's just a great loser.
How much longer are you guys going to continue that?
Katsura Hinagiku's
Butler Network!
Hello. I'm Katsura Hinagiku.
How did you all like this week's Hayate no Gotoku?
It was an episode where I had the most lines to say.
So they put me on the Butler Network, too,
but I don't know what I should talk about.
What? What is this picture?
W-W-What is this?!
When was this taken?
Hey, who's responsible for this?!
See you again!
Hi, everyone, how are you all?
Next week will be an episode
featuring us, the Student Council Trio.
You need to hurry and go buy
a HD recorder with a Blu-Ray disc slot.
So, what will the episode be about?
You'll have to wait and see.
Okay. Stand by until next airing, then!
Next week. Normal story.
I'll be making appearances, so don't worry.
Next week, combine, grand cross, to Hayate no Gotoku!