Why did this happen?!
The event site for Full Moon's live
performance was suddenly unavailable!
It seems someone claimed to be a
staff member and cancelled it!
Unfortunately, the performance
was to be cancelled too!
However, by transforming a ship
into a stage,
the performance became a success.
Full Moon shined brilliantly
on the last night of summer vacation!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Why do I like you?
That's too easy to answer.
When is this gonna
be over?!
Hurry, hurry...
What's up with you two?
Do you have to pee?
Okay.
Good work, Full Moon.
Oh, okay.
Thank you very much.
Okay, it's over!
Thank you!
- Thank you!
Ms. Oshige, let's go home.
Huh?! H-Hey!
What's the matter?
Explain!
Hadn't she mentioned it?
These days her people
are really strict!
You're home way past
your curfew.
I'm sorry.
Even if you were
visiting friends,
you would bother them
if you overstayed your visit.
Please be careful from now on.
Yes, ma'am.
All right, gotta go shopping.
Dr. Wakaoji...
You're so cute.
Hello, Mitsuki?
Yes... Good morning.
Hey Mitsuki,
what are you doing today?
Huh?
I was playing with the accessories
from the live performance
the other day.
Is it work?
No, not work.
It's just...
Huh? What is it?
Can you guess?
Come on!
What is it?
Why don't you come
on out?
I'm right here in the neighborhood.
Oh, if possible could you bring
Takuto and Meroko along?
See you soon.
Hello, hello?
Ms. Oshige?
Hello...
You moved here?!
That's right!
I thought that if I lived
close by
it would make it easier
for you to go out, Mitsuki.
That makes sense.
You sure are a great manager!
Thanks.
Um... Where do you want this?
Oh, please put it in
that room.
Please put that in
the corner over there.
Okay.
This is a pretty big place.
Making money, right, Manager?
Huh? The rent is nothing
compared to mid-city.
Oh, really?
This will let me back you up
even more than ever, Mitsuki!
If I have this much room,
I can set a room aside
just for you, Mitsuki.
For me?!
Yes.
For example, this room could
be set aside
just for your singing lessons.
Or it could be a private room
for when you write lyrics.
Wow!
Oh!
It's been soundproofed.
Kind of like a private studio
for Full Moon?
Just like a professional artist.
She is professional, after all.
I still have a long way to go.
Ms. Oshige, thank you
for doing all this for me!
Don't mention it.
Living in an apartment with
a view of the ocean was my dream.
Huh? So she did it for
herself, after all.
Yeah, I guessed she did.
So this is why she went to the trouble
of asking us to come over too.
Who the heck does she
think Death Spirits are?
Oh no!
Huh?
Excuse me.
You dropped something.
Huh?!
What's that?
I'm so sorry.
No problem.
I'll put it in the cart.
That's Mitsuki.
I wonder what she's doing
in a place like this.
In any case, I must report
this to Mrs. Koyama.
Huh?
Oh yeah...
I've summoned
one more person,
besides you guys,
as reinforcement.
Huh? Who is it?
Oh, here he comes.
Oh!
Dr. Wakaoji!
So you were the
reinforcement, Dr. Wakaoji?
Reinforcement?
Thank you for your trouble.
There's a parking lot in the back.
U-Umm...
What was the important business
you needed me for?
I'm sorry.
There were too few men.
Huh? Oh...
That woman sure has
a lot of nerve.
You've got to be that tough
if you're gonna be a manager.
B-But is it really okay for me
to help a woman move?
- W-Why is Dr. Wakaoji in a place like this?
- Don't worry about that kind of thing.
I mean, we do have
a relationship, right?
"We do have a relationship"?!
I don't really know whether
I'll be of any use to you.
Yippee, Dr. Wakaoji will
help us too!
Well then, I'll go park my car.
That woman!
What the heck is her relationship
with Dr. Wakaoji?
Umm... Would you like me to do that?
I'm...I'm all right!
See?
Umm...
Mr. Death Spirit...
I'd like to move this over there.
Th-Thank you.
She's so mushy with
my Dr. Wakaoji.
I will get to the bottom of
who that woman is!
Wow...
Looks like we've somehow
managed to get everything in order.
Yes, you saved the day.
Thank you very, very much.
Don't mention it.
I'm glad I was able to help.
Why are they so friendly
with each other?
As I thought, those two must be...
Ms. Tanaka?!
Huh?!
W-Why are you in
a place like this?!
Oh...umm... That's because...
What is it, Mitsuki?
Who's this person?
Ms. Tanaka...
Who's Tanaka?
She's the housekeeper
at Mitsuki's house.
This ain't good!
It ain't good?
That goes without saying.
If her relationship with
Manager comes to light...
I see.
Ms. Tanaka...
Uh...this is...ummm...
Dr. Wakaoji!
Y-Yes?!
You had a fiancée?!
By fiancée, you mean...
You're talking about me?
I idolized Dr. Wakaoji!
He was my dream!
He was my hope!
U-Umm... Ms. Tanaka?
Please calm down.
I do not have that kind
of relationship with Ms. Oshige.
I don't understand
what's going on?
I see. All right.
In exchange...
Let's battle it out!
Huh?!
The person who is best suited
as Dr. Wakaoji's bride
is someone who can cook,
do laundry and clean perfectly!
Let's battle it out to see
which of us is more suited
to fill that role!
Dr. Wakaoji...
Do I have to participate
in this battle?
If doing so will calm
Ms. Tanaka down.
All right!
I'm getting very excited!
We're getting into
a sticky situation again.
All right!
Let's battle it out clean and fair!
Okay! Do whatever you want!
What am I gonna do?
This has turned into
a big mess.
Ms. Tanaka... Ms. Tanaka?
That's strange.
Hasn't she come back
from shopping yet?
One condition a good bride
must meet
is the ability to make
good miso soup!
Go, Mitsuki!
Huh? Oh...
Cooking miso soup battle...
Begin!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
More...here! There!
And miso!
Well? There! More!
It's ready!
Here you go.
Wow...
- I'm digging in!
Delicious...
It's wonderful.
What?!
What's the matter,
you two?!
Well, I mean, she lives alone.
So cooking's not her forte.
Next, a cleaning battle!
On your mark... Go!
I'll do okay on this one.
Oh my gosh...
All right!
Finished!
I'm not done yet!
All right.
Next is a laundry battle.
On your mark...
Start!
Why?!
Why a washbasin in
this day and age?
All right! I'm done!
Ms. Oshige, are you all right?
My arms...
I can't lift them.
How annoying!
And...
Here goes!
W-What's this sudden breeze.
And moreover, it's hot!
M-Meroko!
You're overdoing it!
I'm doing this so that
this side will dry sooner.
Power up!
No!
The laundry!
W-What?
I don't have a clue about
what's happening!
Did I...overdo it?
As I thought...
This kind of thing is over my head.
For one's beloved husband...
One cooks delicious meals.
One irons his shirts.
On weekends they enjoy
going shopping together.
The house has a warm atmosphere
and many friends gather there.
But...but...
That's impossible!
First of all,
I haven't lived my life with
the aim of becoming a bride!
What do I care?!
I'll live my life out as
a single woman!
Some might call me
an ungrateful child,
and even if I'm called a
lady-in-waiting in the workplace,
I'll save up my salary
and collect a juicy amount
of employee pension benefits!
I'll live my life out with
the reputation
in the neighborhood
of being a nasty spinster!
M-Ms. Oshige...calm down.
You're beating around
the bush,
but the long and short of it
is that you're admitting defeat, right?
If it will make you
leave these premises.
Hey!
Are you really okay with that?
Don't you feel mortified?!
Sorry to have bothered you.
But young people these days...
Their parents sure haven't
given them any home training.
It's pitiful!
Huh?!
Gimme a break!
Parents have nothing
to do with this!
Oh, really?
If your parents had given
you proper home training,
you should have been able to make
a better showing in this competition.
Cooking! Laundry! Cleaning!
And that's not all!
Sewing! Evening drinks!
Park debut!
Can you handle all of those?
Let's start the next battle!
That's right! Go for it!
Ms. Oshige...
This is getting interesting.
Well, if you win this time,
I don't mind giving you 4 points.
Such confidence.
She thinks there's no way
she'll lose, huh?
But if she wins...
Ms. Oshige will then come
from behind to win!
I'll win, no matter what!
Okay then, for the last,
let's have a shopping war.
- A shopping war?!
Everything you need for sukiyaki!
The one who purchases it all
at the least cost within 30 minutes wins!
Sounds good!
I'll take you on!
And so, the last competition
will be a sukiyaki battle!
Oh... Is there something
I can make a sound with?
Come on, let's go along too!
Umm...
Hello.
Welcome.
I'd like some meat for sukiyaki.
Some sukiyaki beef, right?
Comin' up!
Umm... Sir...
Could you give me
a little discount?
For a beautiful young lady like you,
I'll take 30% off!
Really?!
Thank you, sir.
Wait a second!
Oww...
You played hooky from
work yesterday
and went to play pachinko,
didn't you?!
W-Why do you know that?!
Don't try to pull
a fast one on me!
Last week, you lied
about having a meeting and
went to buy betting tickets
for the horses, didn't you?
I'll tattle on you to your wife.
Umm...
How about 30% off?
Can't you give me half off?
Th-Thank you always
for your patronage.
I'm no match for Ms. Tanaka.
Oh...that's cheap.
Excuse me!
Be right there!
I wonder what she's doing
at the fish market?
No idea.
Umm... Ms. Oshige?
What is it, Mitsuki?
You don't put fish in sukiyaki.
Huh?! You don't?
Of course you don't.
What's up with them playing
around like that?
Is it possible that she's
never eaten sukiyaki before?
That's unbelievable!
Oh, they're going to
the milk shop next.
Let's follow them.
It looks like this is another
win for me.
They're coming, they're coming.
Dr. Wakaoji?
Do you think there
are enough eggs?
Wouldn't a carton of ten
have been better?
No, eggs are high in cholesterol,
so one per person is plenty.
That's so like a doctor.
Not at all.
W-What's...that?
They make a nice picture together.
They make such a nice picture
together it makes me jealous.
Sorry to be late.
Listen, you!
Huh? But I'm within the time limit.
It's my loss.
Huh?
I acknowledge it.
This is your win.
Huh?!
What do you mean by that?
You can't cook. You're no good
at laundry either.
You're terrible at cleaning
and shopping too!
Ms. Oshige...
But the two of you
look very good together.
Well, I wish you both happiness!
Let's be friends since we're going
to be neighbors from now on.
So what was all this about anyway?
The entire day today...
I think...it's all okay now.
Yeah...
So Ms. Oshige has now
become Mitsuki's neighbor.
Ms. Oshige?
Huh?
Y-Yes!
Please take good care
of Mitsuki.
S-Sure...
Let's do our best,
okay, Mitsuki?
Yes!
I'm so happy! Mitsuki's second single
is finally slated for release.
Yeah. Lots of things have
happened to date,
but now it's time to celebrate!
And what song is she going with?
She's doing a cover of
one of her father's songs.
I see. I sure hope it's another hit.
What are you saying?!
As long as I, Meroko, am on the case,
that definitely will not be a problem!
There's no mistake that
it'll be a huge hit!
Next time on Full Moon:
"My Father's Song"
- Look forward to it!