The Dollars?
I don't know the details,
but there are lots of them.
And they're all a little nuts...
Absent on the first day...
I said to leave me alone!
Just stay away from a guy
named Heiwajima Shizuo.
Orihara Izaya?
He's dangerous, so stay away.
Oh, Simon.
He pulls customers in for that
Russian sushi place over there.
Khorosho. Khorosho.
Russian sushi!
It's good.
It's cheap!
Mister, don't run!
It's Russian sushi!
Excuse me.
Do you speak Russian?
Yes, I do.
Good.
How can we get there?
Just go straight down this road.
You on a trip?
Yes.
This is a very nice city.
I'm sure you'll enjoy yourselves.
Thank you.
If you like, drop by
my shop sometime.
Ikebukuro... A sprawling city
as far as the eye can see.
To the north, there's a massive
entertainment district.
A vast city, in which a million people
gather every day, Ikebukuro.
This city's overflowing
with strangers...
Both him and her...
They've come to this town looking for
something, seeking something.
Trying to change something.
Rampant
Evil
The class representatives haven't been
decided yet. Any volunteers?
A new city...
No one knows who you were.
A chance to become someone new.
But...
Sonohara... Sonohara Anri.
Anyone else?
Then, that's it for the girls.
Sonohara, it's your turn now.
U-Um...
Is there a boy who wants
to be class representative?
I kinda do, but it seems
like sort of a pain.
But I kinda don't want to make
anyone else do it...
You do it.
Me? Seriously?
But isn't it a pain?
I'll do it.
U-Um...
Ryuugamine Mikado.
Sonohara-san.
Uh, about that meeting tomorrow
with the other classes...
That'll be one of my first times
in a meeting like that, so...
I'm sorry! I've got something I must do.
Goodbye!
You're pretty good.
I remember in elementary school,
when you cried over someone starting
rumors about you and a friend.
And now you're going for a hunter's
chance of a love-love rendezvous.
Whatever.
But your last push was weak.
If you don't improve,
you'll miss your shot at a romance-comedy
school life and waste your move to Tokyo!
I'm not after...
And so, let's go hit on girls.
See me? See me right here?
Witness the birth of a casanova!
I don't think they're really
into high-schoolers, man.
They come here seeking change,
but change doesn't come easy.
Your surroundings may be different,
but you're still who you were.
No way!
I've got a boyfriend already.
It doesn't matter!
Having a drink with a boy who
hits on you isn't cheating.
Hey, did you hear?
Yumi's new boyfriend
is with the Dollars.
Seriously?
Isn't she scared?
Fascinating!
Why don't we grab a drink,
and you can tell me everything!
The Dollars are like one of those
rampaging gangs, right?
Huh? They don't rampage.
In this city, there are those who form
cliques and, at times, turn violent.
Youth is always on a rampage!
So about that drink...
Each of them chooses a
color as their symbol.
They're called "color gangs."
But this group, whose power and influence
have been expanding,
has no specific color.
Colorless - transparent - that's the
group color of the Dollars.
They're known as a special group.
They recruit and grow their ranks via their website.
<Anonymous> The Headless Rider belongs to the Dollars.
> The Headless Rider
> The Dollars
Who's Simon?
Those crazy murders are the work
of the Dollars, too, they say.
Yeah?
So, like I was saying, let's get a drink,
and we can talk...
I'll take you someplace nice.
The Dollars?
<Kanra>
Yeah, I know them.
<Tanaka Tarou>
What kind of people are they?
They're amazing.
<Kanra>
I heard they just worked out a
deal with the Chinese mafia.
And the thing where that yakuza got stabbed,
that was one of their low-enders.
Man, they're all running away
'cause you're so gloomy.
Kida-kun!
Yo!
Uh, the guy with the
manga name...
Mikado-kun! That's it.
Wanna hit Tora no Ana?
Suzie Yasuda-sensei's having
a book signing today!
Don't be so loud about stuff like that!
Why? What's wrong with talking
about Suzie-sensei?
The Dollars?
<Setton>
Yeah, I've heard the name.
<Tanaka Tarou>
I heard about them from
a friend today.
<Setton>
I've never actually seen them.
Do they really exist?
<Tanaka Tarou>
You think it's just some
kind of internet prank?
No, I don't know.
But even if they do exist,
<Setton>
you should stay away from that stuff.
The Dollars?
They fight a never-ending battle
against the Flame Haze
sealed within the basement
of Sunshine 60, right?
No, Yumacchi.
That's the angel who shouts, "Pipirupirupiru,"
flying through the sky, panties showing.
Why are you asking about the Dollars?
I dunno, really...
That story earlier scare you?
I've heard a lot of rumors.
They're said to be pretty dangerous.
Oh, I see...
You shouldn't go near
them just for fun.
Don't ask questions.
Ooh, he's so cool!
He's like the protagonist's brother
who's all adult and stuff!
The type girls who have
it for their dad's love?
- No, no...
- Shut up!
There are places in the city
where you shouldn't go.
You won't get sick!
Try it once!
Once won't kill you.
I'm hungry.
Yeah...
Let's get some food before
picking up the next one.
The Headless Rider?
No way!
It's too early in the day
for that spooky stuff.
They're really working hard.
At times, some people are swallowed up
by the town and disappear.
And some frantically look for them.
I'll find her.
I know I will!
My love will draw her to me.
Harima-san?
Harima-san!
I-I'm sorry! I mistook you
for someone else!
And...
the city is overflowing with danger.
Hey.
Like here.
Come on. Let's go somewhere...
And there.
They were supposed to
be seeking a change.
You're kidding me!
They felt like something
might change,
that something might happen here,
in a new town.
But what awaited them was
the deep darkness lurking within what,
at first, seemed a dazzling city.
They stopped going forward.
Could they really make it here?
They got scared.
I know how you feel.
Board the train and you're
treated like a molester.
Walk through the city and shady
people try to scam you.
Go home and it's trouble
with the neighbors!
And then the Dollars and
the Headless Rider...
That's the concrete jungle of Tokyo!
But you must overcome it.
You swore you'd become a
true Ikebukuroian, right?
Overcome these trials, Mikado!
Ryuugamine Mikado!
Well, don't worry. I've got your back.
Kida-kun...
And when we're hitting
on girls, you smile.
Smile!
I think you're not gonna have much
luck hitting on girls over twenty...
What?
The whole point is talking
to them. It's fine.
So you're still walking around all big,
even though Harima Mika is gone.
And you're the class rep now?
Bullying?
And really stereotypical stuff, too.
When it's this over the top,
it's actually not that scary.
I called my boyfriend today.
Youko's boyfriend is with the Dollars.
Hiroshi!
Yo, you! I'mma call my Dollaz bruthaz.
Let's have some fun, naw'mean?
This type is found in every country.
It's really refreshing to see someone
go back to the classics.
I should save her, but how...
Stop it, you guys!
No way. They'll kick
the crap out of me.
Then...
Oh, Sonohara-san!
Fancy meeting you here.
See you, guys!
So cool...
That's it!
That's the only way!
Bullying?
So you're going to make them stop.
And, at times, things happen
in this city that defy imagination.
U-Umm...
Wh-What?
W-W-Wait!
What do you want?
U-Um...
Bullying's lame.
Pathetic, really.
Butt out, old dude.
Yeah, not my problem if you get
the shit kicked out of you and die.
Whether I break your jaw,
or whether you call me old dude
when I'm still twenty-three,
you and I will never have anything
to do with each other.
Huh?!
Humans are weak things.
Well, I'm not into hurting chicks.
So I guess I'll be into smashing
their cell phones instead.
What's with him?
Bored.
That's enough cell phone
smashing for me.
H-Hiroshi!
Yo yo yo!
Hey, man!
Violence?
Ooh, scary!
Wh-Why, you...
Whoa! I give up!
Wait! Please wait!
I'll get you for this!
The kamaitachi youkai is here.
Man, that's great...
Trying to save a girl
who's being bullied.
It's been a while, Kida Masaomi-kun.
Oh. Hi.
That uniform's from Raira Academy, right?
Congrats on getting in.
Oh, thank you.
It's rare to see you in Ikebukuro, Izaya-san.
This is the Orihara Izaya that
I absolutely am not to piss off?
Oh, this is just a friend.
I'm Orihara Izaya. Nice to meet you.
I-I'm Ryuugamine Mikado.
That name sounds like
an air conditioner.
So what brings you to Ikebukuro?
I came to see someone.
And I did.
No way. That's a convenience store trashcan,
and it just came flying at us.
Why?
Oh, shit!
Izaya-kun...
A bartender?
Didn't I tell you never to set
foot in Ikebukuro again?
Izaya-kun...
Shizu-chan. Weren't you
working at West Gate?
I got fired ages ago.
And I told you not to call me that.
My name is Heiwajima Shizuo.
Heiwajima Shizuo?
Another guy I absolutely
am not to piss off?
Oh, man. Shizu-chan.
You still mad I got you
blamed for that thing?
Oh, no. I'm not mad.
I just want to beat the shit out of you.
You know, your violence can't be stopped
by words or reason, Shizu-chan.
I'm no good with it.
It's a real problem...
Let me go.
There! It's him!
How dare you humiliate me?
We'll show you what happens
when you fuck with the Dollars!
A bartender outfit?
No way. He wasn't here
a minute ago...
He-Heiwajima Shizuo?
What the hell do you want?
In the face of terror, men lose their
ability to make sensible decisions.
You aimed for my head, didn't you?
You know that might've
killed me, right?
And since you knew that when you did it,
you tried to kill me, right?
So no matter what happens to you,
you can't complain!
Those with overwhelming power cause
instinctive terror in normal men.
Like violence personified...
Like one who lives on violence...
No... He is the very avatar
of violence himself.
Hey, we're the Dollars, man!
Just kidding! We're not really the-
Morons!
Don't run! There are only-
OK, have fun!
You aren't getting away.
Why?
Why did he come from above?
That's not really the right question,
but since you're interested,
I was delivering sushi to a regular customer
who lives on that building's top floor.
Simon, you...
Shizuo. Fighting is bad.
Shut up!
Don't get in my way!
Hey, Mikado!
Let's get out of here now!
No way! Mikado!
Ah! I-I'm sorry!
Sometimes, the city will
give you presents.
Very small... But very big miracles...
The adventure you longed for,
the possibility that a new
story may begin,
and...
U-Um...
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Sometimes, nothing begins at all.
I've found you!
My love...
The Dollars did it again.
I heard!
They picked a huge fight with
Heiwajima Shizuo in broad daylight!
The Dollars picked a fight, I heard.
War's broken out between
the Dollars and Shizuo.
So I heard.
<Kanra>
No, that's not it at all.
<Tanaka Tarou>
I happened to see it.
They weren't really the Dollars.
No, not that.
<Kanra>
Just now, some people calling
themselves the Dollars,
attacked pedestrians and
took their money.
Eh?
<Tanaka Tarou>
<Kanra>
Scary, isn't it? Horrible, isn't it?
You should steer clear of the Dollars.
<Tanaka Tarou>
Thank you.
<Kanra>
The Dollars sure are scary, huh?
Izaya came to Ikebukuro.
I figured this was my chance to
erase him, once and for all,
but Simon stopped me.
What was he doing here, anyway?
This city's overflowing
with strangers...
They've come to this town looking for
something, seeking something.
Trying to change something.
Welcome! Welcome!
Myself included.
Sushi is good!
Eat some sushi!
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Utterly
Alone
Listen to my story.
A story like no other, of her and me.
Please let me tell it.
Next time:
Utterly Alone.
I'm sure you'll be stunned, shocked to your very core.