Misato West High School
Yuu, it’s about time you get changed!
Matcha Cake
Lay off it, will ya?
Can’t it wait ‘til I’m finished my matcha cake?
Can’t you eat it while we walk?
That wouldn’t be good manners!
Well, you have a point, but…
I’m gonna show you something neat!
You still haven’t changed yet?
Do ya want another hour of P.E. or something?
I don’t think they’ll let you wear it home.
You might be in a bit of trouble if you’re caught like that.
See? What’d I tell you?
Matcha Cake
We all wanna go home, but you’re holding us up.
Shizuku
What’re you writing?!
I guess this works out.
I was gonna grab something from the vending machine.
Come for a sec, Kaede.
Matcha Cake
I’ll just finish it by the time they get back, then!
glance
Matcha Cake
mu
nch
Matcha Cake
I’ll change you myself  then!
Lemme finish it!
Quite squirming!
What’s all the ruckus, Harupoppo?
And Yuu too…
I forgot they were still here!
Um… I was just stripping her…
Strip?
Oh, Haruka!
What’s wrong?
We’re back!
Why can’t you just change…
if ya got time to horse around?
kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
I find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
while at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
I just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
We may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings run deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
If things stay like this
dou ka shichau
I might go crazy
gaman de wa
Nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
by just holding back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
Won’t you kiss me? It’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
Can I kiss you? It’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
With our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
What was that for?!
You really saved me there!
I thought I was gonna drown for sure…
You saved me
It was on purpose!
But didn't you say you’d rescue me if I was drowning?
That’s not how I meant it!
… rescue? Was someone in trouble?
President Mitsuki!
Try to be safe, you two.
Okay!
Haruka in a bikini…
squeeze
We didn’t think you could make it!
President Mitsuki!
I just thought it’d be nice for a change!
That’s all there is to it…
Are you sure?
Isn’t this a prime chance to observe those two?
Well, at least try to play a little.
Hold on…
There we go!
My sis can’t swim, y’know!
Swimsuit Fanservice... with a Side of Tumbles
You okay, Sis?
Thanks, Yuu…
We’re sorry…
My glasses!
We gotta find them quick!
Where’d they fall off?!
I’ll look for you, don’t worry.
You should get out.
They were right under me!
Now you’re missing something a bit  more important!
You guys having fun?
We sure are!
Good thing we’re indoors, huh?
You can say that again!
Who’d have thought you had a pool inside  your house?
I knew we could count on you, Kotone!
You arranged all this?
You bet.
So go ahead and enjoy yourselves!
She may not look it, but she's quite the aristocrat!
O-Oh really...?
I had no idea...
Take that!
But why’re we at a pool  to relax after the festival?
It does  seem a bit weird, huh?
You two don’t know either?
Well it was Shizuku who decided for us.
Shizuku did?
dot
W-Well… swimming’s a great way to stay in shape, right?
…since you gotta move your body so much.
Doesn’t the drink defeat the purpose…?
This was just the easiest place to go with...
Let’s take a dip, shall we?
Okay.
Um, can you not swim either?
I’m pretty much in the same boat.
Haruka took the trouble to come talk to me!
We don’t really need  to swim, right?
That’s not gonna cut it!
I think I’ll give you two a little crash course right here!
That’s not intimidating at all…
Would this  be more to your liking?
The first one was plenty scary…!
Haruka ditched me…
Shizuku, let’s play!
Hey, c’mon! Shizuku!
Hey there!
Get up, Shizuku!
Okay, okay…
Come join us in the pool.
I-I have fragile skin…
It’s very delicate, so I need to be careful…
You’re way out of form there, Harupoppo!
The butterfly is the basic of basics!
You too, President Mitsuki. Looks like you’re gonna need more training.
C’mon, you’re missing swimming class!
She’s looking this way, y’know.
It’s just by chance, I’m sure.
Please spare me!
Who cares if we can’t swim?!
Looks like they need something to sweeten the deal.
Hello? Bring it in…
What could that be?!
That’s Yamada, over there.
Yamada?!
There’s Suzuki and Tanaka too!
Those who show good progress…
…will get one of these!
I’m not pleased in the least!
It actually worked?!
Yay!
I follow Yamada, and what do I find?
Shinobu?!
I see you’ve deigned to visit, Big Sister.
Huh? Who’s that girl?
Kotone’s little sis. I think she’s in primary.
I’m 11, thank you very much!
S-Sorry…
Shizuku!
I knew you were the one making her stay at your place!
She came and asked us herself though…
That’s obviously a fib!
What a weak excuse!
Although, since way back, Big Sister’s been that way…
Hello…
Whenever  she came over to play, Big Sister would always…
always…
Shizuku!
Can you cut that out?!
She would draw her attention away from me…
It was just annoying to me, though…
But I’ll have you know, Big Sister…
Father and mother are really upset about you leaving the house!
I mean, you even completely snubbed your betrothal proceedings.
You’ll be staying here from now on!
What’s slowing you? Come, hurry.
Wait, hold it!
Get your soaking hands off my Mr. Chappy!
F-Forgive me!
Hey, Kotone… are you really okay with this?
This is coming from an outsider, but you don’t seem very happy about this.
Well, I mean…
What about you, Shizuku?!
Are you fine with this?!
I’m fine…
I don’t think it’s in her best interest to keep staying at my house…
If you have someone picked already, you ought to face them yourself.
Don’t just use me as an escape!
Don’t just kiss me without thinking!
Shizuku!
C’mon now, Shizuku…
Did you really mean all that?
Like I’d hand her over to the likes of you! Thieving little cat!
Shinobu!
Hold it, everyone!
How about settling this with a race?!
She was still going at it this whole time…
Why not, then? Shizuku vs. Shinobu – Kotone stays at the winner’s house!
That would be a swimming race, correct?
Yamada. Prepare me my swimsuit.
At once.
I’m sorry, guys…
There’s something I’ve kept secret this whole time…
I can’t swim at all.
We had a hunch…
Shizuku.
Use this.
I’m all set to win.
Why’s the stuffed toy tied to your back?
That’s Mr. Chappy, to you!
Mr. Chappy has the best doggy paddle out there.
We’re an inseparable pair.
We’re assured victory.
How is that even fair?!
She actually bought it…
Sakura Trick
On your marks…
She really gets to me…
S-Shizuku… try your best.
That made her happy, didn’t it?
Stupid…
That stupid Kotone…
But…
Our winner is Shizuku!
Hey!
Mr. Chappy’s not supposed to get this  heavy when wet!
You did something to him, didn’t you, Yamada?!
My apologies…
Isn’t that great, Shizuku?!
You did it!
Way to hang in there!
Congrats!
Was that Yamada’s way of helping out Kotone…?
Yuzu… you seem pretty calm despite all this.
That was quite the lovers’ quarrel we just witnessed.
I-I guess it kinda got to me…
Did you catch Shizuku mentioning a kiss?
That was just the kiss on the cheek from before, right?
You really think so?
Yeah, I really  do!
You gotta keep that imagination in check, Kaede.
There’s nothin’ more to it.
I guess you’re right…
Little Sis
Big Sis
Swimsuit Fanservice... with a Side of Tumbles
End
Little Sis
Big Sis
I’m heading out!
It’s gotten quite chilly…
I’m so glad I wore a scarf today.
Haruka!
Kyaaah!
Yuu came up and hugged me from behind!
Good morning…
But with that runny nose… don’t tell me…
Shopping With Yuu
You should’ve wore a scarf or something.
I did have one, but I gave it away.
…gave it away?
Wait up, Yuu!
I can’t see where I’m going…
Yuu, where’d you g—
I think she's coming after you…
This could be bad!
I told you I only need one  scarf…
Oh, it’s just President Mitsuki.
Haruka?!
But seriously, you’re going to catch a cold, Yuu.
Put it on.
I’ll pass!
Why are you so stubborn?
Oh my…
You’re taking exams right now… wouldn’t it be bad for you to catch my cold?
I doubt that’s  your reason.
Little Sis
Big Sis
I’ll be going on ahead, okay?
You’re that  picky about a neckwarmer?
Then do you mind if I use it?
Go ahead!
Yay!
I got a hand-me-down from Yuu!
Although it’s really a hand-me-down from my sis.
I haven’t even wore it once yet.
So it’s not yours?!
You didn’t want it since it was a hand-me-down?!
The scarf I had before was getting pretty old.
So my sister was like…
I’ve got a spare. You can use it.
See?
I even had one in mind from when I was window shopping…
But why can’t you just use it anyway?
It’s not good to be wasteful, y’know.
I’ll give it to you, then!
Don’t let it go to waste now, ‘kay?
Right, see?
Good morning!
Mornin’!
Yuu brought a stranger with her!
That’s Haruka, silly.
See?
So did you manage to finish the biology homework?
Not one bit.
Not a glance?!
Sakura Trick
I was thinking I should buy a new scarf today!
Do you have one in mind already?
It’s all fluffy, and—
Good morning.
Shizuku! Good m—
That’s exactly the one I’m talking about!
If Shizuku’s wearing that one, then…
Oh, this?
It looked really cute, so I bought it up yesterday.
It was the last they had, so I splurged a little.
She just couldn’t stop checking herself out in the mirror!
That’s completely normal!
And stop spying on me like that!
Haruka...
...think they have any left?
I’ve got it!
Why don’t we go search for an even better  one after school today?!
I wanted that one too!
But it looks like she bought the last one…
I gotta have that  one!
Well, you’ll just have to make do with this one then.
Haruka… wanna go shopping with me?
This one’s just not an option, huh?
Sakura Trick
Scarf, scarf… fluffy, fluffy, soft!
Hopefully they do  have some left.
Half-price
So cute!
And it’s even half-price!
I’m really loving the color too!
Think I should try it on?
My scarf!
Okay, I’m sorry!
It really is sold out…
This floral-pattern one look adorable, right?
I wanted the white one…
Should we check out other stores?
They might have something similar.
C’mon, Yuu.
Haruka…
Just go try it on already!
Fitting Room
Half-price
The balance is way off…
If my chest was a bit smaller, the S would be perfect on me…
Sorry Yuu… the S is little, um…
Half-price
How are we fairing, ladies?
Haruka put on some weight, so could we get this in M please?
Half-price
Yuu!
Why, certainly.
Better get dieting, right Haruka?
That’s not it!
I know!
Let’s ask the clerk to check their stock!
Half-price
This would be the M size.
Miss Clerk!
Half-price
Yes?
Shizuku bought a scarf here yesterday. Have any more in stock?!
Oh, Yuu!
How will she know what you’re talking about…?
Half-price
A scarf we sold yesterday?
It’s pure white! And soft! Oh, and fluffy too!
That’s not gonna help…
Half-price
Please give me a moment.
Maybe they have some.
But would she know which one to look for…?
This is the one, correct?
She’s a real pro!
That’s the one!
I was looking all over for this!
It is  quite trendy, after all.
Well then, please take your time.
Half-price
We should’ve asked her from the start, huh?
Right?
Half-price
Haruka… don’t you just love this one?
She already changed her mind?!
I’m going with this one.
Half-price
Okay, I’ll try this one on then.
Haruka, Haruka!
I’ll go cash out!
I can taste her joy…
The Next Day
I should’ve gotten more sleep…
I wonder if Yuu’s wearing the neckwarmer I gave her…
Looks like she went with it today at least…
I-It’s on  Haruka?!
Haruka’s wearing  my neckwarmer?!
W-Why in the world?!
Big Sis
Shopping with Yuu
End
More Silliness
Now what you all’ve been waiting for!
It’s your favorite weekly segment!
It’s not weekly at all…
First up, we have President Sonoda Mitsuki!
Is that really  Yuu’s big sister?
With a body that just won’t quit, we have Noda Kotone!
I can feel the jealousy within!
Agreed.
Our lovely D-cupped Takayama Haruka!
Haruka’s a C-cup!
Yuu?!
Irresistibly cute, we have Iizuka Yuzu!
Cut it out! That’s embarrassing!
Our cute-but-cool, Minami Shizuku!
She actually looks pretty stylish in that…
And our adorably petite Sonoda Yuu!
Is she just diverting attention away from her chest?
Oh, and Ikeno Kaede…
So fast!
Let it be…
I already know all the details…
Extra
More Silliness
End
Sakura Trick
show
won’t you kiss?
Won’t you kiss?
kiss and love!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
The time we share alone
futari dake no himitsu ga
the secret we keep
futari dake no yakusoku
the promise we both hold
aru kara ne
we have it all
yorokobi wakachi aete
If we share in our joy
kanashimi wake aetara
and split our sorrow
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
we’ll be happier than we’d be alone
ashita no omoide wo, saa fuyasou
Memories to come… let’s make them now
ippai ni shichaou ne
We’ll make lots and lots
love you!
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki, tokubetsu na no
The miracle that we met in this huge world… it’s special
anata ja nai to dame dakara
It had to be you all along
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
It’s something we can’t do unless we’re together
ima sugu ni, daisuki kiss and love
Right now, let’s share a kiss and love
Next Episode Preview
Kaedekko, Kaedekko!
What’s up?
I feel like we don’t talk to each other that much.
Just your imagination.
Could it be that you don’t like me or something?
I do  like you… it’s just…
Just?
I just can’t forgive you for having everything I lack!
Next time, on Trick 8:
A Cherry-Colored Wedding
A Cherry-Colored Christmas
A Cherry-Colored Wedding and,
A Cherry-Colored Christmas.
See you all then!
And what  exactly do you lack?
Not telling.