Why, Yuu?
Why did you abandon me?
Until you find your answer,
this dream will continue to haunt you.
This is your inner darkness.
And as for me...
I am your power.
Call upon me when your spirit is about to break.
Succumb to me, and I will sate the vengeance within you.
Speaking of which, Yuu,
you're actually...
Finally.
The day I slaughter vampires has finally come...
Mika.
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
Mitsuba's
Squad
My, my, Yuu.
Someone's looking rather spiffy in their brand-new uniform.
Oh, Shinoa.
You also...
Yes?
Never mind.
"You look amazingly attractive as well, Shinoa!"
So, what are you here for?
To give you your orders.
Orders?
There are vampires from the Kansai region
planning to retake Shinjuku.
So if I go to Shinjuku, I can kill vampires?
Please forget about rushing in
with bloodshed as your only goal.
We need to strengthen our defenses at Shinjuku before—
Are you ignoring me?
When am I not?
Keep that up, and you'll get swallowed whole out there.
We're from the vampire extermination unit,
the Moon Demon Company.
We'll be heading out.
The Moon Demon Company?
The one with elite squads?
What are they doing recruiting kids?
Keep your voice down, dumbass.
Hear that? They're calling you a kid, Yuu.
No, they're calling you a kid, because you're short.
Don't be silly. I still have room to grow.
After all, my sister, Mahiru, was a beautiful woman with boobs like you wouldn't believe!
Really? You have a sister?
If a dead one counts, sure.
Well...
I'm sorry.
I think it's a bit too late for that now.
Now, shall we head out?
In a forsaken, desolate world such as ours...
there's hardly a single person left who hasn't lost a cherished one.
Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
I refuse to accept this!
Why have I been placed in a squad full of trainees?!
What's going on?
I've been in the extermination unit since I was thirteen!
Who knows?
A new member, perhaps?
Let's check it out.
Hey, wait up!
Oh, Yuu!
About time, dumbass.
"Dumbass" yourself, loser.
What's happening here, anyway?
It'd be understandable if I were placed here
to train them as a leader instead.
But that midget, Hiiragi Shinoa, with her stupid, smug little smile is the squad leader?!
Oh, you all made it.
Aha!
Speak of the devil, Hiiragi Shinoa!
That's me!
I know you've been waiting for me, Mitsu.
Damn!
Play nice, Shinoa.
Mitsuba's gonna be in your squad—
No need to worry, Lieutenant Colonel!
The whining of petulant children
is but dust in the wind to adults like me.
You looking for a fight?!
Keep being a pain in the ass,
and I'll throw you both in solitary confinement.
Oopsie.
I'm sorry.
I'll be heading to Shinjuku via a different route.
Before I go, let me make this clear:
this is your new comrade, Sanguu Mitsuba.
Squads of the Moon Demon Company usually move in teams of five.
Any fewer, and you'll run a higher risk of being killed by an armed vampire.
The moment you step outside these walls,
you will not fight each other, and you will not fly solo.
Understood?
You heard the man.
Got it, Mr. Hothead?
No promises there.
If there's a vampire right in front of me,
even if I'm by myself—
What do you think you're doing?
Hm. Nice reflexes.
I understand, Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
You want me to train him, right?
So now the troublemaker wants to teach?
How am I a troublemaker?
Oh, man, everyone here is a pain in the ass.
Wow, if you think that, then it must be pretty bad.
What was that?
Nothing, nothing at all!
Did it hurt?
Hm...
A little.
Moving on!
These guys here are your comrades.
They're more important than even your family.
Protect them with your life.
Now, here's your first mission.
Make your way to Harajuku.
There's a settlement where the vampires keep humans, treating them like personal blood bags.
Crush them, and free the people.
Then head to Shinjuku.
Wow. It's my first time out since I was taken under the army's custody, but this is...
Before the general ed class, you two were patrolling outside as guards, right?
Uh, kinda.
Killing the weak Horsemen of the Apocalypse that wander around the warded barrier is no big feat.
Don't get too cocky.
The Horsemen are much stronger once you're half a mile past the wall.
They're nothing like the ones you've fought before!
One little slip means certain death!
Don't dawdle, and keep formation!
Stay on your toes if you don't want to die, amateurs!
Uh, is she okay?
Isn't she just adorable?
She's feeling the pressure of having
a bunch of rookies' lives in her hand.
It's Harajuku Station.
This is the location...
...but where's the settlement?
It's a Horseman!
Crap!
Don't move, idiot!
What?!
Don't break formation!
Help me!
What are you talking about?!
Hey!
You can't be serious!
Quiet!
What good is this vampire extermination unit
if you can't even save one kid?!
I said, quiet!
Let me go!
This is the vampires' trap!
If you try to save her now,
you could jeopardize the entire team!
Even if I have to use myself as bait, I'll save her.
You will not! We're going to stand by!
Then you can stand by on your own!
I'm through living a life
where people need to be left behind!
Wait!
Yuu!
Please stay in position.
The vampires are approaching.
Be on alert.
She's bait to lure us out.
Bait? Are you kidding?
The Horsemen of the Apocalypse have no will of their own.
Why would one obey the vampires?
It wouldn't.
Their only instinct is to attack humans,
as if punishing us for overpopulating the Earth.
Run!
You idiot!
They're coming!
Get it now?
They toss bait both to lure the monsters out
and to catch humans that come to help.
Foolish humans.
It's the oldest vampire trick in the book! Keep your distance!
Give me your strength...
Asuramaru!
Who is this guy?
Hyakuya!
Your six is wide open, dumbass.
Yoichi, Kimizuki...
You guys...
Demon weapons.
It's the vampire extermination unit.
Call for backup.
We're going to capture them.
Not today, sucker.
That's enough, Yuu.
We're going to retreat.
Pathetic livestock.
We won't let you get away.
Huh?
What did you just say?
Let's fall back.
I won't let you!
Yuu, we're behind enemy lines!
We need to leave before their backup arrives!
Fine.
What were you thinking?!
Your actions placed the whole squad in danger!
We're lucky that those vampires
weren't armed with Class 1 weapons!
If they had...
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
But I don't regret it.
We had to save her.
I really am sorry, though.
If it'll make you feel better,
you can punch me all you want.
I hate people like you the most.
You're the ones who lead entire squads to their doom.
Um...
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
We were just doing our job.
You're safe now.
From now on, the Japanese Imperial Demon Army will protect you!
Yup!
But...
I still hate your damn guts!
Wha?
Well, you know...
Our little Mitsu has a dark past of her own, so be nice.
What do you mean?
It's a secret.
The nerve of that Hyakuya Yuuichirou guy!
Ignoring orders and going off on his own!
I'll never accept him as one of the
Moon Demon Company!
Despite the two clashing hard,
they eventually gravitate toward one another, falling...
...not in love!
Do you really hate Yuu that much?
I do.
I hate people who put their comrades' lives at risk.
It reminds you of yourself
from back in the day, doesn't it?
Idiot! Don't just mindlessly charge in!
Keep the formation—
Who cares about formation?!
Our comrade's about to die!
Yes!
You idiot...
No...
Hurry up... and go.
There was nothing you could've done in that situation.
The squad wasn't wiped out because you broke forma—
Shinoa.
Yes?
Don't look at someone while they're showering.
Come on, no need to be so shy!
W-W-Wait a minute! Stop it!
Take that!
What are the girls doing?
I have something I want to ask you.
Okay?
It's about the place where you were captured,
the vampires' hideout.
Oh, but you don't have to answer
if you don't want to. If it's hard for you—
Ah, I feel so refreshed!
Seriously, Shinoa...
I don't mind.
I want to show my appreciation.
You don't need to.
Don't worry about it.
If you just live the rest of your life
with a smile on your face, that'll be enough.
Ugh.
What?!
It's Omotesando.
What?
It's at Omotesando Station.
According to her,
the vampires are raising humans at Omotesando Station.
Question.
Yes, Kimizuki?
What are we to do with the captured civilians?
We'll ignore them for now.
We don't have room to worry about others.
In Return
for Blood
What's with your face?
If you have a problem, feel free to trek back to Shibuya.
Did I say I had a problem?
As long as I can kill vampires, then—
Also, should the vampires be awake and armed,
we will immediately retreat.
What?!
Retreat again?
This is it.
Honestly, you may be able to manage,
since you have the Black Demon Series.
But if we're doing this, I want us to crush them and come out without even a scratch.
So don't act on impulse—
I won't.
Crush them without even a scratch, huh? I like that.
Then let's move.
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Dawn of
Extermination
"Dawn of Extermination."