This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
Hey everyone! Nothin' to do?
Quiz Trial
How'd you like to be the quiz king of Kamiyama City?!
Smash through the prelims and aim for the top!
Quiz Trial Seven!
Today is a real mess, but I get over it with a sigh
You get the idea, right?
What do you wanna do?
You act as if nothing happened
As if your heart didn't ache
It almost feels encouraging,
the way you're rushing me
Hold it and let it overflow
We're all imperfect
I can't see it well in the light,
but if we can change our future selves
Wake up and run
Go and surpass the mirage
Try to change and run
with the discomfort of freedom
We can reach that shining light
Follow it into the present
Don't hesitate to act
Deep or quick, just keep breathing
Hyouka
Quiz Trial
Dead at Dusk
Question one!
The word "kongouseki" means diamond,
and the word "rokujuugyoku" means emerald.
Is this true? Or false?
So that's the first question, huh?
The answer is...
True!
I'll show you who's the real database here.
There's less and less of you remaining!
Could this be the last problem of the prelims?
Let's see the seventh question!
The word "darui" originates from the English word "dull".
Is this true? Or false?
I don't know...
It feels like it might have originated there...
Right, Mayaka?
What do you think?
I'd say it's true.
The answer is...
You've built enough suspense already!
False!
The prelims are over!
Congratulations to the people who got it right!
We're holding the finals over here!
Finals
Hey!
That's quite an outfit, Fukube.
Do I know this guy?
Ah, thanks.
You didn't notice me at all, did you?
I was focusing on the quiz, you see.
Oh, that's who it is.
So, Tani, how is the Go Club?
The Go Club? Something interesting happened lately.
Wanna hear more?
And if we could have our third finalist...
Oh, over here!
Let's get going.
Oh, you've got something on your head!
Your name and class, please!
I'm Fukube Satoshi from the Classics Club!
Sorry?
The Classics Club!
Whoa, there's a Classics Club?
This school has all kinds of weird clubs, doesn't it?
Yeah!
It's a weird club all right!
After all, even its purpose is unclear!
Huh? Really?
Our club tradition is to publish a yearly anthology, which we've done again this year.
It turned out great!
We really gave it our all!
It certainly did turn out great.
Great in number.
We solved the great mystery of the Kan'ya Fair!
What's that?
The origin of the name "Kan'ya Fair" itself!
It wasn't just a simple shortening of "Kamiyama High Culture Fair" to "Kan'ya Fair" after all!
And the Classics Club...
solved that mystery!
So what did you find out?
If you want to know...
Buy our anthology!
For just 200 yen,
you can discover the amazing secrets buried within Kan'ya Fair's 45-year history for yourselves!
Our anthology, Hyouka, is on sale in the Earth Sci. Prep Room on the fourth floor of the auxiliary building!
I managed to catch the whole crowd's attention.
It doesn't even matter if I win or lose now.
Oreki...
How did you go?
Tanabe said we should ask the other clubs to sell it for us.
So I wanted to ask Irisu for help,
but I just couldn't make it...
I get the idea.
This is bad.
Satoshi did a pretty good job promoting the club.
Promoting?
That's right!
The News Poster Club was planning to release a special edition!
I'll go ask them to write about the Classics Club too!
She's always in a rush.
News Poster Club
Information please!
Excuse me!
Can I help you?
Good afternoon, Tougaito.
Could you write about the Classics Club?
I don't really get what you mean.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was wondering if you'd be able to put an advert for the Classics Club in your newspaper.
Well...
I'm not actually in the club anymore.
I'm in third year, so I retired.
I'm sorry. Then could you introduce me to your juniors?
I could, but I'm not sure if they can help you.
We release a new special every two hours, so our schedule is quite tight.
So there's no way we can get an ad in the paper?
I didn't say that.
We have some free space in the afternoon on the second day,
but there are over fifty clubs doing something for the Kan'ya Fair
so we're prioritizing stuff worth paying attention to.
This might sound harsh, but the Classics Club has only done an anthology, right?
B-But it contains...
Every club is serious about what they write about.
Nonethtless, if you have something worthy of everyone's attention,
I'll ask the others to write about you.
Something worthy?
I see. Thanks for your time.
If you find something interesting, let me know.
I might be able to help you out.
Eru!
Kaho!
Long time no see.
Is old Mr. Juumonji still in good health?
Yeah, he's still going strong.
But you look troubled. What's wrong?
A few things led to another...
Come on in, then. I'll tell your fortune.
This is really amazing.
Um...
I'd like a tarot reading, please.
That won't do.
Why is that?
Eru, you like stuff like this, right?
The Fortune Teller Club
has lost the Wheel of Fortune.
Juumonji
What's that?
I'm doing this on my own, so sometimes I need to step out for a moment.
One time, I arrived back to find the Wheel of Fortune missing from the tarot deck.
That card was in its place.
Juumonji
But why Juumonji? That's your family name, right?
Yeah... I don't get it.
Did you find the missing card?
This note was there as well,
I'll return it after the Culture Fair.
so I think it'll come back to me eventually.
That's not what you'd expect from a thief.
Let me show you one more thing.
Is there something unusual about that guide?
It's identical to all the other ones they're giving out.
I found it alongside that notice.
It was left open at the last page, showing the list of participating clubs.
Could that mean something?
Who knows? I'd be happy just to get my Wheel of Fortune back.
The Fortune Teller Club
has lost the Wheel of Fortune.
Juumonji
All right, time for the high point of the day!
Shimizu and Gotou have five points each,
and Fukube and Tani have six points each, putting them in equal first place.
How will this grand battle end?
Please lend them your support!
Let's see the next question!
Here we go!
The formula for calculating the surface area of a sphere is...
Four pi times r squared—
That was fast!
Are you sure about this? I haven't finished asking the question yet!
Yes.
Then Shimizu, please give us your answer!
Four-thirds pi times r cubed!
Correct!
The formula for calculating the surface area of a sphere is four pi times r squared.
Given that, what's the formula for calculating its volume?
The correct answer is four-thirds pi times r cubed.
Well done!
Shimizu joins the other two in first place with a tied score of six points!
What an amazing dead heat!
Do your best, Gotou!
Now, onto the next problem! Here we go!
I'm sure you've all heard of the Kamiyama High Student Council president.
But what's his full name?
Huh?
Yes, Shimizu?
Kagayama Moriyoshi!
Get some fiber in your diet...
Correct!
Hey, Fukube.
Well, that was a shame.
Yeah. We're tied.
So? What's up?
Something happened to the Go Club.
A bunch of Go stones were stolen.
Not just lost, but stolen?
We found a note left in the box claiming responsibility. It said, "I've taken a few stones from the Go Club."
We don't use them all, so even if they took ten or so we probably wouldn't notice.
Why would anyone steal something like that?
Maybe they want to play five-in-a-row.
It must just be a prank by one of the other members.
See you.
Wait a moment!
I can't let this end in a draw!
This is a battle of wits! Where are you competing next?
At the cooking event tomorrow, I guess.
Okay!
We'll finish our battle then!
I'm looking forward to it!
Here we go again...
I could live without Tani's challenges.
I wonder if Houtarou's doing all right.
Are you open?
Y-Yeah, we're open!
This is the one that explains how the Kan'ya Fair got its name, right?
Can I just read it here?
Nope.
It's only 200 yen, so please buy one.
We've got so many left I could cry.
By the way, your fly's open.
Damn, the zip's broken.
Try using this.
Oh, good thing you had that! Thanks!
My thanks. Here.
An airgun?
A water gun!
We're selling fried potatoes at the acting club,
and putting out fires with buckets is just boring.
Won't you be needing this, then?
That's just my sidearm.
This is my main.
It's an AK.
Wonderful.
Later! Thanks!
A Glock 17, huh?
When light and dark are in balance.
Autumn Equinox
Hyouka
Welcome to
the Manga Lab
To begin with,
Zeamiz
this anthology is a failure.
No one's coming here!
We should draw a poster or something and attract customers!
But we all decided we'd do it like this.
Why are you looking at me?
Manga Lab
Anthology on sale
100 reviews
of old manga!
Who'd want to read a hundred manga reviews? That's just boring!
Kawachi, you should...
What's the point of reviewing them to begin with?
It's just a waste of time. Right?
W-Well...
I hope Fuku will believe me, at least.
I really tried to take this seriously.
Why is it a waste of time,
exactly?
It's all about the readers.
The readers?
That's right.
Manga are fun, but they're all basically the same thing.
Regardless of the author?
Yeah.
Then how do you tell what's good and what's bad?
Don't you get it, Ibara?
That's where the reader comes in.
It's just a matter of how finely honed your critical instincts are.
And those who don't have that can't
appreciate manga for what they are?
Exactly.
That's why reviews are a waste of time.
We should just read what we like
and have fun doing so.
You're saying all manga are the same?
There's no way I could accept that!
I'm not gonna lose this one!
Then tell me,
By that reasoning, does that mean there are no exceptional manga either?
No, there are many such greats.
How do you define "great"?
Anything that continues to be appreciated over many years by many people.
That's greatness.
That's not it.
Truly exceptional manga have been exceptional since the beginning!
Unless they've withstood the test of time, they're only exceptional in your opinion.
You're wrong!
Am I?
The only problem here is your lack of experience!
You just haven't been overcome by anything truly amazing yet!
I see someone grew a sharp tongue.
There's a vast difference in skill and talent between authors!
Tell me, did you read the Dead at Dusk manga that was sold at last year's culture fair?
No.
I'll bring it tomorrow, then.
If even that fails to convince you, I'll have nothing more to say.
So much for selling Hyouka here...
What's going on?
Welcome!
Not to be missed! Fighting now!
Battle of the Maidens
in the Manga Lab
See manga theory hotly debated!
The Priestess vs The Hermaphrodite!
Battle of the Maidens?
Um...
Yes?
What's that?
Sorry, they just finished.
But we'll be holding another one tomorrow,
so I hope you'll drop by!
So, what did you think? How was my promotion?
Did it do any good?
Yeah, kinda.
We sold fourteen copies.
Really?!
Advertising is more effective than I thought.
That's a great start!
Let's keep it up tomorrow as well!
I've got a good feeling about that cooking contest!
The three-man team event?
What? You need three people?!
Seriously?
So much for General Affairs being familiar with the events.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to get us another location to sell from,
and I had no luck getting the News Poster club to write about us.
Don't worry about it.
But...
There was one thing I couldn't stop thinking about...
You couldn't?
Actually, I guess it doesn't matter.
Glad to hear that.
Look! It doesn't say anything about it being a three-man team!
I'm sure of it. I heard people from the Cooking Club talking about it.
That's a shame.
I thought I'd be able to enter alone.
By the way, Mayaka, how did you go at the Manga Lab?
Don't ask.
Mayaka, Chitanda, would you enter the cooking contest with me?
I'll ask the president to let me go.
If if it means we can promote our club, I definitely want to!
Okay! Our hearts are as one!
How badly did you want to enter?
I'm pretty confident about my cooking.
There's no way I'd miss a exciting contest like that!
To all students and guests,
with this announcement the first day of the Kan'ya Fair has come to a close.
All students not on council duty should now make their way to the gates.
Oreki,
did you...
Um... Well...
Never mind!
Where is it?
It's not here...
Oh come on, where are you?
Dead at Dusk
Body Talk
I'll take this instead...
No, I can't do that!
Town
Info
I can't find it...
Why?
The situation is unscientific
A montage of emotions
Who's calling who?
You look away when our eyes are about to meet
I can feel it
Am I just imagining things? It's so cold of you
It takes talent to read minds
You know
I wanna know
Don't you?
I'll fix the fire of youth in your heart while I can
If we can do it today why leave it for tomorrow
I want to solve your mystery
Look for the back of the boy, burdened with secrets
Even today
You are a fantasy and I'm drawn to you
This growing curiosity
There's no twist in the story
I can't stop thinking about it
It's so interesting
But why?
Next time: Wild Fire.
Wild Fire