Before, Selectors for the
battles were chosen randomly,
but now they're being chosen
from among former players.
I don't know who's behind it, though.
So both of you are Selectors already?
Now that we're Selectors,
we can't escape the battles.
Inevitability.
That's what the Selector battles are.
Yeah, I know.
I've decided...
I'm going to win the battles and
get Chi-chan's memories back.
Concern.
I was actually a little worried.
You said you'd never do this again,
so I was worried you weren't
in a good mental state.
Yeah.
I was really shocked.
But I guess we didn't need to worry.
Huh? Why?
If you're capable of baking us a new
kind of cookie in this situation,
you probably aren't that concerned at all.
Yes.
Huh? Well, you both said
you liked the last ones...
Delicious.
Yes, they are good.
Yeah, the cinnamon is perfect.
I'm serious about this!
So serious, I can't sleep at night.
But you got up early to bake cookies.
Riru!
Confirmation.
How much of this situation
were you able to predict?
I planned on being a Selector
again, no matter what.
But I didn't expect to be
dragged into it like this.
It was a complete surprise.
So all Selectors in these
battles are veterans?
Probably.
The one I fought yesterday was a veteran
from the first Selector battles.
Is it possible that anyone who was ever
a Selector will be forced to participate?
I don't think so.
Riru?
The number of participants right now
is far lower than the total
number of previous Selectors.
Yeah.
The number might increase, but...
Doubt.
Is it really possible for Suzuko-san
to get back Chinatsu-san's memories?
Riru said there's a chance.
To be honest, I'm not sure.
All I can tell you is that the rules don't
say the memories have to be yours.
All LRIGs should have the battle
rules imprinted in their minds,
but this time it's vague.
It's like there's a lot that's being hidden...
Fundamental.
First, I need to get back my LRIG.
This is a key card I acquired.
There's an LRIG, Milulun, inside.
Try touching it.
You can't just hand over an LRIG, then...
She become an LRIG?
Yes... At the start, she didn't have an LRIG.
So she used her key card,
and the Selector became an LRIG and
participated in the battle directly.
So that's how you use a key card.
That means Selectors who were once LRIGs
can unlock it to release their own powers.
Wait, that means I can become
an LRIG and fight if I have to!
With you, Hanayo-san, I can beat anyone!
Yeah.
Okay, Hitoe.
I'll get Midoriko back for you!
Yuzuki...
Be careful.
That Layla girl seems really dangerous.
I know.
First, we'll look for her.
We can start by—
Start by what?
R-Ruuko?
What were you talking about?
Wh-What were we...
There's this new cake place
we wanted to try out.
Right, Hitoe?
Y-Yeah!
A cake place? I want to go!
Uh... Oh, right! I've got work, so I can't go today.
Let's go tomorrow.
O-Okay...
Great!
Bye, Ruuko!
B-Bye...
I-I'm going to go home and do homework.
Bye.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
If you lose, your LRIG is taken.
That's the focal point of these battles, isn't it?
Inevitable.
The weight of each individual
battle is much greater.
Hanna-chan, what will you do now?
Idea. Even if you can't get one
in exchange for nothing,
you may be able to get an
LRIG if you pay a price.
If I fight and deliberately lose...
Danger.
If you do that, you'll lose a memory coin.
I think we need to get more information
before we decide if that's the best move.
Fortunately, I have up to ninety days.
Yeah.
Whether we gather information
or hand over coins and LRIGs,
it'll be more advantageous
to act as a group this time.
So that means we have an advantage!
Huh? We are working together, right?
Yes.
Correct.
Oh, dear.
I'm out of eggs.
Grandma, I'll go get some!
Will you?
I'll let you do that for me, then.
Sure!
Eggs, eggs, eggs!
Meow!
Eggs, eggs...
Shiro...
Who's there?
Shiro, come here.
Shiro...
Shiro.
What? I don't like this...
Come here.
Come here, Shiro.
Tama?
What's wrong?
Ruu...
Ruu, I heard a weird voice!
I'm scared, Ruu!
What kind of voice?
I don't know...
It's okay. Nobody's here.
Really?
Welcome home, Ruu.
Thanks. Running an errand?
Yeah. I'm going to buy eggs.
Let's go get them together, then.
Okay!
A Selector battle between a
small number of participants...
Winners and losers are almost entirely
decided after a single battle.
It's almost as if...
This might be a little fun, actually.
Fun? The Selector battles?
No, I mean, of course I'm scared.
But it's like...
Last time, I was so worried and alone,
but now I can fight with you
and Kiyoi-chan at my side.
Question.
Do you really intend to restore
Chinatsu-san's memories?
Yes, why?
Concern.
I'm well aware of the risks involved
in getting memories back.
In the previous battles,
Chinatsu-san set up Selector
battles under Satomi's direction.
Her actions brought sorrow to many Selectors
and destroyed the personality
of her friend, Shirai-san.
When she gets her memories back,
will she be able to forgive herself?
Can you still tell me that
she should get them back?
I...
Concern.
There's something else bothering me.
Isn't there a chance that Chinatsu-san
will be chosen for these battles, as well?
Suzuko.
Riru?
A new Selector was just born.
We meet again, Chi-chan.
Who are you?
Meru.
Meru?
The same name...
You gave it to me.
You don't remember, do you?
That's okay, though.
It's all in here.
After the last battles, I disappeared.
But I was brought back,
along with your memories.
They didn't disappear!
Even my memories with Suzu?
Win enough battles, and you
can get them all back.
Get them back...
Welcome to the Selector
battles, Morikawa Chinatsu.
Satomi Kou's favorite.
Should I bring her to my side, or...
Suzu?
Chi-chan! Where are you?
I've become a Selector.
Chi...
It was just like you told me.
If I win the battles, she said,
I can get all my memories back.
Amazing, isn't it?
I can remember everything I forgot.
Don't, Chi-chan! You don't remember
anything about the battles, do you?
I'll be fine. Meru is with me.
But it's dangerous!
Soon, you won't have to look sad anymore.
I want to laugh and share the
memories we treasured. Don't you?
Chi-chan, listen.
I'll get your memories back!
So don't do the battles...
Thank you.
But this is my problem.
Sudden development.
This is dangerous.
If Chinatsu-san runs into Carnival...
We have to stop her.
Riru, do you know where Chi-chan is?
I can approximate a Selector's direction,
but I don't know if it's Chinatsu...
Tell me.
For now, head toward the station.
Emergency.
Let's have Kiyoi-san help us, too.
Okay. I'll look.
Piruluk.
Right.
Riru, which way do I go?
Riru?
What's going on?
Piruluk...
Selectors are gathering in this town.
Lying to a friend really hurts...
Yeah, but we can't help it.
We can't tell Ruuko.
Yeah.
Hanayo-san, we made it to
the town we were going for.
Which way now?
Hanayo-san, what's wrong?
Are there no Selectors here?
The opposite.
There are Selectors everywhere.
Morikawa Chinatsu?
You're...
Sorry. I'm in a hurry.
Wait.
Did something happen?
I just saw Morikawa Chinatsu over there...
She became a Selector?
Yes.
No way... Why?
But the Selector battles have already begun.
Damn it!
How am I supposed to get my
LRIG back if I can't fight?
That bitch Piruluk...
That girl is a Selector?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
Selector...
You're a Selector?
Good, I've been looking for one!
Lucky Aki!
Aki-lucky!
Let's battle, okay?
Huh? She has no LRIG...
We can't fight, then.
Let's go, Chi-chan.
Yeah.
Hey.
Hell no.
I've finally found a Selector.
I'm not letting you go.
Fight me! All right?
Why is this happening to me?
Am I just supposed to disappear?!
Please! I'm going to disappear!
I don't want to disappear!
If you want, I can introduce
you to the bookmaker...
Wait! Hey!
Suzuko..
Two Selectors. On the other side of that building.
Two... On the other side of the building?
Yeah.
Caution.
If these are different Selectors,
we might end up in a battle.
Yeah, but if it's Chi-chan...
Kiyoi-san?
Yes?
Yes.
Acknowledgment.
She saw Chinatsu-san.
Let's go!
They're heading in the other direction.
Who was that?
Another one, from a different direction.
You finally came!
I got sick of waiting.
Layla-san...
This is her?!
You're Kurebayashi Yuzuki?
H-How do you know who I am?
Someone was nice enough to
tell me all kinds of things.
More importantly...
You've come to do it, haven't you?
With me!
Midoriko!
Hitoe...
Your name's Midoriko, huh?
Come on, hurry.
Yuzuki...
Don't worry.
I'll win and get Midoriko back.
Hanayo-san.
Yeah.
Open!
Yuzuki, an LRIG has to do
what their Selector says.
Don't hold back. Attack with all your strength.
Right!
Unlock. Coin bet.
Out of the way.
Turn end.
Now, come on.
I didn't expect her to take over in turn one.
Hanayo-san, grow!
Summon two Flathro.
Use their effects to add SIGNI to my hand.
Attack!
Wimpy.
Wimpy! Wimpy! Wimpy!
Hanayo-san!
Hey, you.
If you don't use your trump
card soon, I'll crush her.
Unlock! Coin bet!
I'll help you.
Let's give it all we've got.
Right.
Summon Sergeant and Captain!
ARTS: Thunderclap of Violent Supremacy!
This is great.
This is how a battle should be.
Coin bet!
Doping!
F1, Road, Ride Attack!
The goal of the battle is different?
Analysis.
That's the only possible conclusion.
A minimal number of players and harsh rules.
The losing players are quickly
removed from the game,
destroying even the rule involving
losing and winning coins.
This battle is like...
Like?
A battle to decide only one winner.
Only one?
Yuzuki...
Hanayo-san!
Well, that's how it goes.
Why?
I thought you left the battle
once you got five coins.
Leave the battle?
No way!
I haven't had enough yet.
Bring them.
You have strong friends, right?
Yuzuki...
Chi-chan!
Hey, do you remember this face?
You and I were partners.
If you want to be stimulated,
like you were back then...
I'll give you that stimulation,
Morikawa Chinatsu.
Stimulation...
Don't be fooled.
Meru?
He wasn't your partner.
He was just using you!
It's your choice.
Join me or...
disappear here.
There she is!
Well, that's interesting.
The LRIG who traded places
with the hot boy, and...
Stay away from him!
Who are you?
Don't worry about me.
Just don't do anything dangerous.
This is my chance.
If I can get my memories back, then I...
Morikawa-san, you should be
careful about your battles.
You know me, too?
I don't know you people.
I don't know you...
I don't know this place...
Or even how important they were to me.
I want it all back!
Suzuko-san asked me to stop you.
Suzu did?
That's right.
She's a dear friend to you, right?
Don't do anything crazy!
If something happened to
you, Shou-chan would...
Shou-chan?
Morikawa?
Chi-chan!
Hey!
So what's left of her
memories reacted to that?
I won't let you touch her.
Oh?
Kiyoi...
It has to happen sometime.
Can you beat him?
I couldn't last time.
But I can't lose.
I'll make it plain for you, little bitch.
You're not the queen.
You're a pawn, and it's time
for you to leave the board.
Damn it.
Do I...
Do I have to just watch?
Why?
Wish...
Tell us your wish...
Who's there?
Your wish.
What do you want to do?
My wish...
My wish is... I want to save her!
In Shou-chan's place!
What is this?
I'll be joining the battle, too!
You'd better entertain me, at least a little.
Open.
Gathering / Vortex and Turbid Water
I was doing the Selector battles...
Hello!
I'm special!
Wasn't the door supposed to open?
You know how to use the key card, right?
It's to win.
Let's do it again, okay?
That's WIXOSS.
Determination / Warmth and Pain
Determination / Warmth and Pain.