It's summer!
It's almost over.
It's the beach!
Sticky, salty wind.
The bright sun!
UV rays that eat away at your skin.
At night in a yukata
and a charming figure.
Blood service to the
mosquitoes that come flying by.
H-Hopes are up for
a heart-pounding meeting!
In the end, it's only
casual and at that moment.
Really good meals!
On top of being worn out,
soumen noodles every day.
If not that, then food
poisoning from something else.
What you hate is summer!
Or is it us?
I love both of them.
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
Something like this
is good once in a while.
When you think about it, we
weren't doing anything summer-like.
I think the sales and exhibition
event is very summer-like.
Not like that. More like
under the infinite blue sky...
You can't!
Look Sora, it's the ocean!
Isn't it amazing?
I get it, Kaneru-chan...
Take your shoes off...
It's such bad manners!
Isn't she 24?
Yeah, even though
we didn't come to play...
Seriously.
Huh? What do you mean?
9th Edition
There's a slip-up too! Dojin meeting!
What!
Training camp?
Right.
Even at the ocean,
we have to draw dojinshi?
As you wished,
it's the infinite blue sky.
No, no, there are acts that are
perfect for the blue sky, right?
Najimi, you are so bold...
I don't think this is
considered a change of mood!
If you have a problem, please say it
to the planner of this training camp.
Planner?
Justice!
Yeah, it's Justice!
There's something wrong with you!
Don't worry.
This suit is perfect in both
breathability and repelling water.
Not that!
Your clothes don't fit too, but why do
we have to draw dojin at the ocean?
Najimi-san, why don't we
think about it this way?
We pile up the sunlight that hits us
and then use all that solar power as...
...one big ball of energy so our
drawings become more dynamic!
Even if you say something like a sci-fi
hero, it's not going to hit home with me.
Plus...
They say that the density
of a human's amniotic fluids...
...is close to that of ocean water.
Really...
Meaning, putting yourself in the
same environment as when you were...
...inside your mother's womb
will bring more nostalgia to your story.
Why would nostalgia be needed
to draw a perverted manga!
Anyhow, I'm not going to draw!
Really...
Then that becomes a problem...
What does?
Dojinshi sale and
exhibition event open?
Beauty Love and Kaneru Nido's
newly written dojinshi limited sales.
This is amazing, Najimi!
Our books are being announced!
The opening is in the
evening two days from now!
There's no way! What are you guys
doing announcing it on your own?
Seriously, how much
did you hand out?
Najimi-san! We were waiting!
I handed out the fliers to
the next town over! 5,000 of them!
I hope you get a lot of customers!
Chase after her, Hoshi!
What? O-Okay.
Okay, both of you. Throw all the
freedom you get to the draft sheet!
Yes!
More than freedom, the
feeling of being trapped is stronger.
It's okay!
I'm sure if we're backed into a corner,
we can draw something good!
The ocean is over there.
It's like the last stand!
No, it's that I want to
jump in there right now...
Najimi-san...
A-Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
No, Hoshi-kun...
I'm okay...
More like...
Najimi-san, what you are wearing is...
What? Oh, I bought it and not having worn
it even once was bothering me, so...
Is it weird?
Not at all! It's awesome!
Thank you.
By the way, Hoshi-kun, you don't have
to work, so you can go have fun!
Ah, yeah, that's true, but...
Hoshi-kun has to service Justice.
Well, um, yeah...
Even the time we went to
research the hotel together!
I was thinking maybe
if we got into a good situation...
But in the end it didn't become
a good situation anyway!
It's because I let
that slip off my tongue.
N-No...
Servicing...
My gosh...
Justice!
Let's swim together!
I'm sorry, Sora.
During the day, a lot
of people come here.
It should settle down by evening...
Why'd you take a job
at the beach hut anyway?
Then, Najimi, could we play?
I can't play while I'm in this situation.
Then you want to play with me?
N-No!
Sora-chan, I'll play with you.
Wait, Nido-san,
you don't have time though!
Tsuyuri, play with Sora...
Seems like that's
not going to happen.
I'm going to go thoroughly research
the guys' bodies on the beach!
If you say it that straightforwardly...
It's true that that would
most likely be a good harvest.
Please do so.
Yes! Okay, Sora-chan, let's go!
Yeah!
Um, Najimi-san, would you also like
to do some sketches on the beach?
If you want, I can be your model...
How is the cutting
edge of this blade?
I'll go make some yakisoba...
Splish-splash! Splish-splash!
Nido-san, you're not
going in the ocean?
I can't swim...
...but, I am watching
over Sora-chan perfectly!
But if something happens,
you can't swim, right?
I'll call someone with my loud voice!
Please do your best.
Hey, Aioros...
Am I doing a good job
being a guardian?
No! Aioros!
Oh, it's so relaxing!
Tatami flooring is perfect
for Japanese people.
The saying that changing the environment
will help you come up with new ideas is a lie.
I didn't come up with
any good ideas at all.
How about you, Nido-san?
The bath is available now.
Kaneru-chan!
The bath was really good.
Really?
How is it? Are you guys fighting
being in the same room?
We aren't!
By the way, where is
Justice and Hoshi-kun?
The beach.
The two of them
at the beach at night...
How daring!
I never thought I would
have to sleep here with you...
I thought I'd get to sleep under
the same roof as Najimi-san...
Huh?
Oh, nothing...
I borrowed this car
from my older brother.
I see, then I have
to thank your brother.
You'll most likely meet
him eventually, Justice-san...
What do you mean by that?
As the groom's family
and the bride's friend.
Really? Where is that
confidence coming from?
M-Maybe youthfulness...
Really...
What's so wrong about it?
Please stop being
stubborn and accept it!
As a healthy man...
...I've been holding back things
with my all that I shouldn't!
What is youthfulness?
Man, I accidentally
stayed in the bath too long.
The power of the bath is terrifying.
Hey, Najimi-san, wear
this instead of the yukata!
Um, this is such a good chance,
so I'm going to wear the yukata...
A matching look?
Yeah!
I bought it for my comrade
who's working hard with me!
No, it's okay...
What?
I bought it for the two of us...
It makes you feel like
working really hard.
I hope...
Najimi.
You better not have
come to bother us...
Want to go grocery shopping?
Right now, even a
second or a minute is critical.
Go back, go back!
We can't get any meals here.
What?
Justice said no because
it's a training camp.
That guy...
Forget it! You won't die if you
don't eat anything till tomorrow!
No! If I don't eat dinner, I... I...
This is my snack, but do you want it?
That's not enough!
Okay, okay!
Once we buy it,
we're coming straight back!
Yeah, grocery shopping!
Grocery shopping, grocery shopping!
Let's borrow the car from
Hoshi-kun and go to the station.
What, Tsuyuri, you can drive?
Most likely...
Hey!
Wait, the two of them aren't here.
They're over there.
Justice!
Hoshi-san!
W-What happened?
Seems like he was
stung by a jellyfish and sank.
He's not breathing.
What?
What? Leave it to me!
Thank goodness,
that could have been bad!
N-Nido-san?
Nosebleed...
N-No, it's not!
H-Hey, what's the matter, Nido-san?
It's not!
Wait!
I became a terrible hassle.
I'm sorry. I never thought
you would save me.
What are you saying?
You are one of our valued friends!
Then, about me and Najimi-san...
That's a different story.
You should rest for
a little while in our room.
Also, we want to go grocery
shopping, so could we borrow your car?
Ah, I see.
Here you go.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Are you Junichiro's friends?
Yes...
You are?
The next episode is also
a story at the shore.
Fall down...
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
Next episode, we come here and a
mysterious new character shows up.
We come here and it's
actually a normal kind of preview.
10th Edition
This is what it's come to.