Hitoe!
No...
You guys missed quite
the show, by the way.
Hitoe was acting all hardcore.
"I won't let anyone hurt Ruko!"
And then I kicked her ass!
--[HITOE grunts]
--Stop it!
[AKIRA] Can't have these little
nerds getting any big ideas,
you know.
If you want to
battle me that badly,
then let's get it over with!
She's here! Finally!
The rain kept me.
I hope I'm not too late.
[AKIRA laughs] I did exactly
what you asked me to!
--what you asked me to!
--[IONA] Ru.
Tama is here.
[AKIRA]
...came running here right away
with her little buddy Iona!
Not too shabby,
if I say so myself!
What an Aki-Lovely plan, right?!
[AKIRA laughs]
Um, so what do we
want me to do next, Urith?!
Just say the word!
Oka-- [grunts]
[RUKO gasps]
[AKIRA coughs]
[URITH (I)] I seem to recall
asking for a good show.
[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA]
Urith...
What a letdown.
[gasps]
[MAYU]
What was that?
I've never seen such a thing.
Iona is the Girl of Black.
Tama is the Girl of White.
But how is it even possible for
darkness to long for the light?
Is it because she went
to the outside world?
And because she met Ru?
[giggles] Oh, Ru.
I have the feeling you're going
to add a twist to their stories.
And make them
far more interesting!
You brought them
here of all places?
What would you have done
if someone saw you?
[gasps] I... don't know!
I'm so sorry--I know
I let you down this time,
but please don't stop loving me!
Holy crap...
Please forgive me... Okay?
[MILULUN] Ooh, look at
poor Aki-Lucky grovel!
[AKIRA]
Shut up!
Pipe down, you
stupid little bitch!
[MILULUN] Stupid? You're
the one who screwed up!
Um, about that.
Uh, it's Hitoe's fault!
This all happened
because of her!
That stupid, four-eyed uggo.
She didn't even have
her LRIG with her.
But don't worry, 'cause look,
I got her and Ru-Ru to show up!
[URITH (I)]
How unsightly.
Huh?
What were you thinking?
Hurting her? And leaving
a mark on her face?
Huh...?
[URITH (I)]
How disgusting.
What? Is it really that bad?
Her face... [gasps]
You think it's disgusting?
[whimpers]
[URITH (I)] Scars are best
placed elsewhere,
in spots where
they can't be seen.
[URITH (I)]
Delicate places-- like this.
Ones that are softer
and easier to harm.
[RUKO]
Stop it!
[grunts]
Get away from her right now!
[HITOE groans]
[gasps]
[URITH (I)]
There's no need to be afraid.
I'm not interested in you.
No, too easy.
You're much too frail.
[HITOE whimpers]
Ruko and Iona.
You're a different story.
I'm simply dying
to battle the two of you.
[gasps]
I asked her to find
a way that would ensure
you'd come to me,
but unfortunately,
--she took a tactless approach.
--[AKIRA mumbling, sobbing]
I'm disgusting.
[URITH (I)]
Such a foolish girl.
[RUKO]
You want to battle us?
But why?
[URITH (I)] It's simple really,
so I can break you.
This girl's nuts.
--[AKIRA] She hates me...
--[URITH (I)] Things of beauty.
Things of power.
Things of splendor.
And things that epitomize all
that's right in the world.
Those are the things
I love seeing broken.
All things are at
their most brilliant
when they're being
broken into tiny bits.
It's obvious, right?
[URITH (I)]
It started off small at first.
[URITH (I)] Breaking this
tiny thing, or that.
[crunching]
[URITH (I)]
Watching its life fade,
feeling its body
go cold in my hand.
And since these
were small things,
it was easy to hide from adults.
But soon that wasn't enough.
[gasps]
[HITOE whimpers]
[URITH (I)] Thankfully,
I realized everything was fine,
as long as no one found out.
All I needed to do was scar
someplace that couldn't be seen.
That way, no one
could say a word.
And the softest place
that can't be seen.
From the outside,
anyway, is the heart.
[HITOE gasps]
--No, stop it!
--Don't you dare hurt her!
[URITH (I)]
What, with brute force?
As if I would ever
do something so crude.
And besides,
where's the fun in that?
[URITH (I)]
Instead...
...I just lead them to hate
themselves with a passion
that overwhelms them.
So overwhelming,
as a matter of fact,
those poor, pathetic souls
end their own lives.
[HITOE whimpers]
[URITH (I)]
But, I failed once.
A mistake led to discovery,
so I had to behave myself.
Acting like a normal
good girl, making friends.
[URITH (I)]
All the while,
suppressing the overpowering
need to break someone.
But that life was
so dreadfully boring
that I became the one
who felt like dying.
[URITH (I)]
And then...
...I met someone.
[URITH (I)]
An LRIG.
[gasps] Tama!
To me, being a Selector
is purely transcendent!
In the real world, I have to
worry about harming people,
but in battle there's no need!
There I'm allowed to scar and
injure as much as I please!
There's no authority,
no law to stop me!
[URITH (I)] I've broken so many
innocent girls, I've lost count.
I stomped their
fondest wishes away.
Denied them all hope.
I crushed their very hearts.
Still to this day.
I can hear their cries,
and it's wonderful.
You're disgusting!
That's it?
That's your wish, Urith?
To ruin people's lives?
To make them miserable?
[URITH (I)]
No.
I just wanted to ride
the storm, that's all.
That beautiful vortex
of sorrow, hate, and regret
that I hold oh-so dear.
That's why I actually
wanted to be an LRIG.
[URITH] You mean
I can become one of them?
Really?
That's right.
In fact, there's
already a Selector
highly deserving of you waiting.
Now, let's see.
I must say that frightful
new appearance of yours
will look quite
fitting beside her.
[IONA] And then,
the two of us became a pair.
[chuckles]
[RUKO whimpers]
[URITH (I)] Indeed,
but truth be told,
you were a bit too
refined for my tastes.
[chuckles] Say, has this
thought ever crossed your mind?
That the real world
can just go to hell?
[URITH (I)]
Think about it.
There's nothing here;
just false images, deceit,
and pretentious lies.
But the battlefield
isn't like that at all.
There is something there.
The truth.
Where else can you battle for
your fondest desire,
then savor every miserable sob
of your fallen opponents?
It's sublime!
It's where I was
meant to be! [laughs]
I wanna stay there forever,
watching the madness.
All that lovely despair.
That's why I'm going to
continue to win my battles
time and again,
crushing every wish!
Repeating the cycle
till the end of time!
[gasps]
So come on, let's battle!
You, too, Iona.
That is why you
became her LRIG, right?
Ruko, please listen.
You're the most powerful
Selector I've ever met.
As a result, I'm dying to hear
what whimpers you'll make
when I crush you
into little pieces.
What kind of screams
will you let out?
I just have to know.
[HITOE]
Stop!
Don't do it, Ruko! [grunts]
It might not be my style,
but if you refuse to
battle me here and now.
I will break her.
Get away!
[IONA]
Let's do it, Ruko.
Are you sure?
Yeah, she's serious.
There's no telling what
she'll do if you refuse.
Iona!
You want to save Hitoe, right?
Look, Ruko,
don't worry about me!
[whimpers]
[TAMA]
Ru!
[thunder cracks]
[RUKO] If I win,
you have to let Hitoe go.
[HITOE]
Please! Think about this!
If you win, gladly.
Let's do this, Iona.
[IONA]
Right.
[URITH (I)]
Oh, Ru.
You have such beautiful,
hopeful eyes.
Too bad I'm going to carve
them into pits of despair!
[RUKO, URITH (I)]
Open!
[MAYU]
Iona...
Tama...
And of course...
...Ru.
[phone rings]
Hello, Kominato residence.
Oh. Mrs. Uemura, how are you
doing this evening?
What? Hitoe's not back?
And she's not
answering your calls?
Well, let's begin, shall we?
Grow, Tama!
Now Grow!
Am I really disgusting?
[URITH (I)]
Urie!
[TAMA yells]
Oh, Tama.
Wow! That was super!
Urith...
[RUKO]
Here I come, Tama!
Iona! Death Beam!
[IONA grunts]
Just as I expected, Ru.
Making you fall to pieces is
gonna be worth all the effort!
Huh...?
Launch Skyju, attack!
Summon No Gain, Life Burst!
Ruko...
Tama...
It's all wrong.
They're friends,
they shouldn't fight!
[MILULUN] Sure looks
like Urith is having fun!
Isn't that right, Aki-lucky?
[AKIRA]
No...
Urith...
Don't leave me,
I'm begging you...
[IONA]
I feel it again.
Ru's light is spreading
through my body.
Shining within me.
Illuminating every
inch of my being.
You're actually serious,
aren't you?
About beating Tama.
[TAMA grunts] Ru...
I know what you're feeling.
I wanna do the same
thing that you do.
Tama, Ruko! Stop this!
[RUKO]
I've gotta save Hitoe!
And to do that... I have to win!
[IONA] Even... if it
means sacrificing your friend.
[RUKO]
I'm sorry, Tama!
[TAMA]
Ru... It's okay.
I understand.
Ruko...
Tama...
Enough!
Please don't hurt each other
just because of me!
I'm not worth it!
[TAMA]
Yes, you are, Hitoe.
That's exactly why
I'm doing this.
You're my friend.
[IONA grunts]
And I'll do anything for you!
Vimana, attack, go!
[TAMA gasps]
[screams]
[RUKO]
Tama!
[HITOE sobs]
I'm sorry...
You're friends...
...but you're fighting
because I got caught.
I'm an idiot!
And this is all my fault!
[YUZUKI]
Hitoe!
[gasps]
Do not look away from this!
Yuzuki...
[YUZUKI]
We can't do anything...
[gasps]
[YUZUKI]
We can't help...
All we can do is watch.
[YUZUKI]
So... that's why...
...we can't let
ourselves look away!
[gasps]
[URITH (I)] My, such
a beautiful style of battle.
She really is incredible, Iona.
I can understand why
you wanted to have her
as your Selector so badly.
However...
I won't let you savor something
so beautiful just for yourself.
I want to love her, too,
in the only way I know how.
I say we share this in full.
You, me, and Ruko.
I'm going to love you
with all my fury!
Until you let out the sweetest
of shrieks, my little Ru!
[AKIRA whimpers]
[AKIRA]
Urith, what is this?
I've never actually
seen you this happy before.
Why with her?
And not with me?
[URITH (I)]
How disgusting.
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
She... She thinks I'm hideous...
Revolting...
[URITH (I)]
Things of beauty.
[AKIRA]
No...
Urith told me...
She told me I was
beautiful and precious.
She wants to be with me.
[AKIRA] Of course she does,
I'm her Aki-lovely.
Aki-lovely.
Aki-lovely. Aki-lovely...
Tama! Arc Aura!
[TAMA yells]
[IONA groans]
Are you okay, Iona?!
[TAMA]
Come on.
I'm fine This battle
isn't over yet!
Ener Charge!
Hurry up!
Ru! Iona!
C'mon, you gotta!
Get this over with
and beat me!
Please, guys...!
Tama...
Poor thing...
[whimpers]
We will, and we're... sorry!
[sobs]
[RUKO]
Iona... Grow.
[IONA]
Everything is shining in white.
It's so bright.
[MAYU] That strange thing
is happening again.
Dark is crossing
once more with light.
Well, well.
Ru is adding another
twist to their stories.
[TAMA gasps]
It's level Five?
[HITOE, MILULUN gasp]
Color Milulun impressed!
[AKIRA]
--lovely.
Aki-lovely.
Aki-lovely. Aki--
Launch Dark Matter!
[YUZUKI grunts]
--[MILULUN] Yikes!
--[HITOE grunts]
Tama...
[MILULUN]
Dude, Baroque Defense!
I know that one for sure!
That little maneuver can negate
any attack, if you hadn't heard!
Tama!
[TAMA]
Wow...
[gasps]
[TAMA]
I'm jealous...
You're so... strong together...
I think... I might even lose.
But... Hitoe will be saved...
Tama...
[IONA]
As I thought.
Huh?
[IONA]
Tama is light.
There once was a girl of fate.
[gasps]
[IONA] She was in
solitude from the moment
she was born into her world.
A solemn existence.
[MAYU growls]
[IONA] She didn't know
the world outside.
And was neither
loved nor touched
by any other soul at all.
Her life was one lived alone,
and her bitter isolation
made every day
feel like an eternity.
[IONA]
Remember Fumio Futase's story?
[gasps]
About a Girl of Black
and a Girl of White?
Well, those two girls are
both from the same person.
An original girl.
The one that we know as Mayu.
For us, she's something more.
Mayu...
...is also our mother.
[gasps]
[gasping]
[MAYU]
You're so bad.
[gasps, grunts]
Iona!
[IONA whimpers]
[MAYU] Just when everyone was
starting to have so much fun,
[MAYU] You had to go and
ruin things, didn't you?
Oh well.
You are cruel and wicked, Iona.
You bring misery.
As the Girl of Black.
[IONA] Your strength
flowed into me, Ruko.
It felt nice and warm.
[MAYU]
A... lot... of... friends...
[TAMA] I feel like something's
trying to take me over!
[MILULUN] Guess it was
just one big game after all!
[RUKO] Next time:
"This World is My Property."