This is weird! This is weird!
This is seriously weird!
Why am I so popular?
And where the heck am I, anyway?!
Whoa! That's gotta be the monster!
Volume 1 is about to end!
Save me, Daddy!
That's enough!
No matter your reasons, I will not forgive scoundrels who'd pick on a little girl!
Stand back, Zecchan.
I'll handle this.
Yeah!
Thank you very much, stranger!
Your skill with the war scythe leaves me in awe!
I'd like to ask a question, however.
Why is this happening to me?
Before I knew it, I was in an unknown place, chased by these dogs,
and I have absolutely no idea who I am!
It's "Please Quest Me" to you!
Th-That's amazing.
Three outs, Zecchan!
But hang in there.
You've been chosen as a Master!
I think.
Ooh, I see now!
It all makes sense!
So, what's a Master?
Huh?
Please !
Einzbern Consultation Room
Please! Einzbern Consultation Room.
Part 4
Saber is...
Saber is strong against Rider.
Rider is strong against Lancer.
Lancer is strong against Berserker.
Berserker is strong against Archer.
Archer... Archer is strong against money...
Wallet...
In the Grail War, Archer is... wallet...
You shouldn't be sleeping here.
Zecchan, wake up.
You'll catch a cold.
Sorry, I fell asleep!
Please forgive me, Instructor!
This always happens to me after lunch...
Wh-Who is this fish person?!
Did you eat my instructor?!
No, not at all, Zecchan.
Sorry, I didn't think it'd scare you that much.
All right, face... off!
You thought it was an adorable Deep One?
But lucky for you, it's everyone's favorite instructor, Iri!
I-Instructor, I'm glad you're okay, but that wasn't nice.
Where did you buy that mask?
I didn't buy it. It's a present.
Our new customer gave it to me, saying it's nothing much.
Yeah, he's quite right about that.
Our customer has to be either a really successful artist or a failure of one to bring us a gift like that.
That's not it at all.
He was being honest when he said it's nothing much.
He's a polite gentleman with glistening eyes.
Instructor, everyone in Japan says that when presenting gifts.
I'm sure he was just really excited.
Exactly!
There's a fish monster on the loose!
Calm down, Zecchan.
He's our new customer, Caster.
I-I see.
You've got to be part-fish or something...
but I apologize for being rude.
I am Student No. 0, studying under Instructor Iri.
You can call me Zecchan!
How kind of you.
It is very nice to meet you, adorable little girl.
How delicate, yet brimming with juicy vitality!
By the way, little girl.
Are you interested at all in being tortured or sacrificed?
No way! Totally not!
I can't handle pain at all!
Please control yourself, Caster.
Luring a student right in front of her instructor isn't a very knightly thing to do.
My apologies.
I just could not stop myself from pulling a
Cyrano de Bergerac upon feeling her throbbing flesh.
Dear me, it seems this sort of conversation does not go well without Ryuunosuke.
Ah, Ryuunosuke...
Your endless, endless flow of innovative ideas!
Words as beautiful as a peacock!
If only we could talk all night about our perspectives on art once more...
S-So he was hitting on me just now?
Instructor, will I end up in the Guinness record books because Caster-san's the first guy to ever hit on me?
Of course you will, Zecchan!
I'm sure nobody will ever break your record!
What a bleak future.
It feels like my luck with guys is the worst ever...
Now that we've introduced ourselves, let's get this consultation started.
Caster, tell us what's troubling you.
Nothing.
Yes?
Nothing is troubling me.
I, Gilles de Rais, saw the light during my final moments.
This Grail War was filled with everything I ever wanted from beginning to end.
Why would anything be troubling me?
I-I guess that makes you a winner.
It's the complete opposite of what I heard about Lancer-san.
But in that case, why come to Instructor Iri?
This is where we listen to the troubles of others.
Indeed.
The Great Grail was wondering where
Caster was and asked me if he was lost.
What's that all about?
You see, while I do not have any
troubles or regrets, I do have a question.
I found someone who understands me, a friend, and new hope.
During my final moments, I even got back the light I had lost.
My happiness is absolutely perfect.
Indeed.
Your eyes didn't shed tears of blood, a Fate/Zero specialty.
Yeah.
His eyes look like they're about to pop out, though.
Yet I cannot help but wonder.
I was saved.
But was my beautiful Holy Virgin, Jeanne, also saved?
I simply cannot stop thinking about it.
Is she still burning in the inferno of those
in power and made to suffer eternal pain?
If that is the case, I must return to the Holy War once more.
She was just a young girl, but to save her country,
she kept her own little weaknesses and the greedy screams of the people to herself!
She believed in God, in her country, and in justice!
Yet all she got for accomplishing such a great feat was everyone's betrayal!
Even God-the same God who used her as His
apostle of salvation-was oblivious to her screams!
How foolish yet holy this maiden was to pray to Heaven
and offer the Lord everything with a smile even during her final moments!
If her soul is in Purgatory, who will go save her if I don't?!
I can't disappear just yet.
You poked my bulging eyes in admonishment
when you had the chance, just like Jeanne used to!
Calm down, Caster.
It'd be troublesome if you didn't go back-
I mean, you don't need to stay here.
Jeanne-san has already been saved.
She was widely acknowledged as a saint after her death and is now a popular idol featured in all kinds of media.
An idol?
Does she have a fanclub?
Of course she does.
You can have this, Caster.
I ordered this specially for you.
This flag... This flag...
This is a flag, right?
It's a flag, right, Zecchan?
Yeah, it's totally a flag in Japan!
It's no ordinary flag either.
See the "President" there?
It's proof that you're the No. 1 member in the fanclub.
Running the fanclub will be a lot of hard work,
but if you put this on, you'll have a very high chance of becoming a manager someday!
Can I really have such a marvelous item?
You've done more than enough to deserve it.
You've tormented not only the people of
Fuyuki City, but the production staff as well.
Now, put it on and go back to where you belong!
May you receive the Grail's blessings!
Thank you very much, ladies.
Once I, Gilles de Rais, have taken my place as a
Heroic Spirit, I will definitely reunite with Jeanne.
He finally left.
I don't like him.
He reminds me of the nightmare I just had...
Oh? Could you tell me about your nightmare?
Yeah, it's about when we first met.
Oh, when you were drowning up in the hill.
Well? What did you remember?
Your name, where you live, or your Mage lineage?
You don't have to worry at all!
My mind is so blank that it's clear!
I have no doubts, just like today's middle-school girls!
Okay, now that Caster-san has left this world...
What lesson would you like today, Zecchan?
Ah, could you please teach me about
the various types of Noble Phantasms?
Since I'm apparently a Master, I should at least learn about them.
Zecchan, you're such a good, hardworking girl!
Since you see yourself as a Master, let's charge ahead!
Teach me! Grail-san,
What is the Grail ?
～The 726th Grail～
All right, here's a lecture on Noble Phantasms.
They can be weapons the Heroic Spirits used in their
legends, or they can be famous anecdotes given form.
You already know these Noble Phantasms are the Servants' trump cards, right?
Yeah!
Like Saber-san's Excalibur, and Lancer-san's Gae Dearg, right?
Then there's...
Zayd-san's Noble Phantasm isn't passed down in legend, but the Assassins themselves are a famous anecdote.
So by virtue of being the Old Man of the Mountain, the ability that establishes them as Assassins...
Their superhuman abilities in life have been sublimated as their Noble Phantasms!
Very good, Zecchan! That's exactly it!
Assassin's Noble Phantasm is a very special case, yet you were able to understand it.
You really would make a great teacher!
The most common Noble Phantasms are the demonic or holy swords the Heroes used.
Saber's Noble Phantasm is her very famous holy sword.
In the case of Rider's Ionian Hetairoi, his life has been sublimated as a Noble Phantasm.
He is acknowledged by all as the King of Conquerors.
Noble Phantasms have ranks, don't they?
Does a higher rank mean it's stronger?
Only in terms of power.
Saber's Noble Phantasm has the greatest attack power
and reach, but using it requires a large amount of mana.
The attack sweeps even the ground with it,
and Saber herself becomes exhausted.
Her identity is also instantly revealed.
It basically works like a warship cannon.
But firepower isn't everything in battle.
Her opponents are simply human-sized Servants, so huge beams aren't really necessary.
Firepower just large enough to defeat opponents is sufficient.
I see.
It's all about the cost and efficiency.
Saber-san's Noble Phantasm is strong but has a large cost.
So who would have a low-cost Noble Phantasm?
Lancer, of course.
The effects of his anti-unit Noble Phantasm can be seen in one-on-one fights.
Mana costs are low, and continuous fighting has no effect on the Servant's ability.
I see.
I thought the Lancer class was boring compared to Saber and Archer,
but I guess his plainness is proof of his superiority.
They aren't called the Three Knight Classes for nothing!
I feel bad for Lancer, though.
In this Grail War, both Saber and Archer have extraordinary Noble Phantasms.
That goldy!
You're supposed to conceal your Noble Phantasms, but the way he spams them is so unfair!
And you can't tell what they are either.
I suppose he has no trump card.
Or rather, everything he does is a trump card, so he has no need to hide anything.
Nobody knows his legend very well.
He possesses the original forms of all Noble Phantasms.
Basically, he's the eldest king in history.
Yeah!
It's crazy how he even has a UFO!
It looks like a pedestal...
Actually, more like a UFOtable!
It's called Vimana.
Let's see.
Anti-Unit
Gae Dearg, Gae Buidhe, Invisible Air
Anti-Army
Spellbook, Ionian Hetairoi
Anti-Fortress
Excalibur
Anti-World
Enuma Elish
Noble Phantasms also have types on top of ranks.
Here, this table tells you which Noble Phantasm is suitable for what.
So Caster-san's Noble Phantasm is anti-army.
Anti-Fortress
What kind of Noble Phantasm is it?
I thought it just summons lots of gentlemanly octopus things,
but they combined to make this humongous monster...
That thing was summoned from another world with the intention of suicide.
Caster can control ordinary minions, but not something of that scale.
Once summoned, it will hungrily feed on lives to grow.
Eventually, it will get too big and die.
Wars are fought to defeat your opponent and gain
from it, but what Caster did aimed only to destroy.
Just like a massive bomb.
He thought nothing of taking over the city and simply sought to destroy everything.
By summoning that thing, Caster had become a threat independent of the Grail War.
The Servants cooperated because they are fighting to win, not to destroy.
Ooh, I'm so touched!
They all hate each other, but they're all Heroes!
Somebody couldn't read the atmosphere, though.
All right, that's all for today's lecture!
Worktime's over, Zecchan!
Since we were talking about Caster and all, let's go fishing!
We're fishing for octopuses!
Whoa, fishing for octopuses is really difficult!
We should just settle for catching mackerel.
Squid would also be delicious!