When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Sh-She's dead?!
I confess, I already have
a good idea of who the culprit is.
What?!
This is one of those
so-called "dying messages".
I'd say you're wrong there...
Who's there?!
It can't be! You're the culprit?!
Sunday Suspense
The Beautiful Rich Great
Young Detective Lady Saw It!
The Case of the Murdered Female
Teacher Amidst Clouds of Steam!
As a mysterious beauty smiled bewitchingly in a steamy open-air mixed bath,
it was a night in a ravine quiet of the passion of man and woman,
that a monkey ran off uttering a death cry and wept softly
at the far ends of love and sorrow.
In Cooperation With
Boonies Hot Springs Tourist Association
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
This episode of "Hayate"
is very suspenseful!
But as always, please enjoy it
with your whole family.
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
The Beautiful Rich Great Young Detective Lady Saw It! The Case of the Murdered Female Teacher Amidst Clouds of Steam
Beautiful Rich Great Young Detective Lady
Nagi Sanzenin
The autumn breeze truly is quite pleasant.
I agree, Miss.
Assistant and Butler
Hayate Ayasaki
And the autumn leaves are very beautiful.
Aren't you glad we took the plunge
and came for a trip to the hot springs?
Assistant and Maid
Maria
Yeah, definitely!
By the way, Miss, where
is the inn we're going to stay at?
That's it!
Th-That's the one?!
Oh, my! How very classic!
The only way to enjoy hot springs
is to relax quietly at a rustic inn!
But it seems to be giving off
a rather ominous aura...
What?
There's a very "untouchable"
atmosphere about it...
We just heard a scream come
from that inn, didn't we?!
Yes!
What is the matter, ma'am?
Waitresses
The Student Council Girl Trio
Guest in the Next Room
Shiori Makimura
What happened?!
And Her Lover
Eight
Corpse
Yukiji Katsura
Um, this is different than before.
Shut up! I'd never get married
if I stayed looking like that!
I smell a case.
You're the one who did it.
Hmm, I never expected to get caught up
in a murder case at the hot springs.
What a delightful... I mean,
what a troubling situation this is.
For starters, we must contact the police!
Y-Yeah, you're right.
This is terrible! This is terrible!
No need for that!
She sees through to the one and only truth.
With the looks of a snooty softy
and the brains of a societal bum.
Her name is Great Detective Nagi!
The kiddy backpack doesn't
look out of place one bit.
That's not the jab you should be making!
Sis!
The Corpse's Little Sister
Hinagiku Katsura
I always thought you
were a no-good big sister,
but I never imagined you'd end up like this!
You have my sympathies,
but please try to remain calm.
Yes, I know.
There's actually something
I'd like for you all to see.
What?
A video...tape?
Yes.
I just received it
earlier by bike messenger.
I suspect it was taped by my sister.
What?!
First of Spring
I wonder if it's recording properly...
That's this room, right?
Yes, it appears to be.
Hina, by the time you see this,
your big sis may already be
one of the stars in the sky.
They put it well when they
said "beauty dies first".
Where does she get off saying that?
Um, never mind that.
The background scenery...
The truth is,
I was asked to come to this inn
by a letter from an unknown sender.
It seems this person
has a grudge against me.
But I don't know who it is yet.
I think they'll be visiting me
here in this room soon, but...
I don't really care anymore.
Hina, I want you to know,
if I should end up dead,
my killer will be the person
who shows up after this!
Make sure you catch the person
and sue them for plenty of damages! Got it?!
It's coming!
What?!
This is where it ends?!
No way! It got cut off
at the most crucial part!
This is awful!
It's almost as awful
as a mother who tricks her child
by putting honey on cucumber
and says, "Here's some melon!"
No, as awful as saying soy
sauce on pudding is sea urchin!
No, no!
It's as awful as putting dried seaweed
and soy sauce on mandarin oranges
I see.
and calling it salmon roe!
After killing the victim,
the culprit probably erased the part
that revealed who the murderer is
and then sent the tape.
In other words, this is a challenge
issued by the culprit to me!
I confess, I already have
a good idea of who the culprit is!
What?!
Is this true?!
Yes! The culprit is...
The culprit is?
None other than you!
What?! Me?!
But I'm just the guest
in the room next door!
But she's a super low-key character,
who's never appeared since Episode 23...
I appeared in Episode 25, too!
I've even seen through the trick,
right slick and lickety-split!
Trick #1
You summoned the victim to a meeting.
Don't come any closer!
You just try laying a hand on me
and I'll make you pay all the bar tabs
that I've accumulated!
Bills
What?!
And using a speckled snake
that just happened to be passing by...
Snaaaaake...
There you have it.
How about it? Perfect
detective work, right?!
You ask how it was, but...
Not to mention, you totally borrowed
the most famous trick in the universe.
Apologize to Sir Doyle.
Caught in the act! You're under arrest!
What?! You're wrong! I'm not the one!
Do not argue with me! Give it up!
Nooo!
Grab!
Don't treat my honey like she's a criminal!
Watch out, Miss!
That's my Hayate!
Miss, it appears the culprit
is someone else.
Yes, to be honest,
I had a feeling that it might be.
I see...
Which makes you three the suspicious ones!
Trick #2
Wh-Where in the world am I?
You three summoned the victim to a meeting
and using a giant speckled octopus
that just happened to be passing by...
Oooooctopus...
There you have it.
What's this giant speckled octopus about?!
More like, we weren't even in the scene!
Now, allow yourselves
to be arrested without resisting!
There are others more likely
to have motives, aren't there?!
What?
Oh, a motive...
Yes, you have a point there.
The person who might have the biggest
grudge against the victim would be...
It'd have to be none other
than the butler-in-debt.
What?!
H-Hold on a second! What are you saying?!
Stare...
Please don't all of you look at me
with such suspicion, too!
And of all the people,
I trusted you the most, too.
As I said, I am not the one!
Trick #3
I told you, it's not me!
With the speckled elephant
that just happened to be passing by...
Eeeelephant...
You look like you wouldn't
hurt a fly and yet...
Miss, your deductions are nonsense
based on hunches and inspiration!
Oh, Mr. Yama? I've caught the perp.
Besides, the scene has
switched somewhere along the way
This solves the case, but it won't
bring the victim back to life.
from a hot springs inn to Africa!
Wait, who the heck are you talking to?!
I guess we'll talk again on the
rooftop, gazing at the sunset.
HEY!
How many times do you have to kill me
before you're satisfied?!
The story's not making any progress here!
It's really embarrassing to be lying
here dressed like this, you know!
Hinagiku!
Uh, yes, ma'am!
I expect you to do things
properly, as scripted!
Yes, ma'am.
Plop.
Oh, what could that be?
Hibiya
Oh, that's a so-called dying message!
What's a "dying message"?
You don't even know that?
Allow me to explain.
A dying message is a hint
that the victim leaves conspicuously
right before death.
Cheney
Hibiya
I see.
But "Hibiya"...?
Allow me to explain some more.
Hibiya refers to an area close to Ginza,
which includes Yurakucho,
which is in Chiyoda Ward, Tokyo.
Incidentally, this is also where Japan's
first electric traffic signal was set up.
We don't need such in-depth information.
Anyway, if we can decipher
the meaning of this message,
we'll know who the culprit is, right?
It's suddenly becoming more
like a serious mystery now!
Yeah!
But this is very difficult.
Difficult?
No, this is not even close.
This is nothing compared
to the secrets of the pyramids and UFOs!
What?!
Uh, I don't know about this different
character with the glasses...
That's exactly right!
What?!
That's my Hayate!
You have a good instinct.
Just what I'd expect of my assistant!
Y-You think so?
Indeed. This crime was perpetrated
by a different character,
who is currently not here.
What?!
A different character?
That's right.
After murdering the victim,
the culprit ought to be
hiding somewhere else now!
And where in the world is that?
Don't tell me you're
going to say it's Hibiya.
Take another close look at that.
What?
Hibiya
No matter how you look
at it, it says "Hibiya".
Wrong.
This message includes
the kaki-no-tane crackers next to it, too!
What?!
Listen closely. What's written
there are the radicals on the right.
If you assume the crackers
are the radicals...
"Mixed Bath"
Surprise! It reads "mixed bath"!
Amazing, huh?
What a deduction out of left field...
Furthermore, this inn actually
conveniently has a mixed bath.
What?!
The culprit is certain to be here!
S-Surely not... No matter how you look at it,
there's no way that's true.
There he is!
And just who might the culprit be?
To be continued in the second half.
Your valuables! Quick!
(Kaneme no mono o! Hayaku!)
Did you pay the ward tax?
(Kuminzei haratta?)
The Flunking Girl Trio's
The Flunking Girl Trio Gluttony
Like a Dream
Gluttony, Like a Dream!
You know.
What?
Is this eating or a hot springs fan
service scene? Can we clarify that?
What?!
The effects of this hot spring are...
Rissy, that's after we eat! After we eat!
This is a merry-go-round of tastiness!
We haven't eaten yet! Not yet!
Gilgamesh.
That's not right!
Granny, isn't this delicious?
Who's there?!
Now, don't you say that the art is different
from the previous scene.
M-Maria, when
in the world did you get in here?!
Wait, so you're the culprit?!
No, I'm not!
Then, why?!
Now, now, don't sweat the details.
A sexy scene is a cliché
of suspense drama, right?
What?!
She is using a towel for this shoot,
but when you are actually bathing,
please refrain from using them in the water.
Oh, really!
Now, let's ride this momentum
and go for Cliché #2!
A gourmet scene!
Now, please enjoy!
Have your fill of this
fresh bounty from the sea!
We have prepared a magic show
for you after the Japanese ballad show.
One bottle of gasoline,
warmed to body temperature.
Yum.
And Cliché #3!
Bar Dead End
Interviewing people
at a bar on the outskirts of town!
Bar Mistress Klaus
So, what do you want?
Do you know anything about this person?
Do I know anything?
Hah! Do I ever!
That woman is my long separated
elder sister's friend's cousin
and she's the thieving bitch,
who stole my lover!
I feel like this has become more like
a daytime drama instead of suspense.
Damn you, you she-pig!
I'll turn you into cutlets and eat you!
Cliché #4.
I'm not done yet!
Yay! We did it!
Makimura and Izumi have the advantage!
Yes, this is building up in a nice way!
No, no, this is just getting tedious.
It's terrible!
Wait, Maria, could it be that you've
been in the hot spring this whole time?!
Yes!
Oh, and so, I went back to our room
and I discovered something terrible!
What?!
What is it, Maria?!
Quit dragging it out and tell us!
The body has disappeared!
What?!
I-It's true!
She's gone.
A body going missing
is as suspenseful as suspense gets!
This is bad. The case
is 5 seconds away from going cold!
But I wonder who hid it.
It's got to be the culprit, of course!
The culprit?
Yes,
he thinks he's interfering
with my investigation by stirring things up!
All right, since it's come to this...
Wh-What is this all of a sudden?!
These guys should be able to
find some kind of definitive clue.
And so, we've spotted this
on the underside of the table.
Th-This is...?!
It appears to be a voice recorder.
Let me see that!
So, the scream we heard was this?
So it seems...
But why? What does this mean?
I got it!
The mystery is solved, my dear Watson.
"M-My dear Watson"?
Next Nagi's hint.
Now, do you know the culprit and the trick?
Uh, um...
Give me candy!
Oh, no, wrong. Trick or treat!
Huh?
Trick or treat!
Huh?! W-Wait!
Give me candy! Trick or treat!
It's been really tough
for Halloween to catch on in Japan...
Wrong kind of trick.
Why have we suddenly come
to a place like this?
It can't be helped.
Having the climax scene
on an overhanging cliff
is the biggest suspense dramas cliché.
We just need Eiichiro Funakoshi
and we'd have it all.
And now, I will explain how
this incident was perpetrated.
Hey, wait!
This crime was actually not
perpetrated in that room!
What?!
If you assume that it happened
at a completely different inn
in a different room, it all makes sense.
What do you mean?
Explain it to us so we can understand.
Roger that.
Trick #4
First, the culprit met
with the victim at some other inn.
And on that occasion,
the culprit recorded the victim's scream.
After this...
Hey, h-hold on! It'll show, it'll show!
The culprit went to a different inn
with a similar construction.
In other words, the culprit snuck her body
into our room at that inn.
Be gentle!
Oh, stop! Be gentle!
And then...
Setting the victim's scream on a timer,
the culprit created the illusion
that the crime had taken place there!
We just heard a scream come
from that inn, didn't we?!
Yes!
It was all a plot to create an alibi!
Me! Me, me! I have a question!
What is it?
Where's the proof?
With just the voice recorder,
it seems a bit forced...
The greatest proof is
on that videotape we saw first!
What?!
On this tape!
Play!
First of Spring
I wonder if it's recording properly...
Stop!
I don't see anything unusual about it...
Don't you notice something
about the scroll hanging there?
First of Spring
In Dire Distress
Here Goes the Afro
The Actual Room
Oh, my, it's completely different
from the one in that room.
Precisely.
The culprit wasn't thorough
and failed to pay attention
to the difference in the hanging scrolls!
There are also 4 other discrepancies.
Those who find them all
will have a chance to win...
Now that we've gotten this far,
you know who the culprit is, right?
Um... um...
Oh! I seem to recall there was
one person who came late!
Yes! And she brought
that videotape, didn't she?!
As I recall, she said it came
by bike messenger or something,
sounding oddly defensive about it...
If she's actually the culprit,
that just might explain everything!
Which means...!
What?
M-Me?!
Hinagiku, I never imagined
that you were the culprit.
But it totally makes sense now!
Yes, she is the least
suspicious of all of us.
Which is exactly what makes her suspicious!
Yup, yup!
That was brilliant detective work!
I never imagined that I'd be caught,
but you're right. Just
as you said, I'm the culprit.
No, you're wrong!
What?!
The culprit is not Hinagiku.
Hold on! This is supposed to be my scene!
The shock of this has woken me
from the tranquilizers!
Considering this turn of events,
I'm the only one who could be the culprit.
But that would be too normal and boring.
Um, it's hard to tell who's talking,
so would you mind stopping that?
You've all forgotten to begin with!
That there's one more person
that's incredibly suspicious!
What?!
One more person?
That's right! That person is...!
That person is?!
The person behind the Voice from Heaven!
Me?
M-Miss, isn't that too deus ex machina,
no matter how you look at it?
This is fine as it is.
But I don't know if our audience
will be satisfied with that...
This is a suspense story
starring me and produced by me.
I will permit no one to complain!
Hey!
A huge wave!
Run!
Hold it right there!
Sis?!
That's enough already!
What's the big idea eliminating
my presence halfway through?!
You're a corpse! Quit coming back
to life over and over again!
Like hell I can pretend
to stay dead the whole time!
Darn it! The script I pulled
an all-nighter to write is ruined!
Since it's come to this,
I'll fall back to my last resort!
And now, it's fan service time!
The best thing to do in autumn really is
to lounge in a hot spring
and admire the colored leaves.
Agreed! It's so soothing!
I hope you all have a "Good
Journey, Like a Dream", too.
This is pure heaven!
Wh-Why is the men's bath this small?!
Huh? Did you say something?
Don't move! It's caught! It's caught!
What's gotten caught?
No! Don't move!
And so, that was the
"Gluttony, Like a Dream",
the deluxe 20 minute special.
Next time, they will be combating siblings.
Oh, we'd forgotten!
There's no time left!
This Week's Butler Battle
Come forth, Mysterious
Butler of Darkness No. 2!
Defeat the butler Hayate Ayasaki
and make him one of us!
Make him one of us!
Go!
B-Fire!
Here goes!
What? This is...?!
B-Fire!
Go! Hayate Blaster!
Just you remember this!
If you're going to fight,
bring it on, Mysterious Butlers!
Huh? Wait, what am I doing?
This Week's Butler Battle
The End
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Ba-boom! Boing-oing-oing,
boing-oing-oing! I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I'm everybody's idol, Yukiji Katsura!
What are you doing here, Miss Katsura?
That's cold, Ayasaki. But more importantly!
When in the world is my character
song going to be finished?!
Hmm, with Miss Katsura,
I don't think the sales seem that promising.
Agreed.
Pairing up with Tama on a character
song would probably be about just right.
You've certainly learned
to speak out, Ayasaki.
Our next guest will be the hamster!
See you!
Preview
So, Miss, you used to
call Sakuya "Big Sister Saku"?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
A thing of the unpleasant past.
You've never looked after li'l kids,
and that's why ya still haven't
grown outta bein' a kiddy.
Don't mock me! If I had younger siblings,
I could look after them
way better than you, Saku!
For real? Then prove it.
Very well!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Do You Like Pretty Rich Big Sisters?"
Did you know?
Next Hayate the Combat Butler
Do You Like Pretty Rich Big Sisters?
The first thing the Wright brothers flew
was the younger brother's mobile.