Hey, quit slacking, transfer student.
Start cleaning.
He's such a weird guy.
He's always staring out into space and daydreaming.
Just like an airhead!
Lucky! The rain stopped.
It's pretty.
We almost missed it.
Because it's an expected view.
But unexpectedly, those kinds of views are usually the best.
The ship will depart on Monday at midnight.
We must meet with the people who will pick us up at Hotaru before the evening.
So we only have five days left, huh?
It'd be great if they'd just let us leave without any fuss.
I wonder if they will.
We should still be careful.
I don't want to leave any trouble behind.
If we can leave without a trace and disappear just like smoke, then...
Scythe!
What is it, Miss Garland?
Where's Phantom?
You better not be scheming anything.
Phantom?
I thought she'd be with you today.
She's nowhere to be found.
Crap!
Just take your eyes off her for a second, and...
This isn't something new.
She'll come back at night.
Weapons are missing, too.
A lot of them.
Oh?
That sounds pretty dangerous.
I wonder what she wants to do.
Whatever.
I can probably guess where she went.
Contact McGuire and Mr. Shiga. I'll go after Phantom right away.
So it has begun, huh?
She's just a kid.
Is something wrong with your head?
I'm just continuing what Zwei left behind.
But-
Drei?
Yep. That's my name from today on.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'll be counting on you.
Hey.
You're not gonna run away, right?
Jesus...
I'm not a babysitter.
I'm sorry for what happened the other day.
It probably scared you.
Not really...
Back when I was living in the U.S., she was my...
I didn't think she'd come all the way here for me.
I never thought she'd punch me right after seeing me.
But I'm glad I was able to see her once more.
Even if she hit me...
I've already talked to her about it,
so I guess that's the end of it.
Okay.
I'll pay you back next time.
Let's go to a movie again.
Later.
Good bye.
Huh? Why?
Oh yeah, Mom's not coming back today.
Yo, it's not like this is the first time we've met.
Don't be so scared.
Why are you here?
You're Godoh's princess, right?
Godoh? Are you talking about my uncle?
Uncle, huh?
Whatever, I'll leave the explanations for later.
Umm...
You might not see these very often in this country,
but yeah, it's real.
Get on.
Let me tell you about...
...your beloved Reiji's secret.
I thought you'd be arriving soon, Phantom.
Just give me a second.
Great timing.
I have something to talk to you about, too.
Cal...
The game continues.
No one is allowed to touch Zwei or Ein.
If you guys don't abide by that rule,
I'll kill the princess.
I won't let anyone get in my way.
Don't touch my prey.
Quit doing such stupid things.
Do you really hate Zwei that much?
No shit!
I'll never forgive traitors and bastards who ruin other people's normal lives.
There's a line you should never cross.
Wake up already, Cal.
If you cross it, you'll fall into hell.
I've always thought it was weird.
Lizzie, why were you always so kind to me?
I didn't want you to become an assassin.
Both Zwei and I,
we thought the same way.
Everyone is so selfish...
I am Phantom.
If you don't like it, try stopping me.
Right here, right now.
I'll draw when this song ends.
If you don't shoot by then, you must be one hell of a naïve person.
So naïve that you deserve to die here.
Cal.
I...
...don't want to shoot you.
Cal!
Why didn't you shoot?
You're asking me why...?
Are you sure you want such a heavy one?
Yeah, I don't want to shoot unless I have to.
But this thing... This thing is getting heavier and heavier...
It's too heavy...
Clau...
This will go on for three or four days, so eat sparingly.
Why are you doing this?
Please explain the situation.
Why are you doing this? Even killing someone...
That's my-
This is the last person you contacted, right?
You read this as "Reiji", right?
Who are you to Reiji-san?
A previous apprentice...
...and his ex.
You're lying.
Why do you think that?
What do you know about him?
By the way, Reiji was the one who taught me how to use this.
What do you think he was doing back in the states?
He was an assassin.
And he was the best of them all.
He killed countless amounts of people.
No way...
He lied to you.
Two years ago, Godoh Daisuke died in Los Angeles.
If I remember correctly, he's your uncle, right?
How do you know-
Of course I know. And I know more about it than you do.
Godoh Daisuke was a part of a gang...
And he's not your uncle, but actually your brother from a different mother...
I know everything.
You're lying!
What's up with you?
Are you unsatisfied with being the daughter of a gang family?
That's not all.
Godoh Daisuke didn't die by accident.
He was killed because of your beloved Reiji...
Stop it!
It's up to you to believe it or not.
However, there will be a bloodbath soon because of you.
Think about what I told you when that happens.
You'll understand everything.
What's your goal?
A death match.
A death match with Reiji.
No way...
The sun's up.
Now, let it begin.
Hello?
Sorry, this ain't Mio.
What did you do to her?
Don't worry.
I don't plan on doing anything to her.
You're already so busy with the escape preparations,
I don't think you'll be able to handle an extra hostage.
So I'm looking after her for you.
I wasn't your only target?
This has nothing to do with her.
Didn't you want to return to a normal lifestyle?
Just as you wished, I'm protecting the lifestyle that you wanted.
I won't let the Godoh Group or Inferno do anything.
You'll be fine as long as you go to school normally.
But you can't just disappear out of the blue.
I don't know where you're running to,
but if you leave my sight,
Mio will be seeing her brother!
Remember this. I'm always watching you.
This time, you won't be able to run...
This time...
I can't believe she betrayed Inferno.
That just shows how much she hates me.
We should act independently now.
Independently?
My, my.
Fujieda Mio was kidnapped by Phantom!
Why are you letting that bitch run free?!
You've got pretty amazing sources.
Quit messing around with me!
Wasn't this part of your calculations?!
No way.
That girl is Bro's memento!
She's not your toy!
This event might damage the name of Inferno.
I will try my best to protect Ms. Fujieda Mio.
I'll go search for Drei,
and you'll follow her instructions.
I'll kill her and rescue Mio.
But she's watching us...
If we were to do anything reckless, Mio will...
Even if I'm gone, Drei won't do anything to Mio.
Why are you so certain?
Her only target is you.
But...
We're not cornered yet.
Control your emotions. The one who can't do that...
...will die.
Don't worry, Mr. Shiga.
I've summoned my private staff.
The ultimate weapons that were perfectly trained.
Extreme determination with suppressed emotions.
They will end everything.
I promise you a satisfying end.
They won't fail, no matter what.
We are...
...ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
We are phantoms with no identity.
If you can live on...
...that'll be proof that I lived.