"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
You've been doing all sorts
of stuff for a while now,
but do you know what's inside?
They all seem the same anyway.
Oh, isn't this common sense?
If you don't do this, all the money
in the world wouldn't be enough!
That piece of common sense has
a rather narrow strike zone...
At least, that's not an ordinary
person's common sense.
"Ways to Spend Summer"
It's not just for figures.
There are people who seek out
the cards they want, too.
How do you tell when it's cards?
They all weigh the same.
Stuff like this has always
had legends and rumors.
Like the location of the good cards,
or that there are certain
markings, or a set pattern...
By the way, I can usually get the card I want
if it's the type that makes you buy candy,
if the box has been freshly opened.
There's a pattern behind it...
If you think about it
normally, that's amazing...
But there's no way I can praise her for that!
If it's that easy to figure out, don't
the valuable ones disappear quickly?
That's right. In regions
where the masters live,
the rare cards and the secret
figures disappear really quickly.
When the display at the shop looks
like a fill-in-the-blanks exam sheet,
I feel nothing but despair.
But the real problem is that there's
still hope that I might have a shot...
That really is a problematic personality.
I hear that some of those
collectors just rake it all in,
and buy a whole bunch?
Oh yeah, they're out there.
When you buy it in a bundle,
it's faster to complete the set,
and it gets easier to read
the shipment patterns.
Is that so?
Well, it's what you call grown-up shopping
that lets your wallet do the talking.
Thanks to a part-time job.
I see... Grown-up shopping, huh?
You say grown-up shopping, but
what you're doing is so childish.
You have a strong wish to dominate,
or rather, you just want
it all to yourself...
Perhaps it's more appropriate
to say "big kid shopping"...
Am I the only one that
thinks doing something else
with that much zest would be more productive?
Recently, Akihabara has been
in the media eye a lot,
for one reason or another.
Yeah, with content that's
really painful to watch.
The specials are good,
but there's no way the content they
come up with is very friendly.
Of course, they're exaggerating at times,
but don't you think they're based in fact?
But, despite that, things
that started among otaku
have become a fad lately,
like in dramas and songs.
News and tabloid shows use anime
or game music all the time, too.
No... I think they use
stuff like that because
they think ordinary people won't
notice where the music comes from.
Speaking of otaku...
You see on bulletin boards often
that male otaku want to date
female otaku that share
similar tastes and hobbies,
but you never hear from female otaku
that want to date male otaku at all.
Why is that? When you get
obsessed with 2-D images,
that love goes deeper in girls than boys?
Maybe it looks like they feel
uncomfortable about the future?
I'm sure that a lot of them have proper jobs.
Or rather, don't go asking me about it!
Now that it's hot, they
suddenly start to show up.
They're so noisy and quick, so I hate 'em!
They're dirty, too.
They say that Musashi Miyamoto was able
to catch a fly with his chopsticks.
Whoa, seriously?
I can't believe he wanted
to touch something like that
with an item you use to hold
food with. That's so disgusting.
Is that how it is? Though I get it...
So amazing! I can't slap mosquitoes at all.
Oh, why?
Like when it gets smushed,
and I get blood on my hands,
it's a bit disgusting.
You have a point...
That's my blood.
But what do you do if a mosquito
stops on your arm and stuff?
I'll try to shoo it away, like,
"shoo!" or try to blow it away.
Did you know?
When you tense your arm
when a mosquito bites it,
the mosquito can't pull out.
You're kidding!
Just watch...
You are already dead.
And you are already bitten.
And when you tense your arm even
more, the mosquito explodes.
Stop it, stop it!
Itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy...
Maybe it would have been better
to just hurry up and slap it.
Miyuki-san, are you going overseas
again during summer vacation?
No, we're not going this year.
But I think we'll be visiting
our relatives in the country.
The girl living nearby who attends
Ryouou comes with me often
when I go to the summer
festivals back in the country.
She's like a little sister to me.
Really?
I see, so you're going to go to
a summer festival, Iwasaki-san?
You seem like you'd look great in a yukata.
That's not true...
"Thud"
I know that she's complimenting me,
but I can't honestly be happy about it.
It's like she's saying that I'm flat...
"Izumi"
Welcome! I'll be right out!
Hey, morning.
You just got up?! You're such a sloth!
No, there's something that's
been on my mind lately...
What's that?
Like, "Did the alarm clock go off?"
And, "It's not like someone else
turned the alarm clock off, right?"
Oh, I know what you mean!
How the switch has been turned
off, and you don't know about it!
Despite that, it gets hot in the afternoons,
so you can't stay asleep for all that long.
It's already way into the afternoon.
Kona-chan, it's morning! Get up!
Izumi-kun, would you like
to eat lunch with me?
I thought I'd walk home together
with you, Konata-kun...
Hey, Konata.
Why is that game's main character
so popular, unconditionally?
Dunno. Maybe it's because
it wouldn't be a game
unless he was popular to a certain extent?
Geez, you have to properly
do all your homework!
It's not like I'm worried about you at all!
All right. If you say so,
Konata, I'll do it...
Hey, Konata.
Why do heroines in those kind of
games never have any boyfriends,
despite being so cute and having
such wonderful personalities?
Couldn't they take their pick?
Dunno. Maybe because it wouldn't
be a game if they were taken?
Hey! Konata, I'm here to play!
Though the main reason is to
see how Yutaka was doing...
Oh, Sis, good evening!
Konata, your dad was calling for you.
Okay!
Yutaka started on her homework,
so lend me some manga...
Konata, are you all right?
Don't you have to study?
Haven't you been playing
for all this time now?
No, it's not like that!
You just have bad timing,
catching me on break every time!
Really?
"Grin, grin"
But doesn't that end up meaning
that you take a lot of breaks?
And so, I have an image
to uphold in my house,
so I'd like to sit in front of the desk,
but I end up taking lots of breaks.
Geez, it's like that because you
don't usually study seriously!
But I have to say,
it's not that I don't
understand how you feel.
What, Kagami, you have a hunch
about this kind of thing?
Well, if I take a so-called break,
and start reading a book
I've been wanting to read,
I end up taking more breaks even
when I go back to studying.
You can't really stop stuff
like that in the middle.
Even with manga, you think about
stopping after the next volume,
but end up reading several dozen
volumes of a given series...
Or when you rent DVDs for a drama
you missed a few episodes of,
you end up watching the entire series.
Yeah, but then the rest of the
episodes turn out to be boring.
I see. So, Director, you started
to gather dolls, then...
Sis, can I change the channel?
Sure. I was just watching a random channel.
Is there a show on that you want to watch?
Yeah. They're going to start the
Cross-Country Sweets Special now.
That's right, you love sweets too, Yu-chan.
It's like something Kagami's
family would watch.
That looks tasty!
This is the Haruhi Dance of the sweets world!
But you know, stuff like this...
Even when you see something you like,
usually the shop is really far
away... Doesn't that depress you?
Like, we live in Saitama, but when
they say the shop is in Nagoya...
It's always like that, but I can't
help but watch. Such a shame!
"Summer Class Day"
"Gloomy"
Yuki-chan, good morning...
Wait, what's wrong?
I went to the dentist yesterday, but...
You're still going?
I escaped from the office in the middle...
Please tell me if it hurts.
It hurts!
Oh, it will be over very soon.
Okay...
...and that's how it went.
That's so true. They never stop!
Just listening to that puts me in pain!
Not only do we have classes
during summer break,
they give us homework too!
I can't deal with all of
this! It's summer vacation!
But you don't do most of the
homework yourself, anyway.
In the first place, unlike
elementary school or junior high,
you don't have research
projects or book reports.
So don't you think it's easier now?
You just have to solve problems.
There were also art projects
and posters as homework...
Stuff like that, you know, you can
have your parents help you out,
and the parents get really gung-ho
and finish it for you, right?
I've gotten awards for those
things, like posters and stuff.
Oh yeah, there was that.
I told Dad it was thanks to him, and
that I had a better opinion of him.
He seemed really happy about it!
Isn't that where a parent
is supposed to be angry?
Lucky Star!
You have to buy at least
five in one shopping trip!
When I see this commercial,
I always get jealous.
When I was a kid, and read
fairy tales about candy houses,
I always wanted to eat a tummy
full of sweets and stuff.
I know that feeling,
but when you actually get a
hold of a whole bunch of stuff,
even when it's your favorite,
you kind of lose interest in it.
I see...
That's right. It's smelly all year.
So, I was thinking. Summer vacation
homework really is a pain,
because you try to do it all in
the second half of the vacation.
That was sudden... Or rather,
that's pretty obvious.
And I'm thinking that if I work on
it bit by bit from the beginning,
I won't be fretting in the end.
You finally came to that
conclusion at this age?
In the end, you're a senior already,
so do it without losing concentration!
So, I'm heading over to your
place tomorrow, so be ready.
I'll bring a souvenir.
So that's what you mean by "bit by bit."
Are you planning on coming here
every day during summer vacation?
Maybe every other week.
Shut up.
Hey there! It's hot out.
S'up. Yeah, no kidding.
I've got air conditioning going in the room.
Oh, so pleasant, so pleasant!
You're totally unwinding.
Every year, right when you don't
want to do anything, summer ends...
And before I know it, summer
vacation is already over.
Don't go saying stuff like that.
Set a quota for yourself this year
to properly do your homework, okay?
Well, every year before vacation starts,
I think about how I need to do my best...
Really?
This is the season that you see a lot of
"I haven't done my homework"
situations in manga, too.
You're right.
When I read stuff like that, it
feels like I've got the idea.
Don't you feel like you don't
have to do it after all,
when you think about how
everyone else is doing it?
Of course not. Do it!
In the first place, if you're talking
like that, don't come over to copy mine.
I'm getting a bit thirsty...
I guess I'll bring some cold barley tea.
Oh, Sis...
I'm sorry, but can you bring me
my math problem set book
from my room, please?
Sure, sure.
Man, it's hot!
Because you don't want to leave
the air-conditioned room,
you try to ask someone a favor
when they're stepping out...
But sometimes it takes a while
before someone decides to step out.
And in the winter, you don't want
to get up from the kotatsu heater,
so you ask someone that stands
up to do something for you.
Hey...
S'up! It's so hot out!
S'up.
Welcome.
I've come bearing ice cream.
Take whatever flavor you want!
I mean, it's not like I'm
contributing with the homework.
Those eyes of the Marimokkori...
I see!
Why is it that at times like this,
you start thinking that you wanted
to eat the flavor that
someone else is eating?
I'm currently reading manga about
entrance exams to Tokyo University.
Oh, that series?
Don't you think when you read it
that even you can somehow get
accepted to Tokyo University?
That is, if you work that hard!
Now, that's being awfully simple.
Let's say that you can use that
method to enter Tokyo University.
Without friends who'll toss aside their
class material to study with you,
teachers that will give you
extra classes like that,
and a leader to take control
of the situation...
Don't you think the plan would fail if
you didn't meet all those conditions?
I see. I guess things don't
work out that well...
There are quite a few out there...
People who think that after
reading manga or watching a drama
that they can easily change themselves...
Well, I think about how I
need to do my best and study,
but somehow I always end up getting sleepy.
Do you have a good way of staying awake?
I heard it's better to take short naps,
instead of forcing yourself
to stay up too much.
Is that true after all?
I heard that somewhere, so
that's what I'm doing...
But my naps turn into hours
of real sleep... see?
You have such a weak will!
Hello!
Hello, Yutaka-chan!
Um, can I have a moment?
What's wrong, Yu-chan?
You can ask us older girls whatever you want!
A friend from junior high
apparently has a boyfriend now,
and she asked me, "What should
I get him for his birthday?"
But I'm not sure what the answer should be.
What should I do? I feel really awkward.
F-For the time being, Yu-chan,
there are places on the 'net that
you can seek that kind of advice.
So why don't you look at places like that?
There might be threads
that ask the same thing.
I'll lend you my computer, too!
I'll do that.
They had Trai_ Man and stuff like that,
but you can get advice
on those things as well?
It's getting pretty normal nowadays.
Nowadays, anything goes, I guess.
That's true. I feel like the
answers to the math drill sheets
are lying around somewhere, so I get jealous
of all the current elementary
school and junior high kids.
I feel that with the evolution
of technology and community,
the train of thought and willpower
of the users are put to waste...
Especially when I'm looking at her.
This is strange. I was just
going to copy homework.
When things are a little different
and I have a gallery watching,
I feel something like pride
suddenly popping up...
Come to think of it, when is the
festival at your place, Kagami?
What are you talking about?
It's over already. It was the
same as what we did last year.
Why didn't you tell me?
We have college entrance exams coming up,
and if we told you, we knew
you'd definitely want to go...
We didn't get to go either, okay?
Instead of ours, why not go
to your neighborhood festival?
Is that over as well already?
My neighborhood? Come to think of
it, I wonder when they hold it?
They're out there...
The ones that show up to
festivals held elsewhere,
but show absolutely no interest
in the ones in their neighborhood.
Are you the type that doesn't want
to bump into friends around here?
Oh man, even if we've got exams,
I can't just study forever!
By the way, there is a fireworks
show near my house tomorrow evening.
That's it! All of us should
play together at least once!
I guess it will be a good breather.
Come to think of it, there's a fireworks show
near your house tomorrow, right, Minami-chan?
Yes.
Oh... I would like to see Japanese fireworks.
So let's all go watch it together, Minami.
Minami-chan, are you free tomorrow?
I'm fine...
Then it's decided, Minami!
Let's go, Iwasaki-san.
Yeah...
Wait? Iwasaki-san?
It's a pretty famous fireworks
show, right, Min--Iwasaki-san?
It's really hard to change
how you call someone
when you're used to using one way!
Oh, but it's pretty far away,
and since it's popular, it'll
have a big turnout, right?
Yu-chan, will you be all right?
You just got over a cold recently, right?
Oh! I heard that it was
going to be hot tomorrow,
so shall we save it for another day?
No, don't worry about me.
It's always like this.
As the health rep, I'll be with
you, so it will be all right...
Yutaka...
I see... That's true! Thank you, Minami-chan!
And so, it turns out we're
going to go see the fireworks.
But facing entrance exams,
studying for entrance exams...
It's boring, because there's
so little room for play.
Kagami and the others
are so serious about it.
Well, I see where they're coming from.
Konata, you can do as you please.
I dragged Kanata around
to all sorts of places,
and made quite a few memories.
She scolded me for it,
but adolescence won't wait for you at all!
Then I guess I'll find a boyfriend
and go make some memories.
That is absolutely forbidden!
I won't allow anything like a boyfriend!
Uh, Dad, what you're saying makes no sense.
By the way, you want to come with
us to the fireworks, Yu-chan?
Konata, how much do you have to
test your father's personality?
Actually, I'm already going.
We're going to meet up
at Minami-chan's house.
I'm so saddened by all of this!
Oh, you are?
We'll be going now!
Take care.
The train is here!
You're late!
Sorry to make you wait.
Yutaka-chan came with you?
Oh, um...
Hey! Over here, over here!
Hello there.
Yeah, hello.
Patricia-san!
You all here for the fireworks
as well, Konata-san?
You look good in that yukata!
What the heck?!
"Iwasaki"
Huh?
I see... so Minami-chan was the
girl living near Miyuki-san.
What a coincidence!
I'm really surprised!
Yeah...
Welcome.
Now, here you go.
Excuse us!
Thank you!
Oh? I don't have enough?
I have the right number, though...
Mother, are you counting yourself as well?
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Nine.
Oh my, you're right.
Now I get it.
Sorry to have bothered you!
So this is Minami-chan's house!
Wow, a huge dog! So scary!
It's all right.
It doesn't bark at all, and it's
really friendly towards people!
I see... even when they're big,
if they act like that, it actually
makes them look a bit cute.
What? It's growling and stuff?
So she's the type of person that
somehow makes all dogs growl.
When I was a kid, I always wondered
if fireworks still looked round, even
when you saw them from the side.
Oh? They don't look flat?
Come on...
They broadcast fireworks
shows every so often on TV,
but the atmosphere you can enjoy
when you watch it live is wonderful.
You're right.
But I've been thinking for a while now...
You know how every time
a giant firework goes up,
they announce the name of some
shop in the shopping district,
like, "This one was brought
to you by this-and-that"...
Doesn't that really crush the mood?
Y-You're right.
Huh? Yu-chan, you look a bit pale...
I'm fine.
I'll be fine, so you all go watch.
But...
I'll stay behind.
Minami-chan!
That was wonderful.
Man, this really felt like summer!
But...
Unlike in manga, you're left with
more than beautiful memories.
I got bitten by mosquitoes all over!
Itchy!
They say it itches more if
you scratch it, you know?
And when you take the yukata off, the
line made by the sash itches too!
Oh, right, right!
So pretty...
It really was pretty.
But I'm sorry I troubled you.
Oh, there they are. Hey!
Yu-chan, were you guys fine with
all the bug bites and stuff?
Yeah. We weren't bitten at all.
Oh, there are people who get bitten easily,
and then there are people who
hardly get bitten. I'm jealous.
No, maybe the mosquitoes
read the atmosphere here...
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
This is Akira Kogami, your navigator!
I'm Daisuke Ono, the assistant.
Time flies by, and Lucky Channel
is already on episode 20...
You're not a crow today.
You're not a dog today.
Beep. Then would you like to take a look
at the relay footage, just in case?
"Studio" "Forest"
I wonder exactly where Shiroishi-kun
is walking about right now.
Wow, Mt. Fuji is so pretty!
Oh well, that's enough.
Then, bye-nee!
Bye-nee!
Shiraishi-kun? Shiraishi-kun!
Missus! This is what you wanted, right?
Hello! This is Minoru Shiraishi.
Now, I'd like you to listen up! "Omuko
Rumba (the bridegroom rumba)!"
One, two, three, four!
♪ The voice of happiness echoes ♪
♪ A church in June ♪
♪ The epitome of happiness ♪
♪ Is truly this moment ♪
♪ Ah, if things were going
to turn out this way ♪
♪ I shouldn't have bought that house ♪
♪ To think that the
bride would run away ♪
♪ It's a situation right out of a manga ♪
♪ Fretting, Omuko Rumba
(the bridegroom rumba) ♪
♪ Someone help me, oh my god ♪
♪ What am I going to do now? ♪
♪ Even my boss from work is here ♪
♪ One two three, two two three,
Omuko Rumba (the bridegroom rumba) ♪
♪ No! ♪
Cha-ra! Cha-ra-ra! Cha!
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
Misao here.
Ayano here.
Hey, Ayano,
Hiiragi is awfully cold-hearted.
She always runs over to see that shorty.
Now, now...
Does our love not reach Hiiragi at all?!
Next episode: Pandora's Box.
Ayano is giving me the cold shoulder too.