So, Fuku-chan, what you're
trying to tell me is this...
Chocolate poured into a form,
then cooled and hardened isn't homemade.
That's why you won't accept it.
That's what you're saying, right?
Well... to put it plainly, yes.
I see.
Okay, fine!
Fuku-chan, if that's the
way you feel about it...
I won't forget this!
Next year, I'll slap you across the face
with a masterpiece that
will satisfy even you!
Kaburaya Middle School
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
The Case of the Homemade Chocolates
It's just too hard to make chocolate
out of cocoa beans, isn't it?!
It does look that way.
But I'm not giving up.
I just have to make the greatest
handmade chocolate there is!
And if Fuku-chan still has any complaints,
I'll lock him up against a wall somewhere,
and read every last word
of this book to him.
And if that's still not good enough...
I'll cram the chocolate into his mouth!
S-Stob!
Mayaka-san... I'm with you!
Huh?!
Hey, man...
If there's anything I can do
to help, please tell me!
I know, Chi-chan! Do you know of
any place that sells ingredients
to fancy pastry shops and so forth?
Let's see... There's a store
next to the market
that deals in ingredients
intended for professional use.
Do you want me to show you where?
Really?!
Yes.
Hooray!
Make sure that Fuku-chan...
He won't hear anything from me.
All right, how about this Sunday?
Have they forgotten I'm here?
Okay, show me where it is.
Oh, Oreki...
Hm?
Don't you say anything either, okay?
Yeah.
I mean it!
I won't say a thing.
And I'd appreciate it if you'd
stop glaring at me like that.
Game Center
That's Satoshi's bike.
Hey, Hotaro! Nice timing,
passing by here like this.
What do you say to a game
for old time's sake?
I guess there's no reason
for me to hurry home.
I haven't been in here since middle school.
Me either.
I'll take the Viper II. Hotaro,
you'll take the Raiden, right?
It's the only one I know how to use.
Area: Airport. Get ready.
I was sure he'd concentrate
on evading, but...
Is this how Satoshi usually fights?
No, this is clearly different.
Satoshi's play back when
we were in middle school
was focused only on winning as his goal.
He would do whatever it takes to win.
And if he did lose, he didn't
try to hide his frustration,
and was an awfully sore loser.
Come on, move!
Let's switch places and go again!
Is he trying to draw me in?
Man, that was a good game!
Superb joystick action there.
Well done, Hotaro.
Yeah.
Hey,
there at the end, why did
you charge in like that?
When it comes to robots, hand-to-hand
fighting is more adventurous.
Don't you think so?
Yeah, this is who Satoshi is now.
He's changed since middle school.
Jeez!
What good will it do to tense up now?
I'm sure he will accept it from you.
I sure hope so.
By the way, Chi-chan,
is there anyone that you like?
Huh?
Um... I...
Itchy... Hm?
"This chocolate bar is a present to you.
From Oreki Tomoe, trembling
with 'sympathy.'"
Sympathy
Oreki-san, good morning.
Morning. So tell me,
how did Ibara's chocolate go?
It's finished. But it was
quite a bit of work.
She had to sample different
kinds of chocolate.
I'll bet she gobbled
them up in no time flat.
Oh, that's not nice, Oreki-san.
Sorry.
However, as a result, she
completed her masterpiece.
That must be what it means to put
one's whole heart into something.
It's really nice.
So, what's she going to
do with the chocolate?
Well, from what I heard, Mayaka-san
can't get out of her Manga Club.
That's why she's going to leave it
in the club room, or something.
It's too bad.
Hm...
I think Satoshi will be thrilled
with the whole production.
Oh...
Oreki-san, um...
Today... is Valentine's Day...
In my family, it's our practice not
to give year-end or summer gifts,
and as such, on Valentine's Day, too...
Does this mean...?
Um...
Is she saying...
what, exactly?
It's supposed to snow today.
No way, for real?
I didn't bring an umbrella.
W-We're going to be late, huh?
Y-Yeah.
Shall we get going?
Earth Science Prep Room
To Fuku-chan, please accept
this Valentine's chocolate.
Hotaro...
Are you on your way to the club room?
Nope, I'm waiting in the library
until either the sleet lets up,
or it turns to snow.
It's too cold in the club room.
Are you going to the club room?
Yeah, I am.
Apparently, Ibara is stuck in
Manga Club and can't come.
Word travels fast. Chitanda-san?
Well, I'll be off.
Satoshi...
Good luck.
With what, for heaven's sake?
Earth Science Prep Room
Hm?
Library
Oreki-san...
Oh, Chitanda...
Do you know where Fukube-san is?
He didn't show up?
No. I thought maybe
something had come up.
I saw him around a half hour ago,
and he said he was
going to the club room.
All right, I'll wait a little longer.
Fukube-san is taking his time.
Oreki-san!
Please wait! Something awful happened!
It finally stopped sleeting,
and I was about to go home.
Sorry, but tell me about it tomorrow.
Hey...
I'm sorry, but at least
hear what I have to say.
This is all my fault.
I carelessly left the room open,
and did the worst thing to Mayaka-san...
Satoshi...
What happened?
Oh, well...
The chocolate...
Mayaka-san's chocolate...
has been stolen!
Huh?
Ugh...
All right. I'll help you out.
Okay.
I didn't want to see Ibara
once she found out that her
chocolate had been stolen.
After all, I don't handle
the horror genre very well.
A History of Hannya Masks
Risshun ('Dawn of Spring')
When the first signs of spring appear
Hyouka
Ah, Oreki-san...
Freshly waxed
No entrance
It doesn't look like we can use
the west stairs to the 4th floor.
Hm...
Let's go up by the east stairs.
Oh, excuse me a second.
Industrial Arts Club Graduation Exhibit
Does this look level to you?
It's crooked.
A trapezoid?
You lowered it too much.
Huh? Hm...
How did that happen?
It was sitting right here.
Heart-shaped, about this big,
in clear plastic wrapping.
That's pretty big.
It was right here until I went
to go look for Fukube-san.
When did you return to the club room?
Just after 5:00. If only
I had taken the trouble
to lock the door during those 15 minutes.
Chitanda-san, this isn't something
you should beat yourself up over.
I'm far more at fault
for having been so late.
Have you told Ibara about this?
No, I haven't. Maybe it's cowardly of me,
but I don't plan to do that until
I've looked as much as I can.
And it's nowhere in this room, right?
Right. Fukube-san and I searched
the room and around the building.
Satoshi, too?
I ran into her on the stairs, so we
both came to the room together.
I see. By the way, how long was
that Industrial Arts guy there?
Industrial Arts?
The guy with the glasses.
The boy from the Industrial Arts Club?
He was putting that poster up
when I went looking for Fukube-san.
Perfect. If the Industrial Arts
guy was there the whole time,
he might remember who came and left.
That makes sense!
Hold on. Isn't it possible
that he's the culprit?
No way. What kind of culprit hangs
around after stealing something,
casually hanging up a poster?
True enough.
People who have passed by here?
Yes.
Sure, I remember.
There were a total of three of them.
Three of them? W-What sort
of people were they?
Did they have any
distinguishing characteristics?
One...
Two...
Three?
Mm-hm.
In other words, the culprit
is still on the 4th floor.
Satoshi, what clubs are
here on the 4th floor?
I believe it's the Classic Lit Club,
the Light Music Club,
the Astronomy Club,
and the Philosophy Club.
But then, I think that we
and the Astronomy Club
are the only ones who
haven't gone home yet.
I have to say, this is unusual...
You getting into this like you are.
It could start sleeting again, you know.
Leave me alone.
We'll be able to get it back now, right?
But why would anyone do such a thing?
That is the question.
Let's start by exploring the possibilities.
Elective Classroom ♪5
Yes?!
Hm? The Classic Lit Club?
Please return our chocolate!
There was something we needed
to ask you about, Senpai.
Hm? What?
Um...
As it happens, some Valentine's
chocolate was stolen from our room.
We're looking for any
witnesses who saw anything.
Chocolate? I doubt we have
ourselves a love bandit!
Did you see anyone up here
between 4:45 and 5:00?
Only thing I thought
I'd do here is fumble
Hm... We were pretty much
in the swing of things here.
or take double damage. It's miraculous.
I don't remember the time, but
Nakayama and Yoshihara stepped out.
Can you let me replenish my items?
And Oda might have left, too.
I don't think we can.
Three out of the five, huh?
Did anyone pack up and
get ready to go home?
No, nobody.
Oda-san is the girl over there?
That's Nakayama! And let
me just say, Mr. Detective,
nobody came back in here
with any chocolate!
Hey, guys! Did any of you get even
a glimpse of anything chocolatey
while you were in here?
Senpai, would you mind
not rubbing it in, please?
I wish I could say I saw some.
Got shut out, huh?
There you have it.
Anything else you wanted to ask?
Thank you very much, Senpai.
I apologize for any disrespect.
Well, that's okay.
Okay, let's get back to it!
You're too late, Senpai!
Sawakiguchi-san was upset, wasn't she?
Of course she was.
But we must do whatever it takes
to get Mayaka-san's chocolate back!
Hotaro...
For now, let's just go
back to the classroom.
It's about time we wrapped this up.
Is there any way to get to the
4th floor other than that stairway?
Realistically speaking, just the
stairway that was being waxed.
But there were no traces of any use.
Okay. Come to think of it,
did you check the girls' restroom?
I'll go check!
Do you really think it's in the restroom?
Not a chance in a million.
A chance in a million isn't...
Satoshi!
I can pretty well guess what happened.
Just keep your mouth shut.
Okay.
It wasn't in there.
In that case, there's only one possibility.
Huh?
What are you all doing in here?
Um, Maya...
So anyway,
how was it? My chocolate?
Right down to business, huh?
Ibara...
I'm sorry, Mayaka-san!
I left the room without locking the door,
and the chocolate was
stolen while I was out.
I'm sorry!
Hm, is that right?
It was stolen, was it?
Mayaka-san, I...
Don't be so upset.
Chi-chan, there's nothing
for you to apologize about.
Still, it does kind of hurt.
I'm going home now. Chi-chan,
really, don't let it bother you.
Please step aside.
What are you planning to do?
I'm going to find that chocolate,
even if I have to resort to
somewhat forceful measures.
If I don't, I won't be able
to face Mayaka-san tomorrow.
This isn't your fault.
I can't forgive myself for what I did!
Mayaka-san was supposed to
have a happy memory of today!
I can't say that I understand how you feel.
I'm not as easily moved as you are.
But let me deal with this. There are
some things I need to consider.
But I can't do that while you're here.
Do you have any idea who it was?
Yeah.
Nakayama, from the Astronomy Club.
Ibara's chocolate was a
pretty decent size, right?
So you couldn't hide it
under a boy's school uniform.
You might hide it on the inside,
but it would make you move unnaturally.
But with a sailor uniform,
you could pull it off.
If you strapped it to your leg,
your skirt would hide it for you.
I will give Ibara's chocolate
to Satoshi within the day.
Let me take this over,
while you relax and go home.
Very well.
I will trust you, Oreki-san.
Should we get going?
Yeah, okay.
Satoshi, let me see your drawstring bag.
I'm giving Ibara's chocolate to you.
This fulfills my promise to Chitanda.
Satoshi was the one who
stole Ibara's chocolate.
Nicely done, Hotaro.
The moment I heard that the
chocolate had been stolen,
I was thinking that the only one
who would do such a thing was Satoshi.
I became certain when we talked
to the Industrial Arts Club member.
Satoshi said "You lowered it too much."
If he hadn't previously said
"You should lower the right side,"
he wouldn't have responded
the way he did.
Satoshi probably hid in the
3rd floor boys' restroom,
waiting for Chitanda to pass,
Earth Science Prep Room
then recovered
the chocolate from the vacant club room.
But it was bigger than he expected.
It wouldn't fit in his bag,
and there were no suitably
large bags in the room.
If he fled with it as-is,
and happened to bump into
Chitanda, he'd be called out.
Which meant that the action
Satoshi took was...
Did you even hesitate when you broke it?
This makes us even.
Even?
Last April, you concocted that tale
about the Joro Spider Society
so that I could get away from Chitanda.
Ah, that's right, I did.
But no one was hurt by that.
Except for you, that is.
You'll at least explain to me
why you did it, right?
And if you tell me it was all a joke...
What if I do?
I'll have no choice but to pound you.
For both Chitanda and Ibara, with my fists.
Well, I don't want to get pounded.
I'd rather not say. But...
I guess I'm going to
have to say anyway, huh?
Hotaro, do you think
I'm the compulsive type?
I think you fixate on your interests.
That's where you'd be wrong.
People like that apply
themselves to something,
and don't want anyone else in
that field to get the better of them.
And you're not like that?
No, I'm not. I'll never be
the best person at anything.
But to be more exact, I've...
stopped trying to be the best.
You felt something was out of place
at the game center, didn't you?
About how I wasn't
preoccupied with winning?
Yeah.
The old me wanted
to win for winning's sake,
and was fussier about a lot of things.
It was no fun, you know? Winning
after focusing so hard on winning,
but not having any fun
doing so, is hard to handle.
If you don't have any fun
winning, how fun can it be?
So, one day, I just grew tired of it.
I became particular about
not being particular.
After that, I really have enjoyed
myself more. Every day is happy!
But there was one problem with it...
Mayaka.
Mayaka is great. Really great.
There's no one else like her.
Having Mayaka wanting to be
with me is like a dream come true.
So then...
However...
Is it okay for me to be
preoccupied with Mayaka?
Without a doubt,
I want to be with Mayaka.
But I don't want to be
preoccupied with her.
It's all about what I want. I'm not
thinking about how Mayaka feels.
Heh, don't you think
that's pretty self-centered?
I really don't want to take
Mayaka for granted, either.
Besides, if I let go of my lighthearted
self and embrace Mayaka,
I might go back to being my old self.
That's something that terrifies me.
Is that why you didn't accept it?
Exactly. And now it's this year.
But I still haven't found my answer yet.
This was the only way not to accept
chocolate that I couldn't accept.
But you also ended up hurting Chitanda!
Things don't go as smoothly
for me as they do for you.
Mayaka and I didn't figure on Chitanda-san.
Mayaka-san! Please wait up!
Chi-chan...
Um...
I'm sorry, Chi-chan!
I actually know who stole the chocolate!
Huh?
The truth is, after last Valentine's Day,
I told Fuku-chan that I would
wait until he found his answer.
Today was my day to test if he had.
Then the chocolate was...
I think Fuku-chan probably has it.
Is... that right?
I really am sorry that all this
effectively put one over on you.
That's okay. I'm the one who seemed
to blow it out of proportion.
So, when Oreki-san said that
the Astronomy Club girl stole it...
I think he was telling a white
lie to cover for Fuku-chan.
I see.
But how unkind of Fukube-san...
Playing along like it was stolen!
You think so, too?!
Yes I do!
That really is galling! But the
most galling thing of all
is myself, for still liking Fuku-chan!
Okay, Chi-chan, let's go
out for cake, right now!
Right!
Well, Hotaro,
that's everything I have to say.
What will it be?
This isn't something we can tell Chitanda.
No way, huh? I'd rather get pounded.
So, is your answer at least on the horizon?
I think my answer will come soon.
Okay.
For being as deft as you are,
you sure are ham-handed.
"Sorry, I didn't know
anything at all about you,"
might have been something I
should have told him, but I couldn't.
Yeah, I safely managed to get
the chocolate back to Satoshi.
Is that right? That's a relief.
So, don't give it too much thought.
Oreki-san, thanks for
everything you did today.
Yeah...
Mayaka
Hello? Listen...
I need to talk to you.
It's bitter.
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "The Doll That
Took the Long Way Around."
The Doll That Took the Long Way Around