You!
It's been too long, Cure Flower.
Dune!
He's...
the Desert King?!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
It's so good to see you again,
Cure Flower.
Fifty years ago, you sealed away a portion of my power with the HeartCatch Mirage.
I would like it back.
That's not happening!
You call yourself the Desert King, but
you're like the least threatening guy ever!
Quit acting all big and tough!
I admire your confidence.
So, who'll be first?
Blossom Impact!
Did we get him?!
Blossom!
Piece of cake.
Your turn.
Moonlight!
Silly little fools.
Please stop!
I won't let you lay a finger on Cure Flower!
Tsubomi!
Hang in there!
Shall we dance, Cure Flower?
A fairy could never stand up to me.
Coupe...
We're here to escort you, King Dune.
No...
Grand...ma...
It's All Over...
The World's Become a Desert...
Remember this, Cure Flower?
This is where you and I did battle.
The Great Heart Tree...
Now then.
What are you going to do?!
I'm taking my power back.
Come.
Now, watch as the Great Heart Tree meets its end.
Stop!
I shall see all that you have dedicated yourself to protect these fifty years be destroyed.
How could you?
Now that the Great Heart Tree is no more, your planet lies defenseless.
It's the end of your world.
Hear me, humans!
Earth is now under the control of the Desert Apostles.
Your oceans, your rivers, your
forests, and soon you yourselves
shall be drowned under a sea of sand!
The Earth...
Grandma...
Tsubomi! Tsubomi!
Huh? What am I doing here?
It's terrible! It's terribllllle!
What happened?
The Great Heart Tree hash wilted away!
We couldn't protect it.
Potpourri...
If the Great Heart Tree is no more, then...
No...
All this in just one day?
Dune has to be behind this.
Lord Coupe must've used his
power to protect the greenhouse.
Mom.
Tsubomi?! Wait!
I'm going too!
Please, Lord Coupe, keep this place safe!
Mom!
No...
Grandfather!
Big brother!
Is this...
Our home...
This can't be happening!
Erika...
Welcome home, Tsubomi!
How could he?
How could they do this?
Tsubomi...
I don't know what to do anymore...
This appears to be the only place unaffected.
Yeah.
We should probably stay inside for now.
What's wrong, Erika?
It's nothing.
Erika!
Momo!
Thank god.
I was so worried!
What's going on?
Hanasaki! Hey!
Yuri!
Boss!
Hayato!
Big brother!
You're safe, Hayato!
Yeah!
Nothing's gonna stop me!
I'm gonna be there for you no matter what, Yuri!
Thank you.
Big brother, I was... I was so...
I had you worried, huh?
It's okay.
Besides,
if you keep looking so glum,
I'll be the one worried about you.
I'm fine, really!
That's the smile I know.
Tsubomi?
Something on your mind?
Yeah! It's not like you to zone out!
How did you all survive?
Everyone else got turned into those crystals.
Hanasaki!
Our hearts aren't as weak as you think!
Yeah!
If we let this beat us, the Precure would never forgive us!
The Precure?!
Right.
The Precure taught us to keep our hearts strong!
I know they're out there, doing their best to protect the Earth!
So we're gonna do whatever we can!
Yeah!
Everyone...
Hanasaki.
I-I'm so sorry!
It's just the flowers I was raising bloomed, and they were so pretty that I really wanted to show you...
Aya!
Everyone has their very own Flower of the Heart within their heart.
And each flower is its own variety and color.
No two are the same.
Our very own Flowers of our Hearts.
And no two are the same.
These precious flowers...
I...
I was letting my heart consider giving in,
but I've had it up to here with this!
Tsubomi?!
As long as you don't lose hope,
then I know the Precure will never give up!
Everyone, get inside!
There may be only four of us, but we're not alone!
Yeah!
Their hearts are with us!
All right! There's no way we can lose now!
Come on!
Seeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
HeartCatch Precure!
We've gotta transform too!
Right!
Let's do this!
Go get 'em, Precure!
You can do it, Precure!
Precure Double Impact!
Now's our chance!
Right!
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world.
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
If we're to save the Great Heart Tree, then it's even more important that we save Kaoruko.
I'll do whatever it takes to save my grandma!
But where are they keeping her?
Lord Coupe?
Wait, is that where my grandma is?!
You're going to come with us?
Next stop: the enemy base!
Full speed ahead!
Precure!
Go get 'em!
Please, look after yourselves.
O-Okay!
Thank you very much.
We'll all be praying for your safe return!
Thank you!
Um...
Could I take a photo of you all?!
Sure, go ahead!
All right then!
Gimme a smile!
Good luck, Precure!
Precure!
We'll save you.
So please, just hang on.
The Precure are coming?
But the Great Heart Tree should be gone.
How do the Precure and their fairies survive?
The Great Heart Tree isn't dead yet.
And it never will be, as long as
people have hope in their hearts!
King Dune.
We will eliminate the Precure before they reach the Planet Fortress.
I leave it to you.
I won't let that happen!
Soon, the Precure shall be no more. Let us enjoy the moment.
Dune...
Once the Precure are gone, the humans shall despair.
Which means the Great Heart Tree will wilt away for good.
Kaoruko must be in there.
We'll have to fight our way through.
Bring it on!
We're not gonna back down!
We'll rescue Grandma.
We'll save her...
and the whole world!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself in the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
The world falling into despair will only heighten my beauty!
I won't let you ruin this glorious moment!
Who is stronger, you or I?
It's time we found out, once and for all!
We have the light of hope in our hearts!
We'll fight for the people we love!
HeartCatch Precure:
Kumojacky! Kobraja!
We Will Never Forget You!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!