Myoudou             Festival
Yuri, are you leaving already?
Yeah, I have some things to take care of.
Well, I guess we've gotten most of our class's preparations done already.
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Fashion Club
in progress
Now recruiting!
What do we do?! There's only three days left!
The school festival
begins in 3 days
The show can't run over half an hour, and we have seven models...
Wait, no, nine models, nine.
And we need to do the billboard and the posters and...
Wait, we need someone to handle the lighting!
Erika, we're good to go on the dresses for the show!
Dresses are okay. Dresses are okay.
No, they're not!
I still haven't finished Yuri's outfit!
Still not ready. Still not ready.
Is everything okay, Tsubomi?
Can you get it done in time?
Yeah, just a little bit left to do.
That's good!
Excuse me, student council president.
Excuse me, student council president. Excuse me, student council president.
Wait, no!
Would you mind checking over the
school festival documentary for us?
Oh, I see. I'll be there in a second.
Go ahead. Don't worry about us.
Thanks, everyone.
It's gotta be tough for the student council president too.
Wait! We're supposed to be meeting our class to work on our schedule!
Oh, that's right. You're on your class committee.
Leave the rest to me and Erika.
Okay!
Sorry about this!
It's all right! We've got everything under control!
Everyone's in such a hurry.
Argh! We can't get all this done in three days!
Erika's really panicking about this.
It's our dream debut event for the Fashion Club!
We'll just have to give it our all and make it a success!
No... we will do it, no matter what!
I can always count on you, Tsubomi.
Probably.
We Can't Wait for the School Festival!
The Fashion Club's in a Panic!
All right, I'm going to go find Yuri!
Wh-What should we do?
We've only got two days left!
I wonder if Yuri will like it.
Oh, Momoka!
What's the matter, Tsubomi?
Is Yuri with you?
Afraid not. She left already.
I think she was heading toward the junior high area.
She hasn't gotten to try on her outfit yet, right?
Right! Well then, I'd better hurry back!
Hanasaki!
Huh? Yes?
Up here!
Oh, Boss!
It's a real help having you model for me, Hanasaki!
G-Glad to help!
What on earth am I doing?
Thanks to you, it looks like I might just be able to get this comic book published in time for the festival!
That's great!
But you really are a perfect match for Cure Blossom, image-wise.
I-I really don't look anything like her!
Please try to stay still, Hanasaki!
R-Right! I-I'm sorry!
Okay!
What are you doing, Tsubomi?
Thanks, Hanasaki.
Glad I could help! Anyway, I need to get going.
I've finally caught you, Hanasaki!
What?
I really want your opinion on something.
H-Huh?!
The Photography
Association
is right this way!
The Photography
Association
is right this way!
I'm kinda in a bind 'cause I don't really have any photographs I can use for the main attraction here.
I'd love it if I could cover it with pictures of the Precure, but...
Um, back to the point, what about using some photos of people preparing for the festival?
Preparing?
That's right!
When people are really putting their all into
something they enjoy, they always look so happy!
I'm sure it'd make for some wonderful photographs!
Hey, look at this one!
This is one of my favorites!
Wow, that's such a beautiful sunset.
Isn't it?!
I knew I could count on you! Thanks, Hanasaki!
You're quite welcome!
This is an announcement from the student council.
The school day is about to end.
Please finish what you're doing and begin clearing away.
I can't dawdle like this!
I've gotta go, sorry!
What do we do?! There's only two days left!
You should check what still
needs doing before the festival!
Got it!
Huh?! This isn't mine!
Could we have these stamped by the end of the day?
Ichuki?
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Just gotta keep at it, I guess.
C-Come in.
President, we'd like your approval for the positioning of the signs at the main gate.
Oh, I'll be right there.
Taisho-era Romance Café & Fashion
There it is!
These are our costumes?
They're kinda simple, aren't they?
Are you wearing those at your café?
Huh?
Oh, yeah. They don't exactly scream Taisho-era romance, though.
How about this?
You could try taking some large strips of lace and attaching them to the apron like this!
Whoa, you're amazing, Erika!
I know, right?
We should make these tablecloths match your aprons too!
Erika's totally forgotten about her Fashion Club work.
Squishy-squish, squishy-squish.
What happened to all my papers?
You sheemed to be having trouble, so I squishy-squished them for you!
Potpourri, you did all this for me?
Did I do well, Ichuki?
Thanks, Potpourri.
It wash no problem!
Yuri!
I wonder where she's gotten to.
You really are such a softie, Tsubomi.
I just can't bring myself to refuse when people want my help.
You should go check the junior high again!
Right!
Ow!
I-I'm so sorry! I shouldn't have just turned around like that.
Sugiyama?
Hanasaki!
I should be the one apologizing.
I was in a hurry.
I guess the Movie Research
Club's got a lot to do too, huh?
Yeah.
We still haven't finished the movie we're going to be showing.
Ah!
I really have to get going! Bye!
Sugiyama!
I need to get to work too!
Yuri!
This is an announcement from the student council.
Please halt any work you're doing for the school festival.
I'll just have to find Yuri tomorrow!
We did it!
Huh?! What is it?!
The fashion show's a huge success...
She's even thinking of the fashion show in her dreams now.
in
day
Just one day left.
And we've got our on-stage rehearsal at 4 o'clock.
Yuri left really early again today too.
I wonder where she keeps running off to.
Well, Yuri and I have pretty similar physiques, so if it fits me then it shouldn't be a problem...
Huh?
What's the matter, Momoka?!
I don't think I can get my head into this.
Whaaaaaaat?!
What do we do?!
There's no way we'll get it fixed by 4!
Just leave it to me!
Got it!
All okay!
Flawless as ever, President!
Well, you know...
You really are good at this!
I-I'm not really that good...
The 53rd Myoudou Festival
Fashion Club
in progress
Now recruiting!
How'd it get this late?!
Aikidou Club Exhibition
Sorry, but our time's up!
U-Um, could you two just...
Hmph, I'll be looking forward to watching your "fashion show."
And I have high hopes for the Drama Club's "performance."
She's always like this.
Give it a rest, Erika!
Will you please get going with your rehearsal already, Fashion Club?
Come on already, Erika!
Tsubomi, smile!
Oh man, she's so nervous.
Sorry for being so late!
You came in your training gear?!
Wow, you're so cool!
Is this really gonna work out?
They're finally done!
Things are looking up!
Yup!
Well then, all that's left is to wait for the real thing tomorrow!
I guess so!
What is it?
Huh?! E-E-Erika, what about preparing the billboard and the posters?!
I totally forgot!
The billboard and the posters...
What do we do?!
My grandfather's pretty good at doing billboards.
I think it'd probably be better if we asked someone else.
Dang it, what are we supposed to do now?!
We'll just have to make them together!
It's fine! There's still time!
Tsubomi!
Hanasaki!
I finally finished the front cover!
Wow, that looks beautiful!
It's my magnum opus!
Hanasaki!
Can I please take some photos of the Fashion Club?!
For your photography exhibit, right?
Yeah! I'm running with your idea for the main display, Hanasaki!
Oh! U-Um...
I have a favor to ask of you two!
Huh?
I wonder if I can get this done by tomorrow.
What the heck is this?
I don't remember filming this!
I'll never get it done now!
The screening's going to be ruined!
That's right! I'm going to ruin your pathetic little movie!
Wh-Who are you?!
The Flower of your Heart is wilting.
So I shall take the Flower of your Heart!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
You're up, Desertrian!
Yeah! You all have such great smiles!
It's so nice of you to want to use
my photographs for your posters!
I've gotten pretty good at this from doing my cover.
Thank you both so much for helping us!
Huh?! You want me to be your MC?!
Please, Azusa!
We're begging you!
Well, you did make that costume for me before.
It'd be the least I could do!
Yay! Thank you, Azusa!
Now we just need to find someone to manage the lighting.
Wh-What on earth is that monster?!
There's no way I can finish my movie by tomorrow.
Movie?
Tsubomi!
They stole the Flower of the Heart from that boy from the Movie Research Club!
Sugiyama.
Mo... vie!
I need to go tell everyone to evacuate over the intercom!
Okay!
We should find somewhere quiet and transf—
This is bad! We need to get
everyone out of here, quickly!
Right!
Everyone, the campus grounds are dangerous at the moment, so please stay within the school building!
The 53rd Myoudou Festival
Everyone, hurry and get inside!
This way!
Hey, you!
Don't worry about the billboard! Just run!
The Precure will come and save us soon!
Get somewhere safe, quickly!
Mooovieeee!
Aren't they here yet?!
I guess not.
Jeez, what's taking them so long?!
Y-Yeah, seriously.
Well, Tsubomi and I just need to go and...
Where are you two going?
It's dangerous to run off alone.
Come on, just give us a chance to transform already!
I guess the Precure must have turned tail and fled.
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
Let's all hide!
Okay!
Just like that, Desertrian!
Destroy all in your path!
I'm sorry, but we really have to go and...
Stop that at once!
Hm?! Who's there?!
A silver Precure!
I'll never finish this movie in time.
This stupid festival should just go away!
This is a scoop! A genuine scoop!
I wanna see too!
Hey, it's dangerous up there!
Moviiie!
Would you really not regret seeing the school festival disappear?
You should think about what it is you truly wish to achieve!
Vie...
Tch. Seems like it's time to use this.
Sink into the darkness, and let your dark heart control you!
Dark Bracelet!
Now you'll be fighting me!
Are you two okay?!
Boss, Azusa! Hurry and get Kanae to the infirmary!
Quickly!
Right!
My heart shall falter no longer
Gather, Floral Power!
Moon Tact!
I'll pick myself up and keep moving forward
Knowing the tears I shed that fateful day
Have guided me back to where I am now
What was that just now?!
The shard of the moon I thought lost
She moved so quickly.
Moonlight is so strong and pretty!
Slowly begins to return
No matter how hard you fight, it doesn't change the fact that the Flower of his Heart is crumbling beyond repair!
Let my courage grant me the strength
To bring forth the future we desire
You're wrong. I won't let it wilt!
I won't give up until every heart is filled with light!
The light of the silver moon
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Silver Forte Wave!
Envelops even this sadness I feel
So let me use this power I've been granted
To bring light to the darkness
You're pretty good, Cure Moonlight.
H-Huh? Where's my film?
You mean this?
Thank goodness it's safe!
That's really important to you, isn't it?
Yeah, it's very precious to me.
I really want to show it tomorrow at the festival!
I totally know how you feel!
Hey, Sugiyama!
We need to work together and get this done!
Yeah, we have to get it done in time!
I want everyone to be able to enjoy our movie, after all!
Well then, I guess all's well that ends well.
Wait, no it's not! We still haven't found anyone to work the lights for the fashion show!
Oh yeah...
Um...
I could do that if you like.
Huh?!
I'm pretty much free tomorrow, and I
know my stuff when it comes to lighting.
Th-Thank you so much!
All right!
In the language of flowers, a Chinese bellflower means "unyielding love."
I'm glad he didn't lose his love for movies!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With thish, the Great Heart Tree hash recovered a little more!
Looks like we will get everything done in time after all!
Y-Yuri!
Huh?
It really suits you!
Yeah!
This really is a beautiful outfit.
It took me forever to find a pair of shoes to match it.
Is that why you kept vanishing so early every day?
Yes. You went through all the trouble of making this
for me, so I had to make sure I got the shoes just right.
All right then! Let's give tomorrow's fashion show everything we've got!
Right!
The 53rd Myoudou Festival
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
The school festival is now underway!
Your shtage awaitsh you!
I can't stop shaking.
But what we really can't stop is our passion!
Let the girly, poppy fashion flow forth!
Are you all ready?
Yeah!
Our fashion spirits are going into overdrive!
HeartCatch Precure:
Everyone's a Star!
This is Our Stage!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!