I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
Hey, Spike.
It's ready.
I'm just about finished.
What's cooking?
Special. Bell peppers and beef.
Asimov Solensan.
He's our next target.
Listen, Jet...
This guy's a major player
in the syndicate.
Operates all around the asteroids.
You said "bell peppers and beef."
His name's Asimov Solensan.
Are you listening to me?
There's no beef in here.
So you wouldn't really call it
"bell peppers and beef," now would you?
Yes, I would.
Well, it's not!
It is when you're broke, all right?
What happened to the million Woolong
reward we got for that last guy?
The repair bill for that
cruiser you wrecked,
and the one from that
shop you trashed,
and the medical bill
from the cop you injured...
killed the dough!
Now, three days ago,
there was a big shootout
between his group
and a rival syndicate.
He killed his own guys
then took off like the wind.
Word is he's hiding out with
some sweet thing in Tijuana.
TJ? That place is for small fries.
Yeah, well, this small fry
is worth 2.5 million.
I don't feel like it.
Speaking of beef, they say in TJ,
the carnitas are outta this world.
Attention, please...
We will be arriving at our
destination shortly...
Please prepare for departure...
We look forward to serving you again...
Please line up single file...
Proceed along the yellow line...
Caution is advised at all times...
Please pass through the gate when the
credit sensors indicate debit mode...
We hope you had a pleasant flight.
I'll head over there after
I hit up the cops for some clues.
All right, then I'll check in
with old man Bull.
You think you can
trust that old codger?
Nice tune. Real easy.
Thief!
This again? Son of a bitch!
Takin' my money like that,
you cheatin' dogs.
Why, the only reason you can even
live here is 'cause of what I done.
I busted my tail to dig that gate.
For criminy's sakes, you always say
the same thing when you're losin'.
We all dug that gate together,
and you know it.
That we did. We worked
like there was no tomorrow.
And what do we got to show for it?
Gimme a beer.
And I will have a bloody mary.
In fact, make it a double.
I've got the vodka, but I'm afraid
I'm fresh outta tomato juice.
I'm sure there's one can
in the back room...
I'll check.
Premium Red Eye.
You're a buyer, you know the score.
Check it out.
Is that... real Bloody Eye?
I'm gonna need a little proof.
Let's have a demonstration.
Yeah... keep those eyes open.
This is real mystic and all,
but do you have anything to eat here?
I see.
The red-eyed coyote will appear in
the Zona Norte at the far end of town.
That is what I see.
A red-eyed coyote north of town?
You, Swimming Bird.
The swimming bird will meet a woman.
The bird will be hunted by this woman.
And then... death.
- One more time...
- What's that?
I was killed once before.
By a woman.
You take women too lightly, my friend.
On the contrary. Catch you later.
Wakan Tanka, guide his spirit.
Presidente, eh?
Think I'll have some on the house.
Damn... Just look at this.
Asimov went berserk.
No joke. We gotta take care
of him before the cops move in.
Maybe we should just let
the cops deal with him.
As long as he's using that Red Eye
on himself, you can't beat him.
We got to. If we don't
get that Bloody Eye back,
trust me, we'll all be
twistin' in the wind.
Maybe so, huh?
Yo.
Tell me some more.
I am starving.
So you're hungry too, huh, baby?
You know, it's better to just
leave the water running.
So you don't clog the drain.
- Oops.
- Sorry.
Thank you...
- Excuse me?
- Hm?
It's your hot dog.
Yeah, I can see that.
Just keep it.
Sorry, my stomach
just took over my brain.
- It does that sometimes.
- Really?
Nice ship.
Yeah, it's a blast from the past.
I've had it for ten years.
It looks like it's been around.
Guess you could say
we've done some traveling.
I'm actually a traveling performer.
I can't tell when you're
joking and when you're not.
Yeah, I hear that a lot.
- Ever been to Mars?
- I was born on Mars.
I hear they have everything there,
not like here.
There's parks and festivals,
and the people are happy there.
It must be a great place to live.
Sure, if you're rich.
Then I'm sure we
will be quite happy.
Planning to escape to Mars, huh?
Go ahead and run.
How far do you think you'll get?
Who are you?
I'm just an old-fashioned cowboy.
You're a bounty hunter.
Yeah, that's right.
And you are after us.
Your boyfriend is sick.
He's a small fry.
I don't bother with his type.
A wise decision.
Now who's the small fry?
Asimov, that's enough!
Let him go!
Adios, cowboy.
Why'd you stop me?
He would've been dead in another
minute. I wanted to see him die.
Asimov, please, this has to stop.
I think you liked him. Didn't you?
You left me there for so long, Asimov.
I was just waiting
for you to pick me up.
Let's go, Asimov, like you promised.
I want to get out of this life.
I know that I can be happy on Mars.
Having ourselves a little nap, huh?
- I had a sweet dream.
- That's heartwarming.
And you can go right ahead and
finish your dream back on the Bebop.
I'm cashing in my chips on this one.
It's impossible to catch the guy.
There's no way to win it.
When Asimov left his syndicate,
he snuck some stuff out with him.
Serious brew.
This stuff's a total mind-frag.
It's a new kind of eye spray the
syndicate cooked up. Very pure.
Takes two months to make one vile.
Our boy took off with every drop,
which made him rather unpopular.
They keep sending hit teams after him,
but all they get back are corpses.
Seems Asimov's been pumping up
by doing the stuff himself.
It's called "Bloody Eye."
No kidding. You know they're
planning to go to Mars?
Mars?
But before that,
they've gotta sell these.
Is that what I think it is?
Yeah, I grabbed it out of his pocket.
You... met him?
Yeah, so to speak.
He nailed you, huh?
The red-eyed coyote will appear in
the Zona Norte at the far end of town.
This again? Goddamn son of a bitch!
Takin' my money like that,
you cheatin' dogs.
Why, the only reason you can even
eat here is 'cause of what I done.
I busted my tail to plant those crops
along with my two good buddies.
We're the buddies you're talkin' about.
Yes sir, that we are.
We planted those seeds
like there was no tomorrow.
You were always plantin' seeds
of a different kind, though.
So do you have any bloody marys?
I only have beer.
- I got tomato juice.
- How much?
30 million Woolongs. For 50 packs.
15 million Woolongs.
I'm in a hurry.
I've got other customers.
Show me.
Looking for this?
Do you know how much you're worth?
What?
2.5 million Woolongs.
That's your bounty.
I said you were a small fry.
You look surprised.
You look ridiculous in that outfit.
I thought you weren't after my bounty.
There's no thrill in the cheap ones,
Asimov, you know?
I think you do better
as a thief, bounty boy.
Now hand it over.
Glad to.
I have to pay you back, don't I?
You trust your eyes too much, Asimov.
You're not a chameleon, you know.
You can't see everywhere at once!
Let's go!
Over there!
Follow him!
What the--
Don't move!
I don't want to hurt you!
Idiot!
If we lose these things, we're fragged!
Do you understand?!
How you doing, kid?
Rotten! You're late, Jet!
Damn!
Asimov...
Stop it, please!
That stuff is going to kill you!
No!
We'll never get out of here now.
I'll never see Mars.
Adios.
Hey, Spike,
get it while it's hot, buddy.
- It's ready.
- What is it?
Special. Bell peppers and beef.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
- Well, the show's finally underway.
- What's all this?
Next week,
we're totally changing gears.
- It's gonna be anime for all ages.
- What's the story?
House pets wreak havoc
throughout the stars.
What?
No, the guy who talks to animals
will not make an appearance.
But anyone who loves animals should
gather 'round and watch this show.
Hey, can we say stuff like that?
I'm taking no responsibility for this.
Caution! Small children should
sit far back from the TV.
- Come on! How far back?
- About three quarters of a mile.
- That's too far!
- Okay, half a mile.
"Stray Dog Strut"