That's good, Annie.
I expect the best from my daughter.
Move! Who told you it was time to rest?
Hold on. You mean you haven't heard?
The Titan kid and those big shot handlers
of his have been summoned to the capital.
Which means they'll be passing through here today.
Is that so? Well then maybe this time
they'll just dissect him and get it over with.
I just hope he doesn't stir up any trouble.
I say let him pass through and
seal the gate shut behind him!
Infidel! To even suggest sealing the gate!
The hands of heretics must never
taint the sanctity of our Walls!
Maria! Rose! Sina!
To even think of defiling the three goddesses.
We tempt the specter of damnation!
These lunatics all worship the
Walls as if they're some kind of gods.
It creeps me out.
Damn cult. Can't believe they're still around.
Let's go.
Look who's finally awake!
You look so terrifying when you're
asleep I didn't dare disturb you.
Prob'ly should've. Sorry.
You've been pretty lax in your duties, recently.
Look, Marlo. You've upset her.
She's antisocial, not upset.
Knock it off, you guys. She fought in
the Battle of Trost before coming here.
Whichmakes her the only one of
us who's ever seen any real action.
She's just been through hell.
Probably takes time to readjust.
Ah! So. You have a crush on the new girl, huh?
What could you possibly see in her?
I dunno, Hitch. Maybe it's that she got into the
MP's based on skill, unlike some I could mention.
Oh. I don't know what you're implying.
Why don't you clarify?
That's enough, you two.
Great. Thanks, guys. I called you all here
'cause I've got actual work for you today.
Not just the same ol' crap.
It's got somethin' to do with the
Scouts being summoned to the capital.
Sometime today, they'll be passing
through town along the main street.
HQ has already provided a security detail, so we're
only being asked to assist until the convoy's clear.
ODM use in city limits has been authorized.
You'll follow beside the convoy, as additional security.
There's a barge waiting to take
you to the starting point. Dismissed.
Sir! A question, if I may.
Hmm? Go ahead.
What exactly are we supposed to
be protecting this convoy from, sir?
Hmm?
It's just that I've never heard of anyone
defying the government. They're just glad to be safe.
There are petty criminals, sure.
But I find it hard to imagine any actual organization
existing within the wall that would attempt a strike.
I mean, what possible motive would they have?
Man! Aren't you serious? You can be in charge of this.
Everything you need to know is right in here.
Uh... Huh?
We officers are busy enough as it is.
Prove that you can handle this one yourselves.
Oh, and you better not screw it up, got it?
Hey, sorry 'bout that. Back to business.
Who's turn was it?
Damn. This stinks!
Got that right. The amount of slacking that
goes on in this outfit is even more than I imagined.
I mean, that is why I chose to join, but still.
I might've thought twice if I'd known that meant
the rookies got stuck doing all the work all the time.
Seriously. Wish someone would've warned me.
Bastards. They're all irresponsible,
self absorbed imbeciles! All of them!
Hmm. So what's that make you, Marlo?
You chose to join the Military Police.
You're a slacker just like the rest of us.
You're wrong, Boris.
I'm nothing like the rest of you degenerates!
I joined up because the Military
Police is in dire need of repair!
Wow. That was great, Marlo!
I never pegged you for the crusader type!
Just how do you plan to fix it?
By working my way to the top, of course.
And then once I'm in charge.
I can install a new system to make sure all
those who are dishonest pay for their transgressions.
It's as simple as that.
The MPs just need a little discipline, and nothing more.
I'll shape them back into the
people they're supposed to be.
Wow. That is something!
And I thought you were a total buzzkill before!
Well, that's a rather lofty ideal.
So, y'know, good luck with all that.
What's the point?
I think if a do-gooder like you was
actually put in charge of this regiment,
you'd quickly find yourself working alone.
Really? That's the first thing you open your mouth to say?
Don't get me wrong, I don't doubt your sincerity.
I know conviction when I see it.
You're not the first person I've met who thought they
could take on the world and change things for the better.
It takes a lot of courage to go against the flow.
I respect that.
Of course, it could be that
you're all just a bunch of fools.
They might be, but don't go lumping me in with them!
Is that understood?
Bah! Enough chit-chat. Let's go!
The escort wagons are scheduled to pass
through the outer gate in forty five minutes.
Once we arrive, everyone take up your positions. Got it?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey! Watch it, bud!
What's goin' on? That's our gear.
Shipping it to the Interior?
Isn't it a bit strange, having the
Merchant's Guild conduct the transport?
What're they up to?
Are those bastards illegally selling government property?
Hey, this isn't our assignment!
Look at him! Crusader-man's the genuine article!
Well, I suppose we have the time to spare.
I bet this'll be entertaining.
I'd say we've earned ourselves a drink!
Hmm?
What do you think you're lookin' at? Huh, rookie?
You... You can't sell government equipment.
It's against the law!
Is that so?
Those supplies are the property of the hard-working
citizens who pay for them with their taxes.
And that means...
Can you believe this business? A
rookie blackmailing his superior officers!
I'm thinkin' you got a bright future ahead of you, kid.
Go spend it on a girl, alright? She'll help you unwind.
Wait. Hey!
What you did was against the law!
Hey wait!
You're under arrest for a
treasonable offense against an officer.
Blatant disregard for the rule of law...
Is standard procedure!
So is this!
He's had enough. Don't you think, sir?
So sorry about that fellas!
I hope our idiot hasn't caused you too much trouble.
We'll be sure to drive the lesson home, don't you worry!
Unless, of course... you'd rather have...
a much bigger problem on your hands.
Just this once.
Sir!
So, about that drink.
Yeah. I worked up quite the thirst!
Go ahead.
Aren't you going to "make the
dishonest pay for their transgressions"?
I'm not entirely opposed to helping you out with that.
Is it me, or do those serving
gals get prettier with every sip?
Damn it!
Hey, little lady! You workin' hard? Or hardly working?
You boys are all the same!
Those people you know.
The other "fools" you mentioned.
Would they have done it?
They might've.
I wanted to be brave. To go against the flow.
But when it comes down to it, I'm just another
piece of scum being swept away by the current.
Not sure what to say about that.
Maybe... that's just a part
of what it means to be ordinary.
Simply going with the flow.
Is that so bad? To some people it makes you weak,
but an ordinary person is all I want to be.
Annie!
Hello.
So, you're a full-fledged MP now.
Armin.
So, uh. What's with the outfit?
Why I'm in the rain gear, you mean?
It's a makeshift disguise.
Needed to conceal my ODM rig. See?
What's this about?
Annie. We have a plan for Eren to escape,
and we're hoping that you'll help us.
Wait, escape to where? Stuck behind these walls,
where can you possibly hide that they won't find you?
We'll only need to hide him for a short while.
This isn't a mutiny. We have every intention of returning.
View this as a few loyal Scouts staging a
small act of protest. It's a stall tactic.
We need time to gather enough evidence
to overrun the council's ruling about Eren.
That's all we want.
You're serious about this?
How can you be so sure the evidence exists?
And what is it?
I can't say. I'm sorry.
Sorry, Armin. I'm gonna have to decline.
My lips are sealed, though. Best of luck.
Hold on! Annie, please!
They're going to kill Eren!
They'll kill him for no better reason than
that they fear what they don't understand.
They don't see that their fear is
pushing humanity to the brink of extinction!
Maybe it's too late to change their minds.
But what if we can? We have no choice
but to bet everything on that chance!
I'm sorry. The last thing we want is to cause you grief.
But, well. The only way to sneak
him through the Wall Sina checkpoints
is with the help of someone in the Military Police!
It's our only hope.
But why me? Do I really look
like that good of a person to you?
A good person? I dunno.
Actually, I've never placed much
value in those sorts of labels.
The way I see it, "good" is merely a word applied
to people who are convenient to our needs in some way.
It's purely subjective.
Any way you try to look at it,
labeling people dehumanizes them.
Regardless, if you still choose
to say "no" to this request,
then at least in my eyes that makes you a bad person.
Alright.
Let's go.
We made it. Can't believe it was so easy.
Hush!
The Military Police, hard at work.
I'm almost surprised they bothered to show up at all.
Let's just keep moving.
Hopefully they haven't noticed my stand-in yet, either.
It's not gonna hold up under close scrutiny.
After all, Jean and I look nothing alike.
It's close enough. You both have that same angry
scowl, and the same boulder-sized chip on your shoulder.
Well, yeah! But I don't have his horse face!
Hey. So if I had refused to help you guys out,
then what was your Plan B for getting over the wall?
We would've used our ODM gear to
barge right through the checkpoint.
That's stupid. Why didn't you just
avoid all this trouble in the first place?
You could've escaped before reaching Stohess, right?
I mean, why wait 'til now?
I felt that this town's complex layout would allow us
to squeeze a bit more time out of our body-double ploy.
Of course. A head-on assault is ill-advised.
So as long as the convoy acts like it's following orders.
Then everyone keeps their defenses down.
I see. It's a very good plan.
Ah! There it is!
Here?
Yeah. We'll pass through here.
It's what remains of an underground city
they were planning to build way back when.
And if I'm right, it should lead
us to the vicinity of the outer gate.
Nice work, Armin. That's amazing
Annie?
What's the matter? You're not afraid of
dark, cramped spaces or anything, are you?
So what? So what if I am?
I wouldn't expect a suicidal
maniac like you to understand.
You don't know what it is to be an
ordinary girl, crippled with fear.
A girl who can flip a full-grown man
upside down has nothing to fear from the dark.
Cut the crap and let's move!
No. I refuse.
I'm too afraid. Above ground, I'll help.
Otherwise the deal's off.
Quit being stubborn, dammit!
Just get the hell down here! Move!
We're running out of time, alright?
Stop shouting. Someone will hear you.
I'm sure it's fine, Mikasa.
It seems that, for whatever reason,
this place has been completely deserted.
That hurts me. It really does.
The way you're looking at me now.
If I didn't know better, I'd say you didn't trust me.
Eh, Armin?
Annie. Tell me.
What were you doing with Marco's ODM gear?
It had all the same dents and scrapes.
See, I helped him with
maintenance, so, I know you used it.
Yes. I found it. Found it and took it.
Then the two Titans we had in custody.
It was you that killed them.
No one knows.
But if you suspected all of this a month
ago, why did you wait this long to say anything?
Because even now it's difficult.
I just didn't want... I didn't want to
believe that I was right. So I stayed quiet.
But then, out in the field.
The fact that you didn't kill me then and there.
That's the moment that set us on
the path to our current situation.
Yes. We're here 'cause I let you live.
Of course, I never would've dreamed
you'd end up cornering in on me like this.
Why? Why didn't I do anything then?
Annie, please! You've taken this joke far enough.
Just tell us this is some kinda horrible prank.
It's not too late!
Come on! We'll understand!
Come down, lets talk.
You can prove to us that we're
mistaken by walking down these stairs!
Prove we're wrong to accuse you!
We both know I can't. Like I told you,
I don't have the constitution for it.
Annie, stop!
We're talking about a matter of life and death!
Work with us, Annie!
We can reason this out like human beings.
Enough.
I'm not listening to another word of this.
No point.
I'm going to carve you up again!
Do you understand me, Titan?
You know, Armin. It's nice that I
could be a "good person" for you.
For now, at least, it looks like you won your bet.
But...
I'm going to gamble, too. And here's my wager!
Eren!
What're you...?
It's too late.
The identity of the Female Titan has been discovered.
All along, it was Annie Leonhart.
However, even when faced with irrefutable truth,
Eren can neither bring himself to transform,
nor fight his former comrade in arms.