We're getting everything!
He might be one dashing man,
but to think he had such habits...
Ozu is in the same year I am.
Because he hates vegetables
and only eats instant food,
he has an exceedingly ghastly face
that looks like it came from
the dark side of the moon.
Now's our chance!
He picks on the weak and sucks
up to the strong. He's lazy and a devil.
My soul would have surely
stayed unblemished had I not met him.
And how did you get a duplicate key?
I've earned Jougasaki-san's trust, you see.
You back-stabbing bastard.
Oh, if you move anything, make sure to
put it back exactly where you found it, okay?
He's one serious clean freak.
Clean freak?
Yeah. That's why his girlfriend is
like that instead of flesh and blood.
What are you talking about?
Over here.
A boor such as yourself whose mind is
filled with sex probably couldn't understand.
It's a form of extremely sophisticated love.
T-That's...
Then I was a brand-spanking new freshman
university student and before my eyes
were held out innumerable circle fliers
far surpassing my personal information intake.
In each and every one of them I could
see a door to that rose-colored campus life.
And the one I chose was...
There I was sure lay my
future of pure, sparkling gold.
My new cinema paradise with the raven-haired
maidens dancing on the silver screen!
I decided to join that day
in order to make 100 friends,
led astray by the naive words of
"Let's have fun making movies together."
I was truly an idiot beyond all redemption.
Sincerity vs. Authority
And the movie circle
"Misogi" which I joined that day
was under the authoritarian rule
by the president, Jougasaki-senpai.
Take 12, ready... Action!
Teacher and Student
Go to War
Let's do this, Mars!
Come at me!
I
.
Jougasaki
Cut!
It's just not right yet...
Sorry 'bout this! After the
break, let me do another take.
Right!
Shit... To hell with that.
Pervert!
Wait! I...
While I was annoyed with
Jougasaki-senpai's meaningless production,
it was then that an ominous man
stood besides me with a face of ill portent.
Are you from the dark side
of the moon?
Or perhaps an E.T.?
You say some pretty mean things.
There's no need to worry,
I am your compatriot!
That was my first contact with Ozu,
as well as worst contact.
All he does is parrot what he's
read in how-to-make-movies books.
I'd say it's Godard
and Truffaut and the like,
but the all-time best
is actually that Titanic guy.
It's dangerous to have a guy whose head
is only filled with boobs run the movie circle!
Movies must definitely not be allowed
to be poisoned by commercialism!
Show us a movie circle the way it
should be, with your own two hands!
For the purpose of raising the beacon
of mutiny against Jougasaki-senpai's faction,
I started filming my own personal movies.
Approach
My first work: after the war in the Pacific,
two men continue a battle of historic pranks,
exhausting the limits of
intelligence and physical strength.
A movie of overflowing war and violence.
Of course, it was ignored, and the only person
in the theater that laughed was Akashi-san.
My second work: a sentimental movie
about a man wavering between three women,
patterned after King Lear. It received a storm
of vilification from the women's camp.
And my third work: a man trapped in a never-ending maze of 4.5 tatami rooms
and his attempts to escape from it.
It was DOA after people said "I've seen
this premise before somewhere..."
Akashi-san was the only one
who gave me useful criticism.
Yojou-han
The
End
What was odd was that I couldn't help
but think that the more effort I put in,
the more Jougasaki-senpai's
charisma seemed to rise.
Our next work shall
be Alexander the Great!
It will surely be a super grade-A piece of
entertainment, the culmination of our work!
So, everyone... Will you follow me?
Yes!
Ablution!
When I think back on it now, I was used
as leverage to increase his charismatic appeal.
Undaunted by Jougasaki-senpai, we attempted
to announce a new romance film we were shooting,
but his faction was unanimously against it.
The enemy's first line
of attack was Aijima-senpai,
Jougasaki-senpai's right-hand man,
who always picked on us annoyingly.
Using acrobatic tricks of the
filming schedule and petty things
like turning off the electricity, hiding
the key etc... He shut us out from the studio.
To even borrow the editing equipment
felt like having to near prostrate ourselves.
In the end no one would deal with me,
and I was shut out of the movie circle.
How can he be so celebrated while
we have to resign to ourselves to this?
Now, now... The public is finicky.
But they will always recognize
a film that's true to itself.
And when will that be?
I want recognition now!
You're quite selfish, you know that?
If you're really so motivated, why do you have
such a down-in-the-dumps look on your face?
Shut up!
Thanks to you I've wasted
my perfectly lovely college life!
Oh? I think you're also to blame for that.
After all, it doesn't matter which path you take,
you'll keep ending up right where you are now.
Have we had this conversation before?
Of course not.
It's déjà vu, just déjà vu.
I see...
At any rate, once I met you I put all
my efforts into making you no good.
Why do you haunt me so?
It's the way I show my love! We're connected
by the black  thread of fate, after all.
The Japan Trench
So, here. This is Jougasaki-senpai's transcript.
He's got a great face, but
what's inside his head is a mess.
He's in his eight year?
And moreover, his grades
are dangerously low!
Why do you have something like this?
Please don't underestimate
my information-gathering network.
And to escape from this sad reality,
his heart has been more and more captured
by the boobs of his female circle members.
That's also the reason behind
that last infamous swimsuit audition.
He filmed them in the swimsuits?
There was no exhibitionism
in the actual film.
And that's exactly
what made it so infamous.
As an aside, here are
the marks from the audition.
It shows the breasts' shape,
angle, size, and separation.
He's completely mixed up his
private fetish with his public behavior.
Okay, next!
"Boob, boob, boob, boob..."
So then he's just a boob dictator!
That's right. In short,
he's nothing but a boob junkie.
He's a boob drunkard.
Ozu! I have an idea.
Will you help me?
What are you going to do?
Well, I'm going to leave the circle anyway.
So at least I want to bring down heavenly
judgment on Jougasaki-senpai before the end!
Well, well, that's not very calm of you.
Understood. I'll follow you
wherever you go, Director.
And thus I was driven to action
by my righteous indignation.
Now is the time to throw
cold water on the people.
Or to put it simply, I decided to film an
exposé documentary on Jougasaki-senpai.
In order to save the underclassmen charmed
by Jougasaki-senpai's meager charisma,
I decided to willingly take on
this villainous role myself.
What do you think, Master?
Well now...
Still soft-balling it, right?
The man that Ozu had
brought in as an adviser
seemed to have known
Jougasaki-senpai for a long time,
and Ozu schemed to
his fullest extent to shoot
yet more and more libelous
scenes of his discordant private life.
Ozu was like a kid in a candy factory,
continuously manipulating
the film to deviate from reality,
and the exposé film became nothing
more than a personal attack film.
How about this?
I wonder.
Maybe we should try going this far?
Documentaries are deliberate, after all.
Master, let's keep going on this, yes!
Well, it's sure looking like this will be
an epoch-making work, don't you think?
Oh, and by the way, please
only credit yourself, Director.
Director?
As I left the editing room and
walked aimlessly around Kiyamachi,
under the overhang of someone's house
I was caught by an old woman who
emitted a suspiciously ghoulish aura.
This unplaceable aura was
persuasive, and thinking logically,
there was no way that the fortune-telling
of a creature who emits such an
aura could be anything but spot on.
What do you want to know?
Your face is a face of extreme
impatience... You are unsatisfied.
I feel that you are not in a
situation that you believe suits you,
and I can sense your fiercely earnest talent.
Quickly I did tip my hat to
the old woman's keen insight.
Anyway, I sense there is an
opportunity you can't let pass by.
An opportunity?
As in an excellent chance.
Yes, I know what it means...
This opportunity is always
dangling in front of your eyes.
You must grab this
opportunity and act on it.
I have a feeling I've heard this before...
And if you do not!
You will walk this life
as now, ever unchanging.
That'll be 2000 yen.
Did you raise your prices?
What does the viewer think is best?
Spreading around emotions that can move
a large number of viewers is basic etiquette.
Jougasaki?
The Hollywood system
is the best in the end.
Hey there!
Hi.
How're you doing?
So-so.
It's too bad your proposal wasn't accepted.
But movies are things everyone should see.
I don't care if you make things
you like that make no sense,
but if you want to show them to other people,
at least keep a minimum of etiquette.
Not only are you wasting
the viewer's precious time,
it's basically like showing you masturbating
to other people! I couldn't stand that.
Well, good luck, my brother!
I don't think he gets it.
Ooh, he's scary...
There you are.
Director! I've been searching for you.
And so my determination to push forward
and create a libelous film against
Jougasaki-senpai was renewed.
Below my feet ran the Takase River,
just as shallow as all the mass-produced
independent films Jougasaki-senpai ever made.
Afterwards I returned to the editing room,
and on the morning of the fourth day,
after three days of editing without sleep,
I finally completed the worthless
documentary which one could say
was the culmination of my two prior years.
Finished
We're doing a screening. Please come.
Your chance is during the staff
introductions before they show the film.
Head to the projector room then.
Leave it to me!
This movie was created by
the hard work of everyone in Misogi.
We really put our all into this.
I hope that you will all enjoy it!
Before we start,
let me introduce the staff.
This is Ozu-kun, who helped
with the sound recording.
Playing both sides are we?
And next we have Akashi-san, who was
in charge of the 3D and visual effects.
Akashi-san?
I met Akashi-san during Jougasaki-senpai's
shoot at Mt. Yoshida the previous year.
She was one year younger than me
and in the engineering department,
and she was hired on as
staff for her technical skills.
Always meticulous, with
never an equipment mishap,
she gained the trust of the other staff,
but as she was not one to mince words,
it seemed there was a distance
between her and the people in her class.
With her sharp tongue she held
her own against Jougasaki-senpai,
and although he took an interest in her
chilly, intelligent demeanor (and her boobs),
he never spoke with her, fearful his
charismatic flair would be damaged.
Akashi-san, you sure are fair-skinned.
Me, fair-skinned?
There are plenty of people with fairer skin
than me, so on what basis do you say that?
With such a resolute denial
and then cross-examination,
no man ever dared
speak with her after that.
I sent off a fiery cheer of "Akashi-san, you just
keep doing things your own way!" in my heart.
You created another idiotic movie...
I'm sorry for making you
watch such a worthless film.
It was definitely worthless,
but I didn't hate it.
Now we will start the film!
Please enjoy it to the end.
ALEXANDER
Hey, maybe we should call it off...
I can't bring myself to
do it with Akashi-san here.
What are you saying? What happened
to your pride as a filmmaker?
Speaking of which,
you're on their crew!
It's almost time.
Are you having fun, Alexander?
Drink will not clear my mind, Ptolemaeus.
OK, cut!
Nice work everyone!
Oh, I'm definitely a genius.
Shut off the mic.
Wait, didn't he realize this was recording?
He's got a camera on him.
I-I'm fine...
Please take this!
Thank you...
--What's this?
--Are those his?
What am I going to do? I barely
have enough money to eat, Mommy!
T-This is...
--No way!
--What in the world?
You're kidding me... A wall of boobs?
--Is this non-fiction?
--If so then... wow...
It's a lie, this is all a lie!
Impossible!
Hey, stop the film!
Don't stop it!
I said stop it, stop it!
I'm home, Kaori.
Stop it! Not that!
No!
Kaori-san, you're very pretty again today.
Shall we go to sleep?
Let's change your clothes...
Where is he? We'll smoke him out!
Yes!
You're really fast at running away.
Well, I don't like it when
things get complicated.
There's no need to stop
hanging out with me.
After forcing me to do all that,
that's quite a thing for you to say.
Ah, someone is coming.
W-W-Wait!
Akashi-san.
You created another idiotic movie...
They didn't stop the screening?
The viewers found it interesting, after all.
But Jougasaki-san's
faction is looking for you.
He'll probably be here soon.
Right, understood.
Well, I'm glad the people
watching had a laugh.
That's what he'd call entertainment.
I preferred your earlier films.
This one was of questionable character.
Whatever... It was a hit-and-run.
You are an idiot.
You got that right.
And you haven't kept your promise yet.
Promise?
Whatever, hurry up and escape.
Indeed! Now, Akashi-san, fare thee well!
Do not be fooled by Jougasaki's magic!
Do I seriously look like such a fool to you?
And so I left behind the site of my unproductive,
agonizing struggle over the past two years.
What's this?
When I returned to the boarding house,
someone had sloppily eaten the Castella
that Ozu had brought me the other day.
For some reason I was tired.
I felt like my reason had
crumbled to pieces like that Castella.
I was thinking my next film
would be about true love.
A true love film?
A love romance where
two people tied by fate
would overcome their positions,
ages, and even sexes.
It sounds like it's going to
turn into something weird again.
Let go! Let go, Akashi,san!
--I squished it... I s-squished it...
--Now, now, calm down.
I apologize. I am not fond of moths.
These are called Mochiguman, and they
come in sets of five, but I have lost one.
Worry not! As this Earth is round,
you are sure to meet once again!
Or if you'd like,
I'll help you search for it.
I'd rather you make that movie a reality.
Then it's a promise.
Promise? So that's it...
This opportunity is always
dangling in front of your eyes.
...but I didn't hate it.
Don't get carried away with your dreams.
That's what's I kept telling myself.
I had no confidence I could comprehend
a woman who could understand my selfish movies.
And so I tried watching
my latest, unfinished film.
I can't shake off the feeling of regret
for choosing the movie circle "Misogi"
in front of that fateful clock tower.
If I had joined some other circle, like
for instance the human flight circle "Birdman,"
I would have surely spent
quite a different two years.
You will always haunt me so, won't you?
That's the way I show my love.
Keep it to yourself!