Suppose that one day, I picked
up a microphone and said,
"Today, the weather shall be pleasant."
Anyone who heard that
would probably think,
"Oreki-kun just wanted to do a mic test."
Modern Literature Quiz (10 minutes)
Ten more seconds.
But maybe someone else might think this...
5... 4... 3... 2... 1...
"He just wants to assert that
The correct meaning of 'analogy' is:
a, metaphor b, comparison
the weather will be clear today."
Okay, time's up. Hand up your papers.
Cause of wildfire determined to be arson
Both assumptions may be reasonable.
Fake ¥10,000 bills found
The only way to guess which one is right
23-member gang of thieves arrested
is to rely on luck.
News in pictures
Things are sure getting out of hand lately.
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
Earth Science Prep Room
Does Anyone Have Any Idea?
Now that I think of it,
how did Sekitani Jun's...
How did your uncle's funeral end up?
It went through without a hitch.
Oh, okay.
What?
Nothing... Just...
Oreki-san,
if it's okay with you,
would you mind lighting an
incense stick for my uncle?
Who, me?
Yes. I was thinking of going
to visit my uncle's grave soon.
And, um...
if you'd like, you could come with me.
Hm...
All right.
Let's go.
Okay, I'll be in touch
in the coming days.
Sure.
Oreki-san, you're always
so good at solving riddles,
including the one about my uncle.
I really do think you're amazing.
I don't mind it if you say I'm a lucky guy,
but I wish you'd stop making
me out to be a big deal.
You sure like to keep low-key,
don't you, Oreki-san?
Aw, man, she doesn't get it at all.
Chitanda, someone long ago
said something pretty profound.
What is that?
"You can stick a poultice and
a plausible reason on anything."
Oreki-san, the way to say that is,
poultice
"You can stick a plaster and
a plausible reason on anything."
plaster
Oh...
Is that how it went?
Anyhow, I'm saying that you can
come up with a reason for anything.
Very well. Oreki-san,
let's say that the reason
why you have solved
so many cases so far
isn't because you are talented,
but because you are lucky.
However, don't you think being
able to base guesses on leads,
and then being able to follow
them to make deductions
is itself a kind of talent?
Are you saying I'm a master of reasoning?
Am I wrong?
Yes.
I don't know myself how I arrive
at the deductions that I do.
That's probably because you've
never taken a good look at yourself.
Well, she is right.
In that case, Chitanda, go ahead
and come up with some situation.
I'll prove that I can come up with
a reason for it, whatever it is.
That sounds like fun!
Hm, this is the perfect opportunity.
I'll show her that she
can't depend on me.
All right, what should I choose?
Anyone who was shopping at
Kobundo, near the train station
on October 31st, report to Shibazaki
in the faculty room at once.
What could that be about?
Beats me.
Let's make it that announcement!
Please deduce for what reason that
announcement just now was made!
Hm, okay, fine.
I accept.
Here you go.
Your powers of recollection
are as intimidating as ever.
That wasn't a compliment.
Now...
"Anyone who was shopping at
Kobundo, near the train station
on October 31st, report to Shibazaki
in the faculty room at once."
First comes our word check.
Kobundo
NDo you know what "Kobundo" is?
Yes. It's a small stationery store
across from the train station.
Hm.
It's a store run by an elderly couple.
Kamiyama Station
Kobundo
I've only been to it once.
What kind of a store is it?
Just a regular store.
North Elementary School is nearby,
North Elementary School
so I think that they stock items
that grade-schoolers use.
So it's not a place where high-schoolers
would go out of their way to go?
I suppose you could say that.
Hm.
Shibazaki
Is Shibazaki a faculty member?
Shibazaki-sensei is the vice principal.
Oreki-san, you sure are bad at
remembering names, aren't you?
Leave me alone.
"If I don't have to do
something, I don't do it.
If I have to do something, I do it quickly"
was my unshakeable creed,
but this was an important contest.
I'm going to have to turn up
the heat a little and go at this one.
First off...
Yes?
I know why Shibazaki would
be calling a student out.
Yes. I know why that is, myself.
Let's call the student called out, "X."
Student X
Now we're getting into the swing of this.
Hm?
Why don't you take a seat?
Okay.
At this point, we don't know if
Multiple or single?
Student X is multiple or single.
Shibazaki could be trying to impart
Shibazaki
educational guidance to X.
Student X
Put simply, he
could be chewing someone out.
Why do you think that?
Because when a student is called
down to the faculty room,
it isn't for anything good.
That's inductive reasoning.
Hm...
Oreki-san, are you taking this seriously?
I haven't been this serious
since I started school here.
It's even possible that this is the
most serious I've been in my life.
Hm.
Besides, if this was calling
them in to praise them,
he wouldn't use a vague,
neutral phrase like,
Anyone who was shopping at Kobundo,
he would say it straight.
With a page like that one,
Faculty Room
What's this about?
The Faculty Room?
The vice
principal?
anyone who was involved would be so anxious,
they wouldn't come down.
Is it a trap?
Did I draw attention?
What happened?
Why?
That could be true.
What's more, this page
was an urgent one.
Because he said "at once," right?
at once
No, most pages say
"at once." It's not that.
This announcement deviates
from the standard pattern,
so we can tell that
it was done in haste.
Standard pattern?
Let's say you were making an
announcement addressing me,
asking me to come to Class 1-A.
What would you say?
Let's see... Probably something like this:
"Oreki Hotaro-san of Class 1-B,
please report to Chitanda Eru
in the Class 1-A classroom."
Is that all? Try to remember other
announcements you've heard.
If it were me, I would say,
"Chitanda Eru of Class 1-A,
report to Oreki Hotaro
in the Class 1-B classroom.
Repeat, Chitanda Eru of Class 1-A,
report to Oreki Hotaro
in the Class 1-B classroom."
It's not just school announcements;
these kinds of announcements
are usually repeated twice.
But he only said this announcement once.
Shibazaki... In a rush
We can conclude
that he was in that much of a rush.
Hm?
And not just a run-of-the-mill
rush, either.
It's not?
For the reason that the announcement
was made after school.
Hm, Oreki-san, please don't
omit how you arrived at that.
"Omit." Music to my ears.
O-re-ki-san!
I mean, right? Making the
announcement the next morning
would be far more effective.
Classtime
Sure, Kamiyama High School
may be busy with club activities,
After school
but there are plenty who
leave for home right away, too.
Even so, he made an
after-school announcement,
Night
because the whole reason for the
announcement came up after school.
Going to school
Homeroom
And the reason was urgent enough
that he couldn't wait until tomorrow.
Student X
Meaning that Shibazaki made the
announcement on the possibility
that X hadn't gone
home from school yet.
Oreki-san, doesn't this have
an air of shadiness about it?
Yes, it does.
By the way, what does the
"shade" in "shadiness" refer to?
Dunno.
Next deduction... whatever Shibazaki
wants to speak to X about
cannot be done out in the open.
Whether that's just temporary
or in perpetuity, we can't say.
Is that because he didn't say
why he was paging X-san?
There's that, too, but it comes
up even more clearly than that.
I don't get it.
Shibazaki is the vice principal, right?
Coming down on students is done
by the guidance counselors.
Student X
That's right. Morishita-sensei
is always calling students in.
Where is the guidance counselor's office?
The second floor of the main building.
Guidance Counselor's Office
But X was paged to the faculty room
by Vice Principal Shibazaki.
Faculty Room
That shows that circumstances
are more serious,
and it also shows that information
about this is being kept
at the administrative level.
Or so it could be argued.
Um, Oreki-san...
What?
Going by what you've
deduced up to this point,
it strikes me that X-san is
involved in something bad.
Well, that is what it would mean, huh?
Then...
Student X
X is...
involved in some kind of crime.
Earth Science Prep Room
Soukou ('Frostfall')
When the dew formeth in gray coldness,
and descendeth as frost.
Hyouka
Whoo... This is a game
between Chitanda and me.
There's no need for it to be the truth.
I mean, the whole point when
we started this was to prove
that it isn't so simple for my
deductions to match the truth.
So, then, this crime could be...
Before we get into that,
assuming that all of my
deductions so far are correct,
the school currently
has no police officer,
so it's highly possible that an
equivalent authority is here.
If a crime was committed, it was
probably on October 31st here.
Incident occurs
Today
And yet, the announcement
came today, moments ago,
and was carried out in a rushed manner.
Incident occurs
Announcement
conceivable that immediately preceding,
a request was made by law enforcement.
But that request could have
been made over the phone.
That may be true, but if
it became necessary,
law enforcement would have
to take X into custody.
If that's the case, it would be
better to come here directly.
Custody...? Could X-san have
been paged as the culprit?
It's possible.
Hey, this is a game.
Oh, right. That's true.
If they weren't the culprit,
Shibazaki wouldn't have been rushed,
and could have made the announcement
in his own good time.
That follows.
Now, as to just what kind of crime
X could have committed...
Chitanda, do you have any ideas?
Well, let's see...
First off, there's shoplifting.
Mm-hm.
Beyond that, it's conceivable
that while tracking down someone
who had committed crimes
at other locations,
they received testimony that
someone of their description
Witness
was shopping at Kobundo.
If that's the case,
Larceny
there are any number
of crimes this could be about.
Assault
Interesting, for being such
a quick answer. However,
Shoplifting
shoplifting aside,
I doubt there was any testimony.
Shoplifting
Why is that?
If law enforcement knew what X's
appearance or characteristics were,
they would have probably
told Shibazaki, as well.
He wouldn't use the indirect
"anyone who was shopping at Kobundo."
That's true.
The incident occurred at Kobundo,
Kobundo
and we can assume that the action
X ostensibly took was shopping there.
Shopping
Was the announcement meant to
encourage them to turn themselves in?
It would be weird if that were the case.
Speculation:
Law enforcement doesn't know
what sort of person X is.
However, by making an announcement,
they think they will come to them.
Why would that be?
If I had done something wrong,
and that announcement came along...
Modern Literature Quiz (10 minutes)
Anyone who was shopping at
Kobundo, near the train station,
on October 31st, report to Shibazaki
in the faculty room at once.
Ten more seconds.
Oh, goody. The authorities still
don't know I'm the one who did it.
If this goes right, I could get
away with this free and clear.
Hm...
Under what circumstances would
they willingly come forward
after hearing that announcement?
If they felt guilty about
their crime, maybe?
No, if that were it, they'd turn
themselves in, end of statement.
Today's announcement would
have never happened.
Hm?
Hm...
What's the matter?
Let's set aside the nature of
X's crime for the moment.
But X felt guilty about what they did.
They made an apology
to Kobundo. In writing.
In writing?
Chitanda, what is today's date?
November 1st.
So October 31st was yesterday, wasn't it?
Why didn't Shibazaki say,
"Kobundo next to the train
station yesterday"?
yesterday
Now that you mention it,
that is indeed unusual.
When would you say "October 31st"
instead of "yesterday"?
When you have a form or a note
in front of you that says "October 31st"
and you're reading directly from it.
A form or a note, you say?
Yeah.
Why does law enforcement know
that X is involved in a crime,
but doesn't know what they look like?
Why would they think that X would
come forward if they paged them?
Put another way, why do they think
X feels guilty about their crime?
It's because X sent an
apology letter to Kobundo.
It probably went something like this:
Dear Kobundo:
"I am awfully sorry. I was
shopping on October 31st,
when I committed an unlawful act.
I will pay for the damage I did,
so please accept such-and-such."
Kobundo takes that apology
letter to the police.
Either the police or other law
enforcement follows up on the letter,
and comes to Kamiyama High School.
That was moments ago.
Shibazaki reads it, is taken aback,
and while skimming the letter,
rushes to make a schoolwide announcement.
Just a moment! Oreki-san, in your thinking,
Guilt
Recompense
while X-san wanted to apologize to Kobundo,
Assent
Amicable settlement
they were hoping not to get into trouble
Turn oneself in
Arrest
with the police, right?
First offense
Well, yeah.
In that case, I don't think
X-san would have written
that they were a student at
Kamiyama High School in their letter.
How would the police have
known to come here?
Hm. When the Kobundo
owners were asked by police
if they had any idea who it was,
they probably said that it was a
student at Kamiyama High School.
They could tell that if X
was wearing a uniform.
That's true.
What's more, if X did anything
to make them stand out,
it wouldn't be unusual
that they would remember.
Something to stand out?
And that will be the key
that helps deduce
what the crime that X committed was.
X did something to stand out.
But that by itself isn't a crime.
Purchase
X committed a crime.
What's more, the crime was such
Guilt
that without the apology letter,
they wouldn't have known right away.
X regretted the crime.
X's crime was serious enough that
it involved law enforcement at once.
Whatever X did, it wasn't
as petty as shoplifting.
Then, what?
Shopping that stood out...
Shopping that broke the law...
Kobundo is apparently a stationery
store aimed at grade-schoolers,
so I doubt they'd have
anything of great value.
Crime
Shopping... Shopping... Shopping...
Fake ¥10,000 bills found
23-member gang of thieves arrested
Whoo... For crying out loud.
For crying out loud?
X...
Fake ¥10,000 bills found
...passed
a fake ¥10,000 bill while shopping.
B-But... But... But...!
That is too far out of the realm
of possibility! It's not realistic!
It is not logical!
It's broken!
It's catastrophic!
W-Well...
Calm down.
This is... a game, right?
I-I'm sorry.
Well, you know, there's no need
to take it so seriously.
No, but still, it isn't
possible, Oreki-san.
Why do you say it isn't possible?
What we hear about being
passed around lately
are counterfeit ¥10,000 bills.
Oreki-san, you knew about them,
so that's why you said that X-san
must have used a counterfeit
¥10,000 bill, right?
Yeah.
But X-san could not possibly have
had one. Or rather, even if they had,
they would have had the
chance to exchange it.
What do you mean?
Oreki-san, how do you think that
X-san came by their counterfeit bill?
From an ATM, right?
Counterfeit bills that can
fool ATMs and banks
don't get around that easily.
And if they were that well-made,
it would be strange
that X-san could spot it.
Then, in change... Oh...
Hm...
That's right. You don't get
¥10,000 bills as change.
With the exception of commemorative coins,
they're the highest denomination
of money Japan has.
I know what you're getting at.
In other words,
there's only about one other way
he could have obtained a fake bill.
Bank
ATM
Change
Secondhand
But even supposing that X's
father had his own business,
Secondhand
Father (own business)
and had a fake bill foisted upon him,
if X had received it as
an allowance or something,
they would have been able to tell
their father that it was a fake bill.
This is a fake bill
That's right. If they had earned
it through a part-time job,
they could have also had
a chance to exchange it.
Hm.
What if they found it?
That would be strange, too.
Yeah, someone who would pass a
fake bill to get some pocket money
wouldn't be too quick to write
an apology letter, huh?
X probably felt guilty even
while they were passing it.
Passed a fake bill?
Without knowing where they
obtained the counterfeit bill,
it's impossible for your
deduction to be realistic.
Hm...
¥10,000...
Chitanda, do you like money?
Well, let's see.
I think it's fair to say that
I like it more than I dislike it.
If you dropped ¥10,000 in
the ditch, would you miss it?
I think I would. That is, unless
the money wasn't genuine.
If it was your own money,
there's no doubt you'd miss ¥10,000.
The reason X felt guilty,
even while they were passing it,
was probably because
it was their own money.
X must have gotten that bill from
someone, thinking it was legitimate.
If it wasn't from wages or allowance,
that leaves only one thing...
Money they got back
from loaning it out.
If they got their ¥10,000 back,
and it turned out to be a fake bill,
X would be disappointed. It's hard
to blame them for wanting to use it
at a store run by an old man and old lady,
even knowing it was wrong.
Even so, X-san could have
said it was counterfeit,
and asked to exchange it!
Really? A counterfeit bill is like
the joker in a game of Old Maid.
Nobody wants to get stuck with it.
Yeah, this sounds plenty
plausible, doesn't it?
"Hey, X, I've got the money
I borrowed from you before."
"Ah, Y-senpai, thank you."
"It was ¥10,000, right? Here you go."
"Yes, thanks."
Then, surprise, it's a fake bill.
Y, who X lent the money to,
is in a position higher than X is.
That's why, when Y gave them
a fake bill, they couldn't object.
At this point, we can say
that X is a single person.
Kobundo being a stationery store
that sells inexpensive items,
if a few high-schoolers came in
buying things with ¥10,000 bills,
that would seem out of place.
That wraps that up.
So what about Y?
Y also came by the fake bill.
It could be that they got it
back from a Z above them.
Student X
If we lump everyone Y and beyond
as one collective Y,
then who is Y?
Counterfeiter Y
A store manager
somewhere without a conscience,
or the counterfeiter themselves.
The reason the police might be involved
could be because they anticipate
being able to find out from X
where the fake bills are coming from.
And that... is my deduction.
Hm, after all that talking I did,
not saying anything back...
is a bit mean.
Kobundo is over that way, huh?
"Anyone who was shopping at
Kobundo, near the train station,
on October 31st, report to Shibazaki
in the faculty room at once."
When you think about it, we got
a lot of mileage from just that.
Yeah, we did. End of game.
Oreki-san...
Hm? What?
I thought we started this game
so that you could prove something.
Oh, now that you mention it...
What was it, again?
What was it?
Oreki-san...
would you like to deduce what it was?
Earth Science Prep Room
Give me a break.
Man in possession of
counterfeit currency arrested
Ho... I seem to remember
that whole game yesterday
was over something that
couldn't possibly be true...?
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "Mishap-py New Year."
Mishap-py New Year