Modern Literature Quiz
(10 minutes)
The correct meaning of 'analogy' is:
a, metaphor   b, comparison
Cause of wildfire determined to be arson
Fake ¥10,000 bills found
23-member gang of thieves arrested
News in pictures
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
Earth Science Prep Room
Does Anyone Have Any Idea?
"You can stick a poultice and
a plausible reason on anything."
"You can stick a plaster and
"Kobundo"
"Kamiyama Station"
"Kamiyama Station" "Kobundo"
"Kobundo"
"North Elementary School"
"Shibazaki"
"Student X"
"Multiple or single?"
"Shibazaki"
"Student X"
"Faculty Room"
"What's this about?" "The Faculty Room?"
"The vice principal?"
"Is it a trap?" "Did I draw attention?"
"What happened?" "Why?"
"at once"
"Shibazaki... In a rush"
"Classtime"
"After school"
"Night"
"Going to school"
"Homeroom"
"Student X"
Guidance Counselor's Office
Faculty Room
"Student X"
Earth Science Prep Room
Soukou ('Frostfall')
When the dew formeth in gray coldness,
and descendeth as frost.
Hyouka
When the dew formeth in gray coldness,
and descendeth as frost.
"Incident occurs"
"Today"
"Incident occurs" "Announcement"
"Witness"
"Larceny"
"Assault"
"Shoplifting"
"Kobundo"
"Shopping"
Modern Literature Quiz
(10 minutes)
"yesterday"
"Dear Kobundo:"
"Guilt" "Recompense"
"Guilt" "Recompense" "Assent"
"Amicable settlement"
"Turn oneself in"
"Turn oneself in" "Arrest"
"First offense"
"Purchase"
"Guilt"
"Crime"
Cause of wildfire determined to be arson
Fake ¥10,000 bills found
23-member gang of thieves arrested
"Bank" "ATM" "Change" "Secondhand"
"Secondhand"
"Father (own business)"
"This is a fake bill"
"Passed a fake bill?"
"Student X"
"Counterfeiter Y"
Earth Science Prep Room
Man in possession of
counterfeit currency arrested
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having
antennas is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Mishap-py New Year