It was raining that day as well.
And so you didn't come
because of the rain?
I was supposed to kill you.
It was all set up.
If I had, I would have been free.
So why didn't you?
You chose to be hunted. Why?
Why did you love me?
Let's just go away somewhere.
Escape.
Vanish, and go somewhere
where there's no one else.
Just the two of us.
Was the target terminated?
He got away.
Our agents were cut down.
They ran out of firepower
and were unable to take out--
Why did you come back?
Where's Julia?
I couldn't find her.
Shin, do not follow
in your brother's footsteps.
Keep going, just drive past it.
What?
Somebody might have
gotten there already.
Wait here.
Annie.
I told them you weren't here.
I said you were already dead.
Told them they were
wasting their time.
Don't talk.
Vicious assassinated all of the elders.
That's what they said.
Everyone... they've all lost
their sense of place in the world.
Like kites without strings or tails.
Oh, so you found Julia. That's good.
I'm happy for you.
Annie!
It got a little chilly today.
It's those cold winds...
You won't need all those weapons if
we run away together. You know that.
You're staying.
Then I'll stay too.
I'll be with you until the end.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna
make a bit of a scene.
You're a very lucky woman.
Yeah, right. My timing was perfect
for getting shot at and nearly killed.
I'm really on a roll.
The Redtail won't be
functional for a while.
You're having some
pretty good luck yourself.
That Spike, he was nothing but trouble.
He's probably not coming back.
They may have killed
him already, you know?
It's possible.
So what? Want me
to go looking for him?
Forget it. He's dealing
with his own past.
It's his fight.
You told him to go after her.
My leg is wrecked,
my ship is busted,
hell yes, he was nothing but trouble!
And I don't give a damn!
So what kind of woman is she?
What's Julia like?
Ordinary.
The kind of dangerous, beautiful ordinary
that you just can't leave alone.
I see.
Like an angel from the underworld.
Or maybe a devil from paradise.
This way.
Get down!
Julia!
Julia...
Where's Spike?
Can you help me track him down?
All living things, every being
that walks and breathes,
- each has its own star.
- Huh?
When a life is born,
a new star appears.
That is the guardian star.
The star that warms this planet
is someone's guardian star as well.
The red star you see overhead.
The blue star on the horizon.
And when a life ends,
the star falls and disappears.
Don't say that.
You, Running Rock.
That's not my name.
Don't call me that.
His star is about to fall.
I have dreamed it.
This is ridiculous.
What am I doing here?
Do not fear death.
Death is always at our side.
When we show fear,
it jumps at us faster than light.
But if we do not show fear,
it casts its eye upon us gently,
and then guides us into infinity.
Vicious, here it is.
Her passport was still
inside the pocket.
It'll be impossible for them
to escape the planet now.
A beast that has lost his place.
He has nowhere to return to now.
He will come.
Spike, you're-- you're back!
Do you have anything to eat?
- Huh?
- I'm really starving.
This food tastes terrible, as usual.
For being so bad,
you sure eat a lot of it.
They say hunger is the best spice.
Ever heard this story?
There once was a tiger-striped cat.
This cat died a million deaths,
revived, and lived a million lives.
And he was owned by various people
who he didn't really care for.
The cat wasn't afraid to die.
Then one day, the cat became a
stray cat, which meant he was free.
He met a white female cat.
And the two of them spent
their days together happily.
Well, years passed, and the white cat
grew weak and died of old age.
The tiger-striped cat cried a
million times, and then he died too.
Except this time,
he didn't come back to life.
Yeah, it's a good story.
I hate that story.
I never liked cats. You know that.
Oh yeah, that's right.
- Hey, Spike.
- Yeah?
I just wanna ask you one thing.
- What's that?
- Is it for the girl?
She's dead.
There's nothing I can do for her now.
Where are you going?
Why are you going?
You told me once to forget the past,
'cause it doesn't matter.
But you're the one still
tied to the past, Spike!
Look at my eyes, Faye.
One of them is a fake
'cause I lost it in an accident.
Since then, I've been seeing
the past in one eye,
and the present in the other.
So I thought I could only see patches
of reality, never the whole picture.
Don't tell me things like that.
You've never told me
anything about yourself.
So don't tell me now.
I felt like I was watching a dream
I'd never wake up from.
Before I knew it,
the dream was all over.
My memory... finally came back.
But nothing good came of it.
There was no place
for me to return to.
This was the only
place I could go.
And now you're leaving,
just like that!
Why do you have to go?
Where are you going?
What are you going to do?
Just throw your life away
like it was nothing?!
I'm not going there to die.
I'm going to find out
if I'm really alive.
I have to do it, Faye.
♪ Everything is already over ♪
♪ You say with closed ears ♪
♪ The words only flow ♪
♪ Towards a tomorrow without peace ♪
♪ There's nothing that won't change ♪
♪ Even if my life ends ♪
♪ This love will not disappear ♪
♪ It's something that will live forever ♪
♪ Even if dreams are hidden in darkness ♪
♪ I got a rainbow ♪
♪ Rainbow in your hands ♪
Shin.
- Where's Vicious?
- On the top floor. This way.
Shin!
Shin...
Vicious... he's got to be stopped.
I was waiting... for you to
come back and take over.
So you're finally awake.
I told you before, Spike.
I'm the only one who can
kill you and set you free.
Those words apply
to you as well, Vicious.
Either way, it's going to end here.
Julia is dead.
Let's finish it now.
As you wish.
It's all a...
dream.
Yeah...
Just a dream.
Bang.
♪ Never seen a bluer sky ♪
♪ Yeah, I can feel it reaching out
and moving closer ♪
♪ There's something about blue ♪
♪ Asked myself what it's all for ♪
♪ You know, the funny thing
about it, I couldn't answer ♪
♪ No, I couldn't answer ♪
♪ Things have turned
a deeper shade of blue ♪
♪ And images that might
be real may be illusion ♪
♪ Keep flashing off and on ♪
♪ Free ♪
♪ Wanna be free ♪
♪ Gonna be free ♪
♪ Move among the stars ♪
♪ You know, they really aren't so far ♪
♪ Feel so free ♪
♪ Gotta know free ♪
♪ Please ♪
♪ Don't wake me from the dream ♪
♪ It's really everything it seemed ♪
♪ I'm so free ♪
♪ No black and white ♪
♪ In the blue ♪
♪ Everything is clear now ♪
♪ Life is just a dream, you know,
that's neverending ♪
♪ I'm ascending ♪