I don't wanna! I don't wanna, I don't wanna, I don't wanna!
Why can't I play with Ichuki inshtead?!
Potpourri, summer vacation is over already.
Starting today, I have to go to school.
You're my partner!
So you have to stay by my shide no matter what!
"No matter what" is a bit far.
Now now, calm down, Potpourri.
School will be finished before you know it!
So while we're gone, Chypre and
Coffret will play with you instead!
That's right!
No thanksh. I want to play with Ichuki.
Why not play with her at school?
Shure!
You can't do that!
School is a place of study, not a playground!
Why not?! Why not?! I wanna go, I wanna go, I wanna go!
Figures.
Potpourri!
No.
Ichuki, I...
hate you sho much!
Potpourri!
Po—
Po-Po—
Pot—
Potpourriiiiiii!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Potpourri!
We have to go after her!
Right!
But what about school?
Oh, right.
But...
We'll search for Potpourri for you!
You should all get to school!
All right then. Please find Potpourri for me, Chypre, Coffret.
Leave it to us!
Potpourri! Where have you gone?!
Potpourri...
Potpourri Runs Away!
Itsuki is Heartbroken!
Why did she have to get mad at poor little me?!
I didn't do anything wrong!
This is all Mom and Dad's fault.
Ahh! She'll see me!
Huh?
Found you!
Let me go! Let me go!
Hey, what's your name?
It'sh Potpourri.
You're so cute!
Potpourri!
Where are you?!
I'm really sorry!
I feel really bad about leaving all the cleanup from the opening ceremony to you.
Don't worry.
We can manage on our own.
Thank you, everyone!
It's quite all right. We're always so reliant on you after all, President.
All right then, let's go look for Potpourri!
Right!
Let's do it!
Huh...
So you're a fairy, Potpourri?
That'sh right!
I fight with the Precure to help protect thish world!
But...
I had a fight with my partner Precure.
Huh? Why?
Because she won't play with me at all!
She won't let me shtay by her side.
Then you're the same as me!
Huh?
I had a fight with my mom too.
That's why I
ran away from home!
Ran away?
Yeah!
See...
Mom and Dad didn't take me to the amusement park, or to the beach. They didn't take me anywhere!
They promised they'd play with me.
Mom and Dad don't care about me at all.
Potpourri, summer vacation is over already.
Starting today, I have to go to school.
Then you're the shame as me.
Ichuki won't play with me anymore!
That's why I ran away!
Huh?
I'm never going back home!
Oh! Sho you're not gonna go back?!
Then I'm gonna run away too!
Huh?!
Ichuki doeshn't care about me either!
That'sh why I'm not gonna go back to Ichuki!
Really?!
Yeah!
Then come run away with me!
Okay!
They're gone! Gone! Gone! My cosmetics have disappeared!
Kumojacky threw it out saying, "You can't beat the Precure because you're obsessed with this trash."
What?!
Ah, this is a tragedy!
I can work with you people no longer!
Ah, non, non!
Hold it! If you're leaving, you might as well go fight the Precure.
I get it already!
This whole park will be our new house!
It's sho big! This ish great!
There'sh water here!
This'll be our kitchen!
And this swing will be my room!
Then thish'll be my room!
Huh?
What's thish?
This'll be where we hang our laundry!
And this'll be our bed!
Yay!
Potpourri! Potpourri!
Itsuki!
Tsubomi! Erika!
Did you find her?
Not yet.
I see.
Itsuki, you're soaked.
It's my fault.
If I'd just thought a bit harder about how Potpourri must've felt...
Itsuki...
We'll go look around the botanical gardens again!
Thank you. I'll keep looking around here.
Itsuki, your umbrella!
Itsuki...
Potpourri...
Potpourri!
Sorry about this, Yuri. I didn't mean to hold you up.
It's fine.
Think about how many people you'd worry if you caught a cold.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow!
Okay.
I'm back!
It's pouring, Mom!
Have you brought in the laundry?
The rain isn't stopping.
It ishn't.
Potpourri, now that we're living in
the park, we should take a rain bath!
I don't like cold baths.
I don't either.
That must be my mom!
Mo—
Ah!
Yuri!
I see. So that's why you two ran away.
Yeah.
That'sh right.
But Potpourri, you really shouldn't run off on your own, you know?
Huh?
Because you did, Haruka found out about you, after all.
It'sh fine! Haruka's a good girl!
What would you have done if a
bad girl had found you instead?
Haruka.
I know your mother and father might be busy,
but I'm sure they care about you very much.
You really think so?
I do.
What would you know, Yuri?!
I know very well.
Huh?
That you'd make the people who care
about you very sad if you went missing.
Let's go back.
Okay...
All right...
The rain normally bothers me so, and yet today I find I can truly appreciate it.
It washes away my sadness.
Haruka!
Haruka! Haruka!
She's...
Haruka!
Harukaaaa!
Mom!
She's come to find you.
What's the matter?
Mom's gonna be mad at me.
Potpourri!
We finally found you!
Chypre! Coffret!
Thank goodness!
You found Potpourri for us, Moonlight?
By a lucky coincidence.
Thank you so much!
Where'sh...
Where'sh Ichuki?!
Itsuki and the others had to go to school!
So we searched for you in her place, Potpourri!
I shee.
Wh-Who are you?!
Huh?
The Flower of your Heart withers with such sadness.
How well it complements my feelings!
It's Kobraja!
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
Mom!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Mom! Mom!
Telephone pole!
Potpourri!
You can do it, Potpourri!
I can't... hold on!
Ichuki!
Potpourri!
Ichuki?!
Telephone pole!
Ichuki's soaking wet.
Could it be because she was looking for me?
Potpourri, I'm so glad you're safe.
Ichuki?
I really should've thought more
seriously about how you must've felt.
I'm sorry.
Ichuki...
I'm sho sorry!
I see.
So you're Potpourri's partner, the third Precure?
Who are you?
She's Cure Moonlight!
You're Cure Moonlight?!
You were one step away from losing your partner forever.
Remember that.
I will.
Telephone pole! Telephone pole!
We need to hurry and stop that Desertrian!
Itsuki!
We'll go and find Tsubomi and Erika!
Got it!
Potpourri.
Let's go!
We can stop that Desertrian together!
All right!
Sheed of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
Telephone pole!
Damn it!
Potpourri!
No!
Stop!
I won't make it!
Blossom! Marine!
I'm sorry we're so late!
So you found Potpourri?
Yeah! Thank you!
Now we just need to purify the Desertrian!
Let's do it!
Haruka...
Haruka! Where have you gone?!
Mom! Mom?!
That Desertrian must be her mom.
Mom! Mom!
Don't worry, Haruka.
The Precures will save her, I promise!
Sunflower Aegis!
Precure Double Punch!
Sunshine Flash!
Marine Shoot!
Blossom Shower!
We did it!
Telephoooooone pole!
Mom! M-Mom!
Ah, what an unsightly scene this is.
Just because her child goes missing, she kicks up all this tiresome fuss.
"Just because"?!
Well, am I wrong?
If her child really was so precious to her,
why would she not always keep it by her side?
You're wrong!
Potpourri!
Being by her shide isn't really what being precioush to her means!
Potpourri...
Ichuki is always thinking about me!
Even if she goes to school, or anywhere elshe, she's always thinking about me!
That's right!
Even if we're separated for a while,
that doesn't mean I stop caring for Potpourri!
The same goes for Haruka's mother
whose Flower of the Heart you stole.
She cares about Haruka
more than anyone!
How idiotic.
Get them, Desertrian!
Telephone pole!
Precure Impact!
Impact!
What?!
Telephone pooooooole!
The feelings that bind us are more precious than you would know!
Kobraja, the darkness in your heart shall be illuminated by my light!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
This is why I never go out without sprucing up!
Mom?
Haruka!
Thank god.
I'm so glad you're safe.
Mom...
Mom!
I'm so sorry!
In the language of flowers, a verbena means "the blessing of family."
It's nice that both Haruka and Potpourri were able to put things right, isn't it?
Shure is!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
I'm gonna do some training!
Huh?
I'll learn how to act like a plushie so I can go to shchool too!
Oh, I see!
We'll teach you the ropes!
Just do it like this!
Like thish?
Just like that. Just hold that pose.
You mustn't go back to normal!
But it'sh hard to keep that pose!
I'm counting on you two to help her, okay?
All right.
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
She parted from him most painfully.
Even now, she still bears that sadness.
And she keeps the pain in her
heart locked away from others.
I've always admired Cure Moonlight's strength and beauty!
I want Yuri to be a Precure alongside us!
HeartCatch Precure:
The Saddening Truth!
He Was Yuri's Fairy...
We'll catch everyone's hearts!