We're not asking for freedom if it comes in shackles
Especially in a world so imperfect
Anime-Koi
Presents
Chaika The Coffin Princess
kyou
It's days like today
kyou
that make me want to live
mou)
(I think. I think.)
mou)
It's the important people in my life
who help me make it through
mou)
(I think. I think.)
mou)
ryou
My vision narrows being surrounded by love
ryou
What do you expect me to do on a night like this?
We cross vows at the end of the road
Seeing into ourselves in our own reflections
utsushidaseyo
We're not asking for freedom if it comes in shackles
Especially in a world so imperfect
We're not interested in the answers that only lead to farewells
We'll look for you
until we find you
A "hero"?
Yes, hero. Searching.
Any idea, please tell.
Oh, a hero! A hero, right?
Of course we know one!
We'll take you to him. Come with us.
Grateful!
Toru?
What the hell do you think yo—
Seriously, what are you thinking?
Hey! You little bastard!
Hey, wait! No fair!
Hang on a second!
Are you trying to kill each other? Let me join in too!
Come on, let's do it! Let's kill 'em!
Fredrica...
Toru, mean...
Huh? Why?
Good people, informants. Cruel.
Listen, Chaika.
Don't you realize they were gonna sell you off?
Those guys were obviously shady!
Shocking truth...
Hey, what happened to killing? Let's kill now!
The Pursuer and the Pursued
I told you not to wander around alone.
You're being hunted, you know.
What'll you do if a fight breaks out in the middle of town?
Yes...
Why did you go out by yourself?
I... no help.
Can only use magic.
Cooking, bad.
Sewing, starting fire... all bad.
So you wanted to at least get us some information?
Mysterious person, long time, no information.
Mysterious person?
Oh, you mean Guy?
Eight heroes. Remains scattered.
Taken away, only rumors.
Name, unknown. Location, unknown...
Hey, Fredrica.
You were with the eight heroes who subjugated the emperor, right?
You really don't remember anything about the other heroes?
That little...
Gather remains... my goal.
Give best effort...
Hey, don't worry about it.
You hired us to help you reach that goal, right?
Anything you can't do, we will.
But...
As our employer, all you have to do is keep looking forward.
Toru...
I'm back, Brother.
Welcome back...
...like hell!
What are you doing?!
Oh, yes, that was a close call.
I'm glad I got here in time.
What was "close"?
I got us some food.
This gecko, as well as earthworms, stonefly larva, and some other things.
We won't be going hungry for a while.
Food?
Any word on the heroes?
Nothing of use to us,
but it seems there are many former soldiers in the town of Perimeral.
By vehicle, we'll reach it in about a day.
Perimeral?
Also, this was hanging in the town square.
We'd better make haste.
Wh-What is it, Nikolai?
You're giving him something to dry off with, right?
Just go and do it.
And tell him how you feel while you're at it.
We're all rooting for you.
That's right, Vivi. You can do it.
I-I wasn't thinking anything like that...
Oh, thanks!
I haven't stood under a waterfall in a long time.
It really does firm you up, body and soul.
Hey, that's...
I'm gonna stab you!
Hang on! Calm down! What's with you, Vivi?!
Is something the matter?
N-No, nothing...
You were really getting into that training.
Oh, did it appear that way?
I suppose, as I was trying to clear my doubts,
more power went into my swings.
Doubts?
I just can't believe that Chaika and those saboteurs
are villains who will plunge the world into war again.
In fact, it appears they are constantly moving forward,
following only their own convictions.
Why don't we let her bring back the age of war?
It may be that I envy them.
They know the path that they must follow...
How about this? If you're conflicted,
you could stop here to reconsider your future plans.
As the times change, I think it makes sense
that a cavalier's disposition should change as well.
Taking a wife and having children to safeguard the prestigious Gillette name...
Isn't that an important duty of a nobleman, as well?
That is true...
But it doesn't feel real to me yet.
For starters, I have no one to marry.
She doesn't have to be nobility.
Someone suitable could be very close to you.
Such as...
Gillette-sama!
Leonardo.
Did you find out anything?
Yes. It seems the wanted posters paid off.
There have been multiple reports of
three people resembling Chaika and her companions in the
nearby town of Perimeral.
Perimeral, huh? That's close.
However, there's something curious...
What?
Their characteristics weren't quite the same.
It was a male and two females, but...
Their characteristics?
What should we do, Captain?
We'll head for Perimeral.
Prepare to depart.
Yes, sir!
Brother, I'm sure you've noticed...
Yeah.
Don't be shocked. We're being followed.
What did I just say?
Just continue acting like nothing's wrong.
R-Right.
Hey, could you clear a path? We can't get past.
You, leave possessions. Everything. Go.
Huh? Bandits?
Sorry, but if you want to attack someone, raid the next car.
Not up for discussion?
Chaika, get your Gundo ready.
Her buddies are probably hiding nearby.
Don't move the vehicle.
Akari, keep Chaika safe.
Understood.
A longsword user?
If you won't move, I'll have to move you by force.
A snake blade?
Dance.
Damn it!
Toru!
Don't interfere! Check the perimeter!
Chaika?!
Akari!
Forgive me!
Toru!
I've got the white one here!
Chaika!
Distracted!
Akari!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
There you have it.
Let Chaika...
Let our white girl go!
No, how about you let our red girl go first?
Brother!
That car...
No other choice.
Damn! They got away!
Nothing we can do. Let's go.
That would be best.
You think a magic battle recently took place here?
It's possible.
The taboo emperor's daughter was a wizard, wasn't she?
To be specific, the girl we're chasing, Chaika, is a wizard.
There's too much we don't know...
I think it's in our best interests to go to Perimeral,
the town the information came from.
Gillette-sama.
Why don't we split up?
It's possible that Chaika and her
companions could still be nearby.
If there's even a single footprint,
to an extent, Leo and I can track them.
Then... can I count on you?
Of course.
Yes!
Rude! No touch! Rude!
Rude! Rude! Rude!
Fine, fine.
Well, she doesn't seem to be concealing any weapons.
Yeah.
This is...
What?
I saw the same kind of scar on Chaika not long ago.
On Chaika?
Just who are you?
What's your name?
Why did you ambush us?
The cold shoulder, huh?
We don't know what to call you if you don't tell us your name.
"Hey, you" could get confusing.
Then, I will give her a name.
You will?
Sticky.
Huh? That's a name?
Yes. There's also Slimy, Slippery, Heavy, and other similar options.
Okay, your name is Sticky, then.
I'll ask again. Why did you attack us, Sticky?
Answer him, Sticky.
What are you after, Sticky?
You can't stick to your guns forever, Sticky.
Bohdan.
Chaika Bohdan!
What? What about Chaika?
Chaika Bohdan! Name! My name!
Chaika?
What exactly are you?
Silence again, huh?
It seems we have no choice, Brother.
We'll have to torture her.
Yeah. You're right.
Nice. Very nice.
Treatment, unfair!
Remove clothes, unfair!
Well, you know...
It's standard to make sure you're not concealing any blades or anything.
Relax. I won't take off any more.
I'm not interested in women with small chests.
Kids, either.
R-R-Rude!
What? You'd prefer if I were interested?
This is what a woman's chest should look li—
Idiot. What do we do now?
She doesn't have any remains.
She probably keeps them in her coffin, too.
Coffin?
Which means we have no use for her.
But since she's here, why don't we have a little fun,
then sell her off to a slaver or something?
I'm just kidding.
It's good...
This is very good, Brother.
I just sprinkled a few spices on it, but it worked pretty well.
The juicy flesh and crispy, burnt skin are an exquisite match.
We'll finish this off in no time.
How about it? Ready to talk yet?
You're hungry, aren't you?
Talk, and you get to eat.
Well?
You don't want any? We'll finish it, then.
You like it?
Really? You don't, eh?
Then we'll just finish the whole—
D-Delicious!
I see, I see.
Good.
Here. Say "ahh."
Come on, "ahh."
Spices, exquisite!
You make that look so tasty...
Delicious! Grateful!
But, you know... you're making this difficult for me.
If you're done, I've gotta tie you up again.
Their personalities are like night and day,
but they really do look identical.
Identical?
You and Chaika.
You don't know? Our...
The girl your friends captured.
Her name is Chaika, too.
Anyway, there's more than one person out there
calling herself Chaika, the emperor's daughter, and gathering his remains.
We know of three, at least.
It's likely there are more than that.
I'm going to check for any movement outside.
Right.
West river... waterfall upstream... tomorrow before dawn.
So that's it...
The man with Chaika in that shed wasn't a saboteur, was he?
No. Looks like the information you heard in Perimeral was accurate.
Either Chaika found herself some new employees, or...
Who's he meeting tomorrow morning at the waterfall?
I don't know,
but judging by the aftermath of that fight,
there's no doubt that multiple forces are lurking around here.
That being the case, we should make the appropriate preparations.
Leo, stand back.
Are you after the remains?
Your name's Chaika, just like her.
You look like her, too.
Which means you call yourself the emperor's daughter,
just like our white Chaika, right?
White Chaika, fake!
Real Chaika, me!
Yeah, all fakes say that.
If white Chaika real, show proof!
I don't have any. It's possible you're both fakes.
White, fake...
Gather Father's remains, can't allow.
So you are after his remains.
How many have you found?
Do you want to give him a funeral, too?
Gather all Father's remains.
Then... kill all.
Wha—?
Kill all who killed Father.
Kill all who fled, didn't protect Father.
Revenge?
Yeah, that's the more natural answer.
Where'd you get that weapon,
and where'd you learn to use it?
You can't tell me that, either?
No... memory.
What?
Are you saying... you don't remember what happened?
Yes. Memories missing.
Missing? You mean there's a gap in your memory?
Have memories before war.
End of war, vague.
Only clear memories, past year.
Her, too?
What's wrong?
What? What is it?
Back...
Huh?
Back! Bug!
Oh... A bug went down your back?
Remove binds!
I can't do that...
Back!
Oh, all right...
Where is it?
No touch!
You want me to get it out, don't you?
Pervert!
What?
Planning to caress body! Pervert!
I-I'm not gonna caress you!
Remove binds!
I told you, I can't...
Bug, moving! Back!
Just be quiet!
Brother! Look out!
That was a very close call.
What the hell was "close"?!
I am back, Brother.
Do you have to do this every time?!
Well? How'd it go?
The letter was gone, and this was in its place.
That's Chaika's...
So they agreed to our deal.
Lucky you. Looks like your
companions haven't abandoned you.
Obvious.
This is it. Your affectionate first encounter.
jigoku no soko made nozoki kome
Let's take a peek at the bottom of hell
kuchite yuku no hanakara
It's rotting from the start
shitai mitai ni aruku michi
We're walking on the road like corpses
gira gira to taiyou ga teritsukeru
While the blazing sun beats down on us
omae wa itsuka namae sae
You'll fall into the depths of hell one day
wakaranaku naru kurai ochite yuku
And not even remember your name
hito wa naze ikiru no ka
Why do people live?
inochi kirikizan demo
Even when our life is in pieces
owarinaki bonnou wo daite odore ba
We embrace our endless desires and dance
mujou ka
Is that cruel?
kawaki no tani kara yojinobore
Climb up from the valley of thirst
kaze no oto ga kodama shite
You'll hear the echoing wind
goran warera wo michibiku kairaku wa
See, while the desires guide us
kanashimi wo tsukkitte iku genri
We have to push our way through sadness to get there
osoreru na
Do not be scared
furueru na
Do not tremble
ikiru no da
Live on
White Chaika, fake!
Father's remains, must reclaim!
Toru, contract with me, necessary.
Hesitation... no understand.
Next week, episode 6:
"Red and White."
Red and White