Solitaire
Where are the crystals?
Right here!
I've got all five of them!
Regina!
This is...
What?
The crystals...
Flew away...
Hey! What gives?!
How the heck should we know?!
Geez!
We're going after them!
Let's go too!
Wait!
Where would we go?
You all seem to be at a loss.
Please leave this matter to me.
Mr. Sebastian?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Guided By The Crystals!
To The Princess's Location!
The crystals are currently heading northeast.
They are traveling at Mach 3.
Wow!
How do you know all that?
Satellite data can deliver very precise locations.
Well, that's honest...
What kind of guy is Sebastian?
A butler for the Yotsuba family!
The signal has stopped responding.
What could that mean?
Does that mean we've lost track of the crystals?
Indeed.
Oh no...
Let's go to where the signal disappeared!
Its coordinates appear to be in a glacial region.
Glacial region?
What kind of place is that?
A place covered in ice that stays frozen year-round.
Sounds breezy!
I wouldn't say "breezy" when it's a dangerously frigid mountain of ice.
How do we get there?
Everyone,
leave this matter to me as well.
Sebastian's really something!
He's as resourceful as Batman!
Makoto, is something the matter?
We have to reach the crystals before Regina's team does at all costs!
Indeed we do.
Either way, we can't just let her off!
She broke her promise with Mana!
Yeah!
But Regina was acting kind of strange back then...
Give them the crystal?
Regina?
No...
I want the crystals...
Her eyes looked different...
That could just be her true nature.
I know you want to trust her.
But the fact is that she betrayed you.
She may not wish to settle things with another game next time.
Yeah...
The crystals disappeared around the peak of that mountain.
It is dangerous to go any further by helicopter.
So we have to climb the mountain ourselves?
Indeed.
You all aren't headed for the summit, are ya?
We are.
Don't do it.
That mountain's a sacred one,
and nobody can intrude near the summit.
Even now, not one person has made it to the top.
Really?
Worry not.
The given coordinates are outside the restricted area.
Even then, that mountain ain't something little girls can handle.
Don't go courtin' danger.
But we still have to go!
I know we'll find what we've been searching for there!
Guess y'all have your reasons...
We do.
Then you better believe in the legend of the mountain's light.
Legend of its light?
Legend has it that long ago, on this very mountain,
a group of close friends - a team - was saved by a miraculous light.
I'll be prayin' for ya.
Thank you!
Okay, let's go!
Believe in the legendary light!
Have a safe trip.
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
The light...
Restricted area my foot!
I'm going to be the first man to reach the peak!
You doing all right?
You seem to be out of breath.
This is... nothing!
Besides... I'm still...
A Trump Kingdom... knight!
You're making us doubt the strength of Trump Kingdom's knights.
You gotta know your limits!
I-I'm fine!
I can always jump in and save the day when it's truly needed!
The air's gotten thinner.
It's pretty cold, too.
But we can endure it while transformed.
Where did the crystals disappear?
According to the coordinates, it should be around here,
but they're nowhere in sight.
Maybe they're buried under the snow?
All right, let's dig!
What, the whole thing?
I don't think...
that'll get you... anywhere...
Where are you, crystals?
If that legendary light is real, then please shine!
There you are, Precures!
Regina!
We heard your little chat.
So, the crystals are around here?
We'll gladly take them, then.
Thanks for searching.
How underhanded can you get?
Should you not say something to Cure Heart?
Oh, I will.
I won't give up the crystals.
Regina...
What do you plan to do with the crystals?
That's none of your business, isn't it?
Yes it is!
Those crystals could be the key to saving Trump Kingdom... and the world!
I won't let you have the princess or the crystals!
Hmph! Who cares about some dumb princess?
I only want the crystals.
The crystals!
Regina, what's wrong with you?
You're not the Regina I knew!
Hmph. What did you ever know about me?
Regina!
There's no point in talking any more, Cure Heart.
That girl is...
no longer your friend!
Go away!
The crystals are mine!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Just get out of my sight!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Regina!
Cure Heart!
Mana!
This is all my fault...
It's not.
Mana chose to help Regina on her own.
Indeed she did.
Mana still thinks of Regina as a friend.
Either way, we have to save her.
Ladies, why not put aside our quarrel for today?
Put aside?
You're just going to attack us after lowering our guard!
You can think what you want,
but don't you have a friend you ought to search for?
Well, you three will be in trouble if anything happens to King Selfish's daughter.
Personally, I wouldn't mind if something happened to that girl.
Nah, I don't want my head on King Selfish's chopping block 'cause of her.
I don't think this is the time to squabble.
True.
Let's focus on finding Cure Heart.
Now, let's go too.
It's a rather deep crevice...
Let's all be careful.
Please be safe, Cure Heart...
Cold!
Mana...
What?
The crystals?
Pretty...
Regina, look out!
Mana, look!
The princess...
It's her?
The crystals must have led us to her!
She's beautiful...
Yeah...
Mana...
Here.
I'm sorry for breaking our promise.
You're back...
You're back to the Regina I know!
Wait, Mana!
It's really you!
Of course it is!
You're a weirdo!
But what am I "back" from?
I don't know.
But up until now, you were like a different person.
And when you looked at the crystals, your eyes just... changed.
What about now?
They're not changing.
I wonder what came over you?
But if this is really the princess, we have to tell Makopi right away!
Makopi's been searching for her this whole time.
What for?
Well...
she wants to restore her ruined Trump Kingdom and save its people.
What would happen to Daddy if she did?
That woman turned Daddy to stone...
Hey, Regina...
I don't know what could happen either,
but if your dad turns Trump Kingdom back to normal,
the princess wouldn't have anything to fight over, right?
They can understand each other!
You and I are friends, after all!
But Daddy's really scary...
It'll be fine!
We can help the princess and your dad see eye to eye.
Yeah...
Girls!
Charles!
I lost track of Mana!
Don't worry, Mana must be nearby.
Let us search together!
But there's one problem...
There aren't any more footholds.
I can handle that!
Precure Diamond Shower!
That light was from the Diamond Shower!
They all must have come for us!
Hey!
Girls!
Geez!
You don't need to shout for me to take you along.
Huh?
Huh?!
Why?
I can't use my power...
Mana!
Girls!
Regina, everyone did come!
So, if you go...
It'd be weird if I went with you...
I broke our promise and was mean to everyone...
Then let's apologize.
I'll apologize with you however many times it takes for them to forgive you!
But why you?
Because we're all friends!
You and everyone else!
So,
until everyone understands you, we'll apologize together!
That's dumb!
Huh?
I've never met anyone as dumb as you!
But I'm even dumber for betraying you!
Dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb!
Regina...
Mana!
Charles!
Girls!
Thank goodness you two are safe!
Honestly, I can't let myself trust you.
But Mana would be sad if you weren't around...
Thanks! I knew for a fact you'd all come!
And then I saw the light from that Diamond Shower...
The legend of the miraculous light truly did happen!
And that's not the only miracle!
Ann!
Princess!
It really is the princess!
We found her!
Indeed!
Princess!
Ann!
Go away!
This mountain is mine!
A Selfish!
Huh?
Get 'em, Selfish.
Get rid of anyone in your path to the peak!
I'll be the first to climb it!
Love Heart Arrow!
First...
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
to the top!
Selfish!
Let's go, Charles!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Regina, stand back!
First...
Precure Sparkle Sword!
to the top!
Now, Cure Heart!
Right! Let's go, girls!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Love love loooove!
Huh?
What was I...
We'll be taking the princess.
Princess!
Ann!
Regina!
Mana...
Let's go.
Your father is waiting.
Regina!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
The princess was taken away!
They must be taking her to King Selfish!
Oh no! We have to follow them!
But we have no way to reach Trump Kingdom!
What do we do?!
Dokidoki Precure:
To Trump Kingdom!
Save the Princess!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
A new Precure will appear very soon!
Stay tuned!
Watch Us Again!