Good morning.
Hey, good morning.
It's been a while.
You're tanned...
You've been to the ocean!
Yuuko-chan!
Yuuko-chan, good morning!
Run, Tooru, good morning.
Good morning.
School has started.
Yeah, it sucks that summer break is over.
But it was really fun.
You're right about that.
Hey, it's Nagi.
Good morning, Nagi-chan.
Shh!
What are you up to?
We're going to be late.
Good morning!
Good morning, Kitou-sensei!
What's up? A new term is about to start and you're clearly lacking energy!
One more time!
This is our chance.
Good morning!
Good morning.
This isn't all you've got.
Have another go!
Good morning!
Forgive me, Yuuko.
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
New Term
You're way too uptight on the first day of the new term.
The students aren't going to appreciate that.
It's not like I have to be on good terms with them.
And besides, guiding them is important.
But everything should be done in moderation.
You also have to leave them alone sometimes.
Right?
Satou. Morning.
I think it's best to be left alone. Just like Kamade-sensei would do.
Being left alone when it really matters.
Woah, I'm shivering.
That's right, completely ignore my entire existence!
Stop announcing creepy stuff!
You're making me uncomfortable.
If she could just leave him alone.
How unnerving!
Kitou-sensei, your yelling is giving me a headache. Could you please stop that?
Then how about you go back to your infirmary?
How about you go back to your classroom and your beloved students? Hurry!
I don't like your tone!
What do they say about teasing and affection?
Hey, you two, how about you just go steady?
That's not even funny, knowing it's a joke.
They're in sync, too.
That was a bit too much enthusiasm for the morning.
You think so?
Good morning, Run-chan.
Good morning. It's been a while.
Good morning!
Hey, you're tanned! Where have you been?
She's surrounded by boys again!
I see. That's nice.
There she is: Run-chan's favourite freshman.
Giving it her all from day one.
Despite her height.
Tooru?
You're tall!
We're sorry.
You're all so mean for leaving me behind.
Well, I'm sorry, Yuuko.
That was really difficult to deal with.
Why are you holding a chair?
Who knows?
Good morning!
Yeah, that's it!
It was in this morning's newspaper.
Tooru and Mipo-rin are having a friendly conversation!
Let me in on this!
Japan's politics and economics are...
Shouldn't deregulation come first?
What's up with you? Yutaka?
Japan's politics and economics, deregulation...
It's too complicated, and it completely goes over my head.
By the way, did you see the drama last night?
I did! Hot-Blooded School Drama.
The actor who played the teacher was really fired up.
But that's the point.
Tooru, Mipo-rin!
Good morning!
Hey, you're too close, Yutaka!
Sit down, please.
Good morning!
From today on, it's the second term!
Let's all liven up a bit!
Good morning!
She's fired up.
Start your warm-ups.
Don't leave them out, or else you're gonna hurt yourself.
That's the half-heartedness I like!
Hey, Tooru-san.
What is it?
Continuing from earlier...
Tooru!
Now it's my turn!
Knock it off.
There you go again.
Summer break was long! I missed you!
You met her on the school day, right?
I don't remember a thing.
I see.
Is she...
So, your three minutes are over.
Get away from her this instant.
Eh? Already?
Yutaka!
Yes!
The three minute rule.
It's an agreement as your fans.
Hey, you mentioned something about being a fan earlier.
Did I do something?
You're good at everything, but you're not a jerk about it.
That's right, that's right!
And she's always level-headed and so cool!
Right?
But I'm sure you hear that every day.
Huh? Tooru-san?
Where'd she go?
What's up?
Nothing at all.
Tooru!
Tooru-san, do you have a minute?
I have a favour to ask of you.
Sure, Kitou-sensei.
Tooru.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm going to borrow her for a minute.
I want you to carry some notebooks.
Sure.
It's not fair.
What is?
Even if she's a teacher, I'm going to have her stick to the three minute rule!
Hey!
Please do that for me now.
Sure.
That's it!
That's three minutes!
Any more and...
Just go, Tooru-san.
Three minutes!
There you go.
I got it.
Oh, I forgot.
Could you take this, as well?
Erm, yes.
While you're at it, get me some coffee from the vending machine.
Kamade-sensei, don't make students run your errands!
You're one to talk, Kitou.
Then will you go for me?
Just go yourself!
You, excuse me for a sec.
Whose notebook is this?
K's Poems ♥
Black coffee is fine, right?
Thanks a lot.
Tooru's taking her time.
I'm lonely.
She'll be right back.
There.
What is it?
It's the upperclassmen who hang around with Tooru a lot.
You're right!
The girl with the blonde hair is cute.
Yeah.
The girl with the glasses looks like a prodigy.
Who's the one that looks like a model?
She's the broom girl, right?
Is there a fire?
You're wrong. She's the mop girl.
What's up? Are you sick?
I know a way to stop it!
I think you hit the centre of the back really hard.
That's for hiccups.
That's wrong.
Who are you?
It's a hit to the stomach.
Tooru!
Don't surprise me like that.
It's Tooru-san.
I wonder what they're talking about.
They're really close.
You're right.
I'll help you.
Thanks.
There.
And I'll take these.
You don't have to carry everything for me.
You carried them up until now, so it's even.
She's blushing.
Charming.
Indeed.
Huh?
That girl started talking to some boys.
Eh? Tooru disappeared.
Ah, there she is.
She's got a bat... Are they playing baseball?
Got that covered.
I'm off.
Good morning!
Good morning, Kitou-sensei.
She caught me again.
You're out of luck.
For real.
By the way, Tooru isn't coming today.
She on day duty again?
We're fighting right now, so...
What?
Really?
Are you okay?
It happens once in a while.
They're fighting! What can we do, Nagi?
Why are you getting upset over this?
Calm down!
But a fight... It's just unbelievable!
That's why I'm telling you to calm down!
Anyway, let's ask her what the reason is.
So, why are you fighting?
You see...
It's late. I'll walk you there.
I'm fine.
But lately, it seems like perverts are prowling the streets!
Then you're going to be in danger once you've dropped me off and have to go home alone.
It's fine.
It's dangerous for you, and I'm just fine.
Why do you say you're fine?
You too. How can you say you're fine?
It's in the neighbourhood, so it's okay.
Then it is for me, too!
And for me too!
And like that, we started to yell at each other.
So how did it go after that?
She slept over.
While you were fighting?
Yeah.
Can you even call that fighting?
Run and Tooru fighting...
I wonder if Tooru is feeling sad?
Tooru.
Run-chan is so stupid.
She's drinking her problems away.
I can't just approach her like that.
Did she notice me?
Perfect score...
Then I'll get it for you next time.
Thanks.
A fight, huh?
Tooru seems to be feeling down, but Run is just her usual self.
It's rare for you to read a novel.
Really?
What are you reading?
Run.
You're holding it upside down.
Starting with the equation y = ax² + bx + c...
If you set ax² + bx + c = 0, then...
If casualties happen to result from an accident or disaster...
...then the people directly involved in the incident...
This is long.
Just read it for yourselves.
What are we going to do?
Aren't you worried at all?
I am worried, but I have no idea what to do, either.
It hurts to look at it like this.
Sure does.
Ah, what can we do?
It's troubling me.
If something is troubling you, then tell me!
Kitou-sensei!
There! Tell me whatever is troubling you!
No, there's really nothing bothering me.
Wait!
Keeping your sorrow to yourself is the worst thing to do!
Now, open up your heart to me!
I'm telling you, I'm not keeping any sorrow to myself.
Don't hide it!
Just say it to my face!
Now, now, now!
What are you embarrassed about?
It's fine!
I won't make things worse!
I have no worries!
Wait up, Yuuko-san!
Don't hold back and open up your heart to me!
She's really unlucky...
Run-chan.
Tooru is looking down. I have to cheer her up!
What is it, Mipo-rin?
We're leaving, Yutaka.
Tooru-san isn't in the mood for that right now.
But...
We're going now.
Mipo-rin, you're strangling me!
I shook her off.
Tooru.
It's bothering me. I'm going to make up with her!
I'm going to the convenience store!
Why are we going to the convenience store in this situation?
I need snacks to make up with her.
You're gonna buy her forgiveness?
I'll take these.
That'll be 200 yen.
Should I pay?
kumo ga doko ka ni fuwari tonde iku
雲がどこかにふわり飛んでいく
The clouds gently fly away
sore wo koko de tada miageteta
and I just looked at them from here.
She beat me to it!
Where are you going now?
sora wo tobereba kimi to dokomademo
If I could fly, we could go anywhere together.
Does this mean something?
I'm sorry
ikeru ne nani ga matteru no ka na
行けるね　何が待ってるのかな
I wonder what awaits us.
itsu datte taisetsu na mono wa
What's important to you,
Tooru!
nakushite kara kizuku kara
無くしてから　気づくから
you only realise after it's gone.
sunao ni narereba tsutawaru deshou
素直になれれば　伝わるでしょう
If I could be honest, you'd understand.
ame agari ni kakaru niji no shita futari
雨上がりに架かる虹の下二人
The two of us under the rainbow after the rain,
waraeteru kana ima wa kimi to kono michi wo
笑えてるかな　今は君とこの道を
would we be laughing? Right now, with you on this path
zutto zutto aruite yukou
ずっとずっと歩いてゆこう
I want to keep walking forever and ever.
Ah, Tooru looked sad.
I'm worried about her.
Right...
But she's fine by now, don't you think?
Case solved, I guess.
It sure strained my heart.
I don't have a handkerchief with me.
What's up Nagi, are you touched?
How can you not be touched by this?!
Kitou-sensei, when...
Well then... Let's go home, Yutaka.
Yeah.
You think Tooru is going to be in high spirits tomorrow?
Most likely.
Then I'm going to fool around with her again.
For three minutes.
Eh?
I'll leave then.
See you.
Good work.
Drink it
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
When summer is over, autumn comes in full force.
Too fast.
It's way too fast. Don't you think so, Mipo-rin?!
Is it really?
It's Halloween already?
I won't forgive something like that.
Even if you say that to me...
Some of the important things haven't happened yet!
For example, Tooru and I going moon gazing, or going to the sports carnival.
There's no way that only the two of you are going.
Next time on A Channel, Present.
Next Time!
Present
Obviously, I'll be coming along as well, right?
Mipo-rin is scary...