Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
PERFECT WEATHER
FOR athletics festivalS
On this day...
...the sunniest day in autumn...
...athletics festivals are being held all over the country.
FATHERS AND BROTHERS
ENJOYING athletics festivals
Man...
I came to cheer for my daughter...
...but I didn't expect such a turnout.
This was worth the trip.
FATHERS AND BROTHERS
ENJOYING athletics festivals
I got some great pictures.
Look.
Isn't this a great shot?
Dad.
If you put it like this...
Which daughter are you talking about?
Don't Need Me to
Have a Blast
Maybe I should cut my hair for the athletics festival.
Go for a really short look.
You're going to cut your hair?
But it took forever to grow it so long.
I wasn't that serious about it...
That profound response...
...must have something to do with a guy!
Stop connecting everything to that subject!
And you stop talking so much!
But if Kagami cut her hair...
That's what I heard...
...but it's not unusual, right?
Ya can't!
Tsundere girls hafta have twintails.
Sorry I have a boring face!
Oh, yeah. The athletics festival's coming up.
Sounds like a pain.
Wouldn't expect to hear that from a young person.
Kona-chan's good at sports, so she's okay...
...but someone like me...
...just drags everyone down.
Don't worry.
What event are you doing, Onee-chan?
Well, it's Kagami, so you know...
A bread eating contest.
I've been wondering...
Are you trying to pick a fight or something?
So what are you going to do, Kagami?
I guessed right?
Did I guess right?
She pisses me off!
So I plan on doing some independent training for the athletics festival.
Since fall is for sports.
But are you really training for the athletics festival?
Aren't you actually training for the main event afterwards?
What do you mean?
You want me to say it?
She really pisses me off!
So Miyuki's participating in the inter-class relay.
Well, I can understand that one.
She was originally supposed to be in the obstacle course.
Obstacle Course
Matsuo
Shiraishi
Yamata
Izumi
Takara
Okay.
No more candidates, right?
I've never tried it, so I can't wait.
That's no good, Miyuki-san!
Your body sticks out too much for an obstacle course.
Like Here
And here
You'd have to go through stuff.
Like Here
And here
After I said that, she was switched to the relay.
Isn't that something a middle-aged guy would say?
Oh, yeah.
Did you guys ever have a scavenger race in middle school?
Sure did.
I was called up once... Me?
For what?
...but he never told me what the criteria were.
Too many unspeakable things come to mind.
Well, just ask Miyuki-san when you don't know the answer.
Don't ask her something like that.
It's impossible to answer.
And she really went and asked...
A character trait that would come up in a scavenger race...
...that people wouldn't want to tell you about?
Perhaps he needed a person with a mole on her face.
Some people are sensitive about that.
I guess it was expected...
...but that was one masterful dodge.
But I'm pretty sure she's wrong.
I enjoy athletics festivals...
...but we have tests right after.
Once the festival's over...
...there aren't any more events, which is kind of sad.
Midterms.
Practical exams.
Finals.
All we have is tests.
The second semester is a drain on your energy with events like the cultural festival and the athletics festival, right?
Right?
Midterms are particularly rough.
They also say that fall is for reading...
...so maybe I should read something.
It's also a good season to study for tests.
And there's a whirlwind of new game releases before Christmas!
But finals come first.
Oh, yeah!
You two.
Could you stop trying to avoid reality?
I see.
The athletics festival's coming up, huh?
You know about the starter's pistol?
I thought it was a real gun until middle school.
No way...
That was when I knew I wanted to be a cop.
That misunderstanding led to something totally unrelated.
That's right, Konata.
When's the athletics festival at your school?
This Sunday.
Th-This Sunday!?
Why didn't you tell me such an important thing earlier?
But we just got the notice today.
There's no time to waste!
Why's he in such a hurry?
Okay!
Today's the big day!
Show me the fruits of your training!
Sensei!
I'm the type who does well without ever training!
Don't say that out loud!
Anyway, you better show some backbone in the team chicken fight!
The fundamental strategy is to rush in from all sides and whack 'em good!
So attack from their weak side, right?
But we only need to take their hat...
Hitting people's kinda...
Don't sweat the small stuff.
That's one of the mistakes of youth.
So we're just boys.
Onee-chan!
Do your best!
Good luck!
Hey.
How is that anpan attached to the string?
It's probably attached to a clip or something.
So you can't take it off very easily.
Bring us victory!
Girls must be elegant!
Like an eating contest could ever be elegant!
Ready!
She did it!
That's Kagamin for you.
That person has an incredible camera.
Man, he's so easy to understand.
Hey.
Aren't you in the 100 meter dash next?
Technically.
How can I learn to run fast like you?
It's important to visualize.
Visualize.
Ready!
Set!
That's one ancient visualization.
Goal!
Like that?
Are you serious?
3 meters and 25 centimeters.
So they measure from where your hands reached.
This is it!
That's Kagami.
Dived straight into the sand, huh?
One, two, three.
I've heard that timing your steps is important for hurdles.
Steps?
One.
Two.
Three.
I get it!
One, two, three.
Set!
One...
Um...
Three, two, three!
One, three, huh?
Um...
I started with my right foot, so...
I don't get it!
That was my left foot, so...
Three, three, three.
Three, two, three...
She's knocking every single one down.
You could say she's got talent.
Geez Louise.
I totally sucked.
Man...
I told you.
I thought my daughter was in this.
A common occurrence.
It's finally time for the last relay.
Yuki-chan!
Do your best!
No...
I told you that my daughter's...
Hold on a second!
I'll do my best!
I haven't even done anything yet!
Okay!
Go for it!
Pedal to the metal!
Awesome!
We're in second!
Not bad.
Sachi, over here!
Okay!
We've fallen to third.
This is what you call a race.
Keep at it!
Okay!
They're working pretty hard.
This is getting interesting.
Will Yuki-chan be okay?
Okay.
Okay!
Go, Miyuki!
Yay!
Yuki-chan's so cool!
That's our Miyuki-san.
Don't forget to give the spectators some eye candy.
It's Tsukasa.
Oh, well.
Happy Henry Likes Beer But Could Not Obtain Food.
Hey!
Can you do something about that?
Sorry.
I chose to play the alto part in a quartet for music class...
...but my fingers are getting numb.
Why did you choose the alto part?
I-I thought the lower part might be easier.
Why don't you condition your fingers on an easy song for now?
You missed most of the notes.
So try to match me.
Ready and...
H-Hold on!
Play by yourself.
Somehow seems wrong...
Try blowing a little softer.
If you relax, it might go a lot better.
I see.
Softer...
That's it.
I'll give it a try.
Isn't she doing more breathing than playing?
I was thinking we should try the cafeteria occasionally...
...but it sure is crowded.
It's pretty overwhelming.
And waiting in line is annoying and exhausting.
Sure sucks.
Haven't you gotten used to this kind of thing from those events?
When I'm not eagerly anticipating what awaits me at the end of the line, it sucks.
True to your desires, huh?
That's right.
I went to a theme park once...
...and thought that I had lined up for an attraction...
...but the line was for the restroom.
It's a fundamental rule to check what the line is for first.
And I waited two whole hours...
I've also gotten in line a few times...
...and when it was finally my turn...
Cream Puffs
Sold Out
...the person before me had bought the last one.
Terrible...
Don't even wanna picture it.
You're just unlucky.
Look, everyone.
What shall we have today?
Deep-fried
Tempura
Fox
Miso Ramen
Soy Sauce Ramen
Curry
Daily Special B Meal
Daily Special A Meal
Eggs
Soba
Udon
S M L
Well, I guess I'll go with curry.
They can't screw it up.
I'll go with ramen.
Me too.
I was planning on having miso ramen today.
With lots of corn...
...and seaweed, too!
Kagami's probably having ramen, pudding, and an éclair.
If I have enough room to eat more.
You always have more room.
What about you, Yuki-chan?
I'll have a sandwich,
with strawberries.
Sounds like something you would have.
Right?
By the way...
Isn't a strawberry sandwich considered a dessert?
Would it count as lunch?
Th-That's true...
You pick some odd issues to be concerned about.
What about those chocolate cornets you always have?
Wouldn't sweet pastries be considered a dessert?
Stupid Tsukasa has the gall to give me lip...
Anyway, moving on...
Unfortunately, Miyuki-san...
The line for sandwiches is over there.
Typical behavior.
Walking is healthy.
Look.
It's your turn, Kona-chan.
Curry please.
With extra sauce.
Okay.
You're pretty shrewd.
I'll take what I can get.
Okay.
Next person?
Soy sauce ramen please.
With hard noodles.
Okay, please wait one moment.
Okay.
Here's your curry.
I'll go get a table.
Countin' on you.
Thanks!
Let's see...
Next person?
Yes.
May I please have miso ramen?
Sorry.
The last person ordered the last of our noodles.
We're out of ramen.
Say.
If you're okay with soy sauce, do you want mine?
I'm okay with fox udon.
Thank you, Onee-chan.
Hey, Onee-chan.
You're the older sister because you came out first, right?
Yeah.
I was thinking that it's a good thing I'm the younger sister.
Why?
Because it would be so pathetic if an older sister had to ask a younger sister for her help with homework and stuff.
I'm pretty sure that copying homework has nothing to do with that.
Besides, we're twins.
Neither of us is really older or younger.
Stop worrying...
...and do your homework.
But if I were the older sister...
...and all dependable and responsible...
Onee-chan!
Show me your homework!
Again?
You're so hopeless, Kagami.
That was wack!
Hey. You okay there?
Get a grip.
I did it!
Newtype...
...published my...
...very own...
...postcard!
In the May issue...
That one that has Akira-chan standing on Shiraishi.
Saitama province.
Izumi Konata.
Good for you.
Look at it!
Kinda amazed they published this.
A-Amazing!
What a surprise!
This is pretty rare, yeah?
Like, seriously, huh?
Now I have one more thing to look forward to buying!
You don't need to praise me so much!
1,260 yen...
...and 567 yen, huh?
I'll have enough points after one more book.
Then I should just get something...
No.
Then I'd be falling into their trap.
I'm not so easy to fool.
That would be an unplanned purchase for the sake of points.
That's their strategy.
I'm not dumb enough to fall for that trick.
Oh!
I forgot that the fifth volume was out.
Okay!
Your total comes to 2,587 yen.
Oh, well.
Extra, yeah...
I'm sorry. I can't get it loose.
I don't want to let go.
I thought that only ever happened in manga or games...
...but it actually happens in real life.
Guess so.
Which means...
Those two definitely triggered a flag.
Konata...
Fantasy refers to the world of illusion.
Can't tell the difference between dreams and reality?
Good lucky!
I come with a dreamer's heart to spread love again!
I'm Lucky Channel's navigator, Kogami Akira!
And I'm the assistant.
Shiraishi Minoru.
We've already reached the eighth episode of this program.
That's true.
If we don't come up with some fresh material...
...we'll be accused of abusing mannerisms.
What was that?
What am I doing!?
No.
I just wanted to try some new things...
You said it.
You know...
Do it.
That's right!
I was walking around town the other day...
...and someone came up to talk to me.
Was it some salon doing a survey?
Geez, Shiraishi-san.
Do you actually mean that?
Of course, it was a fan.
This would never happen to you...
Right!?
I-I-I-I-It wouldn't!
That's true...
Right!?
You're the assistant...
Well, keep workin' hard.
B-But...
I've already received this many...
A oopsie-daisy.
...fan letters.
H-How!?
Hey, Itou!
Haven't I gotten any!?
Incredible. I feel like a real voice actor.
So I did get some.
Only one?
Your membership has almost expired...
Hey!
This is that stupid online service!
Everybody who's watching!
Please send me fan letters, too!
Big, big, big recruitment drive!
Akira-sama.
Shouldn't we get to today's topic...
Don't get too cocky.
You're easily replaceable.
I'm so sorry.
Ta-da!
I have an announcement to make!
Wow!
We'll be creating figures on this program!
Akira-sama!
The clipboard!
The clipboard's upside-down!
Oh, you're doing it on purpose!
You're a genius, Akira-sama!
Actually...
...this project is...
Peel.
P-Peel. Peel.
Don't touch me.
Peel. Peel. Peel.
Huh?
That's weird.
This project is...
Don't touch me.
This is...
Peel.
What's wrong with this thing!?
H-H-Hey, Seishi!
A-Akira-sama, calm down!
I got it, okay!
That's the name of your manager in real life!
This is my prop!
Could you have...
Of course not!
Okay!
Then we'll decide which figure to make based on your votes!
Have fun waiting for us to turn the character into a figure!
Everyone, please vote!
Okay.
That's all for today.
Look forward to next week's Lucky Channel!
Bye-bee!
A character from the actual show's obviously gonna win the poll.
What's with this?
Like I have a chance in hell.
No, you can't be sure yet.
I see.
They're finally going to make a figure of me.
What are you talking about?
This is...
That was great, Yuki-chan!
Thank you for listening.
I never expected this side of you.
Please...
It's embarrassing.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
Let's sing a song together.
Let's do that.
Sing! Sing!
A duet, huh?
Which song do you know?
Let's see...
Then I'll sing a song while we're waiting.
There's never gonna be a break, huh!?
You should also sing!
What is this?
Journey to the West.
Machaaki's Son Goku was great.
Huh?
Wasn't it Shingo-chan?
That was the third remake.
This one ran from 1978 to 1980.
The original series!
How old are you!?
This is a long intro.
This was when the actors delivered the main narration.
Like I would know!
Here it comes!
You're shouting again!?
Born from an egg on a mountain
It's in English. Forget that.
That's it after all this build-up?
Preview
Next time on Lucky Star!
I'm Miyuki.
When describing an enormously large object...
...it is described as being super-dreadnought.
The word dreadnought in this expression...
...was derived from a British ship commissioned in 1906...
...the HMS Dreadnought.
In other words, something super-dreadnought would be larger than a dreadnought-class battleship.
Well, that was the original meaning, but now, it's being used in the former context.
Next episode:
「Just a Feeling」
Just a Feeling.
Look forward to next time!