Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
A-Akira-sama, calm down!
Now, it's time to begin.
Let's go!
Ngaah~
Hurry up and start already!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
PERFECT WEATHER
FOR athletics festivalS
On the brightest day of this fall,
sports festivals are being held all over the nation.
FATHERS AND BROTHERS
ENJOYING athletics festivalS
Well~
I came to cheer on my daughter, but I didn't expect it to be so lively...
I'm really glad I came.
FATHERS AND BROTHERS
ENJOYING athletics festivalS
I got some good pictures.
Isn't this one great?
Daddy, whose daughter are you talking about?
Even without me,
you can have a blast
Maybe I'll cut my hair for the sports festival.
I'll go all out and cut it short or something.
Onee-chan, you're going to cut your hair?
Even though you worked so hard to grow it out?
Eh?
I just thought I'd throw that out there...
That nonchalant response...
It involves a guy!
Why does everything point in that direction?
Tsukasa, you talk too much!
But if Kagami cut her hair...
I heard that changing one's style now and then...
...is normal, right?
No!
Tsundere faces must be complemented by twintails.
I'm sorry my face is boring.
Now that you mention it, the sports festival is coming up soon...
How annoying.
That's not something a youth should say.
Kona-chan, you're good at sports so it's fine for you, but me...
I'll just get in people's way.
Don't worry.
Onee-chan, what are you going to do?
Well knowing Kagami, she would probably do...
The bread-eating contest!
I've always wondered...
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
So what are you going to do, Kagami?
Was I right?
Huh? Was I right?
She's getting on my nerves.
I've been doing some training to prepare myself for the festival.
Since fall is for sports.
But are you really doing it for the festival?
You sure there isn't another reason behind it?
Like what?
Do you want me to say it?
She's really getting on my nerves!
Really~
Miyuki's doing the relay?
Well, I can kind of see that.
She was supposed to do the obstacle race at first, but...
Obstacle Course
Matsuo
Shiraishi
Yamata
Izumi
Takara
All right, no more volunteers?
I've never done it before, so I'm excited.
You can't, Miyuki-san!
Miyuki-san, your body sticks out a lot, so you can't do the obstacles.
Like Here
And here
You have to dodge and evade stuff.
Like Here
And here
I said that, and now she's doing the relay.
That sounds like something an old geezer would say.
Speaking of which, did they have scavenger hunt at your middle school, Kagami?
Yep, we did.
I've been called on before, but...
In the end,
they never explained to me why they called on me for the scavenger hunt.
I can think of so many things...
Well, let's ask Miyuki-san about anything we don't know.
Don't ask stuff like that...
It'll be hard to answer.
You're actually asking?
A sensitive trait about you that they might call on for a scavenger hunt...
...but not tell you about?
Yep.
How about "A person with a mole on their face"?
Some people are really sensitive about stuff like that.
What a way to evade the question!
But I don't think that's it...
I'm excited about the sports festival, but we have tests right after.
After the sports festival, there aren't many more events so it's going to be lonely.
There are just the midterms, standardized tests, and final exams left.
The second semester is really tiring between the culture and sports festivals.
Especially the midterms.
Some call it the "fall of reading", so maybe I'll pick up a book and read or something.
It's a comfortable season to study for tests.
Right before Christmas, all the new games will be coming out!
Even though we have finals afterwards...
Uoh!
Oh, yep, yep.
You guys...
How about you look at reality for once?
I see.
So it's almost time for the sports festival?
You know those guns they use to start the race?
I thought those were real until middle school.
Impossible...
That was one of the reasons I wanted to become a police officer.
Something completely irrelevant leading to that, what an imagination!
Speaking of which, Konata,
when is your school's sports festival?
This upcoming Sunday.
T-This Sunday?
Why didn't you tell me something so important earlier?
Well, I just got this announcement today.
I need to get ready!
What's the rush?
Today's finally the big day!
Let's show 'em what we've been practicing for!
Sensei!
I didn't practice much, but I'm good at winging it!
Don't say that so bluntly!
Anyway, make sure you give your all for the mounted battle.
Surrounding them from all corners and beating them to a pulp is the basic strategy.
Attacking from the angle where they are the weakest, huh?
But all you have to do is take their hat...
I'm not sure about beating...
Don't worry about the little details...
It's something all young'uns do.
So we're little runts, huh?
Onee-chan, do your best.
Go for it!
Hey, how is that anpan stuck to the string?
I'm sure it's clipped on or something.
So you can't get it off that easily?
You must win!
Elegantly as a girl should!
There's no such thing as an "elegant" bread-eating contest!
Ready...
Yes!
As expected from Kagamin.
That person has an amazing camera.
He's so easy to read...
You're doing the 100 meter race next, right?
I guess...
How can I run fast like you, Kona-chan?
What's important for these things is the image.
Huh?
Ready...
Set...
This is a pretty nostalgic "image".
Something like this...
You were serious?
3.25 meters.
Ah, they measure the shortest distance...
Here it is!
I did it!
That's Kagami for you, sticking her head into everything.
One, two, three...
I hear it's good to time the hurdles with the number of steps.
Steps?
One... Two... Three!
I see!
One, two, three...
Set!
One...
Ah!
Um!?
Three, two, three...
One, three...
Huh?
Um, uh... I started on my right foot so...
Eh!
I don't know!
Am I on my left foot now?
Wow, she's knocking them down everywhere.
Just a little more.
I did pretty bad...
I thought my daughter was going to be in it...
I'm sure this happens a lot...
Finally, the last relay.
Yuki-chan, do your best!
My daughter is...
I'll try my best!
Wait a sec...
I haven't done anything yet!
Yes!
She's in second!
Not bad.
Right here!
We're going to become third...
This is a race.
They're trying pretty hard.
It's getting interesting now.
Is Yuki-chan going to be okay?
Whoa!
GO MIYUKI!
Yay!
Yuki-chan, that was so cool!
That's Miyuki-san for you...
Even giving them some fanservice.
That must be Tsukasa.
Oh well.
H, He, Li, Be, B, C, N, O, F, Ne...
Um...
Can you do something about that?
I'm sorry.
I chose the alto recorder for my quartet at school...
...but I'm about to cramp my fingers.
Why did you choose the alto?
I thought the accompaniment would be easier so...
Why don't you try your fingers on something easy?
Okay.
You're missing most of them.
Let's try it together, ready and...
H-Hey...
Play by yourself, Tsukasa.
It just doesn't seem right...
Why don't you relax a little more when you play?
If you loosen up a bit, it might sound better.
I see...
Relax...
Yep, yep.
Okay, I'll try it.
Why does it seem like you're breathing more than actually playing?
I thought we could eat at the cafeteria for a change...
But it gets pretty crowded, huh.
It's so depressing.
Lines are such a hassle and they make you tired...
I don't like them.
Aren't you used to them from your events?
But I don't like lines with nothing to look forward to at the end.
You're so honest about your own greed.
Speaking of which, the last time I went to an amusement park...
I thought I was in the line for an attraction, but it ended up being the toilet.
It's common knowledge to check what the line is for before lining up.
I waited two hours...
Oh, me too...
I've waited in lines before, and when my turn finally came around,
Cream Puffs
Sold Out
they had sold out at the person right before me.
Ah, I don't even want to imagine that.
Tsukasa, you're just unlucky.
Ah, what are you going to get today?
Deep-fried
Tempura
Fox
Miso Ramen
Soy Sauce Ramen
Curry
Daily Special B Meal
Daily Special A Meal
Eggs
Soba
Udon
S M L
I guess I'll just get curry.
You can't go wrong with that.
I'll get ramen.
I was thinking about getting miso ramen today.
With lots of corn and wakame on it.
Kagami, you're getting ramen and pudding, aren't you?
Only if I have room later...
You always have room...
Hmph!
What about you, Yuki-chan?
I'm getting a sandwich...
The strawberry one for now.
Ah, that's so like you, Miyuki-san.
Isn't it?
By the way,
isn't a strawberry sandwich considered dessert?
Does it count as lunch?
I-I guess so...
You're nitpicky about the weirdest things.
Ah!
What about the choco cornet you always eat, Kona-chan?
Isn't that considered a snack?
Tsukasa, how dare you interfere with the punch line...
Well, putting that aside...
Unfortunately for you, Miyuki-san...
The sandwich line is over there.
That's so her.
Well, walking is good for your health, too.
Hey, it's your turn, Kona-chan.
Can I get curry, please?
With some extra roux?
Here you go.
You're pretty straightforward.
You have to take what you can.
Okay, next person.
Can I get a shoyu ramen please?
Make the noodles hard.
Okay, coming right up.
Thanks for waiting.
I'll go get a seat for us.
I'll leave it to you.
Thanks.
Next person.
Oh, yes...
Can I get miso ramen please?
Oh, I'm sorry.
The previous person got the last of our noodles.
So we're sold out of ramen.
Eh!?
You know, if you don't mind shoyu ramen, do you want this?
I'll get a kitsune udon.
Thanks, Onee-chan...
Hey, Onee-chan?
Hm?
They decided who was older by who came out first, right?
I guess so...
I'm glad I'm the little sister.
Why's that?
Because it would be so pathetic if the older sister had to come to her younger sister...
...to ask questions about the homework and other things.
I don't think that has much to do with who's older...
Besides, we're twins, so I don't think being older or younger matters.
Don't worry about it and just finish up your homework.
Okay!
But if I were the older sister...
Maybe I would be smarter like Onee-chan.
Onee-chan, can I see your homework?
Again?
Oh, you're so hopeless, Kagami...
Hey, are you okay?
Whoa, that turned into something outrageous.
Hang in there.
Dun dun...
Newtype...
My postcard...
Is in it!
On May's issue.
Saitama-ken, Izumi Konata...
The one with Shiraishi lying underneath Akira-sama...
Heh, that's cool...
Look, look!
Good job for getting in.
A-Amazing!
I'm so shocked!
Something like this never happens!
Oh, tell me about it!
Now I have one more thing to look forward to.
Don't praise me too much...
1,260 yen and 567 yen...
One more and I'll have all the points I need.
Then, I'll just get something else...
No, that's exactly what they want me to do.
I'm not falling for that one.
Making me buy stuff I don't need because I want the points!
It's their scheme...
I'm not foolish enough to fall for that one.
I forgot that volume 5 is out!
All right, I'm all set now.
That comes to 2,587 yen.
Oh well...
Extra, yeah...
Oh, I'm so sorry.
They won't come apart.
Maybe they don't want to.
I thought that only happens in manga and games.
I guess it actually happens.
Yep.
Which would mean...
Those two must have triggered massive flags right now!
Konata...
A fantasy is defined as an illusion or fanciful thought.
Can you not distinguish between dreams and reality?
Lucky Channel~
Oha-Lucky!
Bringing you love with a dream-colored heart...
Lucky Channel's navigator, Kogami Akira here!
And I'm her assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
I can't believe we're on the eighth episode of this show already.
That's true.
If we don't come up with something new, people will call us out.
What's that?
Now what am I gonna do!?
Um...
It's just that I thought it would be nice...
You said it...
If we tried different things and...
Then, do it.
Ah, that's right!
The other day I was walking through town and someone came up to me.
Was it a survey for a salon?
C'mon Shiraishi-san, are you serious?
Of course it was a fan.
That doesn't happen to you, now does it!?
I-It doesn't...
Of course... NOT!
You're my ASSISTANT.
Well, best of luck to you...
B-But, I've gotten all these fan letters!
W-Why is that!?
Hey, Itou!
Yep, I feel like a celebrity.
Aren't there any for me?
So there is one...
Only one?
"Your membership is about to expire..."
Hey!
This is from the fatty at the video rental store!
Everyone watching the TV right now, please send fan letters to me, too!
I'm co-collecting them right now!
Akira-sama...
I think we should cut to the chase...
Don't get cocky.
There's plenty of people who can replace you.
I'm sorry...
Tada!
We have an announcement!
We're going to have figures of this show now!
Akira-sama, flip it.
The clipboard, it's upside-down!
Right, so you knew about it all along...
You're so good, Akira-sama!
To tell you the truth, the plan this time is...
Don't touch me.
Huh?
That's strange...
Um, the plan this time is...
Don't touch me.
This plan is...
*peel* *peel* *peel*
Hey, what's up with this!?
H-Hey, Seishi!
That's mine, that's mine?
That's the name of your real manager!
It's my prop, you hear!
Why you...
I-I'm terribly sorry!
So, we're going to decide which figure to make based on your votes!
Send us your vote for which character you want to see.
E-Everyone, please send in your votes.
That's it for today.
Look forward to next week's Lucky Channel!
Bai-bii!
A poll like this...
A character from the series is obviously going to win.
What's this?
As if I have the slightest chance.
That hasn't been decided yet.
Ah, so finally I'm going to get my own figure, huh?
What are you talking about?
These things are-
Yuki-chan, you're amazing!
Thank you for taking the time to listen.
I saw a surprising side of Miyuki.
Oh no, you're embarrassing me.
Then, Miyuki-chan, let's sing together.
Yes, let's.
Oh, sing, sing!
A duet?
Which one can you sing?
Let's see...
While they decide, I will...
You're going to sing nonstop?
Kagami, you should keep singing, too!
What's this?
Saiyuki!
Machaaki as Son Goku was so great!
Huh?
Wasn't it Shingo-chan?
That was the third remake.
This was the theme song to the series that aired from 1978 to 1980.
The original series!
How old are you!?
What a long intro...
This is where the narration starts.
How should we know?
Ah, here, here!
Achaaah!
More screaming?
Born from an egg on a mountain
Ah, it was in English?
Nevermind then.
That's it, after dragging it out?
Preview
And next week on Lucky Star:
Miyuki here.
In order to describe something of enormous intensity or size,
we use the term "super-dreadnought".
This term originated from the British battleship that was commissioned in 1906, the "HMS Dreadnought".
In other words, something that was a "super-dreadnought" belonged to a class larger than a dreadnought.
While that was its original meaning,
it is now understood in its present context.
Next time: "That Kind of Feeling"
That Kind of Feeling」
Look forward to it!