Class 3-B, Kurumi Ebisuzawa!
Here she comes!
C'mon, what's wrong with you?
Don't slack off! It's not gonna clean itself!
But the floor's so slippery, Kurumi-chan!
Ya moron, call me Sarge!
Whaa...?!
You're getting way too into this today, Kurumi-chan!
Call me Sarge, dammit!
All right, I'll show you how it's done!
Follow me, Private Takeya!
Yessir...
Put your back into it!
Roger!
C'mon!
Be careful not to slip and fall, you two!
Got it- whaaaa...!
Hey, stop, stop!
Are you alright?
I-I'm okay.
Ow, where the hell were you looking?!
But it's just so slimy!
Jeez, be careful!
Those two sure are energetic.
It's a good thing Yuki-chan had an extra swimsuit.
You look great.
I'm not happy to be dressed like this.
Why did you even bring these back
from the mall in the first place?
You could've brought something you needed instead.
Well...
we are girls, of course.
Still...
CONFIDENTIAL
Faculty Emergency Evacuation
Manual
Only open this manual when:
-  The principal or other official has ordered it
-  An A-1 warning has been issued
-  No outside communication has been received for more than 10 days
We just found out about that yesterday...
Is it alright to be goofing off despite that?
Wow! Taromaru's butt is wiping it clean!
I understand your concern,
but let's avoid thinking about it for now.
Wow! Taromaru's butt is wiping it clean!
I understand your concern,
but let's avoid thinking about it for now.
Alright, you're promoted to Second Class!
I understand your concern,
but let's avoid thinking about it for now.
It's such good weather for a swim, after all.
Umm, this isn't a pool.
It's the water storage tank, isn't it?
School Living Club
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
When you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
Let's do it together! (Yeah!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
You know what you have to do after school
Come on, now, get together!
Don't sneak off to go home! (Hey!)
How about club? Let's get something done!
Don't go playing around!
That girl says "I'm back" (Welcome back!)
We'll be fine as long as we're together (Club!)
Everybody say: let's all be friends
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
when you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
I love you so much! (Yeah!)
We are enjoying our lives
We're having fun 24 hours a day
The red sun shines bright on the roof
I tried shouting out to it (We're doing great!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
Vacation Day
That morning
CONFIDENTIAL
Faculty Emergency Evacuation
Manual
Only open this manual when:
-  The principal or other official has ordered it
-  An A-1 warning has been issued
-  No outside communication has been received for more than 10 days
Did you get any sleep?
How am I supposed to sleep after that?
Yeah, I understand.
Hey, that key had Megu-nee's name on it, right?
Yes.
So that means Megu-nee knew about
everything from the beginning.
She knew what was happening and hid it from us.
Is that what you're trying to say?
I-I dunno.
I really don't know.
I think that probably wasn't the case.
The front says not to open it
except in certain times, right?
They might've been given it a long time ago,
so even if she read it then...
...It might not make a difference
after it all happened, huh.
God dammit! Is it a virus or
a biological weapon or what?!
I'm going crazy just trying to figure it out!
There are a lot of interesting things written in it.
Emergency evacuation areas?
There are two more floors underground.
If you didn't know that, that means
you haven't gone down there yet, right?
That's right.
I wonder what's down there.
Hey, everyone, let's do some cleaning!
O-oh, Yuki-chan, I thought you were
taking Taromaru on a walk.
What's this about cleaning all of a sudden?
Just look!
I let Taromaru off his leash on the roof,
and he jumped right into the pond!
Again? Are you kidding me?
Yuki-chan...
Let's all graduate!
Everyone write 100 pages!
I can't write that many!
Please, Senpai, can you be a little more careful?
Sorry.
It's soooo dirty in there!
There are fish living in there!
I feel so bad for them!
I see. Well, it's warm out today,
so why don't we get wet and
clean out the water tank?
We're just gonna end up playing in it, you know.
Yeah, huh! That would be fun!
Yuki-senpai!
Don't tell me you got Taromaru dirty on purpose
so you could go play in the water!
O-of course not! Taromaru just looked like
he was enjoying the water so much!
You felt like playing in the water too, huh?
Just a little! Just a tiny little bit!
Senpai, we don't have time to be-
Good idea, Yuki-chan.
What?!
Alright. Let's go clean out the water storage tank.
Really, Ri-san?
Yup. We did just buy those bathing suits.
Yay!
Isn't that great, Taromaru?
You should get clean first!
Roger that!
Are you sure about this?
I think we need some time to get our thoughts sorted.
We've got a lot to think about,
between Megu-nee and our future.
Kurumi-chan, that's weird, you're the kind of girl
who looks thinner with clothes on, huh?
Don't say that's weird.
Y..Yuri-senpai.
Hm? What is it?
N-no, it's nothing.
Wow! The sky's so blue!
Yes, what great weather.
Yeah, huh.
Ewww!
Nobody's been taking care of it,
so algae just grew and grew.
It looks like there's a lot of sand and silt in it, too.
Wow...
Jeez, this is awful.
What is this pond here for, anyway?
It's called a biotope.
A freshwater ecosystem was placed
in this water collection tank.
They often use it in biology classes.
Huh!
Hey, what kind of fish are in there?
Rainbow trout and carp, I think.
Alright, let's get the fish into the buckets
and start cleaning.
Alright!
Pool's open for business!
I don't think it's a pool...
It's not like a real pool.
The bottom is bare concrete, so you shouldn't-
...jump in.
First! I win!
Hey, no fair, Kurumi-chan!
Like I said, you shouldn't jump-
I'm drow... I'm drowning!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Oh, you're right! My feet touch the floor!
That's weird, it doesn't smell like the pool.
You moron, the pool smells like the chlorine
they put in to keep it clean.
Oh, really?
Will the fish be okay with chlorine in the water?
People don't put fish in pools.
But it'd kinda be cool if there were fish in pools!
You want to swim with them?
I'd swim with them, and if I got hungry...
You'd eat them alive?!
Grumble...
Mmmm.
I've got you now! Take this!
Hey! It's so cold!
Now that I'm taking another look at it,
it's pretty big, huh.
Look at his belly.
Hey, Ri-san, what're those?
Oh, those are solar panels.
What're solar panels?
They make electricity from the sun.
They let us have a normal life here.
For now, at least.
We have a water purifier too, right?
There are machines that filter
river water and ground water, too.
You sure know a lot about them.
The Gardening Club took place on the roof, after all.
Megurigaoka High is its own town,
and the students are its citizens.
These citizens can carry out various jobs
that help make the town self-sufficient.
You read that in the school information book, right?
I read it so many times I ended up memorizing it.
Though there are only four of us citizens...
I wonder how many people they imagined
this school supporting.
Everything just seems so perfect.
Almost like...
Almost like they expected this
to happen from the beginning.
Let's leave the conversation here for now.
We said we were gonna have fun today, right?
Right.
You're right.
Wow!
Taromaru, you look so cool!
What are you doing?
Ooh, it's cold.
Miki, here it comes!
Huh?
There!
Nice volley!
That's a toss-up! This is a volley!
Alright then, watch this!
Hey!
Don't hit it too hard!
I'm gonna go for the spike!
And then just toss it up.
You don't need to fake us out!
Here!
Whoa...
there!
Hey, that's way off!
I'll get it!
Nice one, Kohai!
I've gotta take it seriously, Senpai!
Okay, let's go!
Here!
Got it!
That feels so good!
Yuri-senpai,
here it comes!
I got, it!
Hup!
Sorry!
Jeez, Yuki-senpai!
Just as I thought, nothing.
Taromaru?
Ri-san?
What is it? Is everything alright?
Ri-san, look!
Oh, now that I think about it, we did have those.
Water guns, huh.
What're those doing in a place like this?
Someone brought them here before.
Do you want to play?
Hey, can you tell me one last thing?
What is it?
You're a pretty skilled gunman.
You've got a nickname, don't you?
Do I, now?
Why's it gotten all serious?
And here you were, going on about
how it was someone else's toys!
I bet they're yours!
That's correct.
I'll let you in on two things you ought to know.
Number 1: You did an excellent job firing rapidly,
but exactly how many shots are
left in those guns, I wonder?
Number 2: I do have a nickname.
They call me the Water Balloon Witch.
What?!
How naïve!
Take this!
No! She bounced the water balloons away?!
Oh no!
And now, our final battle!
Just what I wanted!
Ri-san!
Kurumi-chan!
It ain't over yet!
Senpai, you're getting too carried away!
Sorry.
I just got so into it...
You were so cool, Ri-san!
I wanna be a witch, too!
How do you become a witch?
Let's see, first you have to
contract with a demon, I guess.
Okay, go fetch!
I'm not gonna let you beat me!
Huh?
Wait up!
Yuri-senpai, is that...
Oh yes, it's your CD player, Miki-san.
I'm sorry.
I took it because I wanted to
try out the radio function.
It's alright. Did you pick up anything?
I thought we'd get better reception on the roof, but no.
Taromaru?
Just as I thought...
It's not picking up any stations.
Hey, Kei?
Kei?
You'll hurt your ears if you keep
blasting that noise on your headphones.
You don't have to worry about me.
Just use the speakers.
But...
It's fine.
What're you laughing about?
Look at him.
Do you smell Kei?
I think he wants you to play with him.
Okay!
Wait up!
The wind's getting cold, huh.
Oh, thanks.
Alright, you two, shall we wrap it up?
Okay!
It's pretty clean now!
Now Taromaru can jump in
and it won't be a problem!
Please don't let him jump in!
That hits the spot!
You sound just like an old man, Kurumi-chan.
Hey, it's good!
I wanna take a bath.
Yeah, but it's school, so we've only got showers.
I think the sports clubs had a bath
they could use in the club building.
It'd be a bit of a hassle getting
all the way out there just for a bath.
Did you have fun today?
I had a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun, but...
Mii-kun, what's wrong?
Something on your mind?
It's not that, it's just...
If you're worried about something,
you can just ask us to help!
We're your senpai, after all!
I don't know how comfortable I'd feel
relying on your help, Yuki-senpai.
I-I'd be a big help! So let me help you!
Man, that hurts. You're so rude, Mii-kun!
You need to cake responsibility
and respect your senpai!
Don't you mean "take"?
Take
Ah!
Fine then. You be the senpai then, Mii-kun.
Sorry, that was too much!
Oh jeez, don't sulk, Yuki-senpai.
You won't say mean things anymore?
I won't.
You'll ask me for advice?
Fine.
There's this friend.
A friend?
She was my classmate. We got along real well.
She was really energetic and positive.
And we were always together,
but lately I haven't seen her.
She's not coming to school?
Maybe, I think.
Then you should have more fun!
I should?
Do you hate school, Mii-kun?
No.
Right? I love school, too!
'Cause you're here, and Ri-san's here,
and Kurumi-chan's here, and Megu-nee's here,
I love this school!
Oh, and Taromaru's here, too.
If we have lots of fun, school will be lots of fun, too!
And then...
And then?
I'm sure your friend will come to school!
So don't look so sad, okay?
I agree.
I guess so.
Hey, what're you talking about?
We were talking about how much fun we had today!
Yeah, it was.
I hope tomorrow, and the day after,
and all the days to come are all this fun.
Okay, let's swim in the pool tomorrow!
You really are so immature, Senpai.
Huh-whaa...?!
Let's go underground tomorrow.
Oh, you want to try finding that evacuation area?
I hope there's good stuff down there.
Underground?
I'll tell you later.
I feel like just going to bed right now.
My, don't you want dinner?
Dinner!
That's right, we still have dinner.
We're all pretty tired, so why don't we
make something simple?
We had some Yamatoni canned beef left, right?
Ooh, I wanna have that!
Sure, we have lots left.
We've got some canned mackerel
and canned salmon, too.
Canned grilled chicken could be good, too.
You're so fancy, Mii-kun!
Talking on our way home
Telling each other our secrets
Even when the 5-o'clock chime rings out
I wonder why I feel we still haven't talked enough
A tiny four-leaf clover
Sways in the gentle breeze
Hey, I'm sure that yes, I'm sure
I hope tomorrow will be sunny, too
We walked the road together
Always saying we'd meet at the usual place
Ah, the fluffy clouds above
Seem like they'll be burned, they're shining so bright
Even if, one day, these days
Are but a faded memory
I want to give you
A lot of smiles right now
Next Time!
So you're a witch, Ri-san!
That's what they call me.
Aw man, I want a nickname, too!
Alright, then. How about the "Demon-Witch of Trouble"?
The Demon-Witch
of Trouble
(by Yuri)
"Demon-Witch of Trouble"?
A Rainy Day
Next time on School-Live, episode 10:
"A Rainy Day"