I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
I am of the Rider class in this Grail War.
What the hell are you thinking, you idiot?!
Fate has brought us together to fight for the Grail.
But first, there's something I'd like to ask.
How about...
...yielding the Grail to me and joining my army?
I will treat you both as my friends,
and we shall share in the joy of world conquest together!
I'm afraid I'll have to decline.
I will give the Grail to only one man: my new avowed lord.
Not to you, Rider!
So you disturbed our battle merely to propose that ridiculous plan?
As a knight, this is an unforgivable insult!
I'd be willing to discuss terms.
Shut up!
Besides...
I myself am a king responsible for Britain's well-being.
No matter how great a king you may be,
I cannot lower myself to the rank of subject.
King of Britain, you say?
What a surprise!
I didn't expect the King of Knights to be a little girl!
Would you like a taste of this little girl's blade, King of Conquerors?!
Looks like negotiations have failed.
What a waste! What a shame!
Rider!
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
And link them on to tomorrow
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Crying and embracing the night
Screaming its grief out loud
The distant ideals gently heal
These legs that've stepped forward
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
No matter where I go
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
That moron nearly once conquered the known world?
You're seriously—
So it was you, of all people.
I was wondering what madness compelled you to steal my relic.
I never imagined that you were planning
on entering the Holy Grail War yourself...
Waver Velvet-kun.
Perhaps I'll have to give you some extra lessons as a special case.
The true meaning of Magi killing one another...
I'll teach you all about the fear and pain involved.
You should feel honored.
Hey, Mage!
It appears that you intended to
be my Master instead of this boy.
Don't make me laugh!
Only a man brave enough to ride into
battle at my side could ever be my Master.
A coward lacking the courage to even show himself is nowhere close to being worthy!
And I'm sure there's more of you watching from the shadows!
What are you talking about, Rider?
Saber and Lancer.
The duel between you two was truly magnificent.
I can't be the only Heroic Spirit who was drawn out here by the clear sound of your blades clashing.
Heroic Spirits summoned through
the Holy Grail, gather here and now!
Those too cowardly to show themselves will
earn the scorn of Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
This is...
Yes.
Not good.
Not good, indeed.
That's...
The Servant that defeated Assassin!
In a single night, two insolent knaves dare to call themselves kings in my presence.
You are mistaken.
I'm Iskandar, the legendary King of Conquerors himself.
Nonsense.
I am the one and only Hero King in this heaven and Earth.
The rest of you are merely a bunch of mongrels.
In that case, why don't you name yourself?
No true king would be ashamed of his own name.
Are you questioning me, mongrel?
Me, the king?!
If you cannot discern my identity even in the presence of my glory,
then your ignorance shall result in your death!
I see. So that's how he killed Assassin.
That's his Noble Phantasm.
Kill him.
Berserker?!
Hey, King of Conquerors.
Aren't you going to invite him?
Invite him?
He doesn't seem terribly interested in negotiating to begin with.
Hey boy, how powerful of a Servant is he?
I can't tell.
I can't tell at all.
What?
You may be a lousy Master, but shouldn't you still be able to sense his strengths and weaknesses?
I can't tell.
That black thing is definitely a Servant,
but I can't read its status or anything else about it!
Looks like it'll be another difficult enemy.
That Heroic Spirit has some curse or special ability that conceals everything about him.
But that's not all.
With four others present, we'll have to be very careful.
Why did he materialize here?
No sane Master would choose to send out his Servant amidst all this chaos.
Maiya, keep watching Assassin.
I'll look for Berserker's Master.
Who gave you permission to gaze upon me, rabid dog?
May your scattered remains entertain me, mongrel.
Is that really Berserker?
He's very versatile for a madman who has lost his ability to think.
What? You couldn't tell?
That black thing easily caught the first sword that flew towards him
and used it to deflect the second spear as it approached.
How dare you lay your filthy hands on my treasures...
You must want to die really badly, dog!
That's ridiculous!
Just how long can your impudent thievery keep you alive?
Show me!
How dare you...
You're making me stand on the same ground as you?
I, who belong among the heavens?!
Your impudence has sealed your eternal doom!
Nothing will remain of your corpse, mongrel!
Gilgamesh is serious.
He intends to open the Gate of Babylon even further.
How rash of him to repeatedly expose his Noble Phantasm for all to see.
Your decision, my master?
By the power of my Command Spell...
Quell thine anger and withdraw, King of Heroes.
You dare to order a king to withdraw?!
You've got some nerve, Tokiomi.
You are fortunate, rabid dog.
Mongrels!
See that you've culled your numbers by our next meeting.
Only a true hero is worthy of looking upon me.
It would appear the Master isn't as stubborn as Archer is.
Irisviel, stand back!
What?
So that's it.
Anything that black thing grabs becomes his Noble Phantasm.
Saber!
Well, Maiya?
Can you see Berserker's Master?
No, I cannot.
This is bad.
Damn it.
Who exactly are you?
That's enough messing around, Berserker.
Saber already has business with me.
I won't just ignore it if you insist on interfering further.
Lancer...
What are you doing, Lancer?
This is your chance to defeat Saber.
I will slay Saber! I, Diarmuid O'Dyna, swear this on my honor!
But please watch as I take care of this rabid dog first.
Please, my lord!
With my Command Spell, I order you...
My lord!
Assist Berserker and...
...kill Saber.
Lancer.
Saber, I'm sorry.
Irisviel, I'll stop them.
Take this chance to run.
As far away as you can.
Irisviel, please!
It'll be fine, Saber.
Believe in your Master!
Kiritsugu is here?
Kiritsugu, I know you can turn this into a victory.
I'll kill Lancer's Master now.
It's the only way out of this.
Maiya, attack Assassin on my mark.
Suppressive fire.
Roger.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
He's quite the tough one.
As you can see, our black friend has retired for the evening.
Lancer's Master.
I don't know where you're watching from, but don't
use petty tricks to spoil a battle between knights!
Withdraw Lancer.
If you insist on humiliating him any further, then I shall assist Saber.
The two of us will annihilate your Servant together.
What will you do?
Withdraw, Lancer.
That's enough for tonight.
My thanks, King of Conquerors.
It was nothing.
I enjoy watching the flowers of a battlefield in bloom.
What exactly was your intent when
you first arrived, King of Conquerors?
No idea. I don't really think about these things.
Saber.
Settle matters with Lancer first.
I shall then face the victor, be that you or Lancer.
Goodbye for now, King of Knights!
I hope to enjoy our next meeting as much as I did this one.
Hey boy, don't you have anything nice to say?
Man, I wish he'd man up a little.
Farewell!
Saber, your left arm!
Yes, it was a serious blunder.
It's just as Rider said.
If I don't deal with Lancer first and undo the curse on this wound,
it will damage my chances against the other Servants.
Thank you, Saber.
I survived thanks to you.
I was able to focus on the battle before
me because you were protecting my back.
Saber.
The battle has just begun, Irisviel.
This was merely the first night of the battle to come.
Indeed.
They were all powerful adversaries.
Not a single one of them can be taken lightly.
So this is the Holy Grail War.
They all turned and ran away from my Berserker.
I also humiliated that arrogant bastard!
Tokiomi, if only I could see your bitter face.
Damn Berserker for going out
of control and attacking Saber...
I won't last much longer at this rate.
But if I can control it, I can win.
Wait for me, Sakura.
Excuse me, Kirei-sama.
What is it?
I've come to report that I found
something of note outside the church.
A familiar?
Yes. It was outside the field, but it was clearly sent to observe this church.
Awesome! That was seriously awesome!
Hey, Mister Bluebeard! That was all real, right?
It was all real and not some kind of special effect, right?
I can't get enough of it!
So, the Grail War, right?
You'll take part in all that too, right?
Mister?
It came true...
It came true?
Uh...
Look at her!
Her very existence is the answer!
Her dignified face, her noble posture...
She is none other than the maiden of my destiny!
You know her?
Indeed!
She was abandoned by God and perished in shame.
But she has been revived at last!
What could a miracle of this scale be
other than the fulfillment of my wishes?!
Oh, my maiden...
My holy virgin...
I will come for you soon.
Episode 5
Howl of a Mad Beast
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
If I can find peace in my recollections
While reminiscing about you
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
Proof of the time I spent with you
Is right here with me
You've shown me what it means
To have overflowing feelings
Even if this world were to end
I'll be right by your side
I swear that I will bring you Saber's head.
The next strike will be for real.
Aren't you the one who's mistaken?
They can enjoy the magical atelier of Kayneth El-Melloi.
You seek to lecture me?
I've come for you, O Holy Virgin.
Next Episode
Night of Stratagems