When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright and
sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
My Future Dream
Hamakaze Elementary School
My future dream.
Grade 1, Peach Class, Hayate Ayasaki.
Regardless of whether it
is a weekday or a Sunday,
my parents are always lying
around, doing nothing at home.
My father works on self-realization
and my mother is intent on capturing
the dream of spinning reels.
My father said, "If we win it big,
we'll take a trip to Hawaii!"
But my mother laughed, "They
won't issue passports to us,
"so we won't be able to do that, hahaha."
So there is never-ending
laughter in my home.
And so, my future dream is...
I wonder if it's because of what I was
told yesterday at the Miss's home.
In other words,
your life is...
...utterly meaningless.
No, pull yourself together! I
made up my mind, didn't I?!
That I don't yet know what
the meaning of my life is,
but that for now, I'm just
going to protect the Miss!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Hello, I'm Hayate Ayasaki!
All right! I'm going to
work hard again today!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Long Ago, We Learned from a Space Sheriff
that Being Young is About Not Looking Back
What? My future dream?
Yes!
Hmm, if I had to say,
I worry ceaselessly about what kind of
adult a certain girl will grow up to be.
So I suppose you could say my dream is
that she becomes a respectable
member of society.
Uh...
But why did you suddenly bring this up?
What? No, well...
How do I put this?
A person's dream is sort of like the
driving force behind his life, right?
I see... I-I suppose so.
Wait. But according to that logic,
the driving force behind my
life seems a bit questionable.
Even Ryoma Sakamoto said,
"As human beings, we ought to have
dreams as huge as the Pacific Ocean."
Mozart was also vocal about how "life
is brilliant because we dream".
"The lives of those incapable of
big dreams must be like garbage,"
is another quote from a certain
spy for the British Empire...
Wait. What?
Is something the matter, Maria?
No, somehow, I'm starting to feel
ever so slightly depressed...
But Hayate, you really are
behaving a little weird.
What?
Could it be that Nagi's grandfather
said something to you?
What?!
W-Well, it's important to always
remember one's initial enthusiasm.
I mean, I just plan to continue
to work hard for the Miss's sake
as the true Hayate Ayasaki!
Oh, wait...
I didn't get any sleep at all because
of what happened yesterday...
Anyone... who tries to make you cry...
I'll protect you from them.
Would that... be all right?
When all's said and done,
Hayate is still just so cool.
Wow!
Hayate is working hard.
Oh!
Something about initial enthusiasm
being important and future dreams.
Hayate said that? What future dreams?
He's suddenly become like a salaryman,
who's rediscovered life,
and he's been working furiously.
Could it be for our future together?!
Um, I don't think that's quite right...
No!
I mean, it's good, but I'm
not ready for it yet!
Um, Nagi, do you happen to have
some kind of dream for the future?
Well, sure, it's normal to have lots, right?
What?
For example, I intend to become a manga
author and sell a trillion copies.
So what about it?
Nothing, I just find you too brilliant
to look upon right now...
Hmm, but I wonder what
exactly is Hayate's dream.
I have no idea. He was
stressing it quite a bit,
so he must have a really
big dream of some sort.
But Nagi, the dream you're
envisioning right now
is almost certainly not the same
as the dream Hayate has in mind.
Still, what in the world
could Hayate's dream be?
What? My dream?
Yes.
B-But that was youthful
and rash, if you will...
It's a pretty huge dream,
so I'm embarrassed to
even say it out loud...
Don't worry. I won't laugh or anything.
Well, uh...
What is it?
A 3LDK.
Pardon?
Japanese 6 Tatami
Western 4.5
A 3LDK!
Hamakaze Elementary School
And so, my future dream is...
...to have a house with three rooms
in addition to a large space
that serves as a living room,
dining room, and kitchen,
My Future Dream
and to live in this 3LDK in peace,
without fear of being driven out.
That's enough. You can stop now, Hayate.
The reason for that is...
Sense of Respect
I-I see. So your dream is a 3LDK.
What?! D-Do you think that's a bit too big?
I'm totally fine it it's not inside Tokyo.
I think it's good...
Really?!
The bigger the dream the
more wonderful it is...
Hayate?
Huh? Yes?
That reminds me, your cell
phone is still broken, right?
It really is inconvenient, so please
go buy one on the expense account.
Oh, understood. Then I'll go right away.
Oh, also, it's important to
take a break once in a while,
so please feel free to take
the rest of the day off.
Why don't you go hang out
in town for a while?
What?
I took the opportunity to
buy a really nice one.
Wow, so this is 1seg.
I can even make video calls.
Whoa! I can enter up to 1000
addresses. That's amazing.
Well, not that I need it. I
don't have that many friends.
Come to think of it, I wonder how
everyone's doing back in high school.
School, huh?
I didn't have time for it, so I
completely neglected to go, but...
If I remember right, I paid for
the full tuition, didn't I?
What am I thinking?
Could it be that I still...
...want to go back to school?
All right!
Shiomi Municipal High School
I kind of let the moment
carry me all the way here,
but I'm finding it hard to actually go in...
But I should technically
still be a student here!
If I just go in boldly...
Um...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! But I'm by
no means anyone suspicious...
Is that you, Hayate?
What?
M-Miss Nishizawa?
W-We haven't seen each other since Christmas.
What are you doing here?
W-Well...
Souya and the others were worried, too,
because you haven't been to school at all.
That is, a lot of things happened
since the end of last year...
A lot of things?
Hmm, how should I explain this?
For example, my parents suddenly got
into enormous debt and disappeared.
What?!
And I sort of got gifted to some "very
generous people" as collateral.
Huh?
Father
Mother
N-No way, right?
Well, so with all the things that happened,
I'm working as a butler at a certain mansion now.
What?
O-Oh, come on, is that a joke?
You're awful, Hayate. Really!
But I'm glad.
I finally got to see you for
the first time this year,
so I'm really happy.
What?
No, i-i-it's nothing. I didn't
mean anything by that.
What're you doing flirting out here?
S-Souya!
Wait! It's Hayate!
There were rumors that you'd quit school...
Well, it's not like I actually quit...
Oh, I see.
I'm happy for you, Nishizawa. You've
got your beloved prince back.
Wh-What are you saying? You
must be an idiot, Souya!
It's only natural to worry
about a classmate, right?!
F-For all that, you were on the verge
of tears when you heard he'd quit.
So you were worried about me?
Thank you, Miss Nishizawa.
Y-You're my classmate! Of
course, I was worried!
But in that case, maybe I'll do
my best to attend school again.
What're you saying, Ayasaki?
You've been disenrolled.
Do you think it's all right for a
teacher to utter such a flippant lie?
Don't do this, Nishizawa.
I merely spoke the truth.
What?
Ayasaki's parents came around
noon on Christmas Eve
and demanded the rest of the tuition because
he wouldn't be coming to school anymore!
What?!
Tuition? Didn't you pay it
out of your own pocket?
Because your parents
wouldn't pay it for you?
Y-Yes, basically.
But you returned the money and
disenrolled him? That's too cruel!
No, but his parents...
Ah, I see...
So I can't go to school, after all.
Hayate, where are you going?
Don't tell me you're really going
to just disappear like this.
You can't do that!
It'll be fine!
If you raise the issue with the board
of education or something, surely...
If I did that, the teachers will
end up being held responsible
for my parents' selfish acts.
You don't need to worry about me.
So, this is farewell, Miss Nishizawa.
It was short, but... Farewell,
my high school years.
Wait, Hayate!
I love you, Hayate!
What?!
I don't want this to be good-bye!
So won't you please go out with me?!
In the moment that she said that,
I came to a strange realization.
For some reason,
without thinking, her face
flashed before my mind's eye.
More than anything, I was struck by the
terribly sad expression on her face.
Won't you please go out with me?
What?! Uh, um...
I'm sorry.
What?!
The truth is...
...I'm only interested in
the 2-dimensional world.
Crushed!!
That was a joke. But right now,
there's someone I can't abandon.
Hayate, you jerk!
Being fundamentally bad
at dealing with girls,
Hayate believed it was more manly to refuse
in a way that would make
her hate him, but...
The protagonist of a comedic anime
never gets dumped in a cool way.
I-I have returned.
Ah, Hayate.
What happened to your face?
Oh, it's just a little...
By the way, I heard you bought a cell phone?
What?
Let me see it for a second.
Miss, what are you...?
There!
Nagi Sanzenin
Here! I entered myself as the number
one entry in your address book!
Thank you very much, Miss.
Mhm! E-mail me or call
me as much as you like!
Yes, Miss!
Hayate, I haven't given up yet!
Lady, you better pay for that.
Soft rice cake with strawberry
A dream of spinning is just...
Video Tachibana
Here, Wataru, I finished watching
this, so I'm returning it.
Okay, so what did you think of it?
Hmm, I guess I'd give it about 60 points.
I told you, didn't I? That it's not
a film a girl would understand.
Even so, I'm at an age where I'd like
to learn what boys are thinking!
You can learn what boys are
thinking through monster films?
But Miss Nishizawa, this person
you cared for quit school, right?
That's right! His house was gone and
there were no clues to go on, either!
At the very least, I wanted to see
him one more time and talk to him...
No way you'll ever find someone who's
gone missing like that, moron.
Why would you say something
so depressing, Wataru?!
Wataru Only
Oh...
Say, Wataru...
Hm?
I don't usually watch these anime,
but are they interesting?
Everything on that shelf are shows
that I thought were interesting,
but I don't know if you'll agree.
What?!
Don't "what" me!
Listen here! Ultimately, whether you
think it's interesting is subjective!
No matter where you go with this, you won't know
unless you check it out with your own eyes first!
So quit complaining and watch it first!
Use your head and judge for yourself!
Whether that is something you
find truly interesting or not!
That's the Coach for you!
But that's rented out right
now, so start with this.
"Lunar Rabbit Weapon..."
Bamboo!
Damn it! That bamboo seller's
always interrupting me!
Bamboo poles!
Oh, I just remembered something
I have to do, so I'm going!
Bamboo!
Damn! She ran!
Let's try to value our
customers a little more.
Still, do you think it's possible to
find a missing person in this big city?
He must have been a truly wonderful person.
Wataru, I finished watching
this, so I'm returning it.
Ah, butler-in-debt, what
did you think of it?
I found the life lessons it presented
to be quite informative,
but it seems the Miss
found it dissatisfactory.
The two keep missing each
other repeatedly. However...
Oh, shoot!
Kazuki asked me to get a
video for him, didn't he?
No way! Is that Hayate?!
Meeting him in a place like this!
Could it be we're destined to be together?!
This is no time to be
getting all sentimental!
I have to go after him!
Hayate! Haya...!
Hayate!
He's fast. There's just no
way I can catch up with him.
B-But I have to keep up, so I
don't lose sight of him at least!
Oh, he finally stopped!
Or wait, could it be that he lives here...
Wait. Huh?
Wh-What is this?! It's more
like a mansion than a house!
What's Hayate doing here?!
Oh, that's right!
Hayate said something about
being collateral for debt...
Which means, this must
be a Yakuza residence!
Maybe Hayate's being treated
in horrible ways in there!
What is this?! What should I do?!
Could we have a word with you in the office?
Pardon? A girl who appears to
be a suspicious individual?
I thought perhaps she could be
one of the Miss's acquaintances,
Let me go! Let me go!
so I was hoping to get confirmation.
Tough guys in black! These
people really are Yakuza!
Nooo!
At this rate, they're going to do things to me
that will be unsuitable for a younger audience!
Shiomi High School
Oh, a public high school bag?
Could that girl be from Hayate's old school?
Let go! Come on, let me go!
Um, she doesn't seem to be suspicious,
so please let go of her arms.
Yes, ma'am.
Let me go!
Hey, let her arms go for now.
Yes, sir.
She ran away!
I'm outta here!
Um, I didn't tell you to let her get away...
My apologies. We will catch her right away.
I managed to escape somehow,
but I have absolutely no
idea where Hayate might be.
But the Yakuza sure are impressive.
I bet Wataru wouldn't believe me even if I
told him that they have a great mansion like this.
Anyway, I have to find Hayate
quickly and escape with him!
Huh?
Comedic depiction.
Realistic depiction.
Why?! Why is there a tiger
at a Japanese residence?!
I'm seriously going to die at this rate!
And it's chasing after me, too!
Why am I chasing after that girl?!
Is this the hunting instinct
that I thought I'd lost?!
Yikes!
In that case, I'll follow that instinct
and take this girl...
...and lick her all over!
You! That's a different kind of instinct!
Hayate!
Lightning Kick!
It is a lethal technique
that can only be mastered
by those who have overcome adversity
with hard work and determination!
Um, I haven't had any special
training or anything.
Honestly! Causing nothing but
trouble, the same as ever.
Shoot. I'm being influenced by the
DVDs I've borrowed from Wataru.
That technique name just slipped out.
This isn't what I meant when I talked
about instructive life lessons...
Hayate!
Oh? Miss Nishizawa?
I-I'm so glad! It is you!
Come on, let's hurry up and
escape from this place.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Hey, Hayate.
What have you been doing?
Oh, Miss!
There is something that can
be determined at a glance.
Hayate, who is this girl?
Oh, this is Miss Nishizawa and
she used to be my classmate.
Hayate, who is this little girl?
Oh, this is Miss Nagi and
she's this estate's...
That is a woman's intuition that
even the youngest girls have.
Her destined opponent, with whom she
would fight over one precious thing...
One look, and they each
recognized it instantly.
That they were rivals!
Wait! My backer's a hamster?!
Oh, it got eaten! So weak!
My hamster's so weak!
Y-You leave me no choice.
I'll back down for today,
but next time, I'll bring a
stronger hamster with me!
Wait for me, Hayate!
Oh, Miss Nishizawa!
Still the same old funny
person, that Miss Nishizawa.
You can't, okay?
What?
You can't, okay? You can't leave
me and go somewhere else.
You have nothing to worry about.
There is nowhere else for
me to go except here.
There are some who can't go to school
anymore, even if they want to, so...
Um, Nagi...?
I've decided!
What?
Hayate has been good to me in so many ways.
As his mistress, I must repay his devotion!
Miss Nagi has made up her
mind about something.
Next time, he will be fighting
the giant campus once again.
In the meantime, aside from that...
I'm going to rent these for now!
Hey, thanks for your business!
Keeping busy!
Hey! "Cup-and-Ball and Carrot" is out!
Yes, it got rented out just earlier.
Andarta!
Wataru's video store is
getting a lot of business.
Also currently offering 50% off rentals!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Hello, Hayate Ayasaki here.
I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
Starting today,
we'll be doing this segment with
the Miss's song in the background.
Yes. As the Sanzenin family heir, the
ability to sing is an important factor.
It fully reflects how you are a spoiled,
unmanageable bundle of energy.
A true masterpiece!
What's this? Was that
intended as a compliment?
Yes, of course!
The song vibrantly conveys how
cute you are, if you will!
Cute?! Please!
Bye-bye!
Preview
Miss, some documents have
arrived from Hakuou Academy...
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
The transfer application, right? For you?
Oh, for me.
Wait! What do you mean, for me?!
They're transfer documents for you.
And now, I shall relate the story
of my entrance exam experience.
I'll tell you the Hakuou entrance exam
trends and how to deal with them.
No, thank you.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"I Hear That Those Who Rule the
Summer Rule at Entrance Exams".
I Hear That Those Who Rule the
Summer Rule at Entrance Exams
I saw the promise in you.
So let's go to school together!
Run up to that arena of your dreams!