"The girl is only one in the world."
"That made her the god of this world."
"She found herself on an island when she began to understand things around her."
"There was no one else there."
"She had nothing to do."
"That was the everything the world offered."
Good afternoon, Chihiro.
Ah, Renji-kun.
How much have you written?
I haven't written much.
Probably only about thirty percent.
Looks like I can't do much alone.
Can I look at it?
"One day the girl made a fire at the beach."
"That was because there was a scene in a book where a stranded person made a fire."
"In the deep blue sky, a straight white road climbed up."
"She thought, 'Maybe it's the same as the cloud."
"So she put her head in it, and her mouth and eyes became really painful."
"In haste, she moved away and gazed at it from a distance."
"She then understands that it is useless to her."
"Just like that, she begins to understand things one by one."
"She understood the meaning of understanding."
I see.
How was it?
This girl is cute, right?
She is... cute?
I guess I should rewrite it.
From where?
Everything until now.
Wait a second, why?
Because you said she was cute.
I'm just thinking she shouldn't be thought of that way.
It'll be all right.
With this short of an episode, it'll be interesting.
You are mistaken, Renji-kun.
This girl should be more of a peculiar person.
Peculiar?
She'll hear a joke and take it very seriously.
The readers need to feel worried and uneasy, so...
If she is said to be cute, then I must not have written her existence properly.
Oh, a bento?
Also for Chihiro?
Sure, why not?
Being good at cooking will be helpful as a spouse,
but it would complicate things.
Why?
Because if you are better than your girlfriend, then she can't make a bento for you with love, right?
She's not my girlfriend.
You and Chihiro aren't a couple?
No, we're not.
You're such a carefree person.
So I guess you want no one else but me to be your girlfriend.
That's dangerous... I said that's dangerous.
What is it?
Ah, nothing.
I was thinking about my future career.
Future career?
It's a questionnaire about what you want to be in the future.
I see.
There is this future career questionnaire at school.
What is it?
No, nothing.
I wonder what I should write.
I think you should just put whatever you want to be.
If I had an idea, then I wouldn't be troubled like this.
You don't have anything?
I'm like this but I don't really have any talents.
You're good at cooking, Renji-kun.
I'll think about it more.
Good morning.
You're doing good, good.
You sure are doing this regularly.
You mean making lunch?
Yes! Is it for Chihiro-chan again?
Well, yes.
It's a big help that you're making breakfast too.
Hey, you two still aren't a couple yet?
It's not like that.
I see.
What?
I was just thinking that your reaction didn't seem to change.
Hey now...
Hey, just a hypothetical situation, but if Chihiro and I were to become a couple, would you be happy?
As long as you're happy too.
Are you having fun being with Chihiro?
T-That is...
You don't have to get angry...
It's not like I'm getting angry.
You are a man, so you should practice going out with responsibility.
Responsibility?
Love is a downward hill.
Once it starts, it can't be stopped.
But affection is a rising affair.
You have to climb with the painful and difficult times together.
Ah, but the hardships are with the ones that you like, whereas being with the one that you love is something that cannot be stopped.
So I guess they go against each other.
Maybe they are just like tofu and nattou, something of a paradox.
Yeah, yeah.
"She painted a human being..."
"The girl painted a figure of a boy."
"So, she decided to add a figure of a boy into paintings of landscapes she had painted."
"With no specific reason, she kept those paintings in the same places where she painted them."
"Soon, there was not a single place on that island she did not paint."
"She was always with the boy everywhere she went."
"It meant that the girl and boy looked at each other every time she looked at the paintings."
"However, the girl had no feeling of achievement."
"Would it be a 'human?', she thought."
"This was the 'painting of a human being.' "
"He did not move nor think. He was simply there."
"Lonely? Finally, she could ask herself by finding the word."
"She was not lonely."
What do you think?
I think it's fine.
With this, aren't you about seventy percent done?
I think it should be soon.
Have you thought about the ending?
What should we do...?
Wait.
Up to now, there are two main ideas for the end of the story.
First would be that the girl went into the paintings and lived happily ever after with the boy.
This will be a fantasy story.
Second would be that the boy in the paintings became a real boy.
I don't know how it should end but I think it should be at least a happy ending.
Although it's really up to one's wish on having either a happy or sad ending.
Is that so?
Is there something wrong?
You can tell the story about going into the paintings as a fantasy, but...
you can also say the girl is trying to run away from reality due to loneliness.
You can also think that due to loneliness the girl ran away from reality.
In other words, she's broken.
In other words, she's broken, right?
It depends on one's interpretation, but yes.
I see.
I guess that was my comment for this time.
You're right, I think she is broken.
She has to remember about loneliness.
I see.
It's somehow bad deciding the ending this way, right?
Really?
Because it feels like God is tampering with it.
I guess I can really do it when I try.
I was surprised myself.
When I realized it, we had been talking for so long. It's so enjoyable.
It's all thanks to Renji-kun.
I didn't really do anything.
Because now I've realized that I really can't do anything by myself.
Is that really so?
Umm... Renji-kun.
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
Err, thank you very much.
Yeah, you're welcome.
What is it?
Renji-kun, do you... want to kiss me?
Do you... want to kiss?
You can.
I don't think you're doing this because someone told you to.
And I don't think I've ever met anyone I've been as close to as Renji-kun.
I also think the reason I kept meeting with Renji-kun until now is because I believe in you.
And it seems that you like me too, Renji-kun.
That's why you can kiss me like we're lovers.
I think the setting should be like this.
Why?
Am I getting confused?
Am I thinking that Chihiro is...?
If she is said to be cute, then I must not have written her existence properly.
This girl should be more of a peculiar person.
Wrong!
Wrong.
It's not like that.
There is something wrong.
But....
Why is Chihiro not happy?
Why is she not feeling embarrassed?
Why is she not writing about her facial expressions?
Why is she not writing a single word about liking me?
Why?
That's because God is tampering with it.
It's not like that.
It's not like that at all.
I'm sorry.
I...
You've got it all wrong!
It's not your fault, Chihiro!
Wait, Chihiro!
Please don't... write that in your diary...
Seriously... don't write it.
You've got it all wrong... everything.
"The girl is only one in the world."
"That made her the god of this world."
Found it.
I've found it.
I thought I wouldn't need it.
I thought I wouldn't be able to get it.
I had given up hope, but now I've found it.
That is... a place where I belong.
Hmm, maybe I was too daring.
Maybe it'll stimulate Hirono-kun too much.
I'm going!
Just kidding.
Papa, Mama.
Ah, tomorrow's preparations...
It's done.
This is a place where the sounds have disappeared.
One day my mother disappeared from my father's heart.
My father also disappeared from my mother's heart.
Mama?
What's the matter, Ma-
Since then, the house has lost its noise.
Since then, the house has lost its conversations.
All the color has since disappeared from my life.
Without realizing it, even I disappeared from their hearts.
Since then, I had been living an empty life.
I've finally found a world with voices.
I've found a space not lacking colors.
I don't have to keep it buried away.
I am not able to answer the phone right now.
When you hear the "beep", please leave your name and message.
Yahoo, Hirono-kun? It's Miyako!
Are you awake?
I'm just heading out.
I'll be at the place we promised for lunch.
Don't be late, okay?
Later.
Oh, is it a feeding battle royal?
The laws of nature sure are strict.
It's time.
Yahoo, Hirono-kun.
I'm already there, are you on your way?
I'll never forgive you if you're late.
Hey, you're late you know.
You should come ten minutes early for a date.
Not making the woman wait is the man's responsibility, you know.
You're late, late, late, late!
How long are you going to make me wait?!
Today is going to be all on you, Hirono-kun.
I'll be here, so hurry up!
What's the matter?
Don't tell me you're still asleep.
If you are, then I'm not going to let you off that easily.
Hi-ro-no-kun!
It's Miyako.
You're still not on your way?
I'm still waiting.
Geez, what are you doing?
How many hours are you going to make me wait?
Are you even planning to come?
I will erase your existence from Onii-chan's heart.
And with that, farewell to you.
And then, it's over.
I will make it end.
I'm going to disappear again?
Hello, Hirono-kun?
Did you get the meeting place wrong?
It's the bench in front of the fountain.
You know where, right?
If you don't, then just call me and I'll come and get you.
It's Miyako.
Are you all right, Hirono-kun?
I hope you didn't get into anything bad on the way.
Call me when you get this.
Stop this already!
Call me now already!
I'm really worried!
It's Miyako.
Please answer the phone. I know you're there.
You are listening to this now, right?
Answer the phone. Let's have a talk.
Please talk to me.
Why aren't you coming?!
Why aren't you answering the phone?!
Why aren't you answering?!
Why?!
Why are you not saying anything?!
Hirono-kun?
Please listen and contact me.
I'm not angry or anything.
I'll be waiting here until we meet.
I'll be waiting until I hear something from you.
Please, please...
Come here and meet me...
It's fine if you only show your face...
It's fine if you only let me hear anything from you...
Please...
Hirono-kun, you are coming here, right?
I can keep on waiting, right?
I'll believe you... I'll believe in you, so...
Please...
Answer me.
Send me a mail...
or just a comment, it's fine...
Please... don't leave me alone.
I'll be waiting here.
I'll wait here forever.
Why? Why is it...
We promised...
I believed in you...
Why...?
You don't want to?
Perhaps you don't want to come after all?
Do you hate me, Hirono-kun?
If so, please tell me.
If you hate me, then please say so.
Don't just be silent, say something!
Please, please I beg you, say something!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry for saying such strange things...
You're angry... You're angry, right?
I've always been selfish...
and I do whatever I want.
And I just pull you around...
I'm sorry...
I can't sleep, you know.
I was looking forward so much to the date today.
I was very excited when I thought about you, Hirono-kun.
It's my first time feeling this...
I don't know what to do...
I want to see you...
I want to see you, Hirono-kun!
Help me, Hirono-kun.
Please help me!
I don't want to disappear.
I don't want to disappear!
I don't want to... disappear from your heart, Hirono-kun!
Can you walk?
I'm fine.
It's nothing really serious.
I'm going to the convenience store, what do you want?
Garibori-kun!
I mean for breakfast.
Shall I make something?
Don't say something scary.
That's really mean!
I may be like this, but I'm practicing cooking now, you know.
When you don't need anymore practice, tell me.
Should I just buy whatever looks good?
Okay, I'll leave it to you.
What, it's here-
Messages deleted.
A color without hues...
is pure and cold.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
Clear Colour.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?