suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Nayu!
Na-yu!
It's already 7:00 am!
I won't care if you're late!
Hey! Na-yu!
Yesterday I wore stripes.
So I guess today will be laced.
Nayu!
Nayu, I'm coming in.
Keigo-san!
Which do you think would be better?
Should I wear the light green chequered ones for spring?
But to match my bra, I need to wear these laced ones!
So you got stuck choosing underwear again?
Ah... that's because...
A great day starts with a great pair of underwear.
Right?
Well, for now, put on some panties and come downstairs.
"A great day starts with a great pair of underwear," huh?
Honestly.
Your granddaughter is faithfully following your teachings...
Youko-san...
This Swelling Chest
Keigo-san, amazing!
Cracking them with one hand...!
This is easily done!
Then how about...
I'm... in trouble.
Anyway, Nayu. School going well?
Yup! I've made friends, it's fun!
I see. That's great, isn't it?
There are lots of misunderstandings, though.
Hey, what kind of panties are you wearing today?
Mine are lace, both top and bottom, and they feel-
Nayu-chan, keep your voice down...
Actually, don't start up a conversation like that!
Huh? Why?
It's embarrassing, don't you think?!
Really? Underwear's not something to be embarrassed about.
Anyway, have you two decided what club to join?
There are so many it's overflowing!
Haruka, have you decided?
Let's see...
Something like the cooking club would be good.
My home is a restaurant, and I could give what I
make to my younger brothers as presents, right?
Haruka-chan, you're an older sister?
Yeah. I've got three younger brothers.
Yako-chan, are you joining the Kendo club?
You said you were scouted by an upperclassman, right?
Amazing!
Yako-chan's family runs a Kendo dojo.
They've got lots of students, and her mother and father both instruct!
Ah! Your mother's also a school teacher, right?
Don't bring up my mother.
If you don't hurry, you'll run out of time to change!
Maybe she had a fight with her mum?
Maybe...
School clubs... Which one should I join?
Nayu-chan, Nayu-chan!
Don't stare around so much!
More rumours will start about you-
Ah, I was just thinking about how
everyone's got such cute underwear.
Oh? Haruka-chan, you bought a new bra!
With these, your breasts won't be squashed.
She's touching her chest again!
So they are...!
Lesbians?
It's not what you think! She's-
They feel wonderful !
Hey, your bra! Let me see it!
These will provide proper support for your breasts!
Not that place...!
Hey! How's Yako-chan's underwear?
Hmm? A bra?
Yako-chan's, isn't it?
What? Those are...
My mother bought it and put it in there, I don't want to wear it at all!
Not being honest, eh.
These are certainly cute,
but right now might be a bit too soon for you.
What? Wait, Nayu-chan!
You see, it has cups, right?
For Yako-chan's size, it would be better to-
I am going ahead.
Jingouji-san?
Excuse me.
What's wrong? Those-
It's nothing!
I only wanted Yako-chan to wear
underwear that was right for her, but...
I wonder if I said it the wrong way.
Of course not.
Yako-chan started overreacting.
I'm next.
Nayu-chan, your glasses, glasses!
Ah! Right, thank you.
Ow!
Are you all right?
I'm glad you kept my glasses!
It's going to be Yako-chan's turn soon!
They're increasing the steps!
Our level must be too easy for her.
Not only did she come second place in the National Young Men's Kendo Tournament,
she's great at other sports too!
Looks like she's going to jump!
What's wrong?
She's definitely on a different level!
Yako-chan!
What?!
Your bra!
Talking about underwear again?!
Yako-chan, your bra's...!
Cut it out for me, will you!?
Your bra slid!
What's that?
How juvenile!
Yako-chan, did you put that bra on?
I'm not wearing a bra or anything!
But the cups have slid up!
I said I'm not wearing one!
I guess the cups just didn't fit.
For now, why don't we go somewhere to fix-
No.
Yako-chan?
Never, never-
I'll never wear a bra again!
Where's Yako-chan?
She's cleaning the bathroom,
but it sounds like she's going home when she's done.
Is she... mad at me, I wonder.
Hey, Nayu-chan.
Eh?
What was it like, the first time you wore a bra?
A bra?
I was incredibly happy!
When I thought about how I'd be able to wear one everyday,
I got so excited!
It felt like I had become an adult.
That's quite like you.
Ah, on top of that,
When the tips of the breast began to prickle, covering them was comfortable, wasn't it?
It happens when they start to grow...
That's why I think Yako-chan would be comfortable too, if she wore a bra.
For me, in about third grade, my chest suddenly got larger.
When I was told by my mum to "Wear a bra,"
I was embarrassed to death.
Embarrassed? Why?
You've got such splendid breasts.
What my mum had said shocked me, or rather-
"Your chest is indecent" is what I felt I had been told.
In reality, people do stare at them...
Yako-chan isn't mad at you, either.
It's just awkward for her, don't you think?
It seems like she's had a fight with her mum,
and that's probably another reason.
So it would be best to leave her alone.
But...
"I'll never wear a bra again..."
That was just an outburst, don't you think?
But I don't want her to hate bras even more!
I wonder if there's anything I can do?
Something Nayu-chan could do...?
Eh? They really did make it!
They're trying their best to get new members-
I-I believe that's...!
This is it!
Sign: Handicrafts Club
Nothing ventured, nothing gained!
Sorry, we've never made anything like bras.
Heaven has forsaken me.
There's only one person who can help us now.
Nayu-chan?
Eh? The way to make a no-cup bra?
Teaching you isn't a problem, but...
By tomorrow is rather fast, isn't it?
Thank you, Keigo-san!
It's all for Nayu's friend, right?
Yako-chan couldn't have lost all desire to wear a bra, I think.
I want to do what I can to save that feeling.
I've got to do my best!
Nayu!
Your alarm clock's going off!
Na-yu!
Today we're having scrambled eggs and Napolitana, a Keigo-special!
If you don't come quickly, I'm going to eat it all!
Oi... "Morning Station" is starting...
Little kid.
Bird-brain.
She's fast asleep.
It's late, can't you finish this tomorrow-
Please, Keigo-san!
I want to finish this by the morning!
For Yako-chan's sake!
And so, she ended up going to bed after five.
Nayu, you're going to be late.
Nayu?
Come on, Nayu!
How can you sleep like that?
Wake up now!
Where's Yako-chan?
She isn't here yet.
Nayu-chan!
You look gloomy this morning.
Ah! Good morning.
Good morning.
Ah, right!
I made this, could you take a look?
This is a...
Eh?! You made this?!
Wow! It's cute!
Nayu-chan, you've got some real talent!
R-Really? That's great!
Nayu-chan, your fingers...
Ah, actually, this was the first time I've made a bra.
When I thought about giving this to someone, I got really nervous.
Giving this to someone?
Yako-chan.
It would be nice if she likes it!
You're a good girl.
Haruka-chan?
You're a good, good girl!
Such a good girl!
How did it get like this?!
They are so bold!
A love scene?
What have you been doing since the morning?
Yako-chan!
G-Good morning.
Good morning.
We've got more good weather today, huh.
She's here, Nayu-chan!
Here's your chance!
Yako-chan! Um!
S-Sorry about yesterday...
And so, here you go!
As an apology...
I hope you like it.
Yesterday?
Did something happen then?
Ah, well. She's really not honest!
The bra...
So, do you need that to wash your hands?
Err, um-
I'm telling you I don't need that!
Wait up!
Watch where you're going!
Could it be...
Do your breasts hurt even from the slightest touch?
Why?! How'd you know-
Not really.
Hey, Yako-chan, please take this.
I refuse.
I'm begging you, just for a while-
No thanks.
Yako-chan.
That bra was made for you by Nayu-chan.
Your handkerchief is getting wet!
T-That's absurd!
You can't force me to...
Nayu-chan! Move over a bit.
What are you doing?!
Your briefs are sopping wet-
Haruka! What are you trying to do?!
When you're hungry, you eat.
When it rains, you use an umbrella.
When you get this wet, you have to change your underwear, right?
Victor: Shiraishi!
H-Haruka-chan...
As expected of the older sister of three young boys...
I even got you, Nayu-chan; sorry! Honest!
I'm fine. My underwear wasn't as wet as I thought it would be.
Mine too, but...
For Yako-chan's clothes to dry, it'll take some time-
You still haven't changed yet.
Are you still going to say you won't wear it?
It's not really that I don't want to wear it...
The bra my mother bought for me, and the bra Nayu made for me,
I think they're both cute.
Then why? Why didn't you wear it from the start?
B-Because... Unlike Haruka's and Nayu's, my chest is... f-flat...
Um...
That's why...
Everyone would wonder "Why is that
flat-chested girl wearing a bra?", right?
They'd say "she's trying too hard" or "she's overdoing it", right?
My mother went so far as to buy a bra for me the day before P.E. started...
I don't want to have a sudden "bra début" while changing...
"Isn't that just silly?"
"She hasn't a trace of a chest."
"Look at that bra."
It's impossible, don't you think?!
Could it be-
That's why you got in a fight with your mum?
Sorry it was so stupid.
But I really think it's a bit early for me to wear a bra.
Yesterday in gym class, it became clear to me.
Nayu, I'm sorry.
You went out of your way to make it and yet-
I'm sorry, but-
Sorry, one moment.
Ow! Nayu?!
Yup! It's perfectly fine.
Yako-chan, you should wear a bra!
Huh?
Your bust-top is expanding,
and they probably prickle when touched, right?
That's evidence your breasts are getting bigger!
Okay? Try wearing the bra I made.
Righteo! I'm taking your clothes off!
Stop it! I can do it myself!
I'm not your younger brother, Haruka!
It's fine, it's fine.
Let me go!
I don't need such a stubborn little brother!
Come now, put it on!
I said I can do it myself!
It's so cute!
How's the size?
It's okay.
For girls like you with developing breasts,
a cup-less bra stays in place better.
So, to protect your breasts, even as small as they are,
a bra is an absolute necessity.
Thank you.
It's fine. I had fun making them!
That's right, you made them by yourself!
Ah, of course my family helped.
At first I asked the Handicrafts Club for help,
but they refused, saying that they've never made any.
It would have been nice if there were an Underwear Club, eh?
What the heck is that?!
Nayu?
An "Underwear Club," huh?
That reminds me, it's time for lunch!
I completely forgot!
Let's move, Nayu-chan!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Yako-chan, you too!
I-I'm sorry!
We were in a hurry, and-
Nayu!
Ah, well then, I'm very sorry!
Nayu-chan, let's hurry!
Sorry, sorry!
Hayama... Nayu?
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
This is all that's left.
I'm sorry.
It's a diet, right?
This is also training.
Preview
Hey! Listen!
In England, they say if you wear red underwear while you confess,
your love will blossom!
Is that true?
All right! You've got to wear red to your battles!
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra!
A Windy Day