Wow, Ami-chan...
You were okay with such a big...?
Well, it's part of my job.
Big? Isn't that an average size?
No, it was like—
Yikes, sorry!
Oh, it's just you.
What's so big?
You couldn't mean a pe—
Omigod!
No, there was this huge dog!
They took pictures of me with
it for a magazine shoot!
I mean, pe...?
What did you think I was talking about!?
Maruo, are you okay?
You're acting weird.
Okay! Could everyone please
take their seats?
We'll begin last-period homeroom!
Mr. Class Rep, could you get us started?
Kitamura-kun?
Stand. Bow. Enjoy.
What?
That a joke?
Looks like you're having a rough day...
But cheer up!
Kitamura?
So, the weekend starts tomorrow!
After that,
we'll have the highly anticipated student
council president elections!
Oh, that time of year already?
An event! An event!
So, Kitamura-kun, please cheer
up and do your best.
You're the number one candidate
to be the next president.
Make that the only candidate.
Yeah, baby! Let's party!
We already know Kitamura's going
to be the next president!
Kitamura, good luck.
- We'll help out.
- Not gonna...
I'm never going to be president.
I'm resigning as vice president.
I'm quitting the student council.
I quit.
- I quit, quit, quit, quit, quit.
- Ki-Kitamura-kun?
I quit...
everything!
...Thing!
- ...Thing...
- Kitamura-kun?
Everything!
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
donna kanji sonna kanji
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I act tough as we butt heads.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
Kitamura never replied...
Distant Stars
I wonder what happened to him.
He said he's quitting the student council.
The student council...
Was that spiteful student council
president being mean to you?
What's that?
- Let me go!
- What are you thinking!?
Minorin, what's going on?
Oh, it's terrible, you guys!
Look.
Ki—
Kitamura-kun!
Reception Office
What's he done to his hair!?
He won't answer our questions,
so we brought you in,
as his closest friends.
Do you know why this happened?
I have no idea...
People still snap in such an obvious fashion?
No, I'm not really sure...
What about you, Kano-san?
I don't know the reason or
why he'd act this way.
Besides, if he's left the student council,
his actions are no longer my concern.
Kano-san...
You're wasting your time on that fool.
Oh, wait...
Kano-senpai, you've grown rather cold.
Maybe you're the reason Yusaku snapped.
Hey, Kawashima!
You may be right.
But if that's true, Kitamura will have
disappointed me even more.
Ami-chan, did you learn
anything about Maruo?
Nope.
Though the student council president
seemed to know something.
Kano-senpai?
Taiga?
Officer!
I've brought in the criminal!
Taka-chan! Help!
Kushieda's being so mean!
What did you do?
Nothing!
It's just, Kitamura called me last night.
He asked me how to bleach
his hair, so I told him.
Didn't you see how Kitamura-kun
was acting yesterday!?
Didn't you wonder why he was asking!?
I didn't expect him to go through with it!
Is he actually leaving the student council?
Hey, Ami-chan...
Isn't there anything we can do for him?
What?
That spoiled honors student
is just itching for attention.
The whole "doesn't anyone out there
realize how miserable I am?" thing...
He's a second year and bleaching
his hair's the best he can do?
Pathetic.
Ow...
Dumb-chi!
Aren't you worried about Kitamura-kun!?
Worrying about him would
only make us look stupid!
- What!?
- Just let it go...
Hey, isn't that Kitamura?
Where is he?
C-Calm down, Kitamura-kun!
I said I'm going home!
Ah! Kitamura-kun!
Come back!
Kitamura-kun...
Must be nice, believing such an obvious
cry for help will bring people running.
Come on, people.
Class is about to start.
Hey, wanna go to Kitamura-kun's house?
I don't have practice or work today,
and I'm a little worried, you know?
How about it, Taiga?
Nah, Kitamura-kun might be more willing
to talk with fewer people around.
True.
Then wait for me by the
school gate, Takasu-kun.
I need to drop by the clubroom!
R-Right...
You sure about this?
I'm worried about Kitamura-kun,
but I wouldn't be any help.
And to be honest, I want him
to leave the student council.
Need to get him away from
that damn president...
Taiga?
So you better get the job done, mutt!
Easy for her to say...
Thanks for waiting!
I hope Kitamura-kun's home...
I really do wonder what happened to him.
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
You're kinda quiet.
Um...
Well, uh...
I was wondering what was up
with Kawashima and Taiga...
Kawashima didn't need to chew out a
childhood friend like that, you know?
I'm sure Amin's actually worried
about Kitamura-kun.
You know how Amin works
in the grown-up world?
She knows a lot more than
a bunch of kids like us.
And understands Kitamura-kun
way better than we do.
If you think about it, she's been really patient,
dealing with our immature brains that
can't understand the things she does.
Is she really that mature?
Amin didn't say anything wrong.
Not many people are willing to
be so critical of their friends.
That's why I believe Amin had her
reasons for being so harsh today.
Or more like, that's what I want to believe.
I don't want to say this, but there are
lots of things you don't know, right?
Things about someone you
want to understand.
Yeah...
I just want to believe Amin
is the one who knows it all.
And we're just too immature to understand.
She's like our last hope...
Whoa! What am I saying?
Is Kitamura-kun's house this way?
Kushieda, how should I put this...?
You're pretty kind.
Kind!?
You're wrong! Wrong!
I'm arrogant and...
A phony...
Kushieda?
Kitamura's house ended up being empty,
so we didn't get a chance to see him.
I'm home!
Oh, you're here.
W-Welcome home, Ry-Ryuji-kun.
What?
You eat something off the floor?
Yo.
Sorry to impose.
Ki-Kitamura?
Yasuko-san invited me in,
so I took her up on—
That's not the issue!
Actually...
I ran away from home.
Aisaka, do you come over to
Takasu's place a lot?
Y-Ya-chan said I'm welcome
to eat here whenever I want,
s-so I'm taking her up on her offer...
I see...
It's a good thing you live next to Takasu.
U-Uh-huh...
Man, tatami floors are fantastic.
None of the rooms at my place have them.
Th-The rooms at my place
are all western-style, too!
Oh...
But Japanese-style rooms
are more relaxing, huh?
Uh-huh...
W-We share the same tastes...
Uh, nutmeg, nutmeg...
Okay, let me give you a hand.
Huh? With what?
Sure, I'll peel these for you!
I'm good at that!
Since when?
Oh, I get it.
Basically, you want to impress him, right?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Then, whip up some of your wonderful
sunny-side-up eggs.
G-Got it!
Add the eggs, then cover them with a lid.
Lid? What lid?
The frying pan lid, obviously.
Once you've found it, add a little water...
Add water? Where?
Whoa! It caught fire!
It's burning!
Add water here!?
No!
Uh, Kitamura...
This is...
H-Hey! Kitamura!
Don't eat it!
I've never actually cooked before...
Tastes like sunny-side-up eggs, over hard!
Kitamura-kun...
Aisaka.
You made this to help cheer me up, right?
Thanks.
I feel better already.
Uh-huh...
Oh, Takasu made Salisbury steak?
Yeah, with my special red wine sauce.
Whoa, it's great!
You always deliver.
I-I can learn how to make it for next time...
Sure. Shouldn't be any problem
with Takasu teaching you.
Man, I stuffed myself!
That was heavenly!
Good to hear.
So?
Why's your hair bleached?
Ryuji!
I don't want to be student council president.
Nobody will expect me to
run with hair like this.
So there you go.
That's why?
Y-You don't need to force yourself to
become student council president!
It's your decision to make!
I'll support you!
Yeah, thanks...
Hey, Ryuji.
Put on a game!
Oh! Great idea!
Let's play!
We don't have school tomorrow,
so we can go wild!
Yeah! Wild and crazy!
I fell asleep?
Huh? Where's Kitamura?
What!? Kitamura-kun!?
Oh, Ryuji?
I want ice cream.
Where'd that come from?
We don't have any.
- Ice cream! Ice cream!
- You're so hopeless...
I'll go to the convenience store.
You coming with?
Wait, where's Kitamura-kun?
Oh, he laid his own futon
and went to sleep.
No shame, huh...?
I get to watch Kitamura-kun sleep...
Here.
The nights are cold, so put this on.
Taiga?
I'm...
Useless...
How could I be so happy?
I was only thinking about myself...
While Kitamura-kun was suffering,
grieving, agonizing...
I didn't even realize it...
I'm absolutely useless.
Worthless... Incompetent...
No you're—
I am!
I'm completely useless.
I can't do a thing to help Kitamura-kun.
Not a single thing.
Whenever I was feeling down,
Kitamura-kun was there to extend a hand.
He always helped put my mind at ease.
Always let me know that I belonged...
That I belonged in this world...
Kitamura-kun is...
Kitamura-kun is my...
Last hope, huh?
Taiga, look. It's the Big Dipper.
And that's Polaris.
And Orion.
Where's Orion?
There—those three stars in a row.
Oh, I see it.
Even though they look like they're
right next to each other,
those stars are actually really far apart.
We learned that in grade school.
You know...
It's like Kitamura-kun and me...
Everything we see isn't
necessarily the truth.
How much more will it take for
me to learn the hidden truth?
Just how great is the distance...
between Kitamura-kun and me?
You want to get closer because you
want to understand him, yeah?
You're reaching out to understand
because you love him, yeah?
If so, you should just take it step by step.
Right.
Good morning, Takasu.
Whoa!
Good morning...
I drank the milk in the fridge.
Sorry.
But it looks like you guys
had a blast last night.
Should've woken me up.
M-My bad...
Oh, right...
I had to keep Taiga company
while she binged.
Something wrong?
Uh, no...
Crap, look at the time.
I'll make breakfast right away...
Whoa!
Taiga...
Hey, wake up, you slob!
Leave her be. She's sleeping so peacefully.
She looks so happy...
Stinks like...milk!
An excellent blow for someone
who just woke up!
Ki-Kitamura-kun!?
Oh, no!
Were you watching me sleep!?
Sorry, I was!
No way!
Was I making weird faces!?
- Oh, jeez!
- Calm down...
My hair's a total mess!
We were kicked out.
Oh well.
Let's go grab some—
Yes! Let's grab some fun!
Man, between the culture festival
and practice, I've been so busy!
I haven't had free time like
this for way too long.
Oh! And I know just the place!
He's gone through a hundred or so pitches...
Something really is wrong with Kitamura.
It's healthy for students to work up
a sweat with some exercise.
Something about this seems unhealthy.
Okay! Takasu, you're up next!
Uh, I...
Kitamura-kun!
I'll go!
Oh, Aisaka's fired up!
Taiga?
Just you watch.
I'm gonna slam these balls!
Right! Keep your arms tight.
Hey! You hit it!
Whoa! I may have found
a diamond in the rough!
Amazing!
You're incredible, Aisaka!
Why wouldn't a talented girl like
you join the softball team?
Home Run
We're home!
Man, that home run was so sick!
You've got skills, Aisaka!
Y-You're exaggerating...
Oooh!
Welcome home, kids!
Ryu-chan...
Could you restrain Kitamura-kun for me?
Like this?
Yep.
Now don't let him go.
Taiga, grab him!
I gave Kitamura-kun's daddy
a call a little while ago.
He sounded pretty steamed.
So I thought we should fix your
hair before sending you home.
You're in cahoots with my parents!?
You adults are all the same!
But aren't you going to be
student council president?
We can't leave you with bleached hair, then.
I will never be student council president!
Never, ever!
I wonder if Kitamura-kun made it home...
Beats me.
I guess he seriously doesn't want the job.
Are you sure?
Do you remember
what Minorin said when we went to the beach house last summer?
About why she tells everyone
she doesn't like scary stuff?
You mean...
The briar patch thing?
Kitamura-kun keeps saying he doesn't
want to be student council president.
But I bet the opposite's true.
You're saying he wants to be president?
Think that might be the case?
Even if it is, we can't do anything
until he has a change of heart.
Uh-huh... But...
We can at least help motivate him...
You sure about this?
It's fine. I've made up my mind.
Okay then, put this on.
Let's do this!
- Is this some kind of joke!?
- No way! Seriously?
Student Council
President Candidate
- Give me a break...
- Shaddap!
I have an announcement to make!
Once I, Aisaka Taiga, am elected
student council president,
I'll take over the school and stick your high
school experience and damn memories...
in a m-moggu...morgue!
What!?
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning Love
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
kurodatte icchau
I say black.
sunaoni narenai
A little imp
amanojaku
who can't be honest to herself.
sukito iwaretara
If you say love,
daikirai datte
I say hate.
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
amai banirani
It's like adding salt
soruto kakeru youni
to sweet vanilla...
One Step Forward
Once I'm elected student council president,
they'll all be scared shrilly!
Scared silly.
And I'll bury them in
a bloody mog...moggu—
You still can't say it...
Come, fools!
Shake hands with me at
Ohashi High School!