We're not asking for freedom if it comes in shackles
Especially in a world so imperfect
Anime-Koi
Presents
Chaika The Coffin Princess
kyou
It's days like today
kyou
that make me want to live
mou)
(I think. I think.)
mou)
It's the important people in my life
who help me make it through
mou)
(I think. I think.)
mou)
ryou
My vision narrows being surrounded by love
ryou
What do you expect me to do on a night like this?
We cross vows at the end of the road
Seeing into ourselves in our own reflections
utsushidaseyo
We're not asking for freedom if it comes in shackles
Especially in a world so imperfect
We're not interested in the answers that only lead to farewells
We'll look for you
until we find you
The taboo emperor, Arthur Gaz...
His daughter is the successor to his empire,
and subsequently, the one who will decide its fate.
Fate?
Chaika's existence is only the beginning.
A fate surpassing the imagination of man lies ahead.
You are a mere tool whose sole purpose
is to set that fate in motion.
The Girl who Bears the Coffin
Man...
Isn't there any money lying around somewhere?
A rabbit?
I'll make a stew out of it.
Wha—
Hey!
What are you doing out here in the mountai—
A—
A?
A-Attack?
Who's attacking? Attacking whom?
B-Bandit!
Sorry, but I'm not a bandit either.
I'm currently jobless.
I have no food, so I came to collect some edible plants.
Poor?
Yeah, that's right.
Understood. Jobless and poor!
You're right, but that still pisses me off.
What about you? What are you doing out here?
Is that a coffin?
Mountain. No people. Great idea.
Wait, are you...
Pretend you did not see!
Did not see this!
Is there... someone in there?
Are you a murderer?
Not criminal! Traveler!
Weak traveler!
Going to Delsorant town!
Too far...
How long have you been walking around here?
Three days.
These mountains shouldn't take
that long to get through if you travel normally...
You're lost, aren't you?
Shocking truth...
You got any money?
Thief! Poor! Bandit!
I'm not!
I was just gonna show you the way if you'd buy me breakfast!
If you can trust me, I'll take you
to the town without anyone seeing you.
Keep this up, and you'll never get off this mountain.
Moruzerun... Moruzerun... Emurun...
Zeburun... Wamurun... Tourun...
A unicorn...
Damn...
This sucks.
Run!
Oh, come on...
Just ditch this thing!
No! Not touch! Valuable!
Huh?
What?
Damn it. I take it back.
Don't ever let go of that coffin!
Moruzerun... Moruzerun...
Let's go!
We're jumping!
If you don't want that thing to eat you, hang on tight!
It's no use...
I'm so hungry, my strength's gone.
Sudden! Pushy! Reckless!
Blood...
Treat. Fast!
That was a unicorn. It'll be on us again soon.
Gone...
Can't treat...
We'll never get away from that thing.
What a lousy life I've had.
Give up?
Might as well.
Die?
Probably.
Die, not scared?
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't scared...
But I don't have anything else to look forward to.
In this world, I'm totally incompetent.
A Gundo?
You're a wizard?
Yes.
Incompetent. Same.
I have only this.
Else, incompetent.
This, can do much.
Like... kill a unicorn?
Need time.
During magic technique.
Can not move.
I just need to buy you some time, right?
If I do that, you can use your magic, right?
Yes.
I am steel.
Steel knows no fear. Steel knows no doubt.
When faced with my enemy, I hesitate not.
I am a weapon to destroy thee.
Iron-Blood Transformation!
Zeburun... Wamurun... Tourun...
Come on, you nag!
Kokult elum...
Naikt inte...
Naint kum...
Ee wam, ee wam, milta ru...
Kokult elum...
Crap!
Naikt inte, naint...
Milta ru...
Fly, blade!
The Ripper!
I pronounce the battle over.
I am man.
Alive! Both alive!
Surprise!
What is?
You! Strong!
Well, I was a saboteur, after all.
Not incompetent! Useful!
Huh?
Saved! Because you here!
I guess...
Ask again. Show way.
Sure...
You, name?
Toru. Toru Acura. What's yours?
Chaika Ga— Correction.
Chaika Trabant!
I've done something inexcusable.
If I could have used you more skillfully, you wouldn't have died...
I can't believe he defeated Fayla...
What in the world is he?
I thought the girl had traveled alone all this time.
Did she get a partner?
Terrifying appetite...
Exercise makes me hungry.
Besides, I gotta eat when I can.
You've got money, right?
Mm-hmm.
No problem, then.
What are you doing here?
And where are the edible plants?
Just when I thought you'd finally gotten off your ass,
you bring back a girl instead of what I asked for?
You have me, and yet you're
eating breakfast with an innocent little girl like her?
You're pretty cocky.
You just sit around the house day in and day out,
refusing to do any work at all.
I'm the one earning all the money.
That's wrong.
What a terrible guy.
I've reached the end of my patience.
I feel for you.
It's not like that! Hang on! This is...
Say your prayers!
Hang on, Akari! You're mistaken!
How exactly am I mistaken?
Please, tell your stupid sister,
my dear Brother.
Brother?
Siblings?
Still, once a no-good brother, always a no-good brother.
You forget about your younger sister waiting for breakfast
and eat your fill without her.
Then you trash the place,
and push both the cost of food and
damages on a girl you just met?
I'm so appalled, I can't even bring myself to be angry.
You're like a loser in every respect.
Fayla attacked you?
Can I take your word on that?
Yeah. And she helped me kill it.
She's a wizard.
She's got a Gundo in that coffin.
See? This wound is proof that we fought.
And she bought be breakfast in return for showing her the way... to...
Work request.
Want saboteur siblings.
Work?
That's easy to say...
You don't intend to refuse, do you?
Well, I haven't worked in years...
Springing this on me now is kinda...
Would you rather work or let me have you stuffed?
Make your choice.
Those are my only options?
Or would you prefer that I stuffed you myself?
Aw, damn it!
I really have to work?
Welcome to my home.
I am Robert Abarth.
Albéric Gillette-dono, was it?
Yes.
I was surprised to see that you are so young.
I heard that you were employed by the Kliemann Organization,
so I expected an old man.
The Gillettes are a prestigious family.
May I ask why?
I carry out my job with pride and due responsibility every day.
Ah, forgive my rudeness.
Now, what brings you here?
While I fully realize that it's poor manners
to do so upon our first meeting,
I wish to ask a favor of you.
Oh?
I have heard that you were among the
Eight Heroes who took down Emperor Gaz.
That being said...
I want you to give me the article that you acquired in the
Battle for the Imperial Capital of the Gaz Empire.
Return the article, you say?
Yes.
Why must I do that?
Due to the confidential nature of that information, I cannot answer.
Hey!
Our guest is leaving now.
Count Abarth...
Of course, I understand how you feel.
However, this concerns the peace of not only the kingdom of Wiemac,
but that of the entire continent of Verbist.
Return it after all this time?
I don't think so.
Work, not take long! Easy!
Ruler, Count Abarth's manor. Attack.
Then seize!
Seize what?
Important thing.
When there, I will know.
You sure you're sane?
Sane. Need. Any cost.
What I must do.
What you must do?
Do!
Duty!
Mission! Absolute!
Even if forever...
Will try!
If you're planning to attack, you'll need to make preparations in advance.
Yeah.
I heard that the count comes from a military family,
but when I met him today,
something didn't seem right.
Meaning?
He didn't seem proficient with martial arts at all.
Did he lose his touch in the five years since the war?
And there's something strange about his mansion.
What do you mean?
There were far too few guards.
It's too lightly guarded for a lord's mansion.
That is curious.
Maybe that girl from before
came to this town because she knew Count Abarth
was one of the Eight Heroes...
And she has a partner now.
It's possible that she intends to go after the count's mansion.
Shall we keep an eye out?
Yes.
Please do.
What exactly are we supposed to steal?
She won't say, so we probably don't need to know.
We only need to do our job.
"Our job"...
It feels weird to hear that coming from you.
Anyway, how'd the west side look?
Its construction is the same as the east side.
I never thought we'd be going up against a lord.
Having second thoughts, Brother?
Who's having second thoughts?
I suppose.
Even with no weapons and not a scrap of clothing on you,
I'm sure you'd stand up against countless enemies without fear.
That'd just be stupid, on many levels.
Even if you are my brother,
I won't allow you to insult the Brother I so deeply respect!
Sorry. You're the stupid one.
As long as you understand.
That's okay with you?!
It shouldn't be too difficult to sneak in.
But the lord was a member of the first force to march
into imperial territory in the War of the Gaz Empire.
Which means he must be the militant type.
Maybe we should borrow her magic?
About that...
Are you sure we can trust her?
She's the one who asked for our help. It's not about trust—
No, I mean her skill as a wizard.
Oh, she's pretty impressive.
Whirl, flames! The Burner!
Bread... exploded...
Right. I see now.
It bothers me that there are so few guards, but oh well...
Stick to the plan.
Roger!
Jeez...
You've got your Gundo in there, don't you?
Must bring!
For crying out loud...
I am steel.
Steel knows no fear. Steel knows no doubt.
When faced with my enemy, I hesitate not.
I am a weapon to destroy thee.
Iron-Blood Transformation!
Akari, same as Toru!
Hang on tight.
There.
Open your coffin.
Damn...
For the love of...
Damn! Push harder, Akari!
I swear...
Rough handling...
So, what now?
What are we stealing?
I know, mostly.
No, we're asking you to tell us.
Find out soon.
Efun... Heluste... Ru... Belguil... Fai... Sev...
Come, resounding perception.
The Locator!
Important thing...
Center of mansion.
Found. Pale blue light.
All right. Let's split up.
I'll take the first floor.
Akari, you two take the second floor.
Understood.
Is this it?
So you did come.
You work for the Kliemann Organization, don't you?
It seems you are quite upset that I sent you away this afternoon.
What are you talking about?
No matter.
I was just thinking what a shame
it was that I never had a chance to use my treasure.
Damned thief.
You're a wizard?!
I'm nothing like the greenhorn cavalier that you answer to.
Brother!
Stay back! He's a wizard!
Wizard?!
Stay out of sight!
No...
It can't be...
You should be dead!
What?
jigoku no soko made nozoki kome
Let's take a peek at the bottom of hell
kuchite yuku no hanakara
It's rotting from the start
shitai mitai ni aruku michi
We're walking on the road like corpses
gira gira to taiyou ga teritsukeru
While the blazing sun beats down on us
omae wa itsuka namae sae
You'll fall into the depths of hell one day
wakaranaku naru kurai ochite yuku
And not even remember your name
hito wa naze ikiru no ka
Why do people live?
inochi kirikizan demo
Even when our life is in pieces
owarinaki bonnou wo daite odore ba
We embrace our endless desires and dance
mujou ka
Is that cruel?
kawaki no tani kara yojinobore
Climb up from the valley of thirst
kaze no oto ga kodama shite
You'll hear the echoing wind
goran warera wo michibiku kairaku wa
See, while the desires guide us
kanashimi wo tsukkitte iku genri
We have to push our way through sadness to get there
osoreru na
Do not be scared
furueru na
Do not tremble
ikiru no da
Live on
Journey, finally, begins!
Toru, work, serious?
Slightly worried.
Akari, somewhat strange.
Just as worried.
I gather remains, request support.
Next week, episode 2: "The Lazy Man's Choice."
The Lazy Man's Choice