I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but a sudden encounter changed everything.
I was given a red jewel from which
I gained magical powers.
My unexpected encounter has set two things in
motion, which are slowly building in intensity:
My intertwined feelings, and the beginning of this story.
This was when magic would first
begin to change my ordinary life.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin!
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
No way!
W-What's with this outfit?!
My magical incantation is "lyrical"?
W-What is this?
It's coming!
Protection.
Our magical device uses a "programming"
system that lets our magic take form.
And in order to make that system work,
its user needs to provide spiritual energy.
That thing was born from the source of disgusting and
abominable power, and took that form to protect itself.
To make it stop, you need to seal it with your
staff and return it to its original form.
I don't really understand, but how do I do that?
What you did before was one of your two types
of magic: attacking and defending.
They're basic forms of magic you activate
by wishing with all your heart.
But in order to summon enough power to
fully stop it, you'll need an incantation.
Incantation?
Listen to your heart.
I have no doubt that an incantation will come to you.
Protection.
Lyrical Magical.
If you attack and seal it correctly,
it should change back into a Jewel Seed!
Jewel Seed, Seal!
Sealing Mode, Set Up.
Stand by, Ready.
Lyrical Magical. Jewel Seed Serial XXI!
Seal!
Sealing.
That's a Jewel Seed.
Touch it with Raising Heart.
Receipt Number XXI.
Huh? It's over?
Yes, all thanks to you.
Thank you...
Hey! Are you all right? Come on!
If I'm seen here, I might get in trouble...
F-For now, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Ah, I woke you up? Sorry for being so rough.
Are you still hurt?
I'm fine now. I'm pretty much recovered.
You're right. Most of the wounds you
had have vanished. That's amazing.
Because you helped me out, I was able to use my
remaining magical power to help heal myself.
I don't really get it, but... I see.
Hey, is it okay if we formally introduce ourselves now?
Ah, yeah.
I'm Takamachi Nanoha.
A third-grade elementary school student.
My close friends and family call me Nanoha.
I'm Yuuno Scrya. Scrya is my family name,
so Yuuno's my first name.
Yuuno-kun, huh?
What a cute name.
I'm sorry... Miss...
You can call me Nanoha.
I'm sorry I've gotten you involved in this, Nanoha-san...
Ah, umm...
Um... I think I'm okay with this.
Ah, I forgot. Yuuno-kun, you're still a little
hurt, so you won't be able to rest here.
For now, let's go back to my house.
We can sort the other things out afterwards, okay?
Welcome home.
O-Onii-chan...
And just where have you been at this time of night?
Umm... that is... uh... er...
Oh, how cute!
O-Onee-chan?
Huh? You look pretty down.
Let me guess, you were worried and
went to check on him, right?
Umm... uh, that is...
It's not that I don't understand how you feel, but I still
can't believe you snuck out of the house like that.
Come on, it's all right.
She came home safely.
And Nanoha's a good girl,
so she won't do this again. Right?
Yeah...
Umm, Onii-chan... I'm sorry for sneaking
out and worrying you.
And there we are. Everything's all better.
At any rate, it sure is cute, isn't it?
I'm sure Mom will think it's so cute
and faint when she first sees it.
I'd say the probability of that is pretty high.
Good morning, Yuuno-kun!
Ah... good morning.
Well, for now, I'll say good job at
making it through the night.
L-Likewise.
Last night, when I showed Yuuno-kun
to Mom and Dad...
Ah! It's so cute!
It really is such a cutie, isn't it?
Mom! Please take it easy...
It's so cuuuute!
It certainly looks like a smart, long rodent, doesn't it?
It's called a "ferret," Dad.
I wonder if it can do any tricks?
Here, give me your hand.
It sure is a cool little smart guy, isn't it!
And there was a big fuss for some time.
After that, we discussed what to do for Yuuno-kun's
meals, and the whole fuss over him started again.
In the end, the two of us didn't really
get to talk much last night.
Are you used to calling me by my first name yet?
Yeah, Nanoha.
We only managed to get used to calling
each other by our first names...
...and to start talking like friends.
I need to get to school, so let me hear all about what's
going on with you when I get home, okay?
Ah, that won't be a problem.
Even if we're apart, we can still talk to each other.
You're a mage now, Nanoha.
Ah, this is like when you first called to me...
That's right. We can talk as long as
you have the Raising Heart with you.
Now try talking to me with your heart.
Umm...
Like this?
That's right. It's easy, right?
Y-You're right!
I'll tell you about a lot of things whenever you're free.
Like about me, magic, and the Jewel Seeds.
Okay.
Lyrical Nanoha!
Good morning!
Nanoha! Did you hear about
what happened last night?
What do you mean?
The vet we went to yesterday...
Apparently there was a car accident or something...
...and they said the wall was smashed in.
We've been worried about the ferret...
Yeah...
Umm, you see...
About that, you see...
I see!
So he's safe at your house, Nanoha!
But that's one incredible coincidence, isn't it?
To have met him on the street when
he was escaping from that mess...
Really!
It's not a lie! It's not a lie!
I've only slightly tweaked the truth!
And it looks like my family doesn't
mind having a pet ferret...
...so we're going to be taking care
of him at my house for now.
I see!
Now we just have to come up with a name for him.
Have you decided on one yet?
Yeah. His name is Yuuno-kun.
Yuuno-kun?
Yep. Yuuno-kun.
As I told you before, some kanji are formed
by using the "hen" and "tsukuri" radicals.
By combining these radicals, each kanji can hold many
different meanings, even if made of just one.
This is because each hen radical
has some meaning by itself...
...and each of the tsukuri radicals also have meanings.
For example, to write the word "person,"
you only have to use the ninben radical.
To write out the word "water,"
you use the sanzui radical.
And when writing out "wood,"
you use the kihen radical.
Now then, why don't I give you a short quiz on this?
Using these three hen radicals, what other words can
you think of by combining them with a tsukiru radical?
The Jewel Seeds are ancient relics of my world.
Originally, they were magical stones which could grant
the wishes of those who possessed them, but...
...sometimes the manifestations of their power
become unstable, like what happened last night.
Sometimes, they'll turn on the stone's user and devour
everything in the area, including the user's spirit.
There are times when people will misuse them and get
confused, which can also cause them to run wild.
So why was something so dangerous
in my neighborhood?
It's my fault...
On my home world, I'm an archaeologist.
And one day, I discovered something
in an old rock formation.
I sent a team of investigators to claim
it and put it into safekeeping.
But the ship that was taking it away had some
sort of accident, and there was a big disaster.
Twenty-one Jewel Seeds were scattered
across this world because of that.
And we've only managed to find two so far.
So there's another nineteen left, huh?
Stand.
By the way, don't you think your balsam
plants have grown a bit?
I wonder how many centimeters they've grown?
Let's see... maybe two?
No way! It's definitely grown three!
Huh? But wait a second...
From what you've told me so far, it's not really your
fault the Jewel Seeds got scattered here, right?
But I was the one who first found them...
So I have to find them all,
and return them to where they should be.
Somehow... somehow, I can relate to your feelings.
You sure are a diligent person, aren't you, Yuuno-kun?
Oh, that reminds me.
Have you all been filling out the surveys and
reading the caution forms correctly?
I certainly hope so, because if you mix up what's
a weed and what isn't, it'll be quite a problem.
And of course, please don't forget to write your name,
the date, and how much it grew on it, too.
Umm...
I'm terribly sorry about getting you involved last
night and making you help me like that...
I'd like to stay in your care for a while longer
as I rest and let my magical powers return.
Just a week... no, if I had just five days, all of my power
would return, so if I could stay with you until then...
If your powers do return, what will you do?
I'll leave to search for the rest of
the Jewel Seeds alone again.
I won't allow that.
Y-You won't allow that?
It's impossible for me to help you during normal school
and cram school, but I can help you out any other time.
But it'll be dangerous, like last night.
Well, we've already become acquainted,
and I've heard you entire story.
I just can't leave you alone now.
And if people in the neighborhood are going
to keep running into things like last night...
...it'll be a problem for everyone, right?
Yuuno-kun, you don't have anyone to help
you out when you're alone, right?
Being all alone is sad. Let me help you out.
"If someone's in need and you
have the power to help them..."
"...you should never hesitate to help them."
At least, that's what my dad taught me.
You seem pretty troubled, and I can
help you with my strength, right?
With my magical power...
Yeah...
Though I don't know if I can become a proper mage...
Bye bye!
You're already a great mage, Nanoha.
I'm sure you have an incredible amount
of talent, more than I do.
R-Really? I don't really get it yet myself...
but for now, teach me what you can?
Bye bye.
And I'll do my best, so...
Yeah. Thank you...
Now then, I'll be back at the house any minute now.
How about we eat some snacks
together when I get home?
Ah, yeah... thank you.
I wonder what kind of snacks we should have today?
Sorry!
Yuuno-kun, what was that just now?
A new Jewel Seed has been activated.
It's close!
What should we do?!
Let's stand up against it together. Help me!
Yeah!
Nanoha, the Raising Heart!
Ah, yeah!
It possessed an animal that was in the area.
W-What should I do?
It's a lot tougher when it has a stable form like this!
It'll be fine... probably.
Nanoha!
Activate the Raising Heart!
Ah! How do I activate it again...?
Start from "I, the one who accepted this
mission!" The activation password!
I don't remember that whole long thing!
I'll tell you again, so just repeat after me!
O-Okay!
Raising... Heart...
Stand by, Ready.
Set up.
She activated the Raising Heart
without even saying the password...!
Nanoha! Your protective clothes!
Barrier Jacket.
Nanoha!
Protect Condition: All green.
She took no damage from that impact...
As I thought, this girl has an
incredible amount of talent.
Ow... it didn't really hurt as much as I thought it would...
Umm... all I have to do now is seal it, right?
Raising Heart, please!
All right.
Sealing Mode.
Set up.
Stand by, Ready.
Lyrical Magical. Jewel Seed Serial XVI!
Seal!
Sealing.
Receipt Number XVI.
I wonder if it's all right now...
Yeah.
There's not much else we have to do now, like before.
Huh? I wonder if I tripped and hit my head...?
Good job... I guess?
Yeah. I'd say so.
The first day I, Takamachi Nanoha, started
out as a magical girl had finally ended.
I've made a new friend, Yuuno-kun.
I don't know much about him, magic,
or the dangers that will be coming.
Anyway, a whole lot has happened...
Well, I sure am hungry from all of that.
I guess for now, I just have to keep doing my best!
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
Somehow through everything,
I've become a mage.
I've had to do this and that
as a magical girl...
...and I'm really excited about it
I'm still Takamachi Nanoha but...
These kind of problems
have to come first!
Next time there'll be a problem
that involves the entire town!
This is looking really bad!
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Three:
The Town's in a Lot of Danger?
I, Lyrical Magical,
will do my best!