Rargh!
Oh, my...
Okay!
Hey.
What're you making?
Graduation Album
A graduation album!
Graduation album?
A School Living Club original!
Oh, how nice.
Megu-nee said albums are
better if they're drawn by hand!
You really suck at drawing though, Yuki.
S-Say what?
I see you're helping her, Miki-san.
On the condition that she took
care of her other duties.
Miki's drawings are really good,
unlike Yuki's scribbles.
The one reading a book is Miki, and...
Huh? Who's she?
A close friend of mine.
Class let out early that day,
but the sky was such a beautiful blue,
it felt like a waste to go straight home.
So we took a little detour.
C'mon, Miki!
Coming!
Where do you want to go?
There's this book I want to get...
Okay, the bookstore, then.
Can we go to the arcade after that?
Sure.
This is what the scene currently looks like.
Let's take sticker photos again.
There's a booth with new effects!
What is the cause of this widespread rioting?
Hang on, Kei.
School Living Club
#4
"Outing"
Thank you.
What?
Nothing.
Jeez, come on...
Malls really are the best!
I can't believe you still use a portable CD player.
Don't make fun of me! I'm telling you,
the audio quality is different!
How cute!
You like CDs better, too?
See?
Oh, Taroumaru, you found someone to play with?
I'm sorry. He's just so cute!
It's all right. Thank you for playing with him.
Now, say goodbye to the young lady.
Bye!
Take care.
Western books
Wow, you're going to read that?
I've already read the translated version,
so I think I can make sense of it.
What's happening?
Attention, all shoppers.
An incident resulting in injuries
has occurred in the building.
We are currently attempting
to secure the scene,
and we request all customers
follow mall staff directions...
That can't be good.
Is it a fire?
No way. For real?
Let's get out.
We'd better leave, too.
What's the holdup?!
The escalator's not running!
Don't push! People are getting
trampled at the bottom!
Looks like we can't go down.
That way.
Excuse me, are the elevators working?
I don't know. We just got here ourselves.
Oh, okay.
I don't think they're working.
It's stuck on the first floor.
It's moving...
I'm sure this is all some
kind of misunderstanding.
Yeah... Probably.
What was that? What's happening?!
Were those people in the elevator dead?
I think so. They were covered in blood.
People don't end up like that
from fires or minor accidents.
It's that puppy!
You're safe...
K-Kei, is he hurt?
No, he seems fine.
Then where'd the blood...
I didn't truly understand what
had happened until a little later.
I only knew it was the beginning of
something that could never be reversed.
Let's eat.
Do you think it's an epidemic?
Like in movies?
If they're sick, then someone will
make vaccines and medicines.
Foreign countries will send troops
and doctors and stuff, too.
Yeah.
No point in worrying about it.
You're right.
But no matter how much time
passed, help never came.
Not even the slightest sign of it.
Kei, what're you listening to?
The radio.
Oh, right. You get the radio on that, too.
Yeah, but...
For some reason, I can't even
get one station to come in.
Kei.
It's them!
I want to go outside...
You can't! It's dangerous!
But we don't know how long we'll be safe here!
Kei!
Okay, Miki.
I...
I want to go outside.
We've still got plenty of water and food here.
Let's try to hang in there until help comes.
No one will even know we're
here if we don't go out.
I want to take a shower, too...
We're lucky just to have running water here.
We only have those gross
little sinks in the bathroom!
Sorry... I...
The food will run out eventually.
What then?
We'll...
I guess I'm just being selfish.
Kei...
Bathroom.
I've got a brilliant idea!
What is it?
Something super-duper fun!
Okay, okay. What is it?
Loom
The three of us will...
Will what?
You'll find out the rest tomorrow!
You two are so loud...
Rage Rage
There, there. What happened?
Kurumi-chan's karate chop dented my skull!
Skulls don't dent!
No violence.
Sniffle.
Well, she was being all high-and-mighty.
But rather than just telling you now,
isn't it more fun knowing you'll
get a nice surprise tomorrow?
Fine. Just do this stuff before we go to bed.
She's right. We should get some sleep.
Okay!
Sleep!
But...
You're so noisy, we can't sleep.
Right, Rii-san?
Rii-san?
Only Rii-san...
What're you doing?
I'm leaving.
Leaving?
You're going outside?
Hey! Wait!
Miki, do you plan on living here forever?
I...
Taroumaru...
I should be okay if I go now.
Kei!
You want to be holed up in that
room forever, just staying alive?
Don't worry. I promise I'll bring help.
In the meantime, hold on to this for me.
Goodbye.
Shut up!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
Good morning!
Good morning, Yuki-chan.
Rice!
I've got canned food to go with it.
Pick whichever kind you like.
Ginger soy beef!
I thought we were out.
Morning.
Kurumi-chan, look at this! Ginger soy beef!
Y-Yeah...
Beef for breakfast! Wh-What luxury!
What decade are we in?
Savor it. That's our last can.
Hey, why don't we share it?
You can have it, Yuki-chan.
No way! If it's the last one,
we should all split it.
All right, then we'll split the
other cans three ways, as well.
Yeah.
Okay!
Let's dig in!
Yummy...
You're in a good mood this morning, Yuki-chan.
Yeah! I had a great idea last night.
Oh? What might that be?
Let's go on an outing! A club outing!
An outing?
It's the season for school outings, right?
Yuki-chan...
Great idea, right?
That's bad manners.
Oops.
And have you forgotten?
The School Living Club rules forbid
our leaving the school grounds.
I found a loophole.
We can't leave the school.
But there are exceptions!
Official school functions
don't count as leaving!
Smug
Right? Right?
No, it doesn't make sense.
Clubs don't go on their own outings.
You can be such a stiff, Kurumi-chan.
We'll be the ones to blaze the trail!
I see... Then we'll write a proposal.
Megu-nee will need to approve.
Ta-da!
School Living Club Outing
I believe that since outings are school functions,
the same classification applies to club activities.
There are many things to study outside.
Plus, it'll be super fun!
School Living Club - Takeya Yuki
I already wrote one.
Okay... I guess we'll have her look it over.
Yeah!
Thanks for cooking.
I'll go get Megu-nee!
Well, what should we do?
Wait for Megu-nee.
We'll leave it up to Yuki.
She's become very proactive lately.
Yeah, she seems to be in good spirits.
Plus, we need stuff that
we can't get around here...
Yes, that is important.
Staff Room
The problem is transportation.
I guess we'll have to use Megu-nee's car.
She said it's okay!
That's wonderful, Yuki-chan.
I guess it's settled, then.
The four of us can fit in my car.
We get to ride in your car, Megu-nee?
But I haven't driven in a long time,
so I'm a bit nervous.
Why don't I drive, then?
Kurumi-chan, you can drive?
It'll be fine! I guarantee
I'm a better driver than Megu-nee.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Hey, hey!
Oh, sorry, Megu-nee...
Well, it's probably a good idea for Kurumi
to learn to drive just in case, right, Sensei?
I... I suppose so...
When did you get your license, though?
Yuki-chan, go get the car keys.
Okay!
M-My car...
School
Leave here        Home Ec room
Entrance
Parking Lot         Athletic Field
The closest safe route to the parking lot
is the Home Ec room by
the second floor barricade.
Taking the ladder down from there
is the shortest distance to the car.
You're going to sprint with
a shovel on your back?
No problem.
No problem
I'm back!
Is everyone ready?
All set, right?
Here's Megu-nee's car key.
Thanks.
Be careful.
Sure. See you later.
Ready...
Go!
The stairs are closed for repairs?
Yes.
The entrance is being repaired, too?
Other classes are still in session, so keep quiet.
Okay.
Kurumi...
Crap! Which one's Megu-nee's?
Calm down, calm down...
There!
Oh, no!
So-rry...
a-bout...
this!
Hang on tight.
Wait! Seatbelts!
Wait, wait!
Please try not to crash my car.
Kurumi-chan, you're sure you can drive?
It's a bit of a different feel than I'm
used to, but no need to worry.
Feel?
I prefer game pads to
steering wheel controllers.
You mean for video games?
It'll be fine! Check out this perfect spin!
No spinning in my car!
Kurumi!
I've got this!
It's bumpy! Are they working
on the road, too?!
We're outta here!
It was like the ending to
a movie I once saw...
Two people driving off
toward the distant horizon,
abandoning their pasts and
setting off into the sunset.
It was just like that.
Where's Taroumaru?
Taroumaru?
Next Time!!
Megu-nee, you love that bear, huh?
This is Guma-chan! Isn't he cute?
Megu-nee, you really are...
What?
...a child at heart.
I'm your teacher!
Next time on Episode 5 of
SCHOOL-LIVE, "Meeting."
#5
Meeting