Finally, I can begin!
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
#06 Lastation's Secret (For Your Eyes Only)
Whoa!
Close shave.
Barely made it!
I'm bored!
Play with me,
Neptuna!
How many times do I gotta tell you, P-ko?
My name's not "Neptuna." It's Neptune!
Neptuna! Neptuna!
Hey!
Don't just yank the plug out like that!
Huh?
Play with me, Neptuna!
Zoinks!
Those two get along like a house on fire.
She's just running rings around poor Neppy.
Histoire,
have you still not found her guardians?
No.
She's been here for three weeks now.
Don't we have any leads at all?
No idea.
Why did she recognize the two of us?
Maybe we should count ourselves lucky that we even found out what her name was.
Yes.
It's a good thing her underwear had the name "Peashy" on it.
Gotcha!
P-Punch!
How's this, Nepgear?
Nice and soft, right?
Yes, Vert.
You can call me Sis if you like, you know.
But my Sis is—
Oh, forget it.
I think I could get used to you being my Sis!
Of course.
And, uh...
I see things have gotten crazy out here too.
The Lily Rank's gone through the roof!
Hey, Vert!
Whaddaya think yer doin' to my kid sister?!
Sis!
What's the problem with getting a little closer to each other every now and then?
"Every now and then"? More like every day!
Nepgear's my kid sister, you hear me?
You sound like a meddling sister-in-law.
Let's keep strengthening our bond, okay, Nepgear?
I actually came here to offer you an invitation.
What? You wanna capture me too?
Are you going for the sisters route?
Zoinks!
Not quite.
Blanc contacted you, didn't she?
She did?
What do you think?
This is Clatter, a long-eared bandicoot.
He's a recent addition to the family.
So cute.
Lemme hold him!
Well?
What do you wanna talk about?
Simply put, we need to talk about network security.
Oh, so you want to base yours off Lastation's unbreakable digital defenses?
Uh...
But of course!
I did spare no expense in hiring the best staff possible to create an impregnable firewall!
Does it also protect the satellite system you put into operation recently?
Indeed.
I could let you copy it,
but let me be honest. It'll cost you.
There are traces of the satellite being hacked into from a server in Lastation.
Excuse me?!
Like I said, there are traces—
Impossible!
A security breach is about as likely as being randomly hit by someone falling from the sky.
Move! Move! Move!
Outta the waaay!
Phew, that was lucky.
Goodness gracious.
How could you be careless enough to plummet from the sky and hit someone?
Sorry, my bad.
P-ko started making a fuss while I was flying over here,
and I ended up reverting by mistake.
Show some self-control!
Sorry.
Oh, yeah.
Introduce yourself, P-ko.
It's me, P!
I never knew you had a child this old, Neptune.
Yeah.
She's the first one I gave birth to, so she's extra-specially-precious to me!
Wait a sec!
She's a lost child who we're taking care of at our Basilicom!
I figured as much.
Holy drumsticks! Blanc actually played the fool!
Rom, Ram.
Be friends with her.
'Kay!
Let's go play.
Okay! I'll play!
Freeze!
Anyway, about what we were discussing earlier...
Let's go someplace else.
Uni.
Hold the fort for a bit, okay?
O-Okay.
Um, Nepgear...
I could use your advice on something.
Noire's been acting weird?
She's been locking herself in her office every night, doing something.
Are you sure she's not just working?
She wouldn't lock the door if she was.
Sometimes I even hear this weird laughter from inside.
I'm kinda worried.
So basically, you want to know what Noire's doing in there on her own?
That's what it boils down to, I guess.
I've got just the thing for you, then.
I just happened to bring this with me.
What is it?
It's an inconspicuous gadget that wirelessly transmits images!
A hidden camera, you mean.
This tiny little thing can compress and transmit HD video in real time!
Isn't it awesome?
I've been wanting to set it up some time and see how it works!
U-Uh...
I can do it here, right?
Bwahahaha!
What's so funny?
It's just, you were bragging about it every chance you got!
You were like, "Lastation's security is the best in the world!"
Bam!!
And now you've got a security breach?
My sides!
There's no use crying over spilled milk.
What's important is to make sure it doesn't happen again.
That, and...
Catching the the person responsible, right?
Whoa, Noire's in serious mode!
I figured something like this might happen, so I brought in a specialist to help us out.
Come in.
A super-duper programmer who's the pride and joy of Leanbox:
Ms. Setag.
Ms. Setag?
Who was that, again?
An original character! It's happening!
Greetings. I'm the one billed as Setag.
Billeased to make your acquaintance.
B-Bill?
A character that makes such terrible puns in this day and age?!
This one's gonna flop worse than Windows Me!
No need to worry.
After this scene is over, I bill never show up again.
Would you be able to identify the culprit?
Billeave it to me.
This looks like a good spot.
Or maybe putting it here would give us a better angle.
Well, she looks like she's enjoying herself.
Nah, it's gotta be here!
It's coming this way!
Watch out! You'll get tagged!
Freeze!
All done!
Hey, it works!
That sure is a clear image.
Doesn't it look good?
It uses NPEG-4, a cutting-edge codec,
to transmit HD images in perfect detail!
H-Huh?
What's wrong?
I'm starting to feel like we're doing something really bad.
Maybe we should take it down.
Yeah, you're right.
Don't go that way!
Sis will get mad!
What's going on?
It's a cross-connection.
Wait...
That means there are other hidden cameras in that room!
What?
Whaaat?!
I think we're close.
I'm so mad!
How dare they spy on Sis?
I'm gonna beat them black and blue!
It almost sounds like you're talking to me.
Well?
Tell us which building we're looking for, Nepgear!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Unfortunately, this reverse tracing device only shows the approximate location.
That so?
Time to kick down every door in sight, then.
Still, I'm surprised you had that thing on you.
Did you just happen to bring that too?
Actually, I never leave home without it.
Portable chargers and tracing equipment are must-haves for any girl.
In what universe?
Nepgear!
I'm hungry!
Is that so?
What now?
I'm hungry! Hungry! Hungwy!
You're such a baby, Peashy.
I'm a big girl now.
I can put up with being hungry for a while.
Me too. I'm a big girl.
I'm a big girl too!
Can you put up with it, then?
I will.
Pat, pat.
You two are so cool.
So they suddenly act all grown-up
when there's a younger kid around.
Huh?
Look, it's our sisters.
What's going on?
Say, Noire.
We didn't have to take action ourselves.
We could've had security take care of it.
That'd just be boring.
If whoever did this thought they could make a fool out of me,
they'll think twice when I pound their stupid face in!
Noire's so aggressive today.
I like it.
That's the place, ain't it?
That's the hideout that Ms. Setag identified.
All right!
Let's go find the culprit.
Keep it down, dammit!
They'll run away if they find out we're here!
Is this where the "look who's talking" goes today?
They went in here, didn't they?
Y-Yeah.
Maybe they're going after the voyeur too?
Clatter!
He ran away!
Peashy!
Freeze!
Put your hands up and turn around slowly.
You're the hacker, I take it?
Answer me. Now!
Oh, don't be such a stranger, sweetie.
Call me Anonydeath!
Zoinks!
A d-drag queen? With that appearance?
Goodness, how rude.
My heart is more ladylike than any other!
Yep, drag queen. Way too obvious.
And I'd imagine he has a bit of a foul mouth, too.
Bingo.
Looks like I was wrong to assume you were some tits-for-brains bimbo.
Who gives a damn about your gender?
Are you gonna own up to your crimes or not?
What?
You're so cute in person.
So much cuter than I imagined.
You can't distract me by saying things like that!
Oh, please.
I'm serious, sweetie.
Serious.
I'm so sorry I took all these pictures!
Noire here!
Noire there!
Noire here, there and everywhere!
Where are you, Peashy?
Clatter!
Where could they have gone?
Peashy!
I'm a huge fan of yours, Noire.
I wanted to learn more about you so badly that I just couldn't help myself.
I don't care about these pictures.
What I do care about is the hacking!
You don't care, you say?
So you don't care about these either?
Noire's sewing!
I never knew you were that kinda person.
I am!
Surprise! I'm rather family-oriented, you see.
These clothes look familiar.
It's just your imagination!
I'm absolutely, positively sure it's just your imagination!
Hey!
I told you these weren't the problem here!
Oh?
Is this what you meant, then?
Whoa! What're these?
Pictures of her cosplaying, clearly.
Oh, so that outfit was from Four Goddesses Online.
Don't look!
The way you panic is cute too!
An exclusive!
D-Damn you.
Have it your way!
I'm gonna throw you in the slammer for peeping!
Oh my.
If I should ever leave this place, all these pictures will be automatically sent around the world.
Are you okay with that?
Huh?
I originally wanted to keep them all for myself,
but covering the world in Noire sounds delightful in its own way.
This is a tough decision to make.
If these pictures were leaked...
...I'd be too embarrassed to show my face in public.
What's the big deal?
Noire looks super cute in these.
You don't sound like you mean it.
Fine!
Go ahead!
But you'll pay for it with your life!
This is how it's got to be.
Dammit.
The monitors are coming our way!
This was fun, Noire.
Oh, and I was lying about leaking the pictures,
so don't you worry.
Hold it right there!
I was able to meet Noire in person.
One little hideout's a small price to pay for that.
Dreams come true!
Huh? What?
Nooo! Get away from me!
Heeey!
Clatter!
Look, it's Peashy and Clatter!
What's wrong with you, Peashy?
Sorry about this.
Sorry.
Geez. What are you teaching this kid?
Peashy?
Is your name Peashy?
Yup. It's me, P!
Sis?
So you're the peeping tom?!
Whoops!
Getting those prints made of my favorites came back to bite me!
You'll pay for this!
You're not getting away, you damn tranny!
Huh? Uni?
Sis?
Oh, all right.
I give up.
He never owned up to the hacking.
Well, he got caught, so all's well that ends well.
Looks like Noire's got bigger fish to fry now, anyway.
You saw them?
Did you see these pictures?
Er, w-we didn't—
Yup!
We saw all of them!
What's "cosplay"?
Wait, why are you guys even here in the first place?!
I'm done with this!
Listen up.
You are all to forget everything you saw here.
Got it?
And you, Uni!
You should know better than to come to a place like this!
P-ko!
Ta-dah!
Delish Pudding
Nep's
Wanna eat?
I smuggled it in with me.
Yeah! I'll eat it!
Oh, but we're going halfsies, okay?
Okay!
Halfsies with Neptuna!
Hello.
It's me.
I found you-know-who.
I'd gone through the trouble of hacking into a satellite,
but then I found her easily through other means.
What?
Yeah...
Say, Uni...
You don't like me cosplaying, right?
I don't mind quitting if you want me to.
Nah.
Don't quit.
You can only do that because you're not too tied down with work, right?
I guess.
I've had some more free time lately.
That made me feel like I'd become a little bit more useful.
I wonder about that.
"A little bit"? Please.
You've been a great help!
Sis!
Move! Move!
Move!
Egad!
What was that noise?
Zoinkers!
Ouch!
Wh-Who're you?
Huh?
Oh, me?
I'm Plutia.
Planeptune's CPU.
Whaaaaat?!
I've come to this universe of countless stars
To start our search for the ultimate game
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
What are you getting so serious for?
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
I get you. I really do
It's not love
But there's desire
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Let's start a New Game+
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
This rectangle pulse
is a love song
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Friendship, love, bifrost
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
Good job, my sweet heart
See you next week!
Impossible!
A security breach is about as likely as being randomly hit by someone falling from the sky.
Move!
What?!
The Fruit (Deep Purple) of Revenge
I was standing in the right place, okay?!