Let's see...
"...I have spent whole days before this inkstone, with nothing better to do,
jotting down at random whatever nonsensical..."
The student council president is so amazing!
Okay, that'll do.
Well then, who can interpret what he just read?
Tsubomi!
Erika, you try interpreting it.
What?! Me?!
Let's see...
Ms. Tsurusaki!
Erika was only trying to get me to pay attention!
I'll interpret it! I mean, please let me interpret it!
Well, if you say so, Tsubomi. I guess that's fine.
Sorry about that, Erika.
"With nothing to really do, I sit at my desk and think to myself
of all those pointless and silly things, and incoherently write them.
It feels so very strange, as though something has exhausted me."
Very well interpreted.
Essays in Idleness is something my grandma used to read to me when I was in primary school, so...
I see.
Well then, who shall we have go next...
I think...
Erika.
Whaaaaat?!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
You made interpreting that look so easy, and without doing any studying either!
And you're great at science too! You're really amazing, Tsubomi!
Really, it's all thanks to my grandma.
Oh, that's right. She runs the
botanical gardens, doesn't she?
Yeah.
More importantly, Tsubomi... why were you spacing out earlier?
Huh?
W-Well, that was because...
It's the student council president!
Shoot!
It seems you know why I'm here, Kurumi.
Uh, yes! About the club roster, right?
The submission deadline has already passed, you realize.
If you don't hand it in by the end of the day, I'll
have no choice but to disband the Fashion Club.
No way!
That's how it is. If you'll excuse me, then.
He's so manly!
Wh-What am I gonna do?!
I only need to find three more members...
Toshiko, Naomi, Rumiko!
Please join the Fashion Club!
I'm begging you!
It's not that simple, ya know...
I do have an interest in style,
but not enough to join a club...
We can do something about that!
Oh, I know!
How about a 20% discount at our shop?
Give us a little more!
Well, in that case...
I'll throw in our special Fairy Drop-Style Notebook!
Whoa!
We're in!
Thank goodness...
Welcome to the group!
My Beloved Student Council Prez!
A Maiden's Heart Laid Bare!
Student Council Office
Kurumi and Hanasaki from the Fashion Club coming in!
Um... is the president here?
Myoudouin just went home, I'm afraid.
We've brought the roster for the Fashion Club, you see, and...
We've already decided to disband the Fashion Club, I'm afraid.
No way!
We've had so many class duties to take care of that we ran late, that's all!
Myoudouin is not the type of person to overturn an already-made decision.
The president had been holding out for you, even though the deadline had passed.
Even today, the president waited for you as long as possible before leaving...
Erika... what do we do?!
We have no choice but to head to the president's home and engage in face-to-face negotiations!
Itsuki is currently engaging in martial arts training with our fellow pupils, I'm afraid.
We'll wait as long as we have to!
There's something we need to
discuss, and it has to be today!
Very well, then.
Once his training has finished, I shall call Itsuki for you.
Thank you very much.
This is annoying... I really suck at sitting on my legs like this.
Wow! He's so cool!
He's just too cool...
Oy.
Hrm?
What's the matter?
You'll regret falling for the student council president, you know?
Huh?
Wh-What are you saying?!
Oh, I'm sorry...
Let me warn you: The student council president is...
Us gossiping will distract him from his practice, you know.
Could this rush in my heart be...
my first love?!
I'm telling you...
I can't stop this, even if I wanted to!
My love only grows stronger!
...I'm not taking the blame for this.
That shall suffice.
You have some visitors.
He's coming closer. What do I do?!
Kurumi?
You have some business with me?
Oh, right!
My legs fell asleep...
Erika, are you all right?!
Y-Yeah...
Um... President!
Let's talk about this outside, all right?
Please don't disband the Fashion Club!
As you can see, we've completed our roster!
However, the board of directors has already approved the list of clubs.
But you told us we had to get it to you by the end of the day!
We just got delayed by our duties, that's all!
Tsubomi, what are you doing?
You need to ask as well!
We're begging you! Please don't disband the Fashion Club!
I suppose I did have to leave early, what with today being a training day at our dojo...
Very well then.
I'll talk with the board of directors again and make sure the Fashion Club is allowed to continue.
Thank you so much!
We did it!
Thank goodness!
M'lady...
I brought you some tea.
Oh, thank you.
Would you two like some?
Oh, yes please!
M'...
M'lady?!
The president's a girl.
Everyone at school knows that.
I tried to tell you, but you didn't listen.
You only just transferred here, didn't you, Hanasaki?
Due to the situation here, I may adopt a male appearance, but I am indeed a girl.
I see...
I seeeeeee!
That's why I said you were better off leaving well enough alone.
I can't believe the student council president was a girl...
My first love lies broken after only three minutes!
I guess all I can say is...
It's great that we can keep the Fashion Club going!
That's it?! You're my friend! You're supposed to cheer me up!
Well, you know... First loves are meant to be bittersweet!
I... don't think I'll ever recover from this!
Stop here, please.
I heard some friends of yours came by.
Yeah.
You mean Kurumi's club?
It's quite unusual for you to have female
friends come by, so it kinda surprised me.
They aren't... really friends.
I'd like it if you could get along
better with other girls, you know.
Brother...
Because my body is so weak, it's left the entire burden of the Myoudouin name on your shoulders, but—
S-Sorry...
Brother...
I said... No, I swore I'd look after you until the very end.
I'm fine living the way I do.
So please, don't worry yourself over it.
Just don't overdo it.
You wish to go and defeat the Precure?
Last time, I merely made introductions.
I assure you that this time, I shall defeat them most magnificently.
Very well.
Then I beg your leave.
What?! She's taking the day off from school?!
She has a fever from the shock of finding out the student council president was a girl...
I guess it's understandable.
When I was a first year, the exact same thing happened to me.
Tell her to get better soon, anyway!
You got it!
Myoudouin!
Please accept these tokens of our affection!
Thank you very much.
Well excuse us then!
A man more beautiful than me exists?
C'est impardonnable...
Even the peony Flower of his Heart is beautiful...
I thought even his heart would be perfectly beautiful,
but it seems I can make use of him after all.
I-It's so cute!
Embracing your feminine side?
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
A handsome man embracing a doll like that...
is beautiful indeed!
He cut Bunny's ear!
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
It's the student council president!
Let us dye this peony with impeccable darkness!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
We can't let it run wild around school!
Go, Seed of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
Staaaaatue!
Nooooooooo!
This style of girl's uniform is just so cute!
I... I...
I want to wear one too!
Huh?
Do you know what you're saying?
But I'm...
a girl!
Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!
S-Somebody help me!
Stop that at once!
Statue!
Hurry and run!
R-Right!
Thank you so much!
So you show yourself at last.
Desertrian, defeat the Precure!
She's so cuuuuute!
You fool!
This really isn't the damn time for that!
Hurry up and defeat the Precure!
Staaaaaaaatuuuueee!
Ms. Tsurusaki!
At this rate, everyone'll get turned to stone...
The student council president?!
You must hurry to Cure Marine's aid!
Right!
President!
I'll purify you and return you back to normal!
Marine Dive!
She's strong...
Très bien!
Even if you are a girl, you certainly live up to your tomboy image.
Wh-What's with that look?!
I am a Commander of the Desert Apostles, I'll have you know!
What's wrong with me liking dolls, huh?!
Just because I have to become an amazing martial artist like my brother, I'm not allowed to like cute things?!
I just want to do things a normal girl would do! I
want to be stylish, to play the piano, and do ballet!
I really love cute things!
So those are your true feelings...
They forced those feelings you kept locked in your heart to the surface, and turned you into a Desertrian...
I've had it up to here with this!
Marine! Let's hurry and purify her!
Yeah!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
What just happened?
We did it!
Where am I?
The student council office.
You collapsed by the statue of the chairman, so we brought you here.
Is that what happened? Thank you.
I feel like I've been having this nightmare.
Um... President?
Would you like to join the Fashion Club?
Huh? Why?
Why should I have to join the Fashion Club?
I'd be a laughing stock...
Tsubomi?
I've been thinking.
All the work you do for the student council...
And all the training you do for your martial arts... They exhaust you, don't they?
If you joined the Fashion Club, I think it'd help you relax a little.
Thank you.
I'll think about it.
By the way...
where's your uniform?
Huh?
She's pretty careless about remembering to consider her appearance, I'm afraid.
You'll have to excuse us!
President!
Hey.
Huh?
What's with the doll?
I've taken a liking to it for some reason.
I guess even you have your girly side, Myoudouin.
I guess I do!
I think a Heart Seed is going to be born...
In the language of flowers, a peony represents
"The nobility, style, and modesty of a monarch."
It's perfect for the student council president!
Yeah, the language of flowers stuff is cool and all, but...
You do realize you're still in your pajamas, right?
I'll go change!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
Everyone's talking about the famous model, Momoka!
She's so cute and gorgeous, I really admire her!
She's really not that great.
Really? I think she's really amazing!
Bland, bland, totally bland!
You're in a really bad mood, Erika.
Hmph! Just cause she's pretty and kinda stylish,
she gets to be a popular model and doll around in all these fancy clothes!
We're sisters, so why do we have to be leagues apart like this?!
HeartCatch Precure:
What is the Cause
of the Charismatic Model's Sighing?
We'll catch everyone's hearts!