All that aside...
I never thought Ai would be the one to save us.
As far as helpers go, she really comes in handy!
But this is no time to be all smiles.
True. We have to find the queen.
You're right.
Excuse me!
Wh-What?
Um, Aida!
Y-Yes?
Please make me your disciple!
Di...
Disciple?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
So...
you're Saotome Jun from the first year's class B, right?
Oh, Yashima, sorry for stealing your seat!
Don't worry.
Oh, yes!
I'm asking because I realized that being your disciple would be a dream come true!
What's a disciple?
Disciples follow around someone they respect
and learn as much as they can from them!
Another one?
Another what?
A lot of students respect Mana,
so stuff like this isn't rare.
So, what made you want to be my disciple?
Well, it happened yesterday.
So heavy...
Are you all right?
Huh?
Let me help.
No, I...
Where to? The library?
Well, yes...
Oh, um, sorry!
Don't sweat it.
I'll handle this.
You looked so strong and reliable...
You were like Prince Charming on a white horse!
What's the horse for?
I want to be a tough, strong guy, just like you, Aida!
Mana's not a guy, either...
I beg you,
please make me your disciple!
Okay.
"Okay?"
Really?
Sure.
If I can help you, I will!
Thank you so much!
Another pain in the neck...
She couldn't reject him...
that's so Mana.
I, Saotome Jun, swear to be the best disciple you've ever seen!
Mana's Determination!
I'll Take a Disciple!
I can't make heads or tails outta all this ruckus!
Line up!
I'm too late!
Guess I'm going without my noodle sub today...
You want a noodle sub?
Pres!
I'll just buy two.
Caf lady!
Got any noodle subs?
Oh, Mana!
Just sit tight!
I'm kinda short on hands!
Then let me help!
Just wait a bit.
Huh? But what about his...
Hey, excuse me, pardon me...
I'll help!
Excuse me, excuse me!
You okay?
Now, what's your order?
Variety sandwich and orange juice!
I want a croquette sandwich!
I'll have a ham sandwich with strawberry milk!
Chocolate bread and milk!
Croquette sandwich and juice here!
Cutlet sandwich and orange juice!
Here, a variety sandwich and orange juice.
Croquette sandwich, strawberry milk, and a ham sandwich.
Chocolate bread and milk,
Croquette sandwich and apple juice,
Cutlet sandwich and orange juice.
Your respective changes are 50 yen, 40 yen, and 240 yen.
Enjoy!
Aida's really something.
We're sold out!
Here.
Sweet!
Thanks, Pres!
Enjoy!
You're a lifesaver, Mana.
Don't mention it.
So, what about your lunch?
Guess you forgot.
You're really something.
You gave up your own lunch for others!
Your kindness knows no depths!
Madam Rikka!
Okay, I'll give you part of mine.
What's wrong?
Aida!
Are you all right?
Yes...
Let's go to the infirmary.
Now she's helping someone else.
I'll help too!
Thank you, Pres.
Good thing it wasn't anything serious.
Doctor!
Oh, what's wrong?
Aida, I hate to be a bother,
but could you take the papers on the desk to the staff room?
Sure!
Huh?
You callin' me a punk, punk?
Punk, you callin' me a punk, punk?
Now now, settle down!
They just keep coming...
I'll help!
First Term Club Budget Allocation
Baseball Team
Soccer Team
Tennis Team
Basketball Team
Pedestrians Crossing
Solitaire
I'm back, Ai!
You take care of a baby, too?
Yeah.
Wanna hold her?
Huh?
Yes! I'll do what I can!
Here.
Sh-She's quite heavy...
Don't do that, Ai!
Oh no, it's nothing.
Look, Ai!
Ai!
Rikka, I know what to do!
I see!
Yo! Checka Racka!
You seem tired.
No surprise. He's been going at Mana's pace.
It's best to eat candy when you're tired.
Please, take some.
Thanks.
Wh-What is it?
You're a real fighter, Jun.
Oh no, I'm nothing compared to you.
But really, today's been pretty busy, huh?
Maybe.
But it was fun!
Fun?
Yeah.
Doesn't it feel nice to make someone happy and get thanked in return?
Nice...
Yup.
I've barely been able to catch my breath,
so I didn't notice...
Can I really change myself...
to be like her?
Yeah, I can, as long as I try!
I have just the thing for one as resilient as you.
So your dreams may come true,
I present you with this Lovies.
Th-Thank you very much.
Curse those Precures...
You had to go into Beast Mode?
My, someone's a hard worker.
I had no choice.
And neither do you two.
Hey, I've just been toyin' with them until now.
That's right!
I've been busy, too!
King Selfish's wrath is vicious.
And with that attitude, you'll get more than a slap on the wrist.
Fine...
This time,
I won't be playing around!
That's cheap.
As long as you hit 'em, who cares?
Precures...
I swear I'll crush you!
Will you you read all of these?
Yeah.
They look like they'll help with what we were asked to do,
so I'll skim them.
You're really something.
I'll take the higher books.
Sorry...
He's hanging in there.
Well, he's a hard worker.
But he seems kinda down.
Whoa!
That serve was just like my next opponent's!
Like that?
Yes, please!
That's our president.
I can't serve like that...
Well, good luck with your match!
I'll carry that!
Well...
It's heavy today, so I'll carry it.
Alice!
Good afternoon, everyone.
Were you helping Mana today?
Yes.
Well, good work.
Good work, huh?
But I didn't...
My hat!
I'll get it!
I'll help!
I'm too small,
too slow,
and too weak!
No matter how hard I try,
I could never be like her.
I want to be bigger and stronger!
More than she is!
But I know I can't...
Aw, sure you can.
I will grant your desire.
Jun!
It's you!
Guess I gotta lift a finger every now and then.
Grant me your darkness!
Wait. What happened?
That's...
an elephant.
Sure is.
Why, it certainly is!
It's...
cute.
What a cute elephant!
Don't call me cute!
It's dangerous here, so run!
Okay!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor elephant who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Cut it with that "heart" junk!
Heart!
He's strong.
But he's so cute...
Don't call me cute!
You still wanna go?
Just so we're clear, I'm not messin' around today.
No kidding!
I have to save Jun!
Save him from what?
I'm just granting his deepest desire, see?
I want to be strong...
big, and strong...
You heard him.
This is what he wished for.
It's not!
Jun didn't want it to be this way!
But I can never be like you!
Which Mana were you following around?
You think you can be like her with strength alone?
Of course you can't!
Mana wasn't always perfect!
But she wanted to help, so she kept trying!
And she still does!
It was never about being able or unable.
Deep in her heart, Mana simply wanted to help others!
Her heart is what's strong!
You're all too kind...
I always slip and fall on my face...
Just like you, Jun.
Tough luck!
The kid can't hear a word you say!
It's over!
I missed?!
How?
What?!
I can't move my leg!
The psyche!
I see!
Jun's heart is fighting back!
I knew you could do it...
Even if you can't be like me,
you're amazing in your own way!
Sit down and shut up!
Now it's over!
What?
Jun, the way you put your all into everything...
makes my heart race!
That's why...
I won't let you have his heart!
Give Jun...
back!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Precure Diamond Shower!
Precure Heart Shoot!
Jun just wanted to be strong, so he worked hard for it!
There's absolutely nothing selfish about that!
Cure Heart...
Huh? What was I...
Simply taking a nap.
Something wrong?
No...
I haven't seen him lately.
What's Jun been up to?
They're so pretty!
But was this flower bed always here?
Do you like it?
Jun!
Wait, did you make this?
Yes.
Gardening's a hobby of mine,
so I planted some flowers I grew.
These is all yours?
Yes.
I realized something.
I can't be as strong as the president.
But...
I thought it'd be nice if my flowers could make others smile.
I think this is what I wanted all along.
Oh, I'm sorry!
I was the one who asked to be your disciple,
but here I am...
No, it's amazing, Jun!
It's great that you made this!
I'm in tears!
Maybe you should take a disciple.
Huh?
Well, uh...
I dunno...
I'm glad Jun's smiling.
So, they're the Precures.
I think I've found a fun playmate.
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
This rose only bloomed in Trump Kingdom, but now it's in our world?
There might be a clue to my queen!
Dokidoki Precure:
We've Finally Found It?!
A Clue Leading To The Queen!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!