Welcome to the Velvet Room.
I see you've formed yet another new bond after overcoming a fierce battle.
It's the Lovers Arcana.
I'm sure this power will come in handy.
The Lovers, huh?
As it blooms, romance can enrich the heart,
but if it's pushed too far...
it'll prick you.
Glaciers of ideas, importing
To my friends, then exporting
To the next, keeping it open
We want no closing
Even without those, our thoughts can be duped
This mind trade no one can stop
An act of thinking is terrible to stop
We just wanna change it up, not drop
And my crew can rock it like uprock
Life is tedious if it ain't flowing
Copy and paste? Constant defaulting?
Put my courage to it
Begin showing off
That's the way we wanna live
Keep going, yeah!
What was so much of transparency
Turned into bright expectation
Instinct tells me to keep going together, going together
It's breathtaking moments in life
Addicted to it, minds craving more and more
I'm believing you and I can do anything
We can change the world
The sky's the limit, we can spread wings
to roadless travel, together we go
Slim Body
It's his fault.
His fault! His, dammit!
Well? Did you see that?
I did it! I'm amazing.
Isn't this supposed to be a peaceful town?
Dojima?
Serial murders, huh?
Dammit!
What the hell?
I thought the victims were limited to people shown on TV!
I never saw King Moron on TV before.
He didn't even appear on the Midnight Channel.
Damn, why'd this happen?
I thought we figured some stuff out, but maybe it was all a big coincidence.
The Midnight Channel might not even be related to the murders.
That can't be.
Then why's King Moron dead?
I don't know.
M-My bad, dude. I was just pissed.
Maybe this is too much for us.
There's no way we could catch someone eluding the cops.
Huh? The fuck you sayin'?
Didn't you get involved because the cops could never solve this case?
The killer's only gonna get away if we pussy out!
Are you really okay with that?
Huh?! None of us ordered this!
It's on the house.
Normally, we only offer this on rainy days.
Th-That's...
It takes Understanding to accept everything, Knowledge to set a good pace,
Courage to attack the pile of meat, and Diligence to keep eating.
It takes all of that to finish the Mega Beef Bowl!
Thanks, but why?
Please enjoy.
Well, let's chow down.
20 Minutes Later
I eat and eat, and I still can't see the rice!
40 Minutes Later
Meat, meat, grease, grease, and more meat.
Seriously, what's with this monster?
At least we made a dent in it... I think.
There's way too much food!
I don't think I'll reach the bottom.
But we'll get there if we just press on.
Yeah, you're right. We'll get there eventually if we keep at it.
Yeah, I'm sure of it!
Damn straight we can!
We may not be able to see it now, but we gotta keep going anyway.
I really can't see...
the bottom of the bowl.
That's all?!
You're a real weirdo.
We gained a lot from that battle.
That'll be 3,000 yen each.
Wasn't it on the house?!
If King Moron got thrown into the TV, Teddie might know something.
Yeah. And I'm also worried he's still deflated.
Huh? What are those guys doing there?
I hope they haven't found out about the TV.
Hi there! Something the matter?
Oh, Yosuke! Great timing.
A Mr. Teddie came by.
Huh? Mr. Teddie?
This feels good.
Whoa, he's here!
This chair feels bear-y good!
You look comfy.
What are you doing here?
You guys finally showed up! I've been waiting.
Teddie, is it okay for you to leave the TV?
You can do that?
Of course! There's an exit, after all.
It just never occurred to me before.
But I got bear-y interested in your world after hanging out with you guys.
Yeah, that happens.
I just knew Master would understand!
Oh, someone asked for my name, so I said, "I'm Teddie!"
We should've known, huh?
Oh Teddie, we need to ask you something.
Huh?
So you're absolutely positive no one's been inside the TV?
That's what I'm saying!
I was all alone as I clawed my way to tiptop shape!
So that means King Moron never went inside.
Then he was killed in our world?
Do you think the killer did it in the real world because he hadn't been successful with the TV?
Probably. We've saved three people in a row now.
So he's getting impatient.
Geez, it's so hot!
Off it goes.
C-Cut that out! Kids are watching!
Dude, you'll scar the kids for life if they see an empty mascot moving around.
I'm not empty anymore!
Off it goes!
Ah, what a nice breeze!
He's not empty!
Y-You're... What?!
N-No way.
Phew, I feel grrreat!
I grew a body so I could score with Chie and Yukiko.
You grew a body? For that?!
How many times must you bring that up?
Say, got any clothes on you? I'm as bare as a newborn baby.
Don't you dare drop your bottom half!
He needs clothes!
He grew a human body inside himself.
Stop it!
Good for him.
No fucking way.
What the hell is he?!
Huh? Whatcha looking at, Dojima?
The people who recently went missing.
I don't think they're unrelated to the serial murders.
More importantly, did you hear about that boy detective?
The one helping with the investigation?
He's still a kid.
What were the higher-ups thinking?
You can't blame 'em, since we haven't made any progress.
I actually blame you for bringing in that weirdo.
Ouch!
Uh, are you really Teddie?
Yes, that's right. What do you think?
Brilliant!
Seriously, don't encourage him.
Okay, but really, who is he?
I was shocked at first, but he's definitely Teddie.
He really hasn't changed at all, so it's actually kinda annoying.
He went nuts in the lady's department.
I did?
You can't follow your instincts when you're in this form, okay?
This is my first time here...
Sorry. We aren't angry with you.
Thank goodness! I was afraid you'd hate me now.
Oh, come to think of it, where's Teddie's head?
Tofu
Oh, they have some!
Pickled Rice bran Radish
Country pickled radish
What do you want? Got a problem?
You're rude, you damn brat.
I'll show you what happens
when you get in my way.
Courage
Brave
Diligence
Staunch
Understanding
Generous
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Informed
A
Courage
Brave
Diligence
Staunch
Understanding
Generous
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Informed
A
Big Bro!
Can I help you?
Who are you?
Are you okay?
Yeah. Thank you, Big Bro.
But what are you doing here?
Huh?
Oh!
Super Special
40% Off!
Took you long enough.
I had to drop by my house.
Oh, my pretty head!
I'm glad you came back to me.
Thank you! Master, you're so nice.
Isn't it great that you aren't empty anymore?
Yeah, but...
I still don't know anything about myself.
Let's find your true self... together.
M-Master!
Yeah! We'll catch the real me.
Why's he so hyper?
He's always been like that.
It's like everything's new to him.
Fine, take this.
What's that for?
Get some Topsicles and share them with Teddie.
Wow, you're so rich!
That's the Prince of Junes for you.
Oh, what's this, Hanamura? You're acting really mature!
Huh?
I see. Hanamura, you really are an adult.
You're an adult, and adults don't sweat the small stuff, right?
Where are you going with this?
Well, we kinda charged Teddie's clothes to your account.
You what?! I'm paying?!
What the hell?! I never heard about this!
It's not our fault we didn't have enough money.
Clothes at Junes are a ripoff, anyway.
It's okay, baby. Don't fight over me.
Screw you! This is all your fault!
Why'd you put it on my account without asking?!
C'mon, let's get those Topsicles, Teddie.
Because I don't have any money!
Give me a sec!
Then don't buy clothes.
These are for Rise.
You saying he was fine the way he was?
Master, please give them to her.
Of course not!
Okay, will do.
Then what's the problem?
At least cover half the tab.
Hey, this could take a while, so why don't we go?
No.
Pay!
Please pay.
No.
I'll treat you!
Sounds good. Let's leave them alone.
Then gimme a steak.
That defeats the point.
Marukyu Tofu
Oh, I see you came after all.
Huh? Aren't you...
Hey, what's up?
What now?!
It's him.
Here to appease Kujikawa Rise next?
Narukami!
Oh, you're all here too.
I still haven't introduced myself.
I'm Shirogane Naoto, a detective.
I am currently helping the police investigate the serial murders.
A detective?
Indeed. And may I ask for your take on something?
What is it?
Wasn't the latest victim, Mr. Morooka Kinshiro, a teacher at your school?
What of it?
The second victim, Konishi Saki, attended the same school.
The media is pursuing that angle, but that isn't what's important.
There's something more to it.
So? What are you getting at?
Mr. Morooka was never seen on TV.
What do you think of that?
Beats me.
Very well. I simply want to close this case as quickly as possible.
I've got my eye on you.
Goodbye.
What was that about?
Sorry for bringing you out here.
My grandma would get worried if she overheard our discussion.
Are you feeling any better?
I'm fine now.
But man, this sucks.
Risette, you sure you didn't see the guy's face?
Yeah, I was in the other world when I came to.
It's just like with Kanji and me.
Um, well...
What is it?
Well, thank you for saving my life.
I'm really grateful!
Don't sweat it!
You're so cute!
It just hit me now that you're the real Risette!
Hey, would you be in trouble without me?
Do you need my help?
Yeah, it'd be good to have you on the team.
Yeah, yeah!
Are these proof I'm one of you?
Everyone wore them inside the TV, right?
Glad to have you with us.
Yep! Now we're friends.
Friends with Risette?
I'll finally get to enjoy my sweet teen years!
Is that story about King Moron legit?
Apparently it is. It was on TV.
More importantly, is it true Risette transferred to our school?
Oh, good morning.
As of today, I'll be taking the late Mr. Morooka's place as your homeroom teacher.
I'm Kashiwagi Noriko.
Nice to meet you!
I don't wanna rush you, but finals are next week.
Don't neglect your studies just because I've bewitched you.
From King Moron to Kashiwagi, things aren't getting any better.
She's well endowed.
Finals are coming up? I totally forgot about them.
Yukiko!
I saw him yesterday.
Gross!
Not him!
Hey, come with me, Yukiko.
Come to my world!
Hey! Back off!
What? Stay out of this!
Yukiko, you'll come with me, won't you? Won't you?
Uh, who are you?
We've never met, have we?
Yikes! You totally forgot about him, huh?
Huh?
Are you fucking with me?!
I...
I—
Who are you?
What do you need her for?
Moron! You'll regret this!
What's his problem?
Slim Body
I committed all of the murders in Inaba.
I am the killer.
291 Rotten Tangerine: I can't believe Risette retired.
292 Rotten Criminal: I committed all of the murders in Inaba. I am the killer.
293 Rotten Tangerine: Yeah, sure. And I've reported you in.
294 Rotten Tangerine: Attention whore.
295 Rotten Tangerine: Let's discuss Risette's ass.
296 Rotten Tangerine: Risette's washed up. Kanami Mashita's going to be the new
Mitsuo, it's dinnertime!
Mitsuo!
333 Rotten Tangerine:
....... If you're the killer, you have to prove it
334 Rotten Tangerine:
....... Don't encourage 292. Let's turn him in.
335 Rotten Tangerine:
....... 292, quit blowing us off.
336 Rotten Criminal:
....... I'll prove it to you!!!!!!!!!!
Finals are finally over.
Why bother with English? I'd just hire an interpreter if I needed it.
That's not the point...
So how'd you do?
My pen wouldn't stop moving.
Wow! That's so impressive!
By the way, where's Teddie?
Isn't he living with you, Hanamura?
Oh, him. He's working for his keep as our mascot.
So you forced him to wear that.
You changed him back.
Rawr!
What's up, guys? Let me join in if you're stud hunting.
Don't bring that up anymore!
This is more like a group date than picking each other up - a triple date!
We'd never go on a group date with you guys.
Well, King Moron would've snapped and started yelling at us if we really were.
King Moron...
He was an ass.
I didn't like him either.
No one ever liked that creep.
But no one deserves to die like that.
We have to catch the killer.
Yeah. The Midnight Channel hasn't come on lately, but we still have to.
That won't be necessary.
They've identified the culprit.
You should leave the rest to the police.
They identified the culprit? Who is it?
They didn't tell me.
I just know that he's a high school student like us.
The killer's a high school student?
As such, your little game is over.
We aren't playing around.
A game?! Aren't you the one not taking it seriously?
You don't deny your involvement?
I don't care if you're some detective. You're just solving puzzles!
You're the one treating it like a game!
Someone dear to us was killed.
I'm not playing around here.
Besides, we made a promise.
Y-Yosuke!
I'm the one treating it like a game? You may be right.
So, what's our oh-so-famous detective doing here?
Did they give you the boot after they caught the killer?
My job is over now that they know who the culprit is.
Although, I admit it's sad they cut me out at their earliest convenience.
But I'm used to it.
You're...
Well, I'll be going now.
Is it really over?
I don't know. If what he said is true...
Are we done getting together like this?
I heard they identified the culprit.
What, so they caught him?
It looks like Shirogane's story was for real.
What's left for us to do?
There's nothing left.
Not yet.
Well, it's raining, so let's check the Midnight Channel.
Yeah, we really should.
No time to waste
but make you pace
It's okay to remove, copy, and paste
I'm doing my way
You do it your way
Don't just follow your left, find the right way
Stereotypes
Too many hypes,
But I'm the epitome of new types
Having the fear is power to my soul
'Cause I overcome them
That's how I roll
Expose your thoughts
Don't be afraid of making mistakes
Rules prevailing in
That may be your greatest rival
Believe in faith and your heart
Your true soul stop being in the shades
Come on, out in the open sun
Beauty of the child of destiny
Delightful days
are with rich density of love
Thorny path
There's no easy way for real bliss
So I keep on fighting for
Beauty of destiny
So now you wanna pay attention to me, huh?!
You think you know me.
Then catch me if you can.
You see that?
Yeah.
Let's go.
All guys like games!
I'll get him in one attack.
How'd you get here?
It'd be nice if everyone came to visit again.
I am nothing.
Master, you're up!
I said I killed them!