[explosion]
[COMANCHE] So you dare to
challenge Giolo Comanche,
the Silver Alchemist,
to battle, do you...?
You've got guts,
I'll give you that...
However...
[crash]
[COMANCHE] Not bad,
not bad at all...
You got off with
just a scratch.
[SCAR]
You can't say the same.
What's going on?
Who is this?
[YOKI] Oh, sir,
you've returned!
Welcome back.
[SCAR] I said,
who is this?!
[MAY]
Pleased to meet you.
[MAY] My name
is May Chang, sir.
[MAY] I was collapsed
by the side of the road...
Your master,
Mr. Yoki, revived me
and brought me back here.
[SCAR]
Master?
If you've recovered,
there's no need
for you to stay.
Be on your way at once.
[SCAR]
What, girl?
[MAY] Allow me to
close your wound.
[YOKI]
It's healed?!
[MAY] It's a skill
called alkahestry,
from the land of Xing.
[SCAR]
She's from Xing?
[YOKI]
That's right sir...
This girl...
crossed the desert...
from the east...
by herself...
to come here... Ha!
Clearly ridiculous.
[MAY]
No, I wasn't alone.
[MAY] I had her
with me, too!
[YOKI] Her? You mean
this little creature here?
[MAY] That's right.
Her name's Shao May.
[MAY]
Oh, your arm...!
That's alkahestry, right?
[MAY] The art of reading
the dragon's pulse,
of knowing the power that
flows through the ground
and how to use it...?
That tattoo
matches the flow
of alkahestry
used in my homeland.
[SCAR] My brother was
a student of alchemy
and alkahestry and he conducted
a great deal of research
into both fields...
The tattoo that I bear is
a result of that research.
[MAY]
That's incredible!
Your brother must've
really been something!
[YOKI]
I'm not really sure
what you two are
talking about...
but your wound is
healed now, sir...
We can be on our
way to Central
without any further delay.
[MAY]
Oh, that sounds great!
I'll go get my things.
[YOKI] What do you
think you're doing?
Didn't he tell you
to shove off, kid...?
We're not exactly
going to Central
for a picnic,
you know?!
[MAY] I know, but
I meant what I told you.
[YOKI] You mean all
that immortality stuff
you were blabbering
about earlier...?
There's no such thing.
[MAY]
Yes, there is...!
And I came
here to find it!
[YOKI]
Oh, shut up...
Kids don't know anything!
[MAY] I already
know that immortality
can't be accomplished
by alkahestry...
but it is possible through
the use of alchemy...
That's why I have
to find him...
the incredible man
I've heard so much about.
[MAY] They say his
hair and his eyes
are golden like the sun...
He wears a dashing red
coat as he strides forth
to save people in need...
The brilliant State
Alchemist... Edward Elric!
[YOKI] What do
we do about her?
[SCAR]
Suit yourself, girl.
[barks and growls]
[HAWKEYE]
Black Hayate...
What's gotten
into you, boy?
[mysterious laughter]
[66] It's dangerous
to be out walking
the streets alone
at this hour.
[66] You never know
when you might meet...
The terrible serial
killer, feared by all...
Barry the Chopper!
[gunshots]
[66] No fair!
What'd you have
to pull a gun for!?
[66] All right,
that's it, lady...
Now I'm gonna
hear you scream!
[66]
Hey...!
How come you're not
paralyzed with fear?
[HAWKEYE]
You actually remind me
of someone else I know.
[66]
Lemme guess...
Alphonse
Something-or-Other?
[HAWKEYE] You've
met Alphonse before?
[66] Oh, so the guy's a
friend of yours, is he?
[66] I'm gonna tell ya
something, sweetheart...
You are one strong woman!
[ROY]
The Philosopher's Stone.
[FALMAN] I can't believe
the fifth laboratory
was being used to make
something like that.
[HAWKEYE]
It gets worse.
There's a chance that
military senior staff
was involved as well.
[ROY] Plus, there
were those other two,
Lust and Envy...
[ROY] Are they the
ones who made you
into what you are now?
[66] Nah, it was the
researchers who did that...
Ripped my soul
right outta my body
and slapped it into this
suit of armor you see here.
[FALMAN] We can
try to track down
these so-called
'researchers'...
If we find them,
maybe they can tell us
who ordered the experiments.
[66]
Fat chance of that...
They were all used to
create Philosopher's Stones...
There's not a single
one of 'em left alive.
[ROY] Silenced and then
used as ingredients...
How efficiently planned.
[HAWKEYE] Do you
think this means
they have
what they need,
or will they try to
make additional stones?
[ROY] I have one
more question for you.
[ROY] A little
over a month ago,
a military
officer was killed
in a telephone
booth in Central...
Were you the
one who did it?
[66] Phone booth--
doesn't sound familiar...
Was he all chopped up?
[ROY]
Never mind.
[ED]
Hello there, Winry!
You look like you're
in a very
generous mood today!
[WINRY]
Hi, Ed! Hi, Al!
What're you doing
showing up like this?
[WINRY] Even Paninya
is holding down
an honest job now,
and you two still can't
stay out of trouble!
[AL]
Really, she is?
[WINRY]
Yeah...
She's given up her former
life as a pickpocket
and now she earns her
money by fixing roofs
and doing other
odd jobs around town.
[WINRY] And what about
the two of you, huh...?
Made any progress yet?
[AL]
Yeah, we have...
It's slow going, though.
[ED] We're still moving
ahead, little by little.
I guess.
[WINRY] Good...
I'm glad to hear it.
[WINRY] All right, I've
done all I can for now.
[ED]
Thanks, Winry.
[WINRY]
I'm missing some parts,
so you'll have to make
do with a patch job.
[WINRY] I'll go
get what we need,
but until then, you've
got some time to kill.
[ED]
Kill some time, huh?
Yeah...
how do we do
that in a town
made up entirely
of automail shops?
[ED]
Al?
[AL]
Brother...
[ED]
What now...?
Did you find a
stray cat or something?
[AL]
Ah... Well... No.
[LING] I feel
so much better...!
You guys are
lifesavers...!
Thanks a lot!
[LING]
Your treat, right?
[ED] When did I say
that I was paying?
[LING] Let's not quibble
over something so small!
[ED] Who're you
callin' small?!
[LING]
How lucky I am
to have found
such hospitality...
so far from home.
[AL]
Far from home...?
You mean you're
not from here?
[LING] That's right...
I came from Xing.
[ED]
Oh, Xing...? That's...
[ED] The country to
the east of the desert?
[LING]
Yeah...
And crossing that
desert was rough,
let me tell you.
[AL] Why in the world
would you take that route?
[LING] I wanted to visit
the ruins of Xerxes.
That route goes by them.
[ED]
The Xerxes Ruins?
[ED] I'd heard there's
next to nothing there.
[LING] I wanted to
see for myself...
Anyway, I was
headed here
to do some
alkahestry research.
[ED]
Alkahestry?
[LING]
Yes...
I believe it's what you here
in this country call alchemy.
[LING] In Xing, it's
known as alkahestry...
It's mainly used in
the medical professions.
[ED] Huh...
Different countries,
different customs, I guess.
Here, alchemy's use
is mainly military.
[ED] It's not
hard to see why.
Even now, we still
have skirmishes
at the borders of Aerugo
to the south and
Creta to the west...
North of us is the
huge country, Drachma...
We have a tentative
nonaggression pact with them,
and Briggs Mountain
stands between us,
making invasion difficult...
But our relationship
is still dicey at best.
[LING]
Sounds like you guys
have got your
hands full, all right.
[ED]
Things began to move
more toward the militaristic...
when the current
Fuhrer, King Bradley,
first came into power.
[AL] I have to say, I'm
curious about alkahestry.
A branch of alchemy that's
medically specialized?
[ED]
I'm curious, too.
[LING]
By any chance...
are the two of
you guys alchemists?
[ED] Oh, yeah,
we are, actually...
I'm Edward Elric...
a State Alchemist.
[AL] And I'm his younger
brother, Alphonse Elric...
It's nice to meet you.
[LING]
My name's Ling Yao.
It's a pleasure.
[ED]
So, Ling...
what else can you tell
us about alkahestry?
We'd sure love to learn more.
[LING]
Nothing...
Yeah, Sorry, but I'm not
actually an alkahestrist.
[ED] If you don't
practice alkahestry,
why come all the way
here to research it?
[LING] Well, see,
I'm looking for something.
[LING] It's possible you two
have heard of it before...
[LING]
The Philosopher's Stone?
I'm very eager to find it.
[LING] Do you know
anything about it?
[ED]
No...
We can't help you.
[LING] You wouldn't be lying
to me, now would you?
[LING] So, do you have
something to tell me?
[ED] Why the interest in
the Philosopher's Stone?
[LING]
I want to achieve...
Immortality!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[LING] Out with it.
What do you know?
[ED]
Immortality? Please...
What a bunch
of nonsense.
[LING]
Not to me it isn't.
[ED]
In any case,
I can't say that
I care too much
for your way of
asking questions.
[ED] Kinda rude,
don't you think?
[AL]
Brother!
[FU] You're going
to fight us too?
[AL]
Hey... Hold on...
[ED] Jeez...!
Is that guy an acrobat?
[AL] Must be a
Xingese fighting style.
Could be tough to beat.
[ED]
Even so...
[ED] They're still
not as strong...
[AL]
...as Teacher!
[PANINYA] What's
happening down there?
[LING]
Off they go.
[LING] Hey, Pops, let's
add some dessert to my tab.
[POPS]
Sure.
[ED]
Crap!
[ED] Damn...!
You're persistent...
Picking a fight
like this just because
I won't give you information...
What're you guys after...?
You and your boss with
the freaky closed eyes.
[ED]
Hey...! I landed one!
[ED groaning]
Owww... It hurts...
[ED]
That's strange...
As soon as
I insulted Ling,
this guy completely lost it.
[AL] Hey! Long
time no see, Paninya!
[PANINYA] What in the world
are you doing here, Al?
Besides getting yourself
into more trouble.
[AL]
Yeah, about that...
can I ask you a favor?
[FU]
Strange...
Every living person
emits a flow of chi.
Yet I don't sense one coming
from this suit of armor...
What is he?
[FU]
You think the aid
of one person will
do you any good...?
How very foolish of you!
[ED]
What's the matter...?
You're starting to
slow down a little.
[ED] If this is the best
his flunkies can manage,
that bastard Ling must
be pretty pathetic too.
[ED]
Just like before...
as soon as
I insult his boss,
this guy completely
loses his cool...
and when
that happens...
[ED] His attacks
become weak and useless!
[ED] Now then,
I think it's about time...
For me to have
a look at your face!
[ED]
A girl?!
[FU] She has a cannon
in her prosthetic?
This country is a place
to be reckoned with.
[FU]
What?!
[AL] Hmm, not too bad
considering it
was my first time.
[FU]
It's Alkahestry...
but without an array?!
[AL] Now...
I wonder how things are
going on Brother's end.
[LAN FAN]
I overdid it.
Look at this place.
Master Ling will be furious.
[ED]
Hey, girly!
[ED] You should
be more careful
about where you
use that thing...
It would have
killed anybody else.
[LAN FAN]
But how...?
You removed your own arm?!
[ED] I spent a
fair amount of time
hunting rabbits when
I was a little kid...
Setting a trap
for you was easy.
[AL]
Brother!
[ED]
Oh, hey Al!
[LING] Okay...!
Good work, guys!
[ED]
Why you--
what are you so
chipper about?!
[LING] You guys've got some
pretty impressive skills...
I know, come work for me
and together we can
take over this country.
What do ya say?
[ED] I've had enough of
your idiotic chattering...!
Just go back to Xing!
[TOWNSPERSON A]
Look...! There they are!
[TOWNSPERSON A] Look at
the mess you've made!
You practically
destroyed our town!
[TOWNSPERSON B]
You're covering the damages.
[POPS] And your
restaurant bill, too.
[ED] Hey wait.
J-Just hold on a second...
This guy and his
little entourage
should be paying
for everything!
[LING]
So sorry.
I no understand much
language of this country...
Okay, Bye-bye now!
[ED] Hey, you get
the hell back here!
[AL]
Huh?
Ah! He ran away!
[ED]
The other one did, too!
You gotta be kidding...
How am I supposed
to fix this place up
with only one arm?
[AL]
It's okay, Brother...
I'll take care of it.
[ED]
What...?
You mean you
can do alchemy
without a
transmutation circle now?
[AL]
Yeah...
I think it's because of
the memories I recovered.
[ED]
And that means...!
[AL]
Don't worry.
You can leave
all this to me.
What's the
matter, Brother?
[AL and ED]
We're back!
[LING] Hello...!
We meet again!
[ED] What's your
sorry butt doing here?!
[LING]
Now, now...
we're all
friends here, right?
[ED] That's how you
treat your friends?
By sicking your
dogs on them?
Those two didn't go easy!
[LING]
Let it go.
I promise I'll give
them a talking to later.
[LING] The girl's
name is Lan Fan...
The old man is called Fu.
Their family has served
mine for generations...
They're quite good
at what they do.
[ED]
Oh...
So, you shake down
strangers for food,
and yet you can
somehow afford
two personal
attendants?
[LING] Well, I am the
emperor's son, after all.
[AL and ED]
Huh?
Emperor's son?
[ED]
That makes you...
[AL and ED]
A prince!
[laughter]
[LING] Not the
reaction I anticipated.
[AL]
Sorry!
We just didn't
see that coming!
[ED] Yeah, the guy who
collapsed on the road
and then mooched
food off us
is the son of an Emperor!
[ED]
Ahhh!!
[LAN FAN] You will not speak
badly about Master Ling.
[ED]
Great to see you.
[LING] No, you're
probably right.
It's not actually
that big a deal.
[LING] The emperor
has a lot of sons.
[LING]
It's like this...
My country,
Xing, is broken up
between fifty different clans...
with an emperor at the top,
reigning over all of them.
[LING] The daughter
of each clan's chief
becomes one of the
emperor's wives...
and bears his children.
[LING] The current emperor...
has nineteen daughters...
and twenty-four sons...
I come in at number
twelve in that line-up.
[ED] Forty-three kids...
that's incredible!
[AL] The issue of succession
must be a tricky one.
[LING]
Indeed it is.
That's the problem
we're facing right now.
[LING] The emperor's
health has begun
to deteriorate recently...
Each clan is doing
everything they can
to curry favor...
and I'm no exception.
[ED] You want to
up your chances
by discovering the
secret of immortality.
[LING]
Exactly!
[LING] Okay...!
The Philosopher's Stone...
What information
can you offer?
[ED]
Not happening...!
The Stone isn't a tool
for some political game.
[LING]
Aw!
Then I'll have to stay
with you until you tell me!
[ED]
Oh no you don't!
Get off of me, freak!
[WINRY]
I'm back!
Did you see that...?
There was some kind of
fight on main street...
So it took a while to...
[WINRY] What happened
to your arm?!
[WINRY] Edward Elric,
you careless little jerk!
[FU]
Young Lord!
[FU] Why do you put
up with this boy?
There's no need to bow to
someone so far beneath you.
[LING] If all it takes
is a little bowing,
I'll consider it a
small price to pay...
The fate of five
hundred thousand
Yao Clansmen rides on this.
[LING] We can't worry so
much about appearances.
[WINRY] So, where are
you headed to break
your automail this time?
[ED] You just assume
I'll break it?
[AL] We were
thinking about
doing some
digging in Central.
[WINRY] You guys are
going to Central...?
I want to come too!
Take me with you!
[ED] What do you
want to go there for?
[WINRY] I'd like to go see
the Hughes family again.
[AL] But... don't you have
a lot of work to do here?
[GARFIEL] It's okay if
you want to go, Winry...
You should take a break
every once in awhile.
[WINRY]
Oh, really...?!
Thanks so much, Mr. Garfiel!
[ED] Okay,
we'll all go!
[AL] Central,
here we come!
[LING] Oh, we're
going to Central?
How exciting!
[ED] I told you, you're
not coming with us!
[YOKI] So, the
little girl is coming
with us after all, huh?
[YOKI]
Sir, there's something
I've been meaning
to ask you...
You never have told
me what your name is...
If you don't mind,
I would very much
like to know it.
[SCAR] Ishvalan
names are sacred...
The Ishvalan people
take great pride
in speaking their names aloud...
as they are gifts from god.
[YOKI]
Well then, sir...
your name must be a
special one indeed.
[SCAR] I have renounced
my Ishvalan name.
[SCAR]
Now go!
Keep moving!
[YOKI]
Right!
[SCAR] I'm walking down
a path of no return.
So I will
leave behind me
every gift I have
received from God.
[NARRATOR] Ed, Al, and
Winry return to Central,
filled with eager anticipation
for the upcoming reunion...
Instead, they are greeted
with the unfortunate truth.
And before long... the darkness
chooses a new sacrifice.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 16. "Footsteps
of a Comrade-in-Arms."
How many sacrifices
must be made
before the darkness
will be satisfied?