I've made it to my second year of high school. It's finally the end of May.
Edogawa told me to be friends that day,
but since then she hasn't been friendly at all.
But—
there was a greater reason behind that.
Edogawa had a secret she couldn't tell anyone.
I'm sure she wanted to become friends with me,
but it seems she was just scared that her secret would come to light,
and that's why she couldn't open up.
But I found out about her secret.
This isn't what you think it is!
I'm not a boy. I just—
How should I say it...
Uh...
I just grow a penis every now and then!
As one who shares her secret,
as her friend, as her close friend,
I must console and protect her.
Kamisama no yubisaki de
In the blink of an eye,
Dekiagaru watashi no kisetsu tachi
the myriad gods change the seasons of my life
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
I thought I could sleep long after the stars faded from the sky,
Nemuri o yusaburu uta
but I was awoken by a song
Sasami@Unmotivated
Mimi o fusaide hito ni magireru to
I try to mind my own business and blend in with the crowd
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
but that makes me feel like I don't even exist
Kokoro o enjiru ni wa
I wish I could follow my heart,
Zatsuon o eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm not experienced enough to filter out the static
Deatta kouya no hana
I come across a diorama of flowers blooming in the wild
Kowakute yasashikute
They look gentle, eerily so
Fureta shunkan ni   Jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touch the flowers, everything in the diorama becomes real
- al
ter
a
tion -
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta
My future has already been mapped out
Watashi no miraichizu
thanks to the whims of the myriad gods
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
But the echoes of the countless sounds around me
Oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
are strong enough to shatter the bleak future that haunts me so
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
With the stars watching us, we grow even closer
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Close enough that I can see your warmth
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our relationship might be one of take without give,
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
but that's the kind of relationship I want to treasure
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 10
Try fighting an invisible enemy
A penis... A penis...
What's wrong, Sasami?
You sound like you're braindead.
It's just... kind of a puberty problem.
But you know...
Why don't I have any more friends, despite me being a second year?
My plan was to charm everyone with my lighthearted cheerfulness,
and then I would make tons of friends!
And still...
What are you doing?
My hands are tired.
I can't even use my chopsticks.
It's a drag.
Don't reciprocate my tone.
You should work for your food.
But getting fed would make me feel loved.
There is no love.
I just look after you because I have no alternative option.
That's so mean!
I love you so much, Kagami!
Don't shout such nonsense that can easily be misinterpreted!
I love how you couldn't abandon me.
I'll feed you too.
I thought your hands were tired.
Just this once.
In contrary to what she was saying, Kagami couldn't resist my charm
and was becoming addicted to me.
In the end we were feeding each other mouth-to-mouth.
That's a horrible, wicked plan.
You're really scary, Sasami.
Those two really are lovers.
I bet they're pure-lesbo.
I bet they aren't interested in girls who don't swing that way either.
Bow before me, plebeians!
Sorry, that was the wrong one.
Good afternoon, everyone!
Now that I've gathered you idiots' attention...
"First Class 2/Left Get-Together."
"3 days and 2 nights of lovey-dovey time at the Kuzuryuu Shrine resort."
It might be a bit sudden, but I'm going on a trip for the holidays!
It's a great resort.  All you can eat and drink, and it's totally free!
And the more the merrier, so I'm inviting you guys!
I'll go through the trouble of inviting you plebeians,
to help you realize the blessing of being classmates with Edogawa Jou!
I-It's not like I want you to come or anything.
But I bet you don't have anything better to do anyway. So it's an order!
Come with me!
This is a once in a lifetime opportunity for you petit bourgeoisie.
Despair!
I despaired!
Pick it up, plebeians! Elegance and refinement!
You didn't tell anyone, did you?
I haven't...
If you tell anyone, I'll kill you.
Edogawa.
What?
Can I go on that trip too?
Of course.
Or rather, I'll kill you if you don't.
Seems like the flu.
Going to that get-together is out of the question.
Oh no... Edogawa's gonna kill me...
A trip is out of question with this fever.
No matter how much you'll hate me for this, I simply can't allow you to go.
If you need me, press this button
or chant "Brother, I love-love-love you!" repeatedly.
As if I have the strength to do that...
Rest then.
What an idiot.
Hooray! Good morning, Mamarin!
How are you?
Tama? What are you doing here?
I'm watching the house!
Tsurugi told me to come over to your place.
That bitch... She left on a trip and made me the babysitter...
Trip? I wanna go traveling too!
With you, Mamarin!
I want to travel with you too, Tama...
Oh right, we could do that!
If we did that, it'd solve all of our problems!
Do you get it?
That wasn't really reassuring.
Anyway, don't move.
That tickles!
Yamato is the greatest of all lands.
Countless peaks and green valleys.
Yamato is beautiful.
I became Mamarin?
With that kiss earlier, I connected a spiritual thread to the meridian on your forehead.
I can control you through that thread.
Like a super robot.
I'm a super robot?
I can see, hear, and feel everything you do from this room.
You should go to the get-together looking like that.
Okay, I'll do my best!
Here we go then.
Did you call me, Sasami?
You need my love, right?
Where should I insert my love?
Show me where your love yearns, my sister!
Thoughts as words, reach as spelled!
Sasami has joined the tele-divine channel.
Can you see this, Tama?
Uh, Mamarin...
Tama has joined the tele-divine channel.
Dekita?
Speak Japanese.
Is this it?
Your name's still the same...
Do what I say now.
Okay! I'll do my best!
What's wrong, Sasami?
Say "Brother, I think my flu is fine now."
Don't read the "say"!
Show him how healthy you are!
Look how healthy I am!
Indeed, you're unusually energetic.
Beg him to let you go on the trip.
So can I go on the trip?
Pretty please!
Mamarin— I mean, I was looking forward to it a lot!
So please grant her—! My wish!
But...
Please, Brother!
I love my kind brother!
What's wrong with you, Sasami?
You pierce right through my soul with these honest revelations of your true feelings!
Ah, you want to marry!
I've prepared the marriage certificate, you only have to sign it.
Only the laws stand between us!
Marry? I'll marry you!
Huh? Normally you'd land a body blow or griplock my head....
Is this a dream?
Even if it's just a dream, I've reached my happy ending!
No, my true ending!
Now I can die!
But if you die, we couldn't love each other!
I wanna be all lovey-dovey with you!
What are you saying?
Get going already!
I'll give it all I've got.
Brother, let's go on the trip!
It's our honeymoon!
Let's go Sasami! Let's write our story of love!
Hooray!
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Here's the itinerary for the trip! Elegance and refinement!
Say "hello" to Edogawa.
Thank her for inviting you on the trip.
Yeah! Thanks, Edogawa!
I'll do my best today as Tsukuyomi Sasami!
Don't say that!
That's quite convenient.
What?
You're welcome!
Now that we're all here, get on the bus, like good cattle.
Then if you'll allow me.
There's no seat for you.
Ah, Sasami!
Our love's been torn apart by fate!
Ah, Tsurugi!
Tama, what are you doing here?
Huh?
I see! Aren't you having fun there?
Good morning, Tsurugi.
Ah, a chatroom!
Tsurugi has entered the tele-divine channel.
That's a merry idea, Sasami.
I totally thought your pillow would be a puddle of tears at this point.
You can get wet elsewhere too!
Why do you always have to throw in some sexual harassment?
I felt sorry for leaving Tama behind, so this is perfect.
But be careful.
Now that you gave the power of Amaterasu to your mom, you're defenseless.
Don't worry. I'm in the safest spot ever.
Huh?
Kagamin has entered the tele-divine channel.
Isn't it great, Kagami?
She was feeling dejected and isolated because you couldn't come.
I wasn't sulking. Nor did I feel lonely.
I was just sleepy.
Good morning, Sis!
If you're pretending to be Sasami, then it's just "Kagami" not "sis."
Okay! Good morning, Kagami!
Don't address your elders just like that!
Then what should I do?
The flu medicine is starting to kick in...
I can't last much longer.
It's a waste, but I'll take a nap.
Good night.
Sasami has left the tele-divine channel.
Mamarin's gone...
Sasami fell asleep?
Will her flu be alright, Sis?
I told you to drop the "sis"!
Then what should I do?
Then...
I see!
Dear Sister!
Why would you call me something like that?!
She said this isn't weird between friends and real siblings either!
Was it weird, Dear Sister?
Did I do it wrong, Dear Sister?
Am I a bad girl, Dear Sister?
Stop... I'm feeling faint...
I have no choice.
This is getting troublesome, so I'll allow you to call me that.
I love you, Dear Sister!
She's started calling her "Dear Sister"...
Oh, Lesbians! The femme and the butch!
They're now beyond our reach!
Farewell, my first love!
You really are the center of attention.
Uh, who are you?
So mean.
I'm in charge of the 2nd year students at the Ko-no-hana Saku Ya Academy.
Uh...
I'm Kitsunebi Youko.
Sorry, I'm horrible at remembering peoples' names!
Let's become much more well-acquainted with each other on this trip, Ms. Yagami.
Kuzuryuu Island
Kuzuryuu Shrine
Bow to the gods.
Bow to each other.
Keep staring! Keep staring!
A bit more and...
Now!
Let's dig in!
Take all you want. Eat to your hearts content.
Get as fat as you want and regret it later, plebeians.
The goddess who bestowed this freedom on you is me, Edogawa Jou.
Revere me! Call me Marianne!
Won't you join us, Edogawa?
Aren't you lonely there, by yourself?
What's wrong, Kagami?
It's free, let's indulge ourselves!
She's on my mind.
Do I smell love? Cheating?
It's okay, go on!
Recently I realized how great NTR stuff are!
It totally turns me on!
Sasami has joined the tele-divine channel.
Hey!
I've been asleep for quite a well, huh?
You're up, Sasami?
How are you?
Not good... My flu's not getting better.
Here you go.
You share your sense of taste too, right?
If you want to taste something, just say the word and I'll get it for you.
Thanks!
You're nice today, Kagami.
I'm always an angel.
Are you having fun, Youko?
Let's drink and speak openly about whatever,
then go to bed to deepen our relationship!
Let me grope your titties!
Is it okay to just ignore it?
She's the butt pimple of the family.
I don't want to be associated with her.
Attention!
The bath is ready, so if you're done eating, go wash yourselves.
Let's go take a bath!
I'll wash your back.
Then!
I'll wash you in the front too...
Straight into an H scene!
I know! Baths hold people's hopes and dreams!
In what universe?!
You should come with us too, Edogawa!
Oh, no, I...
Oh no! At this time it's grown.
Let's go together! And wash each other's backs!
Each other's backs?
No, I can't...
It's okay...
No!
I have my duties.
You should just have fun.
Don't bother with me! Don't get close to me!
What?
Edogawa, you're so serious.
You must be thinking of cleaning up the dishes and other stuff, right?
Has it grown out again?
Don't worry, I've got your back.
If we do it all together, we'll be done in a flash.
Don't try to do it all alone. We're all by your side.
Yeah, I'll help too!
Yeah, we can help with cleaning up!
Tsurugi's first in.
What are you a five year old?
It's grown, right?
She said you can hide it with this.
What does that mean?
Uh...
She says, it turns into a dangerous weapon if you see a girl's naked body, right?
Edogawa, do you get it?
Yeah...
Stay with me! I'll take you to a place where you can be all by yourself.
The water's white here, so you can hide it!
This feels incredible!
Yeah.
There you are, Sasami!
This is bad manners.
May we join you?
Taking a closer look, you're completely flat, Kagami.
Listen to me and drink more milk.
I didn't ask for your opinion!
Tama's out of sight today and Youko ran away too.
I haven't had my fill of cowtits for today.
There's Edogawa!
You've got a body far too good for a high schooler!
Give up yourself to your teacher!
Sh-Shoot!
What's wrong, Edogawa?
Does it hurt? Should I massage you?
Don't touch me!
Sorry!
Something's there!
Something bizarre is near my butt!
Let me join!
No! You must defeat me if you want to pass!
I'm not interested in flatchests.
You can touch mine after we go home!
I want to grope some titties now!
You mustn't touch Edogawa now!
Her big black deadly weapon will fire!
Isn't that nice?
Huh? Look, isn't that Ms. Youko?
What?
Whoa, her tits are ten times bigger than mine!
She's even better without her bra then?
Where are you, Ms Youko?!
That was close.
Tsurugi's so persistent!
It's okay now, Edogawa.
Why?
Why are you helping me?
You saved me at the dinner
and helped me so that they won't find out about my body.
And just now you protected me.
Why are you doing all of this for me?
Well, you might laugh at me for this, but I was happy.
When we first met, you told me that you wanted to be friends.
That's it.
Is it weird to want to help you out because of that?
It feels like friends are there to share secrets with and help each other.
I want to get along with you, Edogawa.
That's just not possible.
After all, one day
I'm gonna kill you.
Sasami@Unmotivated
Okay, no one's here!
They're all on the trip! Now's my chance!
Ah! Mic test! Whatever.
Even if you say "see you tomorrow" as you leave
I end up wanting to meet you right away again
I want to listen to you talking
All the way until I get on the train
I was a bit interested, actually, in singing the ending song.
Some higher-ups might get mad at me if I didn't sing it at least once properly.
But I want to practice first.
I want to show you my best voice.
Being pretty is one of my sales points after all!
I can hear your voice.
It's hard to get the tone right.
I don't speak much with people, so my voice's rusty...
Light shines down like love.
Let's hold hands forever.
I can feel our osmotic pressure,
and I don't want it to stop.
Good job, Mamarin!
Tama! You've been listening?
Yeah! We streamed it and listened to it together!
No way! Why? No!
Preview
It'd be time for the Unmotivated Cinema,
but due to a baseball game, the programme changed,
and we planned on airing the Unmotivated Debate,
but then a participant bailed out due to some sudden sickness,
so as an emergency measure we wanted to re-air the Unmotivated end-of-year special no. 99,
but when we looked for the tape, someone recorded a drama over it and now it's gone,
so I gave up.
Next time, episode 11:
Next Time
Episode Eleven
Love is just    an urban legend
Love is just an urban legend.