We have to curse someone to balance out a wish for someone else's happiness.
That's how we magical girls work, isn't it?
I'm really stupid.
Sayaka!
The hell?
Who the hell are you?
What did you do to Sayaka?!
Stand back.
Grab on.
What are you...
Just do it.
It just...
If you let go of my hand, you'll be frozen in time, as well. Be careful.
What's going on?!
What's that witch?
It was once Miki Sayaka.
You saw it happen yourself, did you not?
Are you running?
If you don't like that option, toss aside that hunk of meat and we can kill the witch instead.
Can you do that?
You must be kidding!
You'll just get in the way in your current state.
We're withdrawing for now.
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll walk upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 9          I won't let that happen
Huh?
Sayaka-chan!
Sayaka-chan, what's wrong?!
Where's her Soul Gem?
Wh-What happened to Sayaka-chan?
After her Soul Gem changed into a Grief Seed, it gave birth to a witch and was destroyed.
That can't... be true.
It is.
That's the final secret regarding the Soul Gems.
When these gems darken and cloud over, they turn into Grief Seeds and we are reborn as witches.
That is the inevitable fate of those who have become magical girls.
That can't be true...
It just can't be.
Right?
That can't be... why...
Sayaka-chan just wanted to save people from the witches; she wanted to become a hero. She became a magical girl wanting to do that...
So why?
She just ended up bearing a curse as powerful as her wish.
She will now live cursing as many people as she had saved.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Are you trying to brag about how much you know?
How can you say all of that like you're so proud of yourself?
That's Sayaka's—Sayaka's best friend right there, you know?
You now understand what you aspired to be, do you not?
Since you decided to bring the corpse with you, you'll have to dispose of it carefully.
If you leave it somewhere carelessly, it'll be really troublesome for you later.
And you call yourself human?!
Of course not.
And neither are you.
Can I come in?
I want to talk to you about something.
So you're alive...
Was what Homura-chan said correct?
Nothing so wrong I'd need to correct it.
Then you're only turning everyone into magical girls to make them witches?
I hope you don't misunderstand, but it's not like we hold any malice towards mankind.
All of this is done to extend the lifespan of the universe.
Madoka, do you know the word "entropy?"
To give you a simple example, the heat energy you gain by burning wood in a campfire
is unequal to the amount of energy it takes to grow the tree you're burning.
When you convert energy between forms, there's loss involved.
And so, the total amount of energy in the universe is diminishing.
That's why we searched for a form of energy not bound by the laws of thermodynamics,
and what we discovered was the magical energy from magical girls.
What... are you?
Our civilization developed the technology to convert the emotions of sentient lifeforms into energy.
But unfortunately, we ourselves don't have any emotions.
So we started to look into all the various types of species across the universe, and we found humans.
The number of human individuals and their reproductive rate
indicates that the amount of emotional energy produced by a single human exceeds the amount of energy that was expended during its birth and growth.
Your souls are capable of generating enough energy to overcome entropy.
The most effective source of energy comes from the phase change between hope and despair of young women
who are undergoing development of their secondary sexual characteristics.
When a Soul Gem burns away and changes into a Grief Seed—in that moment, an enormous amount of energy is released.
It's our job—the Incubators'—to collect that energy.
Are we just disposable to you?
Are we supposed to just die for you?
Do you know how many civilizations are crowded together in the universe and how much energy is used up in one second?
Eventually you humans will leave this planet as well and join us.
You wouldn't want to be handed an empty, desolate universe then, would you?
So if you look at it in the long-term, we believe this to be a beneficial trade for all of you as well.
You can't be serious...
You're telling me that Mami-san died and Sayaka-chan went through so much just for something crazy like that?
That's too much...
That's too cruel.
Our contracts are completely dependent upon you agreeing to them first.
I think that, in and of itself, is quite kind of us.
You're just tricking everyone!
We don't even understand what it means to trick someone.
For some reason, whenever a human regrets a bad choice they've made due to a difference in understanding with someone,
they start to detest that person.
I can't even follow what you're saying.
I can't accept it at all.
We have a pretty hard time understanding your value system too.
Right now there are six billion, nine hundred million of you, and every four seconds, you grow by ten.
Why do you make such a fuss if a single one of you lives or dies?
If you really think that, then you are our enemies.
I came here to try and explain our actions for you, you know?
I wanted you to understand just how significant your sacrifices are, but it doesn't look like that'll happen.
Of course not.
Madoka, someday you will become the greatest magical girl, and then the worst witch.
At that moment, we'll gain an extremely large amount of energy, the likes of which has never been seen before.
If you ever feel like dying to help the universe, just let me know.
I'll be waiting.
Why are you going so far to keep the corpse fresh?
Is there any way to get her Soul Gem back?
Not as far as I know.
Does that mean there are things you don't know then?
Magical girls defy established logic.
I wouldn't be surprised by any absurd things you accomplish.
So it's possible then.
It hasn't happened before,
so I don't know how you'd go about it.
Unfortunately, I have no way of advising you on the matter.
I wouldn't need it anyway.
Who'd get help from you?
You don't seem well this morning, Madoka-san.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I just couldn't sleep well.
Anyway, is Sayaka-chan absent again?
I wonder if I should go see her,
but I'm not sure if visiting her would be appropriate.
It's a little hard for me to talk to her right now...
Hitomi-chan, I—
Why are you going to school like nothing happened after all that?
Madoka-san?
I need to talk to you.
Can you spare a moment?
Hitomi-chan, I'm sorry. I'm not going to school today either!
Huh? Ma-Madoka-san, wait!
Um, what did you want to talk about?
Do you want to save Miki Sayaka?
Huh? We can save her?
If we couldn't save her, would you just forget about her?
I said that in a weird way, didn't I?
You might think I'm stupid, but I don't want to give up until we know for sure that she can't be saved.
She might have turned into a witch, but she might remember the voice of a friend.
If you call out to her, maybe she'll regain her memories from when she was human.
The only one who could probably reach her is you.
Do you think it'll work?
No idea.
I'm saying we do it because we don't know.
If we cut that witch in two, maybe Sayaka's Soul Gem will just kind of fall out instead of a Grief Seed.
Stories where love and courage win out in the end always turn out like that, you know?
When I think about it, I became a magical girl because I always loved those stories.
It didn't even cross my mind anymore, but Sayaka made me remember.
If you don't want to do it, I won't force you.
It'll be pretty dangerous.
I can't promise I'll be able to protect you no matter what.
No, I'll help you out.
I want you to let me help.
I'm Kaname Madoka.
God, you're cramping my style.
Huh?
Sakura Kyouko. Let's do this.
Tasty
Stick
O-Okay.
Excuse me, I don't really feel that well. Could I head to the nurse's office?
defines a sequence called the Fibonacci sequence and its
closed-form expression is given by the equation
Who's the health officer for this class?
Kaname-san is out today.
Then the class rep should go with—
I wonder if Homura-chan'll help us out.
She wouldn't do something like that.
Isn't she a friend?
No.
Well, I guess you could say we're after the same thing...
We're just teaming up so we can take down something we each couldn't do alone.
In a few days, a Walpurgis Night will come to this city.
Walpurgis?
A super-dreadnought-class witch.
She and I most likely won't be able to defeat it alone.
That's why we're teaming up to take it down.
I guess that's how it is between us.
Looks like we've got the place.
I wonder if it's really Sayaka-chan.
It could be another witch, right?
The magical energy pattern matches the one from yesterday.
It's definitely her.
Anyway, I'm going to ask you one more time.
Are you really sure about this?
I'm kind of used to this already.
I've always followed from behind, never being useful for anything.
But please, take me with you.
You're a really weird girl.
Hey, Kyouko-chan?
Yeah?
Am I a coward for letting someone else do all the fighting for me, and not doing anything myself?
Why would you become a magical girl?
Why? Because...
Don't take this lightly.
Not everyone can do this job.
But...
You eat good food every day, and you're surrounded by your happy family every day...
if someone who had no qualms about their life became a magical girl just because they felt like it, I'd never forgive them.
I'd kick their ass before anything else.
Putting your own life in danger should only be done by people who have no other choice.
Anyone else is just doing it for fun.
They're just messing around.
I wonder if that's true...
Someday you may have to fight and put your life on the line, whether you want to or not.
Only think about it when that time comes.
Okay...
Kyouko-chan, why do you...
We were noticed.
She's coming!
Do it like we planned, okay?
Ri-Right...!
Sayaka-chan, it's me.
It's Madoka.
Can you hear me?
Do you recognize my voice?
Don't falter.
Keep talking to her.
Sayaka-chan, stop it.
Please remember.
This isn't something you'd want to do!
You're going to become a hero, aren't you Sayaka-chan?
Please go back to yourself!
You can only be so difficult, Sayaka!
Kyouko-chan!
I'm fine.
This ain't nothing.
Keep calling... Sayaka...
Stop it! Stop it!
Sayaka-chan, recognize us!
Hah, I guess you're finally paying me back after all this time.
I guess we did try to kill each other at first, huh?
I said you were weak...
I guess if I had beat you up even more, you would have just gotten back up.
You're mad, aren't you?
You can't forgive anyone for what's happened.
I know.
Once you feel better, come back to us, okay?
Sayaka-chan...
Please...
Sayaka!
You said you believed you could make people happy with this power!
I beg you, God...
My life sucked. Let me have a happy dream, just once...
Kyouko!
Hey.
Are you...
Take care of her.
I made her go along with my idiocy.
You don't fight with somebody who would put you at a disadvantage, right?
It's fine. That's the right choice.
Protect the one thing you want to protect until the end.
You know... I thought I was doing that all along.
Go.
I'll take care of her.
Don't worry, Sayaka.
It's lonely being by yourself.
It's fine. I'll stay by your side, Sayaka.
Kyouko.
Mi         Homura
Did Sakura Kyouko even have a chance to save Miki Sayaka?
Of course not.
That's impossible.
Then why didn't you stop her?
Of course I would have stopped a pointless sacrifice.
But in this specific case, there was a good reason for us to lose her.
Now you're the only one left who can face the Walpurgis Night.
And undoubtedly, there's no way you can win alone.
In order to protect this city, Madoka has no choice but to become a magical girl.
I will never let that happen... Ever.
Mi         Homura
Illustrator     NamanikuATK (nitro+)
No one will believe the future.
No one will be able to accept the future.
Episode 10   I won't rely on anyone any longer
I won't rely on anyone any longer.
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Aya & Chika
Editor: guymam
limitbreakingcat
Timer: sportsrmyname
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Quality Check: kozu
rune
thedarkhaze
King_Arthur
goof