What do you think?
Ah... Yeah, you look good in it... I think.
Ah... uhm...
I'll pick a different one.
Assassination
Come on, hurry up! We don't have a world of time, you know.
Yeah, I know.
Geez, it's this way. Are you even checking the map?
Yeah, I am.
Ah! I'm gonna go check that store out!
Okay.
Give me your wallet.
What?
Thanks for waiting.
How do you do?
Are you gonna carry that thing around?
Yep.
Hey, I know a cool place, so...
Let's sit over there.
I'll pay for it.
Dummy.
You're too kind.
No problem after all, it was my fault.
Please go ahead.
Well then... Hmm, this is good!
Are you guys students?
Ah, yes.
It's a weekday today.
Oh, you're skipping school.
Today's our school's anniversary.
We didn't wanna go to the school's boring party, so...
That's true. I skipped school, too.
Right?
Sorry.
You got ice cream on your mouth.
Ah... yeah...
You're so careless, Wallace.
Let's go.
Did you get an idea of the structure of the mall?
I drilled it into my head.
How many security cameras were there on the main walkway?
Sixty-eight. There are some blind spots, but we can't carry out our mission there.
Don t interact with others carelessly.
Sorry.
Let's go back and discuss the mission. Our stuff will be arriving soon, too, so...
Okay.
Zwei...
Hm?
Your acting...
sucks.
Having gained Zwei, Phantom can now pursue missions more efficiently.
They're an ideal pair.
Those brats appear dull, but I give you credit for extending our reach to the east coast
five months earlier than planned.
l feel extremely honored.
But isn't it dangerous to use Phantom repeatedly like this?
You're right. I think it'd be wise to be careful here and put it off.
With all due respect... if you trust Phantom and me,
then I implore you to give me permission to carry out the mission.
In order to make absolutely sure that it succeeds, I'm going there myself.
Oh? You're pretty fired up.
Okay. I'll leave it to your Phantom.
Thank you very much.
Wallace Yang... That's the fake name given to me.
He's a student living in Los Angeles.
It's the same name as the first man I killed.
Ever since I killed him, I've been working all this time...
the work of killing people...
Together with her...
I...
Don Lucio...
The boss of a Dallas mafia family.
He tends to stay inside his mansion, which has strict security.
But in three days, there'll be an exception.
He'll go to that mall to purchase a birthday gift for his granddaughter.
That's...
A gift for us.
Our target arrives at the scene around three o'clock tomorrow afternoon.
We'll take up positions in the ideal locations before that.
Where do you think the ideal locations are?
You decide.
Another test?
Master told me to.
We'll mingle with the shoppers and approach the target.
People won't suspect us.
But we can't shoot him inside the mall.
Why?
It's too wide open. There'll probably be many guards, too.
They've also gained control of the security cameras.
We should attack him somewhere inconspicuous and with fewer guards.
Where's that?
There's only one answer.
The moment the target and his guards relax...
That's...
I've heard enough.
That's the right answer.
Let's go back now.
Yeah.
What's up?
I confirmed the target. But I'm being tracked.
There are two tracers on me. Help me fool them.
Come to the fountain in front of the elevator. Run.
How long do you think I've waited?!
Geez! I've already gone around and checked things out by myself!
Sorry.
l don't wanna hear your excuses.
So what are you gonna do about wasting my time today?
Well...
Depending on your answer, I'm going home.
All right, all right. I'll pay for everything you buy today.
Dinner, too?
That's fine.
I've already found all the stores.
You saved me the trouble.
It's your fault, Wallace.
I said sorry, didn't I?
The target is at an antique store in the south mall.
His car will be sent to the south exit to pick him up.
Are we going to proceed?
Thank you very much.
I think this one looks good on you.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'll attack, so cover me.
Got it.
The moment the target and his guards relax...
Now we bring this to close.
Well done, both of you.
What is it?
Nothing.
No, nothing.
Nothing...
I feel honored that you took the trouble to come and greet me.
It's just natural for a superior to show her appreciation to her subordinate.
You did a good job. I appreciate it.
I deeply appreciate your praise.
That boy... transformed...
Are you satisfied?
Yeah, I guess...
Is something wrong?
No. Where are those two?
I'll have them return via a passenger flight after taking care of the equipment.
Are you interested?
Not really.
I see...
Maybe she's tired from waiting?
You're the lady from yesterday...
Taking a trip?
We took a trip here. We're now going back.
I see. Did you have a good trip?
Yes... Very much.
Good. It'd be nice if we see each other again.
Well then!
Okay.
That was...
good acting.
Two hound dogs in a doghouse just waiting to be given a role...
That's... what we are now.
And... again...
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Never mind.
What Master said was right.
He ran through the path that took me two years within three months.
He is... who I used to be...
He is... another me...
I'm afraid...
I feel like...
I might see the truth... who I really am...
I'm afraid...
of your eyes...
Moment
Next episode
We conceal our emotions and pull the trigger.
We take others' happiness away.