Riru, grow.
Summon Kukuri, Ichihito.
Turn end.
Let's go, Ruuko.
Yeah. Yuzuki, grow!
She's using a mainly red deck.
I'll wear her down and then break through!
Summon Amethyst.
Summon effect: banish Ichihito!
Riru!
I'm fine.
Suzu, it's our turn.
Right. Riru, grow!
Summon Kitsunesaku, Fi-ax, and Hanayari!
Activate attacks and do a full attack!
Guard!
Yuzuki, grow!
Coin bet!
Burning!
Riru!
Okay, we're winning.
Yeah!
She's strong!
Will she keep attacking?
Or...
Suzu...
Right!
Coin bet!
Honest!
Coin bet?
Tell me your plan.
Um...
I'll use ARTS: Flaming Stubbornness
on an enhanced Ryuju SIGNI,
then finish the game
quick with an assassin...
Huh?
Ruuko, why'd you just come out and tell her?
I don't know! Why did I do that?
Is this her power?
It doesn't look like she
has another LRIG to use.
Then...
Unlock.
Coin bet!
It's not Tama?
And one more...
Suzu, don't be reckless.
I don't think I can beat her
unless I use my full strength.
I can't lose until I get
Chi-chan's memories back.
Coin bet!
Suzu's amazing.
This is so exciting.
Berserk!
Turn end.
She's not attacking?
What is this?
No. I haven't even grown yet...
Ruuko?
Attack!
Dominating Lightning!
Yuzuki!
The power to force me to attack?
She keeps going beyond what I expect...
She's strong!
Which way?
I know she's close.
Roger.
Then let's find a place with a clear view.
There's another battle going on...
Layla and Carnival?
Oh, dear. So violent.
Hey, asshole! Stop standing there watching!
Come join the fun!
Why? There's no need.
Anonymous is still doing fine.
Right, Anonymous?
Oh, Carnival-sama,
you're so hard on your LRIGs.
It's my turn now.
Turn end.
Without even attacking?
Correct.
Or summoning another LRIG?
In other words, I'm just supposed
to stand here and be attacked?
That's what you like, right?
So mean...
You little shit...
Coin bet!
Doping.
If you want your ass kicked that bad,
I'll hurt you so much, you can
never fight again, you pervert!
I'm going to lose!
Spell: Mad Dancing Flames!
Buff all cards and attack!
Riru, Meru, L-Again!
Those LRIGS work so well together...
Like they were partners to begin with.
It's two versus one, but I
still can't finish this.
She really is...
Strong!
Ruu... are you... battling?
Ruu?
Hope.
We should be able to see the
whole area from up here.
Right.
They're not here?
Absent.
Are they indoors somewhere?
Ruuko...
Th-There they are! I found them!
Confirmation.
That has to be them!
Let's go!
Wait.
I think it'll be over by
the time we get there.
We need to stop their battle now.
But how?
We have to force it to end.
If a third party who doesn't know
about the battles enters that area,
the battlefield should be shut down.
A third party?
Idea.
I don't know if it'll work or not, but...
Well, what next?
Her Life Cloth is at 0.
If you don't come down now, I'll finish her.
Yeah, do it.
Huh? You're going to lose!
I said do it.
This battle's boring. I'm done with it.
Go ahead.
Don't hold back.
You asshole...
You never planned to win from the start?
It killed some time.
They should be finishing
their battle now, too.
What are you thinking?
No matter who's standing in front of you,
you crush them. Destroy them.
That's what a Selector battle is, right?
Not enough.
That's not enough.
A Selector. One who chooses.
And I'm the one making the choices here.
I'm going to make a new world...
Who will it be that entertains me there?
Who will make it to the next stage?
This battle is an audition,
and you're the ones trying out!
That smirk pisses me off...
I'm going to do what I want.
Either way, if I crush
all the other Selectors,
you'll have to fight me for real.
Struggle as hard as you can, Selector.
Yuzuki!
Damn it...
I'm not done yet.
I can't win like this.
ARTS: Flaming Stubbornness.
And then, coin bet.
R-Ruuko, that's crazy!
If you lose this fight, you'll be out of coins!
I have to win.
I decided I have to save
Tama... save my friend.
She's doing this for her friend, too?
I see.
That's right.
Burning!
Suzu, it's coming.
Here I go!
Huh? Where's the photoshoot?
Nobody's here.
Yeah. No way they'd do a photoshoot here.
You put it up on a social network?
Sent.
I uploaded false information that an idol
was doing a photoshoot in this park,
along with the address.
I hope someone comes to check it out...
There they are!
Ruuko!
Hitoe!
Hana-chan?
Good. Looks like we made it.
Mizushima-san.
Kiyoi-chan?
The memories you want back
might not be all good ones.
I'm sorry.
I was so impatient to save my friend,
I ended up forcing you into a battle...
No, I was thinking the same thing.
Inevitable.
So it was one of Carnival's plots, then.
We were lucky we got there
before the battle ended.
But...
Shock!
I can't believe I'm meeting
Kurebayashi-san again like this.
Right?
I'm really surprised that you
and Hitoe know each other, too.
We met by chance at the
store where you work.
Did the manager say anything?
He asked for you to call in.
Crap...
I can't keep it a secret from
my family forever, either...
Yeah.
We have to do something soon.
For Yuzuki and Tama,
and for Hanayo-san and Midoriko-san, too.
We all have our reasons for
participating in the battles.
To protect something.
To get something back.
What Carnival said was true.
This battle is a fight to determine the
master of the room of white windows.
All the answers are in that room.
Only the person who can go there and
have their wish granted is the winner.
Kiyoi-chan,
is it true that the room of
white windows summoned you?
Yes.
I think I've been given the
same information Carnival has.
Tell me.
What's happening to Tama now?
She was summoned to that room as the keyhole.
I think it was Carnival who took her.
Question.
What is the "Eternal" that Suzuko-san
heard about from Carnival?
Eternal... The Eternal Girl?
I heard voices. Lots of them.
What I felt was an inorganic
and merciless system
that drives the Selectors
toward the battles,
and an evil will flowing toward its source.
And... sadness.
Sadness?
Probably the sadness of everyone who was
ever involved in the Selector battles.
"Why must it be me and no one else?"
"If I have to suffer like this,
why shouldn't everyone else?"
I understand a little, maybe.
All of us came from that room.
The job of the LRIG of the beginning is to invite
the girl in front of her to join the battles,
cleverly luring her into
the world of cruel battles.
We don't remember it anymore,
but inside each of us might still remain
the unfulfilled desires of those girls.
Yeah...
Then that "Eternal" is
watching us fight and laughing?
Hypothesis.
Eternal may wish for Carnival to
become the master of the room.
It's letting him control the battles.
I thought the same thing.
But when I went to that room,
I had a vague sense that
there was another mind there.
Another mind?
It was so faint, like it might
disappear at any moment.
Like it would run away if I tried to grab it.
The one thing I do know is that if
Carnival becomes the master of that room,
the chain of darkness will never end.
Yeah.
If there's anything we can do...
Ruuko...
I don't want anyone else to suffer.
Yeah.
Conclusion.
We can decide later who goes
to the room of white windows.
For now, we need to work together
to defeat Carnival and Layla.
Are you okay with that, Kominato-san?
Call me Ruuko, Kiyoi-chan.
Okay, Ruuko.
Homura Suzuko, Kominato Ruuko...
Both of them survived.
Good... Good girls.
Now then, which do I devour first?
It's late...
I wonder if Dad's home.
Chi-chan?
Suzu?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I thought I might find you here.
I wanted to see you again...
Sorry. Bye.
Wait! Chi-chan, you're acting weird.
Did something happen?
I remember it...
Just for a moment,
like a jolt of electricity...
I feel my memories scattered
all around the city.
Each time I do, my heart
feels like it's being choked.
You said that my memories
weren't all good ones, right?
Well...
I can tell that I did something terrible.
I'm scared to face it.
I decided to accept it,
but I'm scared.
I'm scared I'll feel like
I won't belong next to you.
That I won't be able to see you anymore.
No matter what happens,
I'll stay with you, Chi-chan.
Suzu...
This is far enough.
Thanks for walking me home.
It's okay.
I decided to believe you,
but I complained anyway.
I'm sorry.
Chi-chan...
Are you really okay?
Do you need me with you?
Meru...
Yeah. Help Suzu, okay?
Bye.
Chi-chan...
A New Message Has Arrived
It should be done soon
Once it's all over,
let's hang out a bunch!
As long as it's not karaoke.
Hitoe, morning!
Morning!
Good morning!
Are we a little late?
Yeah, let's hurry.
There you are!
Layla-san...
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
I want to do it so bad, I can't help myself!
I can't have someone else taking you,
like that asshole Carnival
tried to do yesterday.
You're my prey.
Fine.
Let's do it.
A battlefield opened.
One is Ruuko.
The other is... Layla?
Why?
Hypothesis.
The enemy must have approached her first.
No...
Yuzuki, grow!
Summon Snow Sled, Reflected Letter.
Turn end.
Yuzuki? What happened
to that LRIG named Tama?
If you don't take this
seriously, you'll regret it.
Unlock. Coin bet.
Here I go!
Summon Segwey!
I'm not done yet!
Despair, anger, hatred...
I was born as an LRIG from
that pile of filthy shit,
and the one faint memory I have...
is of a maddening desire for strength.
I'll carve my power
into my opponent,
and myself,
with my fists!
That proves I'm alive!
Yuzuki!
Ruu...
Ruu is fighting.
Yukki...
Is that you, Yukki?
That's right.
Where are you, Yukki?
Right here.
You and I are one.
Here?
Ruu is fighting alone.
You want to fight, don't you, Tama?
Yeah, I want to fight!
I want to save Ruu!
That's right.
For Ruu, the girl we love...
Yukki!
Go to Ruu.
Okay, got it!
Yuzuki!
Ruu!
Tama!
I'm gonna battle!
Okay!
Unlock! Coin Bet!
Tama?
I've been waiting for this.
Now, let's begin.
The Eve / Trust and Betrayal
I'll let you choose.
I was chosen!
This is my choice!
You chose nothing!
You really do belong with me!
Looks like everything has come together.
Goodbye. Be careful, okay?
Choice / Battle and Battle
"Choice / Battle and Battle."