When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Oh, it'll be spring soon.
The third term will be
over before we know it.
You think so? It felt incredibly long to me.
But the only days you attended school
are that day with the whole fuss
about Miss Katsura possibly quitting
and in the episode that
aired before this one.
I'm technically the main heroine,
so I can't ditch in an episode
centered on Hakuou Academy...
There you go again with that nonsense...
Okay, we're leaving, Hayate.
Sheesh. School is just such a drag.
Well, it'd be a different story if this
were Hourai Academy or Cromartie High.
Also, I'd love to wear the
Ashford Academy's uniform.
The Miss's dislike for school
certainly is a problem...
Well, well, if it isn't...
...Hayata and Nagi!
Man, what a coincidence!
What might you ladies be up to?
We thought we would participate
in some club activities for once.
Club activities?
Wow, I had totally assumed that you
all belonged to the "Go Home" Club.
Curious, Hayata?
What?! No, not especially...
What was that? You'd love to come observe?
Huh?
Then come drop by the club room!
Come, come!
Oh, w-wait!
Just as we'd planned.
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of the
wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong, loving
bond between servant and mistress.
This is a story from when Smiley-Smiley
were still able to fly in the sky.
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
Ordinary Stories
Society for the Research of Video?
Society for the Research of Video
Or rather, this is an awfully
distinctive club house...
This building was apparently designed
to the tastes of our founding senpai.
Oh!
This is 16mm film!
Illustrative Clip
And this is a super-HARP camera!
Oh, I get it!
In other words, this is a film society!
A society for the research of film!
Huh?
What are you saying?
Mr. Rabbit.
Huh? It's not?
We've got no interest
whatsoever in making films.
We can't do difficult things like that.
Then, what do you do?
What else?!
We record and collect interesting and
funny videos, both past and present,
and burst out laughing together!
That is what we do here,
always smiley-smiley Society
for the Research of Video!
For short, we call it...
YouTuubee
YouTuubee!
F-For short?
In other words, it is a "Killing Time" Club.
Who are you accusing of killing time?!
Society for the Research of Video, huh?
It sounds a bit interesting.
What?! U-Unbelievable!
The Miss is taking an interest in
having dealings with other people!
No, isn't she taking an interest in videos?
Come to think of it, are you
involved in any clubs, Little Nagi?
Huh? No, nothing especially right now...
Ah! Then why don't you give this a try?
Our club was originally formed
to make videos of cute girls,
so it's an easygoing club.
It'll at least serve to make some memories.
Hmm, what should I do...
Th-This is an opportunity!
The Miss tends to socially withdrawn,
so this is a unique chance to have
her enjoy a proper school life!
How could I call myself a butler
if I do not encourage this?!
All right!
Wow, that sounds very interesting.
So? So? What kind of videos
do you make, specifically?
Well, our projects are just
kind of scattered over there.
Oh, then let us watch some of it.
As I recall, you said you
made videos of cute girls...
Hello, I'm Hayako Ayasaki.
I'm a slightly mischievous 16-year-old.
Oh, someone wonderful, come
take Hayako on a date!
Oh! That was a great project!
What are you doing secretly taping me?!
And you even dubbed dialogue over it!
What's wrong with that? It's fun.
Incidentally, we have cameras
set up all over the place.
From the top of Mount Everest to Shizuka's
bathing room at the Minamoto residence.
No filming! No filming!
Then how about something like this?
What?
Miss Makimura, I... I just...
Y-You can't, Ayasaki. You and
I are student and teacher!
Oh, I want to stay like
this forever with you!
You dumb jerk! Don't make trouble for me!
Havin' affairs shows what a man's made of.
Women provide fodder for the arts.
This makes it look like I'm some
terribly licentious "sensualist"!
Hey, Hayate, what was that just now?!
Th-They're accidents! Every single
one of them was by complete accident!
Miss.
Let us excuse ourselves now.
What? You're leaving, Hayata?
You just got here.
Being shown any more strange
videos is more than I can bear!
Don't say that!
Please, help us!
Huh? Help you? What do you mean?
You seem to be having fun, my friends.
Ms. Superintendent! Wh-What
are you doing here?
Today is Onsite Club Inspection Day,
which Mistress Kuzuha conducts herself!
Huh? Onsite inspection?
I check to make sure no one is deviating
from what students should be doing.
That's right.
Wow, I guess she does some
serious work once in a while.
Do not be fooled, Hayata.
What?
There's no way she's doing serious work!
You have no idea how the students have
suffered because of these onsite inspections!
For example, the tennis team...
They don't even have a lethal technique
on the order of a Boomerang Snake?
Disbanded.
And the American football team...
They can't even do the Sky Devil Bat Dive?
Disbanded.
Furthermore, the Puppeteering Club...
I have come to save you, princess!
"Will you wind? Or not wind?" is it?
Thank you.
So they're not windup dolls...
Come, let us go home.
Disbanded.
Thus, countless clubs have been shut down.
I don't wanna get shut down!
Which is why we were plotting
to invite into our club
the superintendent's favorite guys,
which is to say, you, Hayata,
and furthermore, to show her
numerous seductive videos of you,
which would strike a chord
with the superintendent!
And yet...
Uh, but there's no way the superintendent
would enjoy seeing such...
Wh-What?!
Th-This was candid video of Hayate Ayasaki
in delightfully embarrassing situations?!
I wish I could've seen it!
I totally wish I could've seen it!
Mistress Kuzuha!
I have made up my mind!
I order the Society for the Research
of Video to be disbanded at once!
What?!
Starting tomorrow, you will be the
Society for the Research of Ono no Imoko
or the Society for the Research of
Eating Udon Noodles Through Your Nose!
Can't you at least make
it a more normal club?
Aw, man, and we were about to
make the best video of all, too.
What? The best video of all?
We were planning on showing
it to you, too, but...
What kind of video was it?
A collection of end credit bloopers!
End credit...?
Oh, you know all those Jackie films?
You know how his films show
bloopers during the end credits?
Those things.
"Those things"...
Oh-ho...
I like those.
I have to say I think
Jackie's not bad myself.
Unbelievable!
The Miss is showing interest in
something that is not 2-dimensional!
As a butler, I absolutely must
do this for my mistress!
Hey!
If you want to back out, now's your chance!
Go for it, Hayate!
This is incredible!
There's no way I can miss this!
Uh, I think it might be
better if he didn't...
Then, here I go, everyone!
So will Jackie do it?!
Fly, Jackie!
Meanwhile, right around the same time...
Oh, Miss Makimura, you can't
videotape stuff like this!
Honestly! I said, no!
I never imagined such old
footage would surface again...
In the world of the internet,
it is difficult to recover video
that has once been circulated.
Be careful with that.
I-I love you, okay? Sheesh.
(Su-Sukinanda kara, mou.)
I'm crying because I'm happy, you moron!
(Ureshi-naki ja, boke!)
First Hakuou Academy Society
for the Research of Video...
...Fun-Fun...
...Ordinary Story Championship!
Huh? What is this all of a sudden?
Come on. What is this?
Why the...
...title says it all!
For the Society for the Research of
Video, safety really comes first!
We have decided to return
to our original purpose
and make videos that the entire family
can enjoy in their living rooms!
Yup!
Uh...
After everything we've been through,
we won't let you back out now.
We entered into a secret agreement
with the superintendent
that if we submit a funny
video with you in it,
she'll triple our budget for the next term!
When did you do that?!
And Little Nagi's given her consent
to cooperate as a member of the club.
What?!
I saw nothing wrong with that.
But what is this Ordinary Story Championship?
So good of you to ask, Nagi-pon!
In other words, Nagi-rin...
...this is what it's about, Nagi Springfield!
Uh, um, won't you please address
me normally as "Nagi"...?
It happened when I was back in grade school.
Um...
I went to this one shabby fishing
village in the countryside.
It was as if time had
stopped in this village.
It was a pretty spooky place to begin with,
but at the bed and breakfast where
we stayed, there was even...
...a crumbling statue of Kinjiro
Ninomiya facing the ocean.
According to the proprietress
of the bed and breakfast...
You see, at night, that statue
turns around to glare behind him
to make sure none of the children
staying at the inn are up.
So you must never stay up late.
Oh, I've heard of these.
I see, so you're going to
collect these common stories.
No!
This is where the story gets good.
When I heard that, it made me want
to see if it was true, you know?
So a bunch of us kids snuck out
in the middle of the night.
It was truly the dead of night.
Even thinking back now, I
wish we hadn't gone, but...
It was pitch black.
And the weather was bad, too.
The wind sounded like people moaning...
We waited for 10 minutes, then 20.
It was summer, but oddly chilly.
And suddenly, we looked around
and we couldn't believe our eyes!
Before we knew it, we'd fallen
asleep and morning had come.
So, what about the Kinjiro statue?
Well, we were all asleep,
so we weren't able to check.
What?!
What a worthless story! And you
spent roughly 17 scenes telling it?!
So, we're going to collect stories like that,
where only ordinary things happen
that aren't worth telling about.
And we want to collect videos
that'll make you think,
"Aw, man, that sure was a waste of time!"
There is no need for such videos!
But everyone's got a worthless
story or two like that!
Come on now. Are you sure
you don't have one, too?
A worthless story that you have tucked away?
W-Well...
I, um...
...used to live in a really rundown
house when I was little, but...
Yeah, yeah?
You have a story?!
This house was really truly rundown
and the windows always rattled at night.
One night, I was at home alone
and back then, our electricity had
been stopped, so it was pitch black.
I tried to get in my futon and go to sleep,
but I suddenly realized something.
That strangely, the rattling sound
was louder than usual somehow.
I should've been scared,
but I went to the window, as if
I was drawn there by something...
I gently drew the curtain aside and
slowly looked out the window...
And the wind was blowing harder than usual.
What of it?!
Nothing happened!
Huh?
But that is precisely what
we were talking about.
That's our Hayata! That was a good story!
Uh, thank you very much.
Me, me, me! I wanna tell a story, too!
Miss Katsura! Where did you come from?!
You know how I'm not in the
night duty room during the day?
One day, after work, I suddenly
felt it the moment I went inside.
I thought, "Oh, something's strange."
At a glance, nothing had changed
in the room, but I could tell.
That something important was gone.
I searched my room thoroughly
and I finally figured out what was missing.
It was...
It was?
...that my wallet was completely empty!
What the hell?!
With a 500 million percent certainty,
that's because you spent it yourself!
Oh? The mic...
If I may be so bold, I think I will
have you listen to my story as well.
Mr. Klaus?! Um, this is our school...
Since it has come to this, I will
appear in any scene I can get into.
Now, ahem.
There was a time at the Sanzenin residence
when we had a dog named Lucky
running loose in the yard.
Come to think of it, we had
a stupid dog like that...
He certainly was a stupid dog,
but well, by around 6 in the evening, he
would always be back in his hut, sleeping.
Lucky
But one day, evening came
and he had not returned.
Lucky
He was left running loose, but he did
not appear to have left the yard.
However, no matter how stupid he was,
it seemed unlikely that he
had gotten lost in the yard.
I looked for Lucky all night long.
But he was nowhere to be
found and a day passed...
And a second day passed...
Lucky did not return to his hut.
However, on the third day, unbelievably,
Lucky was back in his hut!
Ooh!
Wh-Why?!
Uh, that was the end of the story.
Thank you for listening.
What happened to Lucky
during those three days?!
Who knows?
Take that!
Then, could I try telling a story, too?
We were cleaning up around the house
when Kotetsu found an old wooden box.
Unbelievably, what we found inside
was the withered mummified
hand of a water imp!
And there were words carved into
the back of the wooden box.
It said that this hand would
grant its owner any 3 wishes.
So? Did you make any wishes?
Don't do it! There's bound
to be a terrible curse!
The thing is, unbelievably...
Unbelievably...
...we put it out with the
unburnable trash the next day!
What?!
Hey, shouldn't a water imp's
hand be burnable trash?
Sorting and collection of
trash differs by region.
Yes, that is right. It is burnable trash.
Your local municipality will
have the information, but...
Oh, right. That was careless of us.
Lately, there has been a lot of
trash that has been sorted wrongly.
Be sure to properly sort burnable
trash, unburnable trash, etc.
And it's turned into an ordinary
discussion of trash...
and put it out on time on the day of
collection in the trash collection area.
All right, I am next.
Are you familiar with
the term "doppelganger"?
This refers to a phenomenon where you bump
into someone who looks exactly like you.
It is said that those who see their
doppelganger will die soon thereafter.
Supposedly, Lincoln also saw his
the day before he was assassinated.
The Japanese poet Murou Saisei...
He also had just such a doppelganger.
This is sounding rather like an urban legend.
Don't you think "Murou Saisei" sounds just
like "slow saisei (slow motion replay)"?
What?!
"toudai motokurashi
(the darkest place is under the candlestick)"
Also, "toudai motokurashi" and "Taisho
democracy" are exactly alike.
And also "Jurassic Park" and "Juraku
ni nisan-paku (2-3 nights at Juraku)".
This is more like a meaningless
story than an ordinary one...
Whether you believe or not is up to you.
Um...
If you would like, I could tell
a story about my family home.
Oh, Saki!
My family home was rundown
and the stairs creaked
whenever one of us used it.
One day, the entire family
was having dinner downstairs,
when we heard the familiar
noise from the stairs.
So, my mother said, "Our home really
has become rundown, hasn't it?"
And she had it remodeled.
And what an ordinary story that was!
Sheesh!
I've been listening for a while now and
you've been telling some boring stories.
Oh? Wataru?
Oh, I was wondering who
had come, but you are...
Club President! You're our club president!
Club president?
Yup, that's right.
This boy is none other than
the current president of the Society for
the Research of Video, Wataru Tachibana!
Ta-da!
Uh, they just made me their
president without asking,
When in the world?
I will have you know, our
president is amazing.
He makes anime MAD openings that
ordinary people would think were real.
All the "guy voice" videos were
made by the president, too!
What?!
No, it's not true.
When you get down to it, all your stories
are just left hanging there with no punch line.
That's our president for you.
Then, what?
Are you saying you can tell a
funny story that has a punch line?
Hard to say.
All I'm saying is that I want an ordinary
story that touches the heart more.
An ordinary story that touches the heart...
Yeah, for example...
This is about the universe, but...
You know that the universe is expanding
at an incredible rate, right?
Y-Yes...
At the same time, you also know that light's
the fastest thing in the universe, right?
Well, that's common knowledge.
But the universe's rate of expansion gets
faster the farther it is from Earth.
So the farther a star is from
Earth, the faster it's moving away
and finally, impossibly, those
stars surpass the speed of light!
What?!
What did you say?!
Isn't that fascinating?
P-President...
Could it be that's the end?
Thus, they say an incredibly
meaningless day ended.
I wish something nice would happen.
Huh?
A p-peach?! What's it doing here?
Th-This is...!
I can't reach it!
I know! Since I can't reach it...
I'll buy a can of peaches on the way home.
Ring-a-ding. Ring-a-ding.
And here was yet another ordinary story.
Next time, they will fight against
a neighborhood quiz contest.
Right now, we're in front of Yukiji's room.
Let's go right ahead and check
to see if she's up or not.
Oops, but before we do...
To all of you watching "Hayate
the Combat Butler"...
This will probably be the last time
that we will be featured in an episode.
This and that. Looking back, a lot
of things happened, didn't it?
Yup, yup.
It puts us in a slightly sentimental mood.
But the end is the start
of the end of the start.
Let us meet again someday!
And a one, two... Bye-bye!
Miss Committee Chairman,
Red Izumi Segawa
Hey, come wake me up!
Vice Chairman, Blue Miki Hanabishi
It's rare, I tell you! Rare!
Video of me waking up will easily get
300,000 views and 100,000 comments in one night!
Disciplinary Committee Member,
Black Risa Asakaze
I nailed it!
No way!
The End
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate...
17-year-old Maria's Butler Report
Lettering by Rie Tanaka
...and 17-year-old Maria's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Pakkyuruun, I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I am Maria, 17 years old.
The days have been cold, but
I hope you've been well.
When it's cold like this, it's best
not to force yourself to go out
and to immerse yourself
in online games at home.
If you do that, you won't become a
master at living life like Maria.
Oh, my, Hayate. But I'm only a
year older than you, you know.
Oh, pardon me, but you're so mature.
Even kind of middle-aged...
Now, here's today's fan service shot.
Please continue to give your support
to "Hayate the Combat Butler".
Preview
Shine! Jump out! Shake your hips!
The 4256th High School Girls Ultra Quiz!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Your hosts will be myself, Teruo Mikiri...
...and Demonking Abe, tima!
The participating duos will be 10,000 pairs of
girls who have gathered from all across the country, tima!
Now, which pair will win
the crown of victory?
I can't wait, tima!
Next time, "Quiz! Written as
'Foe' and Read as 'Friend'!!"
Why do I have to end up
in this with the hamster?
Quiz! Written as "Foe" and Read as "Friend"!!
Once again, next time on "Hayate the Combat
Butler", we'll be doing... the straining pose!
I feel the surge!