Kaoru.
So we're in the same class this year too?
I'm glad.
Yeah.
If you're happy about it, I am too.
Now that you mention it, where is he?
Hey there! Well don't you look chipper!
Are you that happy about being in
class 10 with all the rowdy kids?
What is it?
Nothin'.
He isn't used to being in a different class than his friends.
This is his first time.
Um, you've got a petal in your hair.
That's okay. I'll get it myself.
You changed me so much I don't remember what I was like before we met.
The breeze caresses our cheeks.
Lullaby of Birdland...
As we run down the slope,
our flimsy shadows extend.
It's like a neverending summer vacation.
It feels like when we snuck into the pool.
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
It's an intense spiral of temptation.
A beat pierces my heart. A strange one.
It vanishes after a quick spark.
Even on bad days, I dress up
and dance to some swing. The music quickly surrounds me.
What is this dance exactly? I can't stop it.
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
The melody...
is like love.
Nishimi!
I'm so happy we're in the same class again!
Are we?
Th-That's cruel.
We just did our self introductions.
Oh, that's right.
You got his ticket for the sleeper car too, didn't you?
S-Sorry about that!
He said to keep it a secret from you.
Because of that, I had a nice trip. Thanks.
It's finally over!
We should've decided the class rep by drawing lots in the first place.
No kiddin'!
Hey, I heard there was already a fight in class 10!
I'm just glad I wasn't put in there!
Hey, you done already, boxing club?
I thought you'd have a little more spirit than that.
Sen!
Hi, Richie!
Don't give me "Hi"!
Why are you fighting on the first day of school?
Just gettin' a little exercise.
That was fun. Been too long since I had a fight.
Hey, Sen! Are you listening to me?
Hey!
Wh-What?
W-Wait a minute!
Don't go!
What do you want?
You're going over there with that banged-up face?
Is it that bad?
Ri.
Sorry, but would you take this guy to the nurse's office and patch him up?
All right, get going!
Ri, he's in your hands.
Okay.
It still hurts a little,
but I should get used to it eventually.
The pain will go away, and I'll be able to relax and smile again.
I'm going to submit this painting to this year's public exhibition.
This is the one Sentaro modeled for.
Um... Uh...
Oh, that's okay.
You don't have to force yourself to give me feedback.
S-Sorry. I don't know much about art.
Oh? That's a strange thing for you to say.
After all, painting and jazz are relatively close cousins, aren't they?
A painting is created on a space called the canvas,
while jazz is created during a time called the performance.
It's like etching your living self into that place and time.
Or something like that.
I was only repeating someone.
Junichi was talking about that
when I went down to the basement.
Fukahori Yurika
It's very interesting to listen to him.
I'd like to talk to him more about all kinds of things.
Um, I went to Tokyo during spring break.
I dropped by his boarding house, but he wasn't there.
Oh, that's too bad.
Apparently, he hadn't been back for a long time,
so there were a lot of letters stuffed in his mail slot.
Someone said he might be staying at another person's place.
Oh.
One of those letters may have been important.
I wonder where he went.
Aren't you done yet?
Just put a little spit on cuts like these and they'll heal up fine.
What'll you do if it gets infected?
Come on, close your eyes.
Wh-What?
Ri'ko, I'm glad you're in the same class as Richie.
From now on, would you look after him for me?
Um, well, I'd better get going.
Richie! Glad I caught up to
you before you went home.
Are those tears?
This glob looks like a tear.
That's the tear of a broken heart.
In Greek mythology, the god Apollo
fell in love with Daphne,
the daughter of a river god.
He became obsessed and chased her all around, but she wouldn't stop running.
At last, she gave Apollo
the ultimate rejection
by turning into a bay laurel tree.
What an awful case of heartbreak!
Of course he would cry!
He was so grief-stricken that he fashioned a wreath out of it!
Who...
Who's he?
This is Matsuoka Seiji,
a second-year student.
He's the great hope of East High's art club.
Oh, stop it! You're embarrassing me!
Kawabuchi Sentaro.
We're both in class 10, huh?
Nice to meet you!
Richie, do you remember that guy from last year?
Nope.
I'm gettin' the chills.
Oh, that's right, Sentaro.
Are you free on our next day off?
I want to get you a present as thanks for being my model.
Hey! Wait up! Hey!
Idiot! Apollo, my ass!
I could never see this guy wearing a laurel wreath!
Ri, do you have detention?
Yeah. I forgot my math homework.
That's unusual for someone as level-headed as you.
Who said I was level-headed?
I'm careless as can be.
I get more absent-minded in the spring, but I better snap out of it.
This song...
It's from "The Sound of Music."
I love this song.
Yeah, I figured you would like that movie.
Oh, no, I didn't see it.
I wanted to, but before I knew it, it'd already stopped playing.
I bet it was a good movie, huh?
How could I miss it?
I guess I thought I'd be able to see it anytime.
I'm pretty dumb, huh?
What is that again?
"My Favorite Things."
Yeah, that's it!
Better not. I had my shot.
Oh yeah, there was somethin' I wanted your advice about, Richie.
About... my date.
With Yurika?
Y-Yeah.
Well then, I'll give the perfect advice for a romantic beginner like you.
Don't go.
That's all.
Huh? What the hell is that?
On a one-on-one date, you're sure to freeze up and blow the whole deal.
D-Don't make fun of me!
I can handle a date, piece of cake!
Oh, sure! You really think
you can keep TPO in mind
in front of that princess and behave accordingly?
T-TP?
You know what it is? You don't, do you?
But for your own sake, you better not go.
TP...
Man, what a pain.
I wish everyone would just stop falling in love.
That idiot! Well, don't blame me for what happens!
Sentaro, don't hold back. Tell me if you see something you want.
Oh, nah. I never get expensive stuff like this.
Even this jacket is a hand-me-down from Jun.
Oh, really?
And from then on, he was all we talked about.
Jun used to be the coolest kid in his high school!
He was good at fightin', smart too...
Oh, really?
We had a good time talkin' about him,
but now all I got left is a feelin' of emptiness in the pit of my stomach.
What are you doing, Sen?
Did your date go well?
C-Course it did!
That's right. A date is a piece of cake for you, huh?
Y-Yeah, that's right.
Liar.
It didn't go well at all, did it? Just like I predicted.
Sen, stay away from her from now on.
What makes you say that all of a sudden?
You really are dense, aren't you?
Any way you look at it, you and a refined girl like that just don't match up.
She's out of your league.
Crap. I went too far.
Hi, Kawabuchi.
What?
I heard you went on a date with Yurika?
She said she had a great time.
H-Hey, is that true?
Did she say anything else?
You wanna know?
Uh-huh! She said you were handsome
and that maybe she'll hold your hand next time!
For real?
Oh, you're already here?
Hey, you wanna try playin'
"My Favorite Things" again together?
What's this? I thought he'd be mad at me for what I said at lunch,
but he seems to be in a great mood.
Hey, what's that?
I thought only jazz was allowed in here.
Oh, that kid with the bowl cut, Matsuoka, forced it on me.
I couldn't refuse, so I just carried it here.
Wh-What's that mean?
Good for you, making a nice friend that lends you records.
Hey, Sen.
Would you come upstairs a second?
Sure.
What, did a new record come in?
Just come up here.
Okay.
Is he going to listen to that record?
What am I so anxious about?
Kawabuchi.
Did you listen to the record I gave you yesterday?
Nah, I can't get into music that has girls squealin' over it.
Isn't that the purpose of making music?
Don't you wanna become popular?
Don't really care about that.
Anyway, I'm not interested.
Well, I wanna be popular.
My dream is to become a star!
Huh? A star?
Seiji
Wait a second! Are those the underpants of somebody who's aiming to be a star?
Oh, these?
I've got a lot of brothers, so if I don't stake my claim like this,
they'll disappear in a hurry.
And we're poor, so we can't afford to buy new ones often.
Amongst all my brothers, I'm called the "good-for-nothing."
Really, singing is the only thing I'm good at.
I wanna prove that I can become somebody who's able to support his family.
To me, this band is the first step. So...
Kawabuchi, I need your talent.
A-Awesome!
That was wonderful, Maruo!
Much better than I expected!
I lost.
All right, now all we need is a drummer.
Seiji, are you gonna tell me who it is you have in mind?
Oh, you'll find out soon enough.
Be ready for a surprise.
Hey, Ri'ko!
Yeah?
School's out tomorrow, so if you're free,
wanna go to the beach?
Ma told me to take the munchkins.
But lookin' after them alone is a tough job,
so I thought I'd ask you along to help out.
Well, if you're busy...
Richie!
Hold on there. You free tomorrow?
What do you say we have us a
clammin' contest at the sea?!
Huh? "Clamming"?
Say, Sentaro...
I like clamming, but...
Ri...
What's "clamming"? Is it some kind of competition?
Oh, Kaoru! Clamming means
digging up clams at the beach.
Oh! It's confusing when this guy
calls it a contest or whatever.
Are you going too, Ri?
I guess.
Great!
Then the threesome's set!
This is gonna be fun!
I'll need to mentally prepare myself this time.
If those two have a romantic moment,
I'll casually get out of their way and just pray for Ri's happiness.
That was the idea,
but maybe that's a non-issue.
I got a hamaguri clam!
That's a short-necked clam.
Hi. Fancy meeting you here, Kawabuchi!
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you.
What cute little girls and boys.
You know, you can find a ton of razor clams over there
Razors?!
You must be Ritsuko.
I've heard about you from Yurika.
She said you were exceptionally cute!
Hey! Where are the razor clams?
Oh, they're right over here. Follow me.
What's with that guy?
Sweet-talking everyone...
Don't criticize the guy when you don't know 'im.
Bro, you come too!
Sure.
Pretty cool, right? Who wants to try it?
Me!
Me, me!
Salt!
Looks like they're having a good
time over there. Shall we join them?
I'll pass. For some reason, that Matsuoka
character rubs me the wrong way.
What's wrong, Taiichi?
Oh, no! I'll be back in a bit!
Crab!
You were surprised when the
crab pinched you, right?
Thank goodness that's all it was!
Hey, Seiji! Don't tell me Kawabuchi's your drummer!
Please, anybody but him!
I-I'm against it too!
He isn't as scary as you think.
All I have to do is set him free from what's tying him down,
and then everything should work out the way I want it to.
Hey, Richie!
Catchin' any short-necks?
Better not underestimate me!
I'm good at this kind of simple task.
Well, I ain't gonna lose either!
All right!
Clammin' contest!
What do I get if I win?
How about the record that Ri's dad gave you?
Forget about it! 'Cause I'm gonna win anyway!
What about the Beatles record?
Kawabuchi, did you listen to it?
Yeah, I heard it. Wasn't bad.
Did it stir up your interest?
I wouldn't go that far. But still...
I'm thinkin' I'll help you out with
that band you're gonna have
for the school festival.
Really?
You'll join my rock band?
Yeah.
Yay!
Richie, don't worry.
I'm so happy!
I'm just gonna be away 'til the festival's over with.
We'll only be apart for a while, Nishimi.
Let's send each other letters, okay?
Fuck you!
I was wrong about you, traitor!
Richie, wait!
Listen to me!
Don't touch me!
I don't want to listen to you!
I don't need you anymore.
Kaoru! Wait!
Kaoru!
I know. I acted like an angry little kid.
But being separated from him scares the hell out of me.
I abandoned him without thinking.
Since coming here, I'd forgotten
that I'm not good at getting along with other people.
It's better this way.
After all, I've made it this far all on my own.
No problem... at all.
Good evening.
Tsutomu, hey!
Look at the end of the counter!
It can't be.
I was waiting for you on that slope.
We made a promise to meet after school.
The goodbye blurred into the distance.
So weak, so twisted, so fragile
had I been back then,
but you gave me a small pair of wings.
I'm searching the sky beyond the twilight
for the faint flicker of light
because I want to tell you I love you.
I wrote a letter to you in my textbook margins,
but I could never give it to you.
It's still just there.