Hey, Shinpei.
Close yer eyes for a sec.
Hey! What?
Okay. Ya can open 'em now.
Wh-What did you do?
It's a gift.
I-I don't get it.
When was the last time ya came back here?
After my junior high graduation, so two years ago.
No kiddin'. Ya didn't even come back for New Year's.
Sorry.
Tell everyone I said "Hi" when ya get there.
What do you mean?
You're coming with me, Ushio, aren't—
I can't go.
Shinpei, make sure to find me.
Wait!
Don't go!
Take good care of Mio.
Ushio!
Huh?
Whoa! No! I, uh...
Sorry! Really! I didn't mean—
I-I'm very sorry!
Port Kada to Hitogashima
That weird dream almost totally ruined my life.
I need to calm down.
A-At times like these,
I need to have a bird's-eye view and calm down.
That was the first time someone's ever slapped me.
Okay. I feel calm now.
We will soon be arriving in Hitogashima.
Hitogashima lies in the Kitan Strait in
Wakayama City, Wakayama Prefecture.
With a population of around 700,
it's known for yomogi mochi and salted squid.
It's a small island supported by tourism and fishery.
I've come home for the first time in two years.
I'm back in my hometown...
for my childhood friend, Kofune Ushio.
I'm attending her funeral.
July 22nd
Hey!
Welcome home, Shin!
Mio?
Hope ya had a nice trip!
Hey! What're you doing?
I was a bit sweaty, so I thought I'd take a dip.
Well, I'm glad to see you're well.
Kofune Mio is Ushio's little sister.
There's no way she can be well so soon after her sister died.
"Take care of Mio," huh?
Jeez.
Come on.
You okay?
The sea's so salty.
How's Tokyo? Ya been to Shibuya?! Have ya?!
Nah, I don't go out much.
I got snot on my towel.
Too much information.
How's the shop?
Yes. Bring that.
Super busy.
Yeah, figures that summer break is your busiest time.
It brings too many strangers here, though.
Recently, even the people I know sometimes feel like strangers.
Yeah, there's lots of tourists this time of year.
Wh-What?
Ya sound like a real Tokyo boy!
Huh? Me?
It really rubbed off on you.
Huh? No way!
We walked to the funeral home
talking about nothing in particular.
Funeral
of Kofune.
Ushio..
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Kofune Ushio
Funeral Ceremony
When I lost my parents ten years ago,
the Kofune family took me in.
Goodbye, Summer Days
That's why Ushio was
both a childhood friend
and a sister to me.
The day before I left the island,
Ushio wanted me to make curry for her.
But I just said, "Maybe next time."
There was no "next time."
The poor boy.
It must be so hard for Shinpei.
Did ya hear?
Dr. Hishigata did the autopsy on Ushio's body.
Autopsy?
That's serious business!
Who was that? Photos ain't allowed in here.
A flash?
Shinpei!
Ya finally came back!
Sou!
Ushio tried to save a drowning child.
She was swept away.
I... I was there, but...
I'm so sorry, Shinpei.
Please...
hit me as much as ya want!
Doing that ain't gonna improve things.
Seeing everyone crying actually is calming me down.
Sh-Shinpei!
Hitogashima Hall
Hey, Sou.
I heard your old man did the autopsy on Ushio.
But it was an accident at sea, right?
See that girl?
Kobayakawa Shiori.
Y'know, from Koba Mart.
She got big.
She's in third grade now.
Remember what I was talking about before?
The girl Ushio died trying to save was Shiori.
I see.
Poor girl.
She hasn't spoken since then due to the shock.
How awful.
It is time to carry the coffin.
Shinpei.
May you lend a hand?
Yes!
I'll call ya tonight to share the rest.
Okay.
Bistro Kofune
Sorry I took so long to get back, Shinpei.
Welcome back, Alain.
Welcome home!
That Mr. Karikiri sure can talk.
Mio, why ain'tcha helping?
My job's eating!
It's almost finished.
Smells great. Ushio used to love that.
Mio, could you set the table?
There's a plate for Sis too.
It's been ages since I've had yer curry!
Thank you for this meal.
Huh?
What'cha up to, Mio?
Why the staring contest with yer own house?
Get into a fight with someone?
Summer Time Rendering
Right.
Okay.
So, why'd she need an autopsy?
Right.
That's just a rumor.
There was no full autopsy.
My old man just helped the police examine her body.
Yeah? Nothing to it, then.
But...
They found ligature marks on her neck.
Ligature marks?
Yeah.
Like someone strangled her.
In other words, it could've been a murder.
On that day, we went to the beach by the
elementary school where tourists don't go.
Ushio noticed Shiori drowning offshore and jumped in.
Mio and I also jumped in soon after, but I didn't see anyone suspicious.
Does everyone know about the ligature marks?
Of course not!
Only Mio, Alain, the police, and my old man know about it.
But given the situation, the police said murder is impossible.
They called it an accidental death and closed the case.
I see.
Yeah, thanks.
Mio?
This is the necklace Sis had on that day.
I think you should have it.
Ushio's...
Hey. Wh-What's going on?
A-At least dry yourself off first.
Hey, Shin.
I won't ever see her again.
I hate that.
I hate it!
I'll never forgive her killer.
H-Hey, Mio. Do you know something?
Come on!
Sorry.
Forget it.
You can take a bath now.
Sis would get mad if she saw me crying like this.
No more crying for me after today.
Pretty.
Shinpei!
Thanks! I'll take good care of it!
She held on to it all this time.
Bistro Kofune
July 23rd
It's best to keep busy to cope with a loss.
I'm sure Alain and Mio were thinking that.
I know I was.
Shinpei!
Yes?
Did ya find who you were looking for?
Huh? I was looking for someone?
Ya said so this morning.
You were looking fer this woman with glasses and huge titties.
Huh? Are ya sure that was me?
Huh?
You've had too much to drink, Mr. Nakamura.
Welcome!
Man, it's hotter than hell out there!
Gimme the usual.
What a day!
This is Totsumura Tetsu.
He's a relative of the Kofunes and a police officer at the only station on the island.
Sorry. The usual?
Whoa! If that ain't Shinpei!
About Ushio, well, y'know...
Tetsu! Welcome.
Mio! Still as cute as ever, huh?
Your usual lunch special with
fried shrimp and medium rice?
Correct!
What happened this morning?
Ya didn't come fer breakfast.
That's right.
Get a load of this!
Some crazy stuff went down.
The entire Kobayakawa family just up and disappeared.
Kobaya...
Kobayakawa Shiori.
The girl Ushio died trying to save.
Disappeared?
Koba Mart wasn't open at eight this morning,
so their neighbor Shiomi took a peek inside their house.
It was completely empty!
Well, that store was under loads of debt.
They might just be running from their lenders.
Hey, Mio!
Where're you going?!
Lunch Specials
Pork Cutlet
Fried Fish
Spaghetti Napolitan
Here you go.
Koba Mart
They just came to the funeral yesterday.
The Kobayakawas.
Yeah.
Sorry for leaving during lunch.
It's fine.
Shiori's been acting strange.
Yeah, I heard she stopped talking after the accident.
No, that ain't it.
It was before that.
Maybe last week?
She said something strange.
That she saw something when she went bug catching on Mount Takanosu.
She did?
A girl who looked just like herself.
After that, she felt like she was being watched everywhere she went.
What's that mean?
Like a doppelgänger?
That's gotta be a shadow.
Who is this?
Nezu. A fisherman.
Shadow sickness is what they call it.
Shadow?
It's a local disease passed down on this island.
Ain't heard of too many people seeing it recently,
but it was pretty common before the war.
If ya got the shadow sickness, ya'd start seeing yer shadow.
And everyone who saw their shadow died.
The shadow kills 'em.
Then the shadow pretends to be that person and kills their whole family.
That's the legend.
Folks who caught the shadow sickness had to be purified by Hiruko.
My gramps used to say that.
What was that about?
Hey, Shin.
When I was little, my grandma said the same thing.
Do ya know about the shadows?
No, but it's just a superstition, right?
Right.
But I saw Sis's shadow.
It was three days before she died.
We were cleaning up trash at Omoto Beach.
That was when...
Look, Mio.
No way!
If that was a joke, it ain't funny!
It's true!
But it vanished right in front of us!
Th-Then three days later, Sis...
I'm worried about Shiori and her family.
Calm down.
I need to calm down.
Mio.
Did you tell anyone about this?
No more crying after last night, remember?
Let's go see Hiruko and ask about the shadows.
Y'know, the thing the old guy was just saying.
Purification or whatever.
C'mon.
Shin.
Hiruko is the nickname for Hito Shrine,
which is located on the northern part of the island.
No answer.
No one's here.
Maybe we can try the hall.
Mio?
What's wrong?
Wait!
D-Did ya see that?
Not clearly, no.
I feel like it was Shiori.
What?
Let's follow her!
H-Hey!
Hurry!
Nothing here.
Did she go farther in?
The old fort is up there. It's too dangerous.
Mio, let's take the bird's-eye view and think.
There it is! Yer patented bird's-eye view!
If that really was Shiori, why would she run from us?
Yer right. I wonder why.
A gunshot?
It's the lady from the boat.
Shin, don't just stand there!
She's bleeding! Look!
What should we do, Shin?!
I messed up.
I'll go get help!
Mio, wait!
Listen closely... to me...
I-It...
Dad always says...
Shin...
...that until ya wash the dishes and clean off the table...
yer not done cooking.
Ushio!
Huh?
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Shadow