VT! Your shift's up?
Finally. How about you?
I'm off to Europa now.
That's got pretty good pay.
It's nothing compared to yours.
I heard you made a round-trip
from here to Venus in 4 days?
Three days.
See what I mean?
Anyway, take it easy.
Thanks.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
VT!
You're still not giving up?
Of course not! How much
do ya think I've bet already?
Suit yourself...
All right. You only get one shot,
and you get no clues.
Yeah! VT, your name is...
...Vivian Tillana.
Nope.
Oh, man!
This is a bad omen...
You be careful now.
Yeah, you know that Cock-Eye guy
that was worth 8 million the other day?
Believe it or not, I was
the one who caught him!
What do you mean, the other day?
That was 10 years ago, you old geezer!
What are you saying, you younguns?!
I was the one that taught Telpsicorei!
You mean the legendary bounty hunter?
Every bounty cowered in fear
just at the mention of his name...
Oh, everyone knows that.
Hey, Zeros.
Welcome, VT. The usual?
Yeah.
What's going on today?
The place is usually empty.
Oh, this?
Apparently a bounty named Decker
is gonna pass by around here.
They're all bounty hunters.
No wonder they all look so cheap.
What was that about
"top secret" information?
This place is full of our kind.
And I got a hangover today, too...
Besides, we don't know the face.
The only clue is a dragon-shaped tattoo...
Faye?
Like that place is gonna be any better.
Welcome to Woody's!
Right now, all of our friends who
are celebrating their birthdays
can get their pictures taken
with Mackey and Mannie!
Moms and Dads, please tell your server!
Hi.
Whadduyawant? Ya wanna get some?
I'd rather be the one that gives some.
I'm fine with that.
Hands in the air, Decker!
Don't be so difficult!
Just get the hell over here.
But I have work!
Just make yourself comfortable!
Git!
P-Please, stop.
I'll give you a good time.
Stop! Someone...!
What the hell are ya...?
VT!
So it's a bounty hunter's job to chase
a woman's ass instead of a bounty?
Sorry, but this is my job.
Wh-What...
Don't play dumb with me.
That dragon-shaped tattoo
is unmistakable proof.
Y-You got the wrong man...
Hey, you over there!
Call the police!
Tell them I caught Decker the bounty!
This is...?
Yakkun, the eight-eyed eel...
Don't be so mistakable!
Why you!
You...!
VT!
You're wearing my patience thin...
Wh-What the hell are ya?
Grudges over lost food
aren't a pretty sight!
Shit, let's get this guy too!
Found him!
Shit, I'll get you back for this!
Uh, just kidding.
Forget about us!
My 12 million...
Really. Bounty hunters are all stupid scum.
You think so?
Yeah!
As far as I know, they're all
living their lives by gambling.
Well, maybe so.
Come over here. I'll treat you to a drink.
What? Bean sprouts are good for you!
Give me a break! That's all we have!
Oh! Here it comes!
Oh, it's you, Faye. That was quick...
What?!
But that sure is a disgusting drink.
It's a prairie oyster.
It's good for hangovers.
You're the second person
I've met that drinks that stuff.
And the first one?
My husband.
VT!
We'll get it this time.
The money!
Once for the three of you?
Yeah!
Suit yourself.
All right! Here we go!
VT, your name is...
I think Adrienne is good...
That doesn't start with a V.
That's why I said we
should stick with Leticia!
You think so?
I can have that money if I guess your name?
Yeah.
I don't remember who started it,
but it kept piling up and here we are now.
Can I try too?
Spike! It's me!
Faye let Decker get away!
Go after him now...
Spike!
Get lost!
Idiotic lying scum!
I ain't treating you!
No, Spike!
Oh, my.
Oh, this, those whachamacallit brothers
did this before they took off.
And you were watching?
Uh-huh.
Why didn't you tell me?
What? I just told you right now!
What...?
Hey, VT, going home?
Got a problem with that?
Come on, Zeros.
...and what are you doing?
Hitchhiking.
My machine was vandalized.
You're really a stupid...
...lying, shameless scum of a bounty hunter?
If you don't stop with all this...!
Follow me.
Can I bring someone with me?
Man! How many times do I
have to say the same thing?!
He was short, bald, wearing
glasses, and a Sarasvati--
Huh?! What?!
I just said...!
Really! Can you turn
that shit-loud noise off?!
They say, "When in Rome,
do as the Romans do."
And it's not shit-loud noise.
It's called heavy metal!
Really, both of you together...
Who do you think is going to repair these?
What the hell am I supposed to do
with that little bit of information?
How many bald people with glasses
do you think there are in this universe?
So I said, bald, short, with glasses,
and driving a gaudy truck
with Sarasvati painted on it!
Yeah?
That you, VT?
Oh, Otto. What's up?
I got into a hit-and-run.
The guy cut in line at the gate entrance,
rammed me, and took off!
Shit, I gotta make him pay for repairs!
Tell me if you see him!
Anything specific?
Let's see...
There was some
oriental goddess drawn on...
Wait a minute! Was it Sarasvati?
Oh yeah, her. How'd you know?
Zeros.
Breaker one nine, breaker one nine.
To all truckers in the asteroid belt.
This is Heavy Metal Queen.
Ring me up if you see a gaudy truck
with Sarasvati painted on it. Thanks.
VT, this is Love Machine.
What's up with it?
Some guy you were chasing ran away?
Something like that.
I haven't seen the guy,
but I'll be on the lookout.
Thanks. It'll help.
This is Sneaky Snake. Did you say
it was a painting of a clown?
Nope.
This is Spider Mike,
Black Panther of Jupiter.
VT, I've never met you but I hear lots
of rumors about the Heavy Metal Queen.
Thanks for the compliment. So, any info?
I passed by someone like the one
you're looking for about 10 minutes ago.
It was around the Linus Mines.
That help?
Thanks, I'll owe you one.
I gotta exchange this too...
There he is!
Trying to throw me off his trail...
Maybe in the next century!
Hey, is the stupid, lying, shameless
scum of a bounty hunter around?
What?! The Linus Mines?!
You're being reckless!
What did you say?
Stay away from Decker!
His cargo is dangerous!
Hey!
Wait! I called first dibs on Decker!
What is this? Really?
Do I have to put this silly thing on?
I would have prefered that it
was your loud mouth that broke.
I heard that.
I'm going out, Jet!
Spike, the main gun on
that thing isn't fixed yet!
Nice try, buddy...
What is this? Isn't this a little risky?
This way!
My 12 million...
Hey! Are you alive?
If you hear me, answer!
I'm fine. It'll take more than that to kill me.
We gotta run. Now!
Decker was a master of explosives.
He's currently hauling the solid
nitro he was making deals with.
All of it? That's enough to
blow up this entire asteroid!
On top of it, this place was an excel mine.
The reactors have been randomly
exploding for a while now...
We gotta get this truck outta here.
How much further is the exit?
A little further...
20 degrees to the left.
There, the exit.
No good.
Behind us!
No, in front!
What's with that?
That's nowhere near enough!
My main gun is busted!
This is all I got!
And this is all I have!
What are we gonna do?
Isn't there another way?
Yeah, there is.
There's a ton of it in the truck behind us!
I don't like this.
I'm not one for delicate operations like this!
Quit whining.
Let's hit it big!
Yeah, now grab one.
That's easy for you to say.
Something is leaking...
That's probably the stabilizer.
That means...
Touch-sensitive.
Wait a sec...!
At worst, you screw up and die.
I got one. What do you want to do with it?
This pod will shoot towards the exit
and self-destruct in 40 seconds.
So get that thing in this
pod within 40 seconds.
What are you going to do?!
I'm gonna do this.
Zeros, we're opening the hatch!
Bingo!
It's clear!
This sucks.
Really...
Thanks for the help, Victoria Telpsicorei.
And give your husband my thanks.
I figured out your name because of this.
Unless you're a hermit,
everyone knows about him...
About the legendary
bounty hunter, Telpsicorei.
It will be a while.
My husband's working in Heaven right now.
I see...
Give the rest to your husband.
I'm sure he's suffering from a hangover...
...so I'll treat him to a prairie oyster.
Too much time has passed by...
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Sitting in muddy water...
...isn't such a bad life...
...if it ends after the first time...
Once in a while, I'll do
the preview by myself.
I'm Jet Black, 36 years old.
I'm often told that I don't look 36,
but you shouldn't judge people by
their looks or how much hair they have.
Things are never what they seem to be.
The next episode is like that, too.
A fairy tale that seems very unlike Bebop.
Next episode: "Waltz for Venus."
Stuff like this is good once in a while...
"Waltz for Venus"