Too much sunlight is bad for your skin!
Are you all right?
My paws slipped!
As a Royal Fairy, Perf just wants to be of service to you!
Well, it's an honor to have you.
But it certainly is quiet.
Haruka and all the other students returned home.
So it seems.
Princess Towa, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I'm fine.
I simply felt a bit faint.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Everyone really is gone!
Indeed.
But I think that makes it a tad exciting!
Today's plan is to rendezvous with Kirara once she leaves work in the evening.
From there, we'll spend the night at Kirara's house!
Princess Towa?
What are you doing?
Princess Towa, do be careful!
Princess Towa, what's gotten into you?
I couldn't resist...
To tell the truth, I've always wanted to try that, but I couldn't well do it around others...
I think that's rather endearing of you!
It did seem exciting!
I want to make Princess Towa smile more and more!
Save Princess Towa!
Fight On, Royal Fairies!
Let me help you!
I'm fine, Perf.
Kirara said that we all handle our own affairs here, did she not?
Princess Towa, what's wrong?
Is it a stomach ache?
You're burning up!
Princess Towa, are you feeling ill?
You did say you were feeling faint earlier!
No, I'm just a bit chilly. I could use some water...
It sounds like you might have a cold!
But why now?
It must be exhaustion from
adjusting to your new lifestyle!
At times like these, you should rest
with a cold towel on your forehead!
I'll go get one for you, so Perf, stay by the princess's side!
Got it!
You're burning up... I'm so sorry for you!
My apologies for troubling you.
Princess Towa, I wish I could take your place...
Your paws...
are so gentle.
They're so fluffy and warm.
Princess Towa, you've got my brother and I with you!
Got it!
Her fever hasn't gone down a bit.
If only Madame Siamour were here, she could tell us what to do!
But Haruka has the Pad...
Oh yeah, we can call Haruka!
Yeah!
It's summer vacation, so she should have her cell phone with her!
Hello.
Wh— Aroma?
Towa's got a cold?!
Indeed.
Ça alors, the poor thing.
In that case, je shall prepare a pot of Hope Kingdom's ancient medicinal thé aux herbes at once!
I'll go pick that up!
Got it!
What? Towa's sick?
Understood. I'll return to the dorm as soon as I can.
Whoah, that sounds harsh!
My show's almost over, so I'll be there the second I get out!
Listen, Perf, I'll be going to pick up some herbal tea!
Take care of Princess Towa until I get back!
You got it!
Full speed ahead!
Oh yeah, I'll wet your towel!
It's sopping wet!
This looks much easier.
It got stuck to me!
I can't do anything for her...
Perf, is something wrong?
Sorry for waking you...
I can't help you at all...
You couldn't be further from the truth.
Having you by my side fills me with joy...
Just having someone there can put one at ease...
Take this.
I've got it!
I'll be back as soon as I can,
so take care of Towa until then!
If anything happens, call us immediately.
Okay, I'm heading back!
Take care!
Oh, such is a journey...
After all my wandering, I find myself naught but here...
Such is life. There's naught to do but gather despair.
However...
nobody's here!
I can't create a Dyspairvil from nothing!
At this point, even that will do.
There's naught but to steal what meager a dream that minuscule cicada might possess!
Now, show me your dream.
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
It's tiny!
Dyspairvil! Dyspairvil! Dyspairvil!
What's that?!
It's Shut!
And... a Dyspairvil?!
What do I do?
I've gotta take matters into my own paws!
Towa, I'm on my way!
Party Roll!
Dyspairvil! Dyspairvil! Dyspairvil!
Be quiet!
What, it's just you?
Where are the Precures?
Princess Towa is trying to sleep, so be quiet!
Twilight?
Twilight is here?!
Dyspairvil, you are naught but to dispose of this mutt and draw Twilight out!
Dyspairvil!
Quit buzzing around!
T-To think a battle could be so graceless...
I'll catch you sooner or later!
Oh my, she must be having fun.
Dyspairvil!
Dys, dys, dys!
That didn't hurt a bit!
You're just acting tough!
Dyspairvil!
I'll protect you, Perf!
Dyspairvil! Dyspairvil!
Bro!
I'm here. Are you okay, Perf?
Yeah!
I gave Princess Towa the herbal tea, so don't worry!
All that's left is to chase this thing off!
Playtime is over!
I've naught but to eliminate you faux-pets and search for Twilight!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspaaaaairviiiiiil!
Dyspairvil.
Haruharu!
Kirara! Minami!
Let's hurry!
Yeah!
Dyspairvil!
What should we do?
Perf, I'll draw his attention!
Take that chance to escape!
Bro!
I'll be fine, so go!
I can't!
Princess Towa told me that just having someone there can put one at ease!
That's why I'm sticking with you, Bro!
I'll fight by your side!
Perf...
Perf!
Right!
Nah-nah, you can't catch me!
Dyspairvil.
Over here!
Dyspair.
Nah-nah!
Dyspair!
Vil?!
Dys, dys, dys!
We did it!
You fool!
You're naught but to crush them
lest my wrath fall upon you instead!
Vil.
Dyspair!
Perf, are you okay?
Yeah!
I've no time to trifle with you two.
I'm after naught but Twilight!
You won't lay a finger on Princess Towa!
'Cause we're...
We're here to protect her!
Perf, what's...
What?
We transformed?
Perf! Aroma!
Girls!
What's with the getup?
That mysterious light allowed them to transform!
I saw it with my own eyes!
Towa!
Princess Towa, you should be resting!
Worry not.
I can't explain why, but I felt so invigorated
the moment you were enveloped in that light!
Come to think of it, we're not tired either!
True, and we ran quite the distance!
Maybe it's because of your warm light!
Twilight!
So you've finally appeared.
Shut!
Is that a... Dyspairvil?
Huh? Since when?
Ah, so that's what's been happening.
Perf, Aroma, allow us to finish this.
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Prepare yourself this instant!
Dyspairvil! You're naught but to crush my nemesis, Twilight!
Viiiil!
It grew in size!
Dyspairvil.
Your opponents shall not be the fairies, but us!
Vil!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair... viiiil.
What's this noise?
This time, you'll meet naught but doom!
I can just do this!
You covered your ears?!
We're Royal Fairies!
It's our sworn duty to protect the Princess Precures!
Dyspairviiiil...
Now's your chance...
Perf... Aroma...
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Scarlet Violin!
Phoenix!
Soar, O wings of flame!
Precure!
Phoenix Blaze!
Burning!
Adieu.
Hmph.
Such a minute amount of despair counts for naught!
You won't be so lucky next time!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Thank goodness!
So, uh, bugs can turn into Dyspairvils?
Seeing you two transform was quite the surprise!
When a Royal Fairy makes a newfound vow to further serve the Princess Precures,
their wish allows them to dress up!
It's a legend in Hope Kingdom,
but it's my first time seeing it moi-même!
You two are practically glowing!
Like an aura of healing.
It's said that the light released from a
Royal Fairy can restore peoples' vigor!
That's why I felt so much better before!
Thank you, Perf and Aroma.
But that doesn't mean your cold's gone!
You need to rest more!
Very well.
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Flora!
Let the flower of yearning bloom
and fix your heart upon the land beyond the bounds
Never give in and never run away
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Come, let's enjoy the summer festival!
You got it! But wait, Yuuki looks kinda blue!
Yuuki? I'm not certain of the cause, but he mustn't give in!
Yeah! Sounds like Flora ought to cheer him up!
Yeah, Flora will—Wait! We can't let him know about the Precures!
Go! Princess Precure:
Fight On, Yuuki!
A Supportive Summer Festival!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Chiba Prefecture - Yotsuba (Age 5)
Saitama Prefecture - Mano (Age 5)