January 28.
The falling rain that night felt as cold as knives piercing our skins.
It's Ishihara, Bro!
He's making his move!
Can you hear me, Bro?
He's probably after the note.
He may already know our hideout!
Hurry!
You have to tell Setsuko!
Bro!
Don't worry about her.
It looks like Ishihara...
is after me.
Listen.
You'll be safe if you stay there.
Leave everything to me.
Bro! Bro!
Mr. Interpreter, would you thank the general for me?
Very well.
And...
Can you relay this to Mario?
"I'm sorry I can't come see you fight."
Do your best in the SDF.
Yes, sir.
Soldier!
Congrats!
You lucky bastard!
Don't think about coming back!
Be sure to wait for us!
We'll meet under that tree!
Find me a date when I get out!
Hey, guys!
Go back to your own cells!
We'll lock you up in solitary!
Are they your friends?
Yes.
They're the most important friends I made here.
"If you'd left me alone, neither of us would've been harmed."
"Is this fate?"
"Unless I kill this evil man, my friends will never find happiness."
Sakuragi Rokurouta made a firm decision.
You seem to be doing well, Sakuragi.
Yeah.
How are you doing?
Oh...
My life's a total mess, thanks to you.
So what?
You're an eyesore.
You're just a filthy stray dog.
You're a piece of criminal scum.
Don't you think it's weird, Sakuragi?
Why the fuck do you look so happy?!
That's fucking unfair!
You hared off and then started living a normal life.
Why?
Why do I have to be so pissed off and scared?
And you know what? I've had enough.
I'm going to put an end to it, Sakuragi!
What's wrong, kid?
You're not gonna beat the American with big swings like that.
Listen.
Don't try to finish it in one shot.
Use your left, and...
This is good, old man.
This is fine.
Seconds out!
Lily.
I'll show you something in the next round.
America's gonna fall.
I'll make him fall.
You overdosed on Philopon and then got a gun.
Were you planning to kill me with this?
I'll do it when I say I'll do it!
And I'll kill that bitch after I'm done with you!
She's way too good for you!
I'll rape the fuck out of her!
Then those kids are next!
I'll kill them all, too!
I'll beat them to death!
Doesn't that sound great, Sakuragi?!
Try and say that again, Ishihara!
You'll do what to my friends?
You can't win, kid.
Not yet.
He's still alive.
There's still fight in his eyes.
Just a bluff?
I figured.
You don't have the guts.
You don't have the guts to kill-
Please stop!
Please spare me!
I'm out of ammo.
Now you can't kill me, Ishihara.
Are you kidding me?
I can't stop now!
We can't go back!
You die!
Or I die!
Is this...
what you want?
Let's... end this.
Mario, you have one and only one chance.
He'll drop his guard and try a straight right.
That's the moment!
Better watch closely, Lily.
America...
is gonna fall!
Mario dug a trap in the ring,
and then he pulled the G.I. into it.
At that moment, Sakuragi was trying to end the long, long battle with Ishihara.
Both of them risked everything on that one moment.
I'm sorry, Hagino.
Please understand.
After Ishihara and Sasaki cornered you, there was no alternative but death.
This note...
contains your regret and despair.
Yet I'm about to give it up to Ishihara.
Forgive me.
I'm really sorry,
Hagino.
Hey, Sakuragi.
What are you thinking?
I just want this to be over.
If it weren't for that,
you wouldn't have turned out this way.
G-Give me a fucking break!
You can't lie to me!
Ishihara.
I'm not asking you to do anything.
Don't try anything with my friends.
I'm simply telling you.
Now, we're complete strangers.
You can do whatever you want with that note.
However...
if you still have a heart,
put some flowers on his grave.
"The happiness of Setsuko and the six boys depended on your note."
"Please understand."
"Please forgive me."
Sakuragi apologized to the departed Hagino.
Two!
Three!
Goodness, what a boy.
He really defeated the American.
No, take another look.
Hey, he's getting up.
He's a G.I.
It'll take more than one hit to put him down.
Hey, kid!
Go on offense!
Hit him with a straight right!
I doubt it'll be that easy...
with my messed up right hand.
"Please don't get up."
"Just stay down."
Mario's wish was shattered when the G.I. got up at the eight count.
"He's also a man."
"He's a boxer."
A fight between men began once again.
What am I doing?
Hey, Sakuragi.
Tell me something.
Sakuragi.
How can you live like that when you're just a stray dog?
How?
Sakuragi!
Please.
Don't go, Sakuragi.
Listen to my side of the story.
The American...
is strong.
I... hit him with my left, just like Bro taught me.
But...
that G.I...
still got back up.
Give me a break.
Boy, you've done enough.
More than enough.
No one will criticize you even if you stop now.
Well, that's good to know.
Then I'll go tell the referee...
Still...
What would Bro do?
Bro would...
Yeah.
He wouldn't give up.
Boy...
Seconds out.
Bro...
I won't give up.
I won't.
No, we have nothing to talk about anymore.
Don't come near me anymore.
I don't want to see your face ever again.
I just wanted some extra cash.
Sasaki insisted, so I couldn't say no.
But...
I didn't think... he'd kill himself.
I was scared.
I've always... been scared.
I don't want to be a guard anymore.
What... do I do?
What do I do now?
Come on, Sakuragi.
Tell me!
Tell me something, Sakuragi!
You should know!
Right, Sakuragi?
Sakuragi!
The knife that pierced his body felt cold at first, but began to burn soon after.
Does it hurt, Sakuragi?
It does, right?
You... drug addict.
You're so fucking stupid.
A knife in my chest... won't make me lose my balls, Ishihara.
Get out of the way, Ishihara.
I need to go somewhere.
Move.
Get the fuck out of my way!
H-He won't die.
He won't die no matter what.
No matter what I do, I can't kill him.
Mario...
Kid, what are you doing?
Use your right! Your right!
He doesn't have a right.
He's been fighting with a broken right hand.
That's enough, boy!
Just give up and fall down!
I made a promise...
Win, Mario.
I made a promise to Bro.
Bro keeps telling me...
to win!
Mario.
It's the police.
Don't move a muscle.
Drop your weapon.
Is he the one?
Yes.
He's definitely the one.
He's Sakuragi Rokurouta.
As the blood flowed out,
he became weaker and weaker.
Putting all his strength into his weakening legs,
Sakuragi walked toward the boxing ring.
"I don't want to miss it."
"I don't want to miss seeing Mario become a man."
Those were the only thoughts that crossed his mind.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
The rain never stops.
Gunshots echo.
As Sakuragi fall to the ground, the faces of his friends pass through his mind.
Then...