I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but a sudden situation changed everything.
I was given a red jewel from which
I gained magical powers.
The unexpected encounter I was drawn
into has been silently set in motion.
And I've been facing each day
as it arrives, head held high.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin!
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
Good evening! Takamachi Nanoha here.
For the most part, I'm just an
ordinary third grader, but...
...recently, a lot of things have been happening,
as you can see here.
Stand by. Ready.
Lyrical Magical! Jewel Seed Serial XX!
Seal!
Sealing.
Nanoha, good job!
Umm... what I'm doing now is acting like a magical girl...
N-Nanoha, are you okay?
I'm fine, but...
I'm just a little tired...
N-Nanoha!
Nanoha! Are you all right?
The Town's in a Lot of Danger?
Nanoha, it's morning already. You have to get up soon.
Today's Sunday... just let me sleep in a little longer...
Nanoha!
I'm Takamachi Nanoha, a third grader.
Nanoha! Wake up, Nanoha!
I met Yuuno-kun, a mage from another world,
through an unexpected encounter.
During the day, I'm just a normal grade schooler.
Nanoha! Come on, Nanoha! Nanohaaa!
But at night, as a magical girl, I help Yuuno-kun...
...find and gather what he's been
searching for... the Jewel Seeds.
Confirmation.
It's already been a week since I met Yuuno-kun.
We've managed to get a total of five Jewel Seeds so far.
And ever since I became a magical girl,
I've felt as though I gained something, but...
Nanoha, I think it'd be a good
idea to take a break today.
But...
Today, you will take a break!
After all, we've already collected five Seeds.
If you don't, you won't be able to last.
And you already have plans for today, right?
Yeah... I guess you're right.
Then I guess I'll take a small break
from Jewel Seed hunting today.
Yeah!
Over here!
Here, here!
Get it!
There's a soccer match today between Midoriya JFC,
which my dad coaches and owns, and another team.
And Alisa-chan, Suzuka-chan, and I all agreed
to come out and cheer them on.
Now then, since the stands are
finally full, shall we begin?
I was thinking the same thing.
Go, go!
Everyone, give it your all!
This is... a sport of your world, right?
Hmm? Yeah, that's right. It's called "soccer."
You kick around that ball and try to get it into
those goals, and if you do, you get a point.
The only person allowed to use his hands
is the one who stands in front of the goal.
Oh? It sounds pretty fun.
Nice block! That was great!
It really was!
Go farther, farther!
Do you have these kinds of sports
in your world too, Yuuno-kun?
Yeah. But I'm always doing research and
excavations, so I don't play too often.
Just like me. I'm not that good at sports.
Game over! With a final score of 2-0,
Midoriya JFC team wins!
All right!
All right, you guys! You all did great!
That was a really strong showing today!
Just like in practice!
Yes!
Well then, to celebrate our win,
who's up for some food?
Yeah!
When you take a second glance at him, he does look
kinda different from a normal ferret, doesn't he?
Now that you mention it, I agree... and that nice
doctor at the vet said he was unique, too...
Ahh... umm... I guess you could say
he's kind of a unique ferret...
Hey, Yuuno-kun. Shake.
He's just so cute!
Such a clever little guy!
He's so great!
Sorry about this, Yuuno-kun...
I-It's all right...
Thank you for treating us!
Thank you very much!
Everyone, you were really great today!
Let's give it our all again in practice next week,
and win the next match just like we won this one!
Yeah!
Well then, everyone's dismissed for the day!
Be careful on your way home.
Thank you very much!
Great job today!
Same to you.
That was just my imagination... right?
Ah, he's so much fun!
Here you go, Nanoha!
Well then, I guess we're all dismissed for today, too?
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, that's right. You both have things
to do this afternoon, don't you?
I'm going out with my older sister.
And I'm going shopping with my dad!
That sounds like fun. Let me hear
all about it on Monday, okay?
Oh, are you all splitting up for today, too?
Ah, Dad!
Thank you for inviting us today!
The match was very nice!
Oh, I should be thanking you two
for coming to cheer us on.
If you're both going home, should I walk you back?
Oh, that's all right. I'm going to be picked up here, so...
Me too!
I see.
So what are you going to do now, Nanoha?
Go back home and relax a little!
I see.
I'm going back too, to take a quick
bath and then go back to work.
Shall we go home together?
Yeah!
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
Nanoha, have you grown a little taller?
Dad! You said that the other day, too!
I don't grow that quickly...
Is that so?
Nanoha. If you're going to go to sleep,
you should put on pajamas first.
You should take a nap too, Yuuno-kun.
Well then, I'm going to sleep until it's time for dinner...
As I thought... it really is exhausting for someone
to use magic they're not used to...
If only I were stronger...
You sure were great today.
Oh, no, not really...
It's just because we had a good defense.
But you sure were cool back there.
Oh, I know.
Here you go.
It's so pretty!
It's probably just some normal stone,
but I thought it was beautiful, so...
Nanoha!
You noticed, too?
What's the matter, Nanoha?
Do you want to come in with me?
Sorry, Dad! Some other time!
I'm going out for a little!
I see...
Have a nice time.
Raising Heart... please!
Stand by. Ready.
Set up.
This is horrible...
This was most likely caused by a human.
If someone puts their strongest feelings and wishes
into a Jewel Seed, it releases its maximum power.
That boy really did have one back then...
I should've noticed, yet I...
I might've been able to stop this before it happened...
Nanoha...
Nanoha?
Yuuno-kun, what should I do in cases like these?
Yuuno-kun!
Ah... yeah. To seal it, you need to get close to it.
First, we need to find the place it sprouted from.
But since it's grown this large, I'm not sure which
would be the best way to start searching...
It'll be okay if we just find where it all began, right?
Area Search.
Lyrical Magical! Search!
Find the place where this growth is at its worst!
I found it!
Really?!
I'll seal it right away!
It's impossible from here! We need to get closer!
We can! It'll be fine!
Right, Raising Heart?
Shooting Mode.
Set up.
Go and capture it!
Stand by, Ready.
Lyrical Magical!
Jewel Seed Serial X!
Seal!
Sealing.
Receipt Number X.
Mode Release.
Thank you... Raising Heart.
Goodbye.
To be able to use long distance
magic even I can't use...
This girl... just how much magical talent does she have?
We've caused a lot of trouble for a lot of people, huh?
W-What are you saying? You're doing what
you can to the best of your ability!
I noticed that he had one...
but I thought it was just my imagination.
Nanoha.
Please, don't look so sad.
I was the one who started all of this...
You're just helping me out with what I have to do.
Nanoha! You've been doing just fine!
Nanoha...
That was my first mistake since becoming a mage...
To cause trouble for someone... is very painful.
By thinking that, I decided to help out Yuuno-kun.
I decided I wouldn't just give it my best...
but to give it everything I had.
And I wouldn't just be doing this to help Yuuno-kun,
but to search for the Jewel Seeds because I want to.
So something like this... would never happen again.
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
All of us went to have some
fun at Suzuka-chan's house.
She has an older sister, a maid,
and lots of cats and kittens!
But something really outrageous
happened to one kitten!
And then who appeared?
A new mage!
What's her goal?!
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Four:
A Rival!? Another Magical Girl!
I, Lyrical Magical,
will do my best!