Rio-senpai!
Well done!
The parts?
Got it!
If you look hard enough, you'll always find it!
So warm!
I'm revived.
But, Rio-senpai, was it your turn for yard duty today?
There was something I wanted to burn.
It's been six months since Kanata came to the fortress.
She's plays pretty well now.
She just has a good teacher.
That's hot!
I finally won't be needing my ear plugs.
Hey, madame, shouldn't you stay in town this winter?
I'm fine.
I won't die that easily.
I've been living on this mountain alone for fifty years after all.
Go on... Go on... Go on... Stop!
It's finally looking like it should, huh?
Will you be fine handling the rest on your own, Noel?
Yes, I'm content.
Well, shall we have some tea then?
Okay.
Hey, Kureha-chan...
Huh...? Where did it go?
It's supposed to be here...
Oh, my. What's the matter?
The military annual was here, right?
Kanata said that she wants to know about Princess Iliya.
I'm sorry.
If it's not there, I don't know where else it can be.
Geez...
Naomi-san might have one!
I'll ask her the next time I see her.
Okay.
Princess Iliya is the eldest daughter of the current Archduke of Arcadia.
I think I've told you before.
Anyway she's a really famous tank operator.
A while ago, Klaus-san said "if she were alive".
Yeah.
She passed away. About two years ago...
In the war?
No.
She was assigned to the royal guard,
but she dedicated herself to enhancing national influence and traveled around the country.
And while traveling to a city, she tried to save a child who was drowning in a river...
But, I'm quite relieved.
This is merely a rumor, but...
Iliya...
Kanata-san!
Yumina-san...
And...
Err, it's Kanata.
Um... Yumina-san... well...
brought Yuuko-chan here...
Oh, Yuuko-chan is the daughter of Martin-san.
Err... actually it's about an old lady named Jacott-san. She lives alone in the mountains...
I sometimes buy vegetables and things from her in the mornings...
Oh, remember those pickled vegetables that you said were delicious the other time?
It was Jacott-san who made those vegetables.
And lately no one has seen Jacott-san...
She's quite frail, so they're worried...
And apparently she lives quite deep in the mountains,
and-
Geez... All right! All right!
I hear you, so just wait a moment.
Okay!
It's said that Princess Iliya
was supposed to marry the emperor of the holy city, Rome,
to improve our relationship with them.
But then that would make her the third empress!
Third! The third one!
Unbelievable, right?
So she'd be practically a hostage, right?
Well, when her highness died, that fell through,
and we have been fighting them up until the truce earlier this year.
Good grief,
we're finally here...
A partially built house?
Didn't you say she lived by herself?
That's what it was supposed to be.
Madame!
I see...
Yuuko did.
Yes.
She's such a kind girl.
She's too good for that sniveler Martin.
This is a lovely house.
Thank you.
I built this house.
That's amazing!
Then what about the one across?
That is for my son...
You have a son?
He now lives in city far away,
but it'd be great if he came home someday.
So it will always be available for my son and that person.
I should maintain the house well.
And when will your son return, Madame?
Very soon.
What's coming soon, is just winter!
You should descend the mountains the snow begins to fall.
I cannot do that.
I...
must complete that house.
Before that happens, I do not plan to move even if I die.
But-
Quit kidding already!
What about winter preparations?
Firewood? Food provisions?
You haven't prepared anything, have you?
It'll work out somehow.
Thank you for your concern, young ladies.
Madame!
Good grief, what a stubborn old lady!
You're both similar, aren't you?
Give me a break.
How am I...
That's because, at times, you're not true to yourself when you speak or listen.
Shut up!
Hey, that letter...
Why did you let me read it?
I heard about it last week during communications.
By the way...
...the Roman army on the Eastern border has been mobilized.
I see. For old lady Jacott, huh?
All right!
Take these, too!
Thank you very much!
By the way,
do you know how things are going with the peace talks?
I...
I'm sorry.
If only Princess Iliya were still alive...
That reminds me, Martin,
didn't Iliya-san have a younger sister?
Here's your 4 million back.
That's the first I've heard of it.
Well, she's not the Archduke's legitimate child, so no one talks about it.
She's third in line for the throne or something like that.
Err, is her little sister...
Bye!
Thanks!
Sorry about that.
Can we walk around a bit?
Hey, Kanata...
What was the village you were born in like?
Just a normal country village.
There were crop fields with many cows and goats,
but there weren't many people.
It's probably different from here.
But it was a nice place, wasn't it?
And you have good parents, too.
I can tell by looking at you.
What kind of place did you grow up in?
I grew up in a small village near the capital,
surrounded by beautiful forests and lakes.
I lived there with my mom.
It was boring.
A peaceful life where nothing ever happens.
My one comfort was my beloved sister...
We had different mothers, but she came to visit once in a while.
I admired her.
She was beautiful and kind.
And she accepted her fate silently.
I learned the trumpet from her.
But she was too kind...
and because of her kindness, she gave her life.
When I first came here, I thought this town was like a labyrinth.
I got lost and ended up here.
I felt like I had finally reached my goal.
But I realized later
that this was merely a dead end.
That's not true!
I often get lost.
But,
I like being lost!
It's all right to be lost, isn't it? Even if it's a dead end!
That's how I met you!
At times, I envy you, Kanata.
If only I could be that true to myself.
That should do it.
Why are you so concerned about me?
You're similar, to my mother.
I don't remember having a pretty daughter like you.
She had a forbidden love, and gave birth to me.
She always waited for him.
A man who may or may not come by once a year.
Mother lived an unfortunate life like that, until she died.
Why did you think that she was unfortunate?
That's because-
I am happy.
He promised he would come back.
That he would come get me.
That promise alone, was enough for me.
How could that be...
What else could I have done?
That's right.
If there were other things I could do, I might have done them.
But you know...
Is that enough for you?
Are you content with just that? Is that really happiness?
Because I have memories of loving him.
I have my memories of him and the hope that I will see him again.
That's enough.
That is more than enough for me.
I thought it was getting cold.
It was on a snowy night like this that I first met you...
When Madame was young,
Seize was a thriving resort city.
She fell in love with the young heir of a rich merchant.
And soon, she had his child,
but that man already had a family.
A blessing or not, that man's wife couldn't have a child,
so he took her child and went back home,
with the promise that he would one day come back for her.
Madame! Madame!
Now that I'm old, I sometimes think...
Back then, if only...
Old lady Jacott!
Life...
is a cycle of loss.
But before you can lose, you must first gain.
However, the happier you are from your gain,
the greater your pain is when it's lost...
But if you have the memories of your happiness...
With those memories, a person can live on.
That's right.
This may not be a great time, but I found it,
the picture of Princess Iliya.
Naomi-san!
Filicia, it's fine.
I think it must have been five years ago,
when the Princess came to Seize.
Is that Shuko?
Rio-senpai!
Actually, I think my parents must have wished
for me to find a husband and succeed the family.
But, I was enchanted by the sound of that trumpet,
and I simply couldn't forget it.
That was...
Iliya-san, wasn't it?
So, you really did meet her too.
How wonderful it was...
the sound of Iliya-san that resounds in me.
Then you and I met.
I think I may have been running away, to this town.
So at first, nothing really mattered.
I thought it was just a place, that I'd leave eventually.
But now,
I truly do not want to leave this place.
That's probably why I must go.
I can do it.
There is something that only I can do after all.
I do not intend to say goodbye.
No matter how far we are separated...
The sound will echo...
The sound echoes...
...and reach out.
Kanata, have I been a good senpai to you?
Yes.
And so, Rio-senpai left us.
She left a sound that will continue to echo in my heart...
...a wonderful...
...wonderful sound of the sky.
Next time:
A Visitor.
A Blazing Field of Snow.