Street No. 06
"The Pandora Maid Service"
And Yet the Town Moves
Antique Shop Kamei Dou
To be ignorant is not about being without shame.
FRESH FISH SANADA
It is about being pure.
Until the time comes, there is no need to know.
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
Kaze wa nandaka suzushige
Doyoubi no yoru wa nigiyaka
Kurai kimochi sae
Suguni harete
Minna uki uki
Uki uki
Downtown e kuridasou
Antique Shop Kamei Dou
Is that you, Hotori?
Wha...?!
How did you know?!
You put your hand over your mouth
and took a step back.
You even know that?!
My guardian spirit let me know...
Shizuka, when did you acquire such powers?!
Fooled you...
A mirror!
You were looking from above, weren't you?
To not be able to see through a novice trick like this...
You can't be my assistant.
Today, I came looking for Tattsun's birthday present.
At an antique store, huh...
Oh...
This scale...
To bring out the flavor of this coffee to its fullest,
you need this much sugar.
I think this has something going for it...
But it's expensive.
Shizuka, is this good?
That's a vague question.
Um, that was...
Oh.
Whoa!
And so...
Are you going to buy it?
Is this deferred payment?!
Oh yeah. Changing the subject,
I recently went to Africa.
Ah, that's why you're wearing such weird clothing.
This is a souvenir for you, Hotori.
Yay! I'm so happy!
What is this?!
It's disgusting, disgusting, disgusting!
It's three kinds of disgusting!
Note: Modern slang term "3K" – for example Kitanai (dirty), Kusai (smelly),
Kimochiwarui (disgusting), three ways to describe a disgusting person or thing.
All three "K"s in Hotori's list all mean the same thing.
But disgusting actually only has one meaning.
For some reason, I was pressed
by the local wealthy man to marry him.
He made me take this mask; that's his family treasure.
But I'm afraid of him finding out where I am
with the powers of the mask...
Ugh, do not want.
There, there...
Think of it as a good luck charm for relationships.
Stop it!
Oh! I've come up with a "Tacchan" present, too.
It's "Tattsun."
A romantic one.
Antiques Shop Kamei Dou
See you later!
I have a feeling she was just trying to
get rid of stuff she didn't want...
What's that?!
Actually, rats don't like cheese, poko.
Fall Festival
Ham
Best Before Date
Cleaning
I'm days early, but...
Chartered
Happy Birthday!
Thank you.
This is the first time since elementary school
that people have celebrated my birthday like this.
Fish
This is something from my family.
People call it "seafood salad"...
Thank you! I'll take good care of it!
No, please eat it while it's still fresh.
So in other words... Sanada, sakana, salada...
Note: Sakana means "fish." So this is "Sanada's Fish Salad."
You rhyme too much!
I didn't even think I'd get complaints for such a thing.
LIST
Well, other than that, we've received
a fruit basket from the vegetable market,
two free dry cleaning coupons from the cleaners,
and various bottled beverages from the dollar store.
LIST
I bought you a cake. Thank me.
Th-thanks.
And so! Now that the party is in full swing,
here is today's main event!
But we just started.
And the main event is Tatsuno's birthday party.
You're such a lousy MC.
H-hang in there...
Here!
It's my present to Tattsun.
Thank you.
It's an old box...
There's something inside.
I know! I'll open this box two days from now...
On my actual birthday!
Unfortunately, that is a wish that
cannot be granted, Tattsun.
Excuse me?
There is no key.
From the time it came into stock
at Antique Shop Kamei Dou,
the key was lost so they can't open it.
What?!
It's romantic because you can't open it.
How about imagining the contents of the box
on a long autumn night?
She said I would be fine as long as I said this.
No way, it's kind of creepy!
Josephine, Jo-star, Jo-Jo.
I just wanted to say it, poko.
Man, this is great, great!
Let's have another birthday party!
After all, this is a café that's always empty.
Sanada, when is your birthday?
February...
It's so far away! You're so useless!
What about you, Granny?
April.
What about you, Senpai?
Me... I'm okay.
Awww, why?!
Don't be shy.
Cafe Seaside will muster all forces to celebrate.
What about you? When is yours?
Mine is May.
A May girl is very smart.
The very smart would hear that and be disgusted.
So, what about you?
Speaking of May...
She changed the subject.
Ta-da! I found Senpai's student planner!
Stop it!
If you open that, something
frightening is going to happen!
Um...
Name: Kon Futaba
Date of birth: September 8th, xxxxx
Address: Tokyo-to Ota-ku Maruko-cho
Oya High
School
September 8th!
That's today!
No wonder... you didn't want to say...
What have you done?
What are we going to do
about this awkward situation...
Do something about it.
H-happy birthday!
Ha... ha...
Happy birthday to you...
Yay...
I know! Present!
I'll go to the snack store!
Stop it with your cheap pity!
I messed with it too much and so it came off, poko.
The only thing I have that can potentially be
a present is a good luck charm for relationships.
Huh. I would rather have that instead.
Instead of this Pandora's Box.
Oh, then...
I'll give Kon-senpai the romantic box
and that relationship thing to Tattsun...
Okay, okay.
It seems everything is going to work out fine!
Before you do that, could you
get this place under control?
Senpai, next year let's celebrate properly.
I've memorized your birthday!
September 8th, Futaba Kon was born.
"Mortifying memories, Futaba Kon."
With this, no one would forget!
Note: Hotori turns the previous wordplay into the kind of mnemonic
that one would see used in a Japanese history class
(9 8)
Kuyashii Omoide, Futaba Kon
Note: Hotori turns the previous wordplay into the kind of mnemonic
that one would see used in a Japanese history class
You're treating me like a bad historical event
like when firearms first entered Japan?!
Cup noodles are most tasty at cook time
minus 45 seconds, poko.
Note: Pun. Kawaiso means "pitiful."
Kawai So
—A few days later—
Hmm... It opened.
You're kidding?! Wow! You can be a thief!
And I'd catch you.
With you as my opponent, I feel that I'll never
get caught even if I'm old and weak!
Well, then.
What's in the box?
A good luck charm?
Well, that's no fun.
This is... a good luck charm for relationships.
That Tatsuno... Didn't this one have
a better benefit after all?
I feel empty now that we've opened it...
Pandora's Box suddenly became an ordinary box.
From between the walls, it's coming, poko.
Some relationship charm you are!
It's pointless for me to be married to a rich man in Africa!
Excuse me!
Oh...
If I remember correctly, you're Hotori's friend...
Tacchan.
"Tattsun."
No, I mean Tatsuno.
I heard you buy things that seem old...
I'll buy it.
Let me see what's in the box.
Antique Shop Kamei Dou
Internet Room
For this assignment,
post it to the remote upload point and turn it in that way.
- Create a website
- Personalize a fictitious company
- Introduce something you like
- District, School etc
Hey! Does upload mean some kind of hill?
Shut up, you need to help out more!
I'll code the tags, so you collect the materials.
Thanks, Suzuki.
Argh! I should've paired up with Suzuki!
I picked a warrior type for some reason.
What I can do is muscle training!
Uhh, hmm...
You don't have to push yourself too hard.
Just make it look nice on the surface,
and make do with that.
I finally finished typing the title.
Maid Cafe Seaside
I'm going to make this site public in actuality,
and attract customers.
Oh, that's a good idea.
You can do the assignment and advertise,
killing two birds with one stone.
Arashiyama...
This... is the illustration you asked for.
Wow, thank you! It's perfect!
Then here is that photo of Tattsun in her
Maid outfit I promised you.
Oh, marvelous!
Come on by!
I'll take this illustration and make it really big...
You are going to be caught for fraud.
Just now you said that I should
just make it look nice on the surface...
Well, after all, you have to change from the inside.
- Create a website
- Personalize a fictitious company
- Introduce something you like
- District, School etc
Well, turn it in within two weeks!
Gah, I didn't make any progress!
In Maruko Town's sky, the moon which is
the pride and joy of the town came out, poko.
Seaside
Thanks for waiting.
Um, the curry...
Who was having it...? Oh well.
You guys share!
So cruel! You are below a regular waitress!
STORE
On top of that, while we're slacking off,
there are words that I don't even want to recall
pinpointed and written here.
You're becoming more and more like Granny.
Okay, as joint responsibility,
I'm adding a salad and coffee.
You moron! Kobu-hei!
Don't displease Maid-sama!
Hey, Tattsun-tsun...
My nickname is devolving...
...do you have a computer in your home?
I do. The one that my little brother uses for his games.
After we're done with work,
let's continue with our assignment.
Oh, but today I heard Kon-senpai
was absent from school with a fever.
Since she's living by herself,
I thought I should go and take care of her...
You're kidding! They say idiots don't catch colds.
She ran into some bad timing...
Speaking of colds, I haven't caught one at all.
The last time I was out sick
was during middle school, I think.
Liar! In middle school you used to boast
that you never close shop.
If you say that, we all had perfect attendance.
It's no wonder I can't catch a cold...
Hey, is Sanada at home?
Hiroaki? Yeah, he's back home.
Good!
And so...
Can I go to second candidate Sanada's
home to do my assignment?
What do you mean "And so"?
You're still on the clock!
This is doubling as advertisement of the store.
There are no customers, so oh well.
Yes!
There are customers right here!
Oh!
You're there every day, and so I thought
you were customer-shaped chairs.
S-so cruel!
Granny is still a hundred times worse!
The sharpness is not the same!
Those knife-like words are pointed on the tips!
Hey! You're going to Sanada's house?
He owns a PC, too.
You can go, too.
Hey, wait up, wait up.
Oh? What about checking on Kon-senpai?
Let's go do that later together, too.
FRESH FISH SANADA
Shurin
Huh? PC? That's fine, but... when?
Now?!
MURAKAMI MEATS
I'll get you something.
Is potato croquet okay?
I'm right in front of the butcher's.
Butcher's?!
Even if she stops to buy some croquets,
she'll get here in just a couple of minutes!
On top of that, a potato croquet is the cheapest!
Say, could you pick up some
custard puffs from Romando?
What?! You're so hopeless.
When did you learn such luxury?
Taking advantage of me, you little...
Good! I just bought myself 20 minutes!
That was close.
White Paper
on Schoolgirl
Uniforms
I have a lot of dirty magazines under my desk!
Excuse us.
I made it...
Oh...
On the important computer...
There are dirty pictures
I collected diligently from the internet!
What is this folder?
Sanada, you're such a pervert!
It could happen!
DELETING DATA
The only path left is to delete the data...
Dirty
There's no comparison!
We're here.
Yo.
Sanada, is it just me, or do you look a little worn out?
I feel like I just overcame the dark side to become a Jedi.
What is he talking about?
Here are the cream puffs.
Sanada, sorry to come by on such short notice.
Oh, I'm totally all right with it...
So, I want to put this drawing
at the entrance of the homepage.
We don't have a scanner, so it's not possible.
Scanners? Didn't you say you wanted to be a Jedi?
Note: She thinks he is referring to the 1981 film, Scanners,
which featured people with telekenesis and telepathy.
I'm not talking about that right now.
A scanner is a machine that
inputs a picture into a computer.
What?! I thought you can do anything
if you only had a PC!
You think just like a middle-aged man
who's behind the times...
We wasted our time coming here!
Let's go back, Glasses!
"Glasses"?!
I erased all of my data for nothing?!
Haruka
Ichijo
Includes latest DVD
30 mind-blowing scenes!
Oh?
Isn't that the novel I lent you a while back?
1/4 Intent to Kill
Man! You just stacked it in a place like this!
I'm taking it back.
No!
Don't touch that!
See? Even if you make it look nice on the surface,
your cover will get blown.
He is the worst! From now on, I'm going to call him...
Pervert Sanada.
It's creepier if a boy his age
didn't own a single book like that.
Come on, let's go feed Kon-senpai
really quickly and go home.
In this world, it's about looks or money,
and it's a circulatory letter, poko.
Note: Pun. Kawaiso means "pitiful."
Kawai So
Kon, Densuke
"Densuke Kon"?! So she was a man after all!
Men are dangerous! Men are pervs!
She's a girl living by herself, so she's using
her dad's name on the nameplate.
Is she sleeping?
Oh...
It's open.
She's so careless.
Senpai, we're coming in, okay?
Careless, careless...
Note: the two are carrying on in the style of the comedic duo Oriental Radio
Care...
...less less less less less!
Let's go!
Tattsun, you're so cool!
Be quiet! We're in a sick person's room!
You're the one who got me rolling...
Such a high fever...!
Senpai, are you okay?
She caught a more serious cold than I thought.
Put a blanket on her! I'll make an ice pack.
Okay!
Kazutoyo Arai and his voice actor look alike, poko.
When she's quiet like this, she's cute.
Uh... I feel bad... I'm going to die, Mama.
Mama...
Senpai!
You should be sleeping...!
I'm going to... have to kill you...!
Calm down, Senpai!
That was close!
You were talking in your sleep,
but it was all muffle muffle...
...so we couldn't tell what you were saying!
Really?
Really!
I see...
Here Senpai, please take it easy.
S-sorry girls...
I can get over this. And I can put myself to bed.
I know, I know.
Hotori can fall off of her desk sometimes, too, poko.
Since she's sweating now,
it seems her fever is starting to break.
I'll make her something to eat, so you be quiet.
What are you going to make?
A rice soup with leeks and eggs.
It sounds good—
It's not for you.
Fine. I'll eat the cream puff we just bought...
They're not here!
What are you talking about?
We gave them to Sanada, remember?
Oh no!
I gave them to Pervert for free!
FRESH FISH SANADA
My dirty magazines
were found out by two girls,
so today is a Sanada Memorial.
Today's cream puffs are bitter...
Kawai So
She has enough CD's to open a store.
She must love music very much...
Oh! It's a guitar!
The strings are thick and it seems like it's missing some...
Is this a guitar for novices?
It's a bass.
You are going to be punched
by every single bassist out there.
Oho.
So this is a bass...
Hm? No sound comes out?
Oh man, you are so noisy.
Here. The amp wasn't turned on.
Sound comes out of this big speaker?
Wh-wh-what?
It's nothing at all.
Here, go back to sleep.
Grrr!
You're the one who flipped the switch!
Seaside
We're back.
I'm sorry we're late!
Okay. Welcome back.
Yo.
Hey! Are you still slacking off?!
I may not be Granny, but even I'm worried
about how your store will end up!
I went back to the store and came here again.
Hiroyuki was terribly upset, did something happen?
Your...
Your son, Pervert, is so unhealthy.
That bastard, did he do something to you?!
There is no way I'd let him!
Really? You're okay?!
You're such a pain! I swear!
Oh?
Really? You're okay?!
Today...
I can't do it anymore, poko.
—Next morning—
MARUKO SHOPPING DISTRICT
Tattsun was absent from school today.
I wonder if she caught Senpai's cold.
Speaking of which, my dad seems to have
gotten sick last night, too.
I wonder if there's a cold going around?
I feel groggy myself, so I'm going home to rest...
Closed
Today
Oh, oh?!
What's wrong, Granny?
Oh... Is that you, Hotori?
Isobata
It's been a while, but I caught a cold.
It's not a big deal, but I don't want
you to get it, so go home.
There's a cold going around, and fast.
Seaside
I have to be careful, too.
Idiots don't catch colds.
Oh my? Am I catching a cold?!
I'm so healthy I hate myself!
Seaside
What should I do?!
Hi, Fu, Hi, Fu, Mi, Yo!
Taikutsuya rock damashi tazusaete
Hitorigurashi no bakuon jinsei
Tennen no chouchin fugu na hoppeta de
Machi wo kaosu ni kyo mo makikomu
Tsundere wa intelligence no akashi nari
Kyou mo kareni wa naze ka kokurezu
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatako
Konna band mo yarase ja ne
Konna member rock ja ne
Mezashite iruno wa ondo ja ne
Tadori tsuku no wa nehan ja ne
Warera wa Meido "Yeah!"
Meido sugata de
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kokora wa meido "Yeah!"
Jiken genba wa
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ahhhh..."
Muteki no meido "Yeah!"
Benpi wa nanzan
Kancho kancho!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kiyoku tadashiku isagiyoku
Seaside wa zessan! Eigyouchu!!
"Meido arigatou gozaimasu!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
And so, the two eloped to a faraway
land where no one knows.
My, how romantic. They ran away because of love.
That old man seemed like trouble
when he was younger, anyway.
Not that kind of trouble. It's when you
fly away on an airplane and run away.
Really?! What if you run away into the sea?
Eh?
Swim away?
You're going to swim to elope?!
Cafe Seaside
Next episode, Street Number Seven,
"The Naito Flight of Love."
Cafe Seaside
STREET NO. 07 "THE NAITO FLIGHT OF LOVE"
We turn groggily round and round, poko.
Cafe Seaside