Summer has arrived at Fumizuki Academy.
'Tis the season for the sun to burn bright above and for water to splash this way and that.
Oh, yes, and nosebleeds as well.
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Fly! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Sixth Period
Me and Pool and Swimsuit Paradise and.
Oh right, Yuuji.
What?
They cut the gas, so there's only cold water.
Why couldn't you have told me that before I went in, you bastard!?
Sorry, dude.
Start with your limbs, since they're the farthest from the heart,
and then slowly move inwards...
Look, man, I didn't ask you how to take a damn shower with cold water!
What the hell is your problem?
Oh, I know! Take a cold shower and you'll calm down in a jiffy!
That's why I'm pissed off to begin with, you dipshit!
Christ, man, your gas is off and you have nothing that could even be considered edible.
Seriously, how the hell are you still alive?
That's rude.
I do have something that could be considered edible.
You'll get plenty of calories from those.
I'm not really into drinking salad oil.
Look at the fridge, man. It's totally empty.
That's rude. It's not empty.
Whatever, I'll just use this to calm myself down.
So which ones are yours?
The coke, coffee, ramen, and the chilled Chinese noodles.
You asshole! You're gonna force me to eat the damn chopsticks, are you!?
Wait, you're serious?
Well, they're more edible compared to the inorganic plastic bag.
You're not getting any chopsticks.
There's no way I'm gonna eat this with my hands.
Hey, don't worry, I brought some stuff for you too.
Diet coke, konjac jelly, and agar.
I can't get any calories from these!
Hey, I'm trying to be thoughtful here. I don't want you to get fat.
I don't think that's something I need to worry about!
Well, all you're taking in is sugar and fat.
Because that's all I eat!
Now I'm getting pissed!
What? You wanna go?
Sure.
I've been planning to settle the score with you anyway.
Great. Same here.
It's in my eyes!!
Not bad...
You too...
But I'm just getting started!
I'm not going to go easy on you!
The staff enjoyed the food after this.
I don't think this really accomplished much...
Yeah...
Damn, I'm all sticky now...
Gotta take a shower...
You first, Yuuji.
I'd have to be out of my friggin' mind.
Then what are you going to do?
I'm gonna find somewhere with hot water.
I see.
So that is your excuse for trespassing, using the showers, and changing into your swim trunks?
Is there anything else you would like to add?
It's all his fault!
It's your fault for not bringing me anything to eat!
No, it's your fault for not paying your gas bills!
I'll be fine as long as there's water!
I bet your water doesn't even work right!
Enough. I think I understand now.
Exactly! It's not my fault!
I understand now that both of you are on a totally different level of intelligence!
You will be coming here next weekend to clean the pool as punishment!
Yes, sir...
That's pretty harsh.
I'm not looking forward to cleaning a pool that big...
Don't say that.
Didn't he say that we'd get to use the pool as much as we wanted in return for cleaning it?
Voyeur, wanna come help?
I'll pass.
By the way, I'm inviting Himeji and Shimada too.
I'll bring the brushes and detergents.
Sounds like fun.
May I come? I want to help out.
Of course!
Hey, what are you guys talking about?
It sounds pretty interesting.
The pool's reserved for us this weekend.
Want to come along?
Pool... That means swimsuits, right?
I'll have to wear my swimsuit...
Akihisa Vision
Oh yeah, Hideyoshi is coming along so he can show his swimsuit to Akihisa.
How do I look?
That's cheap, Kinoshita!
You might be confident, but...!
I agree! You're not being fair!
What are you even talking about?
So, are you two coming or not?
Yes!
Of course!
I've got a lot of prep to do.
You're right. Preparing properly is important.
I need to lose some weight...
All right, now I just need to tell Shouko about it.
You're inviting Kirishima?
So you've finally become a man.
Akihisa, if Shouko finds out after the fact,
just what do you think will happen to me?
I'm sorry.
Morning, guys!
Good morning, Yoshii.
I'm glad the weather's so fabulous today.
I bought a new swimsuit for today's sake.
What type?!
Trunks.
Those are for guys!
I am disappointed.
I can't believe you, Hideyoshi.
Do you hate me that much?
Why exactly am I the one at fault here?
Good morning, Mr. Stupid!
Hazuki...
She forced me to bring her.
Now that we're all here,
let's get changed and meet at the poolside.
Okay!
Hey, come on.
This is the guys' side.
You and Hideyoshi need to use the other side.
I was just messin' with ya!
I was not.
Come on, you two. Stop playing around.
You too!?
No! I can't go into the girls' room by myself!
If you dare change in front of Yuuji...
What's wrong with you people?
Don't worry, Hideyoshi.
Look.
Male Changing Room
Female Changing Room
Hideyoshi Changing Room
So "Hideyoshi" is a gender in and of itself...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, Hazuki-
Isn't this a felony?
I want to call my lawyer.
You guys are getting turned on by an elementary kid in a swimsuit?
Hey, Hazuki!
Give those back! Seriously!
Oh, oops...
Breasts...
Don't play around with these!
They cost me an arm and a leg!
Aren't those breast pads-
Christ!
You saw nothing! You saw absolutely nothing!
Of course not! I saw nothing! Nothing at all!
Someone press the shutter for me...
It took me ages to save up for those... Hazuki, you idiot!
What are you looking at?
Is something funny?
Nah, you look great.
Seriously?
Your breasts, bust, and bazongas are very slender, and really-
You just cracked my toe!
Did you just call me flat three times fast?
No reason to get mad about it.
He might not show it, but he really does like how you look in that swimsuit.
Oh, you silly! You don't need to hide your true feelings from me!
Okay, I won't. Your breasts are really small.
I'm going to rupture your eyes.
My eyes...! My eyes...!
This is so you won't look at other girls.
You're beautiful.
I thank you deeply for the compliment.
Yuuji, you've got something to tell her yourself, right?
Shouko...
Get me some tissues... my eyes won't stop leaking...
She meant what you think about her swimsuit.
How am I supposed to tell her that when I can't even see!?
Man, Yuuji's such a dork. Right, Voyeur?
Huh?
Voyeur!
Sorry, I'll be leaving first...
God dammit! Who?
Who did this to Voyeur?!
Sorry! Tying the ribbons on the back took a lot of time...
Blood loss reaching critical levels!
Is this... a biological weapon?
Yoshii?! What's wrong?
What happened to Minami?
Sometimes she lapses into German when she's upset.
What's going on? What happened?
No looking.
Is this everyone?
Nope, Hideyoshi isn't here yet.
I wonder what he's going to wear.
Trunks.
Oh yeah...
Sorry for taking so long.
Dead
The blood just keeps on coming...
Kill me now.
We're all here, right?
Kinoshita, do you have a grudge against us or what?
Traitor!
You make these promises then turn right around and stab us in the back!
You're really cute, miss!
Can't you tell that I'm a guy?
But you're wearing a girl's swimsuit!
What?!
I told the sales clerk I wanted normal trunks!
Honestly, I think most people would think you're a girl at first glance.
Yuuji, are your eyes okay?
Don't worry, they're slowly recovering...
There are too many things you don't need to see here.
Give me liberty or give me death! Now!
Take this!
Shouko... Sh-Shouko...
You're so good at swimming, Yoshii!
You're not going to join me?
Well, to tell the truth, I don't know how to swim.
I can only float.
I'll teach you.
I'm pretty good at swimming.
Really? Thank you!
Usually it's the other way around - the A rank helping out the F rank with her studies.
I guess Minami's the A and Himeji's the F right now!
Look closer! I'm at least a B!
By the way, Yuuji, I'm a C.
What are you talking about?
Hey, let's play Waterdevil.
Waterdevil? Is that like playing cops and robbers in the water?
Nope.
In Waterdevil, the person who's "it" chases the other people,
and they win if they manage to drown them!
Yeah, that sounds devilish, all right!
It's pretty dangerous, too, though.
I don't think it's a good idea.
You won't let me?
Watch this. Kirishima!
What is it?
You should play Waterdevil with Yuuji.
The rules are simple.
To win, all you need to do is drown Yuuji and then give him CPR afterwards.
Someone... Someone save me!
See? It's dangerous.
You told her to do it!?
You're so stubborn...
Let go of me! I've never done anything to you!
Huh? Rep?
Aiko?
Aren't you Kudou from class A? What are you doing here?
I'm on the swim team.
Someone else came too.
Sissy! Why didn't you tell me you were going to the pool?!
Why the hell are you here?
I have special informants that help me protect you from these horrible, disgusting pieces of garbage!
I'm going to get changed.
By the way, don't get caught if you're going to peek.
She just told us to go for it.
I'm not a man if I don't go.
You'll need to be prepared for the consequences if you want to do that, Yoshii.
Do you want to go home in a hearse?
Somehow, this seems like a bad idea...
In the interest of personal safety, I'll let Voyeur's camera handle the mission.
God dammit!
Man, I'm hungry after all this swimming.
I brought something with me.
I forgot how many people were coming, though, so I didn't mention it...
I made three waffles this morning.
Welcome to the first annual...
...speediest of all competition!
It's a battle of life and death!
Yeah!
The rules are simple.
One lap around the pool. The first person to finish wins!
Himeji made three poisonous waffles. We have four contestants.
The contestant who wins will be spared from eating the waffles, and thus live to tell the tale.
Let's begin.
Ready...
Voyeur just lost a lot of blood...
and I can't see myself losing to Hideyoshi in terms of physical fitness.
Get set...
That means...
...I have only one enemy.
Start!
Bring it!
Spare me the cheap tricks!
My thoughts exactly!
You ain't half bad, Akihisa.
It's gonna take more than this to beat me!
You guys probably shouldn't bother fighting right now.
The other two contestants are already on the return trip.
Oh shit! I'm gonna lose!
This is bad.
I'll take care of Voyeur! You take care of Hideyoshi!
Okay!
You're not getting past me!
Huh?
What's this?
Aki!
Yoshii, what are you doing?!
Wait... Isn't this...
Isn't this Hideyoshi's...
W-What?
Yoshii!
Aki!
Kinoshita, cover up your chest!
Why should I!? I'm a guy!
I have no regrets.
This is going to be a pain to clean up.
That was fun.
Yup.
I feel like I'm gonna pass out any second now.
It's probably due to anemia, not fatigue.
He's right.
Feel like going for a bath?
I'm in!
Hey, come on.
This is the guys' side.
You and Hideyoshi need to use the other side.
I was just messin' with ya!
I was not.
Come on, you two. Stop playing around.
Not this again!
I can't go into the women's bath by myself!
Don't worry, Hideyoshi.
Look.
Male
Bath
Female
Hideyoshi Bath
So it's already caught on...
This is great.
Nice and warm...
What's the matter, Voyeur?
The girls are on the other side of the wall.
What?!
What are you doing?
It's legal! Legal!
Let's wash each other!
Everything that happens in a bathhouse is legal.
What do you mean? What do you want to do?
Umm... Having big breasts isn't really that great.
Your shoulders ache. It's a real pain in the neck.
That's what they all say!
Akihisa, pass the shampoo.
Here.
Isn't this the soap I bought?
Well, it can still foam up, so I figured I didn't need to buy any more.
I am such an idiot for asking you.
Hey, Shouko. Pass me your shampoo.
Thanks.
Yuuji, pass me the soap.
There.
It's like you two are already married!
S-Shut up, Himeji!
You don't wanna know what'll happen if she takes that remark seriously!
There's something wrong-
No! Stop!
Sissy, it simply makes no sense to wear a towel inside a bathhouse!
Take that thing off and have some fun with me!
Why is it always me!?
Hey, did you know?
The bathtubs in bathhouses are all connected.
A butt?
Maybe you'll be able to see something if you dive under the water.
Let's try this!
HOT!
That's where the hot water comes in!
We need to coat ourselves with cold water first!
Let's try this again!
Jesus Christ! My fucking eyes!
How unfortunate.
God damn it... She won't get away with this!
She'll pay for this!
I'll see it no matter what it takes!
With this iron bracelet, it is possible to summon a Being without a teacher's permission.
Awaken!
Summoning Being...
Summon!
Go!
It's Mr. Stupid's Being!
Can you see?
My Being can see it, but I don't feel the least bit excited!
This.
That's right! If I give my Being a camera...
Summoning Being...
Summon!
This isn't a very good idea!
There's no way your Being is
getting past this line of defense.
Just you watch!
Go!
Oww...
Those who have been KIA will receive supplementary lessons!
Why the hell is Ironman here?
Wait, what the hell were you doing there?!
Man, he just can't catch a break.
Oh, I won.
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
Question 7:
What is the legal age for marriage, as stated in the Japanese Civil Code?
Age doesn't matter as long as you're in love.
Thank you for having dreams and aspirations.
Next episode: Me and Shouko and Kisaragi Grand Park.
This will be on your test.