Nishimi...
You're at the head of the class again.
I was worried with your grades dropping there for a while,
but it looks like you've straightened out your act.
Maybe it's because entrance exams are looming...
Or maybe it's thanks to the disappearance of the only thing that got in your way?
Pass it here!
I never thought they'd agree to let us up here, but I'm glad they did.
I heard some third-year thug was monopolizing the key up 'til now.
Hi! Richie-boy!
I'm playing volleyball with the girls.
Wanna join in?
Nah. I'll pass.
Richie-boy!
I know you're lonely without Kawabuchi,
but you should just get over it.
You're right.
Thanks.
Mukae!
Are you looking for Nishimi?
No, that's okay.
It's so cold!
I love milkshakes when it starts getting cold outside!
Hey, earth to Ritsuko.
Yeah.
Could it be that you're worried about Kawabuchi's disappearance?
Y-Yeah, there's that, too...
I know!
It's Nishimi, isn't it?
Like, you haven't been able to talk to him at all or walk home together lately?
Ritsu, you can't wait forever.
You need to make things happen yourself...
Hey, look!
Isn't that Nishimi?
Ritsu...
Were you eating ice cream?
You've got whipped cream on your face.
Um, Kaoru...
Are you coming back to the basement today?
No.
Sorry.
With entrance exams coming up, I've decided not to go for a while.
I see.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Tell Pops that I'm sorry for not being able to come.
Well, see ya...
Wait!
Kaoru, um...
Why not study at my place?
The shop's closed today?
Where's your dad?
He's off stocking up, so it's just me today.
Give me a second.
I'll clean up here.
That's my favorite one.
I always have it out here.
Both of you look so happy.
Look at Sentaro's face—
Stop talking about him.
Should we get started?
English and math, right?
So first of all, the word order is reversed.
This "so" comes before, and the subject and verb change places.
What?
Um... I'm sorry about before.
I wasn't thinking about your feelings when I showed you that picture...
Sentaro leaving hit you the hardest, didn't it?
I'm fine.
Even if he's not around, I've still got you, Ritsu.
W-Wait, Kaoru!
Don't! Hey...
Kaoru, w-wait...
I'm glad he's gone.
Now I can be alone with you whenever I want.
Stop it!
How?!
How could you say that?
You're happy that Sentaro is gone?
Even if you're joking, I don't want to hear such a thing!
I'm sorry about that...
Ritsu, I haven't been able to say this before,
but I'm going to a college in Tokyo.
I'll go home for today.
I'm scum!
The lowest of the low!
Dammit!
Why did things turn out like this?!
East
High
Grad.
They didn't call Kawabuchi's name, huh?
What's the difference?
Everyone's going their separate ways.
We'll all forget being here in no time.
Nishimi...
I won't ever forget the performance you two did at the festival last year!
Excuse me...
Maruo? Could I have the second button on your jacket?
Sure, if that'd make you happy...
Awesome!
I wasn't sure if I'd be able to ask you...
I was crying my eyes out...
I'm so happy!
Farewell and good riddance to this damned slope!
Don't go trudging up the thing tomorrow out of habit!
I see...
So you're going off to a college in Tokyo too, huh?
Well, it'll probably get a little lonely around here...
Nah, we can't get gloomy about it.
It's great news, isn't it?
Oh, that's right.
Ritsuko was accepted at the college nearby.
Hey, Ritsuko! Come down!
Richie-rich got into college! Hey!
Ritsu!
You can stay there, but please listen!
I'm sorry about that day!
You may not want to listen to me, but just hear me out!
The reason I came here was to see your smile!
Your smile always encouraged me, even when things were rough.
I never knew that feeling before meeting you...
So thank you, Ritsu.
Meeting you was a blessing.
Call us as soon as you arrive.
I will.
Kaoru, write me, okay?
Thank you for your patience.
Thank you for everything.
The sleeper express train, Sakura, will depart for Tokyo on track one.
Its next stop will be Haiki.
All passengers, please get on board.
Hey!
I made it in time!
Here, a little going-away present.
Thanks, Pops.
Um...
Is Ritsu...
Nope.
But there's a lunch in there that she made for you.
Well, take care, Richie.
I will. You too, Pops!
See you again!
Ritsu!
It's okay.
When you're sick, you're apt to lose heart,
but like they say, sickness and health start with the mind.
Doctor, you have a good head on your shoulders for someone so young.
Oh, no...
I'm still a rookie.
Dr. Nishimi, we've got an emergency.
Okay, I'll be right there!
Hey,
there's a free bed in the nap room.
Why don't you get a little rest?
No, if I rest now, it's all over.
I won't be able to come back.
Yeah, being a resident on the night shift is even harder than they said it'd be.
It takes a lot of stamina.
Tell me about it...
Our guest today is a pop star, a singer, and an actor!
Please welcome Matsuoka Seiji to the studio!
Guest: Matsuoka Seiji
Hello! I'm Matsuoka Seiji!
Let's start right off with a question.
What do you like more, singing or acting?
What's wrong?
Th-That's...
I like them both...
That's a classmate from high school...
Huh? My little sister goes nuts over that guy!
And I like jazz, too...
Hey! Get me an autograph!
Oh, jazz?!
I see. So Matsuoka's dream came true...
Dream...
I don't believe it...
Kaoru?! Kaoru, is that you?!
Yurika?
How wonderful! You've become a doctor!
Um...
Oh, I'm six months along. Junichi wants a girl, but I wonder...
I think he'd spoil her rotten.
How are you?
Have you been good?
Do you still play the piano?
No...
I'd heard that Sentaro took off, but you've never seen him since then?
Oh, that's right.
This is no time to be catching up.
There's something I've been carrying around to show everyone.
A friend from back home sent me this picture,
but don't you think the person on the far left looks like someone we know?
U-Um...
Can I borrow this?
What the hell am I doing?
I've been trying to forget him all this time,
but my heart is beating so fast.
There's no way I can stop this rhythm in my heart.
If you want the church, it's at the top of the slope.
Young priest? Dunno...
The priest here has been around for years and years.
Yeah, I think he helps raise the orphans from around the prefecture...
He raises children?
Yes, you mean the priest-in-training.
Though I hear he does nothing but cause trouble for the poor priest...
Th-Thank you!
Could it be...
Could it be him?!
Don't see this every day!
Lucky!
Pick me up, too!
What's wrong?
I always thought this day might come eventually.
Looks like it's today.
Enough! What do you two think you're doing?!
I told you that you can only play on special occasions, but yet again, you just do as you please!
Uh-oh!
Run, Richie!
Hey, wait! Sen!
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
It's been so long! How are you? I'm writing now because there's something I want to tell you,
Ritsuko. A friend of mine from back home got married at a church, and in a photo of the ceremony
that she sent me, there's a priest who looks just like Sentaro. I'm not sure of it, but thought it
would be worth looking into. The church is on a small island, so it should be easy to find. I just
wrote this postcard to let you know. If you find anything out, please write back.
Yours truly, Yurika Fukahori
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change