"Autumn, 1957"
Setsuko!
Mario...
Why are you out
so early in the morning?
I'm doing some shopping.
I was in the neighborhood, so...
Here you go. This is the rent.
I told you you don't need to.
It must be tough enough as
it is, surviving on your own.
I do have a real job and all now.
I can't let you constantly
pamper me. It's not cool.
I see.
Say... do you have work tomorrow?
Huh? Umm, yes,
I have the night shift tomorrow.
So you're free in the afternoon then?
A movie?
I-I got them from a friend.
I tried inviting Turtle and the others,
but they're apparently busy, so...
Y-You don't have to
if you don't want to.
I'm not a big fan of movies or anything myself...
I just... don't want them to go to waste...
That might be nice, actually.
Let's go see the movie!
R-Really?
Yeah...
Okay, I'll come get you
tomorrow morning then.
-Are you about to go somewhere?
-Huh?
Oh, it's just that you're
wearing makeup and all.
Yes, I... have to go
somewhere with my parents, so...
I see. Actually...
I kind of like it...
See you tomorrow, Setsuko!
He's so much like him now it's scary.
Everything from his
awkwardness to his directness...
He's just like Sakuragi...
S-Setsuko?
I-Is something the matter?
No, it's... nothing.
I'm really glad to have met a
wonderful woman like you, Setsuko.
For me, it almost feels like
we were destined to meet.
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we can drop
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where rules and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga
We fight this fight forever more
Editing:
Chandy10
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find out fast we’re not alone
You can leave if you want,
Boss. I'll close up shop.
Really? Thanks, Mario.
Heya!
Turtle... Joe...
Friends of yours, Mario?
No, they're just a bunch of idiots.
Wh-Who're you calling an idiot?!
That's good stuff!
Mario! Gimme another!
He's already plastered.
You gonna be okay, Turtle?
Shaddup!
Man, I'm glad your boss is a nice guy!
Aren't you, Mario?!
That reminds me, Soldier and
Cabbage came by the other day.
Really? I see those two still
hang out together all the time.
Same goes for you two.
What's Scam, up to?
Apparently he's attending night school.
Man, he sure loves studying!
Girls are what he needs to be studying!
So, how are things going
with you and Setsuko?
Nothing's... going on...
Those movie tickets I gave you...
You asked her out, right?
Yeah. We're going tomorrow...
Alright! Then lets celebrate!
Open a bottle, Mario!
Well, Setsuko?!
He's very fond of you and
enthusiastic about the idea!
Plus the go-between has
agreed to give us a loan.
once the marriage arrangement is final!
With that, I can keep the factory open!
Hey, are you listening, Setsuko? Setsuko?!
I understand.
Then you agree to it?
Yes...
That was a good movie!
Mario.
--You fell asleep, didn't you?
--N-No...
You did! You were snoring loudly!
Thank you for today, Mario.
I had a lot of fun.
Really? I'm glad.
L-Listen...
I'll ask you out again sometime.
Okay...
Hey, h-old on, Mario!
What are you doing, Turtle?
Are you that weak?
What's with you? You seem
really happy about something.
Not really. I'm the same as always.
Oh, I got it! Your date with
Setsuko must've gone great, huh?!
Th-That's got nothing to do with anything.
Just hold the bag right!
You're embarrassed!
So, how far did you go?
Did you go all the way?
It wasn't like that!
In truth, he wanted to shout out
to her, "I like you! I love you!"
But Anchan lived on inside Mario's heart.
Setsuko's gaze was
pointed in Anchan's direction.
So seeing her smile was
enough to make him happy.
That's all that mattered...
I had a lot of fun, Setsuko.
Thank you. I did too.
Bye for now.
Setsuko...
Hey. What's wrong, Joe?
Setsuko's... getting married?
Sometime this year, she said...
She said she tried to tell you on
your way back from the movies, but...
Oh, well.
Mario...
It wasn't like we were dating or anything.
If it'll make her happy, then...
Are you really okay with this?!
But you said Setsuko--
What do you want me to do then?
What can I possibly do now?
I'm on the run.
What can I possibly do?
Mario...
It doesn't matter anyway.
You just got off work, right?
Have a drink, Joe.
Don't screw with me, old man!
You serve me this shitty booze
and expect me to pay?! Huh?!
I-I'm very sorry.
You don't need to pay...!
Damn right I don't!
Yeah? What do you want?
I'm sorry, sir.
You will need to pay
for the glasses you broke.
It's okay, Mario...!
You work here?
Should've expected such a lousy
place would hire damned brats like you!
What's with that look?
Stop, Mario!
Mario!
Twice!
I'll let you hit me twice first...
Bring it on, Pops!
You're letting me hit you twice first?
Stop it, Mario!
Come on! Stop!
This isn't the place for fighting!
Stay out of this, Joe!
Despite how I look, I do know karate.
I'll knock you out cold in one hit, kid!
One more hit.
You have one hit left, Pops...
You damn kid!
Ouch! It hurts! It hurts!
I-I'm sorry...! Forgive me!
I had a little too much to drink!
I'll never bother you again!
Just let me go...! Please!
Mario... Why did you do that?
He tried to get out of paying his bill.
I bet he's tried it elsewhere.
That's enough.
Don't come here anymore, Mario.
M-Mr. Hayakawa...
I don't like that sort of thing...
"Giving someone a handicap in a fight...
It doesn't get any more spirited than that.
But no one will even commend me for it."
Mario was foolish for thinking this,
but his youth was partly to blame.
Having lost Setsuko,
Mario's heart shattered into little pieces.
Hey, Mario!
You're there, right?
I'm coming in!
Wait! Where are you going!?
I lost my job,
but I still need to apologize to Mr. Hayakawa.
Mario...
I'm okay with letting Setsuko go, really.
I gave it a lot of thought,
but there's nothing a fugitive like me can do.
I'm okay with letting her go...
I'm sorry about yesterday.
You took me in and even gave me a job,
yet I went and acted like a fool.
I enjoyed being able to work here.  Thank you.
Mario...
Can I help you?
That's him!
He's the guy who assaulted me!
So were you the one responsible for this?
You're under arrest for assault and inflicting injury!
What a shock.  I knew I'd heard your name before.
"Yokohama Police Department"
Turns out you're Mario Minakami,
the Shonan Reformatory fugitive.
Which means this is a lot worse
than fighting and hurting someone.
You're going to juvenile prison, I'd say.
You'll get seven years there, I'd say.
Seven years...
Why didn't you stop him?!
Weren't you there with him?!
Yeah...
What, you couldn't kick the guys ass instead?
Sorry...
Mario was going through a lot, though, with Setsuko and all.
It's probably best that she doesn't hear about this.
Yeah.
He's in real trouble this time, though.
He'll get seven years if he's unlucky.
Man!  He'll be 26 when he gets out!
Can't we help him break out like last time?
Us being on the outside makes it a lot harder.
Anyway, we need to gather information first.
Thanks for the drinks, bartender.
Man.  Things are busy again, all thanks to that idiot.
W-wait!
Who are you, exactly?
Us?
We're the seven former occupants of
Block 2, Cell 6 at the Shonan Special Reformatory.
Shonan Special Reformatory...?
If Mario comes back, please treat him warmheartedly.
He's a simpleminded and helpless fool...
...but he's out dear friend!
Minakami. An SDF member named
Tadayoshi Toyama is here to see you.
Soldier's here?
Too bad, though. You've been denied visitors.
What?
The family court decided today that
you merit criminal prosecution.
Criminal prosecution?
In other words, your case is being sent over to the
Yokohama district public prosecutors.
Forget juvenile court-- you're gonna be gettin' a real criminal trial.
No reformatories for you.
You're gonna end up in juvenile prison.
Prison?
Mario...
Don't tell me you're thinking of serving out seven whole years.
We don't expect you to.
Setsuko's wedding is a month from now.
We will get you out before then!
Are you serious?!
He's done for if  it gets sent to the public prosecutors.
They'll indict him, the court'll find him guilty,
and then he'll be sent to prison.
But his indictment could be suspended...
Don't be stupid!
A public prosecutor'd never make the family courts lose face!
It's set up so you'll be indicted for sure!
Whatever the case, we gotta do something fast.
All right! We'll just have to...
Hey, Turtle.
Forget any idiotic ideas
of attacking cops and breaking Mario out.
Hey there, Scam!
Once he gets indicted,
there'll be nothing we can do.
Our only chance is before that happens.
First, we gotta keep the prosecutors from indicting him.
I already explained how that's naive!
Hey, Soldier!
Go steal an SDF tank! I'll blast 'em!
I know it won't be easy.
But we have to do it.
Okay. It's settled, then.
Let's do it!
Yeah!
"Hang on, Mario. We'll save you,
no matter what," the five boys swore.
Only eleven days remained until
the public prosecutors decided to indict or not.
Yokohama District Prosecutor's Office.
"Interrogation Room"
Mario Minakami, age 19.
Committed acts of violence against homeroom teacher in 1955 and
sent to Shonan Special Reformatory the same year.
Caused many problems while at the reformatory
and was placed in solitary confinement six times for violent behavior.
Conspired and escaped with cell mates the same year.
In 1957, despite being a fugitive, assaulted Yoshitaka Kogure at a bar,
inflicting injuries requiring two months for a full recovery.
Is all this correct?
Yes...
But please hear me out!
There's a reason for all of it!
Who asked you for your comments?!
It's because of shit like you that
this country hasn't changed since the war!
I refuse to let evil go unpunished!
I'll make sure you end up in prison!
What could I keep watching over
same ta manazashi
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on running
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it now
a far off distance
The hidden truth.  Mario prepares himself.
This is the time for friends to take action.