King
We Repair Oriental Mattresses
Crimson Crane
Guys, thanks for today.
Your song was really good.
Yeah, I was touched.
You'll definitely make it big, Joe.
Yeah, no doubt about it.
Say, everyone...
You guys free?
Want to grab something to eat and drink?
Darn...
They're all going home.
Well, they're busy.
Damn, they're so boring.
You want to come to my house?
Your place?
We don't have any sake, but we do have food.
Wait, really?
You sure that someone like me is welcome?
Like you're the type to be so considerate.
Then I guess I'll go.
Uncovered invited him over.
Just that simple action made him happy.
Happy enough to be a little flushed.
I'm Kazuo, his brother.
Tatsuo, likewise.
Twins?
And they all look the same.
Welcome.
It's a small place, but make yourself at home.
Thanks.
This guy's amazing, Mom.
He knows a lot of things, and he's working even though he's so young.
Really?
What do you do?
I deal with imports.
I see.
It's surprising for Ryuji to bring a friend over.
This is the first time.
Really?
Maeda, please come play whenever you like.
Thanks!
I feel bad for eating so much.
Don't worry about it.
Say, why'd you suddenly invite me over?
Your mom said you never bring friends home.
Just as you saw, my mom brings food to the table on her own.
My brothers just started high school this year,
and we're dead poor.
But, I figured you wouldn't make fun of—
Are you stupid?!
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
You've got a great family.
Thanks.
You should hurry up and graduate and let your mom rest.
I know.
I'm... thinking of studying law.
Law?
So you're going to be a lawyer?
I don't exactly know what I want to be yet,
but... I'd be able to help if something happens to you guys.
Good luck,
for your family's sake.
Well, I'm going home.
Say, Turtle...
I need a reference book to study, but it's expensive and...
I can't ask my mom—
How much is it?
This is all I have on me right now. Is it enough?
Th-Thanks.
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
Pay me back when you get into college.
The meal I had today was interest.
I really owe you!
You don't owe me anything.
Just go home and study.
Turtle, come over to play again sometime.
My family would love to have you.
Sure, if I feel like it.
Someone had invited him for a meal without a reason.
As a victim of the atomic bomb,
his chest was filled with warmth.
"Whether or not you're poor, having a family is great."
Hello!
Hello, Maeda.
Is Un—
Is Ryuji here?
Isn't he with you?
He left early this morning.
He said he was helping you with work.
Oh, right, right!
I guess I was waiting at the wrong place.
Oh, almost forgot.
Please use this.
My...
Isn't this expensive?
Oh, it's nothing.
It was a gift.
I wanted to thank you for last night.
Damn, that idiot.
Why is he fooling around and lying to his mom?
Hey, Ryu.
Are you sure you can come here so often?
Yeah.
I can get as much money as I want.
More importantly, have you thought about what I said?
Ryu, I can't.
I can't be free unless I pay back my debt.
I'm serious.
I want you, Eri!
I want to be with you!
Thank you.
Even if you're lying, I'm happy.
I'm not lying!
I'm serious!
I really, seriously, love you.
How much debt are you still carrying?
It's not something a student could pay.
But...
My father messed up his business,
and then he disappeared.
We were a happy family of four until then.
We had no complaints.
Every month, I dreamed of finding the right man.
I'd get married and have kids with him.
Eri...
But...
I don't want my sister to be in my shoes.
So I have to do this.
My sister's going to school properly.
I want to pay back my debt as soon as I can.
I have to work hard and pay it off before my sister gets married.
I don't know why I'm telling you all this.
Eri...
It must be because you're so kind.
Hey, Ryu...
Be a responsible man.
Don't come here anymore, okay?
I don't care if she sells her body.
I'll do anything for her.
Even if I'm risking my family and friends,
it's better than losing Eri.
Uncovered, blinded by love,
had lost sight of everything else.
What the...
Am I tired?
Excuse me, Maeda?
Hey, twins!
Uncovered's brothers!
What's wrong?
Are you on your way back from school?
Make sure you go straight home.
Did something happen?
Um, Maeda...
Are you lending our brother money?
Sorry, Uncovered.
I asked you here without any warning.
Nah, it's fine.
I also wanted to talk to you.
You need more reference books?
I heard from your brothers.
You've been going to a brothel.
You're even taking your family's money.
Does my mother know?
Probably not.
Your brothers came to me,
because they had no one else to talk to.
Well, you didn't know a thing about women until just recently,
so I understand your addiction.
But...
there are a million prostitutes here.
I'll introduce you to a new one sometime.
That's not it.
That's not it at all!
If I've offended you, I'm sorry,
but don't make your family worry anymore!
What would you know?
You don't have a family or a woman.
What do you know?!
Uncovered...
Don't speak to me like you know what you're talking about!
You're annoying!
It's none of your business!
Don't ever tell me what to do!
I'm going home now.
Oh, yeah.
The money I lent you.
You can keep it.
Sorry for butting in.
I guess I never understood you.
I thought you were my friend.
Hey, Turtle.
You've been down lately.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
Hey, come on in.
Hey, Turtle!
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
He's been like that for a while.
Oh yeah, I met Uncovered a while ago.
Yeah? How's he doing?
He said he's going to study law.
Be a lawyer or something.
Really?
That's amazing.
He's trying to get into college.
Hey...
How much money did you lend him?
How did you know about that?
I just knew it.
What do you mean, "You just knew it"?
I'm going home.
Hey, Turtle, wait.
Tell me what's going on.
That's unbelievable.
Uncovered's fallen for a prostitute?
In any case, don't let anyone know about this.
I don't want his mother, of all people, to find out.
Sure.
Thanks for coming all the time.
You again?
You seem to have taken quite a liking to Eri, but she's our top girl,
so don't try to pull any tricks on her.
Ryu...
I told you not to come here anymore.
Well, this is your last time, okay?
Eri, I love you!
I want you!
Let's run away together.
Let's get out of here.
Don't be unreasonable, Ryu.
I can't run away from here.
I'll do anything for you.
I'll protect you with my life, so please...
Eri...
Okay.
Wait for me at Senso Temple next Tuesday.
I'll be out that day for a periodic inspection.
In the excitement of first love,
Uncovered trusted her completely.
He thought their love was mutual.
He couldn't see any loss, gain, or future, or his friends.
Even his own family seemed like an ephemeral mirage.
Eri was everything to him.
Please, Mario! This is my once-in-a-lifetime request!
Can you lend me some money without asking me anything?!
2000 yen. Even 1000 yen would be fine!
Please!
I'm sorry, Uncovered.
I don't have much.
Okay.
Sorry to have bothered you.
Hey.
Soldier.
Come with me for a bit.
Fuck.
What's your problem?
Hey, Uncovered.
That woman you like, Eri...
She's a nice woman.
I fucked her in the brothel just a few minutes ago.
What did you just say, Soldier?
You want to hear it again?
I fucked Eri.
How about you wake up, Uncovered?
You fell in love with a product.
You think you have what it takes to love someone like that?!
Are you some big shot who can have a mutual relationship with a prostitute?!
Soldier!
What the hell are you doing?
If he doesn't wake up right now, he'll fall all the way to hell.
So what if...
Eri is a product?
So what?!
You think I don't know?
That's business.
She'll fuck anyone for money.
So what, Soldier?
So what if she's a prostitute?!
I'm running away with her.
I'll do anything for her.
If you get in my way...
I'll kill you if I have to.
Do you know what you're saying?!
You know what'll happen if they catch you?!
Yeah, I do.
Goddammit.
You're the stupidest man in Japan.
"I can't love someone without risking my life."
"I love Eri."
No one can consider his own feelings to be foolish.
His first, life-threatening love had made him a man.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
A life-threatening love.
Friends who quietly watch over him.
Uncovered goes to Eri, abandoning everything he has.