The monster within you is about to be unleashed.
Something about the humans studying
forbidden magic that could end the world.
I think they called it...
the "Seraph of the End."
S-S-S-Sinners...
No, Yuu!
All sinners must...
It's started.
Y-Yuu, please! Snap out of it!
be s-s-slaughtered...
Yuu!
What have you done to him,
Lieutenant Colonel Guren?
How can we, as the frail species we are,
survive in this collapsing world?
Just how many were sacrificed
for your older sister, Hiiragi Mahiru,
to finish her life's work on the Infernal Arms?
As always, the greed of the human species
spirals out of control,
just as we vampires fall prey
to our own arrogance.
War in Nagoya
Don't you agree, partner?
The Human
World
Shi.
Lend me your strength,
Mahiru.
Why the hesitation?
If you want to kill me, then do it.
What about you?
Why didn't you dodge?
I don't mind dying by your hand.
For what, a cheap shot at redemption
for murdering my older sister, Hiiragi Mahiru?
She long yearned for you
and tragically fell into an unrequited love.
A demon possessed her soon after, and then...
That's right.
I killed her.
But she still lives on within that sword, does she not?
You're the possessed one now.
She perfected the Infernal Arms and betrayed the Hiiragi family.
Are you attempting to exploit Yuu under my sister's orders?
What are you really after?
If it happens to be something
detrimental to Yuu's wellbeing,
I'm going to have to ask you to stop.
What are you, lovestruck?
True, she's in here, all right.
But that's all there is to it.
I'm not possessed.
And what if I don't believe you?
Like I give a shit.
Believe what you want, kid.
Chapter
9:
Basic
Analysis
of
Spellcraft
And you're here yet again...
Yuu.
Whoa!
Don't scare me like that!
You're still supposed to be in bed, resting.
I've lazed around enough.
I'm all good now.
That's for the doctors to decide, not you.
Besides...
What?
Oh, nothing.
Is this another one of your porn books?
Well, boys will be boys...
Hey, give it back!
Give it here!
Let's see.
Gimme a break.
Chapter 13: Turning Humans into Vampires
Yuu.
Do you want to turn Mika back into a human being?
I might know a thing or two that could help.
What?!
Interested?
Yup, sure am.
Sheesh, why does it take this much to get you to be a good little boy?
Oh, shut it! Hurry up and tell me!
First of all, cases like Mika's don't come very often.
The vampires dislike adding to their numbers.
More importantly, only the nobles have the authority to turn humans into vampires.
You mean Mika was chosen by a noble?
Do you know which one?
Yeah, I have an idea.
Well?
Isn't this where you get up and declare, "I'm gonna kill all the vampires!"?
No.
Mika's alive. Right now, that's enough for me.
Anyway, do you know some way to turn a vampire back into a human?
I see.
That's too bad.
You sure seem mature all of a sudden.
Is it because you've re-evaluated your reasons to live?
Special Private Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
Please report to the First Office immediately.
Hm? Is that Guren paging me?
No, it's probably the Hiiragi family.
As in, the leader of the Demon Company that
united Japan in resistance? That Hiiragi family?
You should hurry up and go.
Huh?
Now that I think about it,
you're also a Hiiragi...
Ah, about time!
Yes, indeed I am. I'm a very high-ranking person.
Go ahead and worship me to your heart's desire!
Jokes aside, the Hiiragis can be rather scary, so do be careful.
Yo, dumbass.
So the main family calls for you,
and you happily go running to them, huh?
What?
What's with the tone?
Tell me, Yuu. Have you heard of this story?
Once upon a time, an old man freed a crane caught in a trap.
To show its gratitude, the crane wove a beautiful cloth with its own wings.
Seriously, what are you blabbering about?
I was the one who saved you.
And not only that, I also taught you how to live and wield a sword.
Where'd this come from?
You're being awfully preachy.
If you're grateful, it's about time
you returned the favor.
Again, what are you—
I own you.
Don't you dare roll over for the Hiiragi family.
Oh, I get it.
So that's what this is about.
That's right.
That's a load of shit.
I couldn't care less about the power struggle between you—
Shut your mouth, kid.
You may not care, but the world won't stop for—
There's nothing to worry about.
I'm never going to abandon or betray my friends.
Oh?
Well, you've got one thing wrong.
I sure as hell ain't your friend.
What?
Then what are you?
Your superior. Your savior. Your guardian.
Basically, your god.
You're such a pain in the ass.
Huh? Did they send for you too?
How'd it go?
It was just an interview.
I'm apparently moving up a rank for my recent contributions in fighting off the vampires.
A promotion, huh?
Naturally. I am worth it, after all.
If you say so.
Hey! Aren't you going to disagree at all?
You saw it, didn't you?
I was completely useless on that battlefield.
It turns out it was all just talk.
I'm... I'm weak.
And despite all that, I'll probably be the only one to get promoted.
Just because I'm from
the prestigious Sanguu family...
What a pathetic farce, right?
Go ahead and laugh.
Mitsuba.
I'm not laughing.
Anyway, I had no clue.
I mean, two high-class ladies on our team?
I only noticed a little while ago that Shinoa was from the Hiiragi family, too.
You're...
a real idiot, aren't you?
Whatever.
But good job on the promotion.
Climb higher and help me out.
You mean... for your family?
Yeah...
They'll ask you about that in the interview.
They ordered me to keep an eye on you in case you were a spy.
Oh? And what are your thoughts on that?
I told them that it's simply impossible.
"He just doesn't look like he has the brains to fool anybody."
I expected no less from you.
But even so,
thanks for believing in me.
Yuu.
Hm?
The Hiiragi family is terrifying.
Watch out.
Yeah, thanks.
What do we have here?
Why the long sigh?
Oh, Shinoa.
What are you doing?
Nothing much.
Just taking a leisurely stroll, you know?
Did they send for you?
I got promoted to Special Second Lieutenant of the vampire extermination unit.
Ah, I knew it!
So they do hand out promotions to the Sanguu family on a silver platter!
Aw, did I make you upset?
Whatever.
What about you? You probably got a promotion of your—
Nope.
Besides, I wouldn't accept a promotion even if they begged me.
So a Hiiragi can do whatever they want.
Oh, not at all. In fact, I've practically been disowned.
Hm?
So, how many beans did you spill for this promotion?
What do you mean?
About what happened in the battlefield.
About Yuu going berserk.
I kept saying I didn't know anything.
Seemed like they didn't either.
So in short, that was not an official experiment by the Demon Army.
Do you know what it was?
I can't say for sure.
In a world like this,
there's no longer a clear line between friend and foe.
What?
The hell? Why is a vampire...
Seriously, what the hell's going on?
It was a test of your loyalty.
Now then, shall we begin the interview?
And who the hell are you?
Hiiragi Kureto.
Lieutenant General of the
Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
Allow me to test your swordsmanship.
Don't activate the curse.
Sure, but don't come crying to me if I humiliate someone from the almighty Hiiragi family.
You shouldn't believe everything he says, Yuu.
Huh?
Too late.
Possess me, Raimeiki.
You only see what's in front of you.
Is this the best you can do?
That was dirty.
Will that be your excuse
when you're killed on the battlefield?
But you have the right attitude.
You listened to my words without questioning them.
Hard to believe that you're Guren's—
He...
Had it not been for your comrade just now,
you would be dead.
Oh, wait.
Are you going to say it's dirty to attack from behind?
I take that back.
You are indeed Guren's subordinate.
What, it's over already?
Shinya.
What? I don't wanna.
Unlike you, I don't like to bully the weak.
Don't talk back. You're just an adopted son.
Man, what a pain.
Are you kidding me?
Who the hell are you calling weak?
Why, you, of course.
You wanna try me?
Well, those are his orders.
Shall we begin?
Shoot, Byakkomaru.
Bang.
And we're done.
By the way, my Byakkomaru
specializes in long-distance combat.
In close combat, I'm no match
for the likes of Kureto or Guren.
Do you understand what that means?
But it's not your fault.
It seems you weren't properly trained on the Infernal Arms.
Don't let it get to you.
Anyway, does this clear your suspicion?
His reaction shows that he really doesn't know me.
Huh? What are you talking about?
They actually suspect me too,
since I'm good friends with Guren.
The fact that there may be a vampire spy inside the army
is a thorn in their side
that the Hiiragi family can't ignore.
Who the hell cares?
Either way, I'm not a damn spy—
Bring him.
What?!
Kimizuki!
Yoichi!
What the hell is this?!
I tortured them under suspicion of your being a spy.
Stop this bullshit!
Let's start the interview.
You will only speak the truth.
Resist, and your friends will die.
There's very little information in your report.
A star pupil who acquired a Black Demon Series
weapon in an exceptionally short time.
Well, along with those two.
Normally, there'd be a background check for those who go to undertake the Infernal Arms ceremony.
But the three of you were exempt.
What does this mean?
Where did you all come from?
What is your mission?
Mission? I don't know any—
Do it.
Stop it...
Answer truthfully.
H-Hold on!
I really don't know—
Do it.
Please, stop! I'll answer everything I can!
Of course you will.
Now, let's continue.
You grew up in the vampire capital.
However, you managed to escape.
That was when your family was killed by the vampires,
which explains why you're more driven by revenge than others.
That much is written here.
Is this correct?
Yeah, so there's no way I'm spying for—
Just answer the questions.
Ichinose Guren took you in after that.
But why?
Why did Guren save you?
What are you to him?
That's...
Why is your last name Hyakuya?
Are you a survivor of the Hyakuya Sect?
Huh?
No, that's just from the orphanage I belonged to.
The Hyakuya Sect was the largest spellcraft organization in Japan.
They gathered orphans and brought them in
for human experimentation.
You were most likely a lab rat
for their spellcraft experimentation.
What?
I see.
It appears Guren is trying
to harness something inside of you.
Good.
Join me, Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
I will guide you.
Let Yoichi and Kimizuki go.
We're done.
I don't know what you and Guren are fighting over,
but at least he has principles.
And that's exactly why he'll never catch up to me.
You may go now.
My feelings exactly.
My gosh, this is a real hellhole, isn't it?
Are you that worried about Yuu?
Wha—
Of course not!
Why would I worry about that idiot?
Oh, Yuu.
Yuu!
Kimizuki and Yoichi, too?
What's going on?
What happened?!
Bullshit happened. That freaking Hiiragi...
Guren! You have some damn explaining to do!
I heard from Hiiragi Kureto that I, my family,
Mika, and the others were all guinea pigs!
Did you save me just so you could use me?!
Yes. I don't have the luxury
of saving people with no value.
And?
Are you going to throw a tantrum now that you know that?
No. I would've died
if you hadn't saved me.
All I want to know is whether
I'm of use to you or not.
If you need me,
does the same go for Mika?
I don't mind being a lab rat
if it means you have a use for him.
Just tell me how to get Mika back!
Yuu...
Like I said before, everyone here is your family, including me.
We just have to work together
to get your family back.
Then...
If we're on the same team,
then teach me how to use the damn Infernal Arms properly!
That's the plan.
Damn it...
Why don't you finally wet your throat?
Honestly, you look the best at this age.
So just take a—
Excuse me.
Um, I heard that I'd be given special treatment if I offered Lord Ferid my blood.
Hm? And who'd you hear that from, I wonder?
Mika?
Hm...
Come, Mika. Drink his blood to stop your aging.
It's against the law to drink blood directly.
What a goody two-shoes you are.
Are you worried your dear Yuu will come to hate you for feeding on—
What do you want?
Ah, that's right.
I was going to have you attend tomorrow's Progenitor Council meeting.
The Progenitor Council?
Why me?
Because it'll be more interesting that way, Mika.
All right, shall we go?
It hurts so much...
Yuu.
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Complicated
Connections
"Complicated Connections."
Illustrated by Saki Hasegawa