Haruka's Room
Number 4
Haruka's Room!
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Our guest for today...
"If it's about hunting preserve travelogues, I am a giant too!"
The little giant!
He's the vice president of the ESP Research Society at Midorigaoka High School.
Please welcome, Muroto Daichi-san!
I'm a second-year student at Midorigaoka High School.
I'm Muroto Daichi, the vice president of the ESP Research Society.
Nice to meet you.
Muroto-senpai! Only the top of your head is on-screen!
Well, I'd be surprised if I was actually shown fully. It's fine.
I'm used to this. I really don't mind.
This is fine.
As expected from you, Muroto-senpai!
You don't get flustered, even in such a situation!
But Mr. Cameraman, please try a bit harder to fit him on screen properly.
He's playing a game!
Um... where was I...?
I'm Muroto Daichi!
Nice to meet you.
Do you really mean that? You're playing a game!
Do you always do this? Even when you're not on camera?
Not all the time.
I do other stuff, like use the computer and sleep.
Were you always this hollow, Muroto-senpai?
When I'm not on screen, it's like I'm backstage.
What's wrong with relaxing a little?
He got serious!
The End