Goodbye!
Let's go, Kii-chan.
Yeah!
It hasn't changed a bit.
You've been here before?
Yeah, ten years ago.
Anyway, let's go, Koutarou.
Right.
Letting himself get seduced like that...
Satomi-sama needs to
remember he's your knight.
He's being drawn in by her feminine wiles.
He has Sakuraba-senpai, and he's still...
I won't let him get away with this!
dare no koto o kangaeteru no
Who is it that you're thinking of?
haato no supeesu soudatsusen
It's a game for a space in your heart!
senkyouteki ni isshin ittai de
It's an advancing and retreating invasion
yudan naranai na
I still can't let my guard down
a
no
ano ne ima no koto
ne
You see, right now,
honno suu paasento shika
I only have a few percent
aitsu no kokoro ni
tsu
of the space
ibasho ga nainda
in his heart
true
intentions
peek
out
seifuku no poketto
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
true
intentions
out
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
peek
out
My
from
my
uniform's
pocket
honne o shinobasete
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
pocket
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
I
calmly fix
my collar
sotto eri o tadasu
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
my c
calmly fix
Simply revealing all the tricks up my sleeve
sonna kantan ni wa
te no uchi akasenai
would be no good
So I guess I'll just have to wait and see
akumade mada yousumi no dankai
dakedo hontou wa ne
But you see, the truth is
miyabutte hoshii no
I want you to realize it
awai kitai ni mune tokimekashite
My heart throbs from this bubbly expectation
chirachira to miteru
I shyly take a glance at you
onna no ko no daiji na mono
What girls value as important
i
ijiwaru de
a bit mean
ji
wa
ru
de
otoko no ko no daiji na koto
and what guys value as important
mukatsuku
mu
and annoying
ka
tsu
ku
hiku ni hikenai sorezore no jijou
tug back and forth with each other
hoka ni nani mo kangaerannai
My mind stutters, I can't think at all
ma
massugu de
so direct
s
su
gu
de
isshun datte yosomi dekinai
I can't take my eyes off you for a second
ni
nibui ne
yet so dull
bu
i
ne
juujitsukan afureru hodo ni
I'll fill you up with this sense of contentment
mitashite ageru yo
until you can't receive it anymore
jo
u
jouken chiratsukase
ken
Add requirements
yousu ukagatte miteru
See how things go
otagai win-win na
ga
I think we can both win here
i
win-
win
na
to
ri
torihiki shiyou yo
hi
so let's make a deal
ki
shi
yo
u
Someday, With Them...
This hasn't changed either.
What's wrong, Koutarou?
Oh, nothing.
Is it okay for them to be
messing around over there?
Spin, spin!
I'm dizzy!
I told them they could take the day off.
Isn't this risky, since they usually hide?
I'm sure no one will notice them,
given our location.
I see.
Koutarou, let's go to the next ride.
Yahoo!
Stare...
Adult
2 Tickets
You sure this is what you want to see?
It looks like a movie for kids.
Yeah, I've been wanting to see this.
I see.
Well, I don't mind.
They went into the theater.
It's dark in there.
Do you think they might...
You're imagining too much!
What now?
Should we go in too?
That won't be necessary.
I prepared a surveillance drone
specifically for this situation.
I'll have Ruth set it up so it'll
notify us when they leave.
Where's Ruth?
That's weird.
She was here a second ago.
Ah!
L-Look at this!
Rh-Rhinoceros beetles!?
Th-This is...
Th-This is terrible!
Beetle Warriors: Rhinoceros Man Hero Show
A whole bunch of rhinoceros beetles!
Regardless of the evil before us,
we Rhinoceros Warriors will always fight!
Rhinoceros Man Number One!
Rhinoceros Atlas!
So this is where you were, Hercules-chan.
Huh?
I've been so worried.
I thought you'd been multiplying!
Wh-Why is Ruth-san here!?
Are you one of them too!?
She's going to cost me my part-time pay!
I have to deal with her!
Sorry, but I'm taking you down!
Rhinoceros Beetle!
Wait!
That was pretty good.
I'm glad.
We got a reprint of the old pamphlet too.
Pretty cool.
This is...
The same as mine, huh?
I got this from someone I liked a long time ago.
So you came here with the
person you liked ten years ago?
Koutarou, let's go on that next.
Kii-chan!
There!
Hey, be more careful.
Kiriha-san.
There.
Hey, be more careful.
Geez, you're not a kid anymore.
Sorry.
You're right. I'm not.
I have to do what I need to do.
Koutarou, there's something
I want to talk to you about.
It all started ten years ago.
I got into a fight with my
father over something foolish,
and ran away from home.
Ran away from home?
Doesn't sound like you.
Well, I was a young child back then.
And I'd lost my mother,
so I guess I was a bit unstable.
I see.
You lost your mother too, didn't you?
I left home and headed toward the surface, which I was forbidden to do.
And that's when I met him.
I don't remember his name
or what he looked like.
What I do remember is that he
was about the same age I am now,
and that I called him "Onii-chan."
The places we went,
and the feelings I had at the time...
So we went around the park today because...
Yes, because of
my memories with him.
You really liked him, huh?
He was my first and only love.
I was taken back underground and haven't seen him since.
I see.
That's why when we decided to invade the surface,
I volunteered to be the commander.
Wait, you're invading because you
want to see your first love again?
That's why I needed to
recommend we invade peacefully.
I didn't want to drag this town,
where I met him, into a war.
But...
You said you wanted room 106
to mass-produce weapons, right?
That was in order to get you to resist.
Huh?
If I had taken room 106 at that moment,
I risked starting a war right then and there.
It would give credit to the radicals
that advocate military action.
But if I forego the
invasion of room 106,
the radicals would probably take action on their own
and try to invade the surface.
That's why I can't win or lose the fight over room 106.
You have to maintain
control over room 106
until I'm able to peacefully
take over this city.
I see.
It finally makes sense.
You really are too kind to invade.
Guess I couldn't keep it hidden.
Anyway, if you would have just told me earlier,
I could've helped you out.
I see.
I'm sorry, Koutarou.
I was deceiving you
purely for my own gain.
It's fine.
But you know, I guess I feel a little bad.
I think any guy would have fallen for you
if you were hitting on them seriously.
Koutarou...
You really are a guy, after all.
I'm a young guy. It's only natural!
If you really meant what you said before,
I think any girl would be happy.
Ruth...
Ruth.
Ruth!
Your Highness...
Everyone...
What happened to me?
You don't remember?
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
Nothing at all!
Yeah, nothing, don't worry about it!
It was terrible.
You were using a fly swatter to get some rhino—
Well, all of our guests had
a great time, so it's no problem.
Yeah, no problem!
Right...
This next?
Doesn't seem like your kind of thing.
Or maybe it is.
Are you implying I'm some sort of tomboy?
I don't think I like the sound of that.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
You rode this with that guy too?
No.
You must be as tall
as this sign to ride
I couldn't because of that.
I've always wanted to ride it.
Today is the day that dream comes true.
Dream, huh?
Yeah, but Kiriha-san...
Huh?
An earthquake?
Wh-What's going on?
It couldn't be...
What's that?
Wh-What is that?
It's a subterranean submarine
used by the Earth People.
I knew it'd be you, Shijima Tayuma!
Tayuma, what are you trying to pull here!?
Oh, Commander.
Of course I'm here to restore the glory of the Earth People,
and to make up for the lack of leadership from Kurano Kiriha.
Withdraw your soldiers, Tayuma.
I'll forgive the fact you brought
a subterranean submarine.
I'm afraid I will be unable to do that.
Kiriha-san!
I'm fine, Koutarou!
Stand back.
Who are these guys?
Th-They have guns!
From the situation,
I'd imagine they're with Kiriha.
Although they don't seem to be allies.
That Koutarou...
Always getting caught up in something annoying.
Your Highness!
I'll go too!
Huh? Where's Yurika?
Whatever.
I'm a magical girl of love and justice.
It's my job to protect everyone.
I'll use magic to keep people at bay.
Tayuma, do you understand what will happen if you point your weapons at me?
Naturally. I'll tell Chief Daiha you were betrayed and killed by a surface-dweller.
That will get our citizens riled up for the invasion.
So you'd even use my death...
You're going to die for the glory of the Earth People.
You should feel honored.
Fire!
Kiriha-san!
Sis, sorry we're late!
Karama, Korama, disable their guns!
Roger!
Shock, shock!
The Kurano family's prized
automated dolls, huh?
But I have something too!
Come to me, Jack-o!
What now!?
It's a Shijima family earth combat doll!
We're not losing to some earth doll!
We're no real haniwa dolls if we don't win!
Tayuma, do you desire war no matter what?
There's a more peaceful—
A peaceful takeover is a joke!
You've forgotten the
greatness of the Earth People
and befriended the surface-dwellers!
That's not—
That's proof enough!
I know you're obsessed
with that lump of metal!
That's right.
I'll destroy that first and
make it your gravestone.
Jack-o!
Erase everything!
That's enough!
This is a place for everyone
to make memories!
And what about it!?
You won't be able to invade the
surface if you don't understand that!
Kiriha-san understands.
That's why she's trying to merge
with the surface and this town.
It's not about weapons, but hearts and minds!
Koutarou...
You're—
Koutarou!
Why are you concerned
about a surface-dweller!?
Jack-o, do it!
Great work, Theia!
You're supposed to say,
"You saved me, Your Highness!"
Ruth!
Right, Your Highness!
Perfect, Ruth-san!
How come you didn't act like that with me!?
Take that!
You guys really shouldn't try
to lay your hands on my tenants.
Take this, Koutarou!
My Knight,
here's your sword!
Thank you, Theia!
No need to thank me.
Wh-Who are you guys?
My invaders and landlord!
Tayuma, this is the invasion I desire.
Leave this to me and return underground.
And I'm saying that's not enough!
Jack-o!
Second Form!
You want to fight to the end?
In that case...
Karama! Korama!
Right!
I thought this might happen!
I'm not going to hold back.
Kiriha-san, we're going to help too.
Right. I'm counting on you!
Here I go!
Take that!
And that, and that, and that!
It doesn't even look like you're moving!
Blue Knight.
Th-That's not good!
Let's end this.
Damn it.
That's playing dirty.
Koutarou, I'll be your eyes.
You can praise me later!
Sure thing!
Right there!
D-Damn you.
Do you still intend to fight, Tayuma?
If I could have sacrificed you,
the People of the Earth
would have chosen war.
That's what I thought.
But the sacrifice doesn't have to be you!
It can't be!
What is it!?
It's going to self-destruct!
Karama, Korama!
Create an etheric field at maximum power!
I don't care if you burn out your circuits!
Right!
Too late!
I wonder if my magic made it in time.
N-No way.
How could you defend against an explosion that huge?
It seems like the goddess of
creation isn't on your side.
I'm going to start a war.
I'm going to become a hero!
I don't like hurting people.
However, I'll take up arms to
protect those I care about.
Goddess, forgive me.
What are we going to do about this?
I'm sure the government will cover this up for us.
They'll say the ground suddenly collapsed,
or something.
They will?
They want to hide certain things,
even if they know we exist.
Guess we'll have to go on that
roller coaster another time.
Koutarou...
Will you go on a ride with me another time?
No.
I think you should go on that roller
coaster with your first love.
Koutarou...
If you really did come up
to the surface just to see him,
then we should find him!
I'll help you out too.
Thank you, but you don't
have to do that for me.
It's not about me "having to."
We're friends, right?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Satomi Koutarou,
you're my best and only friend on the surface.
akogarete iru no you
I always wanted
anata to sukyandaru
to have a scandal with you
itomenai no kokoro
My heart wants to win you over
ano koyori mo hayaku
before that other girl does
hito wa
Why do people
nande nande
Why, oh, why?
nando
Even though each and every time
kizutsuitemo
I end up feeling hurt
koi ni
It's love
koi ni ochiru
I fall helplessly in love
ikimono nano
Ah, but such is life
marude marude mirukutii
Just like a milk tea
betsubetsu no tokoro de umareta futari
Our hearts lie in separate places
amai amai no mirukutii
Just like this sweet, sweet milk tea
atsu atsu yo ima sugu kyun to nomihoshite
It's steaming hot, so I want you to drink it up in one go
marude marude mirukutii
Just like milk tea
zetsumyou na kaken ga wakaranai no ne
I can't make sense of this breathtaking feeling
torotorokeru mirukutii
It's liquid velvet, just like milk tea
saigo dake chotto dake horori tii tongai
Even though it tastes slightly bitter at the end
I'm telling you Earth People
are really here this time!
Come on, guys. Let's go.
We still haven't gotten our different colored suits, though.
We still haven't resolved me wanting to be red.
Huh? There's no signature from the
Earth People anymore, is there?
I want to see Baron Demon again!
You guys are hopeless...
It's almost Christmas.
I wonder what I should get Satomi-kun.
Wait a second!
I'm going to have you do all sorts of stuff
at the big event at the end of this year!
Invasion Going Well!?
Next Episode
I'm not going to wear that!
Huh?