I understand several consciousnesses were fused into her.
Yeah.
That's my fault.
No, you did a great job as leader.
You kept the Battlefront afloat during its greatest crisis.
Besides, no one could have known there would be so many of her waiting for us.
And that was all Kanade's—
the Evil Kanade's plot.
Even then, they were still so like Kanade, so I doubt I could have done anything better myself.
I guess so.
I feel better hearing you say that.
Hey... You told me there aren't any hospitals because no one gets sick, right?
Then why won't you wake up?
Goddamn it.
There's no such precedence.
We've never seen Tenshi like that before.
There's a possibility she might never wake up.
That would be the greatest irregularity so far, if so.  I'm sure she'll wake up.
She'll open her eyes and just say she overslept.
When she does wake up, which "her" will she be?
Holy crap!  Shiina spoke!
That only proves this is a really critical issue!
And she's right.
That's the real question.
So, which Tenshi is it gonna be?
It has to be the original Tenshi.
The one we went fishing with.
But all the Tenshi that attacked us were aggressive and cruel.
Just talking numbers, there were like 100 evil ones to the single original.
Why doesn't she just wake up already?
Don't you think it's because of all those evil minds crowding in her head, messing stuff up and pushing things around?
So you're saying when she wakes up, the 100 minds could possibly overtake her?
So mathematically speaking, I'd say seeing the original Tenshi is only about a 1% chance.
So now what?
I already have a countermeasure planned out.
I've sent Takeyama-kun, along with some people who can translate the software manual, to Tenshi's Domain.
Where are T.K. and Matsushita?
They're at the infirmary, standing guard.
Actually kinda surprising to know that T.K. totally sucks at English.
So, what you're trying to accomplish here is to wipe the data,
change the username and password, and seal away all the abilities?
That will only be a temporary measure.
You understand that, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
She'll crack through all of that and eventually rewrite the program.
Then we should break the machine itself.
There are plenty of replacements in the computer room that are school property.
Same goes with the software.
Just great.
Hey, you all sound smart today.
Did you eat something rotten?
All we can do now is wait.
Whose side will God take?
Crap.  I'm late for the exam.
Are you okay?
Hey!
Are you all right?
I feel a little dizzy.
Your head is bleeding.
Feeling faint?
I'm fine.
Anything feel strange?  Nauseous at all?
No.
Are you a doctor or something?
No way.  I'm just a student.
Can you get up?
Yeah...
Let's get out.
Still all right?
Yeah.  Thanks.
Horrible...
Yeah.
Anyway, I'll call for help.
Damn it...
No luck?
Let's save those who are still left inside.
I'll help you.
Can you?
I feel a little wobbly, but I should be fine.
I'm Igarashi.
I'm Otonashi.
Let's hurry.
Will we be okay?
I'll go look for an exit.
If I make it out, I'll get some help.
I'll be sure to come back.  I'll borrow this light.
Yeah!  Thanks!
Otonashi!
Let's make sure to get out of this!
Yeah!
Damn it!
What the hell is this...?
Otonashi!
How was it?
It looks a little difficult.
I see.
Listen to me, everyone!
The tunnel is closed off with rubble here and at the back, too.
Our cell phones won't connect, either.
We can't get in touch with the outside.
From here on, we work together.
I don't want anyone trying to survive alone.
We'll gather all the food and water we have, and we'll share it equally.
Wait a moment!
Since when did you become the leader?!
Then who will?!
Who will head up nursing the injured?
He's got medical knowledge.
You're not saying to leave the injured people behind, are you?
T-That's not what I meant, but...
Help will definitely come.
We need to hang tight until then.
Let's all survive through this!
Let me know when you get thirsty.
We'll hand out food when the time comes.
Anyone who feels sick, let Otonashi know.
Please hang in there a little more.
Let me know if there's anything you need.
Thanks.
Otonashi.
How is our food supply?
One packed lunch and some snacks.
We've got one bottle of tea, and I'd guess about five or six bottles of water.
That could last us for three days.
But man, you're amazing.
How so?
You're so dedicated.
You plan on going abroad with some NPO?
No, I hadn't planned on that, but...
I'm just joking with you.  Don't take it so seriously.
But you should save your energy, too.  You'll be the first on your knees.
Yeah.
Hey!
You fucker!
He took the water!
Wait!
Motherfucker!
The water!
Stop it!
W-What's wrong, Mr. Leader?
You gonna restrain me or something?
Sure!  Go ahead!
No one's going to live through this!
I mean, you all know that, don't you?!
That's not true.  We'll be rescued.
Quit being such a nice guy!
That guy just wasted our water!
It's fine.
That was just my share.
I won't drink anything from here out.
So you all can relax.
Someone punch him!   I can't calm down otherwise!
Yeah, I'll give him a good one.
Don't worry.  We'll share mine.
Sorry about that.
Not a problem.
Okay, let's take him somewhere.
You guys, give me a hand.
Fine.
Otonashi!  Otonashi!
Something looks wrong!  Come see him!
Crap.
Come back to us.
Come back!
Goddamn it.
What have I been working toward since that day?
She...  Hatsune taught me the meaning of life.
And then... more life was lost right before my eyes...
Nothing has changed.
I'm still powerless.
Nothing has changed since that day.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Shouldn't you rest some already?
I want to read a little more.
Oh, fine.
There.
We don't want you catching a cold.
But, why won't you get any better?
If only we could find a donor.
A donor?
Igarashi.
Do you have a pen on you?
Yeah.
Unbelievable.
What the heck are you doing?
If I do this, even if my life ends, it will be used for someone else's life.
We can leave behind the meaning in our lives.
You know... you really are amazing, Otonashi.
Look.  They were all in the depths of despair, and now they're leaving hope for others.
You saved everyone's life.
Otonashi...
Hey, Otonashi...
Are you listening?
Otonashi...
Kanade!
I was so worried about you, damn it!
Are you okay!  Is there anything wrong with you?!
The battle was fierce.
"Battle"?
It's a miracle that the me who made that promise to you is the one who woke up.
Look, I remember everything now.
How I died.
On the way to my exam, I got caught in a train accident.
I wanted to become a doctor.
I wanted to be of help to others.  I wanted to live hearing "thank you."
That's how I began.
I studied a lot, too.
But, in the end, I left my body behind in that world with my organs up for donation.
My body should have saved someone.
I'll believe that it did.
I'm sure that certain someone will forever say "thank you" to you.
Yuzuru.
What is it?
You don't have any more regrets?
That's true.  If I was able to save someone, then my life wasn't so bad.
I can think that way now.
Does this mean...  Am I going to be obliterated?
If you have nothing more to regret.
But they're here.
I see.  You want to continue to be with them?
Well, they're my friends.  So of course I do.
But I've got something else on my mind, too.
I wish that everyone could overcome their lives like I did, and exit this world together.
I don't think a new life would be all that bad.
So you agree?
Yeah.
Wait a minute!  Is this the feeling you wanted everyone to understand?
You didn't know that?
Of course I didn't!
Think!  I was stabbed by you the first time we met!
Well, you asked me to prove to you that no one could die.
What a long road she and the rest of them have been taking.
And just how bad can she be with communication?
You're saying we'll become happy if we take classes?!
That we'll feel content if we participate in club activities?!
Yes, since all those that come here are ones who couldn't live out their youthful days.
Really?
You didn't know?
I didn't!
How was I even supposed to figure that out?!
You didn't notice that from the way things were designed?
Now I get it.
This was a place to save young souls.
If Hinata had caught that fly ball, he would have been fulfilled and obliterated.
What a bother Yui and I were.
Iwasawa accomplished the task herself.  She achieved satisfaction and became obliterated.
Nobody's here because they want to be.
We're all fighting against how unfair life is.
But Kanade says that's not true.
She wanted to show us a fair life.
She wanted us to have a normal student life.
That's why she kept trying to persuade those who tried to remain here.
It was all for...
How ironic.
That was all to get us to realize her point, but instead we fought against each other to cling to our individual beliefs,
and eventually it escalated to the point of making weapons.
Now, we're basically fighting every day.
Just how bad at communicating are you?
I know I'm bad.
So you're at least aware of it.
Yeah.
But I think if you're here with me... I might be able to accomplish it.
So you're asking me to help?
You honestly should have already been obliterated.  However, you're still here.
Does that mean I'll be the first person who's able to stay with you?
Isn't that what's actually bothering you the most?
Yeah...
Maybe...
But...
Until that day, I was confident that I was being a good sister, too.
I had everything I wanted to protect taken from me in a matter of 30 minutes.
I just can't accept something so unreasonable.
I can't forgive being given such a life.
It's impossible.
I mean, even more so!
Because she's fighting to carry on that memory forever, I want to help her.
Can Tenshi and I really manage to do that?
It's not promising at all.  It really may be impossible.
But if we don't do it, the fight will continue.
What should I do?
I'm a part of them, but I'm also Kanade's friend, so isn't this something meant for me to do?
Hey, could you help me out?
Shouldn't I be the one saying that?
Oh.  Yeah, right.
What am I saying?
Okay, Kanade.
We'll get the others to graduate.
We'll make sure everyone graduates from this world.
So, we discovered that there were people who swapped every one of Tachibana's tests in an attempt to soil her.
Tachibana has illuminated the discrepancy in the handwriting, proven her point,
and as such will be working again as the Student Council President.
As a result, Naoi, who has been working as the deputy president, will be returning to the seat of vice president.
Why do I have to do this?
She managed to get all of us in trouble.
What good were those flights for?
Yeah!  Seriously!
Oh.  How rare that our opinions coincide.
Of course, since only those who took flight would understand.
We're flying buddies!
Whoa, there.  Do you intend to undress me?
Sure!  Strip away!
Stop it.  You're being loud.
Yeah!  And it's gross, so quit it!
Which is it?
On another note, it looked like she forgot everything that happened these past few days.
It's only natural she does,
since the 100 won.
Those who attacked us won.
I seriously thought that we might be able to get along.
Damn it!
I will have to hear what happened to them in the past, first.
But now that we don't have an enemy to keep an eye on, I can't sneak around Yuri.
So Kanade, I need you to return being the Student Council President.
I need you to fight against them again.
When you do, I need you to do as I tell you.
This sounds like a fitting strategy for me.
Sorry, I'll be leaving you alone again.
But when everything's over—
When it's over?
When...
When that happens, what will happen to us?
The band is dead because of your guitar performance.
—Tenshi."  How dare she~?!
She can tell the notes.
I knew she was special!
It's only one of the many things that I've wanted to do.
German Suplex!!
Prepare yourself!
Was the dumbass cured?
We men will win!
Just whose side are you on?!
Kiss you!
It's a miracle!!
Okay!  I'll grant those wishes!
He took... all my happiness away...