Hurry! Call an ambulance!
Sis.
Ushio!
Tokiko, go to the school and bring the AED!
It's on the pillar by the entrance!
Sou...
Okay!
Run!
What is...
Stay with us!
...everyone doing?
Ushio! Open your eyes!
Sis...
Please! Come back!
Ushio!
Huh?
Whoa! No! S-Sorry!
I didn't mean to... I mean...
I-I'm very sorry!
Are you okay?
You were moaning quite a bit.
Was it a bad dream?
A dream?
This woman...
Um, have you ever been sh-shot with a gun?
What?
Are you really okay?
Uh, actually... never mind.
I feel like this woman has slapped me before.
I'm totally fine.
I just dreamed about a movie.
July 22nd?
Wh-What is this?
I went to Hiruko with Mio on the 23rd.
Mio was killed by another Mio.
No, don't be ridiculous.
That had to be a dream.
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Nagumo Ryuunosuke's Swamp Man.
A horror-mystery set in Wakayama City.
The story is about a young girl who becomes paranoid that her family and friends are being replaced by doppelgängers.
I was reading this before I fell asleep.
That's why I had such a bad dream.
Right.
July 22nd
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Shadow
Wait a sec.
Calm down.
At times like these, I need to have a bird's-eye view
and calm down.
I'm home for the first time in two years because my friend Ushio died.
But why does it feel like I just did the same thing yesterday?
Hey!
Welcome home, Shin!
No way.
Déjà vu?
Hope ya had a nice trip!
Is that what this is?
She's even wearing the same underwear.
Use your brakes!
I did!
Come on.
That's weird.
Everything after that was also a repeat.
Hitogashima Hall
Dad!
Shin is back!
Everyone acted exactly like in the dream.
Said the same things.
Shinpei.
You're so tall now.
You look a bit thinner.
This isn't just déjà vu or a dream come to life.
I'm reliving July 22nd.
My head hurts like it's splitting apart.
My eyes are having spasms.
What's happening, Ushio?
They found ligature marks on Ushio's neck.
Like someone strangled her.
What really happened to you?
Dr. Hishigata did the autopsy on Ushio's body.
Autopsy?
That's serious business!
That flash again.
Who was that? Photos ain't allowed in here.
That's Kobayakawa Shiori.
The girl Ushio sacrificed her life to save.
If I really went back in time,
her family will disappear tomorrow.
And if the same thing keeps happening...
Shinpei!
Ya finally came back!
...it would mean the shadow really exists.
Thank you for this meal.
If you see your shadow, you die.
So yummy.
Was Ushio killed by her shadow?
Not to mention, Mio...
Shinpei?
Ya look pale.
Sorry.
I'm gonna get some fresh air.
This morning, the brakes on Mio's bicycle were broken.
It seemed like someone cut them intentionally.
If someone deliberately did that...
they were trying to kill Mio.
Crap.
I can't see things from a bird's-eye view. I'm so confused.
I feel sick.
Huh?
Totsumura?
What'cha up to, Mio?
Why the staring contest with yer own house?
Get into a fight with someone?
Mio?
What is she doing outside in her school uniform?
No.
No. No! No! No!
That ain't Mio!
It's a shadow!
Wh-What the hell's that?
A shadow?
All righty then.
You are now the police officer Totsumura Tetsu.
My name's Totsumura Tetsu. 34 years old. No girlfriend. No promotion in sight.
That's none of yer business!
Yer as cute as ever, Mio!
Give me your gun.
What? Ya haven't switched places yet?
I failed this morning.
It woulda been easy if she'd been hospitalized.
It ain't like you to go through all that trouble!
Go take care of it now!
Ya got a gun.
A gunshot on a quiet night like this would create a scene.
This ain't America.
Fair 'nough.
I'm just checking things out today.
N-No way. Is this real?
My phone.
Hishigata Sou
Sou!
Not now!
Shit!
So this is where ya were, Shin.
Eavesdropping ain't polite, Shinpei.
Now ya get the death penalty.
You wanna copy him too?
No. He's already...
Is this my blood?
So red...
Oh, I'm dying.
I can finally look from a bird's-eye view.
What?
What is this?
Shinpei.
Wh-Who's there?!
Be careful...
What?
I can't hear you!
Shin.
Take good care of Mio.
July 22nd
Summer Time Rendering
I'm back again.
Did I die?
Why did I come back?
Hey!
Welcome home, Shin!
Think from a bird's-eye view.
I heard it.
Ushio's voice!
She asked me to take good care of Mio!
I can't stop!
Leave it to me!
Crap!
Shin!
I can't swim.
Shin! Breathe!
Mio... Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thanks, Shin.
Recording
It's me.
It's July 22nd, 1:02 p.m.
I've been in Hitogashima for 1 hour and 37 minutes.
I ate narezushi before boarding the ship.
Narezushi is a traditional dish made by pickling mackerel with salt for over a month.
It's quite exquisite.
Try it when you come to Wakayama.
I'd love to know what you think.
By the way, you asked me why I hang upside down.
It's because when blood runs to my head,
it helps me think clearly.
You should try it.
It'll help that clouded brain of yours.
Recording
The rest is in the report.
They're everywhere.
Unthinkable.
I'll just observe for now.
That's all.
Hello? Ally of justice here.
Huh? Wh-What?!
A fight's going on?!
R-Right.
Is this Shinpei speaking?
Yes.
Are ya okay?
Yes. In the shopping district...
The shopping district?
It's a customer at the bar.
Oh, the bar?
Please help!
See from a bird's-eye view and think about what I need to do.
I just have to survive today.
Do you think I'll get in trouble for that?
The false report will keep Totsumura away from here.
He'll be a little pissed that it was fake,
but the important thing is that he's safe, right, Ushio?
For Sou, I texted that I'd call him tomorrow.
Hishigata Sou
I'll call ya tomorrow.
Got it. Actually, can we meet up and talk?
Maybe at your place? Tell me when you're free.
Thanks. I'll get in touch.
I'll also delete unnecessary apps and photos.
Now I have seven gigs of storage.
Storage
Plenty of space to record video.
Turn on airplane mode to silence incoming calls.
Storage
Fully charge the phone.
I'll connect my external battery too.
Thankfully, I know what time it'll come.
Begin recording.
I'll film Mio's shadow and get proof.
I won't go outside, no matter how sick I feel.
Then I'll be okay.
I wasn't killed on the 22nd the first time around.
The color of my right eye is different.
Since when?
Mio's in there, right?
Mio...
Mio!
Jerk! Jerk! Jerk!
Think from a bird's-eye view...
You pervert!
What were ya looking at, Shin?!
S-Sorry.
Mio is safe. Good!
What was that?
Goddamn.
It's right there on video.
July 23rd
Good morning, Shin.
Mio, can we talk?
It showed up in front of our house last night at nine.
It looked upstairs for five minutes, then walked into the mountains.
Who is this?
M-Me?
No.
You were taking a bath at the time.
Th-They call it a shadow.
Mio, you've heard of the shadow sickness, right?
It came here...
to kill you.
I-I... came to kill myself?
Zoom in on the hand.
No way...
So the shadow sickness ain't just a superstition.
I knew it.
Ushio also saw a shadow, right?
Three days before she died.
Right.
I guess she told ya about the shadow.
Well, I actually heard it from you.
And I saw it too. I saw your shadow... yesterday.
Hey, Shin.
My sister mighta been killed by a shadow.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Drifting Ashore