Ouch!
That day, I understood the essence of the boxed lunch.
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed that and I've won
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
The Essence of
Boxed Lunches
This isn't bad once in a while.
Us four friendly gays having lunch together.
It's guys, not gays.
And we don't have four.
Speaking of which, where is Master Kitamura? He said he'd have lunch with us.
Sorry for the wait.
Gosh, pardon me.
I went to fetch this from the student council room.
I couldn't fit it in my locker, after all.
Wh-What the hell is this?
Don't tell me...
This is your boxed lunch?
Correct.
And then...
Today's not a special day, Master!
This is something that only Chama or Mendou would bring!
Haruta!
It's really rude to laugh at him like—
Jesus!
This must be from a comic, huh?
Or perhaps from a different dimension?
You should open it and check it out.
What's up? What's with all the noise?
Show gramps what you got her—
Minorin!
What the heck is this?
Maruo's having a feast!
What sort of party are you guys throwing?
Spiny lobster's antennae are long.
D-Does this "39" mean...
Yuusaku's creation!
Note: 3 can be read as "sa", 9 can be read as "ku", and saku means creation
Exactly.
Yuuksaku, I bet your grandmother was the one who made this.
Huh? Kitamura, your grandmother made this?
Yeah. The company my parents work for took them to Guam for vacation.
That's why my grandmother came over.
This is seriously... homemade quality?
She worked her magic and here's the finished product.
She must love her cutsie little grandson to death, huh?
I don't mean to be ungrateful,
but she did kind of overdo this.
Anyway.
You guys better help me out.
We can eat it?
Really?
Of course!
We'd be wasting my grandmother's effort if the trays aren't emptied.
Which piece should I try first?
Ladies, this is for you.
Thanks for the food!
What is this? It's delicious!
It's really good!
I wouldn't expect any less from Yuusaku's grandmother.
Delicious! I can eat fruit no matter how full I am.
What's the matter, Takasu? Try some.
This strawberry is a work of art!
All right, I'll take this piece of karaage.
Taiga?
What's the matter, Aisaka?
You don't need to hold back.
I-I want to have...
The lobster...
Seriously? Do you have no shame?
I was wondering why you were squirming around! So eating the lobster was your ultimate goal!
This has nothing to do with you!
Well, but...
Worry not. Worry not.
Help yourself.
So good!
The more I chew on it, the better it tastes!
I feel like I'm in heaven now!
What about your own lunch?
I ate it already, of course.
But there's always room for lobster! Always!
Nothing tops the spiny lobster!
It isn't just the looks! The taste is perfect as well!
Takasu.
May I take a picture of your boxed lunch?
I just want to show my grandmother that something normal like this is fine.
It's not very good... I kind of slacked off this morning...
It's fine.
All right, thanks!
I can't let them think this is the best I can do!
Hey, guys, finish it up!
Lobsters are stupid.
If they weren't so yummy, they wouldn't be eaten.
Same with crabs.
Damn Yuusaku.
I ate too much thanks to him.
K-Kawashima.
Hey...
What's up?
Well, you know, Kitamura's grandmother...
Is she a cooking teacher or is she a chef?
I guess she is.
Or is she just a pro?
Right?
I think she's just your average housewife.
Average housewife...?
I believe so.
By the way, what's his grandmother's name?
Huh? Why would I know...
What's with your expression?!
You scared the heck out of me.
Oh, thanks to your evil looking face, I remember now.
Miyo-chan.
"Mi" as in the year of the snake. Miyo-chan.
Miyo-chan, huh?
Show me the best boxed lunch you can pack!
As you wish.
We'll decide who's superior the next time we meet, Miyo-chan.
Hey, you okay?
Kitamura-kun!
Let's have lunch together!
Your grandmother made lunch for you again, right?
Yeah, but look.
It's just an average one today.
Right, not too much money involved.
Let's put our tables together.
Not too much effort involved.
Just enough to fill the empty stomach of a high school student.
Playing by the rules. This will be our first time fighting head on.
All right...
What's up?
Okay.
Bring it on, Miyo-chan!
That looks good, Takasu.
Today's fried pork chops!
Yeah, I had some leftovers from last night.
I woke up this morning and added a quick egg to it to make this.
What will you be using?
That's good. Let's see...
Are you going to be using expensive ingredients since you love your cute little grandson so much?
All right.
Roe with rice? Shark fin with rice?
Huh?
That's rather simple.
I did tell her just some riceballs would be fine.
I didn't think it'd be this simple.
This is way too simple and not enough for a high schooler's lunch.
I am the victo—
Wait, what's that shiny layer on top?
Sesame oil?
That means...
Wait, that's...
So good!
There's grilled meat inside!
I never expected meat to be in it.
This is Korean seaweed, huh?
This is the perfect boxed lunch.
Is this plum?
What about this?
Yeah! It's tuna mayo!
That's my favorite!
You even screamed out "yeah".
Using grilled meat as a surprise.
Then there's the godlike plum one.
And last but not least, Kitamura's favorite tuna mayo.
With the variety, it's easily a perfect combination.
Compared to that...
The sweet taste of dashi is always what I have...
Ryuuji...
Thanks. The fried pork chops with eggs is really good.
Oh, really?
Those riceballs look amazing!
Riceballs for dinner sound good.
Pork chops are yummy, but having them for two days in a row is a bit too much.
Oh, I thought I told you that we had a little too much pork...
No.
Because of Miyo-chan's influence, I wanted to make some fabulous fried food.
But in order to play by the rules...
I have to use the pork chops as leftovers!
That's right, in order to mix eggs with pork chops...
I made fried pork chops for dinner last night.
As a housewife, one must be aware of repetition.
Though I overdid it a little yesterday,
I've gotten back in touch now.
Miyo!
You called my grandmother by her first name?!
Boxed lunch... Boxed lunch...
What should I do?
What should I put in it?
Boxed lunch...
Hey, what should we put in our riceballs?
Salmon is a must, right?
Let's not use sautéed ones... Let's just use regular—
Riceballs?!
There's no way I can win if I make the same thing that Kitamura had for lunch today!
I'm not talking about lunch. I'm talking about dinner.
That can wait.
You know, I'm very confident in my housewife abilities.
I also have pride tied to it.
Huh?
Within the league of high school boxed lunches,
even an above average junior level housewife can't beat a professional one.
I've been a frog living in a well.
Having been thrown into the ocean of professionals...
And after swimming with the shark named Kitamura Miyo...
Skipjack sounds good.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Buying ingredients for my slow dog.
How could you?
You're just buying junk food and pudding!
What! I bought skipjack as well!
Those are for dessert.
Oh, did you know?
If you put soy sauce on pudding, it'll taste like melon!
I'm pretty sure you're wrong about that.
Oh, really?
This isn't the time for this.
Maybe it's not melon... It must be watermelon...
Oh, right!
Something that a shark doesn't have but a frog does.
That's...
Youth!
Hey, Taiga.
Hey, Master Kitamura.
Hey, remember to stop 5mm below the line.
No more no less!
It's nearly there! Nearly!
Shut up!
You're the one who always tells me to not eat this stuff!
What's that? Cup noodles?
Oh, Minorin.
You even brought your own water dispenser!
That's awesome!
You guys are freaking awesome!
What's up? Eating cup noodles for lunch?
I wish I were you guys. I hate my cold boxed lunch.
Smells good!
Good for you...
It looks yummy!
Eating cup noodles at home is normal...
But eating it in class, however, is new.
I'm adding a bit of joy in your average, boring lunchtime.
Kitamura's grandmother won't understand this because she's not young like us.
Today...
I win.
Minorin, you're not eating with us?
There's a special meeting for my club today.
Hey, sup! Kitamura, my man!
Let's go, my man.
Sorry about that.
Yo, Kitamura.
I accidentally overslept, that's why we're having cup noodles today...
Oh, you have hot water?
Y-Yeah.
Let me have some.
Thank goodness...
My grandmother brought me instant soup.
She told me there's got to be someone eating cup noodles, so just ask them for water.
I thought that'd be impossible.
But thank god you're here.
I have this and sandwiches today.
Good for eating during a meeting.
Kitamura-kun!
Sorry, Kushieda, let's go.
See you later, Taiga.
All right.
Sandwiches sound good.
Then don't eat your noodles.
Huh?
No, you can't eat it! Hey!
What the heck are you doing?
You can't eat it! You can't!
What's going on?
I have no idea what the hell you're talking about! Ouch!
Eating cup noodles won't net you any calcium.
Watch out!
No, give it!
Hot!
Sorry for making you wait!
Not enough...
There's not enough...
Despite that...
I brought you a lot on another plate.
Thanks, Minorin!
Don't need to thank me.
Tell me if it's not enough.
We have a lot, lot more.
I'll bring even more.
Thanks!
Anyway...
Filling up on carbs right after school?
Cup noodles aren't filling.
Not to mention, I didn't even get to eat it...
Anyway, I'm fine with the normal boxed lunches Yuuji makes.
Something's gotten into his head.
Taiga, you poor woman...
Have you become someone who can't survive without Takasu Ryuuji feeding you?
Huh?!
It's quite all right. Food is the most important thing in life.
There's no need to be ashamed of being spoon-fed.
Anyway, take your time!
Boxed lunch, huh...
No... No...
No!
This is so wrong.
What's this? Are we having a party?
Looks really good.
But I won't be able to eat it all.
Where's Taiga-chan?
I don't know.
Can I take some to the store?
Yagai-san's wife ran away with some other man.
He's gonna be super happy.
Ryuu-chan's cooking is delicious!
I'm off!
I should eat dinner.
Yum! Yum!
What? She should come over if she's at home.
I bet she's still angry at what happened during lunch.
I have no time for her.
In order to defeat Kitamura Miyo, I must make the ultimate boxed lunch!
I will do whatever it takes to win.
For example, I could put curry in rice that's molded.
Or bring sashimi inside a cooler box to make seafood-don with vinegar rice.
Or I could just make a grand sushi feast!
Hey, stop making those noises! You sound like you're eating leftover food scraps!
One more.
You want more? Wai—
Leftover food scraps?
I failed by using leftover pork chops to make pork chops with egg.
Then I'll just use freshly made, piping hot...
I got it.
This is it! This is...
In... In...
Calling me a cheater?
Say whatever you want, Inko-chan.
Inzaghi!
Whatever.
Do you know Phillip Inzaghi?
That's right. I'll just resort to underhanded tactics.
I'll have to break this wall!
Hot...
Hot!
The Hayabusa bullet train debuted March 5th on the Tohoku Shinkansen line.
Thrilling rail fans and people living in northern...
What's this smell...
What is this?
That's...
What's this sound?
No, I'm just dreaming...
That can't be true...
But...
A rice cooker?
Seriously?
No way!
It smells really good, though.
Smells really good.
I'm hungry now.
So what's up with this, Takasu-kun?
Takasu?
Hey, Taka-chan!
Stop cooking rice in class.
You're kidding me!
Wait, guys!
Hold your horses, Miss!
Why did you point your fingers at me?!
I'm innocent until proven guilty!
Who else would do something like this?
Right, it's me!
Forgive me, Miss!
Leave her alone!
It's... It's nearly done!
Spare her!
Wh-What happened?!
Idiot.
It's over.
What a waste.
If you turn it on again, the food will still be good, right?
Cooking it twice won't taste as good.
Who cares about it being not as good?
You've lost already.
The treasures of autumn.
Fan mushrooms, oyster mushrooms, and lots of other mushrooms...
Huh?
Putting all of those together with piping hot rice would've pushed me to victory.
That's not a boxed lunch anymore.
I know.
First I set the rules, and then I proceed to break them.
On top of that, I didn't even win.
Who cares about all of that?
You should blame yourself for this mess.
Here.
I knew we wouldn't be eating anything good for lunch anyway.
This is for you, my lost dog who's drowning in the quicksand of thought.
Did you make this?
Don't underestimate me!
Even I can make riceballs.
You taught me before.
Hot!
Freshly cooked rice is a weapon of mass destruction!
Be patient! Cold rice won't stick together!
Look!
Hot!
What?
I don't have to give it to you if you don't want it.
I-I'll take it!
Thanks!
How is it?
Hmm...
What's the matter? Are you so touched you're shivering?
So salty!
Let's put some dashi on it.
It shouldn't be as salty now.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hang on, let me put in some chervil.
Here.
Thanks for the food!
Hey, you'll choke if you don't chew.
So good!
This is so good!
Look, the essence is in this plum filling.
I'm a genius.
I see...
You're right.
I'm a genius?
That's right. Putting that comic book boxed lunch aside...
Actually, I take that back.
Miyo-chan's boxed lunches was made to make Kitamura happy.
The riceballs were Kitamura's request.
The onion soup was because she knew Kitamura had a meeting during lunch.
All she had in sight was Kitamura.
But I...
I'm full.
You're the one who's eating my boxed lunches.
What are you talking about?
I'm even hungrier now after eating a bit.
I really want to have a big feast.
Fried pork chops sound good!
Fried pork chops in tea!
Eating pork chops three times a week?
Oh, we still have sliced meat.
That's right! Mille-feuille styled pork chops!
Oh, right, go finish cooking your rice.
Let's eat it for dinner.
Oh, you're so difficult...
You're not going to eat riceballs with tea?
I'll just eat it as it is.
It scared the heck out of me when I took a bite...
Well, it's not inedible.
I think you were trying to be rude there.
I wasn't.
You were!
That's why I demand you to put some cheese on the fried pork chops!
Huh?
I understood the essence of the boxed lunch.
A boxed lunch made for someone you're thinking of... someone special...
will be delicious no matter what.
banira saruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla