Who am I?
Your name is Takuto.
Why am I here?
You're here to create new memories.
I see.
This is the first time I've ever heard her,
but her singing is really good.
Many things have happened in
this year since I made my debut.
I encountered many different people,
became friends with them,
and they've helped me
along the way.
This is a very valuable treasure.
Full Moon!
Madoka and I
went through a lot,
but now they're
just good memories.
No...
It may actually be that I was able to
persevere this far because of Madoka.
Ms. Oshige,
thank you very much.
Those are the only words
I can find to tell you.
Grandma, thank you for
coming to hear me sing.
I hope that you will start
to like my singing.
What's the matter, Takuto?
Are you in pain?
Wait!
Thank you very much.
There's something
I'd like to say to everyone.
Huh? Was that on the schedule?
This year since my debut has
been a very important time for me.
It was a year in which a very naïve girl
experienced many things.
To me, singing is life itself.
It is a very important thing.
Therefore, in order to protect
something so important,
please indulge my selfishness.
I'm going to be
taking some time off.
- What?
Hey, hey, what's this about?
She hasn't told us anything
about that.
What do you mean?!
Are you trying to run away from me?
Madoka.
Today is the last day that
I will see you all.
I can't tell you the reason.
I'm sorry!
It's life threatening?
Is that true, Ms. Oshige?
I can't believe it.
But I will make you a promise!
I'll make a comeback someday,
so that I may meet you
all again one day!
I will!
Madoka...
We'll be waiting for you, Full Moon!
It's a promise!
Hurry back!
Thank you.
Thank you very much!
My sincere thanks to you all.
Let me sing one last song as
a present to you all.
And to one particular person.
Takuto!
This person is
so important to me.
If he had not been there,
I wouldn't be standing here singing.
No, Takuto!
You can't disappear!
This is Mitsuki's last song!
To that person, with heartfelt thanks...
"Love Chronicle."
Don't! No, Takuto!
Please don't disappear!
- Why is it that I've forgotten
- No! No!
- how to fall in love?
- No!
Our meeting is the beginning
of our separation.
Somewhere along the line
I started to believe that way.
When the shoelace on
my dirty sneakers came loose,
you tied them for me.
Seeing your bashful smile
under the morning sun,
my heart pounded instantly.
I don't love you just because
- No matter what...I won't let Mitsuki die!
- I want you to love me.
You gave me the courage
to honestly love you.
We will now—
Meroko!
What are you doing, Mitsuki?!
Sing!
B-But...
Everything's fine over here,
so finish singing your song!
But...Meroko...
Please, Mitsuki.
I want to hear you sing.
You gave me the courage
to honestly love you.
We will now head towards
the dream for tomorrow.
No matter what happens,
I'll never look away.
I don't love you just because
I want you to love me.
You gave me the courage
to honestly love you.
We will now vow
to the coming journey.
No matter what happens,
I'll never let go off this hand, forever!
Izumi?
That was just
a three-dimensional image.
That was what Meroko wanted.
And also...
Don't worry, Mitsuki.
Just leave yourself in
the good hands of Dr. Wakaoji.
Okay.
Ms. Oshige, where are
Takuto and Meroko?
I don't know.
But they'll be all right.
I am certain that those two will keep watch
over you, Mitsuki,
no matter where they are.
Right?
Yes.
IN SURGERY
Where's this?
Are you awake?
Who are you?
I do not have a name.
People have always called me
by different names.
Takuto Kira. You regained your memory
from when you were alive
and have therefore lost the right
to be a Death Spirit.
Normally, your fate would be
to become a ghost left to wander,
but because you have eaten
the Flower of Forgetfulness,
even that is no longer possible.
What are you talking about?
You have forgotten even that,
haven't you?
I don't have the time to
indulge you by chatting.
I have things I need to do.
See you.
What is it that you must do?
It's...
Don't you remember?
I... What I want is to save
that girl's life.
Who do you mean by "that girl"?
That...
I can't remember.
Why can't I remember anything?!
Takuto!
Takuto Kira, Meroko Yui.
Not only did both of you try to
hinder the course of fate,
but you even laid your hands on
the forbidden Flower of Forgetfulness.
This is not something that
can be forgiven.
You will receive punishment
appropriate for your crimes.
And as for Mitsuki Koyama...
- You're not going to take her life.
- No! Please...not that!
Her blood pressure has
suddenly started dropping.
Three more minutes.
Please hang in there, Mitsuki.
I don't care.
I don't care what happens to me.
But please refrain from that!
What do you think gives you
the right to say something like that?
I don't know.
But I'm begging you, please don't
do what you're about to do!
There was a life I wanted to save.
There was someone who
I wanted to save.
I don't remember anything,
but it remains inside here!
It remains inside here!
So please don't kill her!
Please don't take
the life of that girl!
I will do anything to stop you!
If you wish to do that,
you can no longer be a Death Spirit.
Nor can you become a ghost.
Is that all right with you?
Yes.
Takuto!
Takuto! Takuto!
Please save Takuto!
Please make me a ghost instead!
This man here cannot
even remember you.
And you still say you wish
to take his place?
Takuto has taught me many things.
What it is to love someone...
and what to do when you love someone.
Even now, he is trying to save Mitsuki
even if it means giving up his own life.
That's why I would have
no regrets about taking Takuto's place.
Doctor! She's stabilizing.
All right. Continue like this.
Her fate has already been changed.
Huh?
Meroko Yui. Stand up.
I release you from being a Death Spirit.
All right...
Eichi!
Takuto! Meroko!
I'm always being helped by
the two of you, aren't I?
Takuto? Meroko?
Huh?
No! Don't go, you two!
No! You can't go!
Meroko! Takuto!
Mitsuki!
You're awake! What a relief.
Ms. Tanaka, please go get Dr. Wakaoji
and tell him that Mitsuki has woken up.
All right!
I'm so relieved.
You were asleep for one full day.
Mitsuki?
Does it hurt somewhere?
Mitsuki? Mitsuki?
Ma'am?
Mitsuki has gone to the annex.
Again?
Just when Madoka says
she'll come to visit.
The operation was a success,
so she should be able to speak now.
It seems that the two of them
leaving has given her quite a shock.
Even though Takuto and Meroko
are Death Spirits,
they put their lives on the line
to protect Mitsuki.
From now on,
we must protect Mitsuki.
Yes.
Are you on the phone
with Wakaoji again?
President!
It's great to get all fired up,
but exercise some moderation!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll get right back to work!
It looks like she can't see me.
I told you.
I wonder why.
Back then, she wanted to die if
she was going to be in such agony.
I think that's why
they were visible to her.
I wonder where those two
are right about now.
I have no idea.
But what is certain is that
we'll never see them again.
Are we going to be punished
in some way?
Continuing to be Death Spirits...
That's our punishment.
That's right.
I'm giving it to someone who's
just been released from the hospital.
I see. In that case
I'll give you a discount.
Great! Thank you very much.
See you later.
Oh my goodness...
What a cute mascot.
He really likes it.
But he doesn't know why he has it.
It's because he hasn't regained
his memory
after a terrible motorcycle accident
two years ago.
- Now then, it's been six weeks
- Hey! Stop running off your mouth!
- since Full Moon went on a break.
- Sorry, sorry.
Everybody must be worried about her
since we haven't heard any news, right?
So we're doing
a Full Moon Special today!
To start off,
I'd like to wish for her early return.
Just like the title, I would like her
to grasp a new future.
Here is the new song,
"New Future."
Meroko Yui...
I release you from being a Death Spirit.
You can no longer exist
as a Death Spirit.
All right.
Someone like you who has
been touched by true kindness...
You will become an angel.
M-Me?
And you, Takuto Kira...
The feeling of loving someone
and wanting to protect and
save them is wonderful.
But there are few who can
truly act on those feelings.
You are one of those few,
moreover, that girl possessed
the will to avert her fate.
What do you plan to do with Takuto?
Takuto has not yet become
a real Death Spirit.
I will grant you one more chance.
Huh?
Thank you very much!
However, Takuto will have to undergo
the same test again.
If the result is the same this time,
Takuto will immediately become
a ghost left to wander.
Takuto will do fine this time.
That's wonderful, isn't it, Takuto?
Huh?
Why am I here?
Well, I guess it doesn't really matter.
Meroko!
My, what beautiful flowers.
I'm sure they will make
Mitsuki very happy.
I'm so glad.
Hey! Mitsuki!
Meroko!
Oh, Mitsuki!
I missed you!
Meroko! Meroko! Meroko!
Takuto! Takuto!
Good luck!
Takuto!
Takuto...
This is goodbye, isn't it, Mitsuki?
Meroko!
Thank you!
Meroko?
Takuto...