Yuki-senpai made a graduation album.
Graduation Album
In it were pictures of how I met all my upperclassmen.
Back when I was trapped in the mall,
when Kei was with me.
And when she left, too.
I was saved by the upperclassmen,
who brought me back to school.
This is a story from before I was a club member.
And then, I thought it'd be great
if she joined our club!
Yeah, that's right!
Who's that?
I mean, she's wearing the same uniform,
so she goes to our school, right?
So we'll have more friends now!
I'll be fine, just leave it to me!
That's right, you think so too, huh, Taromaru!
Who's...
Good morning!
School Living Club
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Issho ni (Hai!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
Houkago nara atarimae no koto
Saa sa, atsumare!
Kossori kaeruna! (Kora!)
Bukatsu dou dane? Katsudou shichau ne!
Asonderu nja arimasen
Tadaima tte ano ko ga iu yo (Okaeri!)
Minna de ireba daijoubu (Bu!)
Everybody say: tomodachi de iyou ne
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Daisuki (Hai!)
Watachitachi wa tanoshinderu
24 jikan hashaideru
Okujou ni wa akana taiyou
Kanari sakendemita (Genki desu!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
Welcome
How are you feeling?
Why don't you get her some water for now?
Oh, yeah!
Want water?
Huh? Sure, thanks.
Okay!
I'm... at school?
Here you go!
Thank you.
Umm, you're from the same school, er...
from Megurigaoka?
Oh, that's right, we haven't
introduced ourselves yet.
That's right!
I'm Yuki Takeya, a third-year
in Class C at Megurigaoka High!
I'm Megumi Sakura. I'm a teacher here at-
No way, you're a third-year?
That's right!
She's already ignoring me?!
What's your name?
I'm Miki Naoki, a second-year in Class B.
That makes me your senpai!
Is she really older than me?
U-um, where are we?
We're in the School Living Club room!
She won't understand it if you put it like that.
Tell her we're at school.
Oh, sorry, Megu-nee.
"Megu-nee" again! You know better.
Sorry, Sakura-sensei.
Here, have this as an apology.
Thanks!
Wait, this is just a half-empty water bottle!
We're at our school,
Megurigaoka High!
School?
I'm really...
at school...
Okay, so-
Oh, there you are!
Taromaru?!
That's right, he told us you were in there!
Huh?
Taromaru!
I see.
Um, I...
He doesn't like me.
Um, uh...
That's right, Yuki-chan, it's been
a while since she's been here,
so why not give her a tour of the school?
Oh, good idea, Megu-nee!
C'mon!
Let's go, Mii-kun!
Huh?
"Mii-kun"?
Ah, you left the door open.
It's okay, Megu-nee's there!
Music Room
First, here's the music room!
I know.
You know, I was a student here...
I wonder if any people in the
Light Music Club are here?
Clubs are going on?!
Was school completely unaffected?
Huh, they're not here.
Mii-kun, nobody's here, so let's go in.
No, but all of that already...
Maybe I just dreamed it.
See?
Isn't it amazing?
There are so many instruments!
Huh? What's wrong?
Nothing.
It really is amazing.
It wasn't a dream...
Come on now, she won't understand
if you don't properly explain things.
Oh, you're right, Megu-nee.
If you join the School Living Club,
you can sing here as much as you want!
School Living Club?
So whaddya think?
It's a waste of electricity.
Aww!
C'mon, Beethoven, Bach, and Mozart are all watching us!
Who cares?
What?!
Wh-what should I do, Megu-nee?!
For now, could you hold this? It's heavy!
Whaaat?!
No, it's really heavy!
Come on, let's hurry up and go, Yuki-senpai.
Yuki-senpai
Yuki-senpai.
Senpai
Senpai.
S-say that again.
Let's hurry up and go, Yuki-senpai.
Squee
You're creeping me out.
"Senpai" has a nice ring to it!
You've always wanted someone to call you
"Senpai", haven't you, Yuki-chan?
If that's the case, please act more like a senpai.
You're so mean, Mii-kun!
What is this "Mii-kun" all about?
You're Miki, so I'm calling you "Mii-kun"!
Can I?
Just call me Miki.
Huh?!
Don't you think "Mii-kun" is cuter?
I don't want a cute name.
But you're so cute, Mii-kun!
You think she's cute, right, Megu-nee?
Now Yuki-chan, don't force her into it.
What, you don't think she's cute, Megu-nee?
I do think she's cute, but that's not the point.
Um, sorry, but I really don't understand
what you're going on about.
Huh?
Can I ask you something?
Who...
...is Megu-nee?
Huh?
Jeez, Yuki left the door wide open again.
Hey, Yuki, the door's wide open!
Huh?
Neither of them are here!
Music Room
Umm,
Mii-kun, what are you...
Oh, Megu-nee, that's not true!
You do have presence, Megu-nee!
Don't be sad, Megu-nee!
Mii-kun, you're so mean!
Sure, you're hard to notice, but we do see you!
Huh?
Sorry, I meant that in a good way!
Being hard to notice is a good thing!
Ah, wait, uh, jeez!
Tell her, Mii-kun!
Tell her she's not hard to notice!
Umm...
Tell her...
she's here!
Okay?
Yuki!
School Living Club
So, because it was depressing to
live out our lives with nothing to do,
we turned it into a camping trip for a club.
And that's the School Living Club?
Megu-nee and Ri-san came up with it
after things had died down a little.
Um, this Megu-nee, who is she?
Our teacher.
She was always so positive,
always cared so much for her students.
She was a great teacher.
Where is she now?
She's gone.
Megu-nee always protected us.
She was protecting us then, too.
Let go of me!
Yuki-chan, stop!
Megu-nee's still out there!
We have to hurry!
No, you can't!
Megu-nee!
Hey!
Open up, Megu-nee!
C'mon!
Megu-nee!
So that's what happened.
But Yuki-senpai was talking to her just now,
as if she was still alive.
What's that about?
Yuki still sees Megu-nee.
Her ghost?
No, not her ghost.
In her heart, the world is as it was.
That's why, even now,
she still goes to class.
In her heart, Megu-nee is still alive, even now.
I see.
I hope she gets better soon.
Miki-san, I have a favor to ask of you.
Is that alright?
What is it?
While you're staying here,
could you play along with her?
Huh?
But then she'll never snap out of it!
It's not about...
...whether she gets better or not.
I don't think you understand it yet...
What's there to understand?
W-wait, calm down, you guys.
Okay?
Alright. I'll play along until I
get to know Yuki-senpai better.
Is that alright?
Hey, welcome back!
We're back.
I've been waiting for you guys!
C'mon, sit down, sit down!
What, what?
So, what is it?
Okay, everyone!
Let's have a sports festival!
My!
Why a sports festival?
Because it's fun to exercise together!
All of us, with Mii-kun, too!
Like a game?
It's not a game, it's a club activity!
A club activity?
Now, Yuki-chan, Miki-san doesn't
know about our club yet.
Oh, that's right!
School Living Club
Rule #5
School Living Club Rule #5!
Official school events are matters of
the utmost importance!
So...
that's...
why...
we're gonna have a sports festival!
fwip!
Got it?
I don't get it.
Aren't there other things we should be doing?
But things we wanna do are more important
than things we should do!
How useless are you?!
I think it's a good opportunity for you.
Huh?
You can learn more about Yuki.
Okay.
I guess you're right.
Yay!
RED TEAM
Megurigaoka High
Sports Festival
Hamburger
steak
Everyone
participates!
I love Taromaru!
Let's make memories together!!
Opening Ceremony
Festival Program
Beautiful Scavenger Hunt!
Ultra Ball Rolling
Great Ball Toss
Lightspeed 3-Legged Race
Lightning-Fast Sprint
Are you okay?
Great Ball Toss
Mii-kun! ;_;
Don't call
me Mii-kun.
Mii-kun! ;_;
Winners
Loser
Here.
Thank you.
It's kinda nice going all-out and exercising, huh?
Yeah.
It was fun.
I dunno why, but whenever
something like this is really needed,
Yuki comes up with it.
That's why we went to the shopping mall.
She just suddenly said we should go on a field trip.
Huh?!
It was really sudden,
and I thought it was weird, too,
but I'm glad we went.
It's important to think about everything,
but if you're thinking about it all the time,
you won't make any progress.
Think about it all the time...
Of course, there are times when acting out
and moving about aren't right, either.
When it's not right to sit and think or take action,
Yuki is the one who figures it out.
I guess, maybe.
Mii-kun
Food tastes so good after you've
done a ton of exercise!
I agree!
There's lots more left.
It's delicious.
Isn't it delicious, Megu-nee?
Huh, no, it's okay, you can eat this!
It's weird.
I used to think Yuki-senpai and
Megu-nee was so strange.
Huh, no, it's okay, you can eat this!
I used to think Yuki-senpai and
Megu-nee was so strange.
After all, it's not gonna change what's already...
Oh, no, I meant that in a good way!
But now, I'm kind of glad they're here.
Are you happy, living in here, shut away?
That's right.
Back then, we were simply alive.
Hey, what'd you think of today?
Did you have fun?
More than fun, it left me spinning.
O-oh!
Well, living with you is hardly boring, Yuki-chan.
It's so lively!
Though you're more of a danger to us than Taromaru.
What was that?!
I'm glad I came here.
Huh?
Never mind.
Oh, want seconds?
Thank you.
Wh-what is it?
Nothing, just you're a better senpai
than I first thought.
Huh?
You're amazing, you really are.
Huh? Whaaa...?
I'm amazing?
Never mind, you're not.
Whaaa...?!
Oh?
Umm, can I talk to you for a sec?
There's something I have to ask you.
May I join the School Living Club?
Huh?
I can start as a trial member if you want.
I want to know more about Yuki-senpai!
We'd love to have you.
Welcome to the School Living Club!
Opening Ceremony
Okay, there.
Oh, that looks great!
This is from before you joined our club, right?
You were there, too.
All done!
Let's make lots of memories!
Akaneiro ni kimi wa
Nani o kangaeteita no
Mabuta ippai namida o tamete
Gomakashiteita kirei da ne to
Utagai mo naku
Konna hibi ga tsuzuite ikunda tte
Zutto omotteita
Miageta sora wa tooku tooku
Bokura mitsumeteiru
Tada shizuka ni kawaranai mama
Maigo no te to te nigirishimeta
Mou samishiku wa nai yo
Owaru sekai mukou gishi eto
Bokura no yoake ga mieru kara
Mieru kara
Waratte
Next Time!
We did it, Megu-nee! We got a new member!
I'm a senpai now! It sounds so good!
That's right! Like "bam"!
Letters
Next time on School-Live, episode 7:
"Letters"
Right, Megu-nee?