[narrator] When a person
has extreme social anxiety,
they struggle to communicate with others.
[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] For example,
imagine they make friends with someone
in a special situation,
but when they see that person again
for the first time after...
[Ayami] What if I go up to her all excited
and say, "Hi," but then she just goes,
"Oh. Uh-huh," like she thinks I'm weird?
[Mikuni] But on the other hand,
avoiding her would feel unnatural too.
Ugh! Our eyes just met, but I looked away!
[narrator] ...just like that.
[Ayami and Mikuni]
I don't know what I should say to her!
[narrator] That's what it's like.
[Nakanaka gasping] Hey, Agari!
[Agari gasping] Uh... Oh.
I bought you the novel we talked about
when we were on
our school field trip in Kyoto.
[Agari] Uh...
[giggling] It was so thoughtful of you
to bring that for me, Nakanaka.
Thank you so much!
[Nakanaka grunting]
You should be grateful!
[both chuckling]
Did you get Darkness Kikuichimonji
"parentheses L-O-L" back?
[Nakanaka] There's no "parentheses L-O-L!"
So did you make the phone call
all by yourself?
[Nakanaka] Oh, uh... Why of course, I did!
[Yamai] Uh-huh. Really?
- Wow. That's amazing, Inaka.
- [Komi gasping]
So did you make these yourself?
These are so cute!
Uh, I hope you don't mind.
[Onemine] Why would I mind?
These are great.
- [Kaede] Thank you so much!
- [boy] Hey, here he comes!
[students gasping]
[narrator] Makoto Katai
has arrived at school.
[Makoto] Today, for once,
I'm gonna say good morning.
Good morning, Katai.
[Makoto] Huh? Tadano is so nice!
[boys] Katai, good morning!
[Makoto] Huh?
- [Naruse] Hey, Katai.
- [Makoto] Hmm?
About the other night in Kyoto,
your body looked great.
[narrator] The boys love fans.
[Naruse] By the way,
I'll give you copies of those photos
so you can share
that work of art we created.
All right. I'll see you later.
[Mikuni] Okay. See you later!
[Komi grunting]
[Hitohito grunting]
[Hitohito] Komi in her normal state,
but getting into a negative state,
and getting into a
"whatever happens, happens" state.
A second negative state is common.
She's not going...
[upbeat music playing]
[Komi grunting]
[Komi gasping]
[Hitohito grunting]
- [Mikuni] Komi?
- [Komi gasping]
Um, uh, good morning.
GOOD MORNING.
[Mikuni] Oh.
[Komi grunting]
[Mikuni] Hmm. [chuckling]
[Komi gasping]
[Mikuni] Having a conversation
through a notebook is kinda funny.
Hi, Komi, and good morning!
You know Himeko's armor, right?
She said one of the parts is missing.
- [Ayami] Excuse me for a second.
- Okay!
[Ayami giggling]
[Ayami] Good morning!
[narrator] On the other hand,
Tadano was lost in thought.
[opening theme music playing]
[music fades]
[narrator] Lunch break.
By the way, Komi,
what are you doing for Valentine's Day?
[Komi grunting]
[indistinct chatter]
GLANCE
NOTHING YET.
[Onemine] She hesitated just now.
Hey. You wanna come over to my house
and make something together?
Every year
I make something special for my family.
It would be more fun
to invite some friends over
and do it together, right?
NOD
[Onemine] Okay. It's settled, then.
[Kaede] Hey, you guys?
Can I come over too?
[Onemine] Sure. Come on over.
Sorry, Tadano. It's just a girl's night.
Oh, uh, I... I didn't wanna go, anyway.
[narrator] But he was trying to listen.
[dramatic music playing]
[Onemine] All right. Here we are.
- [door sliding open]
- [Onemine] I'm home!
Oh. Those guys, they left a big mess.
[kids giggling, laughing]
- [boy] Welcome back!
- [girl] Welcome back!
[boy] Kaede, thanks for coming!
What a nice home.
[girl] Hey.
What are we going to play today, hmm?
[Komi gasping]
KAZUYA ONEMINE (AGE 6)
NANA ONEMINE (AGE 6)
NONO ONEMINE (AGE 3)
SHOKO KOMI (AGE 16)
[Komi shuddering]
[Komi gasping]
- [Komi shrieking]
- [kids laughing]
[Komi gasping]
Oh. Those are my siblings.
There's four of them.
They might bug you sometimes,
but I'm sure you'll be friends.
[Komi] Uh-huh.
[Onemine] All right. Let's get started.
[all exclaiming]
[Onemine] Komi, melt the chocolate
and the butter over a hot-water bath.
Kaede, sift the flour
and the cocoa powder.
[kids laughing]
[uplifting music playing]
EGG WHITE, EGG YOLK
[both exclaiming]
Oh, come on, you two.
It's really not that big a deal.
Next, put it over the hot water bath
and mix in the sugar,
and then the whipped cream and the brandy.
We're also going to mix in
the chocolate we just melted.
And now let's make the meringue!
[Kaede exclaiming]
♪ It's time to become delicious
It's time to become delicious, now, yay ♪
At this rate, it's going
to take more than a week to make.
Oh! Can we help you out?
Oh, yeah!
Okay. Go wash your hands first!
[Komi grunting]
[kids clamoring]
[narrator] Komi feels uneasy.
Komi, can you go
and help them out over there?
I'll take care of stuff here.
[kids] Our arms are tired!
But the meringue's not puffy yet.
- Keep stirring.
- [kids whining]
[kids] Huh?
[Komi grunting]
WHIP WHIP
[kids exclaiming]
Amazing! The scary girl's cool!
SCARY!?
[Kaede] ♪ You can do it, you can do it ♪
My turn next!
All right! You can do it!
FLUFFY
Wow. You all did a great job!
[kids] Yay!
[Onemine] All right. Next, we're going
to fold in a bit of the meringue.
We'll also add in some of the flour
and cocoa powder we sifted.
Then, we're going
to add the meringue in three parts.
All right.
[narrator] They both ate some in secret.
Now, we bake.
You and the girls go play
for about 50 minutes.
- [kids cheering]
- [Komi gasping]
[whimsical music playing]
[Kaede] Once upon a time
there was a man that was old...
[Kazuya] Hey, scary girl,
how come you don't talk?
[Komi gasping]
Ha! I was just wondering the same thing!
She's just more shy than you kids,
so don't be mean to her.
[Kazuya] Sha?
Not "sha."
Okay. Try saying "Ah!"
Go on. Say "Ah!"
- Ah!
- [Komi shuddering]
[kids] Ah! Say "Ah!"
[Komi sighing]
Ah.
[kids] Oh!
- [kids] Mmm.
- [narrator] They lost interest in her.
Ha! You think the cake's done yet?
Let's check! Come on, shaa girl!
[Komi grunting]
Whoa! Look at that! It's rising!
[Kazuya] Wow!
[Nana] Yeah!
[Kazuya] Hey, shaa girl.
[Komi grunting]
You've got a really pretty voice.
You should talk a lot more, you know?
Yeah, you should!
[Komi gasping]
[dramatic music playing]
I'll try my... best.
[babbling]
[Onemine] Okay, everyone, let's sit down.
It's time to have
some homemade chocolate cake that we made.
[kids] Yay!
[Onemine] Our cake turned out great.
[Kaede] Oh, it did.
[Kazuya] Mmm!
[Nana] Mmm.
Here.
- [Onemine] Komi.
- [Komi grunting]
Whatcha think? Does it taste good?
[Komi grunting]
We did it.
It's so sweet!
- What a delicious cake.
- [man yawning]
Oh, whoa! What is that?
- [Onemine] Oh. You should try some.
- [man] I will.
[kids laughing]
[kids] Good job, sister!
Oh, boy. Looks like we ate it all.
- Sorry, you guys.
- [Komi grunting]
- [Shuko] You're making a lot!
[narrator] Love.
An inescapable part of life.
Today is the day
on which even the most proper of ladies
are allowed to approach
the person they have feelings for.
The girls become lively,
and the boys become fidgety.
That's right, today is Valentine's Day.
[Komi grunting]
TADANO'S SHOE LOCKER
[narrator] Komi gets closer
to Tadano's shoe cubby.
[girl laughing]
What are you talking about?
FLEES
[indistinct chatter]
[Hitohito humming]
GLANCE
[narrator] Tadano is checking further back
in the cubby than usual today.
There's nothing there.
Ah, good morning Komi.
[Komi grunting]
[narrator] Tadano is checking
inside his desk.
There's nothing there.
Well, hello!
Happy Valentine's Day, everyone!
- Here, Komi! Friendship chocolate!
- [Komi gasping]
[lively music playing]
[Komi gasping]
[Najimi] Whoa, Komi!
Did you make these yourself?
Oh, yay! Why thank you!
[Najimi cackling]
All I did was give her
one Tirol chocolate, and what did I get?
Something even bigger in return.
Valentine's Day is great!
[Hitohito] Oh.
Good morning, Komi!
[Hitohito] There she is.
You know, I actually made some delicious,
personalized Valentine's chocolates
just for you.
Here, take this!
- [Komi gasping]
- [Hitohito] Whoa.
Go on. Eat one.
I want you to eat my face.
Lick it, suck on it, and eat me.
After that,
I will finally be inside of you forever.
[Komi grunting]
[Yamai] Uh... uh...
[Komi shuddering]
[Yamai grunting]
[Yamai exclaiming]
[heavenly music playing]
[Yamai squealing]
[Yamai moaning]
- [Hitohito] Huh? Yamai?
- [Komi gasping]
[Hitohito] Hey, Yamai! Are you okay?
[Nakanaka] I can't believe
she's excited about Valentine's Day.
It is an event manufactured
by corporations behind the scenes.
She's letting them manipulate her.
Ignorant fool.
I'm not letting it affect me.
Look, I am perfectly normal today.
Admire my integrity and bow down to me!
- Uh... uh...
- [Komi grunting]
[Nakanaka gasping]
[gasping] Thank you so much
for these, Komi!
[Makeru seething] Komi has more!
Sorry about the cake, Komi.
These are for you.
So who are you giving
your true love chocolates to?
[both groaning]
[narrator] Makoto Katai arrives at school.
[Makoto] Today's Valentine's Day.
I heard there's this new thing where guys
are giving rival chocolates to each other.
Hmm?
I... I brought chocolates for Tadano,
but it would be embarrassing
if I approached him first.
I... I wish
he would approach me first instead.
[Chushaku] You're a young maiden.
[Yamai] Chiarai, here.
Just so you know,
it's obligation chocolate.
You need to give me
three times as much on White Day.
[Shigeo] Thanks so much.
Come on! You've got
to act more happy than that!
- Do not move.
- [Taisei grunting]
The thing poking you
in the back is the real thing.
- No. Please, stop. Please, don't do it.
- [Nakanaka grunting]
[Taisei shuddering]
[Taisei] Huh? Huh?
[Taisei gasping]
- [Nakanaka moaning]
- [Taisei grunting]
[Taisei] It's for real.
[Inaka] Hm?
Uh, Valentine's Day?
But what is that?
[Mono] I'm not saying
I want chocolates or anything...
[Inaka] Chocolates?
So you give chocolate to who you like?
Aha!
I have some karinto.
You want some?
[narrator] They're fantasizing.
- Hi, Katai!
- [Makoto] Huh?
[boys] Sasaki! You're going to die!
- Come on, Kato. You can do it!
- Um...
No, I can't. Everyone's watching!
[Chushaku] Katai is thinking,
"Are they saying something bad about me?"
Um...
Katai, here.
You don't have
to give me something in return.
- [Makoto grunting]
- [boys gasping] What?
[Makoto] Huh.
She gave you chocolates.
What's with the cold reception?
[Makoto] Huh?
What's in this package? This is scary.
[Mikuni] He's so cool.
[Makoto] My mentor's
giving me chocolates? Why?
[Komi shuddering]
[Makoto] What's the meaning
behind these chocolates?
- [narrator] Tadano didn't get any.
- [Makoto gasping] I see!
Instead of waiting, we should make
the first move and approach them!
Is that what you're saying, Mentor?
[Komi] You can do it!
[narrator] Tadano still hasn't received
any chocolate from Komi.
[Hitohito] Hmm?
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, Komi.
Are you passing out chocolates
to all of your friends?
[Komi grunting]
Oh, yeah. Ha. I see.
[Hitohito chuckling nervously]
[both groaning]
AFTER SCHOOL
[dramatic music playing]
[Hitohito] Hmm?
[grunting] It's... it's rival chocolate.
[Hitohito gasping]
Thank you, Katai.
Oh, but I didn't bring anything
for you today.
I'll bring you something
on White Day, all right?
[Makoto] Huh? That makes it look like
I gave him the true love chocolate.
[narrator] Komi wasn't able
to give her chocolates to Tadano.
[Hitohito sighing heavily]
[Hitohito] A pebble in my shoe.
[indistinct chatter]
[narrator]
Tadano was overconfident that day.
Well, I don't think
I'll get any true love chocolates,
but I'm sure I'll at least get a few
friendship chocolates
from some of the girls. [chuckling]
[narrator] Tadano is usually careful
not to get too full of himself,
but this can happen,
even to guys like him.
It's Valentine magic.
However, in reality...
[suspenseful music playing]
[narrator] Zero.
He received zero chocolates.
Chocolates from guys don't count
in today's total.
Sorry Katai, but that's just how it is.
Tadano didn't get any chocolates
from any of the girls he's friends with.
Not from Komi, Onemine, nor Otori.
- He's not popular. Tadano isn't popular.
- [Hitohito breathing heavily]
Oh, welcome home.
So did you get any chocolates?
Hitohito!
[narrator] Zero chocolates.
The stress was so severe
that it made him collapse in a heap.
[Hitomi] Is that the type
of character you are?
[Mom] Hito-chan, what are you doing?
Oh. Here's chocolate for you.
[narrator] Receiving chocolate from your
mother doesn't count either, of course.
And Tadano's mother used "chan"
when she called Tadano's name.
[music stops]
- [Hitomi] Hey, cheer up. Come on.
- [Hitohito moaning]
[Hitomi] Mom and I
both gave you some chocolates.
And you got some chocolate
from your friend too, right?
[Hitomi chuckling] From... from a guy?
[Hitomi snickering]
He said that he only got chocolates
from a guy friend.
[Mom] Wow. I don't really understand,
but he must be a nice kid.
[Hitomi gasping]
Hitohito, go and buy some ice cream.
Huh?
I don't want ice cream.
Besides, it's cold.
You really want it now?
Just do it. These days everyone's starting
to have ice cream in the winter instead.
It's warm indoors,
so people feel like having some ice cream.
Ice cream sales numbers
are growing every year.
[Hitohito] What are you talking about?
I'm going anyway.
[Hitohito sighing]
It's s... so cold. [groaning]
- [Komi gasping]
- [Hitohito] Uh...
Huh?
[Komi grunting]
Komi? What...
[Mom] Oh, can you buy
some dashi on the way?
Dashi? Yeah, sure. I... I got it.
Let's go to the park.
[Komi gasping]
Oh, sorry I bumped into you earlier.
Are you okay?
[Komi grunting]
Oh, good,
because I'd hate to have hurt you.
So, uh... what, uh...
what happened, uh, at school?
I mean, today.
[Komi gasping]
[Hitohito] Chocolate.
She brought chocolate.
Hmm? Uh...
"Student Council meeting minutes."
Uh, why did you come over to give me this?
"We had a student council meeting today,
and Najimi told me to give these to you
since you weren't there."
[Najimi] Why weren't you there, Tadano?
[Hitohito] Uh, sorry.
Thanks for bringing this over.
- BYE THEN.
- BOW
[Hitohito] Are you going home now?
Take care!
[dramatic music playing]
[Komi sighing]
[Hitohito] Why am I getting my hopes up?
I mean,
it's normal not to receive anything.
[Komi grunting]
Whether or not to give out chocolate
is Komi's decision.
Yeah. I just got my hopes up too much.
What am I doing?
But...
I hope Komi doesn't hate me.
[Komi gasping]
[dramatic music swelling]
Uh, Tadano!
[Hitohito] Hmm? [gasping]
[Komi panting]
Uh, yes?
[Hitohito panting]
Yes?
Um...
- [latch clicking]
- [Komi grunting]
Here. [grunting]
[Hitohito gasping]
For you.
It's friendship chocolate.
Oh, why of course it is!
Sure, that's what these are, right?
I never thought anything otherwise.
[chuckling nervously]
FOR TADANO
Uh...
Uh, well, um,
this is a little embarrassing to admit,
but I was kinda expecting
to get some chocolates today.
It looked like you were giving out
chocolate to everyone today too.
Uh, but I... I...
I... I... I didn't get any.
So I, um...
I kinda gave up on the idea.
- [Komi grunting]
- [Hitohito] Uh, what am I trying to say?
Anyway, I'm just so happy
to get these chocolates from you.
Thank you.
This means a lot.
[Komi gasping]
FLAP FLAP
[Komi grunting]
[Komi] Those chocolates I gave you
are the ones
that turned out the best.
Oh, wow! Thank you so much, Komi.
You shouldn't have.
[Komi gasping]
POOF
DASH
[Hitohito] Komi?
Huh? W... where are you going
all of a sudden?
Komi, it's dark already!
Uh, I'll walk you home!
Komi!
[ending theme music playing]
[music fades]