[Hawkeye gasps]
[Hawkeye sighs]
[Selim] No matter
where you are...
I will be watching you...
from the shadows.
[phone rings]
[Hawkeye] Hello?
[Mustang] Hello there, Madam.
This is your
neighborhood florist.
Ah... What are you
talking about, Colonel?
[Mustang] Uh. Sorry.
I kinda got drunk
and somehow bought a
car-full of flowers.
[Mustang]
You wanna do me a favor
and take some off my hands?
[Hawkeye sighs]
[Mustang] What's wrong?
[Hawkeye gasps]
[Mustang] Did something happen?
[Hawkeye] No, sir...
It's nothing.
Are you sure?
Yes, sir... Everything's fine.
[Hawkeye] And sorry
to let you down...
but I don't even
own a flower vase...
Thanks for thinking
of me, though...
Have a good night... Okay, bye.
[dog whines]
It's amazing how
uncanny his timing is.
[Miles] We got a
report on someone
matching Scar's description.
We believe he was headed here.
[Kimblee]
An abandoned mining town?
[Miles] That's right...
Baschool's pretty much
a ghost town since the
mines were closed...
Plenty of buildings to hide in.
This could be tricky.
We'll need to split
into search parties.
All squads are to contact
us here immediately
if you spot Scar.
[Squad Captains] Yes, sir!
[Heinkel] We've got orders to
keep the two of you company.
Yeah, yeah.
[Al] You think they're
Kimblee's men?
No doubt about it.
[Ed] Now let's see...
[Al] What's it gonna take
to ditch these guys?
[Ed and Al] Aah! There was
someone right over there!
There was?
[Al] He went this way!
[Soldier 1] Hey, hold on!
[Heinkel grunts]
[Heinkel] Wait for us!
[Darius] What the...?
[Heinkel] Where are they?!
[Darius] They turned
down this hall.
[Heinkel] Dammit...
They're trying to lose us.
[Ed] And that's that.
I'm pretty sure... we lost them.
But you know what?
This place is...
...too damn biiiiiiggg!
[Al] It's gonna
take weeks to search
every one of these buildings.
It would make things
a hell of a lot easier
if Scar and that girl
just came to us.
[May] Alphonse!
[Ed and Al gasp]
[Al] It can't be...
[Ed] No way...
[May] I can't
believe it's yooouuu!
She did come to us.
What in the world are
you doing here, Alphonse?
[Al] May! I didn't think
we'd ever find you!
Ah... You came
this whole way...
just so you could find me?
[Al] Yeah... I really
needed to see you.
Ahhhhhh!
My sweet Alphonse...
[Al] I need you to
tell me all you can
about alkahestry. Can you--
[May] He followed me
for hundreds of miles!
- [May] He said he needs me!
- [Ed] Al's not the only one!
[Ed] I need to see
you too, little girl!
Tell us everything you know!
You're not leaving until
we've got what we want!
Oh, no! Both brothers have
fallen desperately
in love with me!
I'm sorry, Edward, but
you're just not my type!
Don't play games with us!
[knocking on armor]
[Winry] Let me out, Al!
[Al] Oh! Sorry, sorry!
Ah...!
Mmmh... I kept
bumping my head.
Excuse me?! Who is
this woman, Al?!
[May] How could
you do this to me?!
Am I not enough
for you, Alphonse?
[Al] No! It's not like that,
she's just a friend!
Wait... why am
I explaining this
like I was cheating
on her or something?
[Marcoh] Hey, May!
You shouldn't
go running off like that--
Ah! The Elric
brothers are here?!
[Al] Huh?
Who's that?
Right, my face. I'm Dr. Marcoh.
[Al] What? Dr. Marcoh?
But you look... What happened?
[Marcoh] Why don't you tell me
what you're doing here first?
[Yoki] Huh?
Ahhh! The Elric
brothers are here?!
- [Al] Huh?
- [Ed] And who are you?
Don't act like
you don't know me!
How could you
have forgotten Yoki,
the great proprietor
of Youswell?!
[Ed] Rather easily.
Are you sure
we've actually met?
[Yoki] Ahh!
How cruel! And after
you destroyed my life?!
Huh?
[Yoki] The glorious
mining town of Youswell.
I brought prosperity
to the town as both
governor and foreman
of the coal mine.
The people loved me...
For I was more devoted
to their happiness
than anything.
[Yoki] But alas... we
were cursed by the arrival
of the greatest
criminal of all time...
The State Alchemist,
Edward Elric!
[Yoki] Little did I know it
was an ingenious deception!
[Yoki] These heartless
creatures of avarice
schemed to overthrow me!
[Yoki] And thus... The
mine was stolen from me.
Even worse, I was banished by
the ungrateful townspeople.
The military even fell
for their wretched lies!
[Yoki] I set out to renew my
life in every trade imaginable.
But I failed at each one.
[Yoki] I then tried
to invest my savings.
[Yoki] Only to yet
again be swindled.
[Yoki] Left with no other
options, I called upon
a wealthy family to
request a charitable loan.
[Yoki]
Ahhahah! Ahhah!
Uahh?!
Ah-- Ahh...?
[Yoki laughs bashfully]
[Catherine screams]
[Yoki] Aaaoooww!
[Yoki] None of it
would've happened...
if it weren't for
the Elric brothers.
And that's when...
I swore to myself...
nothing... nothing would stop
me from taking my revenge
upon the ones who
had done this to me!
And it will be a vengeance...
far worse than death!
[May] It's not right!
I'll never let
a thieving hussy like
you take him from me!
Did you, uh... just
call me a hussy?
[Al] I already told you!
She's just a childhood friend!
[Ed] You should think about
something else,
like alkahestry.
You better listen to me, dammit!
Yeahhh, how sad...
Life is hard...
Trust me... I know
just how you feel.
Are you patronizing me?!
So you're telling me
that you lost the girl?
[Kimblee] You're not the most
competent soldier, are you?
[Liam] I'm sorry, sir.
I'll lead a search team.
I need two men
from Charlie Squad.
[Liam] Yes, sir.
[Kimblee] Don't
forget, Major...
I know Scar is our
main objective...
You'll be the first to
know if we locate him.
[Scar] Nothing here, either...
Nothing edible, that is.
You must be Scar.
We'll need you
to come with us...
Mr. Kimblee is waiting for you.
[Scar] I'm impressed with
your tracking skills...
But do you honestly
think that the two of you
are gonna be enough to
take me against my will?
We'll see... But we do
have a slight advantage.
[Gerso] Grrrraaahh!
[Zampano] Rrraahhh!
[Scar] Hmm.
Let's just see
how this plays out.
Chimeras, huh? Let's go.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
I've learned a lot since we met.
Like what it takes to
create a Philosopher's Stone.
I know there's something
wrong with this country...
And there's something
rotten with its alchemy...
We've decided to look
into the possibilities
of Xingese alkahestry and we
figured that she could help.
[Marcoh]
You're on the right path.
But you aren't the
first person to put
all of these pieces together...
This book is a collection
of his research and theories.
[Ed and Al gasp]
It's written in code,
but we believe this book
contains all of the
answers that we need.
If we can decipher what's
in there, then Al and I can...
Perhaps... I believe so...
But they'll be impossible
to translate without
the assistance of Scar.
What do we need him for?!
[several gasps]
What do you think that was?
[Marcoh] That's the
building Scar was in!
You think it's the military?
Look, all of you
just need to stay put
and hide out in here...
Al and I will find
out what's going on.
So Scar's here...
[Gerso] Mm, mm... Aaahh!
[Scar] Hyaah!
[Scar] He's fast for his size.
[Zampano grunts]
[Gerso] Blaaaahhh!
[Zampano] Tired yet?
Y'see, we know
you've gotta touch us
to use your alchemy.
So we'll just keep a nice
comfortable distance
while we attack you.
[Scar grunts]
[Gerso] Blaaaahhh!
[Zampano] Rrraaahhhh!
[Scar] Gyaaahh!
[Scar grunts]
We studied your file
carefully enough to know
that you destroy the ground
when things start to look bad.
[Gerso] We're gonna
beat you to a pulp
before turning you over.
[Scar grunts]
[Ed] Well, look at this.
[Gerso and Zampano] Hm?
I guess we got here just
in the nick of time, huh?
Ah...? Didn't they
just run off somewhere?
[Al] His voice!
Brother... I think these
are Kimblee's goons...
the ones he
brought from Central.
They are? Yeah, I
think you're right.
We've already got
this under control...
You just sit tight while
we take care of Scar--
Rrrrahh!
[Ed and Al] Aaahh!
Talking monsters!
What's wrong with
the two of you?!
We're all on the same side!
[Al] I've never teamed up with
any freaky looking monsters!
Help us! They're pretending
to be our friends
so they can eat us!
[Al] The chubby one
has an enormous mouth!
He could eat you
in a single bite!
[Gerso] You obnoxious
brats... Settle down!
Blaaaaahhh!
Whoa!
[Gerso grunts]
[Ed] Hyaahh!
[Gerso] Whoa... this kid
is even faster than Scar!
[Ed chuckles]
[Al] Uh... Brother?
[Gerso] What are
you laughing at?!
Blaaaahhh!
[Ed laughs]
[Gerso] Rrrahhh!
Heh... Haha! It's so
light! It's incredible!
Amazing! It's like
they're not even there!
This cold weather
automail is magnificent!
[Gerso] You're gonna
regret messin' with me, kid.
Huh? So my punches
are lighter too?
[Gerso laughs]
Let's see how fast you
move covered in my spit!
Your special power is saliva?
Blaaaahhh!
[Ed] Well, if that's the case...
Huh?
Let's break it down...
And revert it to water!
It's f-freezing!
And now...
- [Al] Wahh!
- [Gerso] Uhh! Bwahh!
[Al] What do you think
you're doing, Brother?!
Don't move, don't move,
my skin is peeling!
I think from now on
I'm gonna call that one
the Wet Tongue on a
Freezing Flagpole Attack!
For the last time,
quit attacking us!
We're s'posed to be
on the same damn side!
You shut your snout, pig!
I've never seen you
before in my whole life!
And you must be the enemy
if I don't know you!
I bet you can't even prove
to me that you're on our side.
Fine, I'll transform
back to prove it to you.
Rrrrraaaaahhh...!
Thanks for the
opportunity, sucker!
Zampano!
Heh. It's kinda stupid to drop
your defense during combat.
Dammit! Let me go!
[Al] Alright, big guy.
Why don't you
take a little nap?
[Ed] He just had to
go and free himself...
Do you really think
you're gonna get away?
[Al] Give up, Scar...
It's time to pay
for what you've done.
I will kill you if
you try to stop me.
[Ed] Hmm...
[Ed charges]
[Scar] He's a heedless fool
to charge me without thinking.
You offer your arm to
me? Then I'll take it!
[Ed] I hate to tell you...
but my arm isn't steel anymore!
[Scar gasps]
[Ed] Hyah!
[Scar grunts]
Don't make this difficult!
[Ed and Al yell]
[Winry] Don't hurt them!
[Ed gasps]
[Scar gasps]
[Ed and Al charge]
[Scar] Ahhh!
[Scar grunts]
What are you doing
here, you idiot?!
[Miles] That's close enough.
[Ed] You brought
her here, Major?
What are these creatures?
[Miles] I'd guess they're
the result of some ungodly
experiment by our superiors.
Tie them both to that column.
Right away, sir.
And as for you, Scar.
I regret having to
treat one of my own
people so harshly,
but I can't just
let you walk away.
Not after what you've done.
Your own people, huh?
You two can leave...
We've got it from here.
[Ed and Al gasp]
[Al] Winry!
[Ed] Stop, Winry! Stay back!
Let me go... it's alright.
It couldn't be any less alright.
[Miles] Miss, you
need to stay back.
Just let me...
Please understand.
You have to let me talk
to him... I need to, Ed.
[Ed] Ah--!
[Winry] Why... Why did you
kill my mother and father?
[Scar] There's nothing
I can say that won't
sound like an excuse...
And nothing can change
the fact that I am
responsible for their deaths.
[Scar sighs]
[Soldier 1] What happened?
[Soldier 2] That's
where Major Miles was!
Hmm... This isn't good...
Looks like we've gone
over the twenty-four
hour timeframe.
[Buccaneer] And you
know our ice queen.
Patience and compassion
aren't really her strong suits.
We did the best we could...
We didn't know we'd have
to grope our way around
back in the dark...
Maybe if these guys hadn't
made us douse the lights
so their "monster" wouldn't
see us, we'da made it.
[knocking]
[Buccaneer sighs]
A-Ah...!
[Soldiers] Ahh...!
Welcome back, sir.
[Soldier 8] They made it back!
[Soldier 9] Take these
men to sick bay.
[Advance Party 1] I'm sorry.
[Soldier 9] There's
no reason to be.
I thought you were
ordered to seal up
this hole after
twenty-four hours.
Uh... Yes, sir...
But as you can see,
it hasn't been
twenty-four hours yet.
[Soldiers] Hmm?
[clock ticking]
[Soldier 3] It's a
nice watch, isn't it?
General Armstrong gave it to
me whenever you guys left.
Ahh...
[Buccaneer] General!
Did you find the Advance Party?
There were only two survivors.
Is that so...?
[Buccaneer] May I ask
what you're doing?
[Olivier] I'm looking
at the mountains.
[Olivier] I like the
winters up here.
Everything's black and white...
I appreciate the
pure simplicity of it.
That's not true, sir.
[Olivier] Hmm?
[Buccaneer] You can
see blue if you look up.
There's nothing that's
entirely black and white.
And thanks for showing your
soldiers a little mercy.
It means a lot, sir.
That's nice...
But I don't know
what you're talking about.
It appears we have guests.
Long time no see,
General Armstrong...
Sorry to drop in like this.
But it's somewhat urgent...
Central Command
has a few questions
that they would very much
like to have answered.
[Soldier 4] Fall back!
Everyone back!
Ah--!
[scattered cries]
[Ed coughs]
Damn it!
What's going on
in there, Fullmetal?
You bastard! This is
all your fault, Kimblee!
You were supposed
to be watching Winry!
Ah! Mr. Kimblee, look
up there! On the roof!
[Narrator]
Their encounter is as necessary
as it is inevitable,
despite the unavoidable
grief their meeting
is sure to bring.
Only the passage of emotions
can properly clear the way
for the true path
to follow to be found.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 39: "Daydream."
Has everything they know
of been set into place
by the hand of a
greater reality?