This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
Please enjoy your meal.
What's the matter?
Nothing. I just didn't think you literally meant tea.
Don't worry. It's my treat.
So Nakajou's theory didn't work?
Nor Haba's?
That's right.
How about Sawakiguchi's?
I'm afraid it was no good either.
I see.
My apologies.
No need for formalities.
But I would like to hear what was wrong with their theories.
Firstly, the problem with Nakajou's theory was...
Bored, sitting on the windowsill,
I frown at the wind to hide my awkwardness
Hyouka
I nod uncertainly as I shape
the future in my hands feeling mighty
I feel that the wind is bringing change
I guess that's your fault for calling out to my heart
The cloudy sky tells a tale of what's to come
Spread our wings with more courage than ever before
Light and dark are still vague in the distance
but still we want to know the reason behind kindness
No one so far has ever reached
the shining distance far beyond
Let's get there before the past takes it all
Tea Shop
1-2-3
And that's why Sawakiguchi's theory doesn't work either.
I see.
Out of Sight, Out of Mind
Who refuted Nakajou's theory?
I did.
As well as Haba's and Sawakiguchi's?
That's right.
When I asked you to solve this mystery, you told me not to have weird expectations.
And yet, you have refuted all their theories –
just as I secretly expected.
You expected this to happen?
They weren't cut out for the job.
It's been clear to me from the beginning that they lack the skills necessary to solve this mystery.
So this was all a charade? Then—
Of course, I'm not saying they are talentless. They all have valuable skills.
But those skills are of no use to them in solving this difficult—
Then why—
Without your assistance, we would need to accept one of their theories instead,
and the project would fail in the worst possible way.
You're cold and realistic. A bit too much so.
If required, I can be.
But I have one person on whom I can place my expectations.
I have heard of his skill from three persons.
One is Chitanda Eru. One is someone from outside the school.
The last is Tougaito Masashi.
This person would be our best choice to play the detective,
or so we thought.
It was you, not the Classics Club, who I've been after from the start.
Oreki,
I think you have already proven your abilities in this case.
You are...
extraordinary.
You are extraordinary.
I'd like to ask you once again.
Oreki, please lend class 2-F your aid,
and find the solution to our movie's mystery.
I don't have that kind of skill.
It was just luck.
How frustrating.
Very well. Please listen to my story.
Consider it just for fun.
In a certain sports club there was a substitute player.
She trained as hard as she could to become a full player, but she was never allowed to.
This was because the club had many other people with much more skill than she did.
There was even one player who could only be described as a genius.
Needless to say, the difference between her and the genius was like night and day.
The genius did so well in a competition that she was named MVP.
Winner
Then she was asked the following question in an interview:
"That was amazing. What's your secret?"
Her answer?
"I was just lucky."
I think that answer would have been very painful for the substitute player to hear.
What do you think?
People should take pride in their own abilities.
Otherwise, think about how those on the sidelines must feel.
Am I really...
extraordinary?
Could I have erred in my self-assessment?
Can I really believe in myself?
Irisu, I—
It's not like you to go to school on a holiday. What gives?
Something you've gotta do?
Can't I go to school without having something I need to do?
It's just unusual, that's all.
I received a direct order from Irisu.
I need to figure out Kaitou's murderer.
No way! You?
Oreki Houtarou is helpful and compassionate.
I couldn't quite catch that. Come again?
That's quite different from your usual creed.
Is this because of Chitanda again?
No.
Then why?
"I don't do anything I don't have to."
I thought that was your motto.
Satoshi...
Do you feel like there's anything that only you can do?
Nope.
Nothing?
Didn't I tell you I have no talents?
For instance, I look up to Sherlockians, but I can't become one myself.
I lack that vital spirit needed to delve into the unfathomable maze of knowledge.
If Mayaka took an interest in Holmes,
mark my words,
she'd outdo me in three months.
I just sample each genre long enough to say I've been there.
That's about the most I could do. I couldn't be an expert on anything.
But I get it.
Irisu got you into it.
I can see why you'd feel unsure about your own skills.
You never doubt yourself.
Oh well.
I'm gonna go on ahead.
Mayaka's probably at the school too, so I'll drop by to say hi.
Satoshi!
I don't know how you look at yourself, but I think more of you than that.
If you put your mind to it, you could become the greatest Sherlockian in Japan one day.
There are things more attractive than being a Sherlockian.
But still...
I'm envious.
Really.
Earth Sci. Prep. room
Oreki voluntarily coming in on a holiday? What is this madness?!
Is that a problem?
It's ominous! Like it's foreshadowing some natural disaster!
I felt like solving some mysteries.
You? Why?
Could it be because a certain person called Irisu coaxed you into it?
You're sharp, Mayaka.
Whatever.
By the way, how did it go yesterday?
You mean with Chi?
She made it home somehow,
but when I called her this morning, she was suffering from a hangover.
That's... quite a rarity.
Anyway, let's take another look at this movie.
Kaitou!
B-B-Blood!
H-Hey, is that...
Kaitou's arm was really well done.
It really does look like an arm.
The prop guys were the most talented part of the team, I guess.
Damn it! Who did this?
But...
I really can't imagine this being some kind of complicated twist.
Yeah. It's disguised to look simple.
No.
It wasn't intended to look simple.
Then what?
I think it's because the movie itself is so boring
that it makes the mystery seem uninteresting as well.
A number of volunteers from Class 2-F decided to take part in the Kan'ya fair.
They are currently on their way to the Narakubo area to gather material for their exhibition.
Yeah, it took me a while to realize it was a locked room mystery.
We're still not there?
Yamanishi      Midori
In that way, their performance is quite lacking.
We're close. Should only be about five more minutes.
What do you mean?
The camera work's pretty bad.
That's exactly what you said last time!
Yeah, that's it!
Then how would you do it, Ibara?
Me?
It's quite ti—
Let me see...
For example, here.
It's full of du—
Wouldn't it be better to frame this shot from further away, to show off more of the hall with the actors?
Yeah.
And...
here as well.
Hey, Sugimura! Had any luck up there?
This one's quite clean. We could use it.
I'll come back dow—
And here, if they took this shot from Sugimura's point of view,
it'd be much clearer that he was overseeing the lobby.
The viewers don't get that when the shot's taken from ground level.
Oh, and also...
Sorry, that's enough.
Why?
We could do this all day.
We'll get nowhere if we just complain about technical issues.
Yeah, yeah. It might still be worth considering, though.
Found you, Fukube!
What are you doing, messing around over here?!
Ah, hello, Yamaguchi! Welcome!
Hey, violence isn't the answer, you know?
I'm doing this for your sake!
Yeah, but I have my own priorities too!
What's wrong with you? You think Omichi was kidding around?!
Are you trying to get kept down a year?!
Satoshi, you should take your supplementary classes more seriously.
B-But Hongou's mystery is important too!
Houtarou, quickly, figure it out right now!
What are you talking about?!
But you know—
No! That secret! That locked room!
There he goes.
I don't know what's wrong with that guy.
Here he comes.
Please, Houtarou.
It's depressing when you realize that some things are just beyond our control.
Now that it's come to this,
Fukube!
this notebook will have to carry on in my place!
Come on already!
I get it, I'm going!
For the love of...
Time I got going too.
Oh?
What's with that look?
I can't help you right now, not even for Irisu's sake.
And why is that?
I've got library duty.
I'd have kept today open if I'd known this was going to happen.
It's your fault for springing it on us like that.
Though...
Sorry, Oreki.
All right.
Let's split up and check the building.
Damn it! Who did this?
B-B-Blood!
That won't be a problem. The keys should be here.
I see.
So this was Hongou's true intention.
Limit of Heat
As the Sun's strength falters,
summer's feverish heat breaks for the first time.
Hyouka
Come in.
My first question is: have you figured it out?
I see. Then please elaborate.
This mystery clearly hinges on the locked room.
That guy – I mean, Kaitou – died in a room
where no one could enter or leave.
Don't worry about the formalities.
The left wing was a locked room.
Damn it! Who did this?
The only connection to the outside was the window, and as you can see...
Left Wing
Waiting Room
Hall
Stage
Right wing
...the culprit had no choice but to use the door.
But how?
From the video we have no way of knowing if there was some kind of physical trick to the door,
so the most logical conclusion is that the culprit used the master key.
However, Sugimura was watching the lobby.
Office
Reception
1st Floor
Entrance Lobby
Toilet
Waiting
Room
For that reason, the culprit wouldn't even be able to use the right-hand corridor.
It is, in essence, the second "locked room".
Office
Reception
1st Floor
Entrance Lobby
Toilet
Waiting
Room
Not one of the six characters could have taken the master key from the office and entered the corridor.
What does that mean?
If the culprit wasn't one of those six, there's only one explanation.
There must have been a seventh person.
A seventh person? Like Sawakiguchi predicted?
Yes.
At first it sounded pretty ridiculous,
but if what she said is correct, Hongou was looking for a seventh actor.
Remembering that was what cemented this idea in my mind.
Hongou wrote this script according to the rules, though.
I don't think she'd have some kind of slasher pop up out of nowhere.
There were a few more things in the video that didn't add up.
Satoshi noted them here.
When Kounosu finds the floor plan, it's lit up. Probably from a flashlight.
And then, when they go to look for Kaitou...
The corridor is dim and poorly lit. They use a flashlight there, too.
A flashlight?
Yes. But none of the main actors carried one.
You can see this from the scenes right after it's used,
for instance when they first enter the crime scene.
They had time to hide the flashlight, but there'd be no logical reason for them to do so.
I know, you can say that it's just a matter of lighting.
But before that, please keep this in mind.
And this is something I'm saying as a movie enthusiast, so please don't be offended.
This movie is boring. The acting is bad.
The camera work in particular is extremely amateurish.
But if that was on purpose...
The cameraman was filming from the six actors' point of view.
I think you get it already.
Are you telling me...
The cameraman was the seventh actor?
There were seven of them from the very beginning.
The six actors who appeared on screen,
and the cameraman who filmed them.
Seven in total.
Look at this. The actors glance at the camera every now and then.
It's not safe to sleep here—
They are conscious of the camera's presence.
It's not right to call him the cameraman, so let's call him the seventh character.
It's not unusual to consider there'd be someone holding that flashlight.
The camera work is bad because he can't film the same scene from various points of view.
It makes sense to consider him an actor.
And here's the important part.
The camera stayed in the lobby until everyone else left, then the scene was cut.
Which meant that the camera was stopped and left waiting for the others to return to the lobby.
Therefore, the crime is simple.
The seventh character waited for everyone else to vanish into the theater,
stopped the camera, quickly took the master key from the office,
killed Kaitou, then locked the room using the key.
Then he waited in the lobby for the others to return.
That is my conclusion.
If Hongou has yet to choose a seventh actor, I'd suggest you do so quickly.
Two problems.
Firstly, if this character existed,
wouldn't it be strange that he never says a word, and none of the others speak to him?
Hongou might've considered that as the motive.
The seventh character is always ignored by the other six.
And that's why he never talked to them, either.
Secondly, the people in the theater would be able to figure this out instantly.
Surely anyone would suspect this seventh character who supposedly stayed in the lobby all along.
Not to mention that the second "locked room"
you mentioned is still a factor.
We can assume that the actors could see the seventh character moving around.
Therefore, the culprit would be obvious.
As Sawakiguchi would put it,
"Who cares about a witness or two?"
It makes no difference if the characters figure it out right away.
The important part is making the viewers wonder about the mystery, right?
Maybe that's why there's no detective role in the script itself.
It's because the culprit is clear to the characters,
without them even having to think about it.
Congratulations.
Looks like you've solved Hongou's mystery.
I was somewhat taken aback by your daring conclusion,
but as it fits all the facts, it must be right.
And... thank you.
Now we can finally complete the movie.
I was right after all.
You have talent.
A power possessed by no other.
Uh... Thank you.
Why don't you decide the title of the movie?
The title?
Anything you can think of.
We'd all be happy with any idea you have.
Huh...
Let's see... Something that fits the movie...
How about "Out of Sight, Out of Mind"?
That's a great title! Let's go with that!
Home run.
Everyone in third year...
With the culture fair in October...
There is a preview
screening of the movie
in the media room.
I'm going ahead.
Chitanda
I can't imagine how anyone could have entered that room.
No one could have.
Except for one person: you.
You did it?
It was you?
How could you?
Why? Just why?!
I didn't see that coming.
Yeah!
Hey, wait!
Trying to run away?!
Don't think you can escape!
That was really cool!
Damn, that was one hell of an ending!
Looks like it was a success.
Yeah, to think it was the cameraman!
Hey! I heard ya figured it out in the end.
Well, yeah...
Hell, that endin' sure threw me fer a loop!
Well done!
Hey, Mr. Ace Detective!
Ace detective?
Awesome job!
Though, it sure is a shame that the seventh character didn't like,
go nuts and massacre the rest of 'em when they found him out!
Yeah...
Anyway, much 'bliged!
Laters!
Sure...
By the way, Nakajou!
What?
Your armpits reek.
Eh?!
Pretty nice, huh?
Don't you shower?
Shut up!
I guess Haba wasn't a fan.
Houtarou!
We saw it too.
How was it?
Not bad.
It was interesting. Didn't expect it to be the cameraman.
Is this what you were thinking earlier?
I hadn't come up with it by that point.
Is that so?
Huh? They don't seem surprised at all.
That's Houtarou for you.
Yeah. Annoying as ever.
Well, I guess this is it.
Oreki!
Huh?
I...
Um...
I'll tell you later!
Anyway, well done, Houtarou!
The movie's finished and the Empress approves.
And the viewers seem to like the surprise ending as well.
Oreki.
I've got a question.
What?
Hey!
So you came up with that conclusion?
That's right.
The whole thing?
I guess.
Then what do you think of what Haba said?
Haba?
Um...
The rope didn't show up in the movie.
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
This sprouting warmth confuses us
Don't you understand this feeling yet?
Normally such random glances hold no meaning
Isn't it the same when making friends?
The little shooting stars we wish upon, vanishing into the dawn
are a magic that only unfolds in the night
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
Next time: Fools' Staff Roll.
Fools' Staff Roll