I am quite upset.
No matter how they increase the price of
high-grade vegetables aimed at the wealthy,
there is not a single complaint.
Huh?
However, the price of low-cost, staple foods for commoners such as bean sprouts has gone up as well.
What does that tell you?
Sprouts?
Sorry, but I can't think with that thing pointed at us.
Bean Sprouts
You...
are the one I was asking.
Wai—Ikaruga!
Contact with outsiders is forbidden.
But she's probably...
Yes, indeed.
I see you have no intent to pay me any heed.
Ninja Battle Sphere!
A battle sphere? I knew it!
Why are you after us?
To put it bluntly,
it's because you're the spoilt daughter of a pair of wealthy plutocrats.
What do you mean by that?
You were raised with the lavish affection of your mother and father, right?
All snug and comfortable.
Nice and warm and wanting for nothing.
Ikaruga!
Asuka, please keep back.
I can't!
It appears to be me she's after.
Ninja Morph!
We must fend off the sparks that fall our way!
Naught shall be tolerated!
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't truly smile
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Light does not coil around us like a spiral
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Go past the present and put the shadows in your crosshair
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
Lavenders in Full Bloom!
Ikaruga!
What power!
You cannot harm me with such a prim counterattack.
Rose Melody!
Prepare yourself!
Secret Ninja Art: Niflheim!
A ninja's battle outfit is brought into existence
through their will, ideals, and personality.
As such, it can be destroyed when its wearer sustains great physical or mental damage.
Ikaruga!
I didn't even have time to use my secret ninja art...
That's how strong you good guys are?
I guess that means you're one of the dark ninjas.
Answer me!
What do you aim to gain by assaulting us?
Your backtalk is making me quite irritated.
Well, I'm just here today to meet the two of you.
Go ahead and splurge a little.
Enjoy your short respite.
Ikaruga, are you all right?
It isn't anything serious.
All I could do... was stand there and watch.
Store
We sure went all-out for Master Hanzo's welcoming party.
The most important thing is that we kept within our budget, right?
I guess so.
All that's left is to put our all into cooking it.
So, how did that person know that your family was wealthy, Ikaruga?
You can find out anything if you're a ninja.
That's true.
It doesn't help that your family owns a really well-known business, huh?
We should hurry.
W-Wait!
My most sincere apologies!
I disobeyed your order and made contact with an outsider.
Do with me what you will.
They started it.
Don't worry about it.
No, to violate an order is a ninja's greatest shame.
You're as stiff as always.
Master Kiriya, how can you be so soft and still expect discipline?
Come, Master!
I need you to punish me!
I understand what you're saying.
Master Hanzo!
Kiriya, what Ikaruga says is right.
She has a fine sense of duty as a ninja.
Master Hanzo, I still don't think...
Very well, then I shall punish her in your place.
Master Hanzo, you'll punish me?
Punish her?
Oh, yes, do it harder!
As you wish!
Moonlight Intruder
May the presiders over
warriors be my vanguard
You're so good at this, Ikaruga!
Master Hanzo!
You're so stiff!
These bones are getting old.
Ah, right there!
That's the punishment that Master Hanzo gave you?
Geez!
What are you making Ikaruga do to you, Grandpa?
This is what Ikaruga wanted to do.
Ah, right there!
Ikaruga, let me take over.
No, thank you.
Actually, I did this all the time back home.
Watching you do it makes me want to do it too.
Is that right?
Oh. Well then, if you please.
I feel like I'm home again.
Your touch is as brutal and uncomfortable as ever.
No complaining!
Your dear granddaughter is massaging you.
Ow!
Even the legendary ninja, Master Hanzo, is powerless before his granddaughter, huh?
Those two are family, all right.
Huh? Isn't that obvious?
Sorry I'm late.
So, what happened?
I got a call a moment ago from the Ikaruga family.
The Ikaruga family?
What was your attacker like?
Let's see...
She was all frilly.
What does that mean?
Was she strong?
I couldn't do anything at all.
If Ikaruga hadn't been there...
Ikaruga, I'm so sorry I was so useless.
No, you were only following my orders.
So that's it!
Ikaruga, you sent her packing, huh?
Damn it!
I wish I had been there too!
All I did was simply refuse to face her.
A ninja must only fight for a just cause.
Man, if I were in your place, I'd have gotten her good.
Just like this!
What are you doing?!
Wait a—!
That's not true.
I was actually powerless to stop her.
Absolutely useless...
Ikaruga...
Yes?
May I have a moment?
Of course.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing.
Hoho!
You two sure are good friends, huh?
That's right. Huh, Yagyu?
I'm just keeping Hibari safe, because she can't seem to stay out of trouble.
Gosh, you're treating me like a kid again!
A good friendship is a beautiful thing.
And a good friendship means you two take baths together, right?
Yep!
We take turns soaping each other up!
How positively delicious!
Let me have a turn one day, 'kay?
Grandpa!
Watch what you say to those two!
It's not like that, Asuka!
We're just having a friendly chat.
I knew Master Hanzo would understand!
My brother has gone missing?
Your family called to ask if you had any idea where he might be.
Do you know anything?
To be completely honest, we don't really talk that much.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
I thought I'd at least let you know, just in case.
He is your family after all.
My family...
Yes, of course.
What's the matter, Ikaruga?
sweet
sake
I thought someone was watching me.
What?!
There's nobody there.
I must have imagined it.
Are you all right, Ikaruga?
Pay it no mind.
Now, we've got half an hour until the party starts.
Right!
sweet
sake
Aw, we're not going until morning?
Am I feeling nervous because of what I heard from Mr. Kiriya and that dark ninja?
I'm not usually like this...
As of today, she will be your younger sister.
Play nice.
P-Pleased to meet you.
You're the one, huh?
Dad bought you, right?
Watch your mouth, Murasame!
She's a distant relative.
Yeah, whatever.
It doesn't change the fact that you've given up all hope for me, Dad.
That's enough, already!
U-Um...
Pay him no mind.
Even among our own flesh and blood,
there are times when you have to be especially resolute.
Such is the law of the ninja.
What's this?
Hien. The sword that has been passed down through our family.
As my daughter, the sword now belongs to you.
Thank you, Father!
Ikaruga was adopted into this family to replace their son,
Murasame, who turned out to be useless as a ninja.
Brother,
why did you run away from home?
Who's there?!
Hey, now, watch what you're doing.
Brother!
Long time no see.
Sweet Sake
Senran Kagura
Brother,
what are you doing here?
Stop calling me that.
I don't have a sister.
What are you doing with Hien?
What kind of question is that?
By all rights, this belongs to me.
It's none of your business what I'm doing.
You are wrong.
I received Hien from Father—
Father, you say?
You've got some nerve.
You think you're a part of my family?
Sure, I may not be able to use this very well,
but this treasured sword has been passed down through my family!
It should never lie in the hands of an outsider!
Hien is my...
is actually my...
This is your fault.
This is all your fault!
I really do feel sorry about this.
What?
If you hate me,
then I will apologize as much as it takes.
Just how big a fool do you think I am?
I just want you to return Hien to me.
Then come and take it!
Damn!
When I was in grade school, I took 6th place in the city chain-sickle tournament!
How do you like that?!
Can't move, can you?!
I'm begging you. Please stop this.
You!
You dare toy with me?!
Watch your step.
I will never acknowledge you!
Never!
Goddamn it...
One day, I'll get my hands on that woman and...
Who are you?
I've been watching you since you stepped foot into this school.
You should go home and stick to doing business.
How do you know that?
Stay out of this! I'm—
I'll let you go if you leave now.
Your old man told me you aren't cut out to be a ninja.
He also said you have what it takes to be a businessman.
He did?
You don't need to be a ninja to live life.
Everyone has their own path they must travel.
Wh-Who are you?
It's better for you if you don't know.
Just think of me as an old man who happened to be passing by.
Asuka, if you think you can improve your technique with vigor alone,
you're greatly mistaken!
R-Right!
Hibari, with moves like that, even a child could take you down.
Right!
Show that umbrella who's boss!
R-Right...
She's riding you hard.
What's the matter?
What do you mean?
You're acting a little strange today.
Something get your panties in a bunch?
Not in the least.
There is no telling when the dark ninjas will attack.
We need to get much stronger.
Maybe so,
but I'm telling you, all that yelling at everyone isn't doing us any good!
Katsuragi, it's easy for you to say that when you didn't even fight her.
Gosh, I forgot we had a badass here who did!
I'm just saying that you should take this more seriously!
What'd you say?!
Oh, Yagyu, what do we do?
Both of you, calm down.
Quiet, freshie!
Hey, everyone!
Let's grab a bite!
Grandpa made us some snacks again today!
Her natural cheerfulness brought us all back together.
Perhaps someone like Asuka should be the class leader.
You just have a lot on your plate right now.
Master Hanzo, I didn't notice you there!
Yes, she's my granddaughter, but it still bothers me how positively useless she is.
You're the only one that can lead this ragtag team, Ikaruga.
Oh, no.
Not in the state I'm in now.
I should get going.
Keep an eye on Asuka for me.
Okay.
You guys are all Asuka has for family right now.
Family?
You all laugh together, and get angry at each other.
When needed, you help and trust each other, with your entire body and soul.
What else could you be?
Indeed, this ninja class is one big family as a whole.
For me as well.
In that case,
there isn't a single thing to be worried about.
Ah, Grandpa!
What do you think of my sushi rolls?
Fantastic!
Delicious!
I love you and your sushi rolls, Master Hanzo!
Master Hanzo...
Use of training grounds
reserved for
Hanzo Academy Ninja School
You want to carry on secret ninja art training?
Huh?
Do I have your permission?
No, it wouldn't be right.
Very well.
The waterfall basin in there will do.
Hold on! Ikaruga!
W-Why are we doing cold-water ablutions?
First of all,
you must become one with the sensations of the creature you are summoning.
For frogs, that would be water.
R-Right!
Do you feel like a frog yet?
Y-Yes, sort of.
Next step!
Asuka...
You think she's okay?
She has a long way to go.
Grateful
Heart
I can't do it!
I can't even touch them, let alone get friendly with them.
You're only afraid because you think you are.
I'm sorry, Ikaruga.
You're even wasting your time trying to help me.
Of course I am.
We're family, after all.
Family?
Just keep at it, okay?
R-Right!
A little farther...
Aah! Ikaruga!
You can't even brush it away?
Well, I'd feel bad for the frog if I did that!
You'd what?
It'd just feel too mean to slap the poor thing away.
I'm going to pop over and see how the others are doing.
Huh? Oh, no! You're going to leave me alone with the frog?!
Good luck!
I'm not afraid... Not at all.
No! I really am afrai—!
Look out!
The frog!
Ikaruga, please don't scare me like that!
Looks like you can finally touch it on your own, huh?
Huh? I thought the frog was going to die, so...
Are you still afraid of it?
No. Huh? That's strange.
Why is that?
And for that matter...
it's kind of... cute.
Huh? Huh?
I should have realized it sooner.
That's the kind of person you are, after all.
Huh?
Here I go!
Secret Ninja Art:
Twin Sword Slice!
I did it!
Awesome!
Wow!
That sure was something.
You did it, Asuka!
Nicely done.
Grandpa! I did it!
Mm-hmm! Well done!
How did she conquer her fear of frogs?
Asuka is someone who is naturally nice to everyone.
Because she was so firmly convinced that she was afraid,
she had a mental block that prevented her from thinking otherwise.
Once she was able to voluntarily touch them,
that block was gone in a flash.
I see.
You really are someone she can turn to, Ikaruga.
You've even put me to shame.
I was only doing my job as the class chairman.
Master Hanzo...
Thank you very much.
What are you talking about?
I should be thanking you.
Good heavens, my granddaughter is a lucky girl.
She has such cute little sisters, and a fine older sister, too.
O-Older sister?
Roger.
Looks like it's finally our turn, huh?
I decided on this path
and now I won't hesitate anymore
I have the passion to go forward
and courage to match it
The feelings I accepted
might all be the result of fate
And yet now I stand perplexed
With courage
With pride
And with beauty we will go forth
Let's go according to our dreams
Let's take it all on
They're my guiding light, honest as I am
Every day a kiss
Just like lovers
You looked forward to a real fight, right?
I decided I would believe
Now I try to make it real
Let's go according to our dreams
Next Episode Preview
Hibari, we're training at the beach!
Yay!
I wonder what kind of training we're doing.
I have to make sure not to forget my beach ball!
Let's give it our all, Asuka!
Let's give it our all, Hibari!
Huh?
Next time, "Seaside Training - Ninja Island."
Seaside Training - Ninja Island
Come get it like your life depended on it.