[heavy metal music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[humans cheering wildly]
[Poseidon whistling tunefully]
[squelching]
[exclaiming in shock]
[whistling continues]
[gasping]
Hm. Think you can
predict my every move do you?
You should know your place.
[narrator] Just when humanity
allowed themselves to believe
that they were on the verge of winning,
the gods responded...
- [trident whooshing]
- [blood splashing]
...by tearing apart
the hopes and dreams of mankind.
[Kojiro grunting]
[Heimdall] So fast! I hardly saw him move.
Poseidon's trident tastes blood again!
[narrator] Poseidon's counter to
Kojiro's Hiten Niten Ganryu was simple
and vicious.
Turn the battle into a test of strength.
Hmm.
[Kojiro] Senju Musou!
[straining] Not good!
Even when I can predict his attack,
I can't touch him.
[Poseidon] Medusa Alope Demeter!
MEDUSA ALOPE DEMETER
[Heimdall] Ladies and gentlegods,
there it is!
Strikes as relentless as the storm
that swallowed up the world
in the time of Noah!
The tide has truly turned.
The speed of Poseidon's attacks
is unbelievable.
I can only see their afterimages
forming a dome.
Yes.
And within that dome,
Poseidon's whipping up
a turbulent storm of trident strikes.
How delightful this is.
Truly.
[Kojiro screaming]
[whooshing]
[gulping]
[Kojiro] Come on. You're kidding me.
Just when I thought that I had
finally made it to the bottom.
Turns out there's deeper to go yet.
This isn't looking good.
Is this really it?
Well...
I'm used to losing anyway.
It's the same as ever.
- [old man] Kojiro.
- Huh?
[Kojiro] Master!
[boy] Kojiro!
[swordmasters repeating] Kojiro!
[Kojiro] No...
This is...
[swordmasters] Kojiro! Kojiro!
Kojiro! Kojiro! Kojiro!
You must fight on, Kojiro!
[Kagekatsu] You're not done yet, Sasaki!
Aah! I know you can win! Kojiro Sasaki!
- [swordmasters] Kojiro!
- Huh? What is all this commotion?
Our hearts and blades are one with yours!
Use it to strike him down!
Huh?
Ha.
Those damn fools...
They're right! It is the same as ever.
[growling]
My path to victory
always begins with defeat.
[narrator] Those who lived
by the sword knew one thing.
Kojiro Sasaki's true power
was about to emerge.
[Kojiro] Once...
[narrator] All of the pain
his body endured...
[Kojiro] Just one time.
[narrator] ...every drop of blood he shed...
[Kojiro] I...
[narrator] ...had only ever served...
[clanging]
...to make him stronger!
[Kojiro] I really want...
to claim my first victory!
[narrator] And so, it was at that moment,
that the blade tip of humanity
reached the bottom
of the deep ocean abyss.
[ringing]
[wind gusting]
His foe's tiniest movements,
the quivering of the air,
the trembling of the ground,
he could predict it all.
It was as if all of creation
was speaking to Kojiro,
telling him what the god's
next move would be.
Manju Musou!
What the...?
Kojiro's injured, but he's dodging
all of Poseidon's attacks with ease!
That human is...
How can he evade those attacks?
Poseidon should be too fast.
How many thousands... Tens of thousands...
Millions of moves ahead can he see?
I finally...
[panting]
made it this close to you, god.
[shrieking] Sasaki!
Do it!
[narrator] Since time immemorial,
humanity has staked their lives
upon those well-honed pieces of metal.
To you, the men who forged
the history of the blade...
[Kojiro] Thank you.
NITEN GANRYU OUGI
SOEN ZANKO BANJIN RYORAN
[whooshing]
[crunching]
[melodic string music playing]
[melodic music continues]
[inaudible]
Ugh...
[panting]
Y... You...
little fish.
[triumphant music playing]
[inaudible]
[blades whooshing]
[splashing]
[sighing contentedly] You know something?
I could really get used to
this winning thing.
[Heimdall] And with that, it seems
the winner of round three of Ragnarok,
the final battle between god and man,
has been decided!
Representing the humans, Kojiro Sasaki!
[humans cheering wildly]
POSEIDON VS. KOJIRO SASAKI
TIME: 13 MINUTES, 7 SECONDS
WINNING ATTACK:
SOEN ZANKO BANJIN RYORAN
WINNER: KOJIRO SASAKI
[narrator] Mankind had felled a god.
Confronted with
a reality that should not be...
THE GODS SIMPLY
...the gods responded only with silence.
[shimmering and cracking]
[Heimdall] Who could have predicted
an outcome like this?
Finally, deep into the third round,
humanity snatches victory
from the hands of the gods!
[humans cheering wildly]
We... We did it!
We were actually able to beat the gods!
[swordmasters chuckling]
- [Iori] Kojiro!
- [all] Kojiro!
[humans chanting] Kojiro! Kojiro!
[Kojiro sighing]
They're quite loud, aren't they?
It's the first time I've ever won.
At least give me a second
to enjoy the moment, will you?
[shouting] Kojiro!
[Brünnhilde] You see now, gods?
Open your eyes.
Witness what mankind is capable of!
- [Muninn] There's no way!
- [Huginn] Did humanity really defeat--
[screaming]
[whimpering]
[Loki] Are you kidding me?
For real?
This joke of theirs
just stopped being funny.
Hmm? So I gotta walk back?
Beats having to row a boat, I guess.
But I have to admit.
All that fighting made me so tired.
[gasping]
Kojiro, stay with me.
[groaning]
Please, tell me that you're all right.
I'm just fine. All thanks to you, my lady.
Sorry I had to put you through
all that nonsense there.
Hrist, I'm so glad that you're okay!
[growling]
Of course I'm okay, you noisy little brat!
[whimpering]
Huh, what'd I tell you, Göll?
I promised we'd get
our revenge on those bastards.
That's right! [giggling]
What a relief.
The battle didn't change Hrist one bit.
I'm so glad she's safe.
So now, humanity's shown the gods
they're worthy of survival, right?
- [Brünnhilde] No.
- Huh?
We still have six victories to claim.
I really hope that we're able to win this.
You intend to defeat the gods,
don't you, Brünnhilde?
["Air on the G-String" by JS Bach playing]
ZEUS' ROOM
[Zeus slurping and sighing]
HERMES (GREEK)
ARES (GREEK)
ZEUS (GREEK)
Now then, what's with
all those long faces around here?
- [Shiva grunting]
- Ah!
Oh my.
SHIVA (INDIA)
Don't you even dare
play dumb with me, old man.
Excuse me?
[Loki] Your big brother
Poseidon just got filleted.
But you look pretty chill.
LOKI (SCANDINAVIA)
Ah, then again,
since the last time I saw you,
it's like you aged a couple million years.
[Zeus sighing]
Well, the human was quite simply
a better fighter than old Poseidon.
[slurping]
[sighing]
That's all there is to it.
And besides, you were there watching
the matches yourselves, weren't you?
So I don't need to tell any of you
what these battles are all about.
[sighing]
We might as well just admit it,
these humans are actually
quite powerful indeed.
It seems that little Valkyrie girl
truly intends to see us gods
destroyed before her.
And that means,
it is our responsibility
to respond in kind.
That's exactly what I want to hear.
Then this next one's all mine!
I'm ready to knock those miserable
lowlifes down a few pegs!
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
You see, about that...
Hm? You're really gonna take
another fight away from me?
[bursting]
And I must once again...
apologize.
But surely you understand that a Greek god
must be the one
to take revenge for another.
[growling]
Hmm?
Hm. Not gonna give me
much of a choice, huh?
You Greeks do what you gotta do.
- [laughing]
- [vein bursting]
[Japanese pop ballad playing]
Oh man, the next battle's gonna
be starting any minute now.
Where the heck did that
big sister of mine go off to?
Ah! There you are, Brünnhilde--
Huh?
Why's she with Hermes?
[inaudible]
Hey Brünnhilde, what were you two
chit-chatting about just now?
Me and him? Nothing to be concerned about.
What do you mean?
W... Wait a second,
you can't just leave me behind like that!
The final battle between god and man,
Ragnarok round four!
[Heimdall] The gods have two wins!
And the humans have one.
However this plays out, it's sure to
set the tone for battles to come.
[crowd cheering]
[rumbling]
[man 1] Huh, none of the other battles
began like this.
- [crowd murmuring]
- [man 2] I've never seen anything like it.
[Heimdall] Now, before your eyes is
a replica of 19th century London, England.
[crowd gasping]
The fighter representing humanity has
requested that the fight take place here,
and the fighter for the gods
graciously accepted.
[gods chatting excitedly]
Today, you'll bear witness
to a historic first.
It's god versus man in
a knock-down, drag-out street fight!
[woman] Does the weird arena mean
that the gods are giving us
some sort of special advantage
or something?
[man 3] But why?
Those wimpy humans are embarrassing.
They'll lose even with the advantage.
[Heimdall] I can't even imagine
how this battle will unfold.
Now, representing humanity in round four,
is this man.
Friday, August 31st, 1888,
a monster emerged from a dense fog
of the city with his fangs sharp and bare.
Was murdering five prostitutes during
his reign of terror the ultimate goal?
No.
- Was it to destroy society?
- No.
This lone man
plunged the three million citizens
of London into the very depths of fear.
He's the vilest of the vile,
with a heart of pure darkness!
His moniker is that of the most infamous
killer in the history of mankind!
Jack the Ripper!
Jack the Ripper?
- [man 4] What, he's here?
- [man 5] No way!
[man 6] That's the real Jack?
[man 7] The greatest mystery in the
history of crime is right in front of us.
[man 8] No, this is insane!
Why'd they pick a serial killer
to represent humanity?
[chuckling] Well now.
So that's the choice you decided to make.
I'll give you credit for one thing,
she always fights dirty.
And now, the god who intends
to avenge his brethren's defeat.
This fighter needs no introduction.
But I'm gonna give him one anyway.
The valiant warrior who felled both
the Nemean Lion and Cerberus
with his bare hands.
He accomplished the 12 labors
imposed upon him
and ascended to become
half-human, half-god.
- [horses whinnying]
- The bringer of light to heaven and earth,
the messenger of justice,
the unrivaled hero...
Hercules!
[male god 1] Hercules! Yeah!
- [male god 2] You're the best!
- [female god 1] Yeah, Hercules!
- We're all waiting for you, Hercules.
- Don't let those bad guys win.
- [male god 3] You're our hero forever!
- [male god 4] You can do it, Big Herc!
[chains rattling]
[gate slamming]
[exciting music playing
[Heimdall] Good versus evil.
Evil versus good.
Has there ever been a battle that drew
those lines more clearly than this one?
And now, it begins!
[screaming] Is everybody ready?
[narrator] Seven million years
of human history
is about to come to an unforeseen end.
The apocalypse shall not occur
from the fallout of nuclear war,
extraterrestrial invasion,
nor catastrophic asteroid collision.
The extinction of mankind
shall be ushered forth
by the will of the gods.
The very beings
who created the human race,
and who have now chosen to destroy it.
Will humanity defeat the gods in Ragnarok,
the final battle between god and man?
Can they ensure their survival
for the next thousand years?
Their battle's really happening.
[Brünnhilde] No matter what it costs us,
we have to win.
For the survival of the human race.
[Heimdall] The final battle between
god and man, Ragnarok, round four.
For the gods, Hercules!
For the humans, Jack the Ripper!
-Fight!
- [crowd cheering]
AND RAGNAROK GOES ON