Aisaka?
Kitamura-kun...
Happy new year's.
Y-You too.
Takasu isn't with you?
Ryuji was hospitalized at the end of the year for influenza.
He hasn't left his bed since new year's.
That sounds really bad!
I should go see him...
Kitamura-kun...
Aisaka?
I ended up sleeping through winter break.
What kind of face should I make when I see her?
That time...
She really did turn me down.
No matter how you look at it.
T-Taiga!
Hey! Why'd you close it?
Show your face! Hey!
Taiga?
What's with you, shouting like that?
My noodles are going to get soggy.
Eating crap like that again...
I'll eat here. Otherwise, you'll start shouting again.
Itadakimasu.
I make your share of food every day.
Ever since New Year's, you haven't even come over once.
Can you please stop yelling at me just because Minorin dumped you and you're looking for someone to take it out on?
I'm not taking it out on you.
It just bugs me.
I'm not going to ask for sympathy.
But it wouldn't hurt to hang out like we used to.
It's for your and Minorin's sake.
What an idiot I was.
Even though I said I'd support you with Minorin, I kept hanging around you.
There's no way she wouldn't misunderstand.
Is that why she turned me down?
Yeah...
It could be she just doesn't like me...
No.
I think Minorin likes you.
But she thinks I need you.
Do you really think that she doesn't like you?
T-That's...
I thought she kind of liked me a little...
Sort of...
Don't run away.
I won't go to your place anymore.
I don't need any food.
You don't have to wake me up.
If I try hard by myself, and you keep thinking about Minorin...
I think Minorin will surely give a different answer.
So...
So!
Just do what you have to do!
Don't run away and find out Minorin's real feelings!
I got it.
But...
You'll at least try not to burn the place down, right?
Yeah!
I hereby declare that I'm not going to use the stove.
Take-out forever!
How long will that last?
Forever.
Bye.
Good night.
Don't run away...
I'm going to school.
Ryu-chan! You forgot this.
Even though Yacchan signed it and everything.
Signed?
That Okinawa thing.
That was a close one, I completely forgot.
Okinawa for a school trip?
Sounds fancy.
Yacchan wants to go too!
Now's not the time for this kind of stuff though.
Nothing, I'm off.
When I see Kushieda, the first thing is to greet her.
That's where everything starts.
Takasu-kun!
Here.
It looked really expensive, so I thought I better return it fast.
This...
The bear costume...
Yeah.
My bad.
I completely forgot to bring it.
Don't worry about it.
By the way...
This was left in one of the pockets.
It's okay.
I didn't need it that night.
Ocean! Sun! Okinawa!
Ham! Sweets! Okinawa!
It's Okinawa! Three days, four nights!
Hey, Taiga!
Happy new year!
Huh? You're by yourself?
That's rare. Where's Taka-chan?
Don't know.
Taiga! Taiga!
This, this, read this.
Chinkosu.
Did you hear that?
What good is it now?
Taiga!
Stay still!
Taka-chan, save me!
Taiga is-
Because you keep saying, "chinsukou, chinsukou!"
What'd you do?
But it was so...
Huh?
What's that?
This is...
Well, I don't need it anymore, I guess...
Then I'll take it!
What do you think? Does it look good on me?
Give it back!
W-What?
That's still Ryuji's!
Hurry up and give it back!
Hey...
You're all really energetic at the start of the semester.
Morning, everyone!
Hey!
Morning, Minorin!
I...
I'm going to go get some juice!
But class is going to start.
That idiot.
Why did you run away, you big idiot!?
I wish everything would just burn to the ground...
It was burned to the ground!
But, it won't be canceled.
So, well, it'll be okay, just as planned.
Sensei!
I don't understand what you're saying!
The hotel we were supposed to stay at in Okinawa burned down.
Our end-of-the-year trip will be a three-day and two-night ski trip.
Isn't that great?
What? Excuse me, that really sucks!
It's not like I burned down the hotel.
This is a most unwelcome nonsense!
Why is Ami-chan late today of all days?
She would have been able to do something!
Kawashima-san went to Hawaii for work.
She couldn't find a flight back so she's absent today.
But I'm sure she's been all around the southern islands.
So wouldn't a ski trip be better?
No way!
Oh, Takasu.
Going home now?
Kitamura.
Where's Aisaka?
She's not with you?
She said she had something to do.
If I try hard by myself...
And you keep thinking about Minorin...
She's trying hard by herself with instant food, but I...
Hey, Takasu...
Hey.
Hey, did you see that?
Wasn't that girl just now really pretty?
She's probably a model or something.
Kawashima.
Aren't you supposed to be working in Hawaii?
Why are you here?
Could you please get lost?
We haven't seen each other in a while and you're picking a fight?
I don't like you anymore.
Because you're an idiot.
She said you're an idiot.
Taiga!
What are you...
You're late!
By ten minutes!
You're just a Stupid Chihuahua, don't be so nitpicky.
Here. It's what you asked for.
This is it!
I didn't realize you've become good enough friends to exchange souvenirs.
It's not a souvenir!
I'm going to pay for it!
But this... I ended up not needing it.
Oh, well.
I can still use it.
You're taking it to Okinawa, right?
You haven't heard?
Our end-of-the-year trip will be a three-day and two-night ski trip.
They said that the hotel in Okinawa burned down.
You've got to be kidding!
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Nothing...
Ah, that's right.
Before we go on the trip, I have to tell you something.
Listen.
During the trip, absolutely do not hang around Ryuji.
He's the one hanging around and bothering me.
Ryuji was dumped by Minorin on Christmas Eve.
Really?
To be exact, it was before I confessed!
Before I could confess, she rejected me.
Someone really got hurt finally...
But...
Minorin really does like Ryuji.
But a lot of stuff happened and it's not going well.
Once we're in third year, we'll all be studying for entrance exams, and our class will get separated.
That's why the end-of-the-year trip is the last chance to find out Minorin's real feelings.
Got it, Stupid Chihuahua?
If you're really okay with that...
What a boring story.
I'm going home.
Me too.
It would've been better if you had been the only one to get really hurt.
What are you talking about?
An idiot like you wouldn't get it.
What the hell?
Hey! Why are you following me!?
I have something to do in this direction.
Hey...
I didn't think you'd do so much for Kushieda and me.
Anyway, thanks.
That is, I'm going to work hard during the trip.
Finding out her feelings might be pointless in the end, but...
Idiot.
You and Minorin both like each other.
It should go well.
Really.
Tell me...
What makes you so sure?
Want to hear it?
I have a reason for believing it.
That is, I believe in you.
I believe that you're worthy of Minorin's love.
Anyway, I'm going to go by the station.
There's a new lunch box store in front of the station.
O-Okay...
And what's with your attitude today?
Don't run away tomorrow!
Taiga...
Believes in me.
So if I say I can't move on...
You're kidding, right?
Morning!
Hello world!
Sorry about yesterday.
What are you talking about?
I didn't notice anything.
I'm going to go ahead.
Grab him!
Don't underestimate me!
Nice, Minorin!
Tai-
Whoever gets caught has to carry my bag!
What's with her?
Damn Taiga, damn Taiga, damn Taiga, damn Taiga...
Kushieda?
Oh, this is absolutely positively nothing.
Hand over one of the straps.
Oh, yeah, your hair looks a little shorter.
Oh, this?
I just trimmed the edges.
I wanted to make it really short.
What do you call it, boyish?
When I was in elementary school, most of the time it was really short.
I'd go with my little brother to the batting cages and hit balls one after another.
My nickname was Mr. Lady.
But I'm surprised you noticed.
I guess it's because I'm always looking.
Wow, a shocking confession.
Right?
That's right.
I've got to move forward.
If I remember correctly, your little brother is a baseball player?
He's in a great high school team that usually plays at Koshien.
You must be proud of him.
Actually, I'm jealous of him.
Ami-senpai!
Happy new year!
Morning, Minori-chan.
Have you seen Taiga?
No, but...
How do I put it?
It's kind of like aaaAaa.
AaaAaa?
Dunno.
What is it?
What could it be?
Alright.
These are the groups for the trip.
Wait a second!
Aren't the groups a little strange?
It's you, Ami, Kashii...
Aisaka, Kushieda...
Takasu, Noto, Haruta and myself.
Nine guys and girls.
Our class has more girls, so I think it's a good way of dividing people.
But then Maruo and Taiga...
I mean, that's...
What, if you don't like it, why don't you change groups?
Shut up, Noto!
What did you say?
I said shut up, so shut up!
Shut up??
What do you think, Takasu?
It's fine.
Takasu-kun, you too?
If you really don't like it, you alone can go to another group...
That's not what I mean!
Hey, hey, Great Teacher Kitamura is saying it too!
Shut it, Noto!
Hey, why do I have to listen to you?
We're going to make guides?
That's right.
Each group has to make one by next week and turn it in.
Why do we have to do something so dumb?
I think it'd be better if we all get together and do it, but where can we do it?
Want to come over to my house on Sunday?
Is it okay?
Yeah, my place is pretty big.
This place is amazing.
I wonder how much the rent is.
Takasu's place is next door, right?
Takasu-kun's also in a place like this?
My place is in the building next door.
Alright, let's start.
I borrowed some from previous years for reference.
The guides are inside.
As expected from the Great Teacher! Good job!
I'll get some tea.
I brought some madelines from home.
Aisaka!
I want to use my computer, but where do I plug it in?
It's behind the TV.
Oh, thanks.
You can talk normally to Kitamura now.
Well, yeah.
More importantly, go help Minori.
Kushieda...
I'll help too.
Hey, Golgo.
I'm not Golgo.
Then I'm Golgo.
Don't stand behind me.
I'm the one standing.
Then it's fine.
It's kind of weird to see cups and plates that you can use in Taiga's place.
I haven't come here in a year, so now I've messed it all up.
This is thanks to you.
I haven't done anything lately.
Taiga's doing everything by herself.
She can do it because you were there for her.
Hot, hot, hot.
You didn't come here for a whole year?
Because of that thing with her dad.
After that, I didn't want to just come in here like nothing had happened...
I didn't want to mess up again either.
I kind of wondered what it was like.
That is to say...
You are really something Takasu-kun!
You just walked in without worrying about messing up.
Kushieda...
Hey, they wouldn't notice if we just copy the whole thing, right?
We're going skiing, what's the point of copying the schedule from Okinawa?
Are you dumb?
What's wrong?
We can't show this to Yusaku.
Hey, Ami-chan!
What is it?
You shouldn't worry about it.
That just makes me want to know more.
Shocking, right?
Even if it's just a picture, after being dumped so magnificently...
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
Big Stupid Chihuahua!
What?
I made some tea.
Try to get along.
Actually, I'm kind of looking forward to the trip.
After all, this is the last time all of us in 2-C will do something together.
This class was really fun.
It's kind of sad.
It'd be nice if we could just stay like this.
Yeah, just like this, forever.
Kushieda and I...
Everyone...
Just like this?
She's separating it properly.
That's right.
Just like this won't do.
To find out Kushieda's real feelings during the trip...
Ni... Ni... Nigaori.
Ri.. Ri.. Ri... Richiumu denchi.
Chimame.
Meido-san no heso no goma.
Mandoragora no beni shoga.
Takasu, it's ga, ga.
Ganbaru!
At what?
They're supposed to be bitter things.
Well, useless effort is bitter in its own way.
You're right.
Next, it's ru, ru.
Ru, ru, ru, ru, ru...
To sukyatto suru nigami sawa shibuhiko!
That's right...
Who's that??
Work hard...
And tell her again my feelings from that night.
I'm going to redo my confession from Christmas Eve.
For Taiga too, who is supporting me.
I'm not any good, I'm just all talk.
I hate it.
I can't stand it.