"Outou Festival" "Seeking possible
plans for opening ceremony acts"
The Arts Festival... it's
already that season.
Exams are coming up, too.
Second trimester is always a pain
because there's so much stuff to do.
Isn't there anything else you feel
as the final Arts Festival of your
high school career looms before you?
Opening Ceremony? What is this about?
At the Outou Festival, each year, there
is a tradition to gather volunteers
and have them perform something
as the opening act.
I just thought of something good!
"To Be Decided"
Then, we've decided on
a fortune-telling house,
so before the next homeroom,
please think of what kind of
fortunes you will be telling.
"Tooth-brushing exercises - 7" "History of paulownia
armoires and how to make them - 1" "Haunted house - 6"
You did your best! I'm touched!
And so, I'm thinking about
doing a cheerleading dance.
Cheer?
At the Opening Ceremony
mentioned this morning!
It's the best performance
to liven up a festival!
I see... It'd sure be flashy,
and it sounds like fun.
Doesn't it? We are going to
dominate the talk of the festival!
We... huh?
You mean, we're already included in this?
When I asked the teacher,
I was told that I had to have the
plans down to a certain extent,
including who was going to participate...
How about it, Yutaka?
Me?!
Yu-chan might not be able
to make it, stamina-wise...
Maybe I'll try it.
If I'm not troubling anyone,
I'd like to try it.
Trouble? Of course you wouldn't be!
I welcome you!
Are you going to be all right?
I think it's going to be a big project,
so I might be slowing everyone down...
But this is something that I
want to challenge myself with.
See? Even Yutaka's going that far.
So what about the two of you?
If that's how it is.
Well, if everyone else is doing it...
I have made such wonderful friends!
I see... Fortunes, huh.
But can you tell fortunes at all?
No, not at all.
Like, how bad?
Hey, you came up with the idea...
Fortunes that you tell in an arts
festival can be really random.
By the way, what is your class doing, Sis?
Well, we're doing standard
fare, a haunted house.
I see.
That's so pedestrian.
We couldn't come up with any
other interesting ideas.
Something wrong?
No, I was just thinking how perfect that was.
What are you implying?!
Oh, a real-life demon has gotten angry!
I knew you would say that.
And so, Patty-chan said that she
wants to do a cheerleading routine.
I see!
And so, I thought I'd do
my best for a bit, too...
Wow!
Whoa! But why now?
I've been absent from school so much
that I've never really done
anything with everyone, right?
But lately, I've been feeling a bit better.
So I thought, what I've always been wanting,
and what Patty-chan is wanting right now,
are probably the same thing...
But I still think it would be rather tough.
And so, because we definitely
don't have enough people,
Patty-chan wanted to know if
you would participate too, Sis.
So that's how you're doing it...
Sis, you're good at athletic stuff,
and if people like you and
Minami-chan are with me,
I think I can try my best until the end.
If you're going to go that far, Yu-chan,
and if Patty is saying so too,
then you've got a point...
Yes, hello?
Good evening, Konata!
Oh, it's you, Patty.
I just heard about it, and
was wondering what to do.
Ding ding ding ding!
Time for the quiz!
There is a certain ticket
in my hand right now.
Now, what is this a ticket for?
No way!
Konata, you were really
into Gekisou, weren't you?
Don't you want to have a passionate
handshake with Haruhi?
Oh! A handshake party!
I want to go! I want to go! Aya in real life!
By the way, Konata, were
you saying something?
Yu-chan...
I guess we have to do our
best making memories!
Yeah!
And so, you two, the current
generation is about cheerleading.
What kind of reason is that?
Patty started talking about
doing a cheerleading routine
for the opening ceremony
of the Arts Festival.
I see. Yeah, she'd look good in that.
And it was decided that you two will
be dancing too, Tsukasa, Kagami.
Oh, are there any other people in
your class that can join in, Kagami?
Wait a minute there!
Don't take the ball and run
with it without telling us!
I don't think I can do anything like that...
Come on, you won't get a
chance like this ever again!
It's the opportunity of a lifetime!
We're all doing this amongst
friends, and it's a festival,
so it would be "the more the merrier," right?
It would...
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Tsukasa, you're easy to convince.
I'm against it. I have to make
preparations for our class, too.
Sob, sob...
I just thought that it would be nice
to make memories with everyone
in our final Arts Festival...
You're quick to talk about
"friendship" all of a sudden!
And it's so obvious you're acting!
Yu-chan is really gung-ho about this.
Really?
But is it all right?
I told her that she'd be
better off passing on it.
But she's really giving her
all about doing something
together with everyone else right now...
I-I see.
But they're having problems
with getting enough people.
And that was why they're asking us.
Yeah, I may have been a
bit too forceful about it.
I shouldn't force you into it,
so I'll try asking other people.
Fine...
Eh? What?
Fine! I'll do it!
Sis!
Oh, is it all right?
It can't be helped.
My class can find a replacement
for me in their act,
but you can't find one, right?
Kagami, you really are cute after all.
Ch-Cheerleading?
I'm not sure if I can pull that off well...
Well, right now, I'm feeling
a bit unsure myself...
...especially in volume.
"Well-endowed"
If you could be a part of it, I
think it will turn out really good.
Is that so?
All right. If I can be of any help...
Oh, thank you, well-end... er, Miyuki-san.
The exams are over,
so we're going to start seriously
preparing for the Arts Festival.
But make sure you don't loosen up too much!
Sheesh, really!
When there are a lot of events going on,
it'd be nice to ease up
on the number of exams.
S'up!
Hey, Konata, what's going
on with the cheerleading?
Come to think of it...
I heard "the plans went
through!" Before the exam,
but I haven't heard from her since.
You've gotta be kidding!
We're going to be in trouble
if we don't get practicing...
I mean, we might already be too late!
Let's go ask her.
Sorry. I haven't done the
choreography or anything yet.
You haven't made it? What
are we supposed to do?!
Well... it took time to find an
appropriate song and stuff...
I couldn't quite get something
like Hare-Hare going...
What was that?
In any case, if you were worried about it,
you could have tried consulting
the other people in the group.
You organized it, so take responsibility
for doing the schedule!
I don't understand difficult Japanese.
What are you talking about?!
You're totally fluent!
Anyway, at least figure out
some of the choreography!
We can fix the rough parts
on the fly as we practice!
If you don't get it, ask
someone you can chat with!
Miyuki and I will deal
with the basic schedules
and securing a location to practice!
So I'm counting on you!
Hey, Kagamin...
Huh?
You were so reluctant about this,
but you know, you seem to be the
most passionate about it now...
Shut up!
What are you going to do, Miyuki-san?
I'm going to use tarot cards.
Wow!
What about you, Tsukasa?
Ugh... Actually, I haven't decided yet.
Yuki-chan, is there something
that even I can do?
Let's see...
What about telling fortunes
based on the shape of something?
This shape will most likely show
that your romantic fortune is on the up!
Tsukasa, you just thought
up that one, didn't you?
What the heck?!
Hold on a second... We're going
to try that, starting today?
Is it no good?
It's not that it's bad...
But it will be very difficult.
Well, we're out of time.
We just have to drop the difficulty level
of the really hard parts
as we practice, right?
Like, how bad?
But a huge wave of awe will be
waiting when we overcome them!
We don't want to hear that from you!
We're out of masking tape.
Oh, well, I guess we'll go buy some.
Then can you get markers too?
And replacement blades for the cutter.
And cardboard boxes.
And an issue of Playboy.
And glue.
There was something weird in that list.
Or more like, if there are
that many things to buy,
quit fooling around and someone
hurry up and go buy them!
What were we calling the yakisoba?
It was "Spring's Fragrant Breath."
What was "Fallen Drop of Sun's Dew"?
That was an okonomiyaki pancake.
It's impossible to figure out the menu
just by hearing what they're called.
Japanese culture is interesting.
Though it can be overdone too...
Yoo-hoo!
What are you guys doing, Yu-chan?
Let's see...
Z... 'Zuka cafe?
"1-D Outou Festival exhibit"
"'Zuka cafe 'Class: Wind'"
How's that work?
It's a cafe where you enjoy
simple shows done 'Zuka style.
You can pick a girl in a glamorous dress
or a noble cross-dressed
girl as your waitress!
Cross-dressing...
That's right. Yu-chan and Minami-chan
will be our top servers!
An unfolding kaleidoscope of beauty...
When did we decide all this?
I'm worried about the cheering
too, but will this be okay?
Those two are amazing.
That was wonderful! Now, let's
try it again from the beginning.
Right. They're perfectly
in sync with each other.
By the way...
Is that Miyuki-san being sadistic?
Or is it Minami-chan being masochistic?
True... the dynamic dancing of Takara-senpai
may prove to put pressure on Minami-chan.
What the heck, right?
Knock it off, you two. Go practice.
Lucky Star!
The cheerleader costumes are done!
This is wonderful, but it
is slightly embarrassing.
That type of costume is the kind
that makes the audience happier.
After all, this outfit was chosen by someone
who's really happy to see
girls in these things!
Yeah, I've heard stories about him.
The formidable elder brother
of the Tamura family...
You can look forward to
the 'Zuka costumes, too!
That's right, Yutaka, you guys
are doing a cheerleading routine?
Yeah...
Is it all right if I record it?
If you don't go too far.
I'll be careful...
Though we haven't gotten
a single successful run,
so it's pretty much on the brink of failure.
I'll give you some of my sisterly
power, so you go do your best!
If I were to accept your power, Sis,
I think I'd get needlessly energetic,
only making me more tired in the end.
And so, we don't have much time
left, but we have so much to do!
The arts festival, huh... What
did we do when we had one?
We used to do something like what
you'd call a manga cafe nowadays.
The boys in our class would
all bring their own manga.
Oh, you guys were ahead of your time.
Nowadays it's normal to bring
stuff like that to school,
but back in our day it was rather strict.
It was only during festivals
that we could do such a thing.
No, there are people that bring them,
but it's not exactly allowed either.
Oh, so a fortune-telling house, huh...
Tell everyone to give me
good fortunes if I show up!
Th-That would defeat the
purpose of fortunes...
By the way, back in your day, Mother,
what were the arts festivals like?
Each class and each club
put on various things.
What everyone did were the typical things,
like haunted houses and okonomiyaki shops.
It's strange to think that things were
basically the same then as now...
Speaking of which, were there
any exhibits on cultural items,
such as paulownia armoires?
What's that about? Doing something
like that wouldn't be any fun at all.
Right... You're right...
Okay, let's take a break!
I think we can put on an
enthusiastic performance somehow.
It's not like it's perfect yet,
so let's stay focused and
keep going till the end.
At times like this, it's really
helpful for Hiiragi to be here,
because she keeps us going!
Well, I wouldn't like to be the only one
that doesn't have any memories with you guys.
"Grin, grin, grin, grin"
What is it?! Don't look this way!
"16th Outou Festival" "Now
is the time to glimmer..."
Oh, is that so? I'm
terribly sorry about that.
No problem.
Apparently today is a day just for students,
which doubles as a rehearsal for all of them.
And?
So, we ordinary folk can't
enter until tomorrow.
That's why I said to make sure
everything was okay before we came!
I mean, I heard that Akira-chan
was going to be here today!
Oh, that was a waste of the train fare!
If I had that money back, I'd
be able to buy hamburgers,
and have lived a slightly luxurious life!
Oh, this sense of incompletion
is really good!
Can it. Hey, are you actually
wandering around in that outfit?
It's better this way. I
mean, it's advertising.
Kona-chan's costume is really cute!
You have to start with appearance.
I'm going to tell a lot of fortunes today!
You will buy a soft-serve 5
minutes and 15 seconds from now,
drop it 5 minutes and 28 seconds from now,
That's not fortune-telling...
That's more like a prediction.
hit your head against a sign 7
minutes and 6 seconds from now...
And you're copying it word-for-word!
All of you are wonderful.
But we're not going to lose either!
It was just in the nick of
time, but they're finally done!
So cute!
They are very wonderful.
It's really embarrassing to
walk around in this outfit.
What an outfit...
Oh, no, but it's really cute.
Senpai, it's almost time for
Akira Kogami's stage performance.
Oh, that's right! I'll be right over!
Nice to meet you, ma'am. I'm Akira Kogami.
I hope to do my best today!
Oh, I'm Sakuraba. Yeah.
Today is something like a rehearsal,
so feel free to relax and just
check things out. Please.
Hey, Shiraishi! I'm leaving
it to you to do the rest!
Oh, sure.
I'm Shiraishi, chairman of the Arts
Festival Operations Committee.
Nice to meet you.
I'll basically be leaving
the rest to Shiraishi,
so if you have anything, tell him. Please.
Okay!
Hey, you, why don't you say anything?
You should be going to the monsters' meeting.
Huh?!
Is something wrong? Yeah.
No, nothing is wrong!
We got a little carried
away planning things out.
For now, Akira-sama, you are a valued guest,
so I will escort you accordingly.
And?
After this, we'll have you do a mike test
for Cape Thirties (Misoji
Misaki) In Lucky Channel.
Tomorrow, I'll have you do a
free-talking panel afterwards.
Well, I'll make sure to do it well.
Then, please head to the stage.
Damn that cheeky Shiraishi...
"Lucky Channel"
So cheap!
Morning luckies!
Everyone, thank you for
coming here just for me!
I hope you have lots of fun today!
When will I finally arrive in the arms
of the person I care for so much?
A solitary journey, wandering
and roaming about,
carrying with me the words from that day.
"The 16th Annual Outou Festival"
As far as you can go, searching
for his semblance in shadows.
Let's have her sing...
Miss Akira Kogami, with Cape
Thirties (Misoji Misaki).
♪ Alone... ♪
Okay, that's fine!
Damn you, let me sing properly!
I told you that it was a test, didn't I?!
We don't have any time!
Like I care! I'll kill you!
Oh, I don't understand
such difficult Japanese!
Are all of you ready? This
is the last run-through.
This was an idea that came
off the top of my head,
but now I'm really happy that
I was blessed with this chance,
to do something with all of you like this.
Let's not worry about success or failure,
and just get out there and have fun.
♪ The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait! ♪
♪ The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh ♪
♪ Gotta do your best, gotta just do it ♪
♪ That's time to catch 'n' release, eek ♪
♪ Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop) ♪
♪ Darlin', darlin', freeze! ♪
♪ Kinda lethargic, something's
kinda comin' out ♪
♪ I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different ♪
♪ Worrywarts, high metal bars ♪
♪ Tasty thoughts... And that's enough! ♪
♪ The heated body of that
flying you-know-who ♪
♪ It's what you call a normal girlie ♪
♪ Surprised? I'm the only
one who got seconds ♪
♪ On pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles ♪
♪ Da da da da da ♪
♪ Pom-poms cheer squad ♪
♪ Let's get cherry pie ♪
♪ Happy fun welcoming party ♪
♪ Look up! Sensation ♪
♪ Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet ♪
♪ Collided and it melted
away, in total awe ♪
♪ Go all out to sing, shi-ranger! ♪
♪ Take it away! ♪
♪ I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end ♪
♪ Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion ♪
♪ It's only Monday! ♪
♪ Already in a bad mood? What to do? ♪
♪ I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3 ♪
♪ Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★ ♪
♪ Do your best, be energetic ♪
♪ My darlin', darlin' please! ♪
All right!
Like, how bad?
What, you guys were still here?
We were practicing the cheerleading routine.
I see. And how is that going?
Oh, that's something to look forward to.
Ma'am, we're thirsty!
Huh?
What the heck.
I can at least treat girls
doing their best to a drink.
Yeah! We're so lucky!
Is that really all right?
Yeah, it's fine. A special
treat, today being what it is.
But, in return, for tomorrow's
festival opening,
get them all fired up!
Okay!
What's wrong, Tsukasa?
How should I say it...
It feels kind of strange.
You're right. Actually, I'm
feeling a little lonely myself.
They say that the most fun time of a festival
is when you're getting ready for it.
I see. Tomorrow is the real deal, isn't it?
That's right.
We won't have any more occasions
where we stay at school this late.
When you think of it that way,
it really gets a bit lonely.
Tamura-san, your face is all tense.
Somehow, my stomach hurts...
Tsukasa, you're tense all over.
You say that, but you don't look
as confident right now yourself.
Th-The more nervous I am,
the more focused I'll be.
Maybe I'm so nervous that
I can't move anymore...
Testing, testing.
And now, from this moment,
we're declaring the Outou
Festival to be open!
The first exhibit was planned by
our overseas studies student, Patricia-san.
It's a cheerleading squad made up
of a group of really good friends!
Let's hurry up and give them a big welcome!
♪ Min min miracle Minorun-run! ♪
Oh, excuse me, there's a cell phone...
Whoa, it's my phone! Oh, no... Whoaaaa!
There's trouble up to the very, very end...
I felt so much power draining from
me that I thought I'd fall over!
What timing!
Isn't it, like, really uncool?
They say trouble is always
part of the deal...
Well, you could say that this
is what you can expect from us.
This sense of non-closure is definitely that.
Oh, geez, I'm really sorry about that!
Somehow, I'm sorry!
Now, let's get back in gear,
and have them perform!
The song is Take it Away! Sailor
Suit (Motteke! Sailor Fuku)!
Lucky Star!
♪ Your whims have started
to move once again ♪
♪ It's so sad, this means it's the end ♪
♪ I'm sure you're having
dreams of that girl again ♪
♪ With a sigh, I say
so long to my dream ♪
♪ She's an angel, no, she's a devil ♪
♪ Ah, to you ♪
♪ She's the person that
sets a sweet trap ♪
♪ Your love is paradise ♪
♪ Repeated only to disappear ♪
♪ The "I love you" inside your lips ♪
♪ Maybe, maybe, love is perhaps, maybe ♪
♪ A boomerang that is thrown out ♪