This morning, I woke up to this scene,
having only arrived to Tokyo the other day.
When will I get through that thick skull of yours?
Hey...
You saw my name written on that, didn't you?
Come on, it's just a drink.
I gotta detox. Let's go halfsies.
No.
You kept saying you didn't need any
when we dropped by the store last night!
What'd you expect? I was drunk.
So did you hear back from them?
Not yet. Getting back a place that you've
moved out of once ain't that easy, I guess...
What about work?
They haven't called me back either.
I have somewhere I need to be today, you know.
The dark of night hides away behind an unfinished beat
We take a single breath of its embrace before we're crushed beneath
Although you try and fail and try and fail again
You can seize your chosen future by your own hand
Nothing's set in stone until you make it, so reach your hands out
Trapped in an endless crowd
Crying out with a voice that can't make a sound
And by the break of day
Sounds of footsteps will smother all you can say
Time's march will carry on
But the silent calls remain
The cold, filthy water flows
Through a city full of raw pain
In a world where nothing ever changes
We still have to live to see tomorrow
Though the scorn pervades your voice, we've got no other choice
No other path to tread
We've only got the future ahead
I promise you it's real, this stupid dream I feel
It's like there's no hope left living in this city, but still I try
Looking out and seeing there's a future for me
Reaching out and seizing hold of what I can be
Look around and see
I've been saying it all along
This stupid-sounding song
We're shining a light through streets of hopeless darkness
It's not a dream
Though this town is full of rot and decay
There's no point in giving in to dismay
Even now, there's time, there's time!
The dark of night hides away behind an unfinished beat
We take a single breath of its embrace before we're crushed beneath
Although you try and fail and try and fail again
You can seize your chosen future by your own hand
Nothing's set in stone until you make it, so reach your hands out
The Three Night Owls
This looks more like a hospital than a school.
It's a prep school, after all.
Are you gonna come here every day?
No way.
I don't have the money for that.
Admissions Form
I just have to study here for a bit
and then get into a decent university.
You wanna go to university, huh?
It's not like I'm adamant about going.
It's just that if I don't, it'll be hard
getting around as a high school dropout.
Well, you're right about that.
Hecklers will heckle.
Well, whatever.
I won't pry into the details.
You can just practice during your free time.
Huh?
You'll still be free on weeknights
and afternoons on the weekend, right?
Guess I should think about my work schedule, too.
Hold up.
Starting a band?
You said you would!
I did not!
You did! "Please flip 'em off with me!"
Do something about your finger-flipping habit!
Ow.
That didn't mean I was gonna be a singer,
but that we all have our own roles to fill.
I'm here to study.
You're here to play music.
Huh. That's what it was?
I knew something was off.
You surprised me, too!
It gets this crowded at this hour, too, huh?
Ooh, something an out-of-towner would say!
Shut up.
Anyway, putting your all in studying is fine and all,
but don't you want to try being in a band once?
You know I can't.
I'm not asking you to play an instrument.
I think you'd be a good vocalist, personally.
What?
Vocalist?
You have a nice voice,
and what's more, you have the soul.
I do?
Yeah.
Bands are where people with pent up feelings gather, in my opinion.
Like "I wanna fall in love!"
Or "I'm sick of this world!"
Or "That was so epic!"
Or "I love myself!", or "I hate myself!"
Weren't you going to sing by yourself?
That's what I thought,
but being in a band sure is nice.
When you're with others, some'll talk smack,
then others'll tattle, so things get awkward,
but bringing it up would ruin things so you hold it in,
but since you're always together, it all builds up
and then you get tired of being in the same room
and finally blow a fuse—
You haven't said a single positive thing.
Huh? Oh, I guess so.
Whatever. It's just fun.
You can create things as a group that you couldn't do alone.
What's that?
It's nothing!
This is probably the closest station to your place.
This area doesn't really have city-like vibes.
And that's a good thing.
Your place is over that way,
but let me show you the grocery store this way.
Huh? Okay.
Ow.
Are you sure?
Don't worry about it.
I'm the older one here, anyway.
Think of it as paying for my stay.
But—
It's fine, okay?
Can you put the rest in the fridge?
Warning you though, I'm not that amazing.
But you do know how to cook.
I kind of like cooking, to be honest.
Hm, where's the knife...
It's a bit like writing songs, y'know?
You chop the ingredients
while you wait for the water to boil,
then prep the sauce
while the ingredients are stewing...
You progress on multiple things in parallel,
and then combine their results all into one in the end.
Wow...
Ugh! This knife isn't cutting it.
Sorry for not having a better knife....
That's not something you need to apologize for.
It's just that I haven't been able
to take care of anything....
Even though I chose to live by myself....
Do you think that's funny?
Nah. I just remembered I was like this, once.
You just have to face it head on.
"What do I do?", "I messed up!", "That's how it works?"
You just have to learn by trial and error.
Like realising you don't have plates to put this on.
Sorry about that.
Things I need to buy!!
• Plates
• Ladle
• Tension rod
• Colander
Done.
Thanks for waiting.
You should buy a light soon, too.
Do we just eat out of this?
Nina, you sure you're not from a posh family?
Huh?
That's something a rich girl would say.
Huh? No, you've got it all wrong.
My family's as typical as they get.
Except, they're just a little unique...
We have house rules.
House rules?
Oh, like laws to follow at home?
Yes.
1. Always eat dinner at the table with all family members present.
2. No smartphone usage in the living room.
3. A family meeting is to be held every Sunday evening.
Like that.
Sheesh.
And some parents were amazed that
there was a family doing that sort of thing,
So word about us got around at school.
I think I get it.
But then I stopped attending class
and eventually dropped out....
Why?
Who cares why I did?
Is that it?
How'd you know?
It's written all over your face.
The most popular girl at school.
She's attractive.
And she hops from one hottie to the next.
Oh? Did you get bullied by her?
Yeah.
Why?
Why would I know? Something about me
must have hit a nerve or something.
You didn't try to get back at her?
Girls like her build up a support network so that
you can't retaliate before they start messing with you.
They get everyone to give you the silent treatment,
and at one point I even got hurt enough that I needed to be taken to the hospital,
but school, and even my family,
said not to make a big deal about it.
Stop.
The hotpot's gonna get overcooked.
That's fine. I like veggies soggy.
You really should become a singer.
Huh?
You could probably write five songs
out of those topics just now.
I've wanted to experience being in a band
where I'm not the vocalist at least once.
See what it's like to only focus on playing the guitar.
You're serious?
I'm serious.
Dropping outta high school
means y'got fewer future prospects.
It'll be too late for regrets
when ya figure out what ya wanna do in life.
Then...
Then going to university should be enough, right?
As long as I study and get into university on my own!
No.
If I remain a high school dropout
and don't ever attend university, it's all over for me.
All over, huh?
Sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
It's just that at this rate,
it'll feel like I've lost.
I'll have lost to the bullies, my parents, and my teachers.
Okay, I get it.
I won't ask you again.
Sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
There was some more beer in the fridge, right?
This is heavy!
That one has books.
I'll take the heavy ones,
so grab the others.
I can handle it!
Will one trip be enough?
This is the last big item, so I think it'll be fine.
Can you go double check the room?
Okay!
Not forgetting anything, right?
I really need to study....
Here.
This'll still be useful to you, yeah?
Yeah, I suppose.
It's not like I can play it, anyway.
I guess I should take it back from you, then.
Thanks.
Well, I'll get going!
You sure you don't want me to come with?
I'll be fine!
Okay.
Can I ask for one last favour?
What is it?
I didn't know there was a place like this around here.
You've probably heard about the Tama River before, no?
It's a lot wider than I thought.
I didn't think Tokyo had a place like this.
Tokyo's beyond that bridge.
You were this close to making it.
I was really just a hair's breadth away....
Do you have any requests?
Anything's fine.
I just wanted to hear your voice one last time.
Sing whatever you like.
And good luck on your studies.
I'm just moving back to the same unit
I dragged you to a while back,
so let's go out to eat again when you're free.
Sure.
Give it your all with your music, too, Momoka-san.
I'll do my best to write more songs
you'll fall head over heels for again.
Give'em the finger and blow them away.
Back at you.
Actually...
Whenever you feel like flipping someone off,
try using your pinky instead.
I'll do the same.
Got it.
Alright...
If you found yourself inside my shoes
How would you decide which path to ignore?
All the blank white pages that are set before me
Full of simple questions anyone could answer
It's form over function
But my fingers are trembling anxiously
There's no right answer
No one wins or loses
And it's all so simple
I can only march on
And carve out my own path
No more brooding
If I keep on debating, I'll waste my life
Crap.
Um...
"'You can't give up,' said Jim."
"'The light of hope'"
"'will surely shine in the darkness.'"
I still need to go shopping.
Girls Band Cry.
Note this down.
The pronouns that can be used here are...
Dodgeball sure was fun!
Yeah!
I took down two people!
Whoa! That's amazing!
I am, right?
I haven't spoken with anyone.
I haven't spoken with a single soul this week....
A week ago
Did you finish moving?
Did you finish moving back in?
Yeah, I did. My back's killing me.
Yeah, I did.
My back's killing me.
Take it easy, then.
Thanks!!
Thanks.
It's been
It's been a
It's been a wh
It's been a whi
It's been a
It's been
It's be
Weather
Tomorrow's forecast has been updated.
Guess I should study.
1 New Message from Momoka-san
Did you buy a light yet?
Someone gave me one I'm not gonna use today, want it?
Thank you! Yes, I'll take it!
Can I come over to pick it up now?
Good evening!
Good evening...
I think it was around here...
Found it!
Excuse me!
Hey! You got here quick!
Coming in!
Sorry about the short notice.
The light I was talking about is over there.
Looks like it should do the trick, right?
Thank you so much!
It's fine as long as it turns on.
Sup? Have you gotten used to things here?
Good question....
Since you're here, how about we go to dinner?
I'm working again, so I'll treat you.
Sure! I'll go!
So she's Nina-chan?
Yeah.
This is Awa-san. She gave me that light.
She's joining me as a drummer.
I'm Subaru Awa!
Nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm Iseri.
You're joining us for dinner, right?
Not treating you, though.
What? You're lame!
I don't have the money for that!
That okay?
Actually, I'm gonna head home.
Join us! Nina only turned up in Tokyo a bit ago.
Subaru's the same age as you, y'know.
This is more like hotpot than shabu-shabu.
You added way too many veggies.
Cabbage, if stewed for too long,
loses its texture and tastes nasty.
Here you go.
Go ahead.
Thanks.
What music are you into, by the way?
Huh?
Any bands or Vocaloid artists you like?
If I recall correctly, she's into
Showa era music because of her grandma.
Oh? That sounds nice.
I listen to that sometimes.
Which artists do you like?
Uh, I wouldn't say I'm that into—
Isn't this GureRuchi?
Whoa, it is.
You listen to GureRuchi?
I think I've been to one of their concerts?
And again at a music festival!
Music festival? The one in Chiba last year?
Yeah, that one.
They were a total mess.
A mess, huh?
That would definitely keep them off future guest line-ups.
They haven't held a proper concert since.
Huh. I never noticed,
but I think you're right...
Their debut was pretty good, though.
Do you go to concerts or other events, Nina-chan?
Not really....
Oh, okay.
The pot's kinda getting lonely,
wanna drop some meat in?
Wait, do you not like meat?
Nina-chan?
Sorry, I'll be right back.
No chemistry?
I wouldn't say that.
Then try talking to her a bit.
She's trying pretty hard to find common ground.
What does that mean?
Is she forcing herself to talk to me?
Of course. Everyone starts off like that.
You don't know anything about each other.
She sounds so pretentious. It pisses me off.
You're overthinking it.
She mentioned going to a drama school,
so that's kind of normal for her.
She doesn't mean any harm.
You sure are friendly, aren't you.
You're totally screaming, "Look at me,"
"humouring a miserable girl like her."
in that head of yours.
What's with the pessimism?
I'm not being pessimistic!
If you judge people with that mindset
you'll never be able to talk with anyone!
Hey!
You're right.
I doubt I'll ever get along with others.
Can't help it, I have a shit personality.
Now look here...
I'll forever be alone.
Thanks for treating me.
Thank you for the light.
You're...welcome?
Man, what a doofus.
She doesn't even realise she has what she most needs.
What am I doing?
Even though she reached out to me....
Even though she was thinking about my circumstances....
I'm an idiot, aren't I?
I'm so dumb.
I'm stupid as heck!
I'm the dumbest!
God! Damn! Idiot!
I'm such an idiot....
Shut up!
No you shut up!
Whassat?!
What's that supposed to be?
Shut the hell up!
What? Quit that!
Shut up!!!
That's dangerous!
Shut yer trap!
I can't even plug in the light by myself.
I'll spend my entire life in darkness....
I'm gonna be in the dumps forever....
The dumps....
Let's start a band after all.
What?
Momoka-san?
Subaru-chan?
You should pick a better place to hide your spare key.
And wow, the light's already this tattered.
Like I said, I love your voice.
Why would you lie to me like that?
I'm not lying.
You over-complicate and convolute things,
but that's because you can't lie to yourself.
You're so frail, but you'd rather die than change your tune.
You remind me of what I'd once forgotten—
a song of mine so dear to me
I wish I could hold onto it forever.
I don't...I don't need to hear that!
Why are you laughing?!
What a pain in the ass!
Ow!
Just shove all that pain
into your songs!
Here, have this.
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
I laughed, thinking it a dream
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
I can't even say that I'm lonely
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
Is incapable of making anyone happy
But still, I feel a growing hope
Moving past all of the lies
I just want to hear that I'm not wrong
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
I don't care if I'm still the same today
I just want to sing with you
My emotions stir so often
I've been hated
But I'm going to keep on walking
Proud of myself who can never become anybody
Even if I'm alone
I believe in myself
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing
Next Episode:
A Messy Q&A