“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
The Dollars' boss is your best friend in the whole world,
Ryugamine Mikado.
Take me to that meeting.
We'll accept your challenge, and fight.
It would make sense for a portion of the Dollars to ally themselves with the black biker and go after the Kokinzoku.
If things keep going like they are,
it'll end up as a real fight.
We must exterminate it from reality!
We, the Kokinzoku!
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
I didn't quit back then.
Back then, why did I...
Lost at Sea
Did Masaomi say anything?
Kida?
No, he hasn't been here.
Calm down, Ryugamine, I believe you.
You haven't told anyone I'm one of the Dollars.
Yeah.
There's no reason for you guys to feel responsible for this.
I've decided to quit the Dollars.
Things aren't as clear as they used to be.
I see...
I wanted to ask before,
but are you one of the Dollars too?
No!
I see.
That day,
he told me...
Even then, it won't be longer than three days before that becomes your normal, everyday life again.
If you truly want to escape your normal, everyday life, you'll have to be constantly changing,
whether you're aiming for something of higher or lower standards.
I decided to change.
However...
...this is the result.
Your call has been forwarded to an automatic voice message system.
So you didn't hear me?
I forbade you from brawling, didn't I?
But–
Yeah, I did.
Sh-Shogun.
Are you happy with the way things are?
There's no doubt that the headless rider is one of the Dollars!
Are we supposed to sit back and let them mock us like this?!
Also, if we do, then the Dollars' leader might show up.
I'm going to do some research on the Dollars' leader.
Stay out of trouble until I find something solid.
Got it?
Either way, you can't stop us.
Still, it's nothing to get agitated about.
Even if nothing had happened, it might have come to this anyway.
Do you really think so?
Fights break out a lot in this town,
so it's not really anyone's fault that two kids from the same school were attacked.
Therefore, don't worry about it.
Dollars?
What about you?
Got it?
Well then, I'm leaving private mode.
Okay?
Hey, you!
Don't just walk away after bumping into me!
Hey...
H-Heiwajima...
Shizu...
Nice weather today, isn't it?
Hey, Shizuo.
Yeah, I'll be over there later on. Thanks.
Yup.
He's with the Dollars too, isn't he?
Yes, I heard he was at their meeting half a year back.
Idiot!
Heiwajima Shizuo and that black guy from Russian Sushi aren't with anyone!
Stay away from them if you want to live.
Yo.
Hello.
Are you alone?
Wasn't Kida with you?
No.
Did you want to talk to Masaomi?
Not really.
It's dangerous to walk around alone, though.
There was a Raira student who got jumped.
Do you know him?
I see.
Thanks a lot.
Things have been hectic since that slasher incident.
I hear the Kokinzoku have made the Dollars their enemy.
The Dollars haven't done anything.
They definitely haven't gotten any orders from their boss.
Some people out there aren't happy about that.
Well, that's what the rumors are, anyway.
Are you one of the Dollars, Kadota-san?
No. Why?
I wonder if the Dollars should even exist...
Is the Dollars really a necessity?
I don't know.
At a time like this, even Mikado...
I see.
You were chatting with Saika, or Sonohara Anri-chan.
However, no matter how much you wrote, there was no reply.
Well, things being the way they are, you thought she was feeling depressed.
But really...
What about Anri-chan's phone?
Can't you get through?
Looks like her phone's been cut off.
Even so, what's with this Kanra guy?
He's just writing things to make Anri-chan feel uneasy.
Anri-chan is part of the Sonohara house, isn't she?
Yeah.
She's the daughter of that antiquities guy whose father sold Saika, isn't she?
And the Dollars' leader is in the same class as her, also, she has a friend from the Kokinzoku.
Anri-chan doesn't know that Mikado is the leader of the Dollars.
At any rate, the three are friends,
and the kid from the Dollars and the kid from the Kokinzoku
don't know that about each other.
Probably.
I haven't heard the whole story.
I'm sorry. Please don't ask me anything.
I'm sorry.
It's just like King Ghidorah.
So, what do you plan to do?
Anri-chan isn't saying anything and I can't push her either, can I?
I'll just have to pray that they'll all be okay.
Ya-hooooo!
It's Kanra-chan!
Oh, there's nobody here?
Don't tell me they're off having fun, leaving me as an outcast?
That's okay, though.
I'm totally having fun here by myself!
I guess gaming is the thing to do now, so I'm gonna go.
Bye bye bee!
A few days passed.
I hadn't seen the Dollars' site since that encounter.
I had heard that the town was still in an uproar as always.
However, there hadn't been any change in my everyday life.
Takiguchi-kun got out of the hospital.
At this rate, everything would stay peaceful.
This was my everyday life.
However...
Kida went home already.
Thanks for coming to visit me.
I'm going to go home now.
Yeah? Well then.
See you tomorrow.
You're one of the Dollars, aren't you?
N-No, I'm not!
Of course you're one of the Dollars!
Please get out of here, now.
What the hell are you doing?
Are you betraying us?!
Mother told us to do it.
Our mother told us to stop you.
If anyone from the Kokinzoku is about to attack members of the Dollars,
stop them.
Yes. I understand, mother.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
It's my fault.
Because of me, Kida-kun is...
Is there anyone from the Kokinzoku who can hear me right now?
I have to do something.
I must... I must do something.
Hello?
Move the queen to C-Ke-6.
Move the black piece to G-Ka-6.
Very good. Very good.
Things are heating up.
Come on, spit it out!
I don't know what you mean, honest!
I can't hear you.
You say you don't remember? Don't make me laugh!
That's enough.
We have to make an example for the lower–
Do you guys really not remember anything?
When I came to, everyone was angry...
It's true! It's true!
Could this be hypnosis?
Like, "You're getting sleepy."
It really could've been hypnosis.
After all...
The headless rider is with the Dollars, so it's not improbable that she...
What is it?
Yes. I saw these guys standing with a girl.
A girl?
Now that you mention it...
I saw them, too.
After they met with her, I thought they started acting strange.
What kind of girl?
Right... She was wearing a Raira uniform,
and had glasses on, and she had big boobs...
The girl who was riding with the headless rider had glasses on too, didn't she?
No.
And she had a huge chest, too!
It can't be... It can't be.
You would notice that, wouldn't you?
All right! Let's capture that girl and–
Stop!
I told you before. No brawling allowed.
If we can drag her in here, it'll all be–
You guys understand as well, right? You're not to act until I give the word.
It can't be true.
It has to be a lie.
Still... Still, she... Anri...
Really? Then, I'll show you my notes, too.
What was that? Something's weird.
That's it. Masaomi and Sonohara-san aren't here.
This town sure is big when you're alone.
I even felt like going home when I first came here.
However, while Masaomi was showing me around,
I met a lot of people, and had lots of different experiences,
and now this feels like it's my town.
However, there must be members of the Dollars in there.
Ryugamine-kun?
Perfect timing. We wanted to talk to you.
Okay.
Harima-san,
you wanted to talk?
Oh, yeah. It's about Anri, lately she's...
What's up with her?
What's up... with what?
You mean you haven't noticed, Ryugamine-kun?
Noticed what?
Anri-chan seems really worried.
I was concerned, so I asked her about it,
but she kept saying, "No, it's okay."
Anri-chan used to follow me around all the time, so I'm worried about her.
I never noticed that at all.
And I was wondering if you'd heard anything, Ryugamine-kun.
No, I haven't.
Really?
I'll ask her next time I see her.
Okay, let me know if anything's up.
That's it.
Okay, let's go, Seji-san.
Ryugamine.
You like Sonohara, don't you?
N-No w-well I-I... W-Why?
Don't act like you don't. I can tell just by looking.
If you really like her, don't ever take your eyes off her.
No matter what you know about your girl, or what you see, don't turn your eyes away.
Hug her, and don't let her go.
That's the responsibility of someone who's chosen to love another.
See you later.
I'm going to take up my responsibility and love you too, Seji-san!
Yagiri-kun's a weird guy, but I still thought he was really cool.
We're in this together forever, after all! You know, I...
Little kid thinks he can act all high and mighty.
The Shogun's acting weird, don't you think?
Horada-san!
Over there!
Raira uniform...
Glasses!
B-Big...
The responsibility to not turn your eyes away, no matter what you see or find.
I had no idea that Sonohara-san was worried.
What about Masaomi? Did Masaomi notice it?
Maybe I was too concerned with myself, and wasn't seeing anything else.
Sonohara-san, or the Dollars.
What do I know about the Dollars?
Why didn't I quit the Dollars back then?
I'm quitting the Dollars.
Don't write that if you're leaving!
Kill the Kokinzoku.
Come on, leader, do something!
Who is the leader, anyway?
Do you guys think the Dollars should be here?
We don't need it anymore.
I already said I'm leaving.
I said, stop posting that.
I don't want it to go away. That's why I want the leader to do something.
The leader created the Dollars, so he should take responsibility for it.
What responsibility?
There's nobody above or below. Everyone's free, and that's the Dollars.
You shouldn't rely on the boss only at times like this.
Actually, I remember someone making a post like this a while back:
"The Dollars should try and make themselves a good gang.
There are some bad people, but don't worry about them."
What does that have to do with our leader?
That's right! The Dollars don't belong to anyone!
It's our gang!
We should do whatever we can do.
Die.
I agree! We should protect the town from the Kokinzoku with our own strength!
By patrolling the streets for instance?
We're colorless and clear, so nobody knows who we are.
That's right. That's why.
We can all help each other.
Back then...
Raira... glasses...
boobs...
It can't be...
Sonohara-san?
The queen has been captured by the black pieces.
No way... It can't be...
There's no way...
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time:
Durarara!!
Breakup Announcement
Is this a dream?
No. He told me that.
Why is it that you never know what you have until it's gone?
Next time: Breakup Announcement