I got you!
Oh no!
A substitution technique?!
Too bad for you!
I don't have the time!
Outta my way!
Yeah, goal!
Ninjas.
Those who once served the feudal lords of this country.
It was the name affixed to assassins, spies, and saboteurs alike.
This is a tale of the miracle of love and courage
brought about by five girls who gave up their youth
to fight evil as modern-day ninjas.
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't truly smile
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Light does not coil around us like a spiral
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Go past the present and put the shadows in your crosshair
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to dream anymore
We can reap the future all the same
Maybe now it is time to prove our word
Break your world
The Ninja That Stands Upon Skyscrapers
No doubt about it.
I've taken another step forward!
Your strength is still raw.
You must learn to channel that strength as a sword and shield.
Sword and shield?
You must not flout your strength.
Yes.
You may go!
Okay!
I promise I'll fulfill your expectations and become a first-rate ninja!
I'm doing my best.
Gramps!
It's Asakusa! I'm back!
This brings back memories!
What a wonderful skyline!
Wonderful, you say?
Are you from Asakusa?
You said, "I'm back!"
Oh, were you listening?
I couldn't help but overhear it.
Well, I live in a school dorm in Asakusa, but I've been away for a while for various reasons.
So it brought back all these memories for me, then I accidentally said so aloud.
I'm sorry!
You sure are an interesting person.
Huh?
What school is she from?
Hanzo National Academy.
Founded in 1919, it has a student
population of about one thousand.
It is a famous, elite school.
Whoa, she's cute!
Is she a sophomore?
Let's go chat her up!
Yeah!
She disappeared?
That's strange.
She sure was cute...
C-Cute?!
Sorry, but this is part of my training!
Speaking of which—
But this academy has two sides to it.
Those who know of its hidden side are few and far between.
Just in the nick of time.
Welcome back.
Ikaruga! I, Asuka, have returned!
Good job losing those boys just now.
You were watching?
You shouldn't reveal your presence in the first place.
And yet you just carelessly ran all the way here through the school gates.
I didn't mean to. I was just happy to be back at school after so long.
We are no mere students of this school.
You're forgetting the basics.
I'm sorry.
Why are you looking so down?
It doesn't suit you, Asuka.
Katsu!
Oh yeah, welcome back.
Sheesh, I just can't let my guard down, can I?
What's the problem? It's not like you're losing anything!
In fact, massaging can make them bigger!
No way! I actually wish they'd get smaller!
That'd be such a waste.
I beg to differ!
Ouchies.
What are you doing, Hibari?
I rushed 'cause I thought I was gonna be late and couldn't stop in time.
Oh, welcome back, Asuka!
Good to see you, Hibari.
You passed your promotion exam, right?
Yeah!
That's great!
Thanks.
You should worry about yourself
before cheering on others, Hibari.
Fine by me!
I'm happy even if it isn't me!
How long have you been there, Yagyuu?
Concealing your presence is one of the basics of being a ninja.
Oh, right.
Man, who's whose senior here?
Well, Yagyuu may only be a freshman, but she's higher ranked than me.
That's because Yagyuu's a genius!
Everyone's here?
Good morning, Mr. Kiriya.
Asuka.
Yes!
Good job.
Oh, I didn't do that great...
Fail
Excellent
Pass
Let's see...
Fail
Excellent
Pass
Fail
Excellent
Pass
Fail
Excellent
Pass
Fail
Excellent
Pass
Fail
Excellent
Pass
Fail
Excellent
Pass
Fail
Excellent
Pass
Your scroll was about to be stolen,
so you used a substitution technique,
losing your ninja outfit instead.
You used a smoke bomb in the middle of the city,
and barely met the time limit.
This is amazing.
You got the exact minimum passing grade.
That's something that'd be
impossible to do on purpose.
Don't admire something so weird!
Well, a pass is a pass.
I look forward to your continued progress.
Yes, sir!
As for today's training...
We'll start with martial arts.
Change and gather at the training ground.
Changing room
Mr. Kiriya would be a great teacher if he didn't use all that smoke.
It's probably his signature move.
I like his style!
I need to learn from him!
Yes, that's right, you have to learn!
Not again, Katsu!
Grow! Grow!
No way! What am I supposed to do?
They're bigger than before!
Stop messing around and get ready!
Okay.
I don't want to do this...
What's wrong, Hibari?
I'm hopeless at martial arts.
Hibari.
What?
Just do your best.
Okay!
Is everyone ready?
Let's go.
First up, aerial martial arts.
Ikaruga! Katsuragi!
Yes, sir!
Special agent intelligence class.
Special operative training class.
Otherwise known as ninja classes.
Ikaruga, a senior.
Gotcha!
Katsuragi.
Nice one, Katsu!
Asuka, a sophomore.
That was amazing, Katsu!
Go! Go!
Hibari, a freshman.
Yagyuu, a freshman.
Next up, Asuka! Yagyuu!
Yes, sir!
Here I come!
This is how the five girls live, unnoticed by the normal students.
All while undergoing their superhuman training.
I totally thrashed you just now.
Wait 'til we get to swords.
Sore loser.
N-No I'm not!
I wonder what I should do for lunch?
It's boring to eat out all the time.
Attention, please!
I present to you souvenirs from my trip!
Sushi rolls!
They look yummy!
Well, that settles lunch.
Asuka, where did you get these?
Actually, I stayed with my family yesterday.
Oh, right.
They run a sushi joint, don't they?
That's right.
Let me express my heartfelt gratitude.
Oh my, sushi rolls.
Please have some as well, Mr. Kiriya!
Why, thank you.
Is Master Hanzo well?
Yes, he is.
Gramps actually woke up early to make these rolls for me.
I see.
He sure hasn't changed.
Now that Asuka's back,
we'll leave the academy and do some fieldwork this afternoon.
Leave the academy?
About time!
We've been stuck underground flying, jumping, and meditating every day, and it's dead boring!
So, what's the mission?
Getting rid of delinquents at the shopping district.
It seems some delinquents have gotten together and started causing trouble.
Getting rid of delinquents?
Delinquents are scary...
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Okay!
Senran Kagura
I thought we'd be doing something like secretly escorting a VIP
or infiltrating an embassy to obtain top-secret data.
Those sorts of missions are for our seniors
who've graduated the academy
and become full-fledged ninjas.
That doesn't make getting rid
of delinquents any better!
This is actually more difficult.
We have to deal with normal people without revealing we're ninjas.
Denbouin
Passage
That's exactly why it's training.
Yup, yeah, okay.
Umm, so where are these delinquents?
We're just wasting time, blindly wandering around like this.
Let's split up and hunt for our quarry.
Welcome
back
No surprise that they're not at the temple.
You were at the ferry!
We meet again.
I'm here on a school trip.
Oh, so that's why you were on the ferry.
Well, we have free time now, but I lost track of my friends.
Plus, my school doesn't allow cellphones, and it's my first time here.
Where did you get separated?
Uh, some street or somewhere...
Was it here?
There are many such streets in Asakusa. More details would help.
Are there any places they might have gone to?
Is it okay for you to stick around with me?
It's fine.
You looked like you were busy, though.
Oh no, I'm on a school trip too.
Oh, you did say you were from a school around here.
Yeah, that's right!
I was researching local historical landmarks,
but I finished quickly and had some free time.
I see. That's good, then.
Hey, Yagyuu.
Why did you follow me?
I was too worried to leave you alone.
I'll be fine on my own against a bunch of delinquents.
You might get ambushed.
In that case, I'll just beat the stuffing out of—
Hold it right there.
That uniform... They're from Hanzo Academy.
That gaudy rich kids' school, huh?
What about it?
Mind lending me some money?
I see. You're the ones we want.
Gather everyone, Hibari.
O-Okay.
Gather
Ninja signal flare.
It's a special flare that only trained ninja can detect.
Its effect extends out in a kilometer radius.
We've pretty much covered everywhere.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
It's only right to help out people in trouble.
It's the signal!
What's wrong?
It's nothing!
That's right! We haven't gone to Benten yet.
Let's go check it out!
What's that? You wanna fight?
We can't, Yagyuu.
They're here.
They're from Hanzo Academy too.
All right, you guys ready?
What's with these two?
We've been asked to clean up the shopping district.
You could call us public morals enforcers.
Yagyuu, where's Asuka?
What's she up to?
Good grief.
Clear the area, Hibari.
Okay, leave it to me.
They're making fun of us.
Get them!
There's only one thing to do now.
Let's go!
All right!
I wonder if everyone's okay.
We've come so far and we still haven't found them.
Maybe they went back already.
Yeah, maybe they did.
Work in progress
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Sorry! This path's closed for now.
Are they done yet?
That was over all too quickly.
I wonder what happened to Asuka...
What's she playing at?
How can they stand back up after our attacks?
This energy...
These are no ordinary delinquents.
You guys!
Hibari!
Be careful! These guys have lost their minds!
Lost their minds?
Her movements may be slow, but she has good instincts.
Plus, she's so timid that it's simply adorable.
Could this be...?!
A battle sphere!
Battle spheres.
Pocket dimensions that transcend the space-time continuum, used for battles between ninjas.
Are they...
...ninjas too?
Then we must use our full strength against them.
All right, time to transform!
It's not part of our mission, but circumstances demand it.
Ninja Morph!
The Ninja Morph.
A technique that manifests the power within the body into battle gear.
It is the foundation of a ninja's existence.
With this, ninjas are able to unleash their full potential.
Are you okay?
I-I'm fin—
You've been a big help.
You know, I never got your name.
I'm Asuka!
I'm Homura.
Homura.
See you, Homura!
I tried to make my killing intent obvious, but she didn't even—
I hope you find your friends!
See ya!
There's no need to worry.
For my friends are...
Come, my dear marionettes. Make me proud.
Marionettes?
This is...
The marionettes disguised themselves as delinquents and attacked us?
I don't know.
One thing's for certain though.
They were targeting us.
The marionettes all gave off the same aura.
It was as if there was a single
puppeteer controlling them all.
Are you okay?
Y-Yes...
You're so cute.
I'll be seeing you around!
She's so beautiful.
What is it?
Oh, nothing!
You guys!
Asuka.
What happened to you?!
Umm...
There's a reason for all this.
What about the delinquents?
For someone who's so late, you're awfully carefree.
They weren't really delinquents.
What do you mean?
First of all!
Mr. Kiriyama needs to give you a good lecture about this.
You'd better be prepared for extended meditation.
They're all perfect candidates to be my marionettes.
So how was it?
What was the legendary ninja or whatever really like?
I had expected her to be more accomplished.
In other words, Hanzo Academy's no threat at all.
We can just let them be for now.
We'll find out who the true ninjas are
whether they like it or not.
I decided on this path
and now I won't hesitate anymore
I have the passion to go foward
and courage to match it
The feelings I accepted
might all be the result of fate
And yet now I stand perplexed
With courage
With pride
And with beauty we will go forth
Let's go according to our dreams
Let's take it all on
They're my guiding light, honest as I am
Every day a kiss
Just like lovers
You looked forward to a real fight, right?
I decided I would believe
Now I try to make it real
Let's go according to our dreams
Next Episode Preview
Is there anything you're afraid of, Katsu?
Boobs, I guess!
Help me overcome my mastrophobia, Asuka!
Don't fondle them!
The Legendary Ninja Revealed
Next episode: The Legendary Ninja Revealed!
Risk your life and come get it!