Who's our next target?
Frank Claude.
We've finally tracked him down.
Are you going to dispatch that odd bunch again?
I thought we'd already agreed on dispatching them.
They're going to be flashy about it, aren't they?
It's a necessary measure to raise awareness of our existence.
Their powers are hellfire that will burn down Hell itself,
upon which we will build our world.
Are you hurt?
It's just a scratch.
I will... kill.
I will kill...
so I can live.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to die unless I escape.
I can't run from those black eyes.
What should I do?
If I can't escape, I'll have to kill.
If I can't kill, I'll be killed.
W-Where am I?
What is this?
What was I-
W-Who am I?
I don't remember my name.
What is this?
Japanese?
A travel bag.
Is this who I am?
I'm a Japanese tourist, and...
Why?
Why can't I remember?
The people chasing me might be close by.
Stop doing things by yourself, Clau.
You're making me look bad as a bodyguard.
Do you want to ride with me?
I'll be fine.
I'm just going to check on things. That's all.
I can't let him handle everything by himself.
That slimy bastard.
He's probably playing with some extraordinary toy by now.
Jeez... He makes me want to puke.
But he's contributed much to the syndicate.
I guess he's good buddies with McGwire and the others,
though he's just a puppet himself.
It's Inferno's policy to employ whoever gets the work done, after all.
I know.
But you're treading on thin ice way too much, Clau.
Call me if anything happens.
I'll keep it in mind, Lizzie.
If only you wouldn't drive like that...
Situation Assessment Ability: 074
Awakening Value: 087
I can't believe he's reached these figures just minutes after waking up.
I told you.
He's an outstanding talent.
I'm going to Hell, aren't I?
No, I might actually be there already.
His perception just now was...
It's animal instinct.
You could see it as the id that was hidden inside the ego.
But he's not there yet.
He has yet to reach the heights I'd hoped he would.
It's your turn, Phantom.
But don't overdo it.
Yes, Master.
You better attack me with all you've got...
Those eyes!
if you want to live.
When one's heart,
one's life,
and one's very existence are placed in peril,
the only thing one can count on is one's own instinct to survive.
It's useless to lean on morals or kindness for help.
Only weak individuals who have given up on life
believe that security is something that can be guaranteed.
I've come to loathe this world,
where such thoughts have become commonplace.
Well, if it isn't Ms. McCunnen.
You should have told me you were coming.
What's our status?
We should be seeing the results soon.
Would you like to observe?
Yes.
Please come in.
I don't even know who she is.
Or why she's after me.
I don't even know where this is.
I don't even know who I am.
There's no escape.
There's nowhere to go.
If there's no escape...
then both you and I...
must kill or be killed!
It's starting.
Starting?
Please observe carefully.
Why?
Attack me with all you've got...
if you want to live.
I have no past,
no future,
nor even a life.
Even so,
I don't want to die.
Where should I go?
I don't even know where I'm from.
I don't even have any memories.
How can I be free?
What kind of freedom requires you to kill people in order to earn it?
Please... tell me.
Where is this?
Who...
Who am I?!
Zwei.
You're...
I'm Ein.
You're Zwei.
Zwei?
That's your name.
Starting today, your name is Zwei.
Zwei?
What the hell?
What kind of a-
You are me;
I am you.
How about it?
Isn't he a wonderful talent?
He gave us exactly the results we were looking for.
As this boy has had no military training,
he has no formal understanding of tactics.
He acted out of pure instinct.
Not only that,
he was also able to overpower Ein for just a moment.
How clumsy of you, Phantom.
I deeply apologize.
He's a genius.
He possesses primitive powers that appear
when put under the pressure of a life-or-death situation.
It's almost as if he was born to join Inferno.
Even if what you say is true, do you think he wants this?
No egg will ever refuse to hatch,
nor will a seed ever refuse to sprout.
His will is not the problem here.
And that's where your specialty of brainwashing comes into play.
It's perfect.
Using a combination of hypnosis and drugs,
we've been able to seal away only those memories that concern his own identity.
Please try to understand, Ms. McCunnen.
We're doing him a favor.
He was found under very unfavorable circumstances.
If it hadn't been for us, he would have been killed as originally intended.
But I wanted to give him just one more chance;
one more chance at living a fruitful life.
Traveling alone and Japanese, huh?
What a nuisance.
There's no way anyone can find him now.
It's a complete secret now.
All right, Scythe Master.
I entrust this boy to you.
Thank you.
But "Ein" and "Zwei"?
Couldn't you at least come up with better names for your students?
We'll see how long you can keep ordering me around like that, Missy.
I'm the first woman, Ein.
You're the second man, Zwei.
We are...
What are you doing?
You've done your part, Ein.
Return to your post.
Yes, Master.
We are...
specters that cannot exist anywhere.
We are phantoms with no identity.
Welcome back, Master!
Where are the others?
They're all resting.
In the middle of the day?
What's going on?
Y-You're...
Phantom.
Inferno's best assassin.
A title bestowed only to the top sniper of the syndicate.
My masterpiece.
And him, as well...
That's overkill.
Is that so?
I guess that spells the end for both him and his syndicate.
With this, two of the five syndicates in Los Angeles have been eliminated.
My friends,
it all starts here.
We shall create a new era;
the era of Inferno.
Specters that cannot exist anywhere.
Phantoms with no identity.
You can no longer prove your existence...
other than by killing.