Dela
This is Dela's Bar.
A bar where only ladies may immerse themselves in moody music and fancy conversations.
What's wrong, Dela?
Can't you tell? I'm deeply concerned.
Putting that aside, take our orders!
Listen to me first.
How self-centered.
Shiori, would you say I'm self-centered?
Yeah, very.
Oh, please. You don't have to praise me so much!
We're not.
Don't you think a bird who's very self-centered sounds kind of cool?
Something like this...
Very self-centered!
No toys for you if you're gonna be like that!
I don't need any!
So, Dela, what are you concerned about?
I knew it. You really want to know what it is, don't you?
No, not really...
I want to give this place a makeover.
Whoa! It's my time to shine!
Yeah, this place does seem pretty sketchy.
What do you want it to be like?
Something like this.
What the heck?
Otherworld Bar?
Zombie Bar!
What?! Will only the dead be welcomed here?
This world
Otherworld
No!
A ghostess bar!
I hear they're quite popular around here.
Mister, I think you got the wrong word.
Huh?
To tell the truth, I found it a bit strange myself.
Hey, you've got four sets!
Hurry up and change.
Us?
Yeah, you.
I don't think the customers wear those...
Sounds fun. Let's do it.
Ta-da! What do you think? Does it look good on me?
Pretty good.
Awesome.
Good. Now make some tea.
Coming right up!
Tamako, I think you're supposed to go,
"Certainly, Master. I'll bring you your tea right away" there.
Wait, you're a customer. Why are you making tea?
I fail to see the problem.
That's just weird!
Here!
Tamako, what are you doing?
Well, I brought some sweet been mochi,
so I wanted some tea anyway.
Thanks.
You there!
Wipe my mouth.
What?!
Oh, Dela. What are we gonna do with you?
"Please allow me to wipe your mouth," Tamako.
Hey, you. Give me a shoulder massage.
Certainly, Master.
N-No, I get the message.
Forgive me.
Er...
Well then, Shiori...
Yes?
Could you please let me rest on your lap?
You're going too far!
Okay.
What?! Really?!
So warm...
You're so impudent.
Wait.
Huh?
What's wrong, Shiori?
I want...
What?
Dela...
Huh?
My body and soul is all yours!
...'s feathers.
Feathers?
I really want to make myself a shuttlecock.
You normally use the feathers of a goose or a duck, though.
Well...
You can have as many as you like, Shiori.
Can I have sixteen, then?
Sixteen?
You need sixteen feathers to make a shuttlecock.
Uh, that'd be a bit too much at once.
I might die.
Ghost Bar
Truly a Ghost Bar.
Otherworldly.
Thanks. She'll be here all week.
This is Dela's Bar.
A bar where my plans for a makeover very quickly fell apart.