Hey, did you do that by yourself?
Pretty good!
Hey, let's be amiable.
We shouldn't waste what our
whimsical god has given us.
God...?
Or rather, for these guys,
it would be the devil.
Want some? It's Dom Perignon.
Cheers.
To this ship that has charmed the devil.
What in the world is going on
with the showers in this place?!
This is the fourth time! The fourth time!
Even Buddha gets upset
after the third time!
Hey, are you listening?
The shower broke,
and only cold water comes out.
And the faucet fell off.
If you know about it, fix it!
I'm busy right now.
You can do that any time you want--
We're busy!
Don't just hang up!
What if it's an emergency?
Oh, all right. You'll be
happy if I fix it, right?
Hi, he'll call you back. What's your name?
Okay, Fad. I'll tell him.
Fad...?
Did you say Fad?
It's not hot?
Why don't you fix that?
I told you I'll fix it.
No, your arm.
I mean, reconstructive surgery doesn't
cost that much nowadays, right?
This ship is my ship.
And this arm is my arm.
Don't tell me what I need to do.
Now, you death row inmates.
I'm sorry to say, but the cruise to
the prison on Pluto has been canceled.
This ship will now enter a mystery tour--
What are you going to do?
Do you think this ship is
enough for you to escape?
I wasn't talking to you...
S-Stop wasting your time like this.
If you surrender peacefully...
I told you to shut up.
Don't get so hotheaded, Dig.
Oh, man... there goes our precious hostage.
I'm not letting anyone tell me what to do.
If you got a problem
with that, step forward!
You!
I remember...
You're... yeah...
...that assassin for the syndicate...
Udai.
Caught you red-handed
tossing a cigarette butt.
That would be a fine
of 20,000 woolongs, Jet.
Then I'll need to collect
that loan I gave you
with 7 years' worth of interest,
to cover it... and then some...
When did you buy me that coffee?
That's long past the statute of limitations!
So you still think you're a
gunman with a gun like that?
Sure is a waste of ISSP tax money.
This is?
No, your salary.
Yeah, really...
No, I quit.
Huh, I see...
Tenth day. It's a hard world
to live in for smokers, anyway.
Hmm... I never thought you would...
And, what was it that
you wanted to tell me?
There was trouble on the prison
transport ship headed for Pluto.
That was six hours ago.
Apparently there was
an electrical malfunction;
the prisoners took
advantage of it, and rioted.
I don't know the details.
And?
Udai is on that ship.
We don't know where the ship went
after it left the Ganymede Gate.
The ISSP is frantically searching...
Hey, you... don't get any stupid ideas.
It's out of your jurisdiction.
You think it's a stupid idea?
The reason you quit being
a cop was because of when...
Now that is past the statute of limitations.
If after all this, he lives on...
...wouldn't that left arm of yours cry, Jet?
That story doesn't interest me anymore...
Jet! I'll go around from this side!
Got it!
Udai Taxim!
You are under arrest!
A trap?!
What are ya gonna do?
The guys from the ISSP
are gonna come any minute!
And the pilot's dead.
We're gonna break through, of course.
Easy for you to say.
We only got enough
weapons for self-defense.
What are ya gonna do?
I'm sure they've set up a barricade.
It would be better for us to attack
and break through where they're thin.
Can you... steer this thing?
I was a cop on Venus once.
And now you're imprisoned for life?
Cops are human, too...
You got back?
I'm heading out.
It's dangerous, so stand back.
You're going out. Get souvenirs!
Ed...
If I don't come back,
water the bonsai for me.
Yup!
Bonsai, wise guy, chicken pot pie.
Lights shine bright in the many towns.
HQ, do you read?
This is Group D-7.
We have spotted the prison transport ship.
The ship is sending an SOS.
Apparently they ran into
some mechanical trouble.
We are releasing a lifeboat.
On the boat are 4 officers and 12 inmates.
We're requesting a pickup.
Number 12, Number 13, no response.
We request emergency backup.
Repeat, we request emergency backup.
We have lost sight of the transport.
Current location is seven-four-five.
Group D-7, initiate code ten-eight.
Repeat, we request emergency backup.
No good.
Apparently the police don't
know where they went, either.
What do you think their next move will be?
If they are to hijack another ship,
they'll be somewhere close to their original
route at a place where they can hide...
--I don't think so.
--What?
Europa.
Europa? What makes you think that?
If I was Udai, I would go back to Europa.
But, Udai is already...
He hasn't contacted the
syndicate in quite a while.
He is old-fashioned.
So much so that he's not the right kind
of guy to live in this day and age...
He'll go back. I know it...
The Black Dog that won't
let go once he bites, huh?
Okay, Europa it is.
If you're wrong, you're paying for fuel.
Wait! What the--Ow!
What part of this is fixed?!
Huh?
What's this? Jet's gonna have a fit!
He asked me.
He's not comin' back!
It's okay, just bring
something to wipe this up.
Okay!
What's up with him, leaving
his precious bonsai here...?
Hey, Jet! What the hell is going on?!
It's me.
You seem to have done
something outrageous.
We need a new ship.
There is no further relationship
between us and Udai Taxim.
Are you betraying me?
If you want to feel that way, go ahead.
I have information.
That threat won't work anymore.
Times have changed...
while you were in prison.
You win. He's there.
We should split up. I'll come
around from the other end.
You're crazy!
That ship doesn't have any decent weapons!
You know how I work better
than anyone else, right?
Hey, Jet...
Why don't you quit being a bounty
hunter and pair up with me again?
I'll think about it if we get back.
Heat source detected.
Someone after us?
If it's the ISSP, I doubt
they would come alone.
I found something good in the cargo bay.
And we have the perfect target.
All right, Jet...
We'll approach them using this ice
for cover. Stay there until I signal...
Jet!
I don't know who ya are,
but we'll give ya a warm welcome!
Here ya go!
Bingo!
That guy's got guts to come here alone.
What the hell is he?
Hey, where are you...
He's my visitor.
You've got to be kidding.
I'm not gonna put up with all of this!
You came all the way here to see me?
I didn't come here because I wanted to!
Don't say that, I came
out here just to greet you.
I didn't want to come...
but something else wanted to see you.
What?
The left arm that I lost!
What a happy camper you are.
You never knew anything, did you?
What?
I wasn't the one who shot you back then.
It was your partner.
Jet! I'll go around from this side!
Got it!
It was all planned out from the beginning...
...to get rid of you, who were
a threat to the syndicate...
Udai Taxim!
You are under arrest!
You were long since betrayed...
You were used...
A trap...?!
Why did you shoot?
Was it because he was telling the truth?
You came here to shut him up for good?
Why aren't you answering me?!
It was your fault, Jet.
It ended up this way because
you went in on your own...
You know what happens to people
who go against the syndicate, right?
Either they all quit like you... or they die.
We can't live on with
our pretty little ideals.
That's why you betrayed me...
...and kept fooling me?!
I wanted to team up
with you like back then.
Time for farewells, Jet.
Fad!
Jet...
You didn't...
Did you let me shoot on purpose...?
Can I have... a smoke...?
I guess... I couldn't quit smoking...
Too much time has passed by...
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Sitting in muddy water...
...isn't such a bad life...
...if it ends after the first time...
This time, the three of us
will try to do the previews!
Do you think we can do it?
We only have 30 seconds!
If you're too slow, it'll all be over!
You sure are restless...
Anyway, what kinda story is it next time?
I can't remember...
What are you doing?!
We're already running out of time!
Come on, at least tell them the title!
Next episode... Wait, what was it?
We couldn't do it after all!
"Mushroom Samba"