It had been almost a year since I had joined this base
and then one afternoon, it happened...
Emergency Care
Aeronautic Theory
Amazing! You've become so good at it now, Kanata!
Really? I am so happy! Even Rio-senpai's been praising me recently!
You said that you joined the army because you wanted to play the trumpet, right?
Then...
What is your dream?
The sound of the skies
Beyond the Dream
Dream? Isn't it obvious in your case?
It's to be good at the trumpet, right?
Yeah...
But after I said so,
I was told "It's just a small objective and can't be considered as a dream."
That brat Mishio is getting quite pretentious.
It hurts...
But isn't a dream also an objective?
I'm asking because I don't know!
Oh really?
It hurts...
If it's close and you know clearly how to reach it, it's called "Objective", and...
If it's faraway and unrealistic, then it's called "Dream", isn't it?
Unrealistic...
There you go.
What? Don't you have your own dream?
Do you have one Kureha-chan?
You can say so.
What is it?
D-Dream shouldn't be easily told to others, right?
What about you Noël-chan?
I have, but it's a secret.
You and Rio-senpai have been doing things in secret recently,
does that have anything to do with it?
It's an interest, not a... dream.
Then why can't you tell us?
It's like it will disappear if I say it.
I see... A dream, right?
When I think about it, it's true that I don't have a faraway and unrealistic dream.
It feels so lonely like this.
Does Rio-senpai have a dream?
You could say so.
So nice...
You know, to be good at playing trumpet is already a big objective.
Don't feel so depressed.
That's true...
Don't be so anxious to grow up.
It's nothing.
Let's give our dreamless lady an objective then.
I have to go out for a while, master that music sheet before I come back.
Master it completely, all the way through the third movement.
But it's a really difficult one!
I want to hear you playing it when I come back!
Ah, I'm really looking forward to it.
How did it turn out like this...
Score file
But it's true that for now, I should start with things that I can manage.
That sound...
Klaus-san!
Hmm... You look different than usual.
Ah, perhaps it's because I cut my hair.
I see. Anyway, I came here with an important letter...
It's a dedicated letter delivered directly from the Roman Emperor.
It's also my first time delivering such kind of mail.
And it seems that it requires delivery confirmation.
I can't go back if the receipt isn't signed. Where's Rio?
Is it urgent?
Yeah, as soon as possible.
Then I'll go fetch her right away.
Oh yeah, Klaus-san,
do you have a dream?
Of course, if I manage to work until my pension,
I'm planning to go back to my hometown and get some big fields to farm.
Fields?
Yeah, those extra large ones.
And then, I'll enjoy my home grown rice!
Wow! That's awesome!
People who're always doing delivery work all over the place, like me, usually want to do something of their own.
Thank you very much, what you said was very useful!
Ah! Kureha-chan is preparing dinner in the canteen.
You can join us if you'd like to.
Kureha-chan would be very glad, I think.
Got it.
It's the preparations for the festival.
Are you alright? Kanata-san!
Yumina-san.
I was startled when I saw you driving straight into it.
I've just learnt how to drive, so I'm not used to it yet.
You shouldn't be looking around while driving.
Ok...
Eh? Mishio-san said that?
Yeah, she asked me what my dream was.
But I didn't have an answer.
It's nothing.
Just that I might know why Mishio asked such a question.
Kanata-san! Watch in front of you! In front!
Kanata-san!
Yumina-san!
KANATA-SAN!
Kanata-san, will we make it?
Yumina-san, I don't think so!
We have to make it!
Help me!
Kanata-san!
Yumina-san!
To the countless number of Gods,
I appreciate that I am still alive.
drawing!
handsome guy
I would like to wear
mini-skirts
me rich
I want to be prettier
I would like to be an expert
in
creation
I will marry
Kanata
This is...?
This seems to be called "Emma".
The priest said that it's a tradition since the old time.
By writing your wishes down on it, God will hear them.
I want to eat a lot of
steaks.
And this year's Water Festival is just around the corner, so everyone came to try it out.
Found it! The one Seiya wrote.
I would like to be an expert
in
creation
I will marry
Kanata
"I will marry Katana-neechan"
I would like to be an expert
in
creation
I will marry
Kanata
That's...
What's your impression?
I'm very honoured...
What a pity for Seiya-san.
It seems that you couldn't catch Kanata-san's eye yet.
That's not true! It's just that... I've never thought of marrying.
Then Mishio-san should be able to rest assured.
Don't you know?
The one that Mishio-san loves is Seiya-san.
That's why she asked you what your dream was.
Isn't that cute?
Spread my
To be a better cook
I want to
find
SHUKO
To shake the hand of
Mr. Klaus
To run faster
I will marry
Kanata
drawing!
handsome guy
I would like to wear
mini-skirts
That's right, everyone has their own dream.
me rich
I want to be prettier
Spread my
To be a better cook
I want to
find
SHUKO
To shake the hand of
Mr. Klaus
To run faster
I will marry
It's really promising!
Spread my wings
Why don't you also have a try?
Do you also have your dream?
I'm a servant of God after all.
faster
To be a better cook
To run
To run faster
I will marry
I want to
find
SHUKO
But, if I could secularise, I would like to...
Become a tailor!
A dress tailor?
That's right! I want to make cute clothing of all colours!
Light and Comfortable dresses and those kinds of things...
The kind of dress that makes you feel splendid and gorgeous by simply wearing them!
I think that your current self fits you more.
Spread my wings
To run a complete marathon
To be a better cook
Have a lot of chicks at my
feet
grow, grow
my hair grow,
That nothing changes in my life
To run faster
drawing!
Nothing... It's so good to have dreams!
Yeah!
Wonderful dreams huh?
Oh! It's Kanata-chan!
Maria-san.
Rio went to the glass factory.
You're also searching for her?
Yeah.
My father said that the ordered item was completed so he asked me to deliver it.
Maria-san, why do you work at the glass factory?
Because my dream is to make better artwork than my father and sell it in this shop.
I won't sell them.
Who would put the artwork of a girl who abandoned her home on display to sell?
You're so cruel, Mom!
You were the one who chose to learn from that useless guy.
Call me Naomi-san or Onee-san.
Well... What is the mom stuff and learning stuff all about?
Don't you know Kanata-chan?
My father and Naomi-chan were husband and wife.
A poor decision because we were too young and impulsive.
And the fruit of their love is Me.
Maria
See! The proof is in this picture.
Why did you break up?
You are asking such a difficult question straight off.
I'm sorry!
Well, we should say that our dream differed.
Maria
The most important thing for me was this shop, but in his case, it was making glass works.
And we couldn't make a compromise.
So young at that time... The both of us.
So... Their result is Me.
Take care on the road, don't get distracted by the landscape.
Ok.
Well then, I'm entrusting this to you.
What is it?
A necklace, the one that the Maiden of Flame use.
But that's really strange.
From the timing, I think I should surely have crossed path with Rio somewhere though.
Kanata, maybe Rio is spacing out somewhere on the road.
Also pay some attention to the roadside.
But... Maybe I'm worrying too much.
Then, this year's Maiden of Flame will also be chosen from among the fort citizens, right?
That seems to be the case.
I see.
Well, you also heard from Kanata and the others, right?
What the Roman girl, Aisha, said.
About the Roman version of the Maidens of Flame.
I was quite concerned, so I did some research.
Then, I found out that the Roman tradition is more faithful to the the original story.
A long time ago, those who caused the Maidens of Flame to die...
Created a festival to commemorate them.
And then unconsciously, it became the glorification of the maidens' sacrifice.
So that's...
The truth behind the Water Festival, right?
Kanata.
Found you, Rio-senpai!
Oh, really? Sorry, I was thinking about things.
Is it about the Maidens of Flame?
You heard from Naomi, right?
Yes.
What's your opinion?
I've been asking people about their dreams all day today.
Everyone has a wonderful dream.
That's why I think...
That even if I don't know what really happened before,
if this town and its citizens are here full of dreams, thanks to the Maidens of Flame, then it's just splendid.
Even if people aren't clear about the truth,
they can vaguely feel it.
That's why they're holding the festival with feelings of gratitude and guilt.
Dreams huh?
That's right.
The present exists because there's a past.
And it's also because the present exists that we can believe in tomorrow to pursue our dreams.
A Tomorrow...
Oh yeah! I still have something here for you, senpai.
Here you go.
This is...
Klaus-san needs you to sign the receipt, otherwise, he can't go back.
I see, sorry to bother you with that.
You really are a princess, senpai!
Even receiving a letter from the Emperor himself, that's so awesome!
Say, Kanata...
The world is coming to an end. Did you hear about that?
I heard about it, more or less...
But even so, war is still raging.
Perhaps, for now, there might be a temporary peace between Rome and Helvetia,
but there's also Gallia and the Franks next to Rome, and the western superpowers.
A lot of country are still overshadowed by the war.
They're fighting each other to claim the few remaining land of the humanity,
reducing the already dwindling population!
Remaining land...?
This is...?
This is your first time seeing this, right? It's a world map.
It's been drawn in Rome.
Because there are undiscovered or unreachable areas,
there are plenty of places that are pure speculation.
Here is Helvetia.
It's so tiny!
And you see this vast land... It was once the bulk of the Eurasia Continent.
It has now become a death zone, a "no man's land".
Moreover, this "no man's land" is still expanding.
Around Seize's border, the situation is still alright,
but the north of Rome is continuously being eroded by the desert.
It's predicted that Rome will be completely engulfed by the desert.
I went to Rome by marriage and witnessed with my own eyes...
that the world is really doomed.
We should stop the war as soon as possible...
Before the world is ruined.
So... That's your dream, senpai?
"To make the world peaceful."
Nope.
I would say, this is a...
Well, in Misio's words,
"an objective."
Then, how about your dream, senpai?
You wanna know?
O-k-a-y!
Got it!
Noël-chan!
Roger that.
It's floating...
It seems to be going well.
Well done, Noël-chan!
Marvelous...
It's really amazing! Look at that, senpai!
Takemikaduchi's become so tiny!
And the town!
This is the first step of my dream.
When I was small, I heard from my mother.
Somewhere at the end of this world, there is an ocean of revival,
a piece of land that nurture new lives.
I want to seek that place out.
Starting with this balloon.
Next, I would like to recreate an aeroplane.
The machine that helped man fly in the sky like birds in the old ages.
And then move forward.
To the end of the world, or even further away!
Further away from the end of the world...?
It's just a dream for now.
Just a rough blueprint.
But one day I will, step by step, make this dream come true!
Now, let's determine the Maiden of Flame of this year.
Please don't do it by lucky draw!
Why is that?
Think about last year...
What's wrong?
How about doing it by Rock-paper-scissors?
Let's make it in one turn.
Let's roll!
Cha-chan.
Wow! You look nice, Kana-chan!
Oh really...?
Then, let's finish up the dressing.
For the Maiden of Flame
You have been here for a year...
Time really flies...
Rio-senpai... I have decided on my dream...
Can I be your follower forever?
Because we share the same dream...
Sure!
Thank you very much!
"Want to follow... my dream?"
Ah, I've just written this.
May I have a look?
Please take your time.
That I become a military doctor to save lots of lives...
"I want to be a military doctor and save lots of lives."
In the past, my elder sister was my idol...
But now...
Wow, that's really cool!
My mom was a medic...
When Aisha was shot, I was so ashamed for not being able to lend a hand as my mom's daughter.
You will be able to do it, Kureha-chan!
And so will I.
A lovely wife
"I want to be a lovely bride"...
It's fine. You will be able to do that, Noël-chan!
That's right! There must be someone who loves strange stuff.
Oh really? That's nice!
I've got my own dream.
What have you written down?
I wrote "I want to stay with you all forever."
That's dull...
That's cruel!
So, that you will also be able to find yours and move forward someday.
The dream that only belongs to you.
But it's okay. Until that day, I will hold your hand and walk alongside you.
Until you've found the dream meant only for you.
Until you start to play the music that belongs only to you.
I can hear it.
The steps of a dream. The sound of the future.
Just go ahead,
as I will be staying here...
So that you can come back from wherever you will go to.
Felicia...
Rio-senpai!
Come here, Rio-senpai!
Let's go! To the world we dream of!
Even if the world will be ruined one day...
Before then, that's our future.