Tarou...
It says there's medicine
in the emergency shelter.
Who's there?
Yuki-chan?
Yuki-chan, what's wrong?
Mii-kun!
Mii-kun, get back in the club room!
Senpai?
Hurry!
School Living Club
#11
Scar
Don't worry. I locked the door.
No one will get in.
I-It's okay. It'll be all right.
At this rate...
SCHOOL ONLY
Staff Emergency Evacuation Manual
Right.
I need to get the medicine.
Medicine...
If it works on humans,
maybe Taroumaru can also be...
Yuki-senpai.
What?
This isn't like you.
Mii-kun?
Please, say something silly
like you always do, okay?
Tell me something fun.
Huh?
Something silly?
That's mean, Mii-kun.
It is?
You have no "biscuit" for your senpai.
You mean "respect"?
Right, you have no risu (squirrels).
When Kurumi-chan gets better,
let's go on another club outing.
And I want to go to the ocean with
everyone, instead of the pool.
In fall, I want to eat roasted sweet potatoes.
And when winter comes,
we can go skating or skiing.
I hope we'll get some good snow this year!
Hmm, and then...
I want to go biking with Kurumi-chan,
and shopping with Rii-san,
and go out to eat yummy food with you...
Oh, and Taroumaru too, of course.
And Megu-nee...
Megu-nee...
Mii-kun?
I'm going.
Yuki-senpai, don't leave this room.
Mii-kun!
I'll go with you.
Absolutely not.
If Taroumaru comes back and
there's no one here, he'll be sad.
They don't seem to be drawn to the
room now that the lights are out.
Lock the door as soon as I'm out, okay?
Naoki Miki is heading out now.
Mii-kun...
I should go with—
No way...
I didn't know it was so heavy...
And all this time, Kurumi-senpai has been...
If I get infected, don't hesitate for a second.
Promise me.
Sports Meet
Before I even realized it,
they had given me so much.
Fun things.
Kindness.
Are
you
okay?
Hope.
I can't lose now.
Please, help me...
Kei.
Stay calm, but hurry!
Don't panic, but hurry!
Hey, Rii-san.
Rii-san?
Sorry, were you asleep?
What's wrong?
Nothing... I just wanted someone to talk to.
I've been driving like a maniac,
yet the two of them are out cold.
They must be exhausted.
We should let them sleep.
This car got pretty beat up, though.
You think Megu-nee will forgive me?
Don't worry. I'm sure Megu-nee understands.
Are you sure you didn't want to visit home?
Your house was close to the mall, wasn't it?
Do you think they...
You know, the ones that are
always milling around outside.
Yes.
Do you think they're still... aware?
Well... What do you think?
I don't think so.
Why not?
Because I can't stand to think otherwise.
All those people I knew,
people who were friends, and I...
But I had no choice, right?
There was nothing else I could've done...
So please, remember that
promise you made to me.
You're the only one I can ask.
I know...
I'll keep my promise.
Taroumaru....
You're Sakura Megumi-sensei, right?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Naoki Miki, the new
School Living Club member.
I've heard a lot about
"Megu-nee" from the others.
They talk about how kind and
supportive you always were.
You didn't want to end up hurting them, right?
That's why you've been down
here... all this time...
But they're okay now.
Yuuri-senpai's always thinking ahead,
acting like a big sister to everyone.
Yuki-senpai's constant cheerfulness
keeps our spirits up.
And Kurumi-senpai... Kurumi-senpai's
always there when we need her.
If it hadn't been for you,
I wouldn't be here, either.
The four of us take care of each other,
living here at school as best we can!
So, please...
Rest in peace.
Warning. Warning.
Due to loss of power, the shelter
has switched to emergency power.
The medicine's in here somewhere.
Kurumi           Yuki            Rii
Medical Supplies
Are these handprints...
Emergency Supplies
Tranquilizers, antibiotics, experimental
vaccine for newly-infected...
This is it!
Now we can save Kurumi-senpai.
Sakura-sensei, I promise
I'll save Kurumi-senpai.
Kurumi           Yuki            Rii
LIVE
Excuse me!
Please let me through!
Wait!
Where are you all going?
Hey, wait!
Don't leave me!
Takeya-san?
What are you yelling about?
Megu-nee...
Not Megu-nee. It's Sakura-sensei.
Right...
Now go on into the classroom, please.
But everyone...
Everyone's already inside.
Oh, okay!
I'm here, everyone!
What was that?
No...
There's no time for this.
Was that...
If I don't get the medicine to her soon,
Kurumi-senpai will...
Isn't there any way out?
It's just like in that room...
Why?
I thought I escaped from there.
Is this where it ends?
Am I going to die alone in a
tiny room like this, after all?
No way out, no sign of help coming...
Just like in that mall.
I can't do it! Help! Someone help!
Kei!
I'm sorry.
Taroumaru!
Kurumi-senpai... Yuuri-senpai... Yuki-senpai!
What's wrong?
I have to go.
Something tells me if I don't,
the School Living Club is finished.
I see.
Then you should head for
the broadcasting room.
The broadcasting room?
Then you can save Miki-san...
No, you may be able to save them all.
Okay, got it!
It's heavy!
This way.
It looks like no one's left around here.
I heard a loud siren earlier...
They must have headed toward that.
Hey, Megu-nee, will I ever see them again?
Or are they...
We've made a lot of progress, but we're a
long way off from securing an escape route.
I know. The first floor's going to take a while.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
No one's blaming you.
I'm clumsy, and I'm not that strong.
I'm slowing you all down
just by being here, aren't I?
I'm just a burden, aren't I?
No, that's not true at all.
There are good things about
you that no one else has.
You have a lovely smile. It gives us all strength.
Really?
Of course!
I always feel better when you're around.
And the same goes for the others.
So promise me, no matter what
happens, you'll keep smiling.
And I'll always be watching over you.
Always?
Yes!
Then I'll try! I'll try super hard!
Hey, smiling isn't something you "try" to do.
True.
Oh, yeah...
Yuki-chan.
Megu-nee?
Let me go!
Yuki-chan, stop it!
Megu-nee's still outside! We have to hurry!
It's too late!
Megu-nee! Megu-nee!
Yuki-chan...
Megu-nee!
You're almost to the broadcasting room.
Are you okay? Are you scared?
I'm really scared.
But I've kept my eyes closed to
the scary things all this time,
and had the others take care of the hard stuff.
I don't think I can do that anymore,
or I'll lose everything that's important to me.
That scares me a lot more.
Yuki-chan, always remember
the promise you made to me.
No matter what happens.
Okay. I'll never forget, Megu-nee.
Megu-nee!
Bye-bye, Megu-nee.
Next Time!!
The sports meet where we all had fun.
The club outing we went on together.
The swimming contest in the rooftop pool.
They're all our precious memories!
Next time on the final episode
of SCHOOL-LIVE, "Graduation."
#12
Graduation
Write 100 pages each
I can't write that much!
See you next time.