The person you have called is
currently away from the phone.
Please leave a message after the beep.
U-Uh, Kushieda?
About the party tonight...
Ryuji, you there?
- Hey! Open the window! Ryuji!
- I'll call again later, but you have to come!
- Ryuji!? Hello!?
- I promise it'll be fun. Bye!
Took you long enough!
What were you doing!?
Uh, explain yourself first.
Take this!
What was that for!?
- Stop screwing around!
- Shut up and open it.
You'll understand once you do.
I need to get ready, so I'll
be there in half an hour.
See ya.
Hey!
What, what? What's up, yo?
(My Silky Love)
Every time I think of you
MY SILKY LOVE nijuu yojikan zutto
(My Silky Love)
for 24 hours straight,
MY SILKY LOVE kimino koto omoutabi
(My Silky Love)
It only makes me feel
MY SILKY LOVE modokashii kono kimochi
(My Silky Love)
that much more impatient.
MY SILKY LOVE tada afure kaetteku
It's so simple just to say I love you.
But when you come close to me,
sukito ieba kantan nanoni
kimiga maeni kichauto
my own emotions go awry
and get in my way.
kyaraga sobie watashino
koto wo jamashiteru
I can bring myself to do anything.
That's who I'm supposed to be.
itsumonaraba tsuyoki de ikeru
sonna seikakunanoni
But I just can't break this
wall down no matter what.
donna ganbatte mitemo kabewa kuzusenai
Please understand these feelings for you.
sasshite hoshii kono kimoch iwo
That's why these gazes of mine,
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimini
they tell my love for you.
daisuki dayoto okuru shisen
Now gather up my courage!
saidaino yuukide
A fragile heart made of silk,
yabure souna shirukuno haato
I realized that by meeting you,
kimini atte kizuita yatto
I was so clumsy when it comes to love.
ainiwa bukiyou dattan datte
A forgotten scar left in my heart,
wasure kaketa koino kizuato
and I suddenly felt it sting deep inside.
kyuuni uzuki dashitano kyunto
I have to say that I love you someday...
itsukawa watashi rashiku sukito iwanakya
Or it'll keep making me weaker.
imayori yowaku nacchauyo
Coming!
Christmas Eve Party
Wow!
Stunning!
You're absolutely adorable, Taiga-chan!
Ryu-chan, come check this out, yo!
R-Right...
Ryu-chan, you look fabulous, yo...
Whew, it fits perfectly.
I-Is it really okay for me to b-borrow this?
You aren't borrowing it.
I'm giving it to you.
You're what!?
But it's got R. Aisaka embroidered inside!
Isn't this your old man's?
He left it behind because it doesn't fit.
Just remove it.
It's not funny to have to wear a
hand-me-down from that guy.
If you won't wear it, I'll
have to throw it away.
It's like you were born to
do these little chores.
You told me to remove it.
Evidence goes!
Poo-Poo-Poo...
Poof.
Why can you say that,
but not your own name?
Okay!
Magical Girl Ya-chan is going
to cast a spell on you, yo!
A spell?
Don't touch it.
By the time the party starts,
this will have mixed with your
scent to make a soft aroma.
And now for Ryu-chan...
Here.
Did this belong to my old man?
Nope, yo.
Long ago, when I ran away from home,
I grabbed anything that could be sold.
So this belonged to Grandpa?
Yep, yo!
St-St-Sto...
Stolen?
Here, you'll catch a cold.
This is some crowd.
How many people came?
Doesn't matter. You only have
one thing to worry about.
Got it?
You have a mission tonight.
R-Right...
Oh!
Miss Yuri-chan's all decked out!
So, you're not coming to the party
because you have a date?
Nope.
I'm going to a real estate
seminar for single women.
A real estate seminar?
Yep. I'm going to buy a condo.
But why tonight?
Because women who are out on
dates on Christmas Eve...
lack the willpower to commit.
They won't be ready to act when the
ideal property appears on the market!
Oh...
Um...
I'm interested in learning about
the housing tax credit, so I'm off.
Please try to stay out of trouble.
Yes, ma'am...
Oh...
Um, hello.
I'm glad you were able to fix the tree.
And your grades improved too.
That makes me happy.
Thank you.
I'm sure your hard work will pay off.
Thanks, and I'm sure you'll
find an excellent property.
A wonderful single life awaits.
Um, yeah...
Thanks...
Good evening, everybody!
I thank you for coming to this
Christmas party hosted by
the Patron Saint of Broken Hearts!
We ran into some trouble along the way...
but we've managed to get everything going.
Don't say anything. You'd be playing into it.
Everyone!
I want to thank you for your cooperation!
I hope you're all able to
fully enjoy this night!
So without further ado...
Are you ready?
Let's celebrate Christmas Eve!
Merry Christmas!
Ooh, drumsticks!
I know what this is!
Turkey, right?
No, it's chicken.
There you go.
Delicious.
Now this is what I call chicken turkey.
Uh, right...
Whoa!
Nanako!
There's cake over there!
No way!
Where!?
In that corner.
Wanna go?
For sure!
Kihara's hot pants and Nanako-san's
modest dress... So hot...
Man, why's everybody so dressed up?
I look so drab.
Hell, seedy even.
Hey there!
Watch where you're walking!
You'll make the floor all sticky!
Um, sorry.
Scary...
Takasu.
So this is where you've been.
What are you doing?
I got so irritated by the horrible job
they were doing that I just...
Whoa, I didn't know you owned a fancy suit.
Must be nice.
Your hands are covered with
fried chicken grease!
Oh, didn't anyone tell you?
This is called turkey!
- Chicken turkey, that is!
- Kaoru, you're late.
Oh, sorry.
Hmm? What's over there?
Nothing.
Oh, hey...
I haven't seen Ami-chan!
Isn't she here?
Y-Yeah, probably...
I think I caught a glimpse of her.
No way! Was she smokin'?
In what way?
I don't see her here right now.
Same goes for Tiger.
Tiger, huh...?
Nothing against her, but I prefer Ami-chan.
Good question. Where'd she go...?
It's Christmas. Give me your smiles.
A party night delivered to you.
It's Christmas. Give me your wishes.
On this holy, holy night, I pledge to you.
Ami-chan and Tiger?
Whoa! Incredible!
This year's Christmas is special.
Even though it's not a White Christmas.
- The light from stardust falls to the ground.
- When did they have time to practice this?
It twinkles and brings happiness to everyone.
It blinks, flashes, and
gives dreams to us all.
It's Christmas. Give me your smiles.
A party night delivered to you.
It's Christmas. Give me your wishes.
On this holy, holy night, I pledge to you.
U-Uh, Kushieda?
About the party tonight...
Ryuji, you there?
- Hey! Open the window! Ryuji!
- I'll call again later, but you have to come!
- Ryuji!? Hello!?
- I promise it'll be fun. Bye!
Man, that was great...
Ami-chan and Tiger were so sexy-cute!
Here.
Thanks.
Uh, Takasu?
How long you gonna stand there?
Oh, yeah...
My dream actually came true!
Isn't this completely different?
Well, the sexy-cute part is close enough.
Oh-ho?
In that case...
Am I sexy-cute!?
Sick!
Nasty-sick!
- H-Hey!
- Whoa! I am not part of this!
Damn, you sick exhibitionist.
Maruo!
What are you doing?
Oh, Kihara.
Am I sexy-cute?
Huh?
Um...
Wouldn't that be considered
sexual harassment?
Payback time!
And another!
Could I have some fruit punch?
Yeah, sure.
Kawashima...
Here you are.
Yeah, somehow ended up here.
So? How was the song?
Really great!
When'd you have time to practice?
It wouldn't have been a surprise
if we hadn't kept it secret.
So, was it?
Yeah, you had me completely fooled.
I see.
That's good.
By the way, where's Taiga?
She worked hard, so I should
take her some fruit punch.
She left.
You didn't know?
N-No...
Really?
You didn't notice?
She said she was stopping
by Minori-chan's place.
Her plan's to drag Minori-chan here
before going home herself.
She said something about needing
to get ready for Santa.
Why would she do that?
Why did she leave?
Beats me. Maybe she doesn't
want to see what'll happen?
Well, I did warn you.
About what?
To stop this childish game.
Why are you playing daddy?
Forget it.
Hey, Kawashima?
Honestly...
He won't even listen to me...
The lovely angel Taiga is willing
to shed a layer or two...
or even go buck naked in order to
bring everyone a happy Christmas!
Are you really okay with that?
I want to be a good girl and
be a part of the happiness.
Another happy face lighting
up the Christmas night.
Takasu, could you give
me some fruit punch?
I burned too many calories...
Kitamura.
I'm stepping out real quick.
Hey, Takasu!
This can't be right!
Really?
Kushieda
Are you...
Are you sure?
Yep.
Ryuji is waiting for you to come.
He said he won't go home until he sees you.
He's prepared to stay all night.
Sorry, Minorin.
But you don't actually hate him, right?
I can tell, since we're friends.
I'm supposed to know these things.
Santa isn't coming...
Guess it's no use if I'm a good
girl just around Christmas.
It's not like Santa actually exists.
That's why I'm alone again this year.
And why I'll be alone again next year.
And the next...
And every year after that,
with no one to cling to.
All alone...
No one to cling to?
What's that?
It's coming from the bedroom.
Sa—
Santa?
H-Hold on!
You're so heavy!
Are you really Santa?
What the heck?
Hey!
Over here!
Look!
Santa!
That's my Christmas tree!
I know, right?
Yay!
I knew this would be great!
Awesome!
Santa liked my Christmas tree!
This is real...
Wow...
My dream...
My dream...came true.
Thank you...
Thank you.
I mean it.
Thank you, Ryuji...
D-Don't take that off, dummy! Give it back!
So?
Where'd you find the suit?
I borrowed it.
And what happened to your other suit?
As I was about to say, I traded it with
the person who was wearing this.
I'll get it back later, of course.
N-Naturally...
You picked the worst possible
time to take that suit off.
Man, you're such an idiot!
A complete buffoon!
After I set everything up so
you'd be able to see Minorin!
Why are you calling me names?
Didn't I tell you to have faith
in the lovely angel Taiga?
Minorin should be on her way to the party.
She might even be there already.
C'mon. If you hurry, you can
still make it in time!
But...
I already changed into this, and
I don't want to leave you all alone...
What are you saying?
I'm just fine.
A make-believe Santa came to see
a make-believe good little girl.
It was lots of fun!
Oh, and I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
Even if everything goes well with Minorin,
we're still having a Takasu
family Christmas dinner.
With lots of chicken!
And lots of beef!
Uh, we're avoiding chicken
because of Inko-chan...
Then beef will do.
Get a move on!
Hurry!
B-But...
If you don't go to the party,
that'd mean I lied to Minorin!
Get going!
Hey!
I said to hold on!
Santa already came!
That means I have to be good
for the rest of the year!
So...let me be a good girl.
My real present was getting
Minorin to go to the party.
So please...
Accept it.
Tai—gah!
Mush, you slow pup.
Thanks!
Whew, he finally left...
I forgot to return this.
Ah, what a pain...
Huh?
Why am I...?
Oh, I see.
I've been clinging to Ryuji...
To his kindness...
But it's over now.
I'm sure Minorin will be drawn to Ryuji.
And he's truly in love with her.
Which means...
the feelings are mutual.
So from now on...
I can't be with Ryuji...
I can't walk next to him...
I can't be the one by Ryuji's side...
And I don't...
I don't...want that.
Ryuji...
Ryuji!
Ryuji... Ryuji...
Ryuji...
Ugh...
Now I've done it.
I don't have my cell phone.
And my present is still in
the other suit pocket.
What am I supposed to do?
That's a nice bear.
Hey.
Oh.
Th-Thanks...
Um...
Ku-Kushie—
Takasu-kun.
Sorry, let me go first.
Huh?
Say...
Do you remember the talk
we had that one night,
when we were at Amin's
beach house last summer?
About weird stuff, like ghosts and UFOs...
Y-Yeah...
Well, Takasu-kun...
I'm pretty sure I don't need
to see ghosts or UFOs.
It's probably better that way.
I've been doing a lot of thinking lately,
and that's the conclusion I reached.
I just wanted to let you know.
That's why I came.
Kushieda...
Sorry to be so pushy.
I should go.
What?
That's it?
Hold on...
Was I just...shot down?
It's Christmas. Give me your smiles.
saa CHRISTMAS ippaino egao
A party night delivered to you.
kimi ni todokenda PARTY NIGHT
It's Christmas. Give me your wishes.
saa CHRISTMAS ippai no negai
On this holy, holy night, I pledge to you.
kimi ni chikaunda HOLY HOLY NIGHT
This year's Christmas is special.
kotoshi no kurisumasu kitto tokubetsu sa
Celebrating alone won't be fun at all.
ronrii kurisumasu ja tsumaranai
Your smiles are ever illuminating.
Let's keep their light glowing.
egao wa irumineshon hora kazatte ageru
We hold hands and swing
them back and forth.
yurayura yurameite minna de tewo tsunagi
We'll gaze up at the stars as they twinkle.
pikapika kirameite minna de hoshimiage
It's Christmas. Give me your smiles.
saa CHRISTMAS ippai no egao
A party night delivered to you.
kimi ni todokenda PARTY NIGHT
It's Christmas. Give me your wishes.
saa CHRISTMAS ippai no negai
On this holy, holy night, I pledge to you.
kimi ni chikaunda HOLY HOLY NIGHT
Stay Like This Forever
Shot down by Kushieda...
Whenever I close my eyes—
Takasu-kun!
Hey-yo, man!
I can hear her usual cheerful voice.
And, whoosh!