Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
I want you to keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Everyone is waiting for me to be
the energetic me that I was before.
Too many sad things happened,
and I closed my eyes and
stopped seeing anything,
and caused people nothing but worry.
But nobody wants to see me crying, do they?
My smile... That's right! Smiles!
Not just mine, but everybody's!
I'll aim for a stage with no
battles and lots of smiles! I will! I will!
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Don't make me laugh!
What do mean, you don't want to battle?!
You're just running away
from the competition, that's all!
You coward!
You should think carefully about how
much your attitude just now hurt May.
There are times when you can
hurt someone by not fighting too.
Maybe it's just like Miss
Layla said. Maybe I hurt May.
But even if that's true,
I still won't battle onstage anymore.
My dream is to create the fun
Kaleido Stage that I saw when I was little.
I won't ever lose sight of my dream again.
Someday, with everyone working
together, we'll create it for sure.
May and Mr. Leon, too...
Mr. Leon?
Sophie... I'm so glad...
I've never seen Mr. Leon's eyes look so kind.
I wonder who "Sophie" is...
"An Amazingly Humiliating Performance."
Sophie...
Partner?
Nobody can be Leon's partner.
Nobody but her.
She must be who that woman was talking about.
What does that mean, that she's
the one who could be Leon's partner?
Why did he call her name
while he was looking at Sora?
So she's the one after all...
Okay, break a leg everybody!
Thanks!
Sorry to make you do this, Sora.
No, no, this is my job right now.
Ask me for anything.
The person who can become
my partner is Sora Naegino.
Um, Mr. Leon, today they're letting
me help scatter the flower petals.
I'll scatter them really hard...
no, that's weird...
I'll scatter with all I've got...
no, that's the same thing...
Anyway, let's make this
a great show! Okay, see you!
I won the World Festival and Sora withdrew.
Right now I'm the top star, and Sora is a gofer.
Sora ran away from the
competition yesterday too.
I've won the competitions, but
Sora is still always there in front of me.
Hey, Leon, who is Sophie?
Is this "Sophie" someone
who could become your partner?
I don't know how amazing she is, but
I've got confidence that I can surpass her!
I'll prove I can do everything that she can do!
I'm the one who can become your partner!
The world's acknowledged my skill.
I'll beat Sora and Sophie!
You can't.
Why not?!
If you don't know why not,
you won't even be able to
beat Sora, let alone Sophie.
You won't even be able to
What's wrong with me?
What's Sora got that I haven't got? What?
Adjust the timetable. Plus thirty seconds.
May's even worse than she was yesterday.
Yes.
Um, Mr. Leon, today they're letting
me help scatter the flower petals.
What?
Whoa.
Come.
Huh?
Wait...
Please stop this, Mr. Leon.
Release all the trapezes.
Yes, ma'am!
I'm going back.
Please let me go back.
No.
You've finally come onstage, haven't you Sora?
Let's finally settle things today!
Stop it.
Wait!
The audience is unsettled. This is no good.
Right now, I have to perform.
So are you in the mood to do this now?
Is this part of the show?
It's kind of amazing.
You won't even be able to
beat Sora, let alone Sophie.
I want to win... I want to win.
I want to win against Sora!
Hey, May's not looking half bad!
She's so passionate, it's like she's
trying to take Romeo's love by force!
I've never seen a Juliet like this!
And Sora's performance is so energetic
it's like May's ferocity can't even touch her!
She looks like she's enjoying being onstage!
I'll fall...
I can hear it... I can hear
the audience's voice...
I'm so happy.
That's the Angel's Maneuver
that I saw at the festival...
Leon's acting has changed!
Leon...
He's acting so kind. Is it an act?
Did I lose again?
Mr. Leon, I'm going back.
Please continue the show with May as Juliet.
Sophie.
Please, wait!
Don't go!
Mr. Leon!
This is bad!
They say Leon will need to be in
the hospital for two or three weeks.
Although you could say his injuries are
only this minor because he's so lightweight.
So we're shutting ourselves
down for a month, huh?
I hope that's the worst of it.
Our saving grace is that Ken turned the lights
off so the audience didn't see the moment he hit.
Is the Kids' Stage shut down too?
Looks like it.
We showed the audience a
performance that wasn't fun.
It's not your fault, Sora.
Even monkeys fall from trees.
Even Leon falls from trapezes.
Hurry, Sora! The air feels good.
Right.
You're right! It does feel good.
Told you.
May.
Things kind of got out of control, didn't they?
Did you visit Mr. Leon in the hospital?
I'm not going to go now.
Because I'm not Leon's partner yet.
Do you know who "Sophie" is?
No...
Sophie's probably the only person in
the world who can become Leon's partner.
And Leon's seeing you as Sophie.
You, and not me.
I wonder why...
I mean, my contract was terminated,
and I'm not even allowed onstage...
You probably remind him of her.
How dense you are, for instance.
You're so dense it's a crime.
You've beaten me this far into the ground,
and you haven't even noticed, have you?
I've beaten you into the ground?
Are you sure you haven't got that backwards?
You're dense!
Super dense!
Totally and completely dense!
Extra Special Dangerous Dense!
But I have to admit that
you've got something I haven't got.
I've decided to try being a little more humble.
I'll become demonically humble,
and then I'll surpass you
for sure and I'll scorn you!
See you later.
See you...
What was humble about that?
The insurance procedures and
various related things are going smoothly.
Okay.
Come in.
We've been waiting for you, Mr. Kenneth.
Shutting yourself down, eh?
Is this part of your plan, Kalos?
No.
Plan?
You, Boy.
My name is Ken Robbins.
How is Sora?
Sora thinks she's partly to blame for
what happened to Leon, so she's depressed.
Can't start running yet, eh?
No.
Perhaps expecting them to become
partners was too much after all.
We don't know that yet.
What happened today might trigger something.
That's true.
I suppose I'll watch how
things go for a little longer.
We'll see if Leon Oswald
can become Sora's partner.
Huh? They're questioning Leon and not Sora?
I believe that when that happens,
Kaleido Stage will grow along with Sora.
Please look forward to it.
What are they trying to make Sora do?
I wonder if Miss Layla and
Miss Cathy mean to go back to Broadway.
Yeah, the shows here got cancelled, but,
like, they don't look like they're going back.
It's like, they're really into Kaleido Stage.
Is, like, someone here?
Sora's a real mystery, isn't she?
It's like she's getting her real sparkle back while
none of the people around her are noticing.
I might be one of those people.
Oh really?
I may have made a mistake.
The totally sincere girl
who loves Kaleido Stage...
She jumped into this all alone,
with aspirations in her heart.
I entrusted that Sora with my dream.
I wanted her to reach the
faraway place that I couldn't get to.
I thought no matter how bitter and
cruel a path that was, Sora could succeed.
Because I don't think there's any
other path to becoming a real star.
But maybe I shouldn't have asked
for that kind of ruthlessness from Sora.
What do you think of May?
I'm the opposite: May's the
one who's got my sympathy.
May?
Yeah. May's got nowhere to go with
her feelings of idolization for you,
so she's taking everything
out on Leon and Sora.
Right now she needs someone to become
a goal for her and draw out her power,
but she doesn't have anyone.
If she needs a goal, her potential
future self should be the best goal.
That was always my goal.
Not everyone is as strong as you are, you know.
Miss Layla! You've got a guest!
There's a guest here to see you, Miss!
Um... Miss Layla, the truth is
I came because I want to ask you a favor.
You've retired from Kaleido Stage, so I don't
know if it's okay for me to ask this or not,
but I'd like you to train me!
I want to get hold of whatever
it is that Sora's got and I don't.
I want to change myself more!
So please!
Why not? We've got time, after all.
That's true. All right, then.
Thank you very much!
Sometimes it's nice to
have our tea out here, right?
Yeah. But it's so nice out,
shouldn't we ask Mia and Anna...
It looks like everyone is busy doing
things since we got a sudden vacation.
Oh.
You were really energetic onstage yesterday.
Mia and the others were saying so too.
To tell you the truth, somewhere
along the way I started having fun.
I thought so.
I thought, "The backstage job is fun too,
but maybe the stage is really where I belong."
That's what I think too.
When I heard the audience's voice yesterday,
I was so happy I really cheered up.
I felt like I was getting
strength from the audience.
Hey, the thing you did yesterday
was the "Angel's Maneuver," right?
Yeah.
Is it hard?
Yeah, I guess so.
Which part?
Huh? "Which part"?
Um, it's pretty much like,
when your power and your
partner's power go waaaah,
then all at once you jump up like shoom!,
but it kind of gets hmmmm,
and it's like there's no whoosh,
or I guess it's like yaaa! or zoom!,
so... do you basically get it?
Not at all.
I guess that figures.
Anyway, so it's really hard, right?
Yeah, especially since
I don't have enough of the basics,
so I caused Mr. Yuri a lot of problems.
Let's do a lot of basics work together, then.
No, it's getting late,
so let's all take a bath together and smooch...
It's still afternoon!!
Sora, you're so mean!
Is it bad to do basics work in the afternoon?
Oh! No, no, I was just talking to myself...
No good.
One more time.
Okay.
No good at all.
You can just create
whatever expressions you want.
Right.
No good.
Right now your audience
is Cathy. Do you understand?
Yes.
Continue, then.
Okay!
No good!
No good.
Ugh! No! No good!
Oh no! I overslept!
Tickets to Kids' Stage...
Welcome!
Ken! Why are you dressed like that?
No, wait, when did you learn to ride a unicycle?
Well, I originally wanted to
be part of the cast, you know.
I quit because of my weak heart,
but today is a special occasion.
Now! Welcome to the special
show created just for you, Sora!
Welcome to the Special Stage!
You haven't just enjoyed
watching a show for its own sake
since you came to Kaleido Stage, have you?
So be our audience today.
We all prepared for this in secret!
Sit back, relax, and enjoy this to the fullest!
And now! Let the special show for Sora begin!
Everyone...
Wow, Marion, Rosetta, that's great!
Ta-da!
You're really good, Jonathan!
Good job!
Amazing! Amazing!
That's right, Anna!
Yes!
You're a natural.
She's laughing! If I do it now, it'll work!
Tea!
Sorry.
That's right. I have precious friends.
The audience and the friends
I have here give me strength.
Jump!
With this power, I think
I can even become a real star...
A true Kaleido Star.
So I want to go back to the stage where
these people and the audience are waiting.
I want to go back,
and perform with all I've got!
I want to create a fun show with everyone!
Jump!
I love the fun Kaleido Stage. I really love it.
It seems Sagittarius has
finally regained its brilliance.
But a shooting star is approaching,
aiming for that brilliance.
Whose star is this?
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (favorite)
Harbor light (stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
"The Perfect Dating Manual:
100 Ways To Captivate Her Heart!"
And so, Ken invited me out to eat!
Hang in there, Ken!
Show us what a man you are!
It's time for bravery! Bravery!
That's right, you have to take the lead!
Right, Mr. Policeman?
Huh?! Huh?! Huh?!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Mr. Policeman's Amazing Proposal."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...