What?!
"Pedestrians and vehicles only"
You were playing WIXOSS until 4AM this morning?!
I showed it to Grandma,
and she got hooked on it...
Whoever lost had to peel
the strands off the tangerines, see?
It's all yellow!
Whoa, like, how many times did you lose?
Oh, I forgot. You don't
need to battle me anymore?
Yeah. I figured we can both be Eternal Girls,
so that we both can have our wish come true!
But, I don't have any wishes or dreams...
"Pedestrians and vehicles only"
--C'mon, let's run!
--Let's go.
W-Wait up!
The truth rests solely on
the front/back of a card
It has not yet been solved
Upon the dazzling, dizzying stage,
destroy those entangled emotions
as many times as it takes to satisfy you
What should the tomorrows
wandering after fate's beckoning
choose and discard so that
they can become one?
I can't afford to disclose my reproachable hand
The days spent draining
the already-dry sea of regret
desire within limited words forgiveness
for the unplanned smile
I don't mind forgetting reality
I don't want to know anything now
Okay?
You know, finding Selectors is a real pain.
There aren't many?
Yeah. At least in school,
you were the only one.
Right, Hanayo-san?
Yes, I can identify a Selector
just by looking at them.
LRIGs are attracted to each other.
For example, her over there...
What...?
"Special Winter Edition"
"Attractive wears that will beat the cold"
"Entire Issue★Cute&Cool"
Urazoe Iona?
She's really popular now.
Like, she appeared in dramas and it
looks like she'll put out a new song too.
The girl next to her is one too.
"Entire Issue★Cute&Cool"
Ah, I see her every so often in magazines too.
Her name was...
Akira!
Yeah, that's her! Huh...?
Like, seriously? The amateur model,
Akira, attends Gochu? Seriously...?
Wait? What did you say?
Can you say it again, please?!
Huh?
Yuzuki-san...
Better now than never!
I'll get first dibs and set up
a match after school, and then...
Isn't that... Akira?!
Wow... Her face is so small.
Almost like a tangerine...
All right! Here I go!
W-Wait please!
M-Me...
Please battle me...!
--What?!
She's...
...a Selector too?!
A-A-Are you both one too?
Who are these girls?
How rude. You girls can't
get an autograph from Akira.
Ah? N-No... I'm...
Thanks for rooting for me!
You want my autograph, right?
Let's go someplace else then. You girls too!
Let's go, Ruko!
Akira's too generous.
"Unauthorized Access Not Permitted"
Over here!
So many Selectors here!
Akira's so lucky! Aki-lucky!
Um, I...
So let's get a battle done
before class starts, okay?
First come, first serve!
I...
You're first, right? What's your name?
H-Hitoe...
All right! It's a starty-starty of a friendly
battle between Hitoe and Akira!
Open!
When a battlefield is opened, any Eternal Girl
candidates nearby are drawn into the world.
Hanayo-san!
Wh-What?!
Tama!
My hair's going to get all rumpled, Tama!
It's going to start!
I'll go first. Battle start!
Please, Midoriko!
Okay, leave it to me!
Aki-lucky's LRIG is Piruluk-tan!
Let's go and stompy-stompy them!
Understood.
A green deck, and a blue deck?
Hitoe may have the upper hand then.
Draw! Energy Charge please,
Midoriko-san! Grow!
And, I summon, Sparrow!
"Mystic Beast Sparrow" "SIGNI"
Sparrow, attack!
Yikes! That looks strong!
It worked...? If I can only just
Grow Midoriko-san smoothly then...!
That's so scary! Well, I guess
let's Grow then, Piruluk-tan?
I'm still scared! I wonder
what Hitoe has in her hand?
It's scary, so... let's have
Hitoe throw a card away!
I'm going to choose one of your cards,
okay? Can you toss it away?
Spell, Too Bad!
Let me see... I bet that it's a level 3 card!
Expose.
"Mystic Beast Owl" "SIGNI"
Bull's-eye! Aki-lucky!
The card! It vanished?!
It's one of the strategies for the blue deck.
They can force their opponent to discard a card.
No...
Piruluk-tan, Grow! And, let's freeze
Hitoe's Sparrow while we're at it!
Stop its movement.
Nice and frozen!
It's nighty-nighty until the next turn.
What should I do?!
"Mystic Beast Pandan"
I only have two more cards left... I can't...
Calm down, Hitoe!
Don't get too surprised yet! I can still
do a lot more, isn't that right, Piruluk?
Arts, Peeping Analyze.
I'll have you throw away all the cards of
the level that I'm going to say right now.
All?!
What should I pick...? Level one... Two...
This isn't good!
Her expression is giving it away!
Three... Four...
I got it... Throw away your level 4 cards!
It's a throw away festival, isn't it?
You know, while we're at it, let me guess
why Hitoe wants to be an Eternal Girl.
Poor girl...
She has no friends...
We've got a loner here!
Can I get your autograph?!
Hitoe! Not yet! The battle is
still going on! Don't listen to her!
She's horrible!
Yuzuki-san?!
I'm gonna stop this battle!
I know! I'll call from the outside, just like how
Kazuki did the last time to stop our battle!
--It won't work.
--Why not?!
Kazuki didn't stop the battle
the last time. It was the teacher.
It was an irregular because someone who
knew nothing about the cards stepped in.
And...
There's a huge penalty if the
battle is stopped on purpose.
What do you mean "penalty"?!
Akira's tactics are a lot worse!
She's not breaking any rules.
But...!
This battle's horrible...
But...
Tama?
Go, Piruluk-tan!
Hitoe!
I... don't have any Life Cloth left...
Don't give up yet! Guard the attack!
What's the use? I'm going to lose anyways...
Believe in me, Hitoe!
Hitoe...
Midoriko!
It's over... Akira won.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry... sorry...
Midoriko is the one in pain,
but I gave up... I'm really sorry...
Um...
Hitoe-san!
So, who's going to battle next?
Wait a min. Piruluk-tan?
Sleeping already?
Well then, let's battle tomorrow!
Here, let's share our email addresses!
I don't have a mobile...
No way! Super-rare! How about you then?
Well...
Yuzuki...
Sorry, but we have to run!
I won't let you go until
you share your address.
Ruko!
Were you scolded for being tardy?
I was told to stand in the hall, but then again,
I didn't have to take math class.
Aki-lucky!
Stop that.
There's no way I can beat a girl that good.
Well, but you still gave
her your address anyways.
What choice did I have?!
There's no way we could've gotten away!
I could battle Akira-san--
Don't worry.
As long as you don't agree to battle, it's fine.
Yeah, that's right...
I was watching from outside,
but Akira-san was really strong.
But that girl, Hitoe, was strong too.
I didn't know the Eternal Girl
candidates were this strong.
Am I able to win against all of them?
I know! Yuzuki, why don't
you update your deck?
My deck? You mean, go to the card shop?
Right. Is there a problem?
No...
I've never gone to one before. I want to go!
Okay, let's go together.
Okay!
I didn't know there was
a card shop around here.
You sure know a lot about cards, Kazuki-kun.
Yeah, I've always liked WIXOSS,
so I've been playing it for a while.
When I recommended it to Yuzuki,
her deck had Hanayo-san in it.
Right, Yuzuki?
Uh, right.
Here we are.
"CARD LUCK" "Trading Card Specialty Store"
"Dueling Space" "50 Seats Available"
Here?
"Tables Ready"
The place feels a bit... mature.
"Dueling" "Tables Ready"
Hey, Kazuki-kun!
A new series of WIXOSS just came in.
You're here too,
Yuzuki-chan! It's been a while!
H-Hello.
We wanted to update Yuzuki's deck.
Do you mind helping us?
Sure! I'll do anything to help Yuzuki-chan!
I mean, I love cute girls, you know.
Yuzuki-chan's deck is Red Ambition, so...
...it should cycle a lot better
with the Adamasphere.
Isn't the Adamasphere one of
the cards in the new series?
Right, but there are
no singles out on the market yet.
I can't get it to pull...
What about these cards?
It's a bit of a waste, but they
don't match well with Yuzuki's deck.
Well, do you mind if
I have just this card then?
Huh?
Just a hunch, but I think I can use
this card to search non-colored SIGNIs.
Correct! I'm surprised you
knew that. You're pretty good!
I guess we just have to wait
for a single to come out.
For now, you just have to
get better with the deck you got.
Okay, it's your turn, Yuzuki.
I'll draw this, and charge. Grow.
Wait a minute. Can you show me your hand?
You've stopped at level 2 again.
You can perform better if you
put strategy in Growing you know?
B-But...
This won't do. Your style of battle
is too straightforward, Yuzuki.
What's so wrong in being straightforward?!
Huh?
I... I'm going to bed!
Yuzuki?
Yuzuki is Kazuki's bride!
How cute.
"Yuzuki"
That's not good!
Sisters and brothers can't get married!
Everyone's going to say you're bad. Really!
Bad...
"STARCRAYONS"
Yuzuki-chan!
Straightforward battle...
Being straightforward... Being honest...
What's so bad about that...?
"Mail Received" "Akira"
Akira...
"Battle" "I can't wait to battle tomorrow!"
Battle tomorrow... Yuzu-pon or Ru-ru...
I can't lose...!
You wait here, Tama.
I feel so sorry for Hitoe-san...
But...
I wonder why... For some reason,
I want to battle Akira-san too.
But, that's not good, right? I mean,
everyone is fighting for their wishes.
Battle!
Would asking for Grandma to live
as long as she can be a wish too, Tama?
Huh? You're not with Kazuki-kun?
Yeah. He said he had to do something.
I see...
You're not going to get that?
She's kind of creepy.
This email says that she'll come to our school.
Ruko, let's stop by
someplace and then go home!
I guess that's okay...
"Karaoke Do Re Mi ♪"
Let's go in here.
Karaoke?
They're private rooms, and it'll
be hard for Akira to find us here.
But, I've never been to karaoke.
What should I sing?
Just figure it out when we get in.
Wait, no, no, no! These kinds
of things have to be set first.
I've got to strategize for the long term!
Strategize?
Yes, because... huh?
Kazuki...
Isn't that the person who
was working at the card shop?
Momoka-san, was it?
It looks like that something
had to do with Momoka-san.
Maybe it's a date--
Shut up.
Yuzuki-san?
Ruko, you're a bit... different.
Like not having any wishes and stuff...
You saw that horrible battle...
You also saw Hitoe hurt, but it
didn't seem to faze you at all...
Wait... I didn't mean...
I don't know what you're thinking, Ruko!
What I'm thinking...?
That's... probably... right...
P-P-P-
P-Please-!
P-Please battle me!
Huh?
I found you!
I wasn't sure what to do since
you were running all over the place.
Finding you here is so Aki-lucky!
Akira...
Now, let's battle. It'll be an Aki-rendezvous!
Let's have fun together! And...
...I'll beat you bad.
Sure...
I was looking for a way to get some stress off.
Nodding to the clockwork shadow
opens the door to the end,
bringing in the darkness
There we catch glimpses of the perilous answer
Today's prayer becomes taboo tomorrow
The upside-down maze reflects
the heavens and the earth
The gear begins to turn
Listen carefully among the masses
and that bell resounding in
the skies beckons the soul...
I must move forward even beyond eternity
Because it is the future I chose
The unreachable summer clouds
and flickering heat haze
One day I'll get back my place of smiles
I shouldn't win...
Piruluk-tan, look into her!
Tama? You...
Open!
The wind feels good.
"This Nonsensical Peace."