Mr. Niekawa, how's your daughter?
You know about Niekawa?
Yeah, in name only.
Just who is Niekawa Haruna...?
As if! Shizuo's way stronger than me!
You mean the one who started spamming
Ikebukuro-related message boards six months ago?
Run!
I love you very, very, very, very much, Shizuo.
Kadota, I'm borrowing your door.
So, who am I supposed to ask to pay for my door?
I told Shinra all about it once I returned home.
And that it was all over.
But it wasn't.
You could actually say that it was just beginning.
It turned into a long, long night.
I let Kadota and the others take care of the guy who'd lost consciousness,
and took the girl who was almost attacked back to her house.
It was that girl who's always with Mikado.
She wanted me to show her that I really didn't have a head—
So you did.
Like Mikado, she wasn't surprised at all.
Are all kids like that these days?
No, I don't think being young has anything to do with it.
Celty...?
Umm...who might you be?
Hello, Sonohara.
I'm Niekawa Haruna.
And so, I'm sorry to make you look up a bunch
of stuff about it, but the Saika thing is over.
Yeah, but, that's kind of anticlimactic...something doesn't seem right.
So, what are we going to do about him?
Let's start by calling an ambulance.
Something...
...about this doesn't seem right.
Why?
I'm going to Shinjuku for a bit to kill Izaya dead.
Hey, Shizuo definitely loves Izaya, doesn't he?
It's like a "boy's love" kind of thing—
That's definitely not it.
Well, they might be—
Stop it!
Just thinking about that makes me want to vomit.
Anyway, this is what's important.
Don't touch it. It might possess you.
This is Saika?
But, it's a knife.
I was surprised too, but the guy who was holding it had red eyes...
...talked like a woman, and said a bunch of
nonsensical stuff about love or something.
Love...?
I feel like I'd seen him somewhere before...
But, what does slashing people have to do with love, anyway?
Maybe Saika's a sadist?
I doubt it's the same as sadism.
Saika's purpose is to love people.
It's loved people for so long that it's stopped
loving individuals and now loves the whole species.
The entire human race...
I don't get it.
If it loves people, why does it slash them?
Hey, Sonohara.
Do you know why I've come to visit you?
Is it about...Mr. Nasujima?
Umm, I don't have anything to do with him.
It's just that there have been some weird rumors...
I'm sure that's true.
But, I love Takashi.
When someone loves another person, they
express that love through various behaviors, right?
Behaviors?
Like verbalizing it, holding hands, or embracing.
Um...were you two dating?
We weren't just dating.
We loved each other.
We were happy simply being able to confirm that love.
Yes, forever and ever and ever...
However, one day, he rejected me.
Even though all I did was try to express that love in a concrete form.
Express that love in a concrete form...?
What do you mean by that?
It wanted to express its love through its behavior.
But Saika is a sword.
Even if it wanted to love, it has no body.
So it took over people and—
And kept on slashing them.
Time after time after time...
...in order to verify its love.
To...express its love in a concrete form?
I was rejected by Takashi.
No, I don't hate him for it.
I mean, I love him.
Well, umm...
Even if he won't accept me, even if he comes
to like someone besides me, I can forgive him.
But...
I won't forgive the fact that he likes someone else.
Ever.
Five years ago, Saika disappeared.
But, as you can tell from its posts, it's still full of love.
Wait, Shinra.
I remember!
I've met that guy who had this knife!
He's a reporter.
His name is...
And yet, I shouldn't use other people after all.
This is proof that to be loved, you have to make a move all on your own.
I thought my father would do much better than all the others...
But he didn't.
That's why I'm going to settle things myself.
With you, my rival in love.
That...That man was your father...?
He's Niekawa Shuji, the guy who was slashed in front of his own house.
I wonder what's up with that.
Are you alright?
You...don't feel like you're being possessed or anything, do you?
No, I'm fine.
This isn't Saika.
I mean, look.
How could an ethereal sword that's been on
record for decades have been made in 2009?
What's going on?
I definitely... Please believe me!
I believe you, Celty.
Like I'd ever doubt you.
Maybe that Niekawa guy knew about the
Saika legend and was just copycatting it.
Or maybe—
More importantly, if this isn't Saika, then...
There must be other Saikas.
Right now, somewhere, possessing people and slashing them.
Oh yeah, what about the chat room? What's happening with that?
But I don't have any feelings for Mr. Nasujima...
It doesn't matter what you think of Takashi, Sonohara.
I'm just doing what's right for my love.
I don't love you, but this thing right
here, Saika, will do a good job of loving you.
I failed. I failed.
My sister was...
There are more Saikas...
Infinitely more...
If we had to analyze the situation, we could make only one hypothesis.
Imagine this, Celty:
What do you want after you've loved someone to the fullest extent?
I don't know. Isn't that enough?!
What if you were human?
Next, you'd want something that you could both love.
It couldn't be...
Yes, Saika can breed.
It impregnates the souls of the people it slashes.
Wait a minute.
We should log this chat.
You're going to find Shizuo, right?
IIIzaaayaaa!
Leeet's gooo haaang ouu—
Why're you here, Shizu-chan?
To punch you, obviously!
And why do I have to be punched?
Because you pissed me off.
T/L Note: "Gianism" originates from Doraemon. Basically, it's like a the-strongest-are-the-only-one-that-should-be-heard philosophy.
You shouldn't be spouting one hundred
percent Gianist crap at your age, Shizu-chan.
Shut up!
Just how involved in this are you?
What's all this coming out of the blue?
I'm talking about the Slasher incidents that have my city in an uproar.
What a horrible accusation.
If there's an incomprehensible and dangerous
event, ninety-nine percent of the time you're behind it!
Would you be nice enough to believe in the remaining one percent?
I figured you wouldn't.
I've looked up some things about you.
You're a pathetic excuse for a human.
You've been clinging to Harima Mika like a sycophant since middle school.
And you make eyes at any guy you pass.
Oh, that's right. I heard your parents were killed five years ago.
How do I get out of here?
You said you didn't see the perpetrator,
even though you were in the same room as your parents.
It's simple.
I should just think like I always do—that this has nothing to do with me.
There's no way you couldn't see that burglar.
I wonder why you're the only one who was spared?
Oh, I know. It's because you made eyes at him, too.
Even though you were only in elementary school...
Maybe he had a Lolita complex?
Right...?
It must be easy living like a parasite.
Since you get to leech off people.
It's not easy at all.
What?
It's not easy at all...being dependent upon others.
I think likening me to a parasite is a good analogy.
But, do you realize how much you have
to sacrifice just so you don't get removed?
So, you got Takashi to like you at your own expense?
No. Mr. Nasujima...
...wasn't worth it.
Huuuh.
I see.
Then, die.
A friend of yours?
This is great. I'll stab your friend right in front of you.
I'll deal with you after that.
Wow...
Celty? Why are you...?
What's this?
Did you plan this as well?
If I had the power to know when Celty was going to randomly show
up, I would've dropped a meteorite on your house a long time ago.
How can he be so keen despite being as dumb as a protozoan?
And that's why...I absolutely hate Shizu-chan.
Niekawa?!
Takashi!
Takashi! Takashi! Takashi!
I no longer have any time for you.
I'll just have everyone else kill you.
Everyone else...?
This really isn't the time for them to be dealing with you.
Since they still have something important to do.
I love...Shizuo...
Hey, Shinra. Just how many Saikas are
supposed to come to Southern Ikebukuro Park?
I don't know.
But, Celty...
One of them has to be the original Saika.
Just find that one.
Alright.
So that's the "mother."
I wanted to meet you, Heiwajima Shizuo.
You truly are a sight to behold.
It's just as our mother said;
Everyone knows that my sister was defeated.
The Internet's quite convenient, no?
The mother isn't here, then?
Why?
It was difficult in the beginning for us to learn to speak...
Now our consciousness is just as well defined as our mother's.
Well now, Shizuo, show all of us just how strong you are!
Then we'll all love each other!
We won't let anyone—not even that monster over there—interfere.
The police won't even come!
They're rather busy right now.
Because my sisters are out increasing our numbers all over the place!
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Why...do you like me so much?
Because you're strong.
We want your ridiculous strength...
So that we can love all of humanity.
Just like humans covet superior genes.
Besides, there's no human out there who'd love you, is there?
However, we'll love you.
Pull yourself together, Shizuo!
If you don't think you can do it,
I'll make it so that you can get away!
No, Celty. Actually, I'm happy.
I've hated this power so much.
I thought...no one would accept me for who I am.
However...
All these people—how many of you are there?
Well, we'll just say there are a lot.
So, I guess it's okay.
I guess it's okay to recognize my own existence now.
I guess it's okay to like myself now.
This power that I absolutely hated and wanted to rid myself of...
I guess it's okay to use all of it now.
By the way...
You guys definitely aren't, never have, and never will be my type.
Anyway, the only person I hate more than you is Izaya.
Shinra, there's something I've been wondering.
You said Saika disappeared five years ago, right?
Why is that?
What happened five years ago?
I doubt it was on vacation or anything...
There's a possibility that someone
strong could have been suppressing Saika.
Someone strong...
I've been thinking about you this whole time.
You reciprocated my love, didn't you?
You were even nice enough to use me for money,
And throw me away when you were done with me.
I accepted all that, forgave you, and loved you.
But, you know...it wasn't enough.
It got to the point where that just wasn't enough.
That's when Saika started talking to me.
Just like this...
If I were to give you my blood...little by little...
Hey...
Will today be the day...
...that you accept my love?
Wait!
Please stop it, Niekawa.
Stop hurting people with that blade...
How'd you get away?
Please stop it.
Whatever. I'm sure you had to be saved by someone again.
But I don't want to hear that from you, Sonohara...
From someone so weak she has to live off others like a parasite.
It's not like all I could do was depend on someone else to live.
I chose to live this way.
That's all.
Hmph, you're just splitting hairs.
I don't want you deciding whether people are
strong or weak based solely on how they live!
Hey, Sonohara, have you ever loved someone before?
It's impossible for you, isn't it?
There's no way you can understand me.
You know, I control this Saika with
the power of love. The power of love.
When it first told me to slash Takashi, I resisted with all my might.
But, after listening to it, I understood.
That's why Saika and I have become the mother.
We'll make tons and tons of children
and pass on our love! The power of love!
All to control the human race.
You're right that I can't love anyone.
Ever since that day five years ago,
I've been too scared to love anyone.
That's why I depend on others to live.
No way!
Just like you propagate Saika's children by slashing people,
your Saika is also a child of that blade.
This is the original.
I can't love anyone.
That's why I...
...rely on Saika to love people for me.
No...
I live by feeding off it!
That's a lie...that's the truth...
When a dismal past mixes with the present, she receives an incomparable power.
It was an incomparable routine.
Next Time: The Mutability of Life.