Master, there is no electricity.
Oh… Really…
If I do not recharge, I am unable to fly.
Does your stomach still hurt?
I’m sleeping because it hurts! Stupid.
The World Ramen Delicacy… What a fearsome thing.
Wow! That was pretty good!
Takamichi… This time I will really kill you.
By Lingshen.
What is this!?
What?
What’s wrong?
This is probably a radish...
and maybe a carrot…
Whaddya think?
The carrot wins?
Err… I don’t think that’s it.
Hm… Why don’t we try recovering all the scraps?
Hakase, I think it would be faster if we just made a new one.
Yeah. I guess we’ll do that then.
Anyway, I’ve got an idea.
Oh, what kind of idea?
I’ll explain it to you in a little while.
Come over here.
What in the world is the meaning of this?
It's really weird, isn't it?
Yeah.
There might be something going on.
What do they all have in common?
Figures; the prank's becoming way too long.
But wow, these veggies look pretty gross, don't they?
But when you’re hungry, they're really good!
Such a slow and stupid girl.
We haven’t washed that you know.
That’s no good, Ane-san.
The rat said I’m no good!
Hey, Makie-san!
I’m not a rat! I’m an ermine!
Owwie...
Hakase-san, Lingshen-san!
What's wrong?
Everyone! Please get out of here!
Mechacabra!
Version 2!
Didn’t it get destroyed?
Well, it suddenly moved on its own!
Even when the insides are empty!
Not even my kung-fu was good enough!
Aniki, that’s…
Yeah.
It’s possessed by the darkness!
Here it comes! The prank!
Ah, could it be that…?
Spiiiinny, spinny, spinny, spinny...
Everyone, please stay back!
Negi-bouzu! I want more power!
Lingshen-san...
Alright then.
Partner: Chao Lingshen.
Show me the power within you!
Contract,
Activate!!
Alright!! It’s an armor card!!
Go Lingshen!
Fight-o!
Now's your chance!
Now, Lingshen!
Go get 'em!
Alright!
Lingshen-san!
Note: Giacobini is the name of a comet, and a meteor storm named after it. That’s probably why Lingshen decided to call it a meteor punch. It’s not one punch, its lots of punches!
I call it the Giacobini Meteor Punch!
Note: Moe = burn up/get fired up. This is a pun on the vaguely defined moe from otaku slang.
So moe!
Flamey, flamey, flamey...
Looks like the Darkness is on the move again, Aniki.
Yeah. Let’s go talk to Takamichi about this.
Sensei.
I’ve solved the mystery.
Alright. Now the trap is complete, de gozaru.
Yay! It’s done!
Desu!
All we have to do is wait for the Bonge Bonge to come right?
I wonder if it'll show up or not...
We will lure it out!
With this!
Chupa Tee?
Does the Bonge Bonge like the Chupa Tee, de gozaru?
What are you saying?
He-llo, it's ONLY obvious that everyone loves a Chupa Tee, right?
It's obvious?
By the way, I’ve been thinking about this for a while.
Why do we have to catch the Bonge Bonge?
Ah, now that you mention it...
Hmm, I hadn't thought of that.
Asuna,
why do we have to?
Eh? Well, let's see... That's right...
For whatever reason, I guess.
Don’t ask a question you don’t know the answer to.
Oh well, that’s alright.
Come on everyone, hide!
The Bonge Bonge is coming! Quickly, quickly!
What the?
It’s here already!?
The Bonge Bonge?
No. From the size, it doesn’t look like it, de gozaru.
Stand back.
It’s the mechacabra desu!
It's wearing the Chupa Tee!
See? Everyone loves it!
Now's not the time for that!
Why is the mechacabra here!?
Is someone inside?
Ah, I bet it's Negi!
You annoying brat wanted to surprise us, right!?
I don't think that's it.
That is not Negi-sensei.
That mechacabra has a killing intent.
The solution is in the zodiac?
That’s right.
Alright,
The first ones to be possessed were Yuuna-san,
Kaede-san,
and Chiu-Chiu-chan.
These 3 are all Sagittarius.
Wait a minute! I'm not a Sagittarius; I was born on February 2. That's Aquarius!
I’m on June 1st, so I’m Gemini.
But those are based on the Solar Zodiac, right?
I’m talking about the Lunar Zodiac.
The Lunar Zodiac?
I’ve never heard of it.
Aniki, know anything about it?
Yeah. Onee-chan said something about it once before.
In astrology, all the stars including the sun exist in the zodiac.
That’s right. In other words, in lunar astrology, Yuuna-san and Chiu-Chiu-chan are also Sagittarius.
Wait! Stop calling me "Chiu-Chiu"!
Stop breaking into a sweat about it, Ane-san!
I see. This is very interesting.
Please continue your story, Chizuru-san.
Okay.
The next ones to be possessed are Makie-san, Mana-san, Ayaka and Natsumi.
These four are Pisces.
So I am Pisces, eh…
By the way, where’s Maki-chan?
Over there.
Moving on...
The next ones are Ako-san, Sakurako-san, and Satsuki-san.
These three are Aries.
I see.
Then it’s definitely related to the Lunar Zodiac!
If that’s the case, then what is behind all this, Chizuru-san?
Divination.
Exactly. The one who possessed the girls is very well versed in astrology.
What about it?
We know now the possessor is well versed in Divination. Can we solve this problem?
Well, I don’t know about that.
What do you mean you don’t know?
So all you did was solve the mystery, Ane-san?
Yeah! But hey,
Knowing this makes things just a tad less mysterious, huh?
True, that it does, but…
The question to what is going on still remains, right? Aniki?
Aniki?
What is the matter, Negi-sensei?
You don’t look too good.
Do you need to go to the infirmary?
Divination.
Ne
gi
ma!
Go!
Let's Go!
Ne
gi
ma!
So moe-moe, aru!
Negima Negimi Negimu Negime Negimo…
Negima Negimi Neg-… ugh…
Out.
Oh!
Another unnatural phenomenon attacks Class A.
Alright! The base flavoring is ready!
Yay! Let’s cook it!
The magical world strikes again!
The book-!
Note: Alright, “Honkakuteki” means full-blown, but this is a Japanese pun. “Hon” means book in Japanese. So this could also mean: “This is one pinch from a book!”
This is one book-blown pinch!
15 points.
Spicy, isn't it?
Nah, more of a mild flavor.
This isn't the time for that!
Note: The same thing. This time the narrator says: 本当に大変 (Hontou ni taihen!)
Get it? HONtou ni taihen!
This is a problem of encyclopedic proportions! Meanwhile, the culprits are here!
Looks like that time has come, mya.
Seems like it.
Let’s begin communications.
Note: CQ is a code used by wireless operators to ask everyone listening in on a particular frequency to respond.
CQ, CQ, BBQ
If you're barbequing, coat it with sauce, then grill, turn it over, and grill again.
Be serious.
Oh, I’m sorry.
If you go out with Year 3 Class A, you will become popular! In a good way.
There is no such character as Class A, mya.
Well, cut it out and start the communications, mya.
CQ, limited express, exclusively limited express; The Line 2 High Speed Train has already passed.
Please step back into the area between the white lines while you wait. Tha….
CQ, CQ, this is Motsu.
So we'll finally get to see its presence?
Alright! Time to transform!
Black Rose.
Pork Bone Magic?
Yeah. I found some really old magic.
What is it and what is it for?
The source of the magical powers.
In other words, I'm learning about the master of the magic that was released.
However, since it’s very old magic, there isn’t a precise method to activate it.
That’s why I’m trying out various ways to do it.
Then, the ramen research has no particular purpose?
You could say that.
In any case, Chachamaru-kun…
Yes.
Why are you all soaked up?
I cannot fly so I swam here.
Ah. I see.
Oh! It’s out!
This might actually work!
Oh. Looks like something is happening.
Awesome!
Pork Bone Magic is successful!
Is this person the owner of all the magical power?
So that’s how it is…
Nekane-san?
Yeah. Have you seen Nekane onee-chan?
Ah. Nekane-san…
…went upstairs just now.
Upstairs…
Thank you very much!
Wait for me!
Aniki, why are we looking for Nekane nee-san?
Motsu-kun, Shichimi-kun.
You really aren't sent from the Magic Academy.
Who was that transmission addressed to?
Well, that er...
Is it the Master of the Darkness?
The Master of the Darkness?
You are also born from that which stole the Star Crystal.
The Shriek of the Soul.
You are the fragment fairies, aren't you?
The… Shriek of the Soul?
Dunno...
Stop playing innocent!
Now, turn into Fragments!
Sleeping light, beyond the door of journeys.
To the other side of the mist!
Was I mistaken?
Too bad…
You missed.
No!
We aren't the monstrous things you've mentioned to us.
Desu mya~.
Then who did you call just now?
Oh. That was a different. It was a PRIVATE matter. In a good way.
Then you guys and the Star Crystal…
As a matter of fact...
...we've got nothing to do with it, mya.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Don't get your knickers in a bunch about it, mya.
Just when I thought I got it figured out...
Black Rose Baron!
Come on, don’t step on me!
Geez... ow ow ow... Oh?
Takahata-sensei?
Baron. There is a question I want to ask you.
A question?
The person who stole the Star Crystal… you know that person, right?
What are you trying to say?
The culprit that I'm looking for,
the Master of the Darkness, is someone I know, isn't it?
The people in Class A who were possessed by the Darkness were targeted according to their Lunar Zodiac signs.
In other words, the person who stole the Star Crystal and the Master of the Darkness,
is one who is knowledgeable in divination. And the only person I know that specializes in divination is...
Anya.
What did you say!?
Is that true, Aniki!?
The worlds that were spawned by the Darkness…
…were all places from my memory.
They're all places where I played with Anya.
Negi-kun. You're wrong.
They are not the same as your memories.
Baron!
Is that enough, Nekane-kun?
Takamichi…
I have ascertained it.
The source of the Darkness is Anya.
Anya?
Takamichi, is that true?
Yes. No mistake about it.
You don’t look too surprised, Negi.
Did you know already?
I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
You already knew the Master of Darkness was Anya,
and disguised yourself as the Black Rose Baron
to try and secretly protect Negi-kun.
You could have notified the Magic Academy.
Why did you do it alone?
If I did that, then Anya would be punished.
But Anya stole the Star Crystal, and is targeting Negi.
If we discovered all the Fragment Fairies and completed the Shriek of the Soul, the Anya within the Star Crystal would awaken.
If I did that, I figured I could talk to Anya.
To try to convince her?
Nekane-kun, that is impossible.
Impossible or not, if we don’t try…
Even if you say so, the Star Crystal has incredible magical power.
Can you really do it?
It’s a shame, but you don’t have the kind of power to stand up to it.
Of course, I don’t either.
Onee-chan.
Why did Anya steal the Star Crystal?
Why me?
Tell us, Nekane-kun.
Anya is lonely, that’s why.
The fortune-telling job didn’t go as well as planned.
She couldn’t socialize with the others on the stage either.
Even though she's strong-willed, she's still a child.
I think it was hard on her.
Anya…
Anya always had you in mind, Negi.
She always said, “I don’t want to lose to Negi!”
Despite that, I told her you were doing well.
I said you made a lot of friends.
I'd keep talking about you.
I should have realized earlier.
But Anya…
She held on to “I don’t want to lose to Negi”...
And made a move on the Star Crystal.
It’s my fault.
If I didn’t say such unnecessary things…
None of this would…
I knew that I had to do something.
I wanted to try and save Anya.
Onee-chan!
Bonge Bonge!?
Catherine.
That voice…
Is that a fairy from the Darkness!?
Negi!
Sleeping light, beyond the door of journeys!
To the other side of the mist!
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
It combined into one!
That’s the Shriek of the Soul!
The Star Crystal.
Master.
She is possessed by the darkness!
Eva-san!
Negi, it’s me.
Anya!
I will not lose!
I will not lose to you!
Never…
Anya…
And so, the enemy awakens!
It’s Negi’s childhood friend Anya!
Anya is going after Negi!
What will you do, Negi?!
Will you fight, Negi?!
Will he win?! We'll find out next time!
Let's go!
Having a fighting spirit is important to an athlete!
That's probably why Yuuna's so drawn to military things!
I see.
Next time, “Hold on, that’s not what I meant Negi-kun!” by Yuuna
“That’s right! I’m your partner after all!” by Ako.
Alright. Give me your arm.
Eh!? You're going to inject me with that?
It’s okay, with these nutrients, you can fight for 24 hours straight!
No… That’s not…
Chamo-kun, what is your full name?
Albert Chamomile...
Sounds, uh... interesting.
What about yours, Motsu?
Note: Motsu's molding his name to be like Matsui Hideki of the New York Yankees.
Motsui Hideki.
The Major Leaguer?
Note: Another pun on Matsui Hideki's nickname, Godzilla.
Please call me “Gorilla Motsui”.
Monkey!