Isn't dropping out a bit much?
Can't we just start after graduating?
Didn't the live house manager already tell us?
Lots of people waste their opportunities like that,
just because they hesitate too much.
Yeah, but what about our parents?
Can't we just take a gap year?
Ooh, that might work.
We can just go back to school after finishing our album.
That's no good.
Trust me, we'll make it.
You heard the agency.
We're in the middle of a girls band revolution.
If we come to Tokyo, we'll definitely be a hit.
And they'll be backing us.
I don't think it's going to be that easy...
Agreed.
They didn't tell us to drop out of school, did they?
Come on.
No, but I still want to bet everything on this.
That's some confidence there...
If we make an escape route, we'll
definitely want to use it at some point.
Having an escape route means we'll
have somewhere to look other than forward.
But…
That's why we shouldn't give ourselves any way out!
Momoka.
Hey, wait for us!
AIM FOR THE BUDOKAN!
We're going to make it, I'm telling you!
Sooo…does anyone need a bathroom break?
I asked you a question, Momoka-san.
Shut it.
Answer me first.
You little-
Don’t provoke her!
I'll take that bathroom break.
Got it.
IF YOU WERE TO CRY
Start by apologizing.
Huh?
She's right, you know.
So you're on her side now?
There aren't any sides.
But that outburst was entirely your fault.
The stage is a place to communicate with the audience.
A sacred place.
Not a place for you to vent about everything that's wrong with your life!
I knew it was the only place I could get you to listen to me.
And I was right!
Guys...there are other people here, you know.
You're not off the hook either. Why didn't you stop her?
Me? There's no way I could.
This is embarrassing. I'm out.
We should see where this goes.
Besides, this is all your fault.
My fault?
Yes, your fault!
You just decided to quit out of nowhere, without talking to us or anything!
I don't want to hear that from the girl that sprung the whole pro thing on me.
Both of you are kinda in the wrong, you know...
Aren't you the one who stirred
this whole thing up in the first place?!
I humbly apologize.
Anyway!
I’m not giving up.
Fine, be all gung-ho about it like an idiot.
But you'll regret it someday.
Do you even understand how popular Diamond Dust are?
That doesn’t mean we should give up before even trying.
I don’t want to end up having to admit
that we were in the wrong!
Get real, will you?
You're the one avoiding reality, not me.
Just shut up already.
What do you even know about me?
Then tell me. Why did you keep going?
If you think your music isn't enough,
why didn't you just call it quits and go back home?
Why start a new band?
In any case, you shouldn’t drop out of school.
It's my decision to make.
Fine, do what you want then.
Running away again?
Stop running!
Just shut up.
We're sorry for the disturbance!
They're acting! We're in the middle of filming for a TV show!
Passionate, aren't they?
I'd label that as "stupid".
If you want to hit me, go ahead. I’m used to it.
In fact, I want you to.
It’ll finally give me a reason to hate you.
Because you'll be just like them.
Need some water?
Guess this is the end.
No, it's the beginning.
Thanks for bringing me back.
We'll be in touch tomorrow.
Finally, I thought I was gonna suffocate here.
Hey.
What?
Where did that guitar come from?
I got it when we were leaving.
Huh?
Is there a problem?
Mine-san gave her one of her spare guitars.
"Your voice is raw and genuine, like Momoka's. I'll be cheering for you."
Or so she said.
Sorry about that.
I told the owner you’d bring back the car.
Got it, no worries.
Maybe I'll get off here too then.
I can give you a ride.
It'll be a pain, won't it?
There's lots of traffic where I live.
The trains are still running, so I'll be fine.
Don't forget to take something
for your motion sickness next time.
Go away.
- See you soon.
- Drive safely!
Are trains still running at this time?
Nope.
But I thought a talk would be nice.
I was trying to be considerate, you know.
It's kind of nice here. Pretty relaxing.
Maybe I should move in here.
I'll let you know if my roommate moves out.
Eh? Being roommates with you, huh...
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
Did Rupa and Tomo know what Nina was planning?
I don't think so.
But they probably weren’t too surprised,
considering how Nina was acting lately.
You’re the only one who
didn't notice anything.
Why didn't you stop her?
It's her choice.
You understand how reckless this is.
We haven’t even released any music yet.
But we passed the selection for the festival.
And Rupa-san got offers from labels before.
Seriously?
It might sound crazy to you,
but remember, you were a part of Diamond Dust.
As for Rupa-san and Tomo-chan,
they’re supposedly some kind
of famous mysterious duo online.
And to top it off, a while ago,
a certain singer tweeted that she liked Nina’s voice.
And it got people talking.
For real?
Plus, we gained a ton of followers.
And based on the festival's feedback survey, we have the largest amount of people
coming to see us specifically.
I see...
Nina isn’t completely
disconnected from reality, you know.
Maybe beating Diamond Dust is a bit much for now,
but we can at least take our first step towards that.
What about Rupa and Tomo?
They wanted to go pro in the first place.
And you?
I'm just going with the flow.
One thing’s for sure though,
we’re not going to be young forever.
Anyway, the rest is up to you.
Turns out everyone was on the same page, huh.
Not exactly.
But it's like Nina always says.
If we're serious, we need to cut off our escape routes and set concrete goals.
That’s why we shouldn't give ourselves any way out!
Ummm...this one, and...
And, uh…
This one...
I guess that'll do for now.
A Minor.
F.
G.
How the heck do people do this...
Let’s see…
Freedom, freedom, from now on I'm free!
Tomorrow and the day after I’ll do what I want!
Jakkajan.
Dear Dad.
Thank you for raising me until now.
From now on, I’ll try
my best to make it on my own.
I won't be needing money anymore.
I'm returning my bankbook.
Nina.
Muneo Iseri
Step right up, step right up!
What are we, a sushi place?
Was that wrong?
Just say hello like a normal person.
You've been here a million times before.
Well, you don't really pay attention to this stuff
when you're a customer...
Yummy.
Put those thoughts into action and you're fired.
C'mon, really?
What do you think, genius?
Ugh, why did you have to work here of all places?
It’s my first job, so I thought
it'd be nicer with someone I know...
You're taking too damn long!
We asked for the bill ages ago.
My apologies.
Where are you even from, anyway?
Pretty cocky for a foreigner.
Hey-
I apologize for the wait.
Watch it next time.
Thank you for coming.
Rupa-san...
Don’t worry. It happens all the time.
I guess I need to be more "rock" too.
I'll go check the stock.
So, what happened with Momoka in the end?
Nothing much.
If we try to talk now it'll
definitely turn into a fight again.
Just saying, if this goes on for much longer, we’re out.
I get it.
Hey, step right u-
One medium.
Hello!
One medium!
Would you like a beer with that?
Nina.
Would you like to order something else?
Do you have some time after this?
No, I...
do!
Girls Band Cry.
We can conclude that there was no bullying or harmful intent involved.
Just a small incident that escalated a bit.
Can we leave it at that?
Perfect.
Now, I want both of you to submit your apology letters,
and end things on a good note with a handshake.
Iseri-san?
Where are we going?
Somewhere close by. We'll be there in a bit.
Alright.
Did you want to go somewhere in particular?
Not really.
Just thought it would be nice to drive
with you like this for a bit longer.
Ugh.
They could at least give us an update or something.
Don’t worry.
The opposite of love is indifference.
If they still want to talk after fighting so much,
that's basically proof of their affection for each other.
More like proof of their stupidity.
Is this where you wanted to take me?
Come on, open the door.
What can I rely on to guide myself?
I just need to follow the manual of common sense
And all its meaningless words.
Days pass and are all the same.
Diamond Dust.
This is what trying to survive after
cutting off your escape routes looks like.
There's no room for luxuries like
making the kind of music you love.
To survive, we constantly have to think.
What kind of music is going to sell? What can
get people talking? What's the optimal choice?
And chase those things.
That's not always true.
Doing what they truly love
is something very few artists can boast about.
YEAH, I'M NOT THEIR FAN ANYMORE.
The original Diamond Dust members
FAKE AS HELL
THE VOCALIST SUCKS
didn’t want to go down that path either.
THE DD I KNOW IS DEAD
THE BAND'S GARBAGE WITHOUT MOMOKA
But this is the choice they made to ensure their survival.
Maybe, but that still doesn't mean
your music won't resonate with a wider audience.
You got your song rejected once,
and left the band without even trying again.
But they found a wider audience as they are now.
They were right.
At first, they were adamant about it.
"An idol band? Yeah right."
"We’ll make it with our own music, just watch us."
But the higher-ups weren't having it.
And sure, technically,
critics loved us. But we weren’t profitable.
Our commercial songs were the
only ones that ended up being hits.
That’s how this world works.
You start to feel more and more pressure,
and in the end, you're forced to make a choice.
And only one choice allows you move forward.
They made that choice.
That's not something you can blame them for.
Anyway, I don’t want you to make the same choice I did.
You asked me why I formed a band again
instead of going back, right?
When I heard you sing back then,
I saw myself in my early days.
You didn’t care about money or success.
You were just singing what you loved.
I saw the past me that I had loved so much.
The me that I no longer was.
That’s why I wanted you to sing as yourself.
Free from any constraints.
I wanted to be able to listen to you over and over.
Thank you for everything!
We are Diamond Dust!
Make some noise for the next band too!
Then what about my feelings in all this?
Nina.
Did you ever stop to think how I'd feel about this?
Nina!
Let go of me!
I'm a person, not a memory of your past.
So don't trap me in it!
Alright, now shake hands and make up.
What can I rely on to guide myself?
Iseri-san?
Iseri-san!
Nina, wait!
Everything is so white
Everything is so slow
All the answers are empty of substance
Even if your fingers are trembling…
Your songs have given some of us the strength to keep going.
What you need to protect
isn't some vague memory of yourself,
but your desire to reach people with your music.
Expressing yourself.
Your anger, your joy, your sadness.
That's why you started a band.
That's why you sang at the school festival, why you came to Tokyo,
Why you wanted to make a living from it!
What are you so afraid of? Stop being a coward!
Look at me.
Right in front of you is someone
who gained the strength to keep going thanks to you!
Someone who felt so much happiness just getting to sing with you,
someone who would have bet everything on you!
Someone who believes in you and loves your music…
Momoka-san.
I'm not your excuse to run away.
Momoka?
No doubt about it.
It's her.
Nina, let's go!
Come on, hurry up.
Hina.
- Move it!
- Coming!
Forget it, I'm going on ahead. Take the train back.
Momoka!
Momoka-san!
Momoka-san, wait!
You idiot.
Are you nuts?!
Now we're even.
Why do you always run away?
You shouldn't be the one running.
You stayed true to yourself!
Shut up already!
Momoka!
You don't have to talk to us, just listen!
We heard you started a band.
We're looking forward to hearing you play.
We don't have any regrets, you know!
We're shooting for the top!
Someday we'll prove to you that we weren't wrong.
And until then, we'll do everything we can to survive!
Well, we won't lose to you without a fight.
We'll make you say that we were right.
We’ll show you that we made the right choice!
Huh?
Stop talking nonsense.
For someone who just played like shit out there,
you sure run your mouth a lot!
Momoka.
You’re an idol band.
If you don't have any regrets,
then at least play the part properly!
Be professionals!
We’ll be at the next festival.
Play like you did today,
and we'll be stealing every single one of your fans!
The heck is that supposed to be?
A declaration of war.
Momoka!
I hear you loud and clear!
Get in, Nina.
Do you know that girl?
No...
I've never seen her in my life.
Damn it.
Shit!
What’s so funny?
Momoka-san.
What do you want?
I still like you after all.
What's that supposed to mean?
What else?
I’m confessing my love to you.
My fingers are static My fingers are trembling
There are no written answers Nor any stinging failures
I have always been who I am And I will remain who I was
Even if I fight There will be no tomorrow
Rupa? What is it?
I told you so.
Good grief.
They're a riot, those two.
Nina Iseri: Rina Momoka Kawaragi: Yûri
Subaru Awa: Mirei Tomo Ebizuka: Natsu
Rupa: Shuri Hina: Reina Kondô