Huh?
So this is where you used to live.
I also lived here in Kamakura in my younger days.
What were you called back when you were in middle school?
We just stuck to using surnames, so I was Godai.
Godai?
Godai Kaoruko...
Wait, the youngest ever winner of the National Karate Championships, Godai Kaoruko?
You're remarkably well-informed, considering how long ago it was.
Whaaaaaat?!
No way!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
You lived around here?
We lived a little further up in the mountains, but I remember coming here to shop a lot.
Hanasaki?!
Oh! Mitsuru!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
You're back, then?
Oh, no. My friends and I are just
here to visit during the Bon Festival.
Afternoon!
Nice to meet you. I'm Myoudouin Itsuki.
You're one of Hanasaki's friends, then?!
What of it?
Um, this is my childhood friend, Nakano Mitsuru.
Nice to meet ya.
L-Likewise...
You seem to be doing well, Mitsuru.
How goes your kendo training?
I've been training day in and day out to get ready for the tournament.
I don't have the time to go waltzing
about with girls whenever I feel like it.
Aha, I see the problem.
That's sweet. You've made me remember my first love.
Your first love?
Grandpa was a Hottie?!
Cure Flower's First Love!
I can't go on any longer!
Erika, that's pathetic!
I like to think I keep myself in pretty good shape,
but just climbing these mountain paths is so boring!
Let us go!
Look how well Grandma's doing compared to you!
All right, all right! I get it!
By the way, just what is your
relationship with that Mitsuru kid?
My relationship? We're childhood friends, that's all.
Come on, tell us a bit more than that.
Sure, I guess.
Since he was young, Mitsuru's always been
obsessed by kendo and trained almost constantly.
I was always quiet and rather reserved.
What?!
But whenever I got into trouble, Mitsuru would always appear to save me.
Hmph!
Are you all right?!
Even in junior high, Mitsuru always seemed to appear out of nowhere to help me.
Then, once we'd decided we were going to move to Kibougahana,
I wanted to thank Mitsuru for all the kindness he'd shown me.
Mitsuru!
But you never managed to see him?
That's right.
He seems like a nice kid.
But I wonder why he dislikes me so much.
Yeah, I'm not sure either.
You really don't get it?
Huh?
I really don't.
Me neither.
I don't know either!
Hanasaki
It's amazing how quickly houses fall
into decay when nobody's living there.
This house has a lot of memories for your family, right, Tsubomi?
Yeah! I was born and raised here, after all!
Ow, that hurt...
That's...
Whoa! I recognize that hot guy!
What's the matter?
Whoa!
Wow, that sure takes me back.
Is this your first time seeing a photo of Sora?
Yeah, it is!
So he's your grandpa?!
It's kinda strange, though.
Whenever I find myself in trouble,
a guy who is the spitting image of
this photo always comes to save me!
If it's all right, could you please tell us more about Grandpa?
Yeah!
Like how you met, and when you first started going out!
It's an old, old story.
Please tell us!
It all began when I was doing some secluded training in the mountains to prepare myself for the tournament.
But I always felt so lonely, sleeping there alone at night.
I couldn't take it any longer, so I decided to head back.
All around that little mountain hut, my
favorite flower, lavender, was blooming.
Hi there.
Huh?
Please come in.
I don't want to disturb your playing.
I enjoy performing more when there's an audience.
So please, come in.
Yessir.
I mean, um, right...
Oh, just a moment. I'll get you some lavender tea.
You live in this mountain cottage all by yourself, Sora?
Yes.
Nature has blessed this place well, and as such I'm able to live a self-sufficient lifestyle here.
Aren't you lonely out here on your own?
Of course I am.
But the trees, plants, and leaves
provide me most excellent company.
Actually, I do happen to have something rather special.
A music box I made.
If ever you should feel lonely, then just listen to its melody.
Thank you...
And that was how I met Sora,
and how I found my first love.
That's beautiful!
And after that, you went on to
win the karate championships?
I did.
I managed to continue my training, thanks to that music box.
After winning, I went on to study
botany with the same enthusiasm,
and I became closer and closer to Sora.
What happened then?!
We got married.
Eventually, after Youichi was born, Sora made a promise to me.
I'm going to grow a beautiful field of
lavender on this mountainside, just for you!
Once it's finished, will you listen to me play my cello again, amongst the lavender?
And then...
Don't tell me...
Sora went up to Heaven and left me here alone.
So you never found out where the lavender field was?
That's right.
Eventually Youichi got married,
and you were born.
But it's so strange.
I've grown so old, and yet, in my mind,
Sora is still the same as he was back then.
I suppose because he passed on so early, I
still think of him as he was when we first met.
This was Grandpa's?
This is the last memento of his I have left.
Huh? What about the music box?
It's...
I...
What's the matter?
I loved that music box so much and always listened to it,
so Grandma gave it to me as a present,
but when we moved, it vanished from my luggage.
I'm so sorry, Grandma...
I've already forgiven you, you silly girl.
Besides, I'm sure that music box is helping to calm someone else's heart as it calmed mine.
The summer sea, and not a Kumojacky or Kobraja in sight to ruin it.
I'm going to make this a summer to remember!
Or I would, but...
this whole place is full of lovey-dovey couples!
This is all those accursed Precures' fault!
This time I'll defeat them, once and for all!
Sorry to bother you.
Mitsuru!
H-Hi there.
What's the matter?
W-Well, I have training this afternoon...
It won't be over till late, so...
Okay...
I mean, uh... I was running through the mountains recently, and I came across this lavender field.
Huh?!
You like flowers, don't you?
I just wanted to tell you about it, so...
Is that the same lavender field?!
Sora's?!
Mitsuru, could you show us where it is?!
Sure!
It's just beyond the pass up ahead.
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
Thank you, Itsuki!
I'm going on ahead!
Huh? Mitsuru!
Damn it all!
I thought the lavender field would be a
good place to give her back the music box.
Can I really give it back to her, though?
What do we have here?
Whoa! A weirdo!
Hrm?
The flower of a troubled boy's
heart. How beautifully it wilts!
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
It's your cue, Desertrian!
Mitsuru?
Music box!
A Desertrian?!
It's Mitsuru!
They made him into a Deshertrian!
Huh?!
Please save Mitsuru!
Right!
Sheeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Music box!
Sunflower Protection!
Whaaat?!
Bombs away!
I've had Hanasaki's music box all this time!
What?!
Huh... I feel sleepy...
I saw something fall out of her car when she was moving, so I picked it up!
So that's what you ran after us!
I chased after you to try to give it back, but I just couldn't catch up!
Hanasakiiiiiiiiii!
So that's what happened!
Blossom!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Hanasaki, I...
Mitsuru...
That's enough of the boring chit-chat.
Fact is, as much as he sits there worrying, he
didn't have the guts to give the music box back.
What a useless brat.
He's not useless!
It's through those worries and
uncertainties that people mature!
Using his heart and making it into a Desertrian is just cruel!
I've had it up to here with this!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Hmph! I'll defeat you next time, just you watch!
You got the Flower of his Heart back!
Let'sh return him to normal!
You've finally come around?
Hanasaki...
So this must be the lavender field you were talking about, Mitsuru.
It's really pretty.
Hanasaki!
Here!
You held onto it for me when it fell
out of our car during the move, right?
Huh? How did you know?
Now, now, don't sweat the details.
Mitsuru, thank you so much!
Ha.... Hana... saki...
Mitsuru?
I... I... I...
I!
Oh, right. What did you want to tell me just now?
It's nothing. Forget it.
Hanasaki.
I'll see you again, won't I?!
Of course you will!
In the language of flowers, lavender means "I'll be waiting for you."
It looks like Tsubomi finally
realized Mitsuru's feelings too!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
Thank you for keeping your promise, Sora.
I really would like to hear you play your cello for me again one day.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Ahh! It's over!
What are you freaking out about?!
Argh, but it just won't end!
Erika, none of the viewers are gonna
have any clue what you're talking about!
Try to make it at least shound like a preview!
Summer vacation's almost over! But that loathsome beast won't leave me alone!
Nothing can come from loathing, you know!
You need love! Love will get you through it!
Homework
HeartCatch Precure:
Sabark's Greatest Plan Yet!
We Haven't Finished Our Summer Homework!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!