♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1,
LET'S JAM ♪
I'M GONNA GO LOOK.
YOU'RE NOT.
I'M GONNA GO
LOOK FOR MY WOMAN.
YOU CAN GO
LOOK FOR THE OTHER ONE.
ARE YOU SEEING JULIA
BEHIND MY BACK?
I FEEL LIKE I'M
IN A CONFESSION BOOTH.
YOU'RE NOT A PREACHER
BY ANY CHANCE, ARE YOU?
IF THERE'S ANYONE
WHO NEEDS PITY HERE, IT'S YOU.
WE STILL HAVEN'T SETTLED
THE SCORE FROM LAST TIME.
MAKE YOUR MOVE.
STEP ASIDE, LIN.
LIN.
[GASPS]
I WAS IN THE SAME SQUADRON
AS VICIOUS ON TITAN.
YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T
NEED COMRADES.
I'M ATTRACTED TO THAT WORD...
TO THE POINT OF TEARS.
YOU SEE, THAT'S WHAT
WE WERE AT TITAN.
WE WERE ALL COMRADES.
[RUMBLING]
[YELLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
WHAT'S THAT SONG?
JULIA.
NICE MELODY.
YOU MIND IF I PLAY THAT TUNE
ON MY SAX WHEN I GET BACK HOME?
[GASPS]
WHEW.
[MUSIC PLAYS]
WHEN I CAME HOME FROM THE WAR,
THEY PUT ME IN PRISON.
THEY THOUGHT I WAS A SPY.
I HEARD IT WAS VICIOUS
THAT TESTIFIED AGAINST ME.
I STARTED TO GO CRAZY.
SO THEY GAVE ME SOME NEW DRUG
THEY WERE TESTING ON PRISONERS.
IT WAS HIGHLY ADDICTIVE.
AND THE SIDE EFFECTS... WELL,
MY HORMONES WENT OUT OF BALANCE,
AND THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED.
SINCE I CAME HERE,
THERE'S BEEN ONE OTHER PERSON
WHO KNEW ABOUT VICIOUS.
YOU'RE ONLY THE SECOND ONE,
AND THE SECOND ONE
I'VE TOLD ABOUT THIS.
WHY ARE YOU GOING
TO SEE VICIOUS?
DIDN'T YOU SAY HE FRAMED YOU?
I WANT TO FIND OUT IF HE DID.
HE'LL MURDER YOU.
DEATH DOES NOT FRIGHTEN ME.
YOU'RE LYING.
EITHER WAY, I DON'T HAVE
LONG TO LIVE.
WHY DID YOU BRING ME HERE?
MAYBE I WANTED
TO BE WITH SOMEONE.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU JUST
HELP SOMEONE SELFISHLY,
AND YOU TAKE THEM HOME,
AND THEN YOU GO OFF TO DIE.
UHH! OOH
ARE YOU SURE
IT WAS THIS WOMAN?
OH, YEAH.
IT'S BEEN 6 MONTHS SINCE I
SAW A WOMAN IN THE FLESH
AND 2 YEARS SINCE I SAW
A GIRL THAT GOOD-LOOKING.
TRUST ME. I WOULDN'T
MAKE A MISTAKE ABOUT THAT.
MAN, I SURE WOULDN'T
WANT TO LIVE AROUND HERE.
SHE SAT OVER
THERE TALKING TO GREN.
JULIA USED TO SIT
IN THAT SAME SEAT.
JULIA?
ABOUT 2 YEARS AGO,
SHE WANDERED IN OUT OF THE BLUE.
A MONTH LATER, SHE DISAPPEARED.
YEAH?
WHAT KIND OF GIRL WAS SHE?
SHE WAS A REAL WOMAN.
[THUNDER]
I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN KEEP YOU ALIVE,
AND I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN KILL YOU.
I'M JUST WATCHING A DREAM
THAT I NEVER WAKE UP FROM.
IT'S LIKE
I'M WATCHING A DREAM.
BE CAREFUL WHEN YOU'RE
WITH THAT WOMAN.
WOMEN ARE ALL LIARS.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT.
WHEN THIS IS OVER,
I'M GETTING OUT OF IT.
ALL OF IT.
WHEN I DO,
WILL YOU COME WITH ME?
ARE YOU GONNA BETRAY ME?
NO.
PLEASE.
THEY'RE GONNA KILL YOU.
OH, YOU'RE FINALLY UP.
YOU'VE BEEN SLEEPING FOR 3 DAYS.
YOUR EYES ARE DIFFERENT COLORS.
MY LEFT EYE SEES THE PAST.
OH?
WHAT ABOUT YOUR RIGHT EYE?
[CAWS]
I'M NOT DEAD.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
[GRUNTING]
WHICH WAY IS WEST?
[SQUAWKING]
THANKS A BUNCH, PAL.
TRANQUILIZER GUNS.
THEY'RE MOCKING ME.
[GRUNTING]
EXCUSE ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR A BLUE BUILDING.
IT'S CALLED
THE ORLANDO APARTMENTS.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS?
[GRUNTS] I DON'T KNOW NOTHING.
ASK SOMEBODY ELSE.
HEY, COME ON.
FORGET IT.
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING TO DO
WITH FOREIGNERS EVER AGAIN.
I'M JUST ASKING
FOR DIRECTIONS.
I'M GONNA GO FIND
AN HONEST JOB SOMEWHERE.
WHAT'S UP WITH HIM?
HUH?
[YELLS]
[CRASH]
HUH...
BLUE APARTMENT BUILDING.
HUH?
FAYE.
FAYE, WAKE UP.
IT'S YOU.
WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
OH, I GET IT.
HE'S ONE OF THOSE
KIND OF GUYS, HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU MEAN GREN?
HE'S NOT LIKE ANYONE ELSE.
GREN AGAIN.
MANGAN WITH
DOUBLE REVERSE DRAGON.
GREAT. HE'S USING
AN ANCIENT CODE.
JULIA WAS HERE.
RIGHT IN THIS TOWN.
YO.
WHAT?
GOT ANYTHING?
NO.
I GOT A LEAD.
CATCH HIM YOURSELF.
TH
IS GUY'S FROM
THE GROUP YOU'RE AFTER.
CODENAME JULIA.
HIS NAME'S GREN.
ESCAPED FROM A MILITARY PRISON.
HE HAS A VERY HEFTY
BOUNTY ON HIS HEAD.
IF YOU CATCH HIM,
I'LL LET YOU BACK ON.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
HELLO.
I'M STANDING ABOVE YOU.
UNDER THE ROOF OF THE BUILDING
THAT'S CLOSEST TO THE SKY.
I'LL SEND A WOMAN OVER.
UP TO YOU.
ALTHOUGH I WAS LOOKING FORWARD
TO SEEING YOU PERSONALLY.
YOU MESSED UP THE BEBOP
BUT LEFT THE OTHER SHIPS INTACT.
SWORDFISH AND HAMMERHEAD
ARE FULLY MOBILE.
WAS THAT, LIKE, A HINT
FOR US TO COME AND FIND YOU?
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
WERE YOU JUST
TESTING US OR WHAT?
WHY'D YOU COME AFTER ME?
I WANT MY MONEY BACK.
- THE SHIP'S SAFE?
- YEAH.
THAT ONLY HAD 20,000 IN IT,
YOU KNOW.
IS THAT RIGHT?
DUMMY.
SO WHO'S THIS JULIA?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE GOT SOME KIND
OF HOLD ON SPIKE.
THAT'S ALL I CAN TELL YOU.
HMM.
[SNIFFS]
[WHIMPERS]
WHERE'S MY SOUVENIR?
IS IT HERE?
IS IT HERE YET?
[WHIMPERS]
IT'S READING XPLUS.
IT'S REAL.
GIVE IT TO HER.
THIS IS THE TITAN OPAL
YOU REQUESTED.
TELL GREN THAT
I SEND MY REGARDS.
YOU SAVED ME
FROM THAT SCORPION,
AND YET YOU LIED
AND SOLD ME DOWN THE RIVER.
IT'S YOU.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WHEN YOU GAVE ME
THAT MUSIC BOX,
YOU DIDN'T THINK I'D EVER
BREAK IT OPEN AND LOOK INSIDE.
WHY WOULD I?
SO YOU FOUND
THE SOLAR TRANSMITTER.
JULIA FOUND IT.
THE MOMENT SHE HEARD
IT WAS A GIFT FROM YOU,
SHE TOLD ME
TO OPEN IT UP AND LOOK.
AND WHAT ABOUT IT?
ARE YOU TRYING TO
KILL ME AGAIN? IS THAT IT?
WE FOUGHT THAT
BLOODY WAR TOGETHER.
WE WERE COMRADES.
YOU RISKED EVERYTHING
SHOULDER TO SHOULDER
ON THAT BATTLEGROUND OF DEATH.
I LOOKED UP TO YOU.
I BELIEVED IN YOU.
THERE WAS NOTHING
TO BELIEVE IN.
THERE'S NO NEED TO BELIEVE.
VICIOUS, LOOK OUT!
[GASPS]
THERE IS NOTHING IN
THIS WORLD TO BELIEVE IN.
VICIOUS!
LIN DIED PROTECTING YOU.
SOUL IS LOST.
HE WASN'T PROTECTING ME.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
HE WAS PROTECTING THE ORDER.
[BEEPING]
YOU'RE IN THE WAY.
[COUGHING]
[GASPS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
HEY, COME ON.
HEY!
GREN, TELL ME WHERE JULIA IS.
I'VE GOTTA FIND HER.
JULIA'S GONE.
HOW DID YOU KNOW HER?
WHAT HAPPENED?
I NEED TO KNOW.
[COUGHING]
YOU'VE GOT AN INTERNAL INJURY.
I DON'T KNOW IF AN AMBULANCE
WILL EVEN COME OUT
TO THIS PLACE.
PUT IT AWAY.
CAN YOU LIFT ME UP THERE
ONTO THE SHIP AGAIN?
HUH?
I WANT TO GO TO TITAN.
YOU CAN'T MAKE IT THERE
IN THIS CONDITION.
IT WOULD TAKE TOO LONG.
I'M NOT GONNA MAKE IT ANYWAY.
DYING ON MY WAY THERE
WOULD BE A GOOD WAY TO GO.
I WANT TO GO BACK ONE LAST TIME.
IF I CAN'T DO THAT,
THEN AT LEAST I'LL BE ON MY WAY.
CAN YOU HELP ME TAKE OFF?
I GET IT NOW.
YOU'RE THE ONE, AREN'T YOU?
YOU'RE SPIKE.
JULIA WAS ALWAYS
TALKING ABOUT YOU.
YOUR EYES ARE DIFFERENT COLORS.
I REMEMBER HER SAYING THAT.
SAID YOU GET A STRANGE FEELING
IF YOU KEEP LOOKING
STRAIGHT INTO HIS EYES.
WHERE'D YOU MEET HER?
WHERE WAS SHE?
RIGHT ON THE CORNER BARSTOOL.
SHE SLIPPED IN
WHEN I WASN'T LOOKING.
SHE'D ASK ME TO PLAY
THE SAME SONG
EVERY TIME SHE CAME IN.
STRANGE LILTING TUNE.
AND THEN SHE WOULD SMILE.
OH, WHAT A SMILE.
SO SAD.
SO BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT ARE YOU
BRINGING IN?
NOTHING.
HURRY UP AND GET INSIDE.
WE'RE TAKING OFF.
JULIA.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
HMM?
OH, NOTHING.
JUST THINKING ABOUT SOMEONE.
WHERE'D YOU GUYS GO, ANYWAY?
SOMEPLACE VERY GOOD.
HOW COME EDWARD GOT LEFT OUT?
OH, I'LL TELL YOU
ABOUT IT SOMEDAY.
NAH.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
OH, ED, ANYTHING BUT BLUE.
A STAR JUST FELL FROM THE SKY.
THAT IS NOT AN ORDINARY STAR,
MY SON.
THAT STAR IS THE TEAR
OF A WARRIOR.
WHAT WARRIOR IS IT?
A LOST SOUL WHO HAS
FINISHED HIS BATTLE
SOMEWHERE ON THIS PLANET.
AHH.
A PITIFUL SOUL WHO COULD NOT
FIND HIS WAY TO THE LOFTY REALM
WHERE THE GREAT SPIRIT
AWAITS US ALL.
WHAT IS GOING ON
IN THIS WORLD?
THOUGH YOU'RE ALIVE,
DARKNESS LOOMS ONLY INCHES AWAY.
A WORLD WHERE ANY MOVE YOU MAKE
COULD BE A DANGEROUS MISTAKE.
SO WE WILL STEP AWAY
FROM THE MAINSTREAM
AND LIVE LIKE VAGABONDS
AND COMMON DROPOUTS.
PSYCHEDELIC RHAPSODY
FOR SOMEONE JUST LIKE YOU.
NEXT EPISODE
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY."
DON'T YOU WANT TO HANG OUT
AND WASTE YOUR LIFE WITH US?