[crashing and yelling]
Run, Ed!
[Envy] Bastard!
[crash]
[splash]
[Ed] Ling!
Alright, Envy... Time to die!
Help me... Kill me...
Help me die... I beg you...
Please kill me... Please!
[evil laughter]
[voices]
I don't want to die.
Where's my mommy?
[voices] Come closer, boy.
Help me.
[laughter]
Come on! Snap
out of it, you idiot!
Why didn't you attack him?
A person... Those are people...
They need our help...
They're trapped inside him!
[Ling] That's a trick,
Ed...! He's a monster!
But they-
Listen to me! Those
things are monsters!
[voices] Kill me!
Can you feel the power?
[voices] Mommy!
Give me back my son!
Shut up...! Stop it!
[voices] Father!
Do you like this power?
[voices] Please let me die!
Help us!
Stoooop!
[Nina] Big brother.
Wanna play?
Let's play.
I'm done playing with you.
[Ed screaming]
[Ed] Al... I'm sorry.
[voices] Come join us.
The pain won't stop.
Open your eyes, Ed!
Please, wake up!
[voices] Come and
die with uuuss.
Wake up!
[wincing in pain]
Ed, nooo!
[Worker] Steady,
steady...! Alright...
[Factory hand] Oh,
this little cat?
Yeah, I saw one that
looked just like it
by the factory earlier...
I thought it seemed
like a weird pet
for a guy in a suit
of armor to have.
Armor? Aaahh!
That thing we fought?!
[evil laughter]
That suit of armor's
gonna pay, big time!
He stole Shao May from
me...! Kidnapped her...!
That creep!!
That's her...! Shao Ma-
[Scar] Hold it.
You see that fat one?
I overheard them call
him a Homunculus.
[May Chang] A Homunculus?
He has the power to recover
from any type of injury...
So he's practically immortal.
He is...? That's even more
reason for us to go after them!
[Scar] You're
missing my point...
I don't know if
we can stop him.
[Scar] What's the
armored boy doing with him?
[May Chang shivers]
Is something wrong?
This place...
it's strange...
I could feel there
was something wrong
with this country
since I got here.
But this place...
It's the source of it...
Can you feel those things...?
Crawling beneath us?
[Shao May whimpers]
[Al] What's the matter...?
Are you cold...? It's okay.
This way!
[Al] Woah...
I didn't know there were
tunnels like this under Central.
[Al gasps]
[Shao May whimpers]
[Al and Shao May gasp]
[Al] Hey...!
What's with all that?
Huh...? Oh... The
gatekeepers did all that.
The gatekeepers?
They won't rip you up
as long as you're with me.
[growling]
[Al] Just pretend
they aren't there.
[Al] Do we have
much further?
Not too far...
It's just ahead now.
[Al] You said your
father made you...
Does he know what happens
to the people you swallow?
I'm sure he does.
Father knows everything!
[Al] Brother... I know you're
still alive... Just hang on.
[voices whispering]
[Ed] What is that? It
looks like... a red stone.
It's his core... A Philosopher's
Stone... I almost forgot.
After all my searching...
It's right here...
in front of me...
[Ed] Open up, Envy...!
Your breath is killing me!
I think I've got a way
to get us out of here!
[Envy and Ling gasp in surprise]
[Ed] C'mon, Envy...! Let me out!
[roaring]
[transmutation sounds]
What are these things?
They're known as Chimeras.
[roaring]
[transmutation sounds]
[growling]
There's no end to them.
[May Chang] It's stronger here.
The feeling... There's
something evil beneath us.
[Scar] Is it more chimera?
[May Chang] No, it's worse.
[May Chang] Are those... people?
Father can make anything!
He made all of us, he did...!
He made me... And Lust...
And he made Envy!
[Father] The gatekeepers
seem to have grown restless.
[Father] Someone's
come to find me.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Crying babies]
[Bradley] I have no memory
of my parents' faces
or their names...
In fact, I don't even
remember my own name.
For all I know, I might
have been abandoned
or sold before I even had one.
[Scientist] Now which one of
you will be the one to step
forward and lead this country?
How 'bout you?
[Bradley] They called us
"prospective Fuhrers"...
And they trained
us to be leaders.
They kept us
confined together...
and they taught us at all
times of the day and night.
We studied political
science, and humanities...
As well as martial
arts... firearms...
and of course, swordsmanship.
[swords clanging, grunting]
[yelling in pain]
[whimpering]
Don't worry... His only
true purpose in life
was to help you further
achieve your goal.
[Bradley] I was certain that
I would be the one chosen
to lead this country.
I firmly believed it
and I endured any
training to make it so.
[transmutation sounds,
screaming]
[Scientist] How disappointing.
Another failure.
[Scientist] Bring the next.
[Scientist] Go ahead
and lie down.
What's going on here?
[Scientist] Just try
not to think about it.
This won't take long.
What are you gonna do
to me...?.! Are they dead?!
[Father] You are the
twelfth candidate.
Do you have what it takes to
become my fury? My Wrath?
[Bradley] A Philosopher's Stone
is created from the life force
of countless human beings
and contains their souls.
Once injected into the
bloodstream, it begins to
take over its new host and the
human body tries to reject it.
My body was repeatedly
destroyed from the inside out
and then rebuilt by the stone.
The only options I had were to
die or to overcome its power.
I chose the latter.
[Scientist] It's amazing!
We've made a new type of human!
Congratulations. You have
been chosen to lead mankind
down the path of destiny...
Everything has been arranged
to provide you with
all that you'll need.
From now on, your
name will be...
King Bradley.
[Bradley] Countless
souls had battled
for dominance within me.
And only the most
wrathful one survived.
I can't tell you if
this remaining soul
was one of those within the
Philosopher's Stone...
Or if it's the one I'd
carried since I was born...
I doubt that I'll ever know.
You've lived your life
before as a human being...
Why choose to be a
Homunculus, sir...?
Isn't there some way you could
go back to being a human...?
Or not?
You suggest I become human
again...? Ridiculous...
Why would I possibly want
to pursue such frivolity?
[Bradley] I've become
something far superior.
Just as you humans take great
pride in your "humanity",
misguided though that may
be... I too am proud...
Because we also take
pride in what we are.
The woman you killed.
She died with her pride
intact, didn't she?
There. That should help.
Thank you, Ling.
[crashing]
[Envy] I collected all the
fragments that I could find.
[Ling] So this stuff...
It's all from Xerxes?
That's right... They're
pieces of a large mural
from what remains
of their temple.
[Ed] When I saw the ruins
of the mural up close...
I thought it was identical
to the transmutation circle
from the 5th Laboratory.
The one they used to create
Philosopher's Stones.
But it's actually different.
The sun represents the soul.
While the moon
symbolizes the mind.
And then there's the stone
canvas of the mural...
This represents the body.
Slow down... Try to
keep it simple, okay?
Basically... The mural
was a summoning circle...
For human transmutation.
I do know that one...
Well I think I do...
Is it used to bring
back dead people?
Not quite.
[Ed] Alchemy is based on the
rule of equivalent exchange...
You can't transmute a
life form from a soul
that no longer exists
in this world.
You can trust me on that one.
So... this is where I got the
idea to get us out of here.
I can't transmute the dead...
but what would happen
if I transmute myself?
You mean a living person?
Exactly... I can use this
transmutation circle
to deconstruct myself...
And then I'll just put
myself back together...
That's human transmutation...
and it'll open the portal.
[Ed] You said that Gluttony is
a defective Portal of Truth...
I'll bet that if we pass
through the real portal,
then we'll wind up
in our own reality.
I'll open up the real portal...
and then you two
jump through it.
What happens if it goes wrong?
Then it'll rebound...
A failed transmutation ricochets
onto the one who
performed it...
[Ed] In this case,
that would be me.
I'm not gonna act like I know
anything about alchemy...
This is all yours.
Right... Hey, Envy...
I've got something else
that I wanted to ask you.
[Ed] The partial mural
I saw in Xerxes...
It would've looked
more-or-less like this.
This is the first thing
that caught my eye...
The symbol for God is
written upside-down...
And beneath it is the
two-headed dragon...
The alchemic symbol for
a "complete lifeform".
Which means... This
basically translates to
"I will strike God to Earth
and become a perfect being".
Well that's certainly
an arrogant concept.
It's not a big deal
to talk about it...
but then there's this.
[Ed] This piece takes
it to the next level.
An image of the lion
swallowing the sun...
Symbolizing the
Philosopher's Stone.
The Philosopher's Stone is
made with living humans...
Isn't that correct, Envy?
Yeah... That's right.
[Ed] How could a nation as
advanced as Xerxes fall...?
Let alone in a single night?
What happened to
its citizens...?
These stone fragments
of the mural...
You put them here
to hide the evidence.
You killed them... You
sacrificed all of Xerxes...
You turned them into a
Philosopher's Stone!
[transmutation sounds,
screaming]
Who was it?!
[Ed] I wanna know who used
this to transmute himself...!
Who slaughtered the population
of a whole country...
Who created all of you...?
Who's trying to make himself
powerful enough to surpass God!
It was your father...?
Wasn't it? Tell me, Envy...
Whoever this guy is, he's
been using you Homunculi
to try and recreate the
destruction of Xerxes
here in Amestris, hasn't he?!
You get us out of here and
I'll gladly tell you everything.
You've spent enough time
beating around the bush...
I'm tired of waiting
for you to ask...
You need to pay a toll,
right...? To open the Portal?
[Envy] This should work.
[voices screaming]
Your body... Those are the
citizens of Xerxes, aren't they?
At one time, but their minds and
bodies crumbled long ago...
All that's left is energy
to be consumed.
They don't even remember
what they looked like
when they were alive.
Is that pity...? How
childish are you?
You're desperate to see these
things as human because you
wanna believe that your brother
still retains his humanity.
Would you hesitate to throw a
bundle of logs onto a fire...
because you pitied the
tree they came from?
These souls can never go
back to being human.
You have to use logic if you are
to determine what a human is.
Don't let your emotions decide.
[Ed] Alright.
Ling... This might not
work out for me...
If so, you gotta warn people
about these guys' plans.
I'm not that concerned about
Amestris. It's not my country.
Are you serious?
You've got people you love
waiting for you, don't you?
So just make it back alive
and tell them yourself.
I'm sorry... But
I need to use you.
Get ready!
[Ling] That pose he makes
when he transmutes...
I knew it reminded
me of something.
[clap]
He almost looks
like he's praying.
[transmutation sounds]
Long time no see.
Too bad this isn't why I'd
planned on opening you again.
Ling...! Jump in it!
You better know what you're
doing...! I'm trusting you!
[Ling] It's exactly like when
Gluttony swallowed us!
[transmutation sounds]
[Ed] Thank you.
Thank you.
[alchemical explosion]
[Ed] The body and the soul
are connected to one
another by the mind...
A portion of my body now hurtles
toward the Portal of Truth...
So there's no point
in struggling...
I have to let my mind guide
me... into the portal.
[Truth] Now what's this...?
You're not even trying to get
your body back, are you?
[Al] So this is it...? Your
father's on the other side?
[Gluttony] Mm hm. That's right.
[Al] There has to be a way
to rescue Brother in here.
[Shao May whimpering]
[grimacing with pain]
[Ed] Alright... I made it.
What the... Were there
always two portals?
[door opening, giggling]
Al!
[Ed] Al! Come on! Please...!
Hurry, Al! Aaaaall!
I can't.
I can only leave
with my own soul.
I'm sorry, I can't go with you.
[door closing]
[crash]
Alphonse!
Look at me! I promise...
Someday soon... I'm
coming back for you!
Just you wait!
Wait for meeeee!
Our memories are
like the flickering
of a great conflagration, their
shape constantly changing
and impossible to grasp.
And as these flames
of time dance,
they cast cruel and
distorted shadows
of our true selves over the
lives that we hope for.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode Twenty Seven...
Interlude Party.
One must never be afraid of
the darkness within themselves.