Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
No Credits ED
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara
as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
ah serofan no umi wo koe
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
mori wo koe
weaving through the forests,
gin no kaze wo nukete
and passing through the silver wind,
tarinai mono sagashiteta
I was looking for something neither of us had
ah jiorama no machi de tada
Ah, within a diorama of the city
naiteta no
I was just crying alone
ano hi sashidasareta
until the day your warm hand
atatakai te ni au made
reached out to me
yureru tsukihi no naka de
I felt your strong gaze
manazashi wo kanjiteta wa
during those swaying days,
nee himitsu no kagi wo
and then, at long last
yatto yatto mitsuketa no
I finally found the secret key
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
remon iro no tsuki no shizuku atsumete
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
anata no yuku sonomichi wo
and shine their light
yasashiku terashiteitai
down upon on your path
make a little wish chiisaku temo
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
dekiru koto ga nai kara
If you say you can't do anything,
anata ga ite kureru kara
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha