Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Thank you, girls.
These illuminations will help soothe the spirits of Kibougahana this Christmas.
I want to meet the Precure! - Mayuka
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
A Christmas Miracle!
We Got to See Cure Flower!
Tsubomi!
Gimme a lift up!
Whoa!
Here we go!
Come on! We're nearly there!
What's it say?
"I want to meet the Precure," huh?
Don't look!
Are you okay?
You're Mayuka, right?
Your dad's Mr. Tachibana from the botanical gardens, isn't he?
Is that your wish written up there?
Yeah.
You should be asking for Christmas presents
from Santa! Save wishes like that for Tanabata!
I don't care about presents.
Mayuka?!
Did we make her cry?
She wants to meet the Precure.
Yeah.
Quite badly, by the looks of it.
I hope I can find Mayuka.
You're lying!
I'm not lying!
The Precure are my friends!
Really?
Of course not! She's a total fibber!
Mayuka, haven't our teachers always said it's wrong to lie?
I-I'm not lying!
I was playing with the Precure last night!
Then let us meet them too!
Yeah, see, she's lying!
Okay.
I'll let you meet them!
You mean it?
When?
F-Five P.M., on Christmas Eve, by
the Christmas tree in the gardens!
Hello there.
H-Hello...
You were at the gardens with us last night.
So that promise you made to your friends about the Precure...
Why are you lying to them like that?
I'm not lying!
I know... I know the Precure will come!
Mayuka told you that, did she?
I'm sorry for all this bother.
It's all right, really. I was the one who went to ask her.
Her teachers have warned me about her behavior as of late.
She's been telling numerous lies to the other kids lately.
At first, it was just trivial little things.
But now, it's reached the point where she's been claiming her mother's an actress,
or that we're incredibly rich.
The problem is, she's not good at making friends.
She's very shy around new people.
Just like you when you were young, Tsubomi.
Yeah.
I'm sure she's only telling these lies so people pay attention to her.
When I was your age, Mayuka, I was so shy I couldn't make any friends at all.
Tsubomi, why don't you go and play with the other kids?
You'll never make any friends unless you do.
I don't want to!
The flowers are my friends!
Aren't you?
So I know
how you must be feeling.
But I never, ever told lies.
And I doubt the Precure would want to meet someone who tells lies to people.
See, the thing is...
I'm friends with the Precure!
Yep. Yep!
You're lying!
No, I'm not!
My friend's a Precure! I mean, the Precure are my friends!
I'm serious! Please! You've got to believe me!
Hey, miss.
Sis?!
Did you say sis?
Ah, what a lovely sound.
Yes?
If I promise not to lie again, do you
think the Precure will come see me?
Of course they will!
Then I won't tell any more lies!
It's a promise, then?
Yeah!
What?
You really promised her that?
Please, make her dream come true!
That's just like you.
Sure, I'll help.
I will also assist.
Aww, fine.
Guess I'll help.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
It's Christmas Eve, ladies and gents!
Why not take home a lovely Christmas cake?
I wish I had a girlfriend.
But it's okay!
Because I love the Precure!
Love?
The Precure?
Wh-Who are you?!
The Flower of your Heart...
...is wilting nicely!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Itsuki sure is late.
It's nearly five!
Bad newsh!
There'sh a Deshertrian in town!
Sunshine's fighting it all by hershelf!
What should we do?!
The obvious.
Our priority is protecting people.
Come on.
B-But...
We have to go.
Mayuka...
I hate lovey-dovey couples!
And I hate Christmas!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Bearing the burden yourself today, I see.
Give up while you still can!
Sunshine.
This time, you're finished!
Winning a fight two versus one is hardly anything to be proud of.
Precure Christmas Impact!
Christmas...
A Desertrian is, alas, no match.
Then let's show them what we can do.
Dark Bracelets!
Behold, the power of a Desertrian
with two commanders at the helm!
Take this!
And now, this!
This is our Christmas present to you all!
The Precure will come, won't they?
She was lying after all!
They'll come!
I know the Precure will come!
Coupe.
I'd like to give Mayuka a little Christmas present.
I want you to help me and help Tsubomi and her friends.
Blossom!
Please, wake up!
The Precure are finished!
Hold on now.
We can save the main course for later.
I suggest a little appetizer first.
So we run wild and wilt the Flowers of some more human Hearts?
Let's do it!
Oh?
Let's ruin that!
Let's go home.
If we wreck this tree, who knows how many Flowers it'll wilt?!
Say  your prayers!
I want to meet the Precure! - Mayuka
A Precure?
A Precure?!
Whoa!
But which Precure is that?
She's not Cure Blossom or Cure Marine.
I am...
You're?
A lone flower, radiant in the holy light!
Cure Flower!
Cure Flower?!
The legendary Precure that defeated King Dune?!
Very well! Bring it on!
Take Mayuka and her friends to safety.
Take this! Blizzard Blast!
Precure Flower Candle!
Precure Flower Carnival!
This is about all I can manage now.
I doubt I could even pull off a Forte Wave.
Let's go help the others, okay?
Flowers of our Hearts,
release the Precure from their prison!
Cure Flower!
We can talk later.
I'll leave him to you.
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world.
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
We'll get you for this!
Cure Blossom
Cure Sunshine
Cure Flower
Cure
Moonlight
Cure Marine
Grandma!
My, my!
Blossom's such a softie!
We're sorry we called you a liar, Mayuka!
Don't say sorry.
But wow, you really are friends with the Precure!
No, I'm not.
I was lying.
The Precure just answered my wish.
I never wanted to tell such a big lie.
I just wanted you all to want to be friends with me.
I'm sorry.
What're you saying, Mayuka?
We've always thought of you as our friend! Right?
Yeah!
I didn't expect your grandma to transform, though!
You can call me Cure Flower, dear!
Grandma?
You!
It's been too long, Cure Flower.
Dune!
He's...
the Desert King?!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
A wind of despair is blowing across our dessicated world.
Is there no hope left?
Is there no future for us?
We've fought so hard as Precure, though!
It can't end like this!
But the Great Heart Tree's wilted too!
Don't give up hope!
It's our duty as Precure to keep fighting!
HeartCatch Precure:
It's All Over...
The World's Become a Desert...
We'll catch everyone's hearts!