Mooom!
What's that cool pose?
This is no cool pose.
It is a technique known as the Incantation of Chigaeshi.
A form of meditation that seals all manner of unearthly beings.
Looks like a super hero!
I'm gonna beat those baddies too!
I am no super hero.
I am a Tsukuyomi priestess.
But Tsukuyomi priestesses fight for justice, right?
So you're a hero!
Your logic is not contradictory...
Now, here I go!
Incantation of Chigaeshi!
Hiya!
Hwa!
Voice effects are unnecessary!
And your pose is wrong.
But mine is cooler!
It looks strong, so baddies'll run away!
Hya!
Is that true?
Hya?
Mom, you're not loud enough!
Do not mock me!
Witness your mother's true strength!
Hoa!
What is it, Sasami?
Is something strange?
I love you, Mom!
What a strange child.
Hiya!
Hiyaaa!
Hwaaa!
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 7
I Forgot How To Speak
Not everything was perfect.
Tsurugi used to be less
motivated and was always tired.
She always lazed around.
Kagami never laughed or even spoke,
and would jump at the smallest noise,
like she was always fighting someone we couldn't see.
That's why I smiled.
I smiled because I had to smile.
Even I was bullied and teased at school, and it was hard.
I had trouble.
But I had to smile.
I can't do anything,
so I always pretend to be happy
to trick Tsurugi and Kagami into smiling once in a while.
Even when I annoyed them,
and no matter how much they scolded me,
I did all I could,
and tried hard to see the good in things.
You idiot!
You were useless!
Tsurugi and Kagami softened up little by little,
This is no time for tears.
and they smiled lots when they were with Mama and Paparin.
Things livened up a lot, and I thought that all the coldness was gone.
But now, everything's ruined.
Tsurugi fell into the underworld,
Kagami broke and stopped moving,
But I stayed positive.
It's who I am.
That's why I have to go.
It's scary, and I can't stop crying,
but I have to keep moving forward.
God, if you can grant my wish,
then I'll grant everyone else's!
Huh?
Do not move.
I am reassessing your body.
My body's freedom...
You've led an unhealthy lifestyle.
Were you slightly thinner, you might have died from malnutrition.
What's happening?
I can't think straight...
I dulled your senses with medicine.
I do not want to trigger the Supreme God's power.
Why?
Where am I?
This...
is where the Tsukuyomi Shrine used to be.
It may lack walls,
but its isolation from society makes it an excellent place to train.
Once it is purified and the barrier raised once more,
it will be fit for a Tsukuyomi priestess to live and hide.
I shall present the question to you once more.
This is the greatest compromise I can offer.
Will you never choose escape again,
and for the sake of the world and its people,
vow to carry out your duty as a Tsukuyomi priestess?
No...
You object?
Did you not already vow to return to being a Tsukuyomi priestess?
That was just... to stop... you...
Then you deceived me?
The medicine... is forcing me...
Don't want to...
That worthless duty... made you die...
so I don't want it.
Not after I've finally gone outside...
Not after I've finally made friends...
You abandon a duty bestowed upon you by Heaven?!
I never asked for it!
Then I will retrain you as much as time permits me.
No...
No!
I don't want...
to try anymore!
I see.
Then I have no other choice.
You spit up quite often as a child.
You might do so if I use your mouth,
so I will insert the medicine directly.
I left you conscious enough to answer the question.
But allowing the medicine to circulate will cost you your mind.
I have nothing left to ask you.
You have nothing left you must say.
And any hopes I had for a human like you
are now gone.
It is unfortunate, Sasami.
Quite unfortunate.
This one was disappointing as well.
He was incompetent and coddled as a boy,
but he disappointed not only by allowing the shrine to be ravaged,
but by acting on his own whims and bringing failure.
No redemption.
If you will not fulfill your duty, you are worthless.
But I cannot let the Tsukuyomi bloodline end.
Therefore, while you have but one desire left,
bear a child, Sasami.
That child will receive the Supreme God's power,
and will become a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Once the power is inherited,
you can disappear to where you please.
My body is not strong,
and because I bore few children, there are few potential fathers.
All because he held back.
N... o...
No... no... no...
Do not throw a fit.
You will bear this man's child,
and you will birth a Tsukuyomi priestess.
I will raise the child,
and the world will be as it should.
No... no...
At least...
let it be Brother...
I refuse.
He has been disowned by the family.
There is no amnesty for being disowned over a blunder as great as abetting your escape.
And I believe that man wished to save you,
or so he planned in coming here earlier.
He was rattling off about making amends,
so I took out the trash.
I must first purify your body.
The ceremony will scent your garb with an incense for childbirth.
Are you broken?
No matter.
Barring a disaster, I only need your body.
I shall explain your final duty to Sasami.
She went quiet when I told her I had killed you.
She seems to be quite fond of you.
You wretched monster.
I would love to kill you if I could.
Why are you using Sasami as a tool to birth a new priestess?
Do you have no motherly love left for her?
When I rose from Hell,
I ceased being human.
And before I am her mother,
I am a Tsukuyomi priestess.
And to think that Sasami truly loved you...
I am aware.
But that is a meaningless trifle...
Brother.
Awakening from hibernation.
Assessing damage...
Automatic repair rate at 38 percent.
Approximately seven hours until combat readiness.
Sasami...
You were worried about me, Meatie?
My foe is is protected by the lord of the underworld,
and is the strongest of the Tsukuyomi priestesses.
Rushing in without a plan would only result in a repeat loss, even for Tama.
The lord of the underworld.
The manifestation of chaos who became a hero, Susanoo.
Susanoo takes the order and authority of Amaterasu and outright negates it with chaos and rebellion.
He is the most troublesome enemy I have made yet.
Thankfully, I have my GPS-like function.
I care not if you are a Tsukuyomi priestesses or a heroic god,
but don't you fuckin' dare mock the Yagami sisters!
The rest is up to you,
Tama.
I must find a way to save Sasami!
Wah!
What a shocker!
This is Tsurugi's!
Why, thank you!
What's this?
This sword is even worse at cutting than it appears!
Now to get out of—
It'll take more than that!
Sasami's scent is...
this way!
This room!
Sasami!
Sasami, it's me!
I came to save you!
Sasami!
Now rest easy.
Whatever happens,
I'll protect you!
B...
Bro... ther...
You're alive...
Yes!
I'm quite alive, Sasami.
So please, don't cry.
Brother!
Ouch!
Hoowhaaa?!
I don't understand!
That was the perfect time for her to hug me, say she loved me, and peck me on the cheek!
You took way too long, stupid!
Moron! Retard! Useless!
Trash! Scum! Cockroach!
It's all right now, Sasami.
Your brother will protect you.
Brother...
You thought you could escape?
I had not expected my barrier to be broken by something thrown from afar.
The Heavenly Gathering of Clouds is indeed powerful.
It is a blade capable of exorcising any evil.
However,
only the sword was sent, and not a capable wielder,
so those evil gods can not yet act.
Move, Mother.
I won't give you a kid.
The meaningless Tsukuyomi bloodline will end with me!
That's my choice.
I'll take this humanity-warping world,
and return it to the chaotic times of the gods!
That's truly the way the world should be!
Even if I'm hit, tortured, or brainwashed into being your tool,
I won't back down!
You tried and tried, and lost everything.
You pretended not to see all the fun and happiness you could have had,
and when you finally fulfilled your duty,
how did the world thank you?
With pain and death!
You have no right to judge!
While you were mentally regressing with your idle life,
others were forced to work even harder in your place!
But you never realized,
always inclining to your worldly pleasures!
One who spits on her value given to her by birth
is no daughter of mine!
You know, Mom,
I really loved you.
You never smiled,
but you were always so kind.
I respected how you protected the world.
You were my hero.
And I lost all respect for the shrine for using you up and throwing you out!
However noble the duty that awaited me was,
being a priestess was a load of crap!
We're humans, not gods!
So just do nothing, and be happy with it!
Know that no words can reach the dead.
It's so far! Geez!
I wanted to save Mamarin,
but I didn't know where she was!
I only got here last time because Kagami took me!
I forgot the way, and got lost...
I was walking forever,
and I only went back to school!
I asked a policeman for directions,
but I didn't remember anything besides Kyushu!
He got mad at me and said not to waste his time,
but I didn't do anything bad!
And now I'll make you pay!
I'm gonna beat you up for hurting Tsurugi,
and go home with Mama and Paparin!
You are quite the reliable cavalry.
Mamarin, I'm borrowing this!
Tama?
Why?
The gods are distributed unevenly.
Those of high-order divinity are dispersed around the world.
A human's cognizance can at first register their existence.
But by conceptualizing the gaps in cognizance,
one can reconstruct itself to give the appearance of teleportation.
I'm in grade school,
so I don't know your big words!
This isn't about being smart,
it's about trying hard!
What?
She teleported the divine blade and had it reappear in the same space as the demonic blade!
What will that do?
According to legend,
the Heavenly Slasher of Wings is more brittle than the Heavenly Gathering of Clouds!
Here, Mamarin.
Mamarin called you Mom...
Dummy!
Mamarin was crying!
You're her mom,
so don't be mean to your daughter!
It was... eaten?
For a god to eat...
What—
I see!
You're of a new generation of gods!
You were created to replace the older generation!
A juvenile god!
Foolishness!
The legends are peerless in beauty,
and you wish to end that which has continued since creation?
That which has been our sun?!
I do not accept you, juvenile!
These chains—
The Incantation of Chigaeshi?!
The form of meditation that seals all manner of unearthly beings!
Damn you, Sasami...
I am your mother!
I carried you for nine months and gave birth to you!
Yet you label me a monster?!
I'm sorry, Mom...
Go back to...
the underworld!
Hey, Mommy,
thanks for yesterday.
How about we have a little chat about your kid's future?
Do not mock me, evil gods!
Do you not care about the fate of this world?!
If I cannot lead this country on its proper course,
then I could never rest in peace!
Sorry Tama,
I'll be away for a bit,
so watch the house for me.
Sasami!
I don't want to talk now.
Sasami,
at least eat something!
Well just...
leave it there, and I'll eat later.
Understood!
Telepathy?
Today's menu shall be your brother's famous Special Ramen.
If you don't eat quick, the noodles will get soggy.
And your dessert will be your brother's love!
I don't need your dessert, so take it back to the chef.
I understand, regrettably.
More telepathy?
Regardless, you received something in the mail,
so I'll leave that with dinner.
I'll be downstairs,
so call me if you need anything.
Tsurugi!
Hello?
Hey, it's me!
Beware of voice phishing!
Listen, I got into an accident, so could you spot me about 50k for damages?
Is this a scam?
Wait, Tsurugi, are you in the underworld?
Hey, I can Transform a phone signal from there if I try.
Long talks are tiring though, so I'll keep it short.
Um... sure.
I smacked around my dumbass brother for getting carried away, so I'm comin' home.
Take care of my sisters.
Also...
it's about your mother.
Back when I pulled her into Hell,
she was torn up from Tama eating her.
But she wasn't completely erased,
so she could still come back,
though I doubt she will any time soon.
For now, anyway.
I see.
Don't get too down.
She wouldn't get far.
And you already chose to go against her.
It'd be rude break down and cry now.
Keep movin' on.
Promise me, 'kay?
Yeah.
I'll try.
I'll try harder.
I'll rest a bit, and I'll go back to work.
In Call
Yeah.
Just don't push yourself.
Keep it up.
Oh yeah, I picked up somethin' your Mom dropped when I was tumblin' into Hell.
I sent it to ya, so I hope ya like it.
See ya.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
I'm back!
Welcome home, Tama.
I am glad you came back safely.
I'm a little tired...
Your battle was one thing,
but you were lost for a long time before it.
Good work.
You can do it if you try.
Although...
the time has come, so good luck with the song.
Sister ran off to the underworld,
and Sasami is in low spirits, so nobody else can sing.
I will sing with you, too.
Really really?
Then I'll do my best!
I'm stuuuunned by the waaaay you laaaaugh
Heeeeey, let's walk home togetheeeeeeer
I can heeeeeear your vooooooice
everywheeere like a re-sounding sim-fonyyyy
I can't go on.
I'm done!
Hey Kagami, were you singing with me?
Of course I was.
To anyone who did not hear me, please turn your TV's volume up and listen once more.
Letting Tama do everything is relaxing.
Aww, thanks!
What a convenient child.
Next Episode
Remiss@Rankings
Time for Remiss Rankings.
Things that don't try.
Things that don't try
Number 3.
Number 3
Crane game arms
Try harder.
Try
harder
Number 2.
Number 2
Pens that don't write when
they still have ink
Do you even care?
Do
you
even care?
Number 1.
Number 1
This preview segment
Hey, I don't know what's coming up next.
Hey, I
don't
know what's coming up next
Next Time, on Episode 8
Next time, on Episode 8.
Tactical Loneliness.
Tactical Loneliness