I'll kill the bastard who ordered them to do this—Kida Masaomi!
Those are the eyes of someone who's prepared to die.
Do you mean that Horada?
What Horada?
I thought I should tell you what he's thinking.
I'm also prepared to kill someone.
I won't let anyone contradict that!
Are you prepared to accept what you're
about to see, no matter how horrible it may be?
Kida!
Why...?
Masaomi...?
Mikado...!
Ryugamine...?
Why...?
This is definitely about as bad as it gets.
So, the black biker shows herself!
Guys, turn all these losers into dust!
Now! Turn on them!
You bastard!
Hey, what's going on?
What the hell is this?!
You piece of shit!
Yo.
Ka-Ka-Kadota!
Wh-Why you...!
If you tricked someone with this disguise, then
you should have been wary about adding new people.
Kadota...
Just what's...
Well, Togusa gave me this idea:
when Izumii got arrested, a guy named
Horada was the only one to get away scot-free.
Then he rounded up about thirty of his friends, had everyone throw on some yellow, and they all snuck into your gang.
Although I left Yumasaki and Karisawa
behind, since they're easily recognizable.
So, we don't get to help out at all?
Well, we are easily recognizable.
I didn't want to remember anything about you.
You're just that despicable.
Are you the one who broke Saki's leg?
N-No...I...
Are you the one who made Saki cry?!
My gun... Where's my gun?!
So it was you!
Damn you!
I was planning on breaking your skull open with that crowbar...
Mikado and Anri don't belong in this type of world.
So there's no reason for them to see a corpse.
That's what I think...
Masaomi!
Hang in there, Masaomi!
Kida!
Celty told me all about your and Sonohara's identities.
I'm sorry, I...
I had no idea...
Ryugamine, I...
You don't have to say anything. I get the gist of it.
So, don't force yourself to say anything.
It probably wouldn't have turned out like this if I'd just talked to you guys about what I was suffering through and worrying over.
I also felt like you were pulling away from me...
I was so scared...
Masaomi...
It's my fault!
I couldn't tell either of you about myself...
Sonohara...
I'm sorry.
Even though you're both very important to me...
...and I've always been so close to you...
You guys are absolutely perfect for each other.
Masaomi...
Hey, can I ask a favor of you if you're going to take me to a hospital?
What?
Take me to Raira General. I have a girl who's waiting for me there.
I'm counting on you...
Masaomi?
Masaomi?!
He looks awful.
Kadota...!
Man, I told him not to run away, but this time
he did too good a job of facing things head-on.
He needs to know what a happy medium is.
So, are these people...?
Yeah, they're all in the Dollars.
There are certain things you can do when you don't have a color.
Even if you tell them to disappear, they are who they are, so there's no way they can.
Hey, Horada's getting away!
This way, Horada.
That bastard...
I'll go after them.
Take Kida to the hospital.
Okay, got it!
I have a van parked out front.
Togusa, I'm counting on you!
Okay!
I've got something to clean up. I'll leave Kida to you.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Horada, Higa's not here!
Leave him!
Sh-Sh-Sh-She's here!
I-I-It's the black biker!
Shut up!
What are we going to do, Horada?
For now, we're going to run away.
We'll escape somewhere and wait until things cool down...
Then, once Izumii gets out of the pen, it'll be payback time!
Horada, in front of us! In front of us!
In front?
Th-That's...Shizuo!
That's Heiwajima Shizuo!
He's alive?!
Um, why's there a street sign in the middle of the road?
How is he still alive? How?!
Horada!
Hey...
You won't get away!
Pull yourself together, Horada!
Th-The black biker!
Calm down, Horada!
You've got some nerve, coming that close to a police bike.
Don't underestimate traffic cops, you brats.
Horada and the others were arrested.
I heard they claimed that Heiwajima Shizuo
destroyed their car, but their words fell upon deaf ears.
Take care of him.
Thank you for everything.
Huh?
Where's Sonohara?
That's it all right.
Now I can finally get that reward from the Awakusu Association.
Okay. However, I couldn't retrieve the bullets...
Well, that's fine.
I would've been lucky if you'd killed Shizu-chan with this.
So, you used me to give Horada that information about Shizuo?
He would've died if you'd hit him in either the head or the heart.
How disappointing.
And that's how it is, Mother.
Huh?
Um...Thank you very much.
Now go home and live a normal life.
Um...so you're Orihara Izaya?
Oh, you're Sonohara Anri?
Or should I say Saika?
What do you want at this late hour?
You're going to let me slash you.
Oh?
Why? Why have you done this?
I haven't really done anything.
Well, if I had to give a reason for my
actions, I guess it's because I love people.
I guess I wanted to see the many faces that mankind has to offer.
Question time!
Was my answer just now the truth or a lie?
I'll know...once I gain control of you.
By the way, what about you?
If you truly want to lead a happy, peaceful life, shouldn't you just slash everyone you know?
That's...
That's not the answer!
Well then, can you say that it's right to not make your feelings for either Mikado or Kida clear, despite knowing they're both attracted to you?
Don't you just use your belief that you can't love others as an excuse to complacently accept how things are?
Aren't you just using your assumption that you can't love others as an excuse to be complacent with how things currently are?
Saika loves people in your stead?
Don't be ridiculous—
Just shut up!
You know...
You shouldn't underestimate me.
I mean, it's not like I got to be Shizu-chan's rival by just pretending to fight with him.
At the very least...
You shouldn't have given this to me.
I'll tell you right now that I won't use it on you.
Just whom should I use it on?
How about that couple walking by over there?
It shouldn't cause you too much emotional pain, since you can't love others.
I'd known for a long time that Higa had fallen victim to the Slasher.
Why do you think I told him to get this gun back for me?
Because of you.
I wanted to declare war on you.
I deeply love people, too.
Like I'd ever hand them over to some sword.
People are my playthings.
Oh, but you can have Shizu-chan; I don't need him.
I'm praying for you to cut him up like a fish as soon as possible.
Good luck!
See you!
You're late.
What's up with your face?
What happened?
I got hit with a pretty good punch.
Hey!
Huh?
Simon?
Hey, I have something to tell you, but you're not going to like it.
You're so cowardly it's funny.
Yeah...I know I'm a coward.
But, Simon...
I love my own cowardice.
Do you remember Masaomi's girlfriend? She called my store.
She told us all about you and what you're doing.
Saki did?
Why would she...?
Because she's truly in love with Masaomi.
It looks like she's turned her back on you.
I see... Saki, huh...
Hey, Izaya...
Don't ransack this town too much.
Simon, I told you I truly love people.
Don't try to trick me with that logic.
In reality, you just don't want to lose to Shizuo, right?
You just have a Shizuo complex, don't you?
You don't realize just how much those around you can tell what you're thinking.
...Simon,
You seem like a totally different person when you're speaking Russian.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What?
You're the one who told Horada about Mikado, right?
I wonder...
Vindictive people like you are just scary.
Geez...whenever someone reacts exactly the way I expect them to,
there are always people like Shizuo and Simon
who turn those expectations on their heads.
That's why I'll never ever stop loving people.
That's it!
That's definitely how I'm able to keep working this piece of shit job.
It's so fun it makes me vomit.
I'll say it again, but I'm pretty sure that humanity hates you.
Probably...
Sa...
I know.
You never came, did you, Masaomi?
You just kept calling Izaya, didn't you?
Again and again...
Izaya laughed as he showed me his phone's incoming call history.
But you don't need to worry about it.
Even if you had come, not much would've changed.
Stop it...
Then at least you didn't get injured...
Let's break up!
Let's break up...
I'm horrible...
What did Saki ever see in me?
The fact that you're oddly obedient.
How long have you been here?
Not long.
Karisawa and the others told me everything.
You're a fool.
You really are a fool, Masaomi.
You've known that for a long time.
Um, there's something I have to apologize for.
Actually, I got caught by those people on purpose.
Izaya told me it'd all stop if I did.
That's why that night...
That night, I went by myself to their meeting place...
And afterwards, Izaya told people about it...
I know.
He told you to, didn't he?
He told you to keep pretending you couldn't walk so he could reign me in.
He probably wanted to turn me into his pawn.
Masaomi...
I have ESP, you know.
This is the first time I've ever disobeyed him.
I think I can finally say it.
I couldn't come save you.
I'm sorry.
But, I still love you.
So, please, don't break up with me.
Hey...
You really are a fool, Masaomi.
You're an absolute idiot.
I can't help it.
Can't you close your eyes to at least one of my faults?
If you know you have one, then fix it.
We'll fix it together.
A few days later, Masaomi disappeared along with Mikajima Saki.
They notified the school that they were dropping out and just disappeared.
Everyday life changed for the three of us that had been living together.
And yet, the city hasn't changed at all.
Russia Sushi!
Neither has he,
Ready, go!
nor have they,
or them,
or him,
It's so tranquil.
Yeah.
Apparently there's internal strife even amongst the remaining people from the Blue Squares,
and the Yellow Scarves have also quieted down a lot.
I see. Then there's no reason to worry about anyone coming after Anri or Mikado for the time being.
Eh?
Wai... What's with that bold change of clothes?
If you're going to provoke me like that, I've got to take a shower and prepare some bed sheets.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Well, usually you'd give me a Hell Stab
somewhere around here or pinch my cheek.
I actually am trying to provoke you.
Or even them.
We'll never regain the everyday life that we've lost, will we?
I wonder if I loved Kida...
Is that why I feel so lonely?
But, I don't know.
I don't really...understand that stuff.
There is one thing I understood.
The Dollars are this city.
Various people come and go, without being dyed a certain color.
There's always something happening.
There are always people hating and loving each other, cultivating friendships, and passing others by.
Just like a city will continue to exist as long as there are people around, the Dollars will also continue to exist.
No matter what anyone says.
Good Evening.
'Evening.
Oh, we have a new person, I see.
Hello,
nice to meet you. I'm Bacula.
Kanra invited me to join!
Huh, I met him through the Internet, but did you as well, Bacula?
No, we know each other from RL.
We're like business partners!
At least that's the front we put up...
Kya!
When are you going to die, Kanra?
That's a harsher quip than I expected!
That's horrible.
Sorry,
Kanra was being really annoying,
So I just...
Um, Bacula,
please excuse me if I'm wrong.
Are you Masaomi?
Is that you, Masaomi?
It...It'd be great if you'd just say something.
You've met me in RL, so please tell
everyone what's so charming about me.
The square root of three points.
Huh?
If I were to express your charm with points,
it'd be the square root of three points.
So, in other words, I'm so beautiful that you can't evenly divide me?
More like you're too difficult for elementary
school kids, so we shouldn't show you to them.
Oh, sorry,
this is it for me today.
Okay.
See you.
Good night.
Um, Bacula!
Please come again!
You're always welcome!
I'll be back. See you!
'Night.
Good Night!
Bacula has left the chat room.
A place to come home to and an everyday life that's been lost...
...also exists on the Internet.
He'll come back.
Eh?
Masaomi will definitely come back.
So, let's give him crap when he does.
Let's pretend to be really mad at him as a joke!
Both of us will do it together.
I still think it's mysterious even now...
...but I also get the feeling it's not.
Anyway, it was something that changed my life.
And yet, it seems like nothing's changed at all.
It was something very, very strange,
and, at the same time, something everyone experiences.
It all happened here in Ikebukuro.