King Selfish is surrounded by an abundance of Egogy.
His resurrection draws near, no?
It does, so I'm putting my plan in motion.
Plan?
Take a look.
If you remove one small part of this fan,
it all falls apart.
Those Precures are the same way.
Without Mana, they'll all fall apart.
I see.
You plan to draw Cure Heart away from her comrades.
I'll crush anyone who tries to stop Daddy's resurrection.
Why isn't it Christmas already?
She's even more excited than usual.
Mana, you've always loved Christmas, huh?
Yeah!
When I was a kid, I wanted to be Santa Claus!
I'd give love to good boys and girls!
It would suit you.
We're all going to see a parade, so I'm super excited!
Yeah!
Merry Christmas!
A bit early for it, though.
Welly well well.
I do believe you might beeeeee Aida Mana?
Aren't you, like, gonna join the Student Council President Speech Contest?
Student Council President Speech Contest?
You haven't heard?
It's, like, who's the most presidential of the student council presidents?
Like...
To deeeetermine a veritable King of Student Council Puuuuuresindents!
King of Student Council Presidents, you say?!
In that case...
I absolutely have to join!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
I've never heard of a contest to determine the King of Student Council Presidents.
It says many Prime Ministers entered in their student years...
In that case, Mana can't refuse!
I'm so hyped!
Hey, it says it takes place on December 24th!
Huh? Christmas Eve?
The time overlaps with the entire parade to boot!
Aww...
Guess I can't enter the contest.
I think you should go.
You want to be the King of Student Council Presidents.
Certainly.
But...
We can always hang out another time,
so go out and win it!
But I've got student council work I need to do over the break...
I'll find a way to finish it.
Really?
Yeah.
So go win that contest.
Rikka!
You're a lifesaver!
Here we go...
With Mana gone, we're gonna be busy.
Rikka, are you sure you're okay with this?
I know you want to be with Mana on Christmas...
Well, a bit...
But soon, we'll enter high school, get careers,
and chase after our own dreams...
We can't just stay together forever, right?
Even if we're apart, we have our own lives to lead...
A Selfish Trap!
A Christmas Without Mana!
Let's see...
This is all the paperwork you need finished, right?
Yeah!
All right, I'll knock this out before I meet up with the others!
Rikka, won't Christmas be a bummer without me around?
Not at all.
That bummed me out...
Look, I want you to become King of Presidents.
So even if we're apart, I'll carry on!
Rikka...
All right, then I won't let you down!
diner
Pig's Tail
Punctual, punctual!
Shall we not take our deeeeeparture?
Like, move it or lose it!
Okay!
You student council members have a lot of work.
I respect how much effort the president and Hishikawa put in.
I just follow Mana's lead.
We're helping out, too!
Gotcha!
Will Mana be all right?
I hope she doesn't flub her lines...
Can't stop thinking about Mana even when she's away, huh?
It's challed love!
Who said that?
J-Just the wind, I'm sure!
This is, like, totally the place!
Please enter, if you'd beeee so kind!
Hello!
Student Council President
Speech Contest
Yoohoo, Mana!
Regina!
Here's my Christmas present to you.
What happened?!
Regina, what's this about?
Without you around, the rest of the Precures will be a cinch to beat.
It'll be a piece of cake!
Your just deeeeeserts, wouldn't you say?
So it was you?
We got tricked!
Oh no! We need to give this to the teachers by today!
Huh?
And this, too!
We've gotta get these done!
What do we do?
All of those?
I'll make copies right away!
Now what?
We won't make the parade at this rate!
Who can we call for help?
Hey Rikka, look at this.
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's Memo?
Rikka, when it gets super duper busy,
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
just take a deep breath and relax!
Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana...
This one's stuck on something!
"You can't work on an empty stomach!"
Eat up if you're hungry.
Mana's   Memo
You can't work on
an empty stomach!
Eat up if you're hungry.
It's my homemade
omelette rice balls!
It's my homemade omelette rice balls!
Wow!
It looks yummy!
She made this for me.
There's another memo here!
Sorry Rikka,
the treasury paperwork
got backed up.
Good luck...
Love ya, babe!
Sorry Rikka, the treasury paperwork got backed up. Good luck...
Of course.
It's like Mana never left.
Yeah, I feel like she's still dragging me along at her pace.
But you sound...
Like you enjoy it!
Oh, do I?
Mana, I love you too...
All right, let's keep working!
No luck.
Just like Regina said, it won't budge an inch.
This is a magical cage, so it won't break.
Okie-dokie, I'm off to crush the Precures, so wait right there!
Bye!
Girls...
European
Park
Wow!
It's beautiful!
It'd be wonderful if Mana could see this as well!
I'm sure she's fighting her own battle right now.
It's her first step toward becoming Prime Minister!
You're right.
Let's take a lot of pictures to show her later.
Yes!
Now, say cheese!
So close!
I know Mana could snatch it if she were here...
Don't worry. You can do it!
All right, one more try!
Okay!
Yeah!
I got it, Mana!
Rikka...
Rikka, you really are lonely without Mana, huh?
No.
I'm not lonely.
She's fakin' it.
No time like the present to fiiiiiiinish them off, right?
Yeah! I want to, like, get some R&R!
Wow, pretty!
It's gorgeous!
Well, aren't those people having fun.
Who needs Christmas, anyway?
No, let's not go there! Everyone's so happy!
Aw, just wipe Christmas off the calendar.
I'll turn you into a splendid Selfish!
Self!
What's with that Christmas tree?
It's way creepy!
It's a Selfish!
Merry Hurtmas!
Girls, let's go!
Okay!
Rachel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Seems the broken fan's all here!
Regina!
Broken fan?
What do you mean?
I mean that without Mana,
you're just like a fan without its crux.
Now ladies and germs, shall we beeeeeegin our battle?
Wait, no!
It was you who led Mana away!
I suppose our disguise was too flawless for you to notice?
That whole speech contest thing was a total fib.
We just wanted to separate you from Mana.
Why you...
You'll pay for taking advantage of Mana's dreams!
Just keep gettin' mad...
Get them, Selfish!
Merry Hurtmas!
Sword Hurricane!
Where is Mana?
I dunno.
Would we really tell you if we did?
Eat this!
How could you, Regina?
Mana stayed up all night thinking up a speech for that contest!
It's her fault for being a sucker.
Give Mana back!
Wh-What's with you?!
Self!
Seeelf!
These brats...
They're pretty strong for not havin' Mana!
What moron said this would be a piece of cake without their leader?
Mana, are you okay?!
I'm fine...
but I have to go...
to my friends...
Seems you're in a bind,
my Sweet Heart.
Seeelf!
Self!
Why?
Without Mana around,
you all should've been helpless cannon fodder!
Sorry, but we're together even when we're apart!
Together when you're apart?
What's that even mean?
Even if she's not by our side,
Mana's
Memo
Rikka, when it gets
super, duper busy, just
take a deep breath
and relax! Don't worry.
You can do it!
Mana's always thinking about us.
And so we think about her, too.
That's why we're together even when we're apart!
Because our hearts...
Are always connected!
Regina, I know you're no different!
Mana is always in your heart!
You're always thinking about her!
Aren't you?
Well, you never seem to shut up about Mana...
It's kinda depressing.
Sh-Shut up, you two!
Mana's the same way!
Mana always has you in her thoughts.
She wonders what you're doing...
if you're feeling hurt or if you're feeling lonely...
Mana's always saying that she wants to talk with you once more!
My chest is tingling again...
Why?
Daddy should be the one I love...
What?
Why'd it get so weak?
It's reflecting Regina's emotional state.
You can't defeat us!
We're all connected by Mana's love, after all.
Selfish!
Seeeelf!
Seeeeeeelf!
Seeeeeeeeeeeelf!
Regina,
you like Mana too, right?
N-No, I don't even...
You like her!
Just admit it already!
Give it a rest!
I like her, okay?
Even I like Mana!
Got a problem?
Is that true?
Mana!
Ooooh, she heard it all!
Well, that's embarrassing.
I'm so glad you're safe!
You too!
Indeed!
Hey Regina, when you said you liked me, did you really mean it?
O-Of course not.
I didn't mean it one bit, duh!
Huh? You didn't?
Come on!
You did mean it, didn't you?
Come on, say it, Regina! Say it!
Cut it out!
Self...
Q-Quit loafing around!
Selfish!
Self!
Girls, let's go!
Kyupirappa!
Precure Royal Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love loooooove!
Huh?
Regina, wait!
We're still your friends!
Our feelings won't ever change!
I'm glad you said you liked me!
Regina, can you come back one more time?
Mana...
It hurts...
I like you...
but I also like Daddy!
You have friends all around you,
but I only have Daddy!
Regina...
Regina.
Daddy?
Where are you, my beloved daughter?
That's right...
I have to go home.
Daddy will be awake soon.
Regina!
Mana, are you okay?
I'm more impressed that you knew where we'd be.
Mr. Klondike helped me.
It's been a while.
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Mr. Klondike came back!
This one's not a fake, right?
It seems he's found the final Sacred Treasure, the Eternal Golden Crown!
Wow!
It's a legendary circlet that can grant its wearer boundless wisdom!
I wonder what mysteries this crown could reveal for us?
Dokidoki Precure:
The Fated Battle!
Ace vs. Regina!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!