Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
Ready, Shinji?
Yes, ma'am.
Release final safeties!
Evangelion Unit 01, lift off!
Shinji?
I want you to just concentrate on walking.
Take a step...
It's walking!
Shinji, pull it together!
Hurry! Hurry, you need to get up!
Shinji, stay calm!
It only feels like your arm is being hurt!
-Where are its defensive systems?!
-Signal inactive.
Field not raised!
It's not working?
-Left forearm damaged!
-Circuits severed!
Shinji, break loose!
Fracture in frontal cranium!
The armor can't take much more!
Skull damage! Severity unknown!
Control neurons
are disconnecting in a cascade!
Pilot readings lost!
Shinji!
I don't know this ceiling.
The Angels have returned.
It's all too sudden.
It's just like 15 years ago.
Calamity never warns before striking.
This might also be considered a blessing.
It means that all our previous
investments were worthwhile.
That remains to be seen.
If it is not useful,
it is the same as wasted money.
Indeed.
Information regarding the Angels
is spreading among the public.
We need a disinformation campaign.
Nerv's work must be carried out
both properly and quickly.
Those concerns are already
being addressed. Rest assured.
This morning at the Prime Minister's
Office in Tokyo-2,
the government held a press--
-The government claims--
-UN Forces Japan were deployed--
They went with Scenario B-22, huh?
Once again, the facts get buried.
The Public Affairs Office was ecstatic.
They say they finally feel useful.
What a bunch of optimists.
I wonder.
I think they're actually terrified.
They have good reason to be.
Well, that's certainly true.
Still, Ikari... can't you manage Nerv
and the Evas better?
First there was Unit 00, and now
Unit 01 needs repairs after its debut.
These bills could bankrupt a country.
I hear you gave that toy to your own son.
People. Time. And money.
You and your son seem to have
an insatiable appetite for resources.
And this is not your only job.
The Human Instrumentality Project.
That is your top priority.
Indeed.
That project is the only glimmer of light
in this desperate situation.
Humanity's only hope.
In any event, there can be no
pushing back the project's timetable
due to the Angels' arrival.
Your budget request will be considered.
The Council will take it from here.
Good work, Ikari.
Ikari, there's no turning back now.
I'm well aware.
Humanity's time is running out.
Yeah, AC is humanity's greatest invention!
What a triumph of science.
Shinji's regained consciousness.
So, what's his condition?
No external injuries, but they say
his memory's a little jumbled.
Was there psychological contamination?!
They say there's no risk of that.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm not surprised.
We threw him into the deep end.
It's no wonder.
His cranial nerves took a lot of strain.
"His heart," don't you mean?
NOTICE OF CONSTRUCTION
GUIDED MUNITIONS SYS. BUILDING NO. 25
-Okay! Okay!
-Keep it coming!
Good, right there!
Once the Evas and this city are
fully operational, we might have a shot.
You think we can win?
Ever the optimist, I see.
Hey, a bright outlook is essential
for people to live their lives.
I suppose.
Your outlook is helpful sometimes.
Later.
Paging Dr. Ugai of
Internal Medicine Department 1.
Please contact Dr. Azuma
of Surgery Department 1.
Medical conference regarding Incident B
will take place as scheduled.
All attendees, please gather
in Conference Room 2.
Are you sure they should live separately?
For the Ikaris, life without
the other around is the norm.
In other words, living together
would be strange for them?
He's living alone?
Correct. His quarters will be
a room in Block Six nearby.
-Is that acceptable?
-Yes, sir.
Are you sure, Shinji?
It's fine, I prefer being alone.
It's all the same to me.
What did you say?!
I said, I'm going to have
Shinji live with me!
I got permission from the top brass.
Don't worry,
I won't mess around with some kid.
Of course you won't!
Don't even suggest that!
-She needs to learn to take a joke.
-You're always doing this!
Right, then! We have to
celebrate in style tonight!
Celebrate what?
The arrival of a new roommate, of course!
You're moving, then?
Yes. We never thought this city
would actually become a battlefield.
Who would?
My husband wants me
and our children to evacuate, too.
Evacuate, huh...
They call this a fortress city,
but we can't count on it to protect us.
I get chills just thinking about
what happened yesterday!
You're so right.
If you don't mind,
we're gonna make a quick detour.
Where?
Someplace special.
It's...
kind of a desolate city, isn't it?
It's time.
Wow!
Buildings are sprouting from the ground!
This is the fortress city built to counter
and defeat the Angels.
This is Tokyo-3. This is our city.
And... it's the city that you protected.
I think your boxes of stuff
are already here.
Actually, I only moved here
recently, myself.
Come on in!
Uh, thanks for having me...
Shinji, this is your home.
I-I'm home.
Welcome back.
I know it's a little cluttered,
but don't let it bother you.
She calls this...
a little?
Sorry, could you put the groceries
in the fridge?
Oh, sure.
Ice...
snacks...
and beer is all she's got?
What does she do at home?
Um, what's this other refrigerator for?
Oh, leave that one alone. I hate to bother
someone when they're sleeping.
Sleeping?
Let's eat!
Let's eat...
This is what makes life worth living!
Aren't you hungry?
It's TV dinner food, but it's pretty good.
Well... I'm just not used to
eating like this.
Hey! We don't put up with
fussy eaters here!
No, I... That's not what I meant!
I...
Isn't this fun?
Sharing a meal with someone like this.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay,
let's do the next one!
One, two, shoot!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
Shoot!
Sorry, Shinji!
Okay, we've now divided up
all our daily chores fair and square!
Yes, ma'am.
Right, this place is your home
starting today.
So no standing on ceremony for anything!
Uh, yes, ma'am.
"Yes, ma'am" this and "Yes, ma'am" that!
Stop being so uptight!
You're a boy, aren't you?!
Let's hear some backbone and confidence!
Yes, ma'am.
Fine, whatever.
Hop into the tub
and wash all your cares away!
The bath is life's washing machine!
Ms. Misato!
What?
Huh?
Oh, him?
He's a new hot-spring penguin.
A what?
His name is Pen-Pen.
Our other roomie.
And... maybe you could cover up?
Maybe I laid on
the cheerfulness too thick.
He might see right through it.
Ms. Misato Katsuragi...
I guess she's not a bad person.
The bath is life's washing machine!
But... I tend to remember
all the bad things when I'm in the bath.
Father...
and Rei Ayanami.
How was Rei, sir?
I understand you visited her
at the hospital this afternoon.
She'll be back on her feet
in 20 days or so.
We need to get Unit 00 up and running
and ready for reactivation by then.
This will be rough... on those children.
No one else can pilot the Evas.
As long as they're alive,
that's what they'll do.
Regardless of how they feel about it?
SHINJI'S ROOM
SCHOOL TRANSFER FORM:
SHINJI IKARI
True, he was put through the wringer.
I don't know if he'll do it again.
Making sure he's operational
is part of your job.
I'm afraid.
Not sure how I should approach him.
Whining already?
You were so dramatic about taking him in.
Shove it!
When I said that,
I just saw Shinji as a means to an end.
I'm no different from Ritsuko.
He beat that Angel.
So why aren't I happy about it?
Another ceiling I've never seen before.
No surprise...
Nothing about this city is familiar.
This is your home!
Why am I even here?
Skull damage, severity unknown!
Operational integrity compromised!
Report!
Synchrograph inverting!
Neural pulse flow is reversing!
Shut down circuits! Block the flow, now!
I can't! Shutdown signal rejected!
It's not getting through!
Shinji's status?
Zero biometrics! Condition unknown!
Unit 01 completely shut down!
Misato!
I guess that's it.
Abort operation!
Pilot rescue has top priority!
Emergency plug eject, now!
I can't! System is
completely unresponsive!
It's what?!
The Eva has reactivated!
Impossible! It should be
completely non-operational!
-Has it gone...
-...berserk?!
We've won.
An A.T. Field!
It's no use!
As long as that field is up...
...it can't touch the Angel!
-Left arm restored!
-Incredible!
Unit 01 has also raised an A.T. Field!
The Angel's phase space
is being neutralized!
No, it's corroding it.
It tore through that A.T. Field
like it was nothing...
It's self-destructing?!
What happened to the Eva?
That's the Evas'...
...true nature.
Circuits connected.
System back online.
Graph readings at normal levels.
Pilot's vitals confirmed.
Expedite unit recovery.
Pilot rescue has top priority!
Shinji? I'm coming in for a second.
I forgot to tell you something.
People will thank you
for what you did today.
You should be proud.
Good night, Shinji.
Keep it up.
TO BE CONTINUED
NEXT EPISODE
With Shinji drifting through his new life,
there was little hope
of him ever making friends.
But the fact that he's the Eva's pilot
makes him a celebrity.
Next episode! "The Silent Phone"!
More fan service coming up next time, too!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming