Long have I awaited this moment, human filth.
With the Subterranean
and Deep Sea kings gone,
the Terror Lizard Clan can at last
reclaim rulership of the Earth!
Now leading target towards point Bravo.
Roger.
We are inbound and on schedule.
We'll be on top of Bravo shortly.
UNPARALLELED PERIL
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
And who are you?
Hello? What is it?
What do you mean, come back?!
You're the one who said some weirdo monster
had awoken and flew me out here!
Weirdo...
That's right.
I was just about to start.
Listen well! I am the Ancient King.
As ruler of the dinosaurs
who once ruled this planet,
"Trouble?" So what?
It's not my problem.
I stand above all other lifeforms.
Hey, shut it!
Can't you see I'm on the phone here?!
I'm so tired of this.
Who's he think he is, ordering people about?
Are you done?
What's with the chin?
Trying to be scary?
Should I be intimidated?
Act brave while you still can, little runt.
Runt?! How dare you!
Ah, so you aren't helpless!
But if you intend to destroy me,
a giant meteor is about the only way.
Fine. I'll do that then.
Don't make me laugh.
How about another 300 million year nap?
Fist of Flowing Water, Crushed Rock.
It goes something like that.
Want to try?
You both look like quick learners.
I bet you'll get the hang of it in no time.
This is the cool thing you
said you wanted to show us?
A sales pitch?
I'll pass.
You do it, Genos.
No, I will pass too.
What I seek is not the art of self-defense,
but absolute destructive power.
You punks!
You dare mock our fighting style?!
I, Charanko, the top disciple, challenge you—
I give up!
Is he really your best?
Yeah...
I heard your dojo was full of skilled fighters.
Well, one of my disciples went wild.
He beat my most skilled students
so badly they're all out of commission.
The rest got scared and quit.
He's that strong?
What's his name?
Garo...
He was my top disciple at the time,
but I gave him a good beating and expelled him.
You must pack a punch, old man.
Hey! This is the famed hero "Silverfang,"
the 3rd ranked S-class hero.
In combat, he toys with opponents, flowing like water,
then delivers a blow like a raging river smashing huge rocks!
A master of martial arts!
You only became a hero recently, right?
You'll regret taking Master Bang lightly!
Enough, Charanko!
Do not disgrace us.
Saitama is many times stronger than me.
Master, you can't be serious...
Mr. Silverfang!
The Association sent me.
An emergency summons has
been issued to all S-class heroes!
Please come to Association Headquarters.
Oh! Is that you, Mr. Genos?
Since all S-class heroes have been
summoned, please come as well.
Is it threat level Dragon?
Here we go...
Charanko, look after the dojo.
Be careful, Master!
If all the S-class heroes are being summoned,
they may need your help too, Master.
Will you come?
I will… since I've got nothing to do.
CITY A – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Oh, it's Silverfang!
It's been a while, Atomic Samurai.
I knew you'd come.
And this is the cyborg Genos and...
Hm? Who's this?
This is the B-class hero Saitama.
His exceptional talent will one day place him
atop Class S, I'm sure, so we asked him to come.
Hi, middle-aged hero dude!
Put 'er there!
No handshakes.
I acknowledge only the strong.
Once you've climbed up to Class S,
I'll greet you properly.
Besides, I'm not middle-aged yet.
I'm only thirty-seven.
Thirty-seven isn't middle-aged?
I had no idea…
Hey, who brought a B-class nobody along?
Don't you think it's beneath us?
And even if you were invited,
a polite person would decline. The nerve!
I bet you're only here for some creepy reason
like getting close to us S-class heroes.
You disgust me.
Get out.
What's with this sassy, lost child?
That is Tornado. Rank 2, S Class.
What do you mean "that"?
I'm a person, you know!
She defeats monsters with her psychic powers.
She is an Esper.
Oh yeah?
It seems everyone's assembled.
We should join them.
Hey...
Stop ignoring me!
CLASS S, RANK 17
CO-CO CONVICT
Maybe this will be my chance
to get closer to Genos...
CLASS S, RANK 16
GENOS
It must be serious.
Almost everyone is here.
CLASS S, RANK 15
METAL BAT
Demon or Dragon, bring it on!
CLASS S, RANK 14
TANK-TOP MASTER
Saitama? The name rings a bell...
CLASS S, RANK 13
FLASHY FLASH
CLASS S, RANK 12
WATCHDOG MAN
Somebody farted.
CLASS S, RANK 11
SUPERALLOY BLACKLUSTER
They're all checking out my guns.
Hell yeah!
CLASS S, RANK 10
PIG GOD
CLASS S, RANK 9
DRIVE KNIGHT
CLASS S, RANK 8
ZOMBIEMAN
No one looks particularly enthusiastic.
And does that pig ever stop eating?
CLASS S, RANK 7
KING
CLASS S, RANK 6
METAL KNIGHT
ABSENT
CLASS S, RANK 5
CHILD EMPEROR
Rank 1's a no show again?
I was hoping to see him.
CLASS S, RANK 4
ATOMIC SAMURAI
Is Silverfang going to take
those youngsters on as students?
CLASS S, RANK 3
SILVERFANG
Well, why are we all here?
CLASS S, RANK 2
TERRIBLE TORNADO
Who knows?
I had to drop everything and then
they kept me waiting for two hours.
CLASS S, RANK 1
BLAST
ABSENT
CLASS B, RANK 63
SAITAMA
Can I have some tea?
My apologies for being late.
We do not know the whereabouts of
Metal Knight or Blast, nor can we reach them.
No sense waiting any longer,
so let's begin this emergency meeting.
You can call me Sitch.
I'm with the Association. I will be briefing you.
Let's get right down to brass tacks.
You heroes are here because
you're the best of the best.
And now...
We're asking you to save the Earth!
However, even with your S-class skills,
there is no guarantee of survival.
Walking away also takes courage.
Should you choose to do so now,
you will retain your S-class status.
But those who stay and hear me out
will not be allowed to walk away.
You will be confined here until the incident
is over in order to avoid a general panic.
Are you all willing to hear this?
Whatever's going on,
it better be worth calling all of us here.
I skipped out on my little
sister's piano recital for this.
If it's a load of crap,
I'm gonna tear this whole building apart.
Like you could do that with that skinny stick.
Yeah?
How 'bout I bust your head open instead?
If you think you can, go on and try, pillbug head!
What was that?!
Hurry up and get on with it.
Otherwise Mr. Pompadour here is going to die.
Hey, bobby pin, you siding with the girl?
The great seer, Madame Shibabawa, is dead!
Shibabawa?
Was she killed?
No.
While looking into the future
for the next six months,
she became agitated and had a coughing fit.
She popped a cough drop in
her mouth and ended up choking on it.
I get it!
So we have to figure out how to prevent
disasters without the help of predictions.
That's the focus of this meeting.
No.
Madame Shibabawa has only been
able to predict a handful of disasters.
Excuse me!
Hey, you there.
Who's this Shibabawa?
A hero?
You don't know?
She was a seer. A great one at that.
She correctly predicted earthquakes
and monster attacks.
We've gotten through many crises
without Madame Shibabawa's predictions.
But even so, we provided a bodyguard
and gave her special treatment.
Yes, because her few predictions
were 100% accurate.
The crux of the problem, though,
is her last, greatest prophecy.
Even as she choked on that final cough drop,
she managed to leave this note.
It is a prophecy that will
absolutely come to pass.
Here it is!
Can you read it?
Th-The earth...
...is in trouble?!
THE EARTH.....
IS IN TROUBLE
What? That's so dumb.
Can I go? I have cram school.
I know you are a prodigy, Child Emperor,
but if you cannot grasp the danger,
it reveals how immature you still are.
What'd you say?!
Listen up!
Madame Shibabawa's predictions
are 100% accurate!
She has predicted many
catastrophes in the past.
A few of them resulted
in the loss of countless lives.
But not once did Madame Shibabawa
use the word "trouble."
This will be something more dangerous
than a Dragon-level catastrophe or monster.
And it will occur in the next six months!
Okay, but we've no idea when
in the next six months.
Yeah, hard to plan for that.
You are correct.
But I want you all to be ready
for a fight in the next six months.
In the next six months means...
it could be tomorrow, or even today.
That's true. Who are you, anyway?
Good thing I'm here.
The building is under attack!
That's impossible!
This is the Hero Association HQ!
A formidable fortress, to be sure!
Time to attack.
Hawk, Eagle, Falcon, Kite!
Yar!
Wipe out these so-called heroes
and the land will be ours!
We will dive straight in!
Follow me, the Sky King!
Father... Above us...
Escape...
Me, the Sky King,
killed like some worthless insect.
Who could have—
What was that?
Who knows?
It flew, so we killed it.
That is good.
Duty, to protect ship.
Emergency power activated.
What was that?
What's going on out there?
I don't know.
All communications have been cut off.
Damn it...
Impossible!
Dad!
We're okay now.
Grab on to me.
That's the way.
Good job.
What is this?
There are survivors?
Ship, failed to kill all.
Then we kill.
That is good.
Get away now!
You think I don't sense your thirst for blood?
I accompanied Master Atomic
and was waiting for the
S-class hero meeting to end,
only to meet thunder and destruction.
Is this your doing?!
Destruction levels at 99.8%?
City A was destroyed in an instant!
Who could have known her prediction
would come true this soon?!
Hey! Why was this building spared?
We assigned Metal Knight
to construct this building.
That's why it's stronger
than the average shelter.
So that's why there are no windows.
We should go outside and see.
To be sure it's the prophecy.
Master! Will you—
Master...
That's big!
Are they aliens?
So that's what blew the city to pieces.
Go back to...
your planet!
A militant creature.
Also cautious.
Hurry. Let us hurry and kill.
That is good.
Can it be killed?
Each of its strikes is lethal!
I can't beat this thing...
Such a weak species.
Easily killed.
That is good.
It's splitting?
Damn, not now...
I will dispose of this. You handle the rest.
Very well.
I will go kill those that ran.
That is good.
I—
Master!
Iairon, you okay?
You know, your left arm...
Master! Swords have no effect on this monster.
Forget me! Retreat!
Outta my way!
Iai! The path of the sword
does not end for you yet!
Stop bleeding!
Yes, Master!
So there is a life-form
on this planet that can fight.
Excellent!
Try to withstand our invasion!
Planet, eh?
You from outer space?
And you got friends up in that floaty toy?
Yeah, that's it.
I doubt you alone have the power
to do all this to the city.
Atomic Samurai, count us in.
You the bastard that smashed this town?!
And if I am?
For all the beautiful men you killed...
I claim vengeance!
Each separate attack must be
delivered with intent to kill!
Dark Angel Flash!
Issue an evacuation warning
to City A and all neighboring cities.
Right now!
And expand the System M
vitals monitor to cover all of City A.
We need an accurate count of the survivors.
What's the threat level?
"Dragon," without doubt.
No...
This might be "God."
Four S-class heroes should be enough
to take care of the enemy on the ground.
The problem is that.
We can't reach it.
Any aircraft would be shot down in seconds.
King, you're one of the top fighters in Class S.
Give us your take.
King, rank 7, Class S.
Said to be the strongest man on Earth,
and I see he is well respected by the other heroes…
There's nothing I can do.
It's too high in the sky.
There's no way to attack it.
But the mysterious craft is currently dormant.
We should use this opportunity
to call in Metal Knight.
What the heck?! That's pathetic!
Aren't you supposed to be the strongest man?
Hey, Tornado.
If you piss King off, he'll kill you.
This city's been blown away,
and you're just going to give them a free hand?
Unbelievable!
Well forget it! I'll take care of this myself.
Wait, I will go too.
I do not know how effective I can be,
but I will attack from the ground.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
I said forget about it!
Take it easy, Genos.
I understand how you feel,
but if you piss her off, she'll kill you.
Very well...
There is no need to team up anyway.
Master has already boarded the enemy ship.
Whether this is the prophecy or not,
there's not a single evil Master cannot defeat.
If such an evil existed,
then I assume the human race
would have perished long ago.
Well done making it this far, intruder!
But this is the end.
You see, there is no way
you can defeat me, Groribas!
My Acid Breath will melt you away!
Isn't it about time the boss showed up?
Well, if he's alive...
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Next
Time
The
Dominator
of the
Universe
I, Groribas, control this preview!
I perfected some new moves.
Now I have like twenty!
But I couldn't show them off,
because, you know, they killed me off first!
Next time on One-Punch Man episode eleven,
"The Dominator of the Universe."
It's your fight now, Lord Boros!