That sound could wake the dead.
Itadakimasu!
How is it?
It tastes great.
Yes, it's delicious.
Well, it's not too bad.
That's great!
This is a local dish from my village.
Is this thing you call "miso" made the same way as soy?
Yes.
I brought some of the miso my mother made.
There's a lot more,
so please eat up!
To Treize?
Yeah.
We've finally received notification about our supplies.
Kureha-chan and I will go sign for them.
We're running low on ammunition, medicine and various daily supplies, right?
We can finally relax a little now.
Where is Noel going?
Carl-san's studio, right?
Yes.
All right.
Kanata!
We'll have some intensive trumpet practice this afternoon.
You really mean it?
Food's ready.
Geez, how improper...
Your father would cry if he saw that.
Like I care.
Have a snack with your tea.
Fortune cookies, huh?
You still don't like them?
The kids at the church weren't responsible, were they?
The way they demand money for their useless superstitions,
it's the same as everywhere else.
Oh my, that's not true at all.
At least these are really delicious.
Oh, my!
Kana-chan seems like she fits in already.
It's cute how she always tries so hard.
You think so?
I'll acknowledge her zeal and diligence,
but it's not that easy to get by with those qualities alone.
What's with that expression?
It's a secret!
What?
That's so annoying.
Well then, off we go.
I'll be back later.
Okay.
Be careful.
Don't cause any trouble for Rio-sempai.
Commencing departure...
Have a good trip!
I don't expect you to get this right away,
but you basically have to control the sound with only your mouthpiece.
Try it!
Y-Yes!
How is life at base for you?
It's fun!
Typical of you to be so easygoing about everything.
I'm a bit envious of your optimism, though.
Come to think of it, why did you join the army?
That's because...
Um... I heard that I could learn to play a musical instrument for free...
But, I know that it's important to protect the c-country!
Doesn't bother me, even if it was for money or whatever...
Those with a clear goal in mind will usually last longer than those who don't.
Um... That's very kind of you.
Then, why did you join, Rio-sempai?
I...
Yeah...
I guess my reason's the opposite of yours.
But that's rare these days.
Especially for brass instruments, you hardly hear them outside of the military.
I heard it a long time ago...
A sound similar to yours, Sempai.
Kanata?
The sound of the sky...
What's wrong?
Hang in there!
Hang in there, Kanata!
Answer me!
No!
Please... just stay still.
I'm hot.
I'm hot, Mother...
Are you hot?
I know... It's all right.
You'll be fine.
Mo...
Mother...
What's wrong, Kanata?
Kanata!
I want to eat... snow...
I understand. Just wait!
Snow...
Where's the snow...
Why would we have any here?!
Calm down.
Calm down...
Medicine!
No. That should be my last resort!
Medicine, medicine...
Medicine! Medicine...
Found it!
...running low on many things, right?
Damn those idiots at the supply base!
Damn.
What should I do?
What should I...
Damn it!
Err... What can I do for you?
Don't tell me the children caused trouble again?
Please forgive my rudeness towards you.
So, um...
Please save her!
Drink this.
That's right.
Her fever is a little high, but this should bring it down.
Is it some kind of terrible illness?
I think it could be malaria.
Malaria? But that's a kid's illness...
Even adults can get it when they're extremely weak.
Very often, the kids that we take charge of are inflicted with this illness.
Even those who appear to be fine can be hit by a fever very suddenly.
She must have been fighting it off this whole time; I'm sure.
Th-Then...
Will Kanata get better?
She won't stay like this forever, will she...?
I think she'll be fine.
I'm so glad.
T-Thank you...
Err...
My name is Yumina.
These herbs have to be boiled.
Give it to her a little later.
Uh, thank you for everything.
Please, don't worry about it.
Caring for the people of this town is our joy and our duty.
May you be blessed with good fortune.
My gratitude for your cooperation!
Ow.
I-I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I'm just like "omiso".
The stuff we had this morning?
No.
Miso dregs...
When you make miso soup, you strain the miso...
What remains are the beans and dregs.
An excess baggage, or a burden,
and so...
I've always felt that way, ever since I was a kid.
So...
I've always wanted to work really hard, so I wouldn't burden anyone.
And yet...
You are a lot more sensitive than you look.
And also, a selfish, spoiled kid...
Did... Did I say something?
Quite a lot... Right?
That's right, sempai!
W-What?
That song you were just singing...
W-What are you talking about?
It goes like this.
How astonishing.
And she's only heard it once.
This isn't the first time I've heard it.
I heard it a long time ago.
I've always wanted to play that song myself.
That's why I...
The song that seems to resound from the sky!
But I guess being an omiso, I'll just remain an omiso no matter where I go, right?
Kanata.
We can't rely on the church for everything, right
The Takemikazuchi is a relic from a previous era,
and inside it sleep many different things.
Different things?
Yeah. You can ask Noel about the details later.
All right, this is it.
Here it goes!
This is...
This song!
This is probably the complete version of the song.
Many instruments, all coming together in harmony, becoming a single piece of music.
It's the same with a tank crew.
Commander, gunner, driver and communications...
Everyone's efforts come together to mobilize one tank.
No one is useless.
And every sound is important.
Don't look at me like that.
I was just repeating...
...the words of the person I admire and respect the most.
To borrow her words... Kanata,
why do you think sempai or superior officers exist?
So that their juniors are able to bother them.
It doesn't matter if you can't do it now.
Just remember the frustration and helplessness you felt,
and how happy you were to be protected.
And someday, when you're in a position to protect someone,
this will help.
So, just cause as much trouble as you like.
I did the same.
Naturally, if you blunder, you'll be scolded and even punished.
But...
When it gets too frustrating, say it!
Even when you're suffering.
All right?
Understood!
From now on, I'll be sure to cause you lots and lots of trouble!
W-Well...
Then, just go easy on me, all right?
Aw, jeez... I should've just stayed behind.
Kanata actually had Rio-sempai nurse her.
What? It wasn't that big of a deal,
and it was merely due to fatigue.
She'll be fine if she sleeps.
Takemikazuchi's lights were on.
Ah, sorry.
I used it for a while.
Was there a problem?
You listened to that song, didn't you?
Yeah.
Didn't you say you never wanted to hear it again though?
I just had a change of heart.
And?
It's a secret.
Next time:
Rainy Season Sky, Quartz Rainbow.