Entou Jyuu.
With this sword pair, the collection of the 12 Perfected Deviant Blades is now complete.
Thank you for your hard work, Strategian Togame.
Emonzaemon!!
Regrettable.
But I must do my duty.
Why?
Why?!
Did I not already say?
That woman is the daughter of the leader of the last rebellion, Hida Takahito...
Princess Yousha...
Princess... Yousha?
The fact that the Princess and the Strategian's battle had to end this way is entirely your fault, Kyotouryuu.
meguriatta ga un no tsuki
巡り逢ったが運の尽き
Our encounter becomes thy fortune's end
Mazui
presents
Katana-
gatari
harari koboreochiru
ハラリ 零れ落ちる
Though words doth joined
kotoba tsuranetatote
言葉 連ねたとて
From my lips run over
dare mo watashi ni aru makoto fure mo dekin jaro
誰もわたしに在る真 触れも出来んじゃろ
Can yet any convey the truth I hold?
sakura mau ga gotoku
サクラ 舞うが如く
As cherry blossoms doth dance
konjou to wa osaraba
今生とはおさらば
To this life I bid farewell
saredo oya ni moratta
されど親に貰った
Indeed this body, parent-hatched,
kono mi ga kawaii
この身が可愛い
I cherish duly
inochi yori omoi
命より重い
But graver than life,
bebe matoi warau
ベベ纏い微笑う
Here, smile-clad
kizu wa taenu kenka joutou
傷は絶えぬ喧嘩上等
Put forth battle, such my scars not fade
kakugoshiiya
覚悟しいや
Ready I stand
nuite wa modosu katana to saya tachikiru ha shura
抜いては戻す 刀と鞘 断ち斬るは修羅
To draw is to return, the sword and sheath, to cut what is the battle
sono sakeme ni ochita yume no fu wa muzan zo
その裂け目に堕ちた夢の腑は無惨ぞ
The heart of the dream abyss-fallen lies bestial
ai mamiete tagiraseru chi wo wakeaeru nara
相まみえて滾らせる血を分け合えるなら
If we share such seething blood as we face,
itoshii sonata todome wo
愛し其方 止めを
Then, my love,
sashitekunnamashi
刺してくんなまし
Deliver the finishing blow
hana no sakari ga oshii kae
花の盛りが惜しいかえ
Dost thou lament the flowers' bloom?
Entou
Jyuu
Gun,
the Flame
What do you think history is?
You naturally have the history that you know
Your own history
Your
own
history
For example...
Let’s say that history is nothing but words
There is no way to determine
if those words are the truth
Not a dark History, rather a false history
That history will also end with this chapter
Bind it, open it
Then close it
Togame! Togame!!
Togame!
Togame!!
Now that it's come to this, I have no more reason to fight you.
That's why I showed some pity.
I avoided hitting her vitals.
She will die soon, but she's still alive for now.
You have a chance to speak with her one last time.
And hear her, Strategian Togame—
No, Princess Yousha's final words.
What will she say as she dies?
Togame!
Togame!!
I can hear you...
Togame!
I feel like my insides have been churned up...
I get it now.
So that's Entou Jyuu...
I understand how it works now.
Who cares about what his sword does?!
Shichika...
I'm sorry...
I'm supposed to be your sword, but I let you get hurt...
Be quiet for a bit...
I'm thinking up a counter-strategy right now.
Well, it could be a scheme, depending on how it goes...
This is pretty rough, though...
Nothing comes to mind...
Togame!!
We lost.
Well, even though I'm going to die, you'll still be alive,
so it's not all bad.
What are you talking about?
You can't die!
I'll take you to a doctor!
It's pointless.
I've already tried to think of some way out, but this is kind of hopeless.
Shichika...
Yes?
When I die, could you make sure the whole country picks up "Cheerio" as a shout of encouragement in my place?
Don't say that like you're giving up!
It seems this is it for me...
That's why, Shichika...
"Cheerio" is my last wish...
How can I spread the wrong meaning to "Cheerio" to the whole country by myself?!
You can do it...
After all, you're the sword I chose.
I can't!
Without you I can't do anything!
Don't say that...
In this past year, I've taught you all I could.
You don't need to rely on my schemes anymore.
Stay with me!!
There are still things you need to do!
Things I need to do?
I walked this path alone for twenty years,
but in this single year with you, you've taught me...
How a person should live...
I haven't done anything to make you change your view of life that much!
You have.
You've taught me so much...
The things I've realize because of you...
the things I've come to understand because of you...
the things I've discovered because of you...
There are so many I've lost count.
I had fun because of you.
I was happy because of you.
I laughed, I smiled, I played because of you...
It was almost like I was a different person...
Because of you, I...
I believed that even I could change.
Togame...
But, in the end, I...
...couldn't change.
This is a fitting way for me to die.
The way someone like me should die.
I was never qualified to hold you.
No one else could possibly hold me!
Didn't you say I was your trusted partner?!
After we finished, weren't we going to keep traveling together and make a map of the country?!
You have me with you, and I have you, right?!
Are you saying that was all a lie?!
It was all a lie.
When the sword collection journey finished, I was going to kill you.
Just like everyone before you.
No way...
Everything was just a tool for my schemes.
Even my own heart...
It's just a pawn on the board.
Heart
Feelings
Emotions
They’re
nothing but tools I can use.
That's the kind of person I am.
I can only live by calculation.
The part of me that trusted you was just another pawn to me.
Kyotouryuu took my father's head in front of my own eyes...
How could I possibly forgive that?
Even so...
Even so, I thought I could forgive you for that.
But even that feeling was just a pawn, too.
Even the thought that you might not just be another pawn, was itself another pawn on my board...
Then... what are feelings to you?!
The emotions that I gained in this last year...
What are they?!
What is this that you taught me, that I feel in my heart?!
A pawn.
Joy, anger, sorrow, fun...
They were all pawns to me.
Insignificant objects that I need not control.
But why did you have to tell all those lies?!
I'd have killed myself for you if you just said the word!
Even if the words were lies,
the feelings weren't.
I simply thought it best to say that at the moment.
Though I know it makes no difference.
But in the end, you're the one who got hurt the most!
I know.
If that weren't the case, I wouldn't scheme.
Then what was the point to your life?
You had the right to be happy!
And yet you kept hurting yourself and hurting yourself and hurting yourself,
and here in the end, you're lying in the middle of the road, dying...
What the hell were you doing?!
Are you stupid?!
You're totally right...
But...
Right now...
I'm very happy.
Even dying in the middle of a road, I'm happy.
Because this way, I don't have to kill you...
Togame...
Finally...
Now I can finally lay down all my burdens.
Couldn't you have done that without dying?!
Did you have to keep going, until it came down to this?!
It wasn't your fault.
Togame...
7th generation head of Kyotouryuu,
Yasuri Shichika.
This is my final order.
Forget all about me and everything that's happened with me, and live on as you wish.
The contract I made with you ends with my death.
You can stop falling for me now.
Like hell!
I loved being with you!
I...
I really loved you!
Shichika...
What am I supposed to do now?
I can't do anything without you!
You really are cute.
Hey, Shichika...
I'm selfish and egocentric...
I'm an idiot who could only think of revenge,
with my stupidity cured only by death.
A terrible woman who treated you as nothing but a tool,
whose only fate is death.
Even so...
Would you mind...
...if I fell for you?
Well met.
Owari Castle
Raise your head.
It is my deepest honor.
I am the eighth Shogun of the Owari Shogunate, Yanari Masatsuna.
At last, an audience.
That woman also had such a wish.
I win.
Let me hear what you have to say then.
First, your Lordship...
I believe I asked for a private audience?
Worry not, they have worked under the Shogun for generations.
Their loyalty to me is absolute.
They would never betray me.
You could say they are part of my own body.
Is that so...
Part of his own body?
Quite a statement to just throw out like that.
It would seem that the eighth generation successor by inheritance is of this low caliber.
You are the swordsmith's—Shikizaki Kiki's descendant, correct?
Yes.
Do you have evidence?
It is foolish to rely on simply on physical evidence when making a decision.
Quite right.
Speak, then.
Yes.
To begin with, the man named Shikizaki Kiki was not a swordsmith.
I won't say they had a good lineage, but he was of a family of soothsayers with a history of several thousand years.
His objective was the falsification of history.
Falsifying history?
It was for that purpose that the Perfected Deviant Blades were forged.
I don't understand.
Why would he wish to do something like alter history?
That is indeed an important point.
Well, at heart, he did it for the sake of Japan.
Has your Lordship ever turned your attention to other countries?
About a hundred years from now,
this country will suffer an attack from foreign nations, and then perish.
Perish??
This was predicted by the founder of the family several thousand years ago.
Princess.
Silence.
You're late, idiot.
What is it?
An invader entered this castle just moments ago.
And why are you telling me this?
I'm in the middle of a very important conversation.
It would appear that the intruder is none other than that man.
I see.
I wonder if this is also as Shikizaki Kiki planned?
That man, huh...
Hey, you... what are you saying?
Such a worthless intruder is of no importance.
No, your Lordship...
This is the end for us both.
Togame...
It doesn't look like I can follow your order.
Why can't they stop him?!
He is but a sole intruder!
Do not underestimate him.
After all, he is the warrior who assembled eleven of the swords.
Wh-What?!
He is the 7th generation head of Kyotouryuu, Yasuri Shichika.
Kyotouryuu...
I see!
The swordsman who uses no sword I read about in the report!
But there are over a thousand soldiers in Owari Castle!
Unfortunately, no number of soldiers will be able to stop him.
You talk too much, Emonzaemon.
But he is right.
Why?
Why is Kyotouryuu attacking my castle?
Is he not your subordinate?
The only one I call my subordinate is Souda Emonzaemon here.
In fact, Yasuri Shichika is under direct control of the strategian.
Then summon the strategian here at once!
Have her command Kyotouryuu to stop!
Unfortunately, she died while collecting the swords.
Oh, did I not mention that?
Well, it would appear that her servant has gone berserk upon losing his master.
But your Lordship, this may be both a blessing and a curse at the same time.
H-How?
He is a part of Shikizaki Kiki's plan, the final piece necessary to ensure the success of our goal.
In other words, the Completed Deviant Blade—
Completed?
It would seem that Shikizaki Kiki's plan included this.
Please look on this as the ceremony that heralds a thousand years of prosperity for the Yanari Shogunate.
So you're saying that we just need stop Kyotouryuu's killing spree?
I don't get your reasoning, though...
Indeed.
There is a bit of a tedious process that we must follow though.
I see.
I do not like them, but they will be used here, like this.
Using the eleven whom your Lordship calls part of your own body,
along with my trusted Souda Emonzaemon, making twelve.
Let us go put the finishing touches on this history.
Kyotouryuu...
I'd like to welcome you at this point...
…but I am at a loss for words.
To think you'd endanger that life which I went out of my way to spare...
Emonzaemon?
Aioi Ninpou: Ventriloquism.
Well, that's not really important.
Kyotouryuu.
I have ordered the soldiers' retreat.
There is no more need for pointless fights.
Nor is there any need for you to run around wildly.
Head straight for the castle keep.
The Princess and I await you there.
Waiting for me?
You've come to avenge the strategian, correct?
I believe that you will be able to break through.
You're wrong.
I didn't come here to avenge Togame.
I came here to die.
What a hassle.
7th generation head of Kyotouryuu, Yasuri Shichika.
We are the eleven retainers to the Yanari Shogunate!
We shall be your opponents!
I am one of the eleven retainers to the Yanari Shogunate, Hannyamaru!
Hannyamaru
Zettou Kanna
I know, Kyotouryuu.
You are unable to bend or break this sword!
Your luck ran out when I became your first opponent.
Houfuku Zettou!
I don't have to hold back anymore.
Zettou Kanna
Broken
First sword.
Oniyadori Furachi
Zantou Namakura
Oh yeah, I never did see through his strike.
And you will never see anything again!
This Kyotouryuu move has no name.
It's that simple of a move.
In other words, that's just how mediocre your attack is.
Zantou
Namakura
Broken
Second sword.
I didn't just learn Sentou Meguri—I have mastered it.
Tomoe
Akatsuki
Sentou
Tsurugi
So what?
I hesitated against Meisai because I couldn't come to terms with her personality.
Sentou
Tsurugi
Broken
Third sword.
Fugi Matsuaki
Hakutou Hari
After killing the man who killed Sabi, I will for the first time surpass him.
Hakutou Kaigan!
If you don't swing in a perfect arc, that sword is so frail it shatters.
All I have to do is shift a little, and I can stop your attack.
When I fought Sabi, I wasn't allowed to break the sword, so my options were limited.
Hakutou Hari
Broken
Fourth sword.
Iga Kairo
Zokutou Yoroi
I won't be careless even with this armor's perfect defense!
I'll run you through before capturing you!
Yoroi transfers any outside shock away from the user by being in contact with the ground.
If I hit you midair where you aren't touching the ground or walls, the shock can't go anywhere.
Zokutou Yoroi   Broken
Fifth sword.
I am of the lineage of the Maniwa Corps.
Maniwa Boufura
Soutou Kanazuchi
Soutou Noinu!
You're using ninpou to negate its weight,
but if you take that away, what's the point to this sword?
Crap—
There really wasn't a weaker Maniwa than you.
Soutou
Kanazuchi
Broken
Sixth sword.
When a warrior with such perfect health as I use it, Akutou Bita becomes something else entirely.
I am a truly immortal warrior.
Uron
Akutou
Bita
Just because you don't die if I kill you,
it doesn't mean you can't die if I keep killing you.
From Red Poppy to Daphne, a mixed-connection fist strike.
You've died 272 times.
Akutou
Bita
Broken
Seventh sword.
Haiga Ou
Bitou
Kanzashi
Doll Fatality: Zephyr Swordstorm!
Shichika Hachiretsu: Revamp
Shichika Hachiretsu
Revamp
It was two against one...
I thought you had trouble fighting against Biyorigou alone...
You were in the way, so Biyorigou couldn't show its full strength.
Bitou
Kanzashi
Broken
Eighth sword.
I cannot imagine there is any meaning to a fight like this.
Sumigaoka Kokubo
Outou Nokogiri
Outo Rakudou, I believe it's called?
The instant I took up this sword, I felt a cruel calmness.
To the point where I thought I could just let you go, as the most honorable of the Owari.
What say you?
I see.
Then I shall grant you death in one blow.
Your words are nothing but talk. They don't move me at all.
Outou
Nokogiri
Broken
Ninth sword.
This thing is kind of useless...
Saraba Kousha
Seitou Hakari
Try throwing it at me?
It doesn't look like there's any other way, so I suppose I'll do that.
Seitou
Hakari
Broken
Tenth sword.
Rogiri Bangai
Dokutou Mekki
Rogiri, Rogiri!
Shikizaki, Shikizaki, Shikizaki, Shikizaki!!
I will free you now.
Dokutou
Mekki
Broken
Eleventh sword.
This is seriously a hassle.
That was fast, Shichika-kun.
Souda Emonzaemon   Entou Jyuu
I suppose this is the true strength of Kyotouryuu, now that you're allowed to destroy the swords.
Didn't you say you'd be waiting in the castle keep?
I deny that.
You might die here, after all.
I thought I'd take a look at your face one more time.
Incidentally, I hated that strategian, but I hold no animosity towards you.
Well, if you do manage to defeat Emonzaemon, come up these stairs.
If you make it that far,
I'll let you kill me.
Hey, Princess... I'm—
Emonzaemon!
This is an order.
Kill him.
As you wish.
But if I kill Kyotouryuu, Shikizaki Kiki's plan will never come to fruition.
That's true...
However, you may not have realized it yet,
but I'm a very denying kind of person.
I want to see Shikizaki Kiki's plans destroyed just as much as I want to see them completed.
I trust that you'll show me one way or the other!
Unpleasant.
I didn't think I'd be facing you like this.
What do you mean?
I mean, manipulated like a puppet in someone's palm.
I wish to fight only for the Princess' sake.
The thought of fighting for the sake of Shikizaki Kiki is extremely unpleasant.
Like I said, you're wrong.
Maybe in the end, it really is pointless to fight for someone.
For both humans and swords.
I came to believe that after Togame died.
At the start, I obeyed Togame without any resolution at all,
and after a while I obeyed her for her sake after finding resolve.
What do you fight for?
If you have to think about it, then you shouldn't be fighting in the first place.
After all, in the end, Togame was only thinking about herself.
She kept telling me to live how I liked until her last breath.
She really was selfish.
I wonder what you call people like her...
But I can't help it.
I fell in love with Togame because of that.
I am the 7th generation head of Kyotouryuu,
Yasuri Shichika.
Let the match...
Begin!
I loved that part of her!
That's why I think now that I was only fighting for myself.
Then what are you invading this castle for?
To die.
Togame told me to live,
but I don't have any duty to obey that order anymore.
I don't think anyone but you can kill me.
You, the one who killed Togame...
Unhumorous.
If this really is part of Shikizaki Kiki's plan, then it really is comical.
Do you think that your movements make you harder to hit?
If you have come here to die then it is unavoidable.
Die, with your regrets!
What will you say as you die?
I-Impossible...
How did you dodge so many bullets?
I didn't dodge them.
I resolved to take them from the start.
Kyotouryuu...
Togame gave me an order—
protect myself.
But I no longer have a duty to obey that order.
Are you trying to die?
I already said so.
He's allowed to break the swords...
And...
he's allowed to hurt himself...
This is Yasuri Shichika's true power.
Shinobazuhou Ikasazukorosazu...
No,
Danzai Entou!
Kyoutouryuu Ultimate Move!
Shichika Hachiretsu!
Kai!
Completed Deviant Blade
Kyotou Yasuri
Entou
Jyuu
Broken
P...rincess...
What on earth is happening down there?
Everything is going favorably.
It won't be long before our wish will be granted.
I-I see...
That's good then...
So the Yanari Shogunate will be granted a thousand years of prosperity now, right?
Yes.
Emonzaemon's dying words.
Steel your heart and listen.
I'm listening. What were they?
"Princess, please forgive me for dying for your sake."
An annoying man right to the end.
Was he trying to impress me with a line like that?
Well, whatever.
How about we finish this then?
Shichika-kun, as promised, you may kill me.
W-Wait!
What are you saying?!
Someone... Someone help!
Unfortunately, I don't think I can take on more than one more person.
P-Princess Hitei!
What are you doing? Save me!
Now now, don't be silly.
I don't have the slightest bit of combat ability.
And if you don't die, this won't end.
Wh-What did you say?!
All that about the Yanari Shogunate lasting a thousand years was a lie.
It was just a means to speak with you.
Why, you...
After all, the collapse of the Owari Shogunate was Shikizaki Kiki's objective.
Well, it was originally supposed to be a different Shogunate and Shogun's household,
but after preventing them from coming to power,
your family took over the country in a similar manner and built up peace across the country.
Perhaps it was history self-correcting itself?
Wh-What are you talking about?
It was a future which could have been.
Well, not future, but the original.
So that's what should have been?
My wish was to kill you.
And now...
that will finally be fulfilled.
Togame wasted her whole life because of you.
Well, I suppose you could say she reaped what she sowed.
Killing you at this point wouldn't do anything to lift any burden off her.
Nor would I feel any better by doing it.
Then...
But...
I have to make an example of you.
Hey, Princess.
Togame told me to thank you if I managed to run into you.
Oh?
I don't recall doing anything she'd thank me for though.
Can I ask one thing?
Ask away.
Deep down, you liked Togame, didn't you?
That unpleasant woman?
I didn't... dislike her.
I see.
W-Wait!
Calm down!
Listen to me!
Spare me!
Please spare me!
Oh, I know!
I'll give you the country!
Don't you want power over the country?
Like I'd give a damn about that!
Cheerio!!
nozomi wa yami no naka
望みは闇の中
My dreams, buried in the dark
umete nao omoidasu yo
埋めてなお思い出すよ
Suddenly, they come to mind
kimi ga watashi ga tooi hi ni
君が私が遠い日に
You and I, when was it?
deatta natsukashisa
出会った懐かしさ
We met, far ago and long away
tabiji wa me no mae no
旅路は目の前の
We travelled the road before us,
owari naki yume wo
終わり無き夢を
Chasing an unending dream,
oikakete mata hitotsu
追いかけてまた一つ
Reaching in the end
wakare wo te ni shite
別れを手にして
Another time to part
adokenai kotoba
あどけない言葉
Innocent words,
kaze ni toketeita
風に溶けていた
Fading in the wind
mata suu ni nabirete wo
また直ぐに旅に出よう
Let us set upon the road again
tsugi wa doko darou?
次はどこだろう？
Where shall it take us next?
Japan really is big.
Ah, there you are!
Found you, Shichika-kun!
I don't remember asking you to follow me.
I'm not such a heartless person as to make you ask me to come along.
But I do remember asking you not to follow me.
Perhaps unfortunately, or perhaps fortunately,
history was not falsified in the end.
The son of one of Masatsuna's direct descendants simply succeeded the seat of the ninth shogun.
Shikizaki Kiki's descendant's attempts for a revolution in history,
attempts to reform the world in history,
and attempts to destroy history.
In one word, they ended in failure.
Shikizaki Kiki lost in the end...
Everything started going off plan starting with Kyuu Shogun...
And then Hida Takahito...
And then his daughter...
It all ended with Princess Yousha.
If you ask me, all that stuff about altering history is like some fantasy tale.
If it it's like you say, and another country will sail here to destroy Japan,
we can just leave it to the warriors of that time to fight back.
Well, the falsification failed, but maybe it can still be altered a bit.
I'm sure Japan in a hundred years won't let itself be ruined like that so easily.
Let’s hope they've got some guts.
What are you going to do now, Shichika-kun?
I've seen most of Noto, so I think I'll move onto Kaga.
Kaga's apparently a pretty rich area.
Shouldn't we replenish our war funds before heading there?
I'll leave that stuff to you.
I don't know why you're following me, but be useful at least.
You're so harsh.
A lot like a certain someone.
In return, if any bandits attack, I'll take care of them.
Oh?
I'll leave that to you then.
Yeah.
However, by that point you might be torn into pieces.
Why?!
After that, there was no more news of Yasuri Shichika.
He may have died by the roadside in the middle of his journey,
or he may have completed the map of Japan, then sailed to a foreign country and continued his journey.
But even after everything was over,
after the historical plan connecting man and swords failed,
be it for a long or a short period, he certainly lived.
That was something surely everyone wanted.
The ones who failed at revenge...
The ones who failed at their goals...
The one's who fell before achieving their aspirations...
The ones who didn't succeed...
The ones who lost...
The ones who stumbled...
The ones who rotted...
The ones who fought with all their might, sacrificed everything,
just to have their work be for naught, yielding fruitless results,
who died unfairly, or perhaps illogically, tragically, without face, full of regrets...
The story which offers a happy future for them, filled with hopes and dreams...
"Katanagatari"
...quietly lowers its curtains here.