Ushio...
Ushio.
Shinpei!
Why're ya here? Did ya come back?
I-I should be asking that question.
Huh?
This necklace is the only one of its kind in the world, and it's wearing it!
Ushio died!
W-We just had a funeral two days ago.
Died?
Yer not her.
You can't be Ushio!
Huh? What're ya saying?
I'm alive!
See? I'm right here!
What's it talking about?
This is a shadow.
No doubt about it!
D-Don't ya remember what happened?
Huh?
Wait.
I...
Why am I here?
What?
That's odd.
You don't have any memory of why ya got here?
I can't breathe.
All I remember is that I couldn't breathe.
I was in the water, and everything got dark.
Oh, come on! No way!
Oh man, I really died, huh?
Then what am I?
A-Am I a ghost?
But my feet are touching the ground.
Does it really believe that it's Ushio?
What's happening?
I remember one thing.
In the end, I wished I could see ya one last time.
I wanted to see ya.
Maybe that's why I'm here.
I'm glad.
Her voice.
Her gestures.
Stop it.
What is this?
It feels like Ushio really came back!
Hey, Shinpei.
I wanted to tell ya something if I saw ya again.
I like you.
Huh?
I'm...
in love with you!
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Jamais Vu
Huh?
Wh-What did it just say?
L-Love?
In what way?
Wh-What're you saying?
Did dying make ya lose yer marbles?
Maybe.
My head feels so cloudy.
D-Don't be fooled.
Take a bird's-eye view of things!
Two days ago, Ushio was put in a coffin and cremated.
She's gone from this world.
It's just acting like Ushio.
What does it want?
Why'd ya come here?
I wish I knew.
Aren'tcha supposed to go see God when ya die?
Why're ya here?
What do you guys want?
What... do I want?
Shinpei, those fireworks...
Is today the 24th?
Oh, uh... yeah.
No way!
W-We gotta hurry!
There was something I wanted to do!
I wanna go to the festival with ya!
H-Hey!
Shinpei! Hurry it up!
It doesn't realize that it's a shadow.
Does it really think that it's Ushio?
Shinpei, I wanna do this!
Why's she still wearing her swimsuit?!
I-Idiot! Ya totally stand out!
Dang, that smells good!
I wanna eat octopus dumplings!
There ain't time for that!
What if someone recognizes you?
How would I explain this?!
Come on over!
Our octopus is cheap and huge!
It's really good!
Hey, try some!
Hey, Shinpei.
Why do we gotta hide?
I'm starving.
Ain't Mio and everyone else here?
I wanna see 'em.
You can't! Absolutely not!
Think about this situation for a second.
Listen, yer dead!
Yer funeral was two days ago!
But...
No buts!
Yer a shadow.
A ghost, uh, whatever. Don't matter.
Everyone can see ya!
What the hell are ya?
Ya don't want me to see everyone?
Of course not!
J-Just hide here until the festival is over.
Shinpei, ya dummy!
That's a whole buncha nonsense! Stop it or else!
Or else? Bit late for that.
It's just like Ushio herself.
I had a conversation with Ushio's shadow.
How it's been two years since I left, and about our childhood.
It had all of Ushio's memories.
Do ya know my favorite author?
Nagumo Ryuunosuke, right?
We went to the mainland once to see a movie based on one of his books.
It was strange.
It knew nothing about shadows.
It didn't remember how she died, either.
Ain't ya worried about Shiori?
Huh? What about Shiori?
To me, it didn't look like she was acting.
Nothing. Never mind.
A call?
Yeah.
Kofune Mio
It's Mio.
Gimme.
Hey! Stop!
Hello? Mio?
Well?
Sis...
Hi, it's me!
M-Mio?
It's just me, yes.
I thought I heard Sis.
Of course not! A-Are ya okay?
R-Right.
Sorry. It must be me.
Where are ya at?
The fireworks are over.
We're by the shrine.
The send-off is starting.
I'm close by.
Yeah.
Got it.
I'll run over.
What'd she say?
You just stay here!
H-Hey!
I-I'll come get ya later.
Ya might not realize it, but something crazy's going on!
Hmph!
Yer the one who told me to take care of Mio.
Regret's the last thing I need.
The heck's he saying?
I never said that.
He's finally here.
Shin!
Ya took forever. I was getting worried.
Mountain.
Sorry, I had a bit of stomachache.
M-Mesopotamian civilization.
Told ya he was just pooping.
What's with the smirk?
On Hitogashima, it's said that gods live in things that come from the sea.
This belief is deeply rooted in this land.
That is the legend of Hiruko-no-Mikoto.
People call it Hiruko for short, the god of fishing.
Driftwood is collected from the beach and burned in the send-off ceremony to send the gods back.
It's quite a crowd.
Around 1,000 people are here.
It's been so long since we went to the send-off together.
Yeah.
Ushio's watching too!
What?!
In Heaven.
Oh, ya mean like that.
Right.
I wonder if it was okay to come
to the festival when Sis just died.
I really wish she was here.
Right.
Hey, Sou.
Ya wanted to talk?
My brother wants to tell Mio how he feels today.
Huh?
I-Is he serious?
I love my brother, but he can be illogical.
However, the illogical sometimes happens.
Yes.
But he has no chance.
Huh? Why not?
Because Mio already has someone else she likes.
Really?
Who?
It wouldn't be right for me to say.
Shinpei!
You too, Tokiko!
I want ya to hear this!
There's something I gotta tell ya, Mio.
I just have to.
Not probably ain't the right time to say it,
but I want ya to know!
I'm in love with you!
P-Please allow me the honor of protecting you!
Whoa, he said it.
He said it.
Sou! Wait!
What're ya saying?
E-Everyone is listening.
Why do ya like me?
I'm flattered, of course,
but I can't say yes.
I just want us to be good friends.
I totally saw that coming.
I got here just in time for the show!
Huh?!
Hey, Sou.
No biggie!
Huh?!
Didn't I tell her to stay there?!
That idiot!
Summer Time Rendering
Th-That pretty hair...
That voice.
Ushio?
What?
What... Huh? Th-That's...
I-I-I'm not Ushio!
"I am the soldier of love, Cure..."
Hey.
Shinpei, they instantly knew it was me.
Idiot! Do ya even call that a disguise?
Sh-Shinpei.
D-Don't tell me...
Sorry.
I just wanted to see y'all.
Did Tokiko help ya get dressed up?
Mio,
ya look great in that yukata!
No.
Mio?
What're ya doing, Shin?!
Get away from that thing!
That ain't Sis!
Huh?
It's a monster!
Mio.
I won't let her go.
Th-That hurts.
Shinpei?
Wait, Mio.
Shinpei!
Explain yerself!
What's yer issue?
Ya can't switch with someone who's dead and turned to ash.
Ya never really wanted to switch places, did ya?
Why won't ya obey?
Don't tell me ya can't hear.
Who... are you?!
Guys, run!
Too late.
Th-This guy...
That ain't Shin!
It's time.
About ten minutes ago
Mio, sorry I suddenly left you.
I really shouldn't be making you worry like this.
I need to apologize later.
Shin.
I wanted to ask ya something.
Got a minute?
What?
I-I didn't even see it move.
And no human can be this strong!
I heard ya got me on video.
How's that possible?
Unless ya knew I was coming.
How'd ya know?
It knows.
Th-This can't be real...
This is crazy.
Did it do all of this?
How many people did it kill?
Who told ya?
The traitor?
Traitor?
I can't ignore that.
It'll be a shame if it messes up our plan.
Find out.
How much does he know?
It cuts off. It repeats.
Something's odd about my memory.
How many times have ya been killed?
This thing...
I-It's my shadow!
It copied me then.
It must have my memory up until that point.
Oh no! If its memory gets updated, it'll find out!
It'll know we're investigating shadows and about Mesopotamian civilization.
No, not that!
Ushio...
Why do they come out like this?
I thought crowds would be safe.
Think!
It's over. It's totally over!
Damn it! Focus on the right thing!
Done?
Hold on.
We don't need him anymore.
Run.
No.
Run or be killed!
No!
Everyone will be killed!
I told ya to hold on.
Don't kill him, Mio.
Why not, Shin?
Take a bird's-eye view of the situation and think.
Remember what Mother told us?
Even if he dies, he can just come back.
A loop?
Are yer memories accurate?
This ain't a video game.
He's not in control of it himself.
But it all makes sense if he's in a loop.
We need to take a bird's-eye view and look at third-dimension issues from the fourth dimension.
He probably can't do that now,
but he might learn how to in the future.
You read too many weird books.
If he goes back to the 22nd with what he knows,
he'll eventually get in our way,
so don't kill him until everything's done.
I'll go up.
Give me his phone.
It's in his left back pocket.
Send people down to get Ushio.
She's in the storage area by the tent.
Fine.
Go.
Ya know who's strict on time.
Right.
Dammit... W-Wait...
Yer so pathetic.
As it turns out, ya can't protect anyone.
Wait.
Stop!
Don't put even a finger on Mio!
Cut it out, Shin.
Yer trying way too hard to be cool.
But it's too late.
In no time, Mother will wake up.
C'mon, stay still.
Yer being stubborn, Shin.
Mio!
Guess I'll break this too.
Narezushi isn't too common here on Hitogashima.
I haven't tried it yet.
Have you?
Huh?
This woman...
I saw her on the ferry!
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Maelstrom