Am I the one who is at fault?
A servant like me,
making my dreams come true...
Nishiyama, you totally isn't cut out
for cute clothes like that, right?!
Welcome!
Thank you very much!
Teru-chan!
Let's play!
Teru-chan! Let's play!
Teru-chan! Let's pla—
Ring the doorbell!
Let's play.
We can play cards.
You came to here in this
sweltering heat just to play cards?
Yeah, we'll draw for the old maid.
You came just to play Old Maid?!
Geez...
Why don't we go somewhere cooler?
Your Birthmarks Have Faded
Shaved Ice
Oh, it's so cool.
I'm alive again.
Oh yeah, did you do
the summer homework yet?
Yeah, most of it.
You haven't started, have you?
Nope.
Let me see yours once you're done.
No.
Do it yourself.
Tch.
How about you, Youko-sama?
Youko-sama?
Is she sleeping?
A-Are you okay?
How rude, who did it?!
It hurt!
O-Oh...
My, how silly of me.
You said that pretty loudly, sleepyhead.
Although you were kind
enough to invite me out...
It is so nice and cool here,
I could not help myself.
Youko-sama, are you tired?
Oh, well, I have been working a lot recently...
Sonobe-san's shop?
The maid's castle.
Oh, I remember you saying that you would
take on more hours during summer break.
The store happens to be closed today.
Don't overwork yourself.
Do you feel okay?
Yes, I feel fine.
Ah! It's swelling up!
A rich girl shouldn't have a lump!
I see.
So that's how it happened yesterday.
However, I hesitate to have you
work in the front like that.
It was an accident, though.
And it happened because she's overworked.
Y-Y-Y-Y-Youko-sama is hurt?
And on her forehead?
On her head?
What if something happens?!
Or if she gets a scar?!
How terrible!
You should get it checked
by a doctor right now!
You should see a doctor.
That's wonderful advice, Futaba.
I knew it was too early for
Youko-sama to start working!
Too soft.
Mitsugu, you have always coddled Youko-sama.
You're the one to blame!
Youko-sama, although you're
a part-timer, this is still work.
I cannot coddle you.
I-I know!
So, please go rest in the back room.
Huh?
Taking care of yourself is also part of working.
Sonobe...
Am I the one who is at fault?
A servant like me, making my dreams
come true by opening this store.
Then, it comes to this,
all because I hired you?
I'm sorry.
It's because I'm such a capable manager.
Is your head okay?
Hey— Yamaji?!
Anyway, she said you need to rest, so go rest!
Miss Sonobe, will the shop be all right?
Sonobe-san?!
What should I do?
How will I get through today?
It sounds like it won't be all right at all!
Oh, that's perfect.
Hayama-chan, why don't you
work in Youko-sama's place?
What, me?!
Come on, you weren't doing anything yesterday.
You're the one who wasn't doing anything,
coming over just to play cards.
Thank you, both of you!
Let's get a move on it,
now that it's settled.
Wh—
Ah!
H-Hey!
Why do I have to wear this?
I have an extra outfit.
That's not what I'm asking!
Why aren't I wearing what Youko-sama wears?!
It looks good on you.
Do you understand Japanese?!
Ah, Futaba-san, have you finished changing, too?
Oh, yes.
We have Futaba.
We'll get to see her wear these weird clothes—
I'm changed!
Why?!
Futaba-san wouldn't fit in my clothes, so...
Why not?
Oh, er, I'm not saying that Futaba-san has
a dynamite figure, but I'm just quite small.
Should that make me feel better?
Ah, you see, I haven't grown since my teens.
More specifically, since junior high.
You're not helping by saying this,
and it's not that specific, either!
Maybe she's saying that you won't
grow anymore either, Hayama-chan.
Let's stop talking about our sizes!
Welcome!
Oh, the usual girl isn't here today.
Yup!
We're here temporarily.
This place always has young girls.
What a fun atmosphere.
Thank you very much.
What do you recommend?
Let's see.
They're all delicious.
But this roll cake is simple and light,
because it's made of fluffy sponge cake
and buttercream that melts in your mouth,
and it goes surprisingly well with Japanese tea.
This moist gateau chocolat has a refined
sweetness that pairs perfectly with coffee.
Gateau Chocolat
The chocolate is rich and dark.
Strawberry
Mousse Cake
The mousse in this cake brings out
the tangy sweetness of strawberry
and interweaves it with fresh cream
for a superb harmony you can't resist!
They all seem delicious.
I'll take all three.
Thank you very much!
Sh-She's good.
They're probably just her own impressions.
So, how about you?
Uh...
It's not like I want to compete, but I
don't want her thinking I can't do my job.
Welco—
Welcome!
What kind of cake are you looking for?
Wow!
You're really dressed as a maid!
Teru-chan, you're so cute!
Oh, you're here, Hayama-chan's onee-chan!
And you look so cool!
Wh-Why are you here?
I told her.
Do your best, Teru-chan!
Here, candy to keep you going!
Oh, is that candy?
Thank you for visiting.
I expected no less from a professional baker.
Or maybe it's a youkai's intuition?
Oh, hey.
I want to help, too.
I want to make cakes
and sweets with Teru-chan.
That's, well...
This is our new gelee.
Full of fruits and containing collagen
and vitamin C, it's great for your skin.
I don't know what to call it yet.
Can you think of a good name for it?
Sonobe-san...
She really can't let big sis make sweets.
I know!
"Derived from Pigs."
Derived from Pigs
Derived from Pigs?!
Big Sis!
You mean, "Derived from Pig Skin"?
Oh, collagen is derived from pig skin, huh.
But "Derived from Pig Skin" is so hard to say.
On second thought, I'll think of a name myself.
Onee-chan!
Where are you, Onee-chan?
I-Is it true that you're working part time?!
Oh my, if it isn't Takezono's—
Oh! I know you.
Young Takezono-sama, I'm the
Nishikawa Family's former maid.
Will you please keep it down?
Youko-sama won't be able to rest properly.
Hi, little boy.
Did you come to see Youko-chan?
Huh? Yes.
I wanted to make sure she was okay and stuff...
You're very kind, Young Takezono-sama.
How adorable.
Your bottom is cute, too.
Your birthmarks have
faded already, haven't they.
Wh-What are you doing?!
She does everything as she pleases.
What the heck!
I don't care if you're her former servant or maid!
I can't let her work here!
Not at this dumb and creepy shop!
Little boy.
Bad.
You shouldn't be talking like that.
You would be hurt if someone
said mean things to you.
Right?
Y-Yes.
He just likes older girls?
Good.
You get a reward for being a good boy.
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
Oh yeah.
This is for Youko-chan so she'll get better quick.
The smell's leaking past the container!
My eyes sting!
Is your Onee-san licensed for these substances?
Does she handle poisonous substances?
Youko-chan, I have food for you.
Don't!
Please, stop!
Nishiyama!
Wanna go have fun?
Hey, Nishiyama!
Nishiyama!
Nishiyama, Nishiyama, Nishiyama, Nishiyamaaaa!
We're all Nishiyamas here!
And how many times did you ring?!
Come on, let's go to a cake shop!
What?
This one!
I hear the new gelee is great.
There were flyers all over school.
I can't spend money right now.
Huh?
Why not?
A camera.
Camera?
I want a camera...
to take cute pictures of my baby with.
Oh, you haven't given up on that yet?
We can be together all day long
during summer break, so I should—
So which looks good to you?
I picked this one - wanna split it?
She's not listening...
And... two of these gelees.
Two Derived from Pigs, coming right up.
Futaba-san, two Derived from Pigs, please!
Two Derived from Pigs, got it!
Derived from Pigs looks like it'll be popular.
No, that gelee isn't—
Sonobe-san, we sold out of Derived from Pigs!
Derived from Pigs is a hit!
Yeah, everyone buys Derived from Pigs.
Derived from Pigs looks delicious, after all!
I'm glad you recovered so quickly, Youko-sama.
It's all thanks to Onee-sama's cooking!
Huh?!
Somehow I've felt...
...strangely energetic since I ate it.
And I didn't sleep a wink last night, either!
Is she actually okay?
Well, either way, she's got energy...
Hmm?
Isn't that Hayama-san and company?
Welcome!
I'm sorry, but we just sold out of the new gelee.
Aw, there's no more?
Th-That's not the issue!
Oh, are these acquaintances of yours?
Yes, they're my classmates.
W-Well, well!
So you work here, Hayama-san?
This is a surprise.
Is it?
Why is my heart suddenly pounding?!
Oh, wow!
You're a maid!
Eh?
Y-Yes...
It's that "cosplay," thing, huh!
Hey, do you call the customers "Master"?
This is a uniform, so it's not cosplay.
What?
It's totally cosplay!
Are you listening, Kondou-san?
Sh-She's...
This is—
But I saw this on TV!
...so oblivious to the atmosphere!
I don't work here.
I'm helping out.
Me too, but only when it's busy.
They're truly lifesavers!
Wow.
That's right, Hayama-san is amazing.
She's unfailingly good with customers,
she works quickly, and she thinks quickly.
Very people her age are so skilled.
No, you're flattering me.
Oh, please.
Anybody could do that!
Customer service is a common student job.
I don't want to hear that from
someone who's never done it.
Also, I doubt someone as overly
proud as you could manage it.
T-True, it is bit beyond me,
since I'm not brave enough...
...to wear such uniform.
Th-That's right!
Nishiyama, you totally isn't cut out
for cute clothes like that, right?!
That's not what I meant!
And you only just started this job!
I'm not sure getting so emotional
suits a customer service position.
Well, would you like to try
your hand at the job?
Experience is good for you.
Oh, sorry, my hand slipped.
Five times?!
Please don't do things that
will complicate our lives.
My motives were perfectly pure.
What's wrong with this place?!
Why did we have to go to
a place Hayama works?
Let's hurry home and have tea!
Wait!
Nishiyama-san!
Wh-What?
You can have these.
They're part of a special order I made.
Additive-free pet treats.
Give them to your kitty.
Isn't this yummy?!
Yes, that might be the best patisserie in the area.
But I'd never have guessed
Hayama-san works there!
You want more?
Sorry, that's all I have.
We aren't open yet.
Have you decided to work for me after all?
What? N-No!
I prepared everything yesterday,
just in case this happened!
Wh-What is this?
Nishiyama-san, smiling the
key element of customer service.
I can't believe I'm doing this...
Come to think of it,
Hayama-san's smile was perfect.
I won't ask you to match her smile,
but try to look friendlier.
There's no way I can't do it, if Hayama can!
Thank you very much!
How was that?
Wait, why'd you photograph me?!
Hmm...
Yours just seems unfriendly,
or perhaps I should say unnatural...
Huh?!
Hayama-san told me that you
have a cat you dote on, is that right?
Yes...
Why don't you imagine playing with it?
Playing...
No, that's not a face for customers.
Was my expression that weird?!
One moment, please!
This is hard...
It's fine, no hurry.
J-Just a moment.
Is it your first day?
Isn't it great you get to
wear such cute clothes?
I know the truth, Nishiyama-san.
You pretended not to...
...but in truth...
...you really enjoyed putting that on!
Good!
Good job, Nishiyama-san.
Bravo!
Wh-What's with the sudden praise?!
She finally complimented me,
even if I don't really get why.
Well, of course!
Anything Hayama can do is a breeze for me.
That's right, I am a capable woman!
Welcome!
Huh?
N-Nishiyama-san?
Oh, right, they work here...
...and yet I let myself be
coaxed, into wearing this...
A dozen financiers, please.
She acted nice?!
What's this about, Sonobe?
I got curious when you suddenly called
and gave me the day off, but...
Well, Nishiyama-san said she could do
anything Hayama-san could do, so.
Th-That's...
When did you make a new uniform, anyway?
The truth is that I made it for Youko-sama.
What?
It turned out too tight across the chest,
but it's just Nishiyama-san's size.
Excuse me!
J-Just a moment!
There are so many customers!
I have to work fast...
Fast...
Nishiyama-san.
It's difficult for anyone until they get used to it.
Strawberry mousse, roll cake...
Nishikawa-san...
...and gateau chocolat,  right?
I'm so sorry for the wait.
We'll be right with you.
How about this one?
It's new!
Ah, high school girls are joining hands
and making merry at my shop.
I'm sorry, but our star Derived from Pigs is sold out.
Would you this roll cake?
Yes, thank you very much!
What a rough day.
Still...
...I got kitty treats.
And...
Middle Camera
Oh my.
Are you here shopping, Nishiyama-san?
Yes, I need a camera to
take pictures of my baby—
What?!
Hey, why are you making printouts?!
To give you as mementos.
I don't want them!
I see!
And by that you mean
you'll continue to work for me?
What?!
Never mind, just delete those from your phone!
Delete them!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade.
Rock, paper, scissors!
– This is Shino...
A    A
This is
Shino...
– This is Shino...
– ...and Selina's next episode preview!
A  A
A    A
A        A
A          A
A       A
A        A
A     A
...and
Selina's
...next
episode
preview!
A             A
A              A
A               A
A                A
A              A
A             A
A          A
Okay, you're a capable woman,
Nishiyama-san, so I leave this to you.
Okay, you
are a capa-
ble woman,
Nishiyama-san,
so I leave this
to you.
Thank you.
What?! Well, fine.
A  A
A A
AA
A        A
A       A
A         A
What?!
Well,
fine.
Next time: Veggies, Meat,
Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Fish.
A           A
A          A
A      A
A       A
Next time:﻿
Veggies,
Meat, Meat,
Meat, Fish.
Next time:
Veggies,
Meat, Meat,
Meat, Fish.
Next time:
Veggies,
Meat, Meat,
Meat, Fish.
Next time:
Veggies,
Meat, Meat,
Meat, Fish.
Next time:
Veggies,
Meat, Meat,
Meat, Fish.
Next time:
Veggies,
Meat, Meat,
Meat, Fish.
Next time:
Veggies,
Meat, Meat,
Meat, Fish.
Next time:
Veggies,
Meat, Meat,
Meat, Fish.
P-Please watch!
A   A
A  A
A A
A    A
P-Please
watch!
clap
You made me do it, so
what's with that reaction?!
A    A
A     A
A      A
A       A
You made
me do it,
so what's
with that
reaction?!
Next time:          Veggies,
Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Fish