WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
Commentary "hosts" are the two seiyuu for 鹿目まどか(Kaname Madoka) & 暁美ほむら(Akemi Homura):
悠木碧(Yuuki Aoi) - affectionately called あおちゃん(Ao-chan).
斎藤千和(Saitou Chiwa) - affectionately called ちわ(Chiwa).
The guest this time is seiyuu for 美樹さやか(Miki Sayaka):
喜多村英梨(Kitamura Eri) - affectionately called キタエリ(Kitaeri).
The seiyuu don't know the full script at this point; only up to episode 10.
Throughout audio commentary, ね(ne) will be left untranslated at my discretion. It means either "Right?", "You know", "Hey" or "Huh?" depending on context.
もう(mou) will also be left un-tl'd. It means something like "Sheesh" or "Geez."
Kyubey (QB) is officially genderless. But for the sake of simplicity,
commentary is translated on the premise it is a male.
Hello everyone! Welcome to the Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika Blu-ray & DVD audio commentary!
With the role of Kaname Madoka, it's Yuuki Aoi!
kanamemadoka
Ahaha~ With the role of Akemi Homura, it's Saitou Chiwa.
Kaname Madoka, huh?
Kaname Madoka.
So it's Kaname Madoka.
It is a difficult but worthwhile position.
Well, seems that we're hosting the audio commentary together this time.
Yes, "hosting," you say?
Yes~
Isn't that right?
Ne! Kind of feels like a radio show!
Right, we were told to "Please go with that sort of feeling," though.
Right, well, for this episode one's starting style, it's like that.
(lol)
That's right isn't it?
What would be good to talk about? (lol)
アフレコ(afureko) - abbreviation for "after recording": adding sounds to a soundtrack after a film has been made; postrecording; postsynchronization; postsynchronisation; postlooping; dubbing; recording.
Right? Um, for us, the after recording isn't over yet, but...
Mm, mm.
Ah, that's wrong, it's time for the first sales, isn't it?
That's right.
Actually, today is airing of the, 9th episode?
Eh? The 10th?
10th is 9th?
9th?
10th-9th
10—
Around there.
That hurts, huh?
Actually, there's a big problem with the current state of this volume right now...
eheh, eheheh~
Yes...
A little bit of episode one reforming.
Right?
A lot to do, huh?
Ne? This is the ED starting from episode three.
Mm, mm.
It really does feel like an ending.
That's right...
But, at this part of the beginning, my first time watching I was like...
Mm.
first time watching...
Ahhhh
Ahhhh.
Like that.
This is like that kind of "Ah", isn't it. Or something.
Mm.
That's about right.
Ne~
Ne!
At first I was wondering "What is this?"
Truly! It's amazing, isn't it... and then, this song!
Ne? Right, I-really-love-Kalafina-songs so,
it was like, really high tension...
That's right.
It was nice.
That's right, it's wonderful.
That's right.
Magnificent, isn't it?
Homura has come.
That's right, Homura-chan is so cool.
Um, you know, in truth we were going to call in a guest when the opening started, but...
Yup!
This time we ended the introduction pretty quickly, so shall we call in our guest early?
That's right, actually for the commentary this time we called in a guest...
Ne!
Yes!
Yup, yup
during after recording she became like a sister!
Yes!
Our episode one guest, is this person!:
Hello everyone! With the role of Miki Sayaka, it's Kitamura Eri!
Ta-da!
YAYYYYYYYY SAYAKA-CHAN!
Yayyyy
Sayaka-chan~
Man, they bring out grand things for episode one (lol)
This is grand.
(lol)
This guy is worrying, isn't he?
There he is! Th-th-th-th-th-there he is!
(lol)
Ne~?
He's cute, huh?
Back then, he was cute!
Ne? I think everyone thought "No way, his mouth doesn't move!?"
That's right.
That's right, ne.
Right.
During the episode one after recording, the cast actually didn't understand any circumstances surrounding him, so...
In actuality, right?
That's right, ne.
Right, right, right.
Yes.
We did it with the story covered in mystery, though...
Covered in mystery, huh?
Yes.
It has become a situation where we all believe in the characters together.
That's right.
Really, for an original work, it's like that, huh?
That's right, ne.
Ne~
Mm. I believe in our quality for after recording, but each time it's like "Next week's script still isn't ready!?"
(lol)
Ah, that's true. What happens next is staying on my mind, you know~
Really. It's kinda like, "I definitely want to know, but knowing is kind of scary."
That's right, ne?
Mm!
Right. With that kind of feeling let's start.
Yes.
Yes!
Yes, I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you!
Ah, this part has come.
Like, "it was a typical dream ending?"
Ne?
(lol)
No matter how many times I see this scene... it's in episode two as well, or no, after this.
That's right.
Don't you think it's like a really "Ah, mahou shoujo item" feeling?
Mm!
That's right.
Ne~?
It has that kind of feeling.
Ah~
The opening has begun, though.
Ah, The opening has begun!
Ne, at this point, only seeing this much, it's like "This is really a mahou shoujo" feeling.
Right right right
That's right, it's really like Madoka will fight while kira-kira (shining-shining).
Ne~
Right, her clothing certainly gave off that feeling... well, well, naturally.
Ne~!
It'll become something troubling, though (lol)
That's right.
Just what is this sort of thing!? (lol)
Where is this kind of thing!? (lol)
Thiiis!
Isn't this fraud!?
(lol)
Yes, seriously, you know...
(lol) seriously, you know...
Right.
I think it really surprised me, you know!
Right?
But in the end, maybe that's what everyone expected?
Right, speaking of expectations, when my friends and such watched, by episode 3 it was like "It finally came."
That's right.
Ahh, I see.
That's when it came.
Right, during this point, episode 3 hadn't come yet.
We were completely completely deceived.
That's right.
The shocking episode 3 is, you know...
(lol)
This first episode was like a rare world of peace!
Ne!
Yes.
That's right.
That's right!
On the contrary, it just created a big feeling of uneasiness!
Right, right.
It felt like everyone was lying to me (lol)
Mm!
Really, don't you think this serves its purpose perfectly?
Mm, mm.
Like, "How will that end up?"
Like,How will it? (lol) up"?
Or maybe it will be fun...
Mm.
Conversely, what is it, for this piece of work, it was extremely SHAFT-san heavy.
It's an amazing golden staff, isn't it?
Right? Right! Really.
Right!
So it was a feeling sort of like... "I can't just smile and laugh."
(lol)
Yes.
If you have layers of history with everyone!
Right!
Right, right. Um, everyone took auditions right?
Yes, that's right.
I had auditions with Ao-chan, right?
That's right! We saw each other.
Mm, right.
It had been a long time since we saw each other...
Then, I said something like "A–Ao-chan! Let's go have a meal, let's go have a meal!" and we went to go have some food together.
Right, that's right.
Ah, is that so?
Right, right.
Somehow, it was a feeling of meeting up after a long time.
Ne?
Right, right, I really remember.
Ne~
How were the feelings during auditions?
Ah, for me, my image of Madoka hasn't changed much since auditions.
Ohhh.
I'd kind of say that she's a normal person. She actually left a bigger impression on me than anyone else. (lol)
Well, that's important you know, that kind of, what is it... natural feeling with your character.
Right.
What is it, somehow... she was the first girl—
She was a natural feeling character?
Right.
Mm, mm.
I thought I'd be able to do a happy-part.
What about you, Kitamura-san?
For me, um, it was like I was just about to get the mom's role, or the dad's, or the friend Hitomi-chan...
Mm!
Ah!
Yes, yes.
Because I took all of those auditions at the same time, but...
Ohh.
蒼樹うめ(Aoki Ume) = Original Character Designer
Somehow, really, um... Ume-sensei was like "What do you yourself want to do?"
And for the next auditions, it was like, "You can freely pick a role yourself, we don't mind."
Ah, right, right, right, right.
That was there, wasn't it?
And then it was like "Ah, whatever role?", I was thinking "It's going to change again, isn't it?"
(lol)
There was a lot to think about!
When I thought about it, upon Sayaka being decided, I was extremely happy about it, but...
I didn't actually think I'd get Sayaka.
You had picked different roles?
I took her in the very beginning, then by the end, probably um...
I was told "Please try out some Sayaka"...
Then somehow, I felt as if Sayaka was really close to parts of myself, too. For example, her tension is high.
To that extent, I thought "Ah, she's fairly close to me."
I did it fairly naturally.
Auditions ended with a feeling of being very fun.
That's right, ne!
Now when it's done, I feel very optimistic with Sayaka, I feel like I endured through it well. Yes.
Ahh~
Right. For me too, I was taking completely different roles at first.
And then, after that, they told me to "Try out some Homura please." I wasn't taking Homura before that though...
But then on the day of auditions, it was the same day as Ao-chama's!
Then it seemed like there were a lot girls even younger than Ao-chan!
That's right.
T–That was true.
Amazing!
For me too.
So like that, everyone was younger, and I was like "Eh? No! Secret! No! I double your score!"
(lol)
(lol) That's...
So! (lol)
So, when the actual cast was decided, or I heard about the cast, I was thinking "Huh? My expectations are high!"
It became a really golden cast, huh?
That's what I thought.
That's right, isn't it?
But I had thought "Eh? Even though this is a mahou shoujo?"
Then when it started...
Ahhhhhh
It became clear then.
Right.
Well, that was a bit of a part to come to an understanding with...
Really, um, you know, there are things like this, which feel cute...
there's that, but then... and there isn't really that much uncertain darkness yet.
there's that, but then? and there isn 't
That's right.
Right.
"Ah, I see, right, I guess that's another life experience."
"Even if there don't seem to be any signs, there might be darkness."
Then, especially Homura, you know.
Homura-chan is...
Seems difficult!
Sort of—
After I saw it, I was like "Ah, this is a really difficult role" but I thought it was really worth doing.
It's difficult~
You're perfect for it!
No, no, no, mou!
せってい(Settei) - Setting, establishment, creation, "configuration"...
But out of all the other characters, Homura-chan is the only one with a settei of having a two totally different types of personalities.
Right? That's true, isn't it?
~Right~? That's true, isn't it?
Really, I thought that part seemed hard, from episode one.
No, no, no, no, but really she was a character worth doing. But you know, that's true for Madoka and Sayaka too (lol)
Everyone, certainly cries a lot, huh? (lol)
Everyone, certai crie— a lot, huh?
Yes.
Truly. It's like Sayaka☆Magika.
Right, I thought that, Sayaka☆Magika!
Well really, in after recording, amazingly...
Ah, seeing the point of origin this time is extremely fun, isn't it?
Yes.
Right.
Ne? Back then it was considerably—
Kira-Kira!
(lol)
Somehow the backgrounds are all kira-kira, too.
Ne~?
There's a feeling of fresh health and vigor.
There's even gags and such! (lol)
Yes, that's right!
Ne~?
Mou.
Mou, the girls being happy. It's so lovey-dovey.
Ne~
So cute~
Right, the relationship between them is so cute, ne?
Ne~?
Mou.
Episode one is precious.
Somehow, it was like "Is there really this much crying?", but now after recording is like... "Hm..."
There is a really dark atmosphere (lol)
Everyone falls dooown↓
Everyone was having fun, huh?
Ne?
Now after recording, this is like a break.
Right, conversely, it feels a bit high tension (lol)
Right, after everything else, ne (lol)
Ah, it's Sensei!
That sensei!
Right.
The sensei who's extremely popular in after recording!
Mou~ Truly, Iwao-san is perfect for her, ne?
Ne~?
That's right, ne.
Cute...
The best~
A super cute type of person, huh?
Cute.
(lol)
Ah...
Sensei...
Sensei is cute, mou...
It's coeducation, isn't it?
That's right.
Right, it's co-ed, isn't it.
Right, right.
Well, in any case, there are a lot of girls in the cast workplace, aren't there?
Mm!
Yes.
For the background chatter, girls tried hard for a guy's voice.
That's right, isn't it.
Right right right.
That was us, you know.
Without guys, we were...
"Uheeee~" and such (lol)
"Uheee Uheee~"
"Uheee!↑"
I thought there might be a few more guys!
Right, right.
Anyone ended up being a girl.
Yes.
Everyone did their best.
بداية عربية
(lol)
Ah, Homura-chan has come!
She's come!
Chiwa-san's first entry!
"Chiwa-san", no, no, no.
It's no good, it's too heartbreaking to see her here.
It's no good~
(lol)
In episode one, really, her image was quite dishonest.
Right?
Then Sayaka was often saying things like "What's with her?"
Then you know, on the other side, it turns out Homura is really a good girl.
No, no, no, no, no.
Truly, you know, when I saw episode one, I thought something like "Hee~ so it's this kind of conversation?"
You thought.
(lol) Really.
Completely!
But, what is it... I interpreted it like "Whoa, amazing! It seems like she'll betray them!"
Then it was said, like "What will happen after this?" Somehow, probably...
When trying to form a guess, I thought she gave off a feeling like a traitor.
Right? right.
That's right, huh?
The "dark" she calls is amazing.
Yes, that's right. This is completely unrelated, but don't you think that white board would be digital?
Like a new white board.
It seems a lot is digital.
High-tech?
Right, high-tech!
Right, and the school is entirely made of glass.
Right, it's a cool school, isn't it?
Ne?
The uniform is cute, isn't it?
The uniform is cute.
It's cute.
A school with no isolated or hidden parts would be extremely doki-doki (exciting).
Ah, that's right!
Ne?
Your gaze would be able to see anywhere!
(lol) That's right.
That's right! That's right...
What do they do when they change clothes? Like in gym.
Everything here gets covered in smoke!
Smoke comes, does it?
For changing clothes?
Changing clothes?
Somehow, the power of science goes "Shun!" and covers all the glass instantly.
Right, "Shun!"
(lol)
All of the glass.
Like a smoke screen?
Right.
Or a something-something that'll pull things away.
"Get this thing away!"
Isn't that a bit scary?
That's right.
Yes, right.
My first time watching, it was like Madoka still hasn't smiled at all, huh? (lol)
Right.
Gradually, Ao-chan's voice when acting her out... well, gradually, her voice was...
Mm...
It got more sorrowful, didn't it?
That's right...
Right, right.
Right, the basics were "Alllways crying."
Doing sobbing.
Mm...
Pretty harsh, isn't it?
Right.
But Madoka was given a lot of guidance, especially right around here.
That's right.
Mm.
Somehow, Madoka is just a normal girl, so all the other characters were guiding her.
Everyone was constantly guiding her, and telling her things to make her heart stronger.
Always saying.
Her courage, too, like "it's okay."
Hold the strongest courage and heart!
Shaken up, shaken up.
She was really scared, wasn't she!? So she was like "Ah, what should I do!?"
Well, after everyone helped her stand, she changed a lot.
That's right.
The way Ao-chan walks is great, truly.
Really?
That's right, yeah.
Her figure when walking was the most distinct, she moves back and forth.
Right!
Always just moving feet in a "mysterious direction", though...
It's amazing she can do that and still keep balance.
Well, I don't really know, though...
It's almost like how a bear walks, or something.
She moves her right foot forward like she's blind.
Puts her feet out way in front...
Somehow, in the old days, wasn't there a cat-type character like that?
They'd always follow their friends, get lost for a long time, then have a hard fight ahead.
Ohh...
It's very much like Ao-chan's walk.
(lol)
Somehow it holds a sort of gentle weightless feeling to walking forward.
I really love that.
That's right.
(lol)
It's elegant, isn't it?
That's right! It feels elegant!
Is that so?
Yeah.
ktkr –Σ(ﾟДﾟ;) Here it is!
This has a bit of a coarse-type feeling, doesn't it?
That's right.
Right...
Homura-chan is...
(；´Д｀)ﾊｱ・・・
Looking at me!
(ﾟ∀ﾟ) (lol)
This doesn't seem like a cool thing to say!
(lol)
Truly—
She's asking Kaname Madoka a kind of tricky question, huh?
That's right. It gets brought up after this, but...
Ne? This.
That's right.
This was a line at the auditions too, and I thought "I definitely don't want this role!" (lol)
(lol)
"Kaname Madoka" is sort of a hard name to say, but very girlish.
"Kaname Madoka" is.
Like you want to put a space in between.
Kaname Madoka.
Kaname Madoka... or something.
Right.
She calls everyone by their full names.
That's right...
Certainly...
Other people's names are relatively hard...
"Tomoe Mami" is also really hard.
"Tomoe Mami" is considerably.
Ah, that's true isn't it.....
This "eye close up" is almost scary.
Scary...
This is quite the glance.
Right here!
Here, here, here!
"Kaname Madoka de mabedebubude"
(lol)
Right.
dokadeadededededubbu
KanameMadokadebabababawuwuwu
Just kidding (lol)
I need a break...
In the actual thing you were able to say it fine. As expected from Chiwa-san.
Ne!
As expected.
No, no, no, no!
That's because, in the real thing, you absolutely have to!
Your life depends on it!
But it's amazing!
Sometimes it's like "Ah, today I may be unable to do this..."
Ah, it's digital.
Right? It really is.
Right? That's right.
She can do anything, can't she?
Right?
Anything...
Ah~ How nice, I'd love to do this just once.
Ne~?
(lol)
You aren't allowed to have your hair like that, are you?
Really!?
Right, they should get mad at her for breaking the rules!
(lol)
Get mad!
But, she's a new student, so that's OK.
Ah that's right.
Looks like it's OK!
I guess it was approved.
Maybe they think that since she just joined a new school, she isn't used to this school's rules yet.
Right! She is ignorant to this school's rules!
Ignorant. But you know, it seems like pink and blue hair are "in."
That's right (lol)
Right!
(lol)
Madoka is the one breaking the rules the most, isn't she~!
Right.
He came!
Ah, he came!
Ah, no good.
Really, well, you know, he looks cute... and well, he's voiced by Emiri-chan, right?
But this white animal REALLY isn't popular.
This white thing.
Right?
I'd say, "This guy again..."
White thing, huh?
(lol) Well, you say white animal, but in that shadow, I kind of see a demon.
(lol)
Well, during the time after recording, right?
When I saw the concept sketches, I thought he'd be easy-going...
Ahh!
At that time there was a lot of hidden meaning in QB, wasn't there?
Right, like "You're putting his face in the shadows too much!"
こわかわいい(kowa-kawaii) - scary cute
こわい(kowai) - scary
かわいい(kawaii) - cute
He's really "kowa-kawaii", huh...
You know, I really love this part.
Mm.
Ahh.
It's kind of... cute...
Mou...
Amazing!
I really like the relationship between these three.
Really liked it.
(lol)
Ne?
It was a casual every-day life with no problems~
Yes it was~
Mou, really...
Well, sorry for saying it now, but you know, Sayaka can actually properly smile and laugh like this.
I kind of feel like crying seeing it now. (lol)
Well, now, it's like their laughter has changed.
Right?
That's right, ne.
Also, at this time, I wonder what Hitomi is thinking in her head!
Uwaaaaa scary!
Ahhhh~
(lol)
Scary.
That's right.
S–She's a good girl though, you know!
Maybe she was a good girl?
Mm...
But you know, being fair and square, everyone is pretty mature, and really direct, but they're pretty selfish. (lol)
That's right, but that's because they're middle schoolers.
That's right, huh?
That's a part which feels very human, isn't it?
Right, right, right.
Ne?
Mm!
For this piece of work, it's really true for Madoka too, isn't it?
Because, "She's a good girl", you can really say "She's really a good girl", but...
She properly runs away.
Right!
A lot.
That's right.
I really like that about Madoka.
I am able to really feel it, though.
In what you'd call a usual mahou shoujo, things are really "kira-kira!", right?
Like when fighting, it's like "I have to fight to protect everyone! Save everyone! I'm on a crusade!", right?
Madoka really has those parts, but Madoka is, really...
She can actually cry, right?
Right.
Like a person, she can cry and run.
Right, rather than an "already-decided crusade," you can see parts to the characters which are like "Somehow we have to get through this."
Mmm!
Right, right.
Right!
After watching it all, or rather, since it's almost over...
When watching episode one again, I'd say "Wow, there's foreshadowing in these kinds of places."
That's right, isn't it?
He looks like a bunny rabbit.
Don't be panting like that!
Right!
(lol)
Even though your freakin' mouth doesn't move!
Around here, what is it, you could say his face is cute!
THIS little thing is cute?
(lol)
And I'm like "Ehhh!?"
Well, his cute parts are cute. It's truly wonderful.
(lol)
That's right.
The balance that all the characters hold is nice, isn't it?
Cute!
Right.
They have proper personality... but they're each individually human.
That's right.
Ne?
Sayaka too, right?
Sayaka...
Since she gets very cocky.
But I like Sayaka, really!
Ah, seriously.
She's cute, isn't she?
Cute~
Getting cocky is... forbidden!
I think that getting cocky is dangerous,
Dangerous, I'd say (lol)
so when the characters get a bit cocky, it's like...
That's right.
"No, no, no, no!"
That's so, that's so.
Don't put up flags, don't put them up!
Right, right, right.
It's just like that, really...
That's right.
Somehow, the inside of a building just being like this normally, is amazing, isn't it?
Ne~?
It has atmosphere, and I really like it.
Right? I really get it.
おしゃれ(oshare) - stylish, fashionable, hip.
"Oshare" means a mix of cool, stylish, fashionable, and/or hip.
It's usually also associated with a very "clean" and "modern" feeling.
In other words, it's the opposite of you.
It's oshare, isn't it?
Oshare, oshare.
Oshare!
Somehow, I want to go to a place like this (lol)
Ne~?
The barriers that come up in a little bit, in which we fight things... those are somehow also very "oshare-scary."
Ah.
Mm!
That's right.
Somehow—
They're scary! But stylish!
Right!
Ne?
Somehow, it's enchanting, isn't it?
世界観(sekaikan) - world view, world outlook, world appearance.
"Sekaikan" is basically the "setting" of a story, but it delves a bit deeper than simply a "setting..."
It is better described as the overall atmosphere that a piece of work holds, from setting, to backgrounds, to characters, to coloring, to shading or music...
This is called the "view" of the overall world, or the sekaikan.
This kind of sekaikan.
That's right, isn't it?
Ahh.
Amazing.
That is definitely true, for this piece of work.
Truly. When seeing that, it was a surprise, wasn't it?
Mm.
She looks so cute when she's surprised!
Oh, he's come!
There it is!!!
Σ(ﾟДﾟ;) Ah...
Uwaaah.
It's fine, just throw him away like that!
(lol)
Run away, run away!!
Get away!!!
MADOKA, RUN AWAY!
(lol)
He's gonna get you! (lol)
(lol) No, no, no...
(lol)
Mou, this is really fun, isn't it?
H–Homura-san, just keep doing it like you were, please!
H–Homursa-san, just keep doing it like you were!, please!
Just get Madoka too!
Homura looks a bit too relaxed!
(lol)
You know, people who haven't watched to the end might not want to hear this, but everyone goes through a lot, don't they?
Probably a lot of painful things, huh?
Right?
Probably a lot of painful things. huh?
But to see a piece of work that changes this much when you watch up to a certain point, then go back to the beginning... is pretty rare.
Certainly.
Mm!
Really.
That's right. So seeing how Homura acts, or the other characters who were already mahou shoujo from the start, seeing their actions...
When you see it once again, it's completely different!
When you see it once again, it's completely different.
Then, these two idiots!
What're you doing?
(lol)
Sayaka, stop...
SAYAKA MAGIKA! (lol)
(lol)
No, no, no, at this point there's no helping it, is there?
That's right.
Right...
But at this point, I'm sure everyone's feelings have changed a little bit, huh?
That's right~
Here it i—
ｷﾀ━━━━(ﾟ∀ﾟ)━━━━ !!!!!ｷﾀ━━━━(ﾟ∀ﾟ)━━━━ !!!!!
Here it is~
劇団イヌカレー (Gekidan Inu Curry) - Staff which designed the barriers.
It's Gekidan Inu Curry-san.
Super cool, huh?
That's right... the music is cool too, isn't it?
I wonder why this kind of thing happens, you know?
Ne?
Mou, really.
Infinitely cool.
Amazing, isn't it?
Mm.
Really, though... even for us in after recording, it's like "What is with this?"
Ne?
Mm, mm.
I've always wanted to ask how they made this kind of sekaikan.
Mmm.
Mm.
It has come.
Right.
Ah... QB is all crumpled up... （ ＾ω＾）
Mmm.
What Sayaka just said, "What is that? A living thing?"
CM = Commercial
That line has changed from when I recorded it for the CM track.
Ohh!
Ah, right.
Really, you know... really, a lot of lines have changed one-by-one, haven't they?
(lol)
That's right~
In this piece of work, actually, despite the program's title, everyone does a lot of lines.
Mm!
Ah, right, right, right, right.
Right!
It's fairly divided.
ヒゲおじさん(hige ojisan) - Mustache Old Man
Ah, there it is, "Hige Ojisan"!
There's Hige Ojisan!
Ahhh~!
Cute.
Cute, isn't it...
I wonder if they'll make a hige ojisan strap.
(mobile phone strap)
Ah, that's right, the German! This is actually German.
What's with this?
It was German.
Everyone decoded it!
Right.
People did that.
Speaking of the Hige Ojisan though, they're chanting about their mistress.
chanting about mistress!
Right, right.
But this sort of sounds like... "ne."
Ne.
It's like "Ne, ne~"
Ne~
They're actually saying some amazingly intense things.
What're they saying?
Like "Cut off their heads!" or something.
It's something like "Offer heads for their queen."
Right...
Right, it's an intense thing to say, isn't it?
Like a scary children's story.
It's scary!
Ahhh~ I don't want this!
Up until now I thought they were cute, the Hige Ojisan have betrayed me...
(lol)
Seems they inserted some retouches around here.
The color is really nice too, isn't it?
Ne~? Hii~!
That's right, truly cool.
I really like it.
Ohh, it's come!
It's come, that technique.
FROM HERE ON OUT—! SUPER—
She's come, the super star has come!
So nice, isn't it?
MAMI MAMI-TAAAAAAAAN!
Super star~
It's Mami-tan.
Mami-ta~n
Man, Mami-san is—
So cool~
Wow, it's like they really changed the color shading here.
That's right, ne.
Mou...
But somehow, in between episodes one and two, I kind of thought Mami-san might be a really bad person.
That's right, isn't it?
Like she could have been the key to it, right?
Ne? That's right, right.
Mm, mm.
When a new character comes in at the final stage, it's like that, isn't it?
Ah, that's true, isn't it?
A difficult first episode, huh?
It's time to end soon, isn't it?
Ah, that's right.
Ne?
That's right. It's coming up pretty soon, but...
Mm.
Really though, for the rest of this, well, there may be people who are watching this, and it's their first time.
I think there are a lot of people who have finished Madoka☆Magika too, but...
Somehow, from the viewpoint of you two, what are this piece of work's charms? Since we're ending soon.
Ahhh~
Mm!
Go, Ao-chan.
Mm.
That's right, in the end, really... the topic of "mental state"...
Um, then the fact that they don't just feel like characters, you can see them as actual people... is somehow, what is it...
Since I thought everyone had a real pulse of life to them, it made me pulse with life as well...
Then throughout the whole second half, I've been thinking about so many various things.
(lol)
But from watching episode one, it's really... "Ah, this really has proper growth, and psychological themes... It's sort of calling to me."
Eheheh~
Ne?
Ne.
It called to me quickly.
As for you, Sayaka?
How did I do?
As for me, you know... I think a significant keyword to the meaning is "mistake."
Ahhh~
That's right.
Everyone grows by making mistakes.
There are a lot of parts where I thought "I believe that is a mistake!"
That's right, ne?
Mm.
I believe that is another one of the charms.
That's certainly true for Sayaka.
Certainly for me!
(lol)
Mou, I can't say that's wrong...
That's something.
Really...
(lol)
Nah, well...
As for Homura, you aren't able to see her true actions until around the very end, but...
Ne~?
I feel as if that leaves a bit of an impression on you, really. That's true for Sayaka too.
Um, there aren't many other pieces of work where actresses take such time to thoroughly, thoroughly create characters...
Really, afterward everyone piques your interests...
Right!
The rest of it bugs you, and bugs you, but you can't help it... it's a piece of work with a lot of love in it too...
It's rather heavy!
That's right, huh?
Heavy, isn't it?
Yes!
It's truly made very throughly, so I'd certainly like to have fun watching to the end!
Yes, please!
Desu!
Yes~!
Mm!
Well, really, we're going to end very soon, but for this version of the show there's a special ending attached, isn't there?
That's right.
Something from Ao-chan.
Right, right, right.
I was asked to please sing a character song for Madoka, well..
I went about it pretty carefree, thinking that around this time there was happiness, but then after listening to it again later,
I thought "Ah, this song hurts." (lol)
It soaked in.
Yes~
I believe it soaked in.
Well, episode one ends here...
When we continue in episode two, we will have a special person for our guest! It'll be fun~
Yes!
Ohh, I see I see.
Yes↑!
Well then, see you again!
Bai-bai~