Awful...
It can't be helped.
It's too heavy a burden for that girl alone.
But, I believe she is also at the height of her preparation.
That's too much! Such a thing shouldn't happen!
If you give up, that's as far as you'll get.
But if it's you, fate can change.
This seemingly unavoidable destruction, and this grief...
It's fine for you to overturn all of it.
Because for that reason, you are endowed with power.
Is that true?
Can a person like me... really do something?
Can I change this outcome?
Of course!
So form a contract with me...
...and become a magical girl!
A typical dream ending?
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 1
It Was As If We Met in a Dream......
Morning, Papa!
Morning, Madoka.
Where's Mama?
Tatsuya went to her. Go help out.
Okay!
Mama! Mama!
It's morning! Morning!
Wake up!
Mama! Mama!
Huh?
Mama woke up, huh?
How are things lately?
Hitomi-chan received another love letter.
That makes two this month already!
Hmph. Guys who don't have the guts to just confess directly are no good.
How's Kazuko doing?
It seems like Sensei is still continuing on.
In homeroom, she gets carried away talking fondly about her loved one!
Since this week makes three months, it's a new record, you know!
Oh, I wonder. This is a very dangerous time for them.
Is that so?
If it isn't the real thing, it could start crumbling around this point.
Well, I believe if they overcome it, then they could hold on for a year, though.
Perfect!
I wonder which ribbon...
Eh? Isn't it too flashy?
About that much is fine, you know.
If a woman takes her appearance lightly, it's all over.
Oh, that's good!
With this, all of Madoka's hidden fans will fall madly in love.
I don't have anyone like that!
You have to think you do!
That's a beauty's secret.
Safe.
All right, eat without leaving leftovers, okay?
'Kay!
Another cup of coffee?
Ah...
Nah.
All right! Well, I'll be back later!
See you later!
Okay! Madoka, you need to hurry too.
Eh? Ah, yeah!
I'm off, be back later!
See you later!
Morning!
Good morning.
Madoka, you're slow.
Oh, cute ribbons.
I–Is that so? Not too flashy?
They're quite lovely.
And so, she said that someone who writes a love letter instead of confessing directly is no good.
As usual, Madoka's mama is so cool!
She's a beauty and a career woman.
It'd be nice if that kind of method could be clearly broken down and understood, though...
Problems to be envious of, aren't they...
How nice. I'd like to receive at least one too, you know...
A love letter!
Oh?
So Madoka wants to transform into another popular, beautiful girl like Hitomi?
Is that why you started your image change with those ribbons?
T–That's not it! This was Mama's...
Now your mama has taught you the secret to being popular?
Inexcusable!
Such a shameless girl gets... this!
N–No, wait! Stop! Sto—
You're a cute one!
But I won't let you become popular with the boys!
Madoka, you're going to become my wife!
Today I have something important to discuss with all of you.
Listen with all of your heart.
Should a fried egg be cooked over hard? Or should it be over easy?
Yes, Nakazawa-kun!
Eh!? Um... I–I think either way is fine...?
Exactly right! Either is acceptable!
If you think a woman's charm is decided by something like how she fries eggs, then you are hugely mistaken!
All of you girls, do not associate yourselves with the type of guy that "sincerely cannot eat eggs over easy"!
Didn't work out, huh?
It didn't work out.
And all of you boys, absolutely do not grow into adults who are petty about how fried eggs are cooked!
Okay! After that...
Today I'd like to introduce everyone to a transfer student!
Uh, that's what you put off until last?
So, Akemi-san, welcome.
Cool! So cute!
Whoa, she's an amazing beauty.
No way... That couldn't be...
Okay! Well then, try a self-introduction!
I'm Akemi Homura. Please treat me well.
Akemi Ho
Akemi Homura
Um, Akemi-san?
Akemi-san, where did you go to school before?
A mission school in Tokyo.
Were you in any clubs or anything back then?
Sports clubs? Cultural clubs?
I never tried any.
Your hair is really pretty, you know!
What kind of shampoo do you use?
There's a mysterious atmosphere around that person, isn't there?
Akemi-san.
Hey Madoka, is that girl an acquaintance?
Before, didn't it kind of seem like she gave you a really strong look?
Well, um...
I'm sorry... somehow it seems that I've gotten too tense,
and I feel a bit...
I wonder if I could be taken to the school infirmary?
Eh? Ah, then I can lead you there.
Me too! I'll go, I'll go!
No, please don't worry about me.
Since I will request it from the official person.
Kaname Madoka-san... you are the health officer for this class, correct?
Eh? Uh, um...
Could you take me? To the school infirmary.
She's really cute!
U–Um, er...
The fact that I'm the health officer... how did you...
I heard it from Saotome-sensei.
Ah, I see!
Um, well, the infirmary is...
This way, right?
Eh? Yup, that's right, but...
No, because, um... perhaps...
It seems like you know the location...
A–Akemi-san?
Homura is fine.
Homura... -chan?
What could it be?
Ah, um, uh... that's a unique name, isn't it!
N–No, I mean, um, you know...
I don't mean it's weird, though!
Er, m–more like it's a cool name!
Kaname Madoka...
Do you think your own life is precious?
Family and friends, are they valuable to you?
U–Um... I–I...
They're... valuable.
My family, and all of my friends... I love them,
they're very important people!
Truly?
It's true! I have no reason to lie.
I see.
If that is true...
You must absolutely never think about something like changing your current self.
Otherwise, it will result in the loss of everything.
You should just stay as the current Kaname Madoka.
Stay as you have been, from now on.
T–This is a prefectural record, isn't it?
Whoa, amazing!
Eh? What's that?
I don't understand the reason, you know.
At first I thought she was a well-rounded student in academics and athletics, but in reality she's a psychotic weirdo!
Kuu～!
Just how far does she want her character to stand out? That transfer student!
Is it moe? Is that what moe is!?
Madoka-san, is this really your first time meeting Akemi-san?
Hmm, thinking about it in a sensible manner, that's right, but...
What's that? Any idea of a nonsensical place you met her?
Um, well... Last night, it was as if I met that girl in a dream...
Amazing! Even Madoka is trying to make her character stand out!
That's mean! Especially since I'm seriously worrying about this!
Ah, it's already decided then! This is karma from your past life!
You girls are companions bound by fate, meeting each other again!
You said "dream." What kind of dream was it?
That's... Somehow, I don't really remember very well, but...
In any case, I just know that it was a weird dream.
Perhaps there is a possibility that you really have met Akemi-san before.
Eh?
Madoka-san, you don't particularly remember her, however...
subconsciously you remember the girl's image,
and perhaps then she could have appeared in your dream.
Isn't that going too far?
What kind of coincidence is that?
That is true.
My, it's already this time?
I am sorry. I need to excuse myself before you.
Is today piano? Japanese dance?
Tea ceremony practice.
Exams are very soon, so I wonder how long I have to continue this.
I'm thankful I was born a petit-bourgeois citizen.
Shall we go as well?
Ah, Madoka? Is it okay if we go to a CD shop on the way home?
That's fine.
For Kamijou-kun again?
Guess so!
Well then, see you.
Bye-bye!
Later!
(Help...)
(Help, Madoka!)
(Help me.)
Who?
Who's there?
We're currently under construction
Floors under reconstruction are CLOSED
(Help...)
We're currently under construction
Floors under reconstruction are CLOSED
Where are you?
Who are you?
(Help...!)
Was that you?
Help...
Homura-chan?
Move away from that thing.
B–But... this little one is injured.
N–No. Don't do cruel things!
This has nothing to do with you.
But this little one called for me!
I heard it! It said "Help!"
I see.
Madoka, this way!
Sayaka-chan!
At a time like this...
What's with that girl?
Now she's a cosplaying random attacker?
Actually, what is that?
It's not a stuffed animal, is it?
A living thing?
I don't know. I don't know, but...
I need to help this little one!
Huh? Where's the emergency exit?
Where is this?
This place is weird...
The path is rapidly changing!
Ah, damn it! What's going on!?
No! There's something there!
This is a joke, right?
I must be seeing a bad dream, right?
Right!? Madoka!
Huh?
This is...?
That was dangerous, wasn't it?
But it's all right now.
My, you gave Kyubey help, didn't you?
Thank you.
That little one is a very important friend of mine.
I was called for.
I heard this little one's voice directly in my head...
Hmm, I see.
Based on those uniforms, it looks like you girls are Mitakihara students too.
Second-years?
Y–You are...?
Right, right. I should introduce myself, shouldn't I?
But... before that...
I wonder, would it be okay for me to take care of a little task?
A–Amazing...
I–It's turned back!
The witch ran away.
If you want to take her down, chase after her quickly.
I'll give her to you this time.
I have business to take care of...
Your comprehension is bad, isn't it?
I said I will let you go.
I think we both want to avoid unnecessary trouble, right?
Thank you, Mami. You saved me.
Be grateful to these girls.
I just happened to be here, after all.
Thank you very much.
My name is Kyubey!
Was it you who called me?
That's right, Kaname Madoka... and Miki Sayaka too!
W–Why do you know our names?
I came here with a request for you two.
A... request?
I want you to form contracts with me and become magical girls!
Waving my hand, I say
"Well then, see you again later!"
それじゃまたねって　手を振って
Forcing myself to laugh, I become lonely...
無理に笑って　寂しくなって・・・
Distant car horns at the traffic light of an intersection
交差点信号　遠くのクラクション
The laughing voice of an unknown stranger
知らない誰かの　笑いあう声
Today I walk alone while coming and going through familiar streets
今日は一人で歩く　通い慣れた街
But somehow, compared to usual...
でもいつもよりもなんだか・・・
It seems as if I'm a bit smaller
自分がちょっと　小さく思えるよ
Waving my hand, I say
"Well then, see you again later!"
それじゃまたねって　手を振って
Fabricating a smiling face, I become lonely
笑顔を作って　寂しくなって
In truth we haven't talked enough yet, but...
ほんとはまだ　話し足りないけど・・・
The words "Well then, see you again later!"
それじゃまたね　って言葉で
Tell the lie "We'll meet again."
「また会える」って　嘘をついて
I say it while smiling as usual
いつも通りの　笑顔で言うよ
See you again tomorrow...
また　あした・・・
Subtitle notes, runes, and extras @ http://tri4.net
I can grant you girls a single wish, no matter what it is!
Eh? Really?
A "wish"?
Anything would be fine.
I can make any kind of miracle happen for you.
Episode 2
I'd Say, "That's Really Delightful."
I'd say, "That's really delightful."