We're not asking for freedom if it comes in shackles
Especially in a world so imperfect
Anime-Koi
Presents
Chaika The Coffin Princess
kyou
It's days like today
kyou
that make me want to live
mou)
(I think. I think.)
mou)
It's the important people in my life
who help me make it through
mou)
(I think. I think.)
mou)
ryou
My vision narrows being surrounded by love
ryou
What do you expect me to do on a night like this?
We cross vows at the end of the road
Seeing into ourselves in our own reflections
utsushidaseyo
We're not asking for freedom if it comes in shackles
Especially in a world so imperfect
We're not interested in the answers that only lead to farewells
We'll look for you
until we find you
So you did come.
You work for the Kliemann Organization, don't you?
It seems you are quite upset that I sent you away this afternoon.
What are you talking about?
No matter.
I was just thinking what a shame it was that
I never had a chance to use my treasure.
Damned thief.
You're a wizard?!
I'm nothing like the greenhorn
cavalier that you answer to.
Brother!
Stay back! He's a wizard!
Wizard?!
Stay out of sight!
No...
It can't be...
You should be dead!
I know I killed you back then! Are you a ghost?!
Ghost?
Why is the magic girl here?
I'm sure we killed her back then!
Well, it makes no difference.
Whether she is real or an imitation,
I won't let anyone have the treasure.
What's the deal with that wizard?
He used magic without any incantations!
Gundo... mansion itself.
Possible, wizard and mansion are one.
Does that mean he can control
anything in the mansion at will?
How do we fight him?
Gundo itself, destroy.
Where's the Gundo?
Center of mansion.
Likely... same as the important thing.
Magic, two places at once, impossible.
Chance to win.
All right. Let's split up again.
I'll draw him away.
While he's distracted, you destroy his Gundo.
Then we'll claim this important thing.
Okay?
Let's go.
The Lazy Man's Choice
I am steel.
Steel knows no fear. Steel knows no doubt.
When faced with my enemy, I hesitate not.
I am a weapon to destroy thee.
Iron-Blood Transformation!
I've seen that technique on the battlefield.
That's the secret saboteur technique of the Acura, isn't it?
Get off my case.
Brat.
This is the center of the mansion.
Can you tell where the nerve center of his Gundo is?
Unclear.
You have no idea?
No.
Damn...
Where is it?
Something!
Akari, there!
All right!
Barrier?
That which forbids, release.
The Breaker!
Removal, success!
All right...
Don't! This, important thing!
I need this!
This?
Yes.
Got him, eh?
So you're a saboteur whose only talent is fighting, right?
So what?
Our present world must be terribly boring for you.
Saboteurs are of no use, after all.
You're a saboteur who's turned into nothing more than a petty thief.
No matter. Before you die, I, the hero,
will teach you what a real battle is.
Heroes must be a pretty big deal, huh?
A mere saboteur is in no position to talk back to me.
The item you seek right now is the proof.
I earned that treasure along with my glory as a hero.
It's not something that anyone can get their hands on.
You understand that, don't you?
It is an unparalleled source of magical energy.
Its power permeates every last corner of this mansion.
This entire mansion is a part of my body!
Too bad for you, little rat.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure that girl I failed to kill before follows you into death.
Cut the crap! What are you talking about?!
I see.
You're just a petty thief being used without even knowing why.
Poor boy.
I don't need a reason to do my job!
What?!
Damn you!
I pronounce the battle over.
I am man.
Looks like your treasure's been destroyed.
Impossible! Is that girl a wizard, too?!
That's right.
Toru! Withdraw! Withdraw!
Goal achieved!
Wait!
What are you going to do with that once you leave here?!
In the wrong hands, it will only bring disaster!
You don't know what it's worth! What would you do with it?!
You wish to sell it?
If that's the case, I'll buy it here and now!
How much?! How much do you want?!
Please! Give it back!
That was pretty sloppy,
but I guess we made it out.
We haven't done such things in a long time. It can't be helped.
So that's your "important thing"?
Yes. Important thing.
If Count uses, magic fuel.
Is that a real severed hand?
Mm-hmm.
Whose is it?
Why is something like that so important?
He seemed to know that we were coming.
It sounded like he knew you, too.
What's going on?
Toru.
Akari.
You're paying us here?
Grateful.
Got important thing.
Job done.
Are you telling us to sever our connections with you?
Grateful.
Who are you?
What is your connection to that girl?
What?
You are a saboteur, aren't you?
If you're only under her employ for the money,
do not involve yourself further.
It's for your own sake.
We only need her and that hand.
If you hand them over quietly,
we won't press charges,
and we will not pursue you.
Gillette-sama, it's no use talking to a saboteur.
I agree.
There's no negotiating with them—
You sure like to talk.
I don't see why I need to let you people belittle me.
It doesn't matter what he is.
Someone who was merely
hired, with no knowledge of the circumstances, is guiltless.
Merely hired? What do you mean, guiltless?
Now, leave the girl and the tube here, and go.
You won't get away!
Akari, carry the coffin and go with her.
Leave the hand to me.
Got it.
This important! Won't give!
Listen. We haven't received our payment yet.
Our job isn't over until
you get away from them safely,
with your important thing.
Until then, I won't let anyone have it.
Okay...
Agreed.
Important thing, Toru, entrust.
Turn right!
Hold it right there!
Hand it over!
Don't touch that!
If you touch it, something terrible will happen!
Yeah, to you!
Nikolai!
Was it you who defeated him?
Who knows?
Just so you know, he's still alive.
I'll ask you again.
Do you know what that girl is?
Do you know?
We have received requests
from many countries, and our actions are right and just.
We are acting with full awareness of what it is we pursue.
We're not like you!
We act in the name of justice.
Justice, huh?
You don't know, do you?
What are you talking about?
About her.
I don't know how much she paid you,
but don't do anything stupid.
Nothing good will come from helping her.
On the contrary, you'll turn the whole world against you.
That doesn't really give me any basis to judge her.
Chaika?
Yes. Chaika.
Chaika.
Very well.
Gillette-sama, that information is highly classified.
What you hold is the hand of Emperor Arthur Gaz of the Gaz Empire.
Emperor Gaz ruled for 500 long years,
during which he exposed the continent of Verbist to many dangers.
The demon king, the taboo emperor, the great sage,
the mad warlord,
the wise emperor...
Known by many names,
he was said to have been the most powerful wizard of all.
The emperor was defeated in the battle for the capital five years ago,
but it is said that his daughter escaped.
The girl with silver hair and purple eyes who hired you is Chaika Gaz,
daughter of Emperor Gaz.
The emperor's daughter?
Not even we know in detail what Chaika Gaz has been doing
in the five years since the war ended.
In any case, we cannot allow her to roam freely.
Why?
There are still many devoted to Emperor Gaz.
Some even wish to lift up Chaika Gaz
and use her to rebuild the Gaz Empire.
Even after his death,
the emperor's remains are still a mass of vile thoughts,
as well as a source of great magical power.
They say that magic could even be used
as an enormous weapon of unfathomable power.
In other words, Chaika Gaz may be the calamity that brings war again
to this peaceful world that we finally obtained.
We cannot allow her to gather the emperor's remains.
That suits me fine.
Huh?
Bring war again, huh?
That sounds good.
What?
War is fine with me!
Why don't we let her bring back the age of war?
Are you...
I'm a saboteur!
This peaceful world pisses me off!
You're saying you wish for war?
Yeah!
Chaika!
Burst with brilliant light.
The Blind!
Wait! You're...
Akari.
What is it, Brother?
Just so you know, you don't have to follow me.
Don't be silly, Brother.
I am with you to the ends of the world.
You...
If you die without my knowledge, I can't have you stuffed.
Too bad for you. When I die, it'll be by explosion.
Got all your stuff?
Yes.
Good.
Ready to go, then?
Toru, Akari... why?
We've been seen by both parties now.
We can't stay in this town.
But I am daughter... of taboo emperor.
I told you. I'm fine with war.
I... I...
I only want to gather.
Father's remains, scattered.
I want to gather.
Want that. Only that.
I only give Father funeral.
What I must do.
Okay.
I'll help you achieve that goal.
If that'll let me break free of this boring life...
I don't see how it could be so bad.
Grateful... from heart.
Chief Konrad.
What is it?
According to the report from Gillette's group,
Chaika has stolen some remains of the emperor from Count Abarth and fled.
What shall we do?
What can we do but entrust it to Gillette's group?
Five years after the war,
the world should be in better shape,
but it's filled with the unrest of the people who too strongly expected peace.
Rebellions, plagues, ethnic conflicts...
We, the Postwar Restoration Agency,
have no time to become seriously involved in matters
which may become a threat.
Understood. I will relay that.
So, do you have a destination in mind, Brother?
Well, I think we should start by crossing this mountain.
In other words, you don't.
Don't worry. It'll work out.
Yes! Can only move forward!
Clear sailing!
shitai mitai ni aruku michi
We're walking on the road like corpses
gira gira to taiyou ga teritsukeru
While the blazing sun beats down on us
omae wa itsuka namae sae
You'll fall into the depths of hell one day
wakaranaku naru kurai ochite yuku
And not even remember your name
hito wa naze ikiru no ka
Why do people live?
inochi kirikizan demo
Even when our life is in pieces
owarinaki bonnou wo daite odore ba
We embrace our endless desires and dance
mujou ka
Is that cruel?
kawaki no tani kara yojinobore
Climb up from the valley of thirst
kaze no oto ga kodama shite
You'll hear the echoing wind
goran warera wo michibiku kairaku wa
See, while the desires guide us
kanashimi wo tsukkitte iku genri
We have to push our way through sadness to get there
osoreru na
Do not be scared
furueru na
Do not tremble
ikiru no da
Live on
Found vehicle!
I can drive!
Journey smooth!
Sometimes, frustrating.
Reason, Toru and Akari, can't drive.
I am exhausted.
Need substitute driver!
The Forest Where the Hero Dwells
Next week, episode 3:
"The Forest Where the Hero Dwells."
The Forest Where the Hero Dwells