Hey, Yoshii.
Yes sir!
Summon!
The Avatar of probationary student
Akihisa Yoshii has special features.
Not only can he touch objects,
but by using his augmented strength...
Go get the world map.
Okay.
...he is forced to help
teachers with their chores.
Yoshii! Bring the desks
to the audio-visual room.
What?
Yoshii! Move the soccer goalpost back.
Again? Why am I the only
one who gets ordered around?!
That's how probationary students are treated.
Man, I'm so ticked!
The probationary student receives
the same pain his Avatar receives as well.
I'll give you a small test next,
so review what you've learned so far.
I'll avenge you.
Dummy.
Hottoite sodatsu mono nanda nandarou
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
Deai mashite wa kantan sugiruyo
Saisho ni kimeta kotae wa hitotsu
Tokimeki mashita goukaku shimasuka?
Koi mo shoubu mo awatenai
Kotsu kotsu kotsu to tetsuya ni tameiki
Watashi no naka ni tensai dreamer
Omou koto mina kanaeba iina
Hito no sekai wa kinishinai
Perfect-area complete!
Zettai koko de matterunda
Perfect-area nozomu koe ga kikoeruyo
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? Tomaranai surechigai
Watashi ga soudan aite nara
"Tomodachi kai?" "Tomodachi desu."
Kanashiki rei ten dane
No! Yarinaoshi kakinaoshi
Honki de one more chance please
Ima yori suteki na mirai ga arunoni
Ima yori suteki ni my life, my life, my life!
"Episode 4"
"Love, Spices, and Boxed Lunches"
Today is Sunday. However...
This is it for today. Make sure
you review when you get home.
Okay.
...despite that, Year 2,
Class F had a remedial class.
By the way, Yoshii, what happened to you?
Well, I tried for a little revenge...
So you got beaten up instead, huh?
Ahh... I'm hungry.
Since he made me do so much
work today, I'm hungrier than usual.
Your Avatar seems convenient,
but he's actually inconvenient, isn't he?
Yuuji. Lunch time.
Shouko! Why? Class A isn't
taking a remedial class, right?
I was studying by myself. If you're
here, I'll come in even on Sundays.
You don't have to.
If you're not here, I won't come
in even during the weekdays.
That can be a problem.
Oh... You brought a boxed lunch today?
What's that?
One sixty-seventh of a cup noodle.
One sixty-seventh?
One half of one half of one half
of one half of one half of one half.
Akihisa, that's one sixty-fourth.
Calculating fractions is
your weak spot, isn't it?
I'm done eating.
How pitiful...
That's a lunch that moves you to tears.
I-I guess it can't be helped. Would
you like me to share my lunch with you?
Really?
I made too much and brought extra with me.
It'll be a waste if I ditch it,
so do you wanna eat it?
I'll eat it!
Hold on a sec, okay? Hm? Huh?
I'm sorry... looks like I left it at home.
Aw man...
After all that effort...
Don't worry.
Thinking that you could do a girly
thing like making a boxed lunch was my...
spine is being shattered!
I told you that I just forgot to bring it!
Almost... Almost...
"I can almost see, but not quite"
"A little further...!!"
"Fingers"
"Eyes"
--Ahh! Ouch! My eyes! My eyes!
--You can't look at it, Yuuji.
You guys are lively, as usual.
--Excuse me...
--Hm?
Is this Class F, the class for idiots?
Hazuki?! What are you doing here?
Ah, Big Sis!
Hazuki, you said?
Ah! Stupid Big Brother!
How amazing, Akihisa.
I never expected your stupidity
to be known to the entire country.
Could you at least say "throughout town"?!
I knew it! It's Stupid Big Brother!
Hey, Hazuki, how do you know Aki?
Because he'll be my husband.
Stupid Big Brother and I are
dating with an eye towards marriage!
What?!
Akihisa was personally
acquainted with Hazuki in the past.
I will explain how he came
to know her some other time.
H-Hey, Aki! What'd you
do to my little sister?!
We're now starting the inquisition.
Ahh! What're all you guys doing?!
The nature of the crime:
the defendant, Akihisa Yoshii,
committed a serious crime by dating a girl
in clear disobedience of the
Inquisition's pledge of blood.
Is it true and correct?
True and correct!
Defendant. Do you have any last words?
Why "last words" before the defense?
Guilty. Death penalty.
--Ahh! Hey! Ahh! Stop it! What?!
--What grade are you in?
--I'm in fifth grade!
--What're you doing?! Stop it! Stop it!
--Well, well, you're more sensible than Akihisa.
--Ahh! Don't touch there! Ahh!
--Ah! Pretty Big Sister!
--But it might feel kinda good. Ahh!
--Hello, Hazuki.
So, what brought you here today?
Oh, that's right! Here!
You left these at home, Big Sis!
My boxed lunch! Thanks, Hazuki!
Good... So you brought both.
See? I wasn't lying. I can make
things like boxed lunches just fine.
Oh, so that was it.
You woke up early, which you
rarely do, and made them eagerly.
So I was wondering why.
Now I know. You wanted Stupid Big Bro...
I-I wonder what she's talking
about. What a weird kid.
Oh, I see. So you made that
boxed lunch for Akihisa, huh?
No! Why would I do that for Aki?!
Then what were you making eagerly?
Th-That wasn't the boxed lunch. You know!
It was a model.
A model?!
A one thirty-fifth scale King Tiger!
A German heavy tank...?!
Good for you, Akihisa. That's bigger
than one sixty-fourth cup noodle.
The size isn't in question here!
It might unexpectedly taste good.
It's an inorganic substance! You can't eat it!
A-Anyway, this is just an extra.
I didn't make it for Aki, okay?!
Oh? What's the matter, Himeji?
What? No, nothing!
Is that... a boxed lunch?
Oh? You made it, too?
Y-Yes... though I couldn't make it that well.
U... Uhm...
To tell you the truth... I made this for Yoshii.
Yoshii, if you like, could you eat this?
We're now starting the inquisition.
Ahhh?! Hold on... Hold on a sec!
Guilty. Death penalty.
I'm not even given an
opportunity to speak this time?!
Please wait! It's not like that!
Ah... This is...
Well... Uhm... It's not like that.
This boxed lunch was... Uhm...
You'll be tortured and then... death penalty!
-Ahh! Hey! Whoa! They really started a fire! Ahh! A real fire!
--Oh? Big Sis?
--Ahhhhhhhh!
Dummy...
Idiot Test
Are you okay, Yoshii?
I'm fine...
If it means I can eat the boxed
lunch you made, this is nothing.
Oh... How flattering.
You can eat it without being interrupted here.
Yeah.
Whoa! That looks delicious!
You're gonna make me blush.
Ah... I forgot to bring
something to drink. I'll go get it.
Ahh... Himeji is cute, smart, and
on top of that, she can even cook...
She's too good for you.
Ah! Yuuji! What're you doing?!
I think I'll have some, too.
Ahh! You too, Hideyoshi?!
What's the problem?
It's just one piece. Don't be so stin--
Yuuji?!
Hideyoshi?! What's the matter, you two?!
This is bad, Muttsulini! We should
take them to the nurse's office!
Muttsulini!
D-Don't tell me this lunch was the...!
No way... when it looks so delicious...!
That was close. My soul was almost taken away.
There's no mistake. They fell
because of this boxed lunch.
To think that the smell
alone is this dangerous...
A... Akihisa...
Hideyoshi!
The plate... Hand me the plate.
The plate?
"Once you've had poison, you
might as well have the plate, too."
That saying means that if you
eat the plate, too, you'll be fine.
This is bad! His thinking ability is paralyzed!
I got something to drink.
Himeji...
Oh? What happened to them?
Um... They got sleepy after eating,
so they said they'd take a nap.
If you sleep right after
you eat, you'll become a cow.
If it means staying alive,
being a cow may be better.
Here you go.
Ah... Th-Thanks, Himeji.
This is bad... What should I do?
"You'd better eat or Himeji will be sad."
"Don't eat it. There'll be consequences."
"...consequences"
"If you tell the truth, Himeji will be hurt."
"Do you wanna die?"
Oh? You're not eating?
W-Well, I feel like this is
too precious to eat, so...
"It's your life that's
precious, right?!"
Could it be... that it was a bother for you?
No way! There's no way that's the case!
I'm very glad!
"Your consideration by itself makes me glad."
"Rather, I'll take just the consideration."
Good...
A-Are you the type who
samples the food while cooking?
People say that if you sample
while cooking, you'll gain weight, so...
And...
And?
I wanted you to eat it first.
The paths of retreat are all cut off now.
Why do the angel and
devil have the same opinion?!
A... Akihisa...
Yuuji!
Sakamoto...
Sorry, Himeji. May I have
something to drink, too?
Could you go buy oolong tea?
Okay, no problem.
Yuuji!
Akihisa... I'll give you some good advice.
Listen good.
From ancient times, there have
existed many spices used as antidotes.
In the time before refrigerators were available,
people used the sterilizing
ability of spices to store food.
And, it is said that in girls'
cooking, love is, indeed, the best spice.
Are you... possibly saying...
That's right, Akihisa.
Neutralize the poison
with the spice called love!
I see... I get it, Yuuji!
This is a trial given to me!
Don't worry. I'll overcome
any hardship for the sake of love!
As long as I have the best spice
called love, no matter what poison it is...
So love doesn't have a
detoxifying effect... noted.
Akihisa is a brave man.
Amen.
Oh? What happened to Yoshii?
He said he got sleepy since he ate lunch.
If you sleep right after
you eat, you'll become a cow.
Come to think of it, what happened to Shimada?
After all that effort...
I wish I had been honest
and asked him to eat it.
I never thought that Himeji would
have a subject that she's bad at.
I'm hungrier now.
Aki...
Stupid Big Brother!
Hazuki?
Do you know where my sister went?
Come to think of it, I haven't seen her.
Haven't you had lunch?
A lot happened and I couldn't consume calories.
Then are you starving?
Yeah... If only I had the
boxed lunch that Minami made...
My Big Sister's?
Yeah. I was wondering what kind
of lunch she made. I wanted to eat it.
Okay!
Aki! Have this lunc--
Let's have lunch, honey!
M-Miharu?!
I looked all over for you, honey!
I did my utmost in making
Miharu's Special Lunch. Please have it!
Why are you here?! Class D
isn't having a remedial class, right?!
If you're here, I'll come in even on Sundays.
If you're not here, I won't
come in even during the weekdays.
Why is this academy full of students
with messed up common sense?!
Nooooow, honey! Let's spend
a happy afternoon together!
--Anyway, shall we look for her that way first?
--Leave me alone!
--I won't let you escape!
--Okay!
--Let's be alone and feed each other!
--No! Don't come near me!
"Fire Hydrant"
Geez. She doesn't have to be so shy.
Honey! Honey!
That darn Miharu...
More importantly, I have to find Aki!
Go, Haiseiko!
Faster!
We shouldn't run in the corridor!
Aki... Good...
This time for sure, I'll give him this lunch!
So it was true...
So Yoshii has got two
girls making lunch for him!
This is the unforgivable truth!
Bring death to the traitor!
N-No! That's not true!
That's not true.
This is... uhm...
Well...
--Guilty! Guilty!
--What?! What?! Hey! Wait! Wait!
You've all got messed up common sense!
Geez... What am I doing?
Go, Haru Urara!
Run at full speed!
You shouldn't run in the corridor, you know.
This isn't a corridor!
I'm already out of gas today.
This time for sure...
--Aki!
--Ah...
Minami...
Big Sis!
Hmph.
I'm playing with Stupid Big Brother!
That's good. But don't bother him, okay?
Okay!
Say, Aki...
Hm?
Uhm... Did you already have lunch?
Hmm... I have... or should I say I haven't...
I see.
Uhm... well...
Hm?
Well... if you're hungry...
Huh?
Uhm... Wh... Wh...
Wh?
Wh-Wh-Wh...
Wh...
Wh?
What's the local specialty of Oshamanbe?!
Huh?
Oh, shoot!
The local specialty of Oshamanbe,
Hokkaido, would be horsehair crabs.
Kubo...
To see that you're at school on Sunday...
Are you studying by yourself, too?
Class F had a remedial class.
Oh? You haven't had lunch yet?
Huh? N-Not really...
Then, would you care to join me?
What? But I don't have money.
Well, well, it can't be helped, I guess.
Since it's just lunch,
I don't mind treating you.
I'll go! I'll definitely go!
Ah...
Well then, see you later, Shimada.
Then, why don't we prepare for
mid-terms together while eating?
What? Mid-terms?
Ah... yeah...
Hazuki, have you had lunch?
Come to think of it, playing with
Big Brother made me forget about it.
Geez. You shouldn't skip meals
or you won't be able to grow.
Isn't this for Big Brother?
No. There's no way that's the
case, is there? I made this for you.
Then, let's eat together!
Okay.
Hm?
Sorry, Hazuki. I forgot that we
still have another remedial class.
Go on ahead and go home.
Okay! I will!
Hmm...
Lunch A looks the best.
Or should I be considerate and get Lunch B?
Oh, Yoshii.
Huh?
"Seasoned Laver Paste"
Mr. Fukuhara.
Good timing. I've got a
problem. I can't open the lid.
Could you have your Avatar open it?
Piece of cake.
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
Open!
Ow!
Those who died with their score reduced
to zero will be given a remedial class!
What?!
Hey! Why?! I haven't eaten anything yet!
--That's all because of your low viability.
--How cute Yoshii is...
Huh?!
What am I saying?!
I shall eat now.
You idiot! Idiot Aki! You're really an idiot!
An ultra idiot! A heaping idiot!
Who'd make lunch for you?!
Who would?! Who would?!
You dummy.
"Other Trash" "Glasses, Cans, Plastic Bottles"
Ahh! Wait!
Aki...
Are you... going to ditch that?
Why?!
Why? Well...
Uhm...
I... I don't think people
should waste resources.
Huh?
For alleviating global warming
as well, you shouldn't waste food!
If you waste food, the
waste-not ghost will appear.
Also, to help the ecosystem, you
should recycle, or how should I say,
we should use our limited
resources more effectively...
that's how I feel.
--Here.
--Huh?
Are you going to eat it?
What?
Or not?
W-Well, then, I guess I'll eat it.
We shouldn't waste our resour--
Minami...?
Dummy!
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
Jugyou owari shifuku no jikan
Tatoeru no nara “Maji de Angel!”
Fui no kokuchi heiwa kowashita
Tsuishi no shirase “Jigoku da!”
Tomodachi tono warai banashi ni
“Iru wake naiyo sonna baka”
Demo hontou wa mune no oku dewa
Sakendetanda “Jibun ga! Sou deshita!”
Chuusha jou de miru “Tsukigime” no koto
Kaisha no namae dato omotteta...
Zutto...
Baka mo tooseba otoko date
Bokura no joushiki hijoushiki?
Ruuru wa muyou sa kono sekai
Yakiniku teishoku gekokujou
Miroyo!
Nishi kara nobotta ohisama ga shizunde iku
Hashire! Mou gohan da
Ouchi ni kaerou! Ouchi ni kaerou!
Question 5. What do you call
the sport in which you go from
checkpoint to checkpoint
using a map and a compass?
Role-playing game!
I knew that would be your answer.
Next week! "Maps, Treasures,
and Striker Sigma V (Five)"!
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!"
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"