Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
midsummer
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
phoenixmyst
mattchewwu2
Tressflin
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetter
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
Are you ready, my little ones?
Ready to advance...
Forward!
Advancing!
Where the heck are our allies?
Left, 40 degrees!
Prepare to fire main cannon!
Distance 400!
Loader, prepare explosives!
Yes, ma'am!
Olga!
Leave it to me.
We've been locked in this thing for three days.  There's no way I'm dying without getting a shower first!
Alignment complete!
Fire!
Target hit!
Anna, notify those behind us.
We've destroyed one enemy unit.  Press the advance!
Roger!
Phylicia, cover her.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Don't worry.  There may be flashes, but it isn't lightning.
I know!
T-Three o'clock!
You're kidding...
Second Lieutenant Anna!
Paper goods...
Bamboo stalks...
Come on, Noel!
If you don't wring harder, they're never going to get clean!
It's so hot...
It might be cold in the winter, but I'm so glad this building is cool in the summer.
Huh?  Wasn't it Rio-sempai and Phylicia-san's turn for cleaning today?
They said they were busy or something, so they asked us to switch with them.
Whose is that?
Phylicia-san's.
She said she didn't really have an appetite, so we should have it.
Then I'll have some!
What're those?
Preparations for dinner?
Ugh.
What are you doing?
You'll get in trouble for playing with food!
I-I'm not playing!
I mean, it's about time for the Bon Festival, isn't it?
Huh?  What the heck is the "Bon Festival"?
Fiesta des Lumières.
Fi...?
The Fiesta des Lumières is a holiday characteristic of the southern part of Helvetia.
It's based on a folk belief that the spirits of the deceased return to the transient world
for a fixed interval each summer.
And to guide those spirits back, lanterns are released to float down the river as markers.
Depending on the region, this same festival is also called the Bon Festival.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Oh, so then it's the same thing!
"The spirits of the deceased return"...
H— Wait just a second!  Does that mean that their ghosts will come back?!
In a certain sense, yes.
Lanterns, huh?!  Wow, that's so amazingly wonderful!
Back in the countryside, we would make fires and such but—
Cut it out!
People who pass on go to Heaven and stay there forever.
The ones who wander the land are the bad ones, aren't they?
What?  That's not true!
But the church—
We're home!
Hey, come give us a hand!
When did the two of you go shopping?
Ah!  Those—
Looked delicious so we bought them.
And we got these, while we were at it.
Would this be okay, I wonder?
No, not like that, Father!
It's like this!
Finished!
That's your mother and father, right?
I see!  Well done!
What?!  Even the church recognizes it?
That Fi— whatever it was?
Yeah.  If it were at a central parish then I'm sure there'd be a fuss about it,
but we're in the middle of nowhere here, you know?
How easygoing...
Where I'm from, we take cucumbers and eggplants and such, and fashion them into horses and cows
to serve as mounts for our ancestors.
And in order to make them happy, we all do a dance!
Are you two going to make some, too?
Yeah.  We only watched last year, but...
Mingling with the local people in harmony is also part of our job, after all.
If you don't really think about it, it's just a pretty little festival.
Isn't it, Phylicia?
Phylicia-san!
Are you all right?
Does it hurt?
No, I'm just fine.
I just messed up a little.
But that's rare, isn't it?
For the captain to make mistakes like that...
You're not Kanata, after all.
You see, it's been hot for the past few days, right?
I haven't been able to sleep well...
I'll just take a small break.
Phylicia-san...
There's something strange going on with the captain, don't you think?
She didn't just leave her lunch, but also skipped work and brought back watermelons...
I'm sure there are a lot of things going on, even for her.
I really think... I should go...
Stop!
Everyone has things they don't want to share with others!
Just let her be for now.
Noel?
Do you know, Rio?
I've read the records.
I know about it firsthand.
So...
Phylicia...
Hold your aim, just like that.  Good!
There, there, it's all right.
And then a monster that looked just like the captain appeared—
Gotcha!
It's hard to believe that, in the distant past, so many creatures lived in this ocean.
Have you heard it said?
"The world is slowly marching to its end, and someday we humans will likely perish entirely."
Something like that... is just a rumor!
But if it's true... I wonder, just what are we fighting for?
I... I'm still alive.
Ideograms...
I'm sorry... I wish I could read your final words.
This equipment...
This can't be— from the former age?!
Captain...
Second Lieutenant Olga...
Martina...
Anna-san...
Why am I the only one...
Why... are you crying?
I see.
There are still people surviving in this world, aren't there?
I'm sorry.
I really am sorry.
Why... are you apologizing?
Because we lost...
to them.
We couldn't protect you.
I'm so sorry.
The world ended.
You can't say...
You guys are just the remnants.
The last remaining bubbles in a ladle of water.
Humanity...
The world can never regain the prosperity it once had.
You can't just decide something like that by yourself!
But that's the truth.
So it'd be a good idea to just end it.
This world of remnants...
In this midst of this despair, this pathos, living must be exceedingly lonely.
No...  No, it's not!
Why is that?
Is there a reason for living on in this world?
That's...
Save me...
I'm here!  I'm alive!  Please, save me!
You are...
I'm very sorry.
If only my unit could've arrived just half a day earlier, things probably wouldn't have turned out like this.
Your Highness, Princess Ilya...
But I was a little surprised.
At what?
After all, last year you ignored the Fiesta des Lumières.
What's changed?
That's...
Nice color, right?
They're made in Treize.
I bought them at the last market.
Wow!
Wonderful, wonderful!
Aren't they?
Take that!
Without a doubt... in the past, that person was everything to me.
I wanted to protect the country, to protect people, the way she did.
But once in while, I think...
What's the purpose in that?
So if she really has come back,
I just feel that I'd want her to answer that.
But more importantly, what about you?
Everyone's been worried.
I imagine so.
I wonder if I've made them worry too much about me.
What a failure of a captain, hm?
It's not just them!
Even I'm—
That is, I...
You what?
Anyhow, don't try to take everything upon yourself!
Even I can at least listen to you!
Thank you, Rio.
Then I'll take you at your word and tell you.
What is it?
The truth is...
I've gotten fat this summer and I've been so troubled over it!
At this rate, I won't be able to fit into my winter clothes anymore!
I've heard that if you only eat watermelon, you'll lose weight, so I thought I'd try it.
Wait.  What's the matter, Rio?
You're still playing dumb?!
I mean, at the Vingt front, you were—
Ah!  Did you think I was recalling that?
A-Are you saying you weren't?
So pretty!
Shall we head out also?
You made one too, didn't you, Kureha-chan?
I-It's not like I believe in spirits or anything like that though!
It's a mission, a mission!
Um...
Who are you sending off, Phylicia-san?
My former comrades and a single soldier whose name I don't know.
He's a benefactor who made me realize something very important.
Could it be that that person is...?
Phylicia-san... if you ever have any worries, I...
Well, I might not be able to help you very much... but—!
Seems like I've worried you.
I'm sorry.
Still, I'm just fine, so don't worry.
But that's too sad.
Even I want to worry about you!
You're always worrying about me, Phylicia-san.
Since I always do such worrisome things...
But I want to worry about you, too!
That's because... I care about you, Phylicia-san!
I love you, too, Kana-chan.
Stay the way you are now.  Please?
Phylicia-san...
You're forever reaching out...
So completely fearless about putting your feelings into words...
I think that's an amazing thing.
Captain...
Phylicia... I also...
Oh, all of you...
You're all so precious.
Please come back next year as well, ancestors.
Dad... Mom...
Mother... sister...
That person is...
Say, Rio.  You were asking earlier if there was some meaning in this world, right?
Yeah.
As the only one who survived that incident, I've also always thought about it.
Why was I the only one who survived?
Moreover, what sort of meaning is there in that?
Then I realized.
Evidently, there's no such thing as "meaning" in this world.
But that in itself is wonderful, isn't it?
Since if there isn't a set meaning, then you can just find one on your own.
And I have found it.  I've found the reason I'm here.
And then, the priest—
And then, and then?
He was just so bad at it, so Yumina-oneechan had to—
What?!
I never want those children to have the same memories I do.
Yeah...
Next time, Telephone Duty: There's an Emergency!