Lunchtime!
Carrot porridge is on today's menu!
Her baby teeth are growing in,
so she should be ready to eat solid foods instead of just milk.
And then...
we'll make some fruit punch to go with it!
Stirry, stirry, stirry!
The Lovely Pad can do that as well?
It is a magic pad!
Here comes the airplane!
Let's try that again.
Now, say "aah."
She won't eat it.
Seems she's not a fan of carrots.
That won't do, Ai!
Picky eaters can't become proper ladies.
Mayhap you might enjoy my carrots instead?
Ai's still a bit young for curry.
T'was simply a joke, of course!
Aguri, do you...
D-Do I what?
Are you avoiding...
your carrots?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
I can't believe it!
Aguri's a picky eater?
You love sweets...
And hate carrots...
A textbook spoiled girl!
Well, I'm still in elementary school...
What don't you like about carrots?
Positively everything!
The odor!
That unspeakable flavor!
Carrot... no-no!
Ai?
It seems Ai has adopted your distaste for carrots.
No-no!
What kind of mother sets a poor example for her child?
That's what you told me when I had that cavity.
If you won't eat your carrots,
then Ai won't eat hers, either.
Wouldn't you say it's your turn to set a good example?
It is for Ai...
I understand.
I shall overcome my loathing of carrots!
No More Picky Eating!
Carrots vs. Aguri!
Now then...
"Aaah!"
I simply can't!
What should we do?
This...
calls for dietary education.
Education?
Is that clear?
Carrots are beta-carotene vegetables rich in nutrients.
They contain an enormous amount of carotene.
Carotene strengthens the immune system, which protects us from disease.
In addition, the body converts carotene into vitamin A.
Vitamin A gives us healthy skin—
Stooooooop!
Nobody wants a boring lecture!
Hey Aguri, carrots are healthy!
Wh-What monstrosity are you?!
I'm the carrot fairy, Carrot!
More like Mana.
I came to make you see the wonders of carrots!
Now, Aguri...
Noooo!
Aguriiiii!
I'm appalled that I can't conquer even a single carrot!
They may be the greatest enemies I've faced yet!
Another plate, if you'd please!
Enemies, huh?
You sure can binge on those cakes, though.
Even I'm ashamed of my own limits.
How can I still call myself a Precure?
Aguri...
Being a picky eater is cute in its own, childlike way.
Nevertheless, we can't let this continue.
It's not just your problem alone, Aguri.
What should we do?
Carrot!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
I grow all
of the Pig's
Tail's carrots!
Grandpa!
Who's the person in this photo?
That's the farmer that owns the Pig's Tail and stocks our carrots.
He put this here so customers could see the guy who grew their carrots.
A bit of an oddball, huh?
That's it!
Dinner is served!
And this is?
My secret recipe!
Ugh, veggies?
I didn't make it for you!
Now, aren't I such a good henchman?
So how about taking this ring off?
That's your game?
Mammo.
What was that for?!
I... hate carrots.
If you want to brown-nose,
you'd do better to defeat those bothersome Precures.
Right, Ira?
Fine, I'm goin'.
Where in the world are you taking us?
We're almost there.
I'm humbled that you asked me to join.
Thank you all for caring so much about Aguri.
Even when I made braised burdock and carrots,
she'd be sure to leave the carrots untouched!
It's been quite the problem!
Yeah, uh, no kidding.
Grandmother!
We're here!
Where are we?
A plantation.
There ya are!
The name's Kadono Aki!
Carrots are the love of my life!
Carrots are?!
Nice to meet you!
And you're the little girl who don't like her carrots?
... Yes.
How's about I show y'all the practice corner?
Practice what?
How to raise carrots!
Why must I aid my mortal enemy?
No, not like that!
These carrots are eaten 'round the world, so put'cher back into it!
Around the world? What could you mean?
Mana?
Perfect, keep it up!
Show me all the passion y'all can muster!
You too, girls!
Very well.
Henceforth, I shall spare no effort!
Perfect! Plow with passion!
Next comes the fertilizer!
Fertilizer?
Don't tell me...
It's compost made from manure!
Manure?!
No scoops!
Grasp it with your bare hands...
and spread your warmth to the carrots!
C'mon!
She did it!
That's the spirit!
Spread your feelings with that fertilizer!
I'm sure Josephina and Marianna are plum happy to feel your love!
Jose... who?
She's Josephina.
And she's Marianna.
You name the carrots?!
Buggy buggy!
The bug is eating it!
The vegetables are so yummy that even bugs want to eat them.
Yummy!
So, how'd you like working the fields?
It's as exhausting as I imagined.
All that work just makes the carrots tastier!
Want one?
I'll have one!
Yummy!
I know!
I want to make nutritious food delicious.
That's what drives me to be a farmer.
It's not just farmers who want to.
We chefs feel the same way.
Mari here does too, right?
Grandmother, too?
Here, Ai.
Still no dice, huh?
Huh?
She hates carrots too?
Well, there's an idea.
I hate veggies!
I wanna eat cake!
You won't grow up big and strong if you don't eat your veggies.
Still don't want them?
Well, I wanna grow up big...
Aw, just skip the veggies.
I will grant your desire.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
I friggin' hate veggies!
What's that?
A house made of candy?
It's a Selfish!
But that form...
with its cookie walls and macaroon roof...
are all arranged meticulously to delight the eyes as well as the tongue!
One forgets it's a Selfish!
I can only say bravo to its artisan!
Wipe the drool, girl.
Seeelf!
Ecatarina! Rachel!
Mr. Kakudo!
Grandpa, take Mari somewhere safe!
What about you?
Trust your granddaughter!
Seeeelf!
Stoooooop!
You're gonna have to go through me!
Self?
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Don't space out, get him!
Selfish!
Oh poor dessert who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Self, Self...
Are you all right?
He fainted while standing?
He's got guts to try taking on a Selfish!
I understand your feelings.
Now leave the rest to us!
Get 'em, Selfish!
Sweeeeeet!
Ai!
Seeeelf...
Eat meeee...
Carrot... no-no!
Ai is crying!
Ai!
Selfy selfy selfy!
It powered up!
Sword Hurricane!
Ai! Ace!
Are you okay in there?
Yes, but...
Good! Cry some more!
Selfy selfy selfy!
Heart!
Aw yeah, I can win!
Girls!
So you don't like us, huh?
If you can eat us, just try iiiit.
I want to make nutritious food delicious.
We chefs feel the same way.
Mari here does too, right?
You hate us, right?
It's true, I did hate you...
but I was wrong to do so!
Ai, watch me.
Oh, what now?
You can't eat it.
I learned...
that carrots have people who raise and cook them.
They have a limitless amount of love packed into them!
Yes!
Carrots are crystals of love!
They are not a foe to be feared, but a friend to be loved!
This is... the energy of love!
I feel one hundred times as energetic!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Self?
Ai!
Ace!
Aw, come on!
What the heck?!
Sorry for worrying you.
Girls, let us go!
Yeah!
Magical Lovely Pad!
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Precure Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love looooove!
And I was so close, too!
Thank goodness!
Eat up.
Yummy!
Why did I spend so long trying to avoid something so delicious?
Ai too!
Here, Ai.
It's carrot soup!
Yummie!
Ai!
Great!
Gweat!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Ai's been pretty cranky lately...
She gets into a bad mood pretty easily.
Oh no!
Bel's gang lured Ai out in the middle of the night!
I suppose it's because we tried to make her sleep during the day.
Who in the world takes a baby for a night on the town?
Is it Bel's fault Ai has been so selfish?
Dokidoki Precure:
Bel's Scheme!
Turn Ai into a Selfish?!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!