Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Well, let's get going.
Let's go!
Stop messing around and start!
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Yutaka!
It's almost time to go!
Oof.
Okay, little sister of mine.
Today's the beginning of your new life!
Let's go with a bang!
Under
One
Roof
I'm here to report that Yutaka's passed and say hi!
Welcome.
Come on, Yutaka.
I-I'll probably be causing lots of trouble...
...but I hope we can get along well!
Just think of this as your own home.
Yes.
Let me start by congratulating you on passing.
Thank you!
It's a good thing she passed.
Now you can meet that handkerchief girl.
I win at life.
Going back in time
The day of Yutaka's Exams
Um...
Are you all right?
Do you want me to take you to the nurse's office?
Right after the exams
So she talked to me...
...and even lent me her handkerchief!
I'm so happy that I might be able to make a good friend.
But Yutaka...
She might've failed.
That won't happen!
People like her definitely pass!
I know how you feel...
She's definitely smart!
Thank you for the baseless rebuttal.
But you know...
...Yu-chan.
What if you fail?
That's actually possible...
Well, you should be fine.
That's right.
I should be able to meet her on the
day they announce results regardless.
I see.
I have to return the handkerchief.
You will be notified of your results by mail.
And then
the day of orientation and uniform fitting
E-Excuse me!
Here.
I'm glad I ran into you.
I've been wanting to return this.
You came to deliver this?
Yes.
I guess I ended up troubling you.
I didn't expect to ever see you again.
I never intended to have this returned.
I was worried I might fail.
Oh.
I see.
If you're here now...
...you're in the same year.
I'm sorry.
You probably thought I was someone's little sister.
I came by car today.
O-Okay.
Then we'll be parting here.
Um...
I hope we can have a great three years!
What a relief.
I already became friends with such a nice person in high school.
I didn't ask what her name was.
Turning back the clock
Make sure you ask for her name next time.
Present
Are you feeling sick, Yu-chan?
I think I got a little carsick.
I took some medicine, though...
Sorry to worry you.
Yutaka's got such a weak body.
Wait.
That's part of it...
I'll rub your back—
...but you need to realize what your driving's like, Cousin Yui.
Thanks~
Even I get a little blargh...
But I'm the only one from my old school who's going to Ryouou...
And I'll probably get sick again like today...
I'm worried about if I can get along with my classmates.
You're a good girl, so it'll be fine.
You're treating me like a child!
Sickly
Little Sister
Brain...
Pure
Cute
...converting...
Walking Pillar of Moe
If Yu-chan got together with our Miyuki-san, it'd be pretty crazy.
That's right.
I'm in Big Sister Konata's house now.
Big Sister.
Good morning!
You're up awfully early when we don't have school.
Morning.
Actually, I'm about to hit the sack.
I was gaming all nigh—
This really is a different environment!
We have to take exams next year, huh?
We've been getting a bunch of phone calls from cram schools.
It's a pain.
If you use caller ID...
...you should be able to pick out those kinds of calls immediately.
Since they use unlisted numbers.
I'm home!
Caller ID, huh...
I've come home!
My...
Is that so?
That must have been difficult.
Not at all...
It's the same for our family.
Well, my daughter's returned...
Yes.
Until we talk again, then.
Sorry to have taken up your time.
Who was on the phone?
It sounded like you were having a lively conversation.
It was a telemarketer.
Um...
Didn't you say that you could pick out those calls immediately?
But you know...
I was bored and felt like having a conversation.
We talked for over an hour.
This should be your total.
Whyistherealreadyanewitem?!
What's wrong, Kona-chan?
Tsukasa!
This world is always a battlefield!
You can never show mercy!
The other day, there was a little item I wanted...
Should I exchange my points.
I spent half a day thinking about it...
...Nah...but
there's other stuff I want.
Okay!
...and ended up deciding to exchange my points...
I'll go on the offensive!
But now there's already a new item I really want!
Look! Over there!
I don't have enough points left!
What to do?!
You sure enjoy your life.
Uh...
You haven't paid...
Would you prefer smoking or non-smoking?
Well...
We're minors...
...so a non-smoking table, please.
Then please follow me.
I'm going to the restroom first.
Hey, Tsukasa!
Over here!
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Hey...
I've been wondering...
Why are the restrooms in these places...
...usually located near the smoking section?
That's true.
Especially when we're in the non-smoking section.
But really...
I wonder why...
So there's a nearby water source if a fire starts.
They have buckets and hoses, too.
They even have hoses?
They do!
They sure do!
Typical of a person who's never worked out in the real world.
What a pain.
Good grief.
You're annoying!
Or maybe to cover up the stink.
And like...
Don't talk about this stuff while we're eating.
Stuff like the stink or restrooms...
Currently, in the city...
...a number of elementary school girls...
...have been approached from
behind while on their way to school...
There are a lot more cases of kids being targeted.
You should be careful, Yu-chan.
That's right.
You have to!
Well, I can understand the perpetrator's way of thinking...
Really...
He's been all over the news for consecutive days now...
...yet he's still going up to little kids?!
What does he want?!
I really want to tell him something!
Man, I'm jealous.
I have no idea what you're thinking...
...but don't do anything that'll get you arrested by Cousin Yui.
Excuse me!
Coming!
Hey!
I'm here!
Welcome!
Oh, where's Kagami today?
She went out with some friends from her class.
I see.
I'm kinda annoyed and then it feels like something's missing...
I guess you're lonely.
It's gotten really warm lately.
Sure has.
We don't have any homework for spring break...
...so it's really tranquil.
Sure is.
Pretty sure that...
...only people who normally work hard have the right to say that.
Don't hit any place weird!
No more!
Say...
Do you even recognize the characters in these robot games?
Some of them.
I see...
Since your manga and anime preferences...
...were influenced by your dad.
Yep.
In that case...
Didn't you have a hard time understanding what your female friends were talking about when you were little?
Why?
I actually saw more of that kind of
stuff, so there wasn't any problem.
Really...
Huh?
Is that your final answer?
Final answer!
Why can't they just tell us?
I couldn't even breathe.
And his face is scary.
And huge.
Looking at the clock, she must have gotten the question wrong.
The show's already over.
Wait, Tsukasa!
Can you stop guessing if they got the question right based on the amount of time left when they cut to commercial?!
But I can't take the waiting...
And they really drag it out...
Isn't that the point of the show?!
But it's what Tsukasa would do.
Yo.
Yahoo!
Let me introduce you.
This is my cousin, Yu-chan.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Yutaka Kobayakawa.
These are my friends Tsukasa and Kagami.
Then you're the ones Big Sister's always talking about...
What does she say about us?
Hey.
What did you tell her?
Though I can guess from her reaction...
See?
Just like I told you.
Did you already have your graduation ceremony, Yutaka-chan?
Yes.
A few days ago.
Graduation, huh?
Brings back memories.
I don't even remember our graduation.
Did you get a second button from anyone, Yutaka-chan?
No, I didn't.
Our middle school uniform was a blazer.
Oh, yeah...
I guess a lot more schools are like that now.
Actually...
...does the practice of getting
something from the person you like still exist?
Really?
That's kinda sad.
Not that I ever did it.
If you read blogs...
...it looks like quite a few people are still doing it.
But you know...
You take it from someone you like, right?
Well, in most cases.
Then...
...wouldn't going to get a button be
the same as confessing how you feel?
Wouldn't it be better to just confess
and get the guy instead of a button?
Ideally, sure.
That's right.
Did you like anyone at your old school?
No.
I was often absent from school...
When I did go, I would soon get sick.
I just made everyone feel bad.
And I'm all small...
...and I look like a child...
...so everyone always teased me.
I never had time to like anybody...
Don't worry!
You'll have no problems if you aren't picky!
Wh-What?!
Pocky!
Yu-chan.
Show me your graduation yearbook.
I wanna see it!
This is kinda embarrassing.
I don't show up very often.
Yu-chan, what class were you in?
You checked the absentee section first, didn't you?!
You could tell?
The differences between middle school and high school?
The fact that joining a club is no longer mandatory.
Doesn't that depend on the school?
Our school's geared towards getting into college...
...so there will probably be more material at a faster pace.
And the commute takes a while...
...so you'll need some stamina.
The decisive difference is that...
...class time naps have grown longer from
grade school to middle school to high school.
Especially during classes you're bad at!
That's actually true!
The teacher sounds like he's talking in a foreign language...
Make sure you don't end up like them.
...and my mind just starts slipping away!
You brought your middle school uniform.
Our uniform is pretty plain...
...so I thought I could wear it normally.
Since I'm no longer close to school.
I see.
What did you guys do with your uniforms?
We gave ours to some younger neighbors.
What about you?
Mine?
Well...
You wouldn't be able to give yours to anyone.
Be quiet.
How rude.
I saved mine for cosplay use like Yu-chan.
C-Cos..?
When you put it that way...
...it really gets on my nerves.
But it's cosplay.
Anyway...
Our old school, huh?
Now that you've brought it up...
...I kind of want to go visit my grade school and middle school.
But there have been a bunch of incidents involving trespassing...
...so people might give you funny looks.
Well, you don't have to worry.
You'll fit in just fine.
Pretty sure that wasn't a compliment.
But vacations sure pass by quickly.
That's true.
Before you know it, it's back to school.
Spring is a pain with physical exams and measurements.
But you've got really athletic nerves. Lucky you.
Hey, Tsukasa.
Which nerves are the athletic nerves?
Hello, everyone!
I'm a little late...
...but congratulations on graduating, Yutaka!
Cousin Yui.
Welcome.
To celebrate...
...let's all go get smashed!
Invite your dad, too.
My treat!
Sis!
We can't do that!
Officer, we're still minors.
W-We can't!
She means juice~
Sis.
I don't think we can go in those places yet.
If you just stroll on in...
...they'll never catch you!
I did it all the time when I was a student!
They never caught me once!
No.
We can't!
Your two relatives will get us caught.
So you did~
We can't, Sis!
I see...
Don't mind.
Since Yu-chan's here...
...we could go to Disneyland or something.
Since it's spring break.
Um...
I really appreciate it...
...but I'm already imposing...
...so you don't have to go so far.
And I already went there on a school field trip a while back.
Yeah, I had a field trip like that, too.
But were you okay?
I didn't get sick.
It was fun!
And I was with my friends.
No...
I was talking about the minimum height for rides.
It was okay!
I'm in high school now!
So I was watching this school drama...
...when I realized there are a lot of
differences between middle school and high school.
Guess so.
They stop feeding you in high school.
That's right.
You make your own lunch or eat in the cafeteria.
Or buy a lunch to bring.
Do you make a box lunch every day?!
P-Pretty much.
That's amazing!
This could get ugly...
You're really good at games!
Skilled at many forms of communication!
You can even cook and do other housework!
I've recently learned how much pressure an older sister feels.
You have to work hard with those eyes on you, right...
...Kagami?
Cousin Yui, wild at the wheel.
Hey!
Doing good?
Cousin Yui, comes home drunk.
Homework?
Just put down something random.
Cousin Yui, never serious about anything.
But I guess it depends on the person.
Make it so I can understand you.
Final answer!
Man, I seriously can't take this.
I finally get to record a line for the actual show...
...but I wasn't even on screen!
Doing it again today.
What are they thinking when they make this show?
Again.
Why am I stuck with this lame crap anybody could come up with...
Akira-sama!
The title call.
Title call!
U-U-Uh...
The title call...
Tiny eyes!
Good lucky...
This isn't the time for that.
Unbelievable. Incredible.
Only my voice. My voice.
My appearance was pointless.
U-Uh...
I wasn't on screen either.
Nobody gives a damn about you!
Windy, huh?
Hey...
Did I ask about you?
Hey.
Did I ever mention you?
N-No...
You didn't say a word about me.
So why did you bring yourself up?
Don't be so self-centered.
Are you an idiot?
You're always like me, me, me.
That's called being overly self-conscious.
Make yourself scarce, Shiraishi.
Sheesh, I'm gonna end up with a dirty mouth.
Listen up.
The issue here is the fact that Akira
Kogami wasn't shown in the actual show.
Sure is.
Let me ask you. What am I?
An idol, right?
An idol depends on her looks, right?
Isn't it a given that I should be on screen?
What do you think?
Y-Yes!
You're absolutely right, sah!
I can't hear you.
T-The staff for this episode...
...acted in a logic-defying manner, sah!
What are you writing?
Revenge of Akira Kogami
Project Full Appearance in Actual Show!!!
Okay?
Here's a request from Akira!
Akira needs everybody's support to appear in the actual show.
The world is waiting for Akira!
Please show your support on the home page
and other places
So send in loads of encouragement!
Loads...
Any method works!
Just give them a push!
Say that you're dying to see me appear in the actual show!
Dying...
Just between you and me.
The other members of the cast...
...can't hold a candle...
...to a performance that features Akira's amazing talent and charm!
She's desperate...
She's really desperate today...
You can't wait to see such a pretty and gorgeous performance!
This is your chance!
Don't let it slip away!
Your feedback...
...can make this a reality!
What is it?
So the second this show ends, start getting to work...
Stop her?
Understood.
Um, Akira-sama...
Shut up!
Stop butting in!
I was on a roll!
How many times do I have to tell you not to get in my way?!
What? Already?
I wanted to tell you more about how wonderful Akira is.
You can see a lot more of my true
charm during next week's actual show.
Just kidding.
Uh...
Look forward to next time!
Bye-bee!
It's over.
I'm in pain.
Hey, you.
Go get the producer!
Me?!
First of all...
Yes.
This week's modified manuscript was wrong.
What's the name of this program?!
Uh, Lucky Channel?
It said Lucky Paradise.
Well...
Also...
What is it?
You've got guts to treat me like this!
Just because your last show was a hit!
Hey, producers!
Wait, you really shouldn't be saying that!
Don't mess with me!
Hey!
Miyagi-san!
Hello, I'm Shiraishi!
Okay! Please listen to me!
I've lived my life wishing for excitement.
Who made my dream come true?
Some futures you can guess. Some you can't.
But there's still one thing I know for sure.
Even to the end of time!
Boooon!!
These looping feelings...
...warp everyone in to play with imagination!
One clear, sunshiny day...
...happiness greater than magic...
...pours down with no end in sight.
It could happen!
When we meet again tomorrow...
...we'll be smiling and humming!
Let's bring together happiness!
It's an easy thing to do!
Keep on chasing!
Try to catch it!
We love big dreams, right?
The End
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Minami Iwasaki.
I'm Yutaka Kobayakawa.
Iwasaki-san.
The two of us are supposed to introduce the next episode.
Do you know what it's about?
I don't.
Sorry.
Really?
That's not good.
I don't know either.
Then we'll stop here.
Next time:
「Can't Change So Quickly」
Can't Change So Quickly.
Is it okay that we didn't say anything?
Look forward to next time.