Wow, we're finally free.
My neck's all stiff from sleeping on that hard floor.
Oh, that's good, mate.
I thought this school was supposed to become our paradise if we tarnished Tenshi's name.
Why aren't you wearing anything?
What's wrong with that guy...?
Next time they come, we'll have our retribution against them, as well as Tenshi.
They're NPCs, so you can't.
Still, this is strange.
What is?
There were no NPCs before that would force us to reflect on our actions.
Maybe Tenshi was acting as a deterrent.
That's possible.
The NPCs are basically there to be an example for what we should be doing,
but their emotions are the same as actual humans'.
It's not any real surprise to find a cranky one amongst them.
So there are NPCs that go above and beyond, too.
Such as that deputy Student Council President...
He's more of a pain than Tenshi since we can't fight back.
What do we do, Yurippe?
How about sex appeal?
And where exactly are you hiding that?
What did you say?!  Have you ever seen me nude?
I can imagine too much already with your clothes on.
You ever touched them?!
They have just the perfect softness, got it?!
How should I know?!
How unwise.
So, what will our activities from here on be?
I see you finally put your shirt on.
We'll take a few actions as tests.
Attend class and make trouble as you'd like for now.
Oh, but don't bother the NPCs too much.
That's all.  Dismissed.
Otonashi-kun.
You hold on to this.
I thought that was valuable here.
Why are you giving it to me?
Just take it.
Tenshi won't be acting against us anymore.
We were able to prove that last night.
The remaining problem is the deputy president.
What sort of obstacles will he be coming up with?
This is so exciting.
Eating a snack in the middle of class!
I ate it!  I just ate one!
I'm eating a snack in the middle of class!
I'm so bold!
[ Note: Reach (riichi), pairs, and dora dora are all mahjong terms. ]
Reach if this goes through.
Sorry.  Reach, Pairs.
Ouch. Are you serious?
Dora dora.  Dealer Mangan.
What the heck?!  Hisako's the only one above 30,000 points...
Ah... just wild heaven.
How could we lose to a girl...?
You guys, keep it down a little more.
Oh, our bad.
Teacher!  Bathroom, please!
You again...  Go ahead.
What is she doing?
Playing the role of a student that goes to the bathroom every other minute.  What a dumbass.
What are we going to do?
We'll just chat some, like this.
Hey, check that out.
Teacher!  Bathroom, please!
Go ahead.
A dumbass.
That's enough, you lot.
Here comes Naoi Ayato-sama.
I need to use the bathroom!
Crap!  Beat it, guys!
I'll be back.
What do you think you're doing?
Seems he can't hear me.
Fine by me.  Take him to the Introspection Room just like this.
What are you telling me to reflect on?!
How can you ask such a question while sleeping in the middle of the class and intimidating an innocent student?
Your ignorance is praiseworthy.
What was that?!
Hey, hang on!  Why should we run away?!
I'm right here!  Bring it on!
Hey, where are you taking me?
Is there any point in doing this?
Let's see...
Hey, are you hungry at all?
I'm not.  Not at this kind of hour.
I see.
At the cafeteria, there's some mapo doufu famous for being so hot that no one can eat it.
I gave it a try only to find out it was surprisingly good.
Well, so...  If you're interested, I'll treat you.
What... do you say?
Why are you still sitting?
O-Oh, yeah.  Coming!
The appearance really is deadly...
I knew it was hot!
I heard most people eat this with rice.
I see.
You don't find this too hot?
It's fine.  Only...
"Only..."?
It's delicious.
I get it.  It isn't so much that you like the spicy flavor, it's that mapo doufu's your favorite meal.
What's wrong?
So I like mapo doufu?
I mean, don't ask me.
That's the first time I've thought of it that way.
Tachibana-san.
What are you doing at this hour?
Can't you tell?  We're eating.
Eating food during break time is against the school code.
I'd forgotten.
You're right.  It is against the school code.
I had forgotten that.
I can tell that she honestly had forgotten about it.
Her favorite food of mapo doufu really is scary...
Take them away.
Damn it!
You shouldn't lock us up just for eating mapo doufu during break time!
Besides, where are we?
This is like a prison.
I'm sleepy.  I'm taking a nap.
H-Hey...  This isn't the time for that!
Is there anything else to do?
Don't you think it's odd that we were shut in such a prison-like place?
It counts as reflecting upon our actions, so it's fine.
Even then!  Who would take a nap in this situation?
Good night.
She's seriously sleeping...
What was that noise?  An earthquake?
Is there a battle?  A rescue operation?
Oh yeah!
I had this on me!
Yuri!  We've been locked up!
It's broken.
Giving me a piece of junk like that!
—nashi-kun?
Otonashi-kun?
Do you copy?  Otonashi-kun?
I copy you!
I'll continue speaking assuming that you can hear me.
Otonashi-kun, listen carefully.
Naoi Ayato wasn't an NPC.
He's a human just like us with a soul.
No way.
Don't you find that strange?
He's been acting as the vice president, so he's been behaving like a role model student.
As a result, he should have been obliterated without being able to maintain his existence here.
But in reality he was being insidious, committing violence against NPCs in the background.
He acted as a role model before others, but then inflicted violence where he couldn't be seen.
That's how he maintained the balance to stay in this world.
What good does that do?
With the deterrent, Tenshi, losing her position, he gained freedom here.
We still don't know what he wants.
On this side, a battle has erupted.
A horrifying scene like you've never witnessed before.
He knows that we can't hurt the NPCs.
That's why he's using them as shields or even taking them hostage.
We have no choice but to obey him.
It's a one-sided massacre.
Our guys are getting killed off one after another.
I think Tenshi's locked up somewhere.
I searched for her at the Introspection Room we were taken to, but I couldn't find her.
I believe she's being kept someplace that's harder to find.
Look, Otonashi-kun, I have this hunch.
Aren't you with Tenshi right now?
Look, Otonashi-kun... bring Tenshi to us.
To end this horrifying battle, we need Tenshi.
We're out of time.  Get out here on the field.
I'm going out now, too.  And well, Godspeed to you.
Damn it!  Why am I stuck in a place like this?
Wake up, Tachibana!
Help!  My friends are in trouble!
What a strange thing to ask.
We're the ones who need help.
Yeah, I know that.
But you might be able to get us out of here!
I'm begging you!
Everyone's waiting!
Guard Skill: Hand Sonic.
Can you take the door down with that?
Doesn't look like it...
I didn't create this with the intention of attacking something.
It's only for self-defense.
"Self-defense"?
"Didn't create this for"...
I get it!
Remember the first time we met?
You stabbed me through the heart and I nearly died.
Only because you asked such a strange thing.
Yeah.  But due to that, I mistook you to be an enemy.
I don't have any memories.
So I actually have no reason to fight against you.
If I'd had my memories...
If I hadn't asked that stupid question in the beginning, I might have been on your side.
There's no one like that.
Well, there can be one, right?
There isn't one.  Even if there were, they'd be obliterated.
I see.  Being on her side means to have an enjoyable school life and eventually to leave her.
I get it now.  This is laughable.
How horrible... I feel so sorry for her.
What a crazy system this world has.
Hand Sonic: Version 2.
This is designed thinner to improve speed.
Version 3.
This one is crude.
That's cool, though.
But this won't open the door, either.
You don't have anything else?
I do.  Version 4.
I made it look like a flower.
Do you find it cute, I wonder?
Actually, it looks deadly, but...
This might work.
There's something I want you to try.
Hand Sonic: Version 2.
Version 3.
Version 4.
It's working!
Let's hurry.
What is this about?
Hinata!
Are you all right, Hinata?!
To come running to me first...
You swing like that?
This isn't the time to joke around!
How did you get out of there?
I broke the door.
How many years do you think it took me to make that place?
I order you as the deputy Student Council President.
Return to the room at once.
Tachibana.  You see what's going on here.
You know this isn't the right thing to do, don't you?
Hand Sonic.
You dare to rebel?  Against God?
I am God.
Is he completely daft?
Yeah, after doing all of this...
How foolish.
No one has yet to realize that this world exists to choose who is God?
It's required that your past memories be horrible to come here.
Why?
Because that's the ticket to becoming God.
We, who have known true pain in life, are the only ones who have the right to become God.
I've reached the finish line.
What are you going to do, having become God?
Give peace.
To us?!
Don't be freaking ridiculous!
It's because they resisted.
While you all have souls that have earned the right to become God,
you also suffer the pain of the memories from when you were alive.
God has been chosen.
So I will give you all peace.
Yuri!
What more are you going to do?!
What...  do you want?
You'll be resting in peace in a bit.
Do you remember Iwasawa Asami?
When she was alive, she lost her voice and gave up on her dream to sing.
Due to her poor family, the end of her life was a sad one.
But here in this world, she made her dream a reality.
That's why she was obliterated.
She was able to rest in peace.
You will be resting in peace soon, too, together with a happy memory.
You don't know my past!
It's possible even if I don't know it.
I didn't just prepare Tenshi's prison over such a long period of time.
I also practiced hypnosis.
Now, close your eyes.
You will now have a happy dream.
You can have a happy dream even in a world like this.
This can't be...  This just can't...  It can't be...
There's no way...!
It's them...
No.  This isn't real.
Don't show me those happy faces...
I couldn't protect you all.
I let you three die, one by one.
One by one...
And none of you survived!
Yet...
You know, I'm glad you were our sister.
Don't...
Don't say that!
Stop it!
Don't obliterate her with a fake memory!
The lives we spent were real!
They were all the real deal!  Everyone lived the best they could!
That's how our memories were made!
They're memories from our lives.
No matter what they are, it's the life we walked!
And you want to be the one to finish painting the conclusion?
Your life should have been the real deal, too!
My brother died.
My twin brother and I were born as children of a prestigious potter.
My brother showed talent from when he was little, and they sold his name to the world as the heir.
I, on the other hand, would be locked up in a room to play.
It was a meaningless life, where no hope was ever placed on me, not even by my parents.
The sky was telling me, "You're the one who died."
That's right... the one who lived is my brother.
And so I swapped places with my brother.
The world would treat me as the one who'd actually died.  And so my life of purpose began.
As rehabilitation from the injury, I was secluded from society.
The strict training they called "rehabilitation" lasted forever.
Shame on you!
All I ever heard was my father's yelling, every day.
How dare you make something like this?!
The training was insane.
My brother had stood on a pedestal so much higher up than me.
But I continued to fight in order to change my life into a meaningful one.
I wouldn't return to the old days, forced to play alone.
I won a prize in a show.
I didn't do nearly as well as my brother could have, but it was the best I could do at my level.
What?  Are you crying?
Don't be ridiculous.
You said it.  This is ridiculous.
Don't shame me like this.
Honestly.  This kind of result is unacceptable.
That was wonderful.  I would follow my strict father and continue training.
And I would become Japan's best potter!
Then, my father became bedridden.
The doctor said there was no chance of him getting better.  He couldn't spin the wheel anymore.
He also couldn't teach the art to me any longer, and he wouldn't yell at me, either.
When I fed him, he would kindly smile.
What is my purpose in life?
With my skills, I can't have my own studio, nor can I sustain myself.
Will I take care of him for the rest of my life?
Answer me, God!
I realized the one who'd died that day was really me.
The one who'd worked hard from then on was my brother.  It was my brother who was in this room, too.
It was him and Father.
My life was all just a fake.
I was never anywhere.
Your life should have been the real deal, too!
You're the one who worked hard!
You're the one who fought!  Isn't that right?!
Who do you think you are?
I can tell.
Since you're right here.
Then, will you accept it?
That I'm me?
Who else other than you could I possibly be accepting right now?
The one inside my arms is you.  There's no one besides you.
It's only you.
Even if you get it, it's a sour persimmon.
I got it!  I got it over Nii-san!
What are you getting worked up over a sour persimmon for?
Still, you're not half-bad, Ayato.
Those are the words I wanted to hear most.
The words of acceptance.
It'll be a monster scream.
It's finally here!
Just how big is it?
It's a carnival of despair.
Wanna do Tornado?
God never falls.
Pull!
In other words, a dumbass.
Overdrive is passive.
I don't want you to underestimate my skills.
You should be able to regain the memory you lost.
Please don't lose sight of yourself.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
This just isn't right...  I can't die off like this...