A charm spell...
Sorry. It's been a curse since birth.
There's nothing I can do about it.
You can blame my origin, or the fact that you were born a woman.
You can't believe that a pretty face will save you from my blade, can you?
How absurd.
I certainly hope not. It would spoil the fun.
I see.
Then the tales of the Saber class's anti-magic abilities were accurate.
Very well.
I'd prefer not to kill a girl who's throwing herself at me, anyway.
It would damage my reputation.
I'm pleased that my first opponent has such strength.
Oh? So you desire a fair fight?
I consider myself fortunate to encounter such a proud spirit.
Well then... let us begin.
It's begun.
Someone's put up a barrier.
Probably the Master of the enemy Servant.
From up there, we can survey the entire battlefield.
Indeed. That is certainly the best vantage point.
Anyone seeing it would think so.
You approach from the eastern wharf.
I'll take the west.
We'll find a point from which we can monitor both the battle and the crane.
Understood.
Let's see what you can do,
my lovely King of Knights.
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
Saber is watching both spears at once.
Lancer's greatest advantage is his opponent's uncertainty as to which he will use.
Long spear in the right hand, short spear in the left.
I wonder which is the Noble Phantasm.
If I were sure, I could attack.
If only we at least knew his true name...
Whoever he is, he's a master of the spear.
However, that will not suffice.
What's wrong, Saber? You're on the defensive!
He's impressive!
Curse that blade of hers.
Without knowing its precise length, I cannot get close enough to strike.
To be able to repel my strikes in such a way,
she must be a master swordsman.
Maiya.
Northeast of Saber and Iri.
On the roof of that warehouse.
That’s Lancer's Master.
Can you see him?
Negative. Not from my position.
Understood. I'll take him out from here.
Assassin?
Something is happening among the warehouses at the mouth of the Miongawa River.
The first battle has finally begun.
Not the first.
To the rest of them, this would be the second battle,
Kirei.
It would appear that Saber and Lancer are the combatants.
Can you ascertain their status with Assassin's eyes?
With ease.
Saber's abilities are especially high.
Most parameters are at rank A or higher.
I see.
I suppose she is considered the strongest class.
Saber likely presents a larger threat than Lancer.
Can you see either Master?
There's only one person other than the Servants who is unconcealed.
Standing next to Saber...
is a woman with silver hair.
Then Lancer's master is wise enough to remain hidden.
That's no novice.
This person understands the rules of the Holy Grail War.
Wait. A silver-haired woman?
Yes. Caucasian.
With silver hair and red eyes.
That doesn't sound human.
An Einzbern homunculus?
Did they create an artificial Master?
I'd thought the only thing Jubstacheit had for us was Emiya Kiritsugu.
Looks like I was wrong.
Then, that woman is the Einzbern Master?
Either way, she'll be a critical factor in the rest of the Grail War.
Kirei, keep your eye on her.
Understood.
I shall keep an Assassin tasked to her at all times.
I can see them.
But Assassin should be dead, so why is he here?
I knew something was strange.
Let's see how this plays out.
Continue to observe Assassin.
I'll watch Lancer.
Let me attack Assassin and draw his attention
while you take on Lancer's Master.
No, Maiya.
Not against Assassin.
We're not equipped to fight Servants right now.
Understood.
There is no honor in a battle fought without an exchange of names.
But allow me to offer my regards.
It is quite impressive for a woman to fight so hard, without even breaking a sweat.
You need not be so humble, Lancer.
Even without my knowing your name, those words from such a master of the spear
do me honor.
I gratefully accept them.
That's enough fun for now, Lancer.
Lancer's Master?
Do not allow this battle to continue.
That Saber is a formidable opponent.
Eliminate her now.
You may use your Noble Phantasm.
Yes, my Master.
So the long spear is his Noble Phantasm?
That's right.
I'll go for the kill now.
Saber, will you still use the prana of the wind
to hide your blade?
I see.
You have a reason to conceal your sword.
My guess is that the sword reveals your true name.
How unfortunate, Lancer.
You will never know the name of my blade.
I'll finish this before you have the chance.
We'll see about that.
I will discover what you hide, Saber.
You've exposed your sword.
The Invisible Air is disintegrating?
What's going on?
That red spear is canceling out the Invisible Air!
I've measured its range.
Now I needn't worry about being struck!
But I still have ways to counter it.
If I simply wait for an attack...
One that's less powerful than the rest...
Saber?
My thanks, Irisviel.
I'm fine. The healing is working.
As I thought, this won't be an easy victory.
But why?
My armor should have easily deflected that strike.
So how did that blade...
The armor itself isn't penetrated?
How can this be?
I can only speculate
that Lancer's blade bypassed the magically woven armor.
So that's it. I see the secret of your spear, Lancer.
Oh?
That red spear cancels magic.
Your armor was created using magic.
If you were relying on it, then you should surrender now, Saber.
You're as good as naked before my spear.
Don't imagine that you'll win simply by defeating my armor.
If I cannot block your blade, I need only to kill you before it strikes.
Prepare yourself, Lancer!
A bold move.
You're betting everything on one strike.
You attempted to balance out the disadvantage of your broken armor
with the advantages gained by abandoning it.
A courageous decision.
I like it.
But in this case,
it is a foolish mistake, Saber.
We shall see.
Tell me your opinion after my next attack.
That was a misstep.
A Noble Phantasm needn't merely be a single weapon.
A trap?
This is bad. Extremely bad.
Wh-What is?
Lancer has begun his ultimate attack.
He'll end the battle here.
Isn't that better for us?
Idiot! What are you talking about?
I wanted to sit back and watch until we saw a few more Masters...
But at this rate, Saber may fall.
Then it will be too late.
T-Too late?
The plan was to attack once they'd knocked each other out!
Indeed, I'd hoped another Servant would answer Lancer's challenge.
Of course...
It would be faster to fight them together than to find them one by one.
Together?
Yes.
Rarely does one have the chance to exchange blows with heroes from another time.
And with the chance to fight as many as six,
I'd hate to miss out on a single one.
Observe Saber and Lancer!
Both are valiant warriors whom I would dearly love to duel.
I cannot let either die.
But isn't that the point?
The Holy Grail War's objective is to kill one another!
To win, but not destroy...
To master, but not humiliate...
That is true conquest!
We watch no longer!
We shall also participate, boy!
You idiot!
What you're doing is insane!
If you don't approve, will you stay here and observe?
I'll go...
Take me, damn it!
Excellent! That's my Master!
Not good. He's severed the tendon.
I can't move my thumb.
I guess you really won't make this easy...
Still, I really do like that!
Get to work, you fool.
You still haven't finished her.
I apologize, my Master.
Irisviel...
I require healing.
I have...
I have, but...
The healing worked. I'm certain.
Saber, you should already be fully healed!
You were sharp, realizing that my Gae Dearg could penetrate any armor.
But it was foolish to abandon your armor.
Had you not done so, you would have blocked my Gae Buidhe.
I understand now.
A cursed blade, whose wounds will never heal...
I should have noticed sooner.
A red spear that destroys magic, a cursed yellow spear,
and beneath the right eye, a mole that enchants women.
First of the knights of Fianna,
Diarmuid of the Love Spot.
Never did I think I'd have the honor of facing you.
Such is the wonder of the Holy Grail War.
But it is I who has the honor here.
No hero summoned by the Holy Grail
could ever mistake that golden blade.
To face the legendary King of Knights
and land even a single blow...
I must be quite skilled.
Now then, since we both know the other's name,
we can duel honorably, as knights.
Or will this dissatisfy you, occurring only after you've lost use of an arm?
Nonsense.
It's humiliating that you would concern yourself over such a scratch.
Prepare yourself, Saber.
Next time, you're mine.
Only if I fail to strike first, Lancer.
A chariot?
Both of you, sheath your blades.
You are in the presence of the king!
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
In this Holy Grail War, I am of the Rider class.
Episode 4
The Demon Spear
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
I can't read his status or anything else!
Irisviel, get back!
That is his Noble Phantasm.
With my Command Seal, I order you...
Believe in your Master!
At last, I have been revived!
Nothing will remain of your corpse!
Next Time
Scream of a Mad Beast