Hurry! Call 110!
Sis?
Ushio!
Tokiko, go to the school and bring back an AED!
There should be one on the pillar by the entrance!
Sou?
Okay!
Run!
What's everyone doing?
Ushio! Open yer eyes!
Sis...
Please, come back!
Ushio!
Huh?
Wha—
I'm so sorry!
I-I didn't mean to—
I-I'm so very sorry!
Are you okay?
You were moaning quite a bit.
Did you have a bad dream?
D-Dream?
Oh, she's...
Um... have you ever been shot by a handgun?
Excuse me?
Are you really okay?
Oh, uh... never mind.
I feel like this isn't the first time she slapped me.
No way that could've happened.
Must've been dreamin' about a movie I saw.
July 22nd?!
Wh-What's going on here?
It was the 23rd when Mio and I went to Hiruko.
And when Mio was killed by Mio.
That's ridiculous!
That was obviously a dream!
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Nagumo Ryuunosuke's Swamp Man.
It's a horror-mystery that takes place in Wakayama City.
It's a story about a young girl
who becomes obsessed with the crazy idea that her friends and family have been replaced by complete copies.
I probably had that nightmare because I fell asleep reading this.
Yeah.
July 22nd
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Shadow
Wh-Whoa, whoa...
Just calm down.
At times like this, you need to take a step back.
Stay calm.
I came back to this island after two years for Kofune Ushio's funeral—my childhood friend.
And yet, what is this feeling like the same thing just happened yesterday?
Hey!
Welcome back, Shin!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Is this what you call déjà vu?
Are ya tired from yer long trip?!
Even the pattern on her panties is the same.
What happened to the brakes?
I tried!
Here.
That's odd.
The events that followed were all a repeat of the past, as well.
Hitogashima Hall
Dad!
Shin's back!
Everyone did and said the same things as in my dream.
Oh...
Shinpei!
You've gotten so tall.
Alan, you've lost some weight.
Déjà vu, premonitions...
This is far beyond all that!
I'm repeating July 22nd!
My head feels like it's been split in half.
I'm seeing weird flashes of light.
What's going on, Ushio?
During the autopsy, they did find marks on her neck.
Marks like someone strangled her!
What...
really happened to ya?
Dr. Hishigata performed an autopsy on Ushio's body!
An autopsy?
Now that's just plum outrageous!
There's that flash again.
Who did that? No photos!
That's Kobayakawa Shiori.
The girl Ushio sacrificed herself for.
If I've really gone back in time, then that family is going to disappear tomorrow.
And if things keep repeating...
Shinpei!
Ya finally came back!
Does this mean the Shadows really exist?
Thanks for the food.
Those who see a Shadow die.
This is yummy.
Was Ushio killed by one?
And Mio, too...
Shinpei?
Your face is pale.
Sorry, I think I need some air.
This morning, Mio's bike brake was broken.
It was like
someone had cut it.
What if that was on purpose?
In order to kill Mio!
It's no use.
I have no idea what's going on.
I can't even begin ta take a step back!
I'm gonna barf...
Huh? What's this?
It's Totsumura.
Whassa matter, Mio?
Whatcha starin' at yer own house for?
You get in a fight or somethin'?
Mio?!
What's she doing outside?
And in her school uniform.
No...
No... No...
No... No... No...
No, no, no, no, no!
That's not Mio!
It's a Shadow!
Wh-What is that?
A Shadow?!
Here we go.
From now on, you are Totsumura Tetsu, the police officer.
Ah, I am Totsumura Tetsu, 34 years old.
No girlfriend. No prospects for the future.
Who asked ya?!
Mio, yer as cute as always!
Your pistol, please.
Huh?
Wait, ya haven't swapped places yet?
My attempt this morning failed.
It should be easier if I can send her to the hospital.
I hate beatin' around the bush, y'know.
Here.
Just barge in there!
Ya got a gun now.
Gunshots on such a quiet night will be heard far and wide.
This ain't America.
Good point.
I suppose today is just for scouting.
This can't be...
Is this actually happening?!
My phone!
Hishigata Sou
It's Sou!
Why now?!
Shoot—
Fancy finding you here, Shin.
It ain't right to eavesdrop, Shinpei.
That's grounds for the death penalty!
You gonna copy this, too?
No, he's already...
Is this blood... mine?
It's so red...
Wait, am I dying?
Oh.
I was finally able to take a step back.
Huh?
What is this?
Shinpei.
Wh-Who's there?!
Be careful...
What?! I can't hear you!
Shin!
Protect Mio, okay?
July 22nd
Summer Time Rendering
I'm back again...
Did I... die?
How did I get back here?
Hey!
Welcome back, Shin!
Take a step back! Take a step back!
I just heard a voice, right?
Ushio's voice!
She asked me to protect Mio!
I can't stop!
Stop! Stop, please!
Leave it to me!
Crap!
Shin!
I can't swim!
Shin, open yer eyes!
M-Mio, are you hurt?
No.
Thanks, Shin!
Recording
It's me.
July 22nd 1:02 PM.
One hour and thirty-seven minutes since arriving on Hitogashima.
Before getting on the boat, I ate something called "narezushi."
It's a traditional delicacy—
the precursor to the modern sushi—made by preserving mackerel in salt, fermenting it for over a month.
It is quite exquisite, I must say.
I urge you to try it if you ever come to Wakayama.
I'd like to hear your thoughts.
By the way, you once asked me why I hang myself upside down.
I'll tell you now.
It's because doing so focuses the blood in my brain and increases my ability to think.
I urge you to try it.
It may sharpen that dull mind of yours just a tiny bit.
Recording
The rest is basically as reported.
It's right there among them. My goodness.
I'll keep watch for the moment.
End transmission.
Hello, this is your ally of justice speaking.
Wh-What'd ya say?!
A fight's broken out?
Y-Yes!
That you, Shinpei?
Yes.
You okay?
Yes. In the shopping district.
The shopping district?
A bar customer.
A bar customer?
Please take care of it!
Take a step back.
What I need to do
is survive today, no matter what.
Did I do something really bad
by making a false report?
But it'll keep Totsumura away from here and safe.
Well, if nothing happens, I'll gladly take the lecture.
The best thing would be if nothing happens, right, Ushio?
Hishigata Sou
I'll call ya tomorrow.
Got it. Actually, can we meet up and talk?
Maybe at your place? Tell me when you're free.
Thanks. I'll get in touch.
I messaged Sou that I'd call him tomorrow.
Now, I just have to delete any unnecessary apps and pictures.
That leaves me with about 7 GB of usable storage.
Storage
That should give me plenty of recording time.
Just in case, I'll put it on airplane mode so it doesn't ring.
Storage
Fully charged, and I'll connect it to an external battery.
Fortunately, I know when it's coming.
Begin recording.
Once I've recorded Mio's Shadow, I'll have definitive proof!
Now I just have to make sure I don't go outside,
no matter what kind of bad feeling I get.
Then it'll all be fine.
I didn't die the first time on the 22nd, after all.
The color of my right eye's different.
When did that happen?
Mio, that's you, right?
Mio?
Mio!
Huh?
Idjit! Idjit! Idjit! Idjit! Idjit!
Shin, ya perv!
Step back! Step back! Step back!
What're you tryin' to look at, Shin?!
S-Sorry...
Mio's safe! Okay!
What the hell?
Holy...
It didn't even try to hide.
July 23rd
Mornin', Shin.
Mio, can we talk?
And then that thing appeared at 9 o'clock last night right in front of our house.
It stared up at the second floor for five minutes before walking off toward the mountains.
Who is this?
M-Me?
No.
Because you were in the bath at that time.
It's called a Shadow, apparently.
Hey, Mio, have you heard of the shadow sickness?
That thing came here to kill you.
I-I'm coming to... kill me?
Here, zoom in on the hand.
Yer kidding...
So the shadow sickness isn't just a superstition.
I knew it!
Ushio saw the Shadow too, didn't she?
Three days before she died.
Yeah.
Oh, I see. She told you about that story, huh?
It was you, actually.
Well, I saw your Shadow yesterday.
Yeah...
Hey, Shin.
Maybe she was murdered by a Shadow!
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Drifting Ashore