Apologies for the wait.
Here are your octopus balls.
Is something wrong?
It's got octopus in it!
Well, they're octopus balls.
I hate octopus.
Make 'em without it.
What?!
Just give up.
You know full well how selfish that kid can get.
Even then, she's goin' pretty overkill.
I mean, get a load of she did to the princess's room!
Talk about poor taste.
And you stooges are ones to talk?
You keep getting whooped by the Precures,
and you've gotten nowhere near enough Egogy to bring Daddy back.
Fair point,
but the Precures have one of the three Sacred Treasures,
the Magical Lovely Pad, and have grown considerably stronger.
Three Sacred Treasures?
Then how about you guys nab a few?
Three minus one equals two, right?
True...
Deep within this palace lies Princess Ann's spear of light,
the Miracle Dragon Glaive.
There ya go!
We Selfishes can't pull it out.
It's got some kinda magic lock on it.
Which is why we've been searching for the princess to undo it.
Understand?
Oh, I understand...
just how incompetent you stooges are!
What'd you say?!
Regina's reawakening means that our time is up.
All we can do is take a do-or-die gamble on that spear of light...
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Solitaire
What are you doing?
Don't you think we've gotten stronger?
Wanna test that?
It is true that we've mastered the Magical Lovely Pad.
I believe it may be time for our final confrontation with King Selfish.
I'll finally see Regina again!
I'll finally take back Trump Kingdom!
Finally!
So, how do we get there?
This calls for a strategy meet!
Agreed!
Let's share our wisdom over a hot cup of tea!
M-Mister!
Hey.
We're Here to See You!
Reunion With Regina!
What made you come back?
How is the princess?
Did you know that Ai came back?
Now, let's calm down. I'll answer one at a time.
Before you do, we'd like to introduce you to someone.
My name is Madoka Aguri.
I'm Joe Okada.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Miss Cure Ace.
You know?
I've heard a few things.
And I've heard much about you.
As well as your fiancée, Princess Ann.
Right!
I returned for one reason alone.
It's about the princess!
What about her?
I tried everything I could,
but the princess showed no signs of awakening.
But while searching for another way, I found an answer.
It was...
What was it?
One of the three Sacred Treasures obtained by the legendary Precure warriors,
the Miracle Dragon Glaive.
Miracle Dragon Glaive...
That's the spear the princess used!
The spear of light that could pierce any obstacle.
It could certainly break the princess's seal!
We can awaken the princess with the spear's power?
Now, one moment.
Where is the princess's spear, anyway?
Underneath the Trump Palace.
In Trump Kingdom...
So much for that.
Since we've got no way to get there and all.
Not to worry!
I can take us there via teleportation!
Wait, you can teleport?
Well, I, uh...
I've been training, yeah!
It's not like I did nothing all day with Princess Ann, right?
What should we do?
We've gotta go to Trump Kingdom!
That's where we wanted to go this whole time.
One can't catch a lion without entering the lion's den, as they say.
I'm hungry.
Well, let's get some food in us before heading out.
We can't fight on an empty stomach!
Oh, in that case,
I have just the thing.
Why octopus balls?
I happened to make too much.
Don't mind if we do!
I'll help myself as well.
It's so yummy!
The spice of the ginger and flavor of the bonito within the rich scent of the breading is...
These octopus balls...
don't have any octopus!
Well, you see...
Faker...
An octopus ball with no octopus...
is just a faker!
Oh... how silly of me to forget to put those in!
We got here in an instant!
So this is Trump Kingdom...
Oh, it's your first time here, Aguri.
Yes...
But I wonder...
why does this breeze that brushes my cheek feel so familiar?
The palace is that-a-way!
We're right in plain sight!
Oh, don't worry about that.
If we take this sewer, we'll reach the temple without drawing any attention.
But the sewers are labyrinthine!
We can't afford to get lost.
Ai?
Is that...
A map of the sewer system?
And is that blinking dot the location of the spear of light?
I see. It makes sense for the three Sacred Treasures to call to one another.
Wh-What?
Oh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
L-Let's get a move-on!
Girls, that's it!
This is the Miracle Dragon Glaive?
Yes, this is definitely the princess's spear!
If I can get my hands on this, I'll be Numero Uno...
Now, just pull it...
Huh?
Wh-What's the matter?
C'mon, take the sp—
Before we do,
you should drop the act already,
Bel!
When did you figure me out?
You were fishy from the start!
I returned for one reason alone.
It's about the princess!
You just called her "the princess"!
Jonathan calls her "Ann" with love!
And that teleportation thing was a dead giveaway!
Not to mention...
The color on your apron is way off!
That scarf looks just like Bel's!
That settles it!
Just like those octopus balls with no octopus...
You're a faker!
If you knew, then why did you come this far?
Why else?
To give King Selfish...
To give King Selfish what?
a stern talking-to!
T-Talking?!
We'll tell him to leave Trump Kingdom
and return the Selfish-turned citizens back to normal!
And then...
we'll make him swear to never harm Regina again!
Th-That's madness!
King Selfish has no reason to listen to the likes of you!
Does he, now?
One of the Sacred Treasures, the Magical Lovely Pad, has already made us much stronger.
And now we have another Sacred Treasure, the princess's spear!
And it's all thanks to you for leading us right to it!
Thank you ever so much!
Not yet...
That spear isn't yours just yet!
Selfish!
You rang?!
Fish, fish...
Octopecs!
Girls, let's go!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor octopus who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Have an Octopunch!
I shall handle this Selfish.
You obtain the spear of light!
Gotcha!
I'll snatch that spear the moment you pull it out!
Seeelf!
Selfish!
Girls!
You ruined it!
Don't attack them until they draw the spear!
Self.
Good, the spear's safe!
Yes, pull it out!
I'll help you, Cure Heart!
Us too!
No good.
It's not budging.
What's this?
Not even the Precures can draw it?
Self...
Selfish!
You really are incompetent.
P-Princess Regina, why are you here?
Something here was making me nauseous, so I came to see what.
I had a feeling it was you.
I haven't forgotten the disgrace you made me s—
Regina!
It's really you!
How've you been?
Have you been eating well?
I couldn't stop worrying about you!
I never asked you to.
I know the truth now.
The only one in the world who truly cares about me is Daddy.
Daddy's the only one I need!
That's not true!
Heart cares about you more than you can imagine!
We all feel the same way.
Regina, let's talk this out again.
I know we'll see eye to eye!
Okay?
Geez...
All you ever do is nag, nag, nag, nag, nag!
Cure Heart!
Don't worry.
Why?
Why are you unharmed?
Because we've grown stronger.
All so you could listen to us.
Don't make me laugh!
We came all this way!
We've fought, we've grown,
and now we're standing by your side!
Come with us, Regina!
Let's try one more time...
to recover your love!
Regina!
This is bad.
If the spear and Regina fall into the enemy's hands,
it'll be my head!
Love love loooove!
My Selfish, too?!
Shut up...
You're just doing this to hurt me again, aren't you?
You can take your love and friendship and shove it!
Regina?
I'm happiest when I'm with Daddy.
When Daddy holds me in his arms,
nothing bad can hurt me!
So stop trying to ruin our lives!
Regina!
I'm getting pumped with power!
Here it comes!
What happened?
It's Egogy!
The Egogy flowing from Regina's body is powering the Selfish up!
Calm down, Regina!
You can't give in to hatred!
I told you to shut up...
The Precures are my enemies...
They're enemies who hurt Daddy!
Selfish!
Focus on the Selfish!
Magical Lovely Pad!
Gather!
Heart Dynamite!
Head over heels...
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Precure Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love looooove!
You still don't understand?
No matter how strongly you reject and despise her,
Cure Heart will continue to care for you.
That is her form of love.
I don't care.
Daddy has nobody but me...
If he lost me,
he'd be all alone...
So I'll protect Daddy no matter what!
The spear!
How could Regina draw the spear when even the Precures couldn't?!
Could the spear have chosen Regina?
The Precures are Daddy's enemies.
Which means...
the Precures are nuisances!
Regina!
I'll eliminate Daddy's enemies!
Begone, Precures!
This is the strength of the Miracle Dragon Glaive...
Cute trick!
But can you hold out?
My apologies, but I can't contain any more!
I won't give in...
Until my feelings reach your heart...
I'll stay standing, Regina!
What?
It's a mirror?
Isn't that Oogai City?
We can see our city!
Th-They disappeared!
Was that the power of the Lovely Pad?
Aww, they ran away.
But they won't be so lucky next time.
Get ready, Precures...
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
What's wrong with Makopi?
She seems to be writing a new song.
I hope it's a song that will touch Regina's heart.
If anyone can make it, it's Makopi!
But that's the part that seems to be troubling her...
Then let's all help Makopi write her new song!
Yeah!
Dokidoki Precure:
Getting Our Feelings Across!
Makopi Announces Her New Song!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!