Why?
This country is filled with the smiles of its people...
Why would you destroy it?
You should know why better than anyone,
Marie Ange.
There exists no love in this world that lasts forever.
All flames soon die out, leaving nothing but ash!
That... is not true!
Ange!
Princess Ann...
Why do I dream such dreams?
Why must I awaken with such sorrow in my heart?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
A Celebration With Everyone!
Her First Birthday!
You are a Leo.
Leo
You are a Leo. You may end up arguing with your friends often,
but eating sweets with them may bring you closer together.
You may end up arguing with your friends often,
Your lucky item is a teddy bear.
Sounds cool!
Lance, it's your turn.
I'm not a stuffed animal, you know.
What are you doing?
Horoscopes.
You find your zodiac sign with your birthday
and learn your fortune and compatibility with others.
I was born on August 4th, so I'm a Leo.
Makopi was born on November 4th, so she's a Scorpio.
Alice is a Gemini,
and Rikka's a Virgo!
Rikka, you're not into it?
Well, there are a lot of people in the world with the same birthdays,
so when you say that they'll all have the same fate...
Wait.
Did they do horoscopes in Trump Kingdom?
We did.
The princess loved them, in fact!
I'm home!
Welcome back!
You seem to be having fun.
Yes, we were just having fun with horoscopes.
Hey, what's your sign, Aguri?
I don't know.
I'll look it up for you.
When's your birthday?
Like I said, I don't know.
I'm aware that birthdays are celebrations where birthday cake is eaten,
but I've never eaten one myself.
But not to worry!
Someone will invite me to their birthday party,
and when that day comes, I'll finally have my chance to savor the phantom treat!
That hope is what drives me forward.
And now, I must bid you adieu.
Bye bye!
Mana, a word?
She's adopted?
Yes. Aguri isn't Mari's real granddaughter.
From what I heard, Aguri had no relatives, so Mari took her in.
Does Aguri know that?
Yes.
They're not related by blood,
but they live as a true grandparent and grandchild would.
So don't treat her any differently, okay?
We did something mean to Aguri...
Well, we didn't know.
We didn't mean any harm.
I don't believe Aguri minded much.
I hope so...
Besides, why didn't Aguri ever tell us something that important?
Rachel's right!
Perhaps she left it unsaid because it was important.
The truth is, I don't have parents either.
I was told I lost them in an accident when I was still a baby.
So I don't even remember what my mother and father looked like.
But I wasn't sad.
We were all supported by the princess's love.
Really?
Why didn't you ever tell us something that important?!
I didn't want you worrying over nothing.
I suppose even the closest of friends don't tell each other everything.
Mana?
What is it?
We gotta celebrate!
Huh?
We'll throw a birthday party for Aguri
and we'll all jump in and celebrate!
When?
Aguri said she didn't know her birthday.
If she doesn't know, then we can just throw one whenever, right?
What kind of logic is that?
We'll have it tomorrow!
Get your presents ready and come on over!
But...
don't say a peep to Aguri about this!
Got it?
Yeah, got it.
What's eatin' you? You look like a dead fish.
Because we came to this stage for you!
I know that deep down, your heart is pure.
And I know that it's brimming with love!
What's with those girls?
One look, and it's all love, hearts, and junk...
I'm dead tired.
Caught a cold?
No.
Figured.
Idiots don't get colds, right?
Who's the idiot here?
She has a point, Ira.
If you blurt out everything with no tact,
girls will never like you.
Hey! That's my pudding à la mode!
Oh, my apologies!
It was in the fridge, so I couldn't resist!
You'll pay with your life!
Ain't that a bit much for just one pudding?
You don't get anything.
Sweets are magical treats that turns a girl's frown upside down!
Where ya goin'?
To the Human World.
The only way to fill my empty belly is to steal all their sweets!
Have a nice triiii—
What, did I say you could stay?
Ow, ow, ow...
Lemme go, c'mon!
Ange!
That dream again...
Aguri...
Can't sleep?
Grandmother...
Thank you very much.
Is something troubling you?
I've been having the same dream every night, so I can't stay asleep...
I've been having one too.
It's one where you grow up.
One where I grow up?
You wear a white dress and makeup...
I'm certain it was your wedding dress.
I'll never get married!
I'll stay with you forever!
So you say.
But the time will come when you'll embark on the journey of life.
That's just the star you were born under.
Grandmother...
Now, go back to bed.
Um...
What is it?
Can I sleep in your bed tonight?
Still such a child.
Sugar?
Check.
Flour?
Eggs, milk, and cream?
Check.
Hello.
Makoto, you're grocery shopping?
You're mistaken.
I am not this "Kenzaki Makoto" of which you speak.
Excuse us.
We really should go with roses, huh?
But we're on a budget...
What are you discussing?
If you're shopping for gifts, I wouldn't mind helping you choose!
Oh, we're fine!
But we're in a bit of a rush, so...
Thank you, I'm sure she'll be delighted.
Now, please keep it a secret from Aguri...
I'm home!
Welcome home.
What is this secret about?
Um...
Sebastian?
Madam was simply collecting shells by the sea,
but sadly ran out of storage for her massive spoils.
As such, we came to Ms. Madoka's residence to borrow a crate.
A crate for the sea, crate by the sea, crate sea, crate sea, crate...
Seacrate!
Well now, have a nice day!
What was he talking about?
I wonder that myself.
Really, everyone has been acting strange today!
The second they see my face, they try to run and hide.
Aguri.
Would you like to eat out tonight?
Even though I just bought groceries?
I made some plans.
Be at the Pig's Tail Diner by 6 tonight.
All right.
Reserved
I don't know what they're scheming,
but it seems I need to make one thing clear to them...
never hide things from me!
Happy Birthday,
Aguri
Is everything Charlmplete?
Everylance looks great!
You're right about that!
I've set the tabchell!
The cake's done!
Happy
Birthday
It's great!
Happy
Birthday
The master chef here's a great teacher.
Aww, shucks...
Girls, we must hurry!
The birthday girl will arrive at any moment!
A birthday party for me?
But why would they keep it a secret?
Because they wanted you to enjoy the surprise.
Grandmother!
Since you've never had a birthday,
they put their hearts into making your first one unforgettable.
Girls...
Now, let's go inside.
But pretend you don't know about the party.
It's no fun if you're not surprised.
Okay!
Happy birthday, Aguri!
Happy birthday!
Surprised, huh?
Okay Aguri, blow out the candles!
Happy birthday!
Thank you very much!
Grandmother, I never knew that birthday cakes were this delicious!
Glad you enjoy it.
I do!
I want to have a birthday every day now!
I came all this way just to see it reserved for a birthday party?
And those lucky brats get cake...
Oh well, I'll go somewhere else.
Just squash that cake.
Who's there?
I'll turn you into a splendid Selfish!
Selfish!
Reserved
Wh-What the?
Look out!
Ai!
Daddy! Mommy! Grandpa!
Had it comin'.
Regina!
Why did you do this?
Hm, now why did I, again?
There was this book Mana read to me.
It had a witch who put the princess into eternal slumber because she wasn't invited to a party...
"Sleeping Beauty"?
Yeah, that one!
I'm the witch.
The witch who nobody saved a slice for!
Aguri, we'll handle her!
Take Mari and run!
Let's go, Grandmother!
We should be able to return everyone to normal by purifying the Selfish!
Let's go!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Oh poor ant who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Let's rock, Precures!
Today's the day we finish you!
Selfish!
Self!
I'll hold off that beast with Mana and the others!
Grandmother, please escape!
Aguri!
I'll be fine!
Now hurry!
I understand.
Don't get hurt, okay?
Let's go, Ai!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
You again?
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Beauty is the mark of the righteous!
With a single wink,
I shall pierce your heart!
Cure Ace!
You tick me off!
So, you get to eat cake with everyone?
You think you were always part of the group?!
Huh?
It's worthless!
We'd all be better off without you!
It is not... worthless!
Mana!
The birth of a new life is a miracle!
You,
me,
Aguri...
Everyone deserves to be celebrated!
Cure Heart...
That tingling pain again...
Why?
Sadface...
Cure Heart...
It's all because of you...
I hate you!
Cure Ace!
I accept your feelings!
Now let us counterattack!
Yeah!
Oh no you ain't!
Diamond Swirkle!
Lie there and cool your hot head down!
Kiddin' me...
Self!
Selfiiiiish!
Girls, let's go!
Right!
Kyupirappa!
Precure Royal Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love looooove!
Cripes!
Precures, I'll remember this!
Officer, it's right here!
Huh?
There's nothin' wrong here.
Grandmother!
Aguri!
Where's that monster?
The Precures came and defeated it.
Right, Mana?
Yeah!
Precures?
Now, let's get back to our birthday party!
Everyone's waiting!
A birthday, huh?
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Aguri, what's wrong?
It seems her grandmother found out she was Cure Ace!
I can never return home again!
Let's not jump the gun here!
I'm sure your grandmother wouldn't want that either!
What do you want to do, Aguri?
I want to stay with Grandmother!
Dokidoki Precure:
To the Person I Love!
Aguri's Career Day!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!