"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
We saw a shooting star the other day.
But, Kagami said,
"Realistically speaking,
chanting a wish
three times is impossible."
A shooting star? How nice!
I've rarely seen them.
I can't see that many stars
from my house.
Oh, that's right,
your house is in
downtown Tokyo, isn't it?
I'm sure I'd just watch it
with fascination,
and be unable to recite a wish.
Seeing wonderful,
brightly shining stars,
one gets a feeling of happiness...
Perhaps that is why the legend goes
that your wishes come true.
You are just so straightforward...
It's blinding!
"Various Ways to Spend Christmas Eve"
It's almost winter vacation.
Though we have finals before that.
Do you guys have any plans
for winter vacation, Kagami?
Nothing.
Come to think of it,
we haven't traveled at all lately.
I went to Asakusa the other day.
Oh? When did you go?
Trains in the winter
make you drowsy, you know?
She slept past her destination?!
Wait... But isn't that in
the opposite direction?
Apparently, I slept too long,
so it doubled back from the final stop,
and I slept past my station again.
And when I came to, it was Asakusa.
Come on, there's a limit on
oversleeping for your destination...
But oversleeping your destination
isn't a completely bad thing.
I was able to take a short trip
to Asakusa as a result, anyway.
Though it's not something
to be doing during your exams.
I thought for a moment that a girl
in a sailor outfit had a machine gun,
and passed by the platform
for a fleeting moment...
I wonder what it was.
You're not going to say that it was
a raid or something, are you?
Besides, you know,
they say that children who sleep
are the ones that grow.
Where did you grow?!
But this one's even better.
My dad, when he went to deliver
his script after an all-nighter,
got on an early train, overslept
all the way to the final stop,
--For real?!
--then the train made a U-turn,
and before he knew it,
he had overslept again.
He went back and forth many times.
--He woke up closer and closer
to the destination station,
--Look, Patrasche... That's
a painting by Rubens...
--but he would always sleep past
it by a very close margin...
He was so tired that he just
wanted to come home and sleep,
but he couldn't manage
to make his way home.
Wow.
And in the end, when
he woke up with a start,
he couldn't figure out which direction
he was heading at the time.
I don't believe it.
Even if I fall asleep, I always
wake up before my station.
That's amazing...
I wonder how you know.
Maybe there's an alarm clock
installed inside?
Though the clock in her stomach
seems to be broken.
What was that?
You're always eating tons of sweets.
Shut up!
But when the train or the seats
are warm, you get really sleepy.
Right. It's just like
a sunny winter afternoon,
when you're drowsing off in the
window side seat of your classroom.
Warm and comfy...
What? Are these comrades
covering for each other now?
It's not like that.
The other day, when I woke
her up on the train home...
Hey, wake up! We're here!
Five more minutes... Honest!
...she said loudly in her sleep.
Everyone around us
was laughing at her.
I have a friend that
said that during class.
Oh, brother, talk about birds
of a feather flocking together.
Eh? We're the same?!
But I wonder why it's five minutes.
Isn't it because it's very upsetting
when you go wake someone up
and they say, "Give me one
more hour," or something?
Well, that's true,
but you say "five more minutes"
about a lot more than just sleep.
Like, "Hold on for
five minutes" and stuff.
You're right.
Maybe it's not too long
and not too short.
Though five minutes spent waiting
for a train seems really long.
It really does.
That may be it.
But in general, the more likely one
is to say "five more minutes,"
the less likely it's going
to be only five minutes.
You know how they say
not to use cell phones
or put makeup on in the train, right?
But isn't it worse when someone leans
up against you, don't you think?
Yeah. Sometimes they're so heavy
that it's easier to stay standing,
even after all the effort
you went through to sit down.
And when sticky hair from
an elderly person comes over, right?
I sometimes think, "Go over there!"
But no matter how many times
they fix their posture,
they always fall over
in the same direction.
Right, right. It's so mysterious.
When I was sleeping,
and this side had a middle-aged man
while the other was empty,
I was thinking that I wanted to
lean towards the empty space,
but I always end up leaning
towards the middle-aged man.
Maybe there's a direction that's
easier for you to lean, or something.
When the person next to me
falls over towards me,
I shrink in on myself like this...
But when I do, their elbows
start hitting my sides.
Don't you think they're actually
awake when they do that?
Eh? Is that so?
Then...
Bye-nee!
Goodbye.
In our school, you know how
some people take the up train
and some take the down train?
Yeah.
Don't you think that the up people are
more refined than the down people?
Yuki-chan is an up person, after all.
Eh? Surely not...
Now, now, let us head back
to the borderlands, all.
What, I have another station left...
S'up?
Yo!
I couldn't study at all last night...
I see.
On the other hand,
I'm pretty psyched this time,
though I hate to say so myself.
How much were you able to study?
--Four whole hours!
--Only four hours.
Huh?
Kagami, you do everything
so carefully.
Well, this is just between us,
but I do study quite a bit.
It's true that you have
a competitive streak, Kagami.
Well, in the end, I have the pride
of being the older sister.
The feeling that I had to stay a step
ahead of Tsukasa was very strong.
Normally, I say that older
or younger doesn't matter,
but I used to think about it a lot.
But wasn't Tsukasa a very
disappointing opponent?
Well, yeah, that's true.
Kona-chan, you've got no right!
It's almost Christmas.
I wonder what this
year's present will be.
So, you still get presents...
Kona-chan, how long did
you believe in Santa Claus?
Wait, Santa Claus doesn't really exist?
For real?!
At Kona-chan's house
Santa never swung by,
so her dad was giving her
presents in his place.
So she thought that he really
was out there somewhere.
That old man really wants to show
off to his daughter, doesn't he...
Hey, Hiiragi!
Oh.
Miss Hiiragi, this is the printout
from the other day.
Oh, yeah.
And so, Hiiragi-chan.
Hiiragi, you dropped
your mechanical pencil.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, Kagami!
Oh.
Kagami-san, this is the printout
from the other day.
Oh, yeah.
Sebastian was so smelly!
Kagami, you dropped
your handkerchief.
For real?!
Oh, maybe I'm dropping by
Tsukasa's class a bit too much...
Lately, my cavity has
been starting to hurt.
My... Don't you hate it?
I hate dentists too.
Yuki-chan, you went to go
fix a cavity the other day.
Is it all better now?
Dentists always take
a while to treat a tooth,
and when they're done with one,
they find another tooth,
and so it takes quite
a bit of time, right?
So I couldn't help but run away,
giving all sorts of reasons.
What should I do?
She's saying it so cutely,
but isn't she doing
something drastic?!
Konata,
how about we all get together
for a Christmas bash?
Oh, sorry. I already have
something to do on Christmas.
Oh, what?
Something involving a guy?
I guess you could say that.
You have plans to go out
with your dad?
I already told Dad that
I was going to be out late.
Don't tell me you're really going
on a date with a boyfriend?!
When did you...
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but it's just a part-time job.
Is that all?
In the first place, I'm not lying,
because most of
the customers are guys.
I thought you had snuck ahead of us.
I was so surprised!
There's a limited-time
event for Christmas,
where we all dress up
like Santa Claus.
You really like that kind
of stuff, don't you?
But, you know,
you guys cosplay as shrine maidens
for New Year's, Kagami.
At your family shrine.
Don't call it cosplay.
About Santa... It's a good thing
that he gives out presents...
But it's totally breaking and entering.
At least, I thought so
when I was a kid.
Don't insult the roots of
a saint's existence that much.
What a disgusting kid!
But, anyway...
Santa is someone that
gives dreams out to kids.
What kind of men seek their dreams
from a shrimp like that?
Oh? Isn't she insulting me
very nonchalantly here?
But can you guys celebrate
Christmas in the first place?
Come to think of it, we got
Christmas presents very normally.
We enshrine the myriad deities
at our place,
we go pay homage to temples
like everyone else,
--♪ Joy to the world, the Lord is... ♪
--and we've even sung hymns in a church.
I see... That's just so peaceful.
--Oh, but our older sister, a shrine maiden,
--Yeah...
said that she wanted to
get married in a wedding dress.
I wonder if that's all right.
When it gets that far,
doesn't it get a bit complicated?
Lucky Star!
Yoo-hoo! It's getting cold lately!
Hey, Sis. Welcome.
What were you watching?
A detective drama show.
Is it interesting?
Not really.
I'm just watching it on a whim.
That's it, I get it! That guy did it!
Wait a minute, detective!
There are strange things
about this case!
There isn't anything strange
about it! This solves the case!
What are you, you're not
involved in any of this!
Oh man, this is why
the cops are no good!
And you're one of those cops, aren't you?!
Why am I getting a phone call now?
We're almost at the point
where the culprit confesses!
How do you know?
See?
I see, so you were the one that did it.
There's no choice,
if you've already found out.
Why do all these 2-hour drama shows
end at the top of a cliff?
Maybe people can't decide to
go through with something
unless they're pushed to the edge?
Yahoo! You doing well?
Evenin', Sis.
What were you watching?
The movie spin-off of
a popular cop drama.
Dad rented it.
The case doesn't happen
in a boardroom!
It happens at the crime scene!
No, no, no, there's no way.
Such passionate turns
of events never happen!
And that's the point you deny?!
If I remember right,
the thief wasn't the guy
who stole the receipt,
but someone who was sent out
by the police chief.
This is why police chiefs...
Something rings a bell?!
You know, on cop shows, they
give cutlet bowls to suspects,
but I heard they can't
do that in real life.
Well, it's all fiction,
so there are a lot of lies in it.
Then the Metropolitan Police Chief
doesn't actually have
that many grandkids?!
The Metropolitan Police
Chief's grandkids?
I haven't seen any as such...
I'd like Mai to exist,
at least, as a glimmer of hope.
What an empty wish...
There are a lot of cases where
adults go after children.
You're right.
You know what I think?
If you make kids learn martial arts,
stuff like that will happen less often.
I hear that Mr. Oyama,
after intense training,
was able to defeat a cow
with one barehanded blow!
I also hear that his daily workout
is defeating twenty bears!
I see!
But even then, after a while,
won't you go back to square one?
When those kids grow up,
they'll be stronger as adults too.
Oh, well, it's, you know...
When you practice martial arts,
they say you grow up with
a straightforward heart.
Oh, I see... but...
Someone with a twisted mind
despite practicing martial arts
is right in front of me...
How rude!
Miss Yui has a younger sister,
so I have a cousin that will be
entering high school next year.
--She was born really frail, but is
honest, pure, and really cute.
--Konata-oneechan!
I see.
But going by the "healthy soul
resides in a healthy body" theory,
those pretty eyes of hers
suddenly start looking like
scheming ones that are
hiding something...
I don't think everything goes
exactly like in the proverbs.
I mean, you're a prime example.
This year is almost over already!
Every time December comes around,
I feel like the year flew by.
So are you guys going
to be shrine maidens
to help your family out
again, Tsukasa?
Well, yeah.
Come pick your fortunes
and stuff again!
About fortunes...
When you pick an "Unlucky" result,
you get a bad feeling
from its negative image,
but when you pick "Great Blessings",
don't you feel like you've
wasted your luck so early on?
Well, they do say "Average Blessings"
is the best fortune...
All right, this is an early present
from your teacher.
I'm handing out report cards!
--Here. Thanks for all the hard studying.
--Kona-chan, how'd you do?
Ma'am, I don't need
presents like this...
It's my policy as Santa
to give you all points
according to how hard
you've worked as presents.
Enjoy it. It comes with a bonus gift:
Winter vacation homework!
What kind of Christmas cake
would you like this year?
When you go to a cake shop,
there are so many cute cakes
that just looking at them is very fun.
I wonder what happens to the
leftover cakes after Christmas?
Perhaps the employees
take them home?
But if nobody decided
to take them home,
maybe they throw
them away after all.
They often relate the prime
marriage age to Christmas.
Yeah, they're both "until the 25th".
Christmas cakes are ordinary
cakes after the 25th,
and when the night ends,
decorated cakes suddenly pale,
and you don't feel like
eating them at all...
I was talking about Santa with
Kona-chan the other day.
Yuki-chan, how long did
you believe in Santa?
I feel like you believed it
for a long time, just like me.
I believed in Santa in the past...
When I was little, I wanted to
write a letter of thanks to Santa,
and I looked it up in
all sorts of places.
But since asking both my parents
didn't lead to any answers,
I looked it up more carefully.
And I came across phrases like
"Stories that Santa Claus was
based on" and "Origin of Santa,"
so my dreams were shattered
pretty early on in life.
Oh, no...
"Report Card"
Miyuki-san, how'd you do? Let me see!
Nothing less from Yuki-chan!
I can't ever come up
with something like this.
It's somehow a bit frustrating
that I'm losing.
Yuki-chan is always at
the top of our class,
so we can't help it.
People like us would never win.
No, I don't care about grades at all.
You know, like breast size. Like this!
I'm getting a bit hungry...
I guess I'll have some cup ramen.
Not yet?
These three minutes spent waiting
seem like an awfully long time...
I'll use this to pass the time today.
Ever done that, and made your
noodles all soggy and stuff?
Yeah! Like with fried noodles in a cup,
it soaks up all the hot water
and everything.
You guys...
I heard that she was going to be late,
but this is a bit too late!
I'd hate to see this as a habit,
so I have to be stern every so often,
as a father.
I'm home!
Konata! Come here!
Just what time do you...
Merry Christmas.
This is a Christmas present
from me to you, Dad.
You must be cold after staying out
so late. Want some hot tea?
Hurray! I'll have some!
Dad is so happy that he just might die.
Yo! Hey!
Miss Yui is in the house!
Sis, you reek of alcohol!
Drunk driving is not good!
I had a bit to drink around here
after I parked my car.
Listen to me! It's Christmas Eve,
yet my husband is out again!
We were planning to
spend it alone together!
Sis, why not drop in on your folks
instead of us for once...
Oh, hello, Yui? It's me.
I was planning on surprising you
by sneaking home,
but the door was locked.
Are you at your parents' place now?
I'm heading home!
I'll go home at top speed right now!
Ignoring the signals and everything!
Like I said, you shouldn't
go breaking the law...
I'll take you home.
I've had my breather,
so I think I'll log in for a bit.
Hey, our teacher's on.
Ma'am, let's have a riot.
Of course, until morning... There.
Please hold on one moment.
"Christmas cakes - 50% off"
They're not leftovers...
They're not leftovers!
"Nanako Kuroi - 27 years old"
"Single"
Because I bought it...
I came here last Sunday too,
to buy some manga.
I'm amazed you'd shell out the
transportation costs to swing by...
Even though I know it's for the points,
you really go pretty far.
You really like this stuff.
In the first place, do you use the
items you get from stuff like that?
No, I don't use any of it.
Well, I can understand. It's hard
to use stuff like that, after all.
Right. It's such a waste
to use it that I can't use it.
Because using it depreciates its value.
Well, uh...
That's how you approach it?
Oh, well...
No!
Yes.
Didn't you get that static shock thing?
Not really.
What? Why not?
Because Konata is always
sitting in front of the computer,
maybe strange electric waves
already fill her body or something?
But don't you really hate winter?
I hear there are times
that you can get shocked
by touching other people's hands, too.
--Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
--Maybe these two actually don't
get along with each other?
What are you doing?
Well, I wanted to see it
one more time...
Whoa!
Stronger!
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
I'm Akira Kogami, your navigator!
Time passes by so quickly that Lucky
Channel is already in episode eleven!
And on that eleventh episode,
I am finally able to relay to you
news that you've all been
waiting so long for!
U-Um...
--Until now, there were so many
passionate voices sent to us
--She's not listening at
all today, as usual...
--from fans asking, "We'd
absolutely, positively like to see
--Miss Akira in the main
segment as well!"
--Hello. I'm the assistant,
Minoru Shiraishi...
--And in the next episode, I, Akira Kogami...
--Hey, shut up.
--I'm going to make an appearance
in the main segment!
--But my intro...
Miss Konata Izumi from Saitama,
who sent a postcard to Newtype,
and everyone else,
thank you so much!
I see, so you have been cast
as well, Akira-sama?
Wait, what's with that
"You're finally showing up in the
main segment in episode 12?"
"I was in the main segment so long
ago, hmph!" way of putting it?!
It's not like that! I'm honored
that I can act along with you
in the main segment
as well, Akira-sama.
Even though you say you've
been in the main segment,
all you did this time was
pick up a handkerchief.
When you start thinking,
"Maybe I can make it in this industry,"
is when you're the most vulnerable!
Remember that, if you don't
want to be gone too quickly!
I'll engrave it into my mind.
Oh? I can't wait for the next episode
if I hear news like that!
Air it right now, please! Okay?
Everyone is trembling...
No, anxious to watch,
already standing by naked!
You know, let's air it right now,
to answer all the feelings of the
dear fans, instead of holding out!
--Can't we do something
about a 30-minute block?
--Well, all things considered, isn't
something like that impossible?
--I'm asking, pretty please!
Well, we'll end it here after all.
So, keep sending messages for me
to the radio show or our homepage!
Bye-nee!
Bye-nee...
Oh, what should I do?
It would be bad to stand out
more than the main characters...
You're right.
There have been many cases
where a friend or nemesis,
someone other than the main
character, ended up more popular.
Oh? Akira-sama?
Is something the matter?
You know...
Yes?
Are you talking about yourself?
Just because you're popular lately...
--Are you getting full of yourself?
--No, no, no, it's not like that!
--Don't you think they'll
make action figures of you?
--No, no, no way...
--Don't you think you can win first
place in the popularity poll?!
--What are you talking about?
--Stop kidding with me!
--There's no way that would
happen. Stop and listen for--
Next up is Tsukasa and
Miyuki-san's duet!
Yuki-chan, let's sing up front.
Okay...
It's strange that you'd pick a song for
Tsukasa and Miyuki to sing, Konata.
I have proper knowledge
of all sorts of songs.
It's an anime song after all.
At times like this, anime songs
come in handy, amazingly enough.
♪ This sort of thing is good,
I wish I could do it ♪
♪ Dreams like that, dreams like this,
there are so many ♪
♪ All, all, all, he will grant them all ♪
♪ He grants them with
a mysterious pocket ♪
♪ I want to fly through the skies ♪
♪ Here, have a Bamboo-Copter! ♪
That's a bad impersonation!
♪ Ah, ah, ah, I love Doraemon so much! ♪
♪ Homework, school duty... ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
Tsukasa here.
Well, the other day, I got
really hungry late at night,
but since it was so late,
I wondered whether I should
eat something or not.
I decided that a little bit wouldn't hurt,
so I chose to go eat something.
And so I went to the kitchen,
and opened the fridge,
thinking I recalled there being
a couple leftover sweets from earlier.
Oh! Is it that time already?
Next episode: Let's Go to the Festival.
"Let's Go to the Festival"
Please look forward to it!