Haruka's Room
Number 5
It's Haruka's Room, you know?
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Our guest for today...
"Mori! Mori! Mori!"
Please welcome my classmate, Moritani Hiyori!
Hold on.
What is it?
That introduction was weird!
You did a better job introducing the others!
I'm sorry. I didn't put enough energy into the "Mori," right?
Please forgive me. I'm still a newbie.
That's not what I was—
Oh, forget it.
Let's continue.
Right!
Hm... You didn't seem to like me much, Moritani.
Why is that? Did I do something wrong?
Um... I felt like you were stealing Manabe away from me.
That made me irritated and so...
So you're saying you love Manabe, right?
You already know that!
It appears that we're not only classmates but rivals in love as well!
"Rivals in love"? So I still have a chance?
Nope. No chance at all.
Damn you!
Please, control yourself!
PLEASE
STAND BY
The End