The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
My motorcycle engine roars as if it's singing a song.
Blow up louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Blow up louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
Why are you asking about the Dollars?
Don't tell me you're thinking about joining the Dollars?
What the hell do you mean by that?!
For starters, why the heck is there
another body attached to my head?!
Or there could have been a freshly-killed corpse.
I'm so excited!
I'm so excited! I'm so excited!
What do you think is going to happen to us if that thing were to catch the eye of a police officer?!
I don't care if they capture her dead or alive.
If necessary, get rid of her on the spot.
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
I'm low on funds this month...
Let's see, now I need a kitchen sponge...
Have a nice day!
The black motorcycle!
She should be around the corner!
Oww!
Oww...
I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
Hey, you're...
Help me!
Huh?
Huh?!
Please!
Wow! The black motorcycle!
This is so cool!
We need to take a pic! We have to!
This is just rad!
Crazy!
The First and Probably the Last
So let me get this straight. You bumped into this beautiful girl at a street corner,
and she was being chased by a villain on a motorcycle.
She had also lost her memory, and by the time I got here,
she had already fallen asleep from fatigue.
And you expect me to believe such a fanciful tale?
It's true! What else do you expect me to say?
However, it would have been climatic if this took place in the morning when you were running late for school.
Even more climatic if she were a new student.
Would have been perfect if she were the princess of some country, and also turned out to be your childhood friend.
Get it? CLImatic and CLIche?
The fact that you had to explain the joke just shows how lame it was.
She doesn't remember anything, and yet, she doesn't want me to call the police.
I really don't know what do, man.
Hmm... guess you'll have to wait it out and see.
Anyway, just put this off till tomorrow,
and decide after listening to whatever it is she has to say.
Yeah...
Well, see you tomorrow.
Yup.
Thanks for coming by so late.
The one on the black motorcycle may remember my face.
The one that's considered an urban legend...
What can I do now that they're my enemy?
I hated living a normal life.
I wanted to live in a way unlike everyone else.
Maybe that's why I decided to take her in.
However, there's one thing Kida-kun doesn't know about.
Her scar.
It's almost like someone sawed off her head
once, and eventually sewed it back together.
An announcement from the lunch stand.
The Jumbo Melon Breads are sold out for today.
Yo, Mikado!
So what happened to that sleeping beauty at your apartment?
Kida-kun, please! Keep it on the dl!
What's this about a sleeping beauty?
I'm good at picking these words up.
So the story goes,
when Mikado was going around a street corner,
he bumped into an amnesic beauty who was being chased by a villain!
So basically, he's living with her right now.
Oh, it's just Kirigamine's inner desire...
U-Umm, my last name's Ryugamine...
And so...
Anyone want to buy these extra lunch passes from me?
See?
Don't worry, no one will believe you.
So, how's she doing?
She was still asleep when I left the house this morning.
Man, she sleeps a lot.
Well then, let's get down to business.
To business?
The reason why I'm trying to use my lunch break
efficiently after eating my lunch early during 4th period...
...is for this.
"Dollars Degree Prediction"...
It's actually some sort of a fad in our class right now.
The entirety of the Dollars is pretty mysterious.
So, it's a game where we say,
"Hey, doesn't he sort of seem like he'd be in the Dollars?"
and cast a vote for those schoolmates.
Wow, it looks like you've got a lot of votes there.
Yeah, since one person can vote for however many they want.
Wow, this Takiguchi guy from class 1-D only has one vote.
So you noticed.
That one vote is from yours truly.
We're actually in the same gym class.
Takiguchi Ryo is undoubtedly a Dollars member.
Why so?
Gut feeling.
So, I'm going to see if I'm right.
Hey!
Excuse me!
Is Takiguchi Ryo-kun in?
Huh?
He's not in here right now.
Is he at the cafeteria?
Who knows. Maybe he's up on the roof.
I think he usually goes up there during lunchtime.
Maybe he's up there smoking.
M-Maybe we should leave him alone.
There could be sketchy people up there.
I'm just pulling your leg.
It's like some cliche from an old manga for someone to be smoking on the rooftop during lunch period.
Yeah, but...
Even if you walk up to him and ask, "Are you in the Dollars?", I doubt he'll tell you the truth...
Just leave it to me, man!
I've got a plan.
Let's see...
Oh?
H-He's smoking...
Yo! Takiguchi!
'Sup.
Hey.
Wow, you compose music?
Just a little.
So, what's up? Need something?
I've got something I'd like to ask.
I'm waiting.
Ahem.
Are you in the Dollars?
Hey-
Kida-kun, what are you-!
Yeah, I am.
Huh?!
I knew it.
I totally called that.
Told you.
I have a knack for this kind of stuff.
Oh, this is an old friend of mine.
Oh, uhh...
I'm Ryugamine Mikado.
So you're the famous one!
Huh?
I'm famous?
Your name, that is.
Oh...
Want some?
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
You?
Danke.
So, Takiguchi-kun...
Mm?
Why did you decide to join the Dollars?
Huh?
I'm not really sure how to answer that...
It was half a year ago or so.
I got an invitation through a text from someone I don't know.
It said that there are no rules or restrictions in the group.
At first, I was skeptical that such a team exists.
But then I thought that it would be kinda cool if it did.
You know...
I don't like ordering people around, and vice versa.
So, what are the Dollars like?
Well, if I had to put it into words... 'Colorless'.
'Colorless'...?
Yeah.
They don't try and expand their influence by getting more people wearing the same color,
like the Yellow Scarves and the Blue Squares.
The Blue Squares?
They're a color gang that was really
influential when I was in middle school.
Wow...
I don't know much about them either,
but I heard they disbanded after causing some incident.
Kida-kun?
So I guess you like being in the Dollars then, Takiguchi?
Yeah.
Do you ever meet with any of the other members or anything?
Well, you only know the usernames of these 'members'.
I've met a few of them, though.
At my workplace, and randomly on the streets.
Though they were all coincidences.
It's like, when you get the feeling that they're part of the group, it turns out they are.
For example?
Well, I can't really explain.
Just ask them like you guys asked me.
I'm sure most of them will tell you.
Uh-oh.
See you slowpokes!
Ever since I found out that Takiguchi-kun was an actual Dollars member,
Mikado!
I decided not to tell anyone.
I know. I won't tell anyone.
I'm sure he wouldn't want for people to
make a big deal out of something like that.
Guys, take your seats!
Only the people who ask should have the right to know.
Rise.
Bow.
And that concludes the representative committee meeting.
I wonder if Kida-kun's disciplinary officer meeting is still ongoing.
I think it should be ending soon.
Slow down!
Harima Mika-san, who used to stalk Yagiri Seiji-kun,
has been missing since the day before the first day of school.
Did you find out anything about Harima-san after that?
No, nothing...
Ryugamine!
Kida told me to tell you to go on home without him!
Huh? Did something happen?
I heard he's in the middle of a heated debate going on at the disciplinary officer meeting!
Later!
Umm...
Well then, shall we go?
Okay.
I-I wonder what Kida-kun is arguing about...
Maybe about uniforms and hair restrictions and such?
Mikado!
You better listen to everything the babe has to say!
Introduce me to her next time, will ya?!
Good luck!
Later!
Uhh...
'Babe' is the name of this foreign person I met at "Russia Sushi"!
Umm...
S-S-She... she has a nose ring,
and Kida-kun must be arguing about nose rings in school!
You know, I've known about you for a long time.
Huh?
When I went to submit my school application,
there was this list at the front desk
where you can check off your name.
And just when I was thinking that it was a cool name,
I saw that someone had just added a check beside it.
And then it just so happened that we became classroom representatives together...
Hang on.
Isn't this like the situation between
Harima Mika-san and Yagiri Seiji-kun?
Stalkers are dangerous!
Well, I guess it's okay since she's so pretty?
But no, wait, it's still bad!
If something goes wrong...
I-I-I'll get stabbed?!
S-She may set my place on fire!
Wait... what if she takes my family hostage?
But if she has a good personality, I wouldn't mind her stalking me...
Hang on a second.
If she's stalking me, then that means she doesn't have a good personality!
I'm just kidding.
It would be troublesome for someone
like me to always be around you, right?
N-No...
Please rest assured.
I'm not a stalker.
N-No, well...
I apologize.
Huh?
Oh, no, I'm the one who was teasing you.
Please don't apologize.
Uhh...
Umm...
Umm... well...
I-I hope we'll be able to get along!
Y-Yes, my pleasure.
Hey!
Takeshi, it's that guy!
Huh?
Who's she talking about?
Can't be me, right?
I'm talking about YOU, dipshit!
What are you playing dumb for?!
U-Umm...
Who might you be?
I had to buy a new phone thanks to that friend of yours!
Umm, I'm not too sure I know what you mean...
So you're a friend of the guy who ruined my girlfriend's cell, right?
I... wouldn't call us 'friends', per say...
Then who is he, your dad?
Your guarantor?
I think you're a little off there...
Huh?
Huh? Huh?!
Are you lecturing me, punk?!
Let me teach you a thing or two
about "hierarchical relations"...!
What?!
So you brought your boyfriend because I don't hit girls?
How admirable of you.
I'd like to make you mine, but sorry, you're not my type.
So go home!
You're such a dick!
Bye!
Okay, Ryugamine Mikado-kun.
I was hiding and waiting for you by the
school gate because I wanted to see you.
I've got some business with you.
And by the way,
why is the black motorcycle woman here?
She must be looking for that girl!
Oh, gosh! I forgot!
I-I'm sorry! I'm in a rush today!
See you later, Sonohara-san.
Huh?
This is way too surreal...
But at this rate, these people will definitely follow me home.
And when that happens...
Help me!
U-Umm...
So...
If you need something from me, why don't we talk about it here.
My business can wait until after her's.
Hello?
Always happy to have your business.
Th-There's something I'd like to ask.
What is it?
So she can communicate...
Umm... who are you, exactly?
I'm looking for a relative of mine who went missing.
I found her yesterday, but she ran away for some reason.
W-What a terrible liar...
I-I'm sorry, I don't buy that.
How much do you know about me?
Well... that you're an urban legend,
and that you ride a motorcycle without headlights that doesn't make noise.
And...
...that you don't have a head.
And do you believe that?
Well... could you show me?
What's inside that helmet, I mean.
I was amazed I was even able to ask such a question.
Promise me you won't scream or anything?
But then again, I felt like...
...I'd been waiting for something like this to occur since a long time ago.
I still don't know how to describe the feelings I felt.
In my heart, I was repeating to myself,
"I knew it. I knew it."
Thank you very much!
And after that, the woman told me the real
reason why she was after that girl yesterday.
She told me that she was a dullahan by the name of Selty,
that she came to Japan to find her head that was stolen from her,
and that the girl who had the sewing marks on her neck looked exactly like her.
It's something that an ordinary person wouldn't believe,
but mysteriously, I believed every word.
Are you a friend of hers?
No, I just met her yesterday.
I asked question after question,
but she's seemingly lost her memories...
Selty-san?
Will you please let me see her?
She's afraid of you, probably because you started chasing her all of a sudden.
I want to see her no matter what!
Do you think you could somehow clear up her misunderstanding?
I'll try.
Gotta be fruit milkshake for lunch.
I think this is a sign that Biribiri's going to become the heroine!
No way! That position belongs to Himegami!
Don't fuck with me...
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?!
That bastard...
He scratched up my car with a pebble!!
Calm down, Togusa!
I won't forgive that son of a bitch!
You're running red lights! Red lights!!
Please wait here for a bit.
I'll go explain the situation to her.
I wouldn't want her to see you right away and for her to think that I betrayed her, Selty-san.
Roger that.
He's pretty careful, that one.
Huh...?
That was the first time I heard your name, by the way.
Never knew you were a foreigner.
Liar.
Throw a rock at my horse again and I'll make you pay.
That's a horse?
By the way...
...don't you think he's really taking his time?
Cleaners at such a beat-down apartment?
It couldn't be...!
I just want to know where the girl went.
This hair I found lying on the futon. This is a girl's hair, right?
I-I really don't know!
P-Please...!
Please, let me go!
You saw our faces, too.
We could get rid of you here and now.
Hey, someone's coming!
I-I'm saved...
You don't need to go after them.
I know where they came from.
I've seen that van before.
If I recall, those guys are from Yagiri Pharmacy.
Yagiri... Pharmacy?
Yup.
It's a company that's been doing poorly lately, and it's on the verge of being absorbed by a foreign company.
The girl with the scars who disappeared...
A dullahan...
There's been a lot of disappearances lately...
That was uncalled for.
Maybe the bodies haven't been found yet...
It could just be that no one's noticed them missing yet.
There's been a lot of disappearances lately...
Disappearances...
Harima Mika...
Yagiri Seiji...
There are even scarier rumors out there.
Really...?
And once they disappear, they're never found.
Human trafficking...
And... the Dollars.
What's he doing?
I hated living a normal life.
To be honest, I was half skeptical...
Please...
Lend me a hand for a second.
I wanted to live in a way unlike everyone else.
All the cards are in my hand.
That's why...
Jackpot.
I...
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My dear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My dear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My dear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Sturm und Drang
I hated living a normal life.
I wanted to live in a way unlike everyone else.
I had no idea that desire would end up
affecting the destinies of so many people.
Next time: Sturm und Drang.