My girl,
what is that lump of rock supposed to be?
It's a Jizou, not a rock!
A Jizou?
Right. It's a statue that protects kids from anything bad that happens.
Really? This thing does?
Do you hurl it at your enemies? It seems a tad heavy for a projectile.
No! We pray to it!
You'll bring down divine retribution if you say things like that, Dela.
Retribution?
Yeah. You'll go through something scary.
Something scary?
Just when I think I understand these people and their customs,
I chance upon some strange behavior, art, or words of theirs.
The more I learn, the less I know.
Baffling. Incomprehensible. Bizarre.
Retribution, eh?
Come on. We're going home.
Sorry, my girl.
It looks like I'll need some time to fully digest the deep impression this has left on me.
Geez. Don't stay out too late.
Off I go.
Dela?
Huh? Where is everyone?
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
So, I stood outside Tamaya at 10 o'clock and spent an hour counting the people who walked past.
Only 13 people passed by in that time!
The heck?!
What the hell're you doin'? Did you even do your homework?!
Let her speak, Dai.
I think this means that not enough people are coming to our market.
It's only a little summer slump.
It's just that time of the year, Tamako.
No one likes going outside when it's this hot, right?
This is where that flyer I handed out earlier comes into play!
I thought up a strategy that'd let people blow off their summer fatigue or heatstroke.
Blow away
summer
fatigue!
Market
Strategy
Blow away
summer
fatigue!
What's this, Tamako?
Natto?
It's natto.
Her name's Kifune!
Kifu?
As far as I'm concerned, you can't have summer without a haunted house!
A haunted house?!
Blow away
summer
fatigue!
Episode 6
I Felt Shivers Down My Spine Too
Welcome!
Hello!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
So you're here too.
Over here!
What's birdbrain doing here?
Birdbrain?! How rude!
By the way, I don't see Shiori.
Is she running late, perhaps?
She's not coming.
She's at a training camp with the Badminton Club.
Wh-What?!
What about Ooji?
Field trip, but I don't think he wanted to go.
Aw, poor guy.
Anyway, I wrote down all the ideas I could come up with.
Haunted
House
plan
Haunted
House
plan
Haunted
House
plan
Haunted
House
plan
Haunted
House
plan
Haunted
House
plan
Ooh, lemme see!
Are you okay?
Sorry about that. I guess I really can't stand birds.
She says she can't stand you.
So, where are we doing it?
Usa Bath said they'd let us use their storehouse.
Really? That's great!
Hey, Dela! What scares you?
Huh?
If you tell us what you find scary, we can use it for the haunted house!
What's a "haunted house" in the first place?
What?! We have to start from there?!
It's a house that's haunted!
Haunted?
That's not much of an explanation, Tamako.
Just a sec.
I looked it up on the Internet.
Whoa, nasty!
Wait! Hold it right there!
So a "haunted house" is somewhere people go to get scared?
Did they get punished?! Is it divine retribution?!
Retribution?
No, it's not punishment!
You know how you get chills down your spine when you're scared?
That's the fun part!
Huh? Being scared is fun?
Don't tell me you derive enjoyment of a carnal natur—
What're you talking about?!
The right amount of fear can spice up one's life.
Just like the suspension bridge effect.
The human heart's a strange, mysterious thing.
Little kids'll be visiting too, so let's keep safety in mind.
You're right. We'll need to watch out for lost kids as well.
Don't you mean "missing"?
Huh?
Just saying.
But it does happen, right?
Kids that previously disappeared show up in the night and—
Hey, stop that!
Just kidding.
Didn't sound like you were kidding at all!
Sorry. I just had to add to the creepy atmosphere.
Hey, record guy!
Please don't play such weird music!
This place has been collecting dust since spring.
Will it do?
Perfectly!
Right, Kanna?
Call me Kanna the Measurer!
Oh, she came prepared!
Impressive!
We'll have to make sure we use as much space as we can.
Looks like we'll be doing more than we thought!
Yeah!
Done measuring.
Assuming a winding course,
we'd need approximately 200 cardboard boxes to make everything.
What? That many?
If it's cardboard boxes you need, leave it to me!
Excuse me.
This is a message to everyone in Usagiyama Market.
Please supply as many cardboard boxes or materials as you can to help with Tamako's plan.
I can bring a few more if you want.
Thank you!
I don't need these anymore, but I figured you could make good use of them.
Sounds good!
I made copies of the flyer!
So you want us to hand these out to visitors?
Haunted
House
Wanna
come?
Natto again.
I'd like to see Shiori again,
but I don't want her to think that I have some strange fear-based perversion!
To deliver this flyer, or not to deliver this flyer... That is the question.
Oh no! This is bad!
You're right. This is bad.
It is?
Very bad.
We'd better do something.
This is a matter that requires careful consideration.
Hm?
Sis.
What?
Where's Dela?
Flyer
He's taking Midori and Kanna home.
Huh?!
Flyer
I wanted to ask him to deliver this flyer...
There, there.
Flyer
Wait. What's that?
Huh?
Weeping willow.
Looks like cherry blossoms.
They're cherry blossoms that are trying to become a weeping willow!
So they're cherry blossoms.
I'm wasting my time, aren't I?
Can you really attract visitors with that attitude?
You'll come, won't you?
If you come, we'll make it three times as scary...
No, five times! Just for you!
I think I'll pass.
Whoops, I forgot my towel.
What the?
I'm tellin' the truth!
Seriously?
Totally.
I saw two fireballs!
Sure you weren't just drunk?
No. I don't drink.
Oh, right. Boring guy.
It's not just me.
Mrs. Uotani said she saw something too.
A salaryman.
On his way home from work.
Totally covered in blood!
Why does this have to happen?
Until now, our market was as peaceful and carefree as could be!
Could this be a curse?
Curse?!
Hey, stop that!
Don't they say you have to perform a purifying ritual whenever you tell the story of Oiwa?
Oh, right! The purifying ritual!
Did anyone do it?
Mr. Yumoto, this year's purifying ritual...
Nobody's performed one!
That's...
For real?
Oh no!
No way!
And on top of all this, we have a haunted house...
That means we have to perform exorcising rituals for ghosts, specters, demons, and apparitions!
Hey, that's just somethin' the kids're doin'.
What are the kids doing?
T-Tamako!
Geez, Dad. What are you wasting time here for?
Oh yeah, Tamako! Actually...
Let's not tell Tamako about this.
Hey, what if she gets cursed?
But she was looking forward to it so much!
Do you want to make her sad?!
It's all right!
We'll all protect Tamako!
Protect me from what?
Nothing! It's got nothing at all to do with you!
That's right. You don't have to worry about a thing!
Done!
Wow, that was quick!
How's it going?
Wait a sec.
Curse you.
What does one do with this thing?
You put a nail in it! Scary, right?
Oh, I see! It's hard to see the tips of one's wings in the dark!
That's not it exactly.
Tamako, you here?
I brought you some snacks!
Wow, thank you very much!
What's this, skipjack tuna?
It's garlic. Garlic's delicious!
Eat loads of garlic!
Oh, and have this too.
My, that looks so cute!
Er...
Oh, but...
You don't have a Dracula, do you?
Should we? I guess we could...
No! You don't need one! At all!
Well, be care—
Do your best!
Okay...
Ta-ma-ko!
You ca-ll-ed?
Got something for you. We thought you might need a few decorations.
Wow! Thank you so much!
Oh no! I ended up bringing alcohol!
Oh my.
What was I thinking? They're all underage!
Well, since I already brought it here, might as well pour some around.
Pour it?
Both bottles?!
There! That's the last spot!
All right. We'll be off.
O-Okay.
Now it reeks of alcohol.
Here we are.
How'd it go?
I wish you all could've seen my Oscar-worthy performance!
Okay, you're up next.
N-No, I'm...
Go make an impression, okay?
My daughter and the whole market's future rests on this.
Don't worry. We'll pick up your corpse!
Now go show them how much of a man you are!
Welcome.
Heatstroke!
Pardon?
Salt.
Uh, right. Salt.
Salt!
Heatsalt!
What on Earth?
I think he's trying to say, "Make sure you keep up your salt intake, or you'll get heatstroke!"
That's exactly right!
Take this too.
I'll be off now.
Th-Thanks.
The people here bring the weirdest things, don't they?
Yup! But I'm glad to see they care!
This... looks somewhat like an altar.
Tamako Market
Curse you
Thanks again!
I hear you're doing a haunted house?
Th-That's right.
Here you go!
Come again!
Oh, you're doing a haunted house?
Are you gals planning on going?
N-No, we're not.
Excuse me.
Keep this between the two of us, but I've seen them!
I mean, we clean up the bathhouse floor time and time again,
but these wet footprints keep showing up!
I've seen them!
This is weird.
I prepared udon noodles,
but there are some missing!
Who did this?
No way! Is this a curse too?!
Man, it's so hot!
Ah, nice and cool.
I feel so refreshed!
Oh no, I fell asleep!
What's this? The flowers have bloomed!
Something strange...
...is happening...
...in this market!
They say weird things are appearing!
Seriously?
What's this about?
Exit
Entrance
Got the other side?
Yeah. Good to go.
Hello.
Oh, Shiori!
What? Shiori?!
Shiori!
Exit
Entrance
I brought some snacks.
Tasty!
Croquettes from Shiori truly are divine.
I hope you'll all relish the taste.
Whatever you say.
So you're doing a haunted house.
Yup. Wanna check it out?
It's more or less done.
Huh?
Good idea.
We need someone to check it out from a visitor's point of view.
In that case,
I shall give it a once over as well.
Would you mind joining me, Shiori?
I hear there's a jinx that lets people get closer when they enter a haunted house together.
What the heck?
I told him about it on our way home the other day.
I wouldn't mind if the two of us grew a little closer!
I guess that's okay...
All right! Now that it's decided,
let's give Shiori a thousand curses!
Curses?
That's right.
We'll curse you to the ends of the world!
The world!
Bring it on!
Such tricks are nothing compared to our love—
Nooooooo!
Hey, was it scary?!
Yup.
You didn't look too scared, though.
No, it was scary.
But what scared me the most was that bird's screams.
Hey, what's this?
We're doing a haunted house. Here's a flyer.
Give me one too.
M-Me too!
Sure thing.
Usagiyama Market's chilly scheme is sure to get everyone screaming!
Please come check out the haunted house!
I hope no one gets hurt today at the haunted house and everyone has fun.
Usagiyama Market
Haunted House
What's this?
Don't tell me it's a curse?!
Stop it, Mr. Yumoto!
Doesn't it look more like a blessing?
A blessing?
What?!
We open in 20 minutes!
Please wait just a little longer!
We should really tell Tamako about this.
If she finds out the hard way, it'll be too late.
Hey, this is where they show up, right?
Huh?
Ghosts!
Huh?!
Tamako!
Mind giving us a minute?
Scary!
Fireballs scary!
Salaryman scary!
Right! And the footprints!
And the udon noodles!
And the flowers!
Something strange's happening in this market!
N-No way!
But isn't that all perfectly normal?
Huh?
Leaving footprints at the bathhouse,
putting out some of the noodles for stray cats,
flowers blooming after they're taken out of cold storage...
It's all perfectly normal, isn't it?
How can she be so calm in that outfit?!
But come to think of it, she's right!
What? It's all resolved?!
That was fast!
Thanks, Shiori!
Now we can hold our haunted house without any worries!
I didn't do anything!
That's our Shiori!
But what about the fireball and the salaryman?
Usagiyama Market
Haunted House
We're currently cursing the last crowd, so please wait a little longer.
Are you okay? Want me to take over?
Nah, I'm fine.
Wow, what a huge crowd!
Oh, if it isn't Asagiri.
Mr. Yagi!
A haunted house, eh?
That's great.
Smells like teen spirit.
Oh, right. This here's my wife.
And this is one of my students.
Pleased to meet you. Things've really taken off, huh?
They have. Thanks to everyone.
Oh?
Will you be okay, Tadashi?
Of course I will!
I'll protect you, so don't worry!
Let's have him show all of us his cool side!
Go ahead.
Wow, this is really well-made!
My students are pretty good!
All thanks to their teacher, of course.
Just kidding.
Come on, Juuko.
Geez, you're such a scaredy-cat—
Curse you!
A ghost!
Juuko! This place is dangerous!
Curse you!
Cold!
Mr. Traveler, sir,
could you hold on to this child for me?
She's a quiet kid who won't be any trouble...
No! That's too much!
We're leaving, Juuko!
Oh wow, this is so well-made.
Gotta head for...
the exit!
Curse you! Curse you! Curse you!
You guys are great.
That was really fun.
U-Um...
Sorry. Tadashi's always like this.
Good job!
That was so hot!
Good work, everyone.
Huh? What's wrong?
Three croquettes, please!
Coming right up!
Here you go.
We got a bit sweaty, so do you wanna stop by the bathhouse?
Let's go check out the florist.
Fine by me!
Good thing we did this, right?
Yup!
It's a roaring success!
Hey, come on, we're all sweaty!
Well, everyone...
A toast to the haunted house's success!
Cheers!
I told you everything would turn out all right!
That's the first time I've heard you say it.
I made some seared skipjack tuna!
Great work, Tamako! You did an amazing job!
Oh, not at all! It was thanks to everyone who helped out!
What's with you?!
Flattery'll getcha nowhere, you know?
Don't act so shy.
Here, a toast.
Like I said, I don't drink!
That so?
Shiori. That was fun, was it not?
Yeah. I'm glad so many people came to see it.
That ghost ruckus happened at just the right time.
Yeah, it got everyone's attention.
But I still don't understand the fireball
nor the salaryman covered in blood.
Oh, that was me.
Huh?!
What?!
What're you talking about?!
Looking at the market in the middle of our summer slump made me think,
"This is bad. Nobody's gonna show up."
So I thought I could put our feathered friend to good use.
It happened on the way home that other day.
Well, see you tomorrow!
'Kay. Bye-bye!
Hey, Mr. Bird. I'll be fine from here.
Really?
Well then, be careful on your own, my girl.
Oh, hold on, Mr. Bird.
Could you return this can of paint to the storehouse?
Very well. I shall.
Also, I hear there's a jinx that lets people get closer when they enter a haunted house together.
Huh?
Why don't you go in with Shiori?
Ah. I-Is that so?
I'll think about it.
Take care on your way home!
Mr. Bird!
You're going the wrong way!
I was hoping someone would see Mr. Bird frolicking about and get the wrong impression.
Someone easily fooled.
That was you?!
What about the salaryman?
That was just paint.
Just having it splatter over the ground would've been enough, but...
Huh? Rain?
As if!
Thanks, Mr. Bird.
There's a schemer among us!
You're awesome, Kanna!
She is not!
I'm sorry, Mr. Bird.
If apologies were enough, we wouldn't need birdcages!
C'mon, it's all good.
You got to go in with Shiori.
That's good, but it's not all good!
She toyed with my pure heart! Unforgivable!
Look out, Dela!
Dela!
Dela! Are you doing okay, Dela?
Choi's on her way there, so take care of her.
Also—
What?!
Who's on whose way where?!
Is something coming?
A huge fuss, an uproar.
But all's well that ends well.
Now all I want to do is sleep.
This is...
a projectile to hurl at one's enemies!
And this scent is...
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
I love all that is springy!
Tamako here.
Bracken-starch mochi's great for when it's hot, too!
Do you prefer soy flour? Or maybe brown sugar syrup?
I'm the kind who chooses "all of the above"!
Episode 7    She Became A Bride!
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?