When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Mistress Kuzuha, please reconsider
and give me a chance!
The Modernistic Cast Iron Top Toy Butler!
No, me, the Cyborg Wheeled Insect Butler!
No, me, the Mountain Bike Combat Butler!
No, to tell the truth,
I am a bit tired of this.
Y-You can't mean that!
Sion, as I recall, our school's
culture fest is coming up, is it not?
Yes! Various groups are starting
to prepare their stalls as well.
Like sweets shops.
Then it is time to go snack plundering!
Oh!
One moment please!
I, the second assassin of the "Mysterious
Butler – Non-Kids' Hobby Faction"
will defeat Hayate Ayasaki.
Do not make me repeat myself.
I said I have tired of this.
I have a gift I would very much like
to present to you, Mistress Kuzuha.
Oh! Those are from the cake shop featured
on that Admatic show the other day!
Mm, you are quite good. Do as you like.
Yes, Mistress.
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Read it backwards or forwards,
"KO-TO-KO" still reads as "KO-TO-KO"...
Um, we're not forming a band
or anything, all right?
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Why?! Academy Culture Fest – Part 1
It's done! I managed to
finish it just in time somehow.
2007 Hakuou Academy Culture Fest
All right.
Today, I am definitely getting back
to the estate to see the Miss.
Oh? Hayata, where are you going?
The school building is that way, you know.
What?
Festival loving Miss
Committee Chairman, Red!
Vice Chairman, Blue!
Disciplinary committee member, Black!
Together, the three of us are...
...the student body council!
Come shake our hands
at the culture fest hall!
Ooh!
G-Good morning.
I never imagined you would really
complete the arch overnight.
Yes, it was worth it for us to twiddle
our thumbs until the last minute
before we begged you for help.
If we hadn't made it on time, we
would've gotten a real earful from Hina.
Well, I'm glad we were able to
salvage the situation somehow.
I need to get going now...
What?
Hey, where do you think you're going?
We still need you to do
work in the classroom, too.
What? Uh, um...
We feel bad for making you work hard alone.
This is the least we can do
to make up for it.
Let us sweat by your side together!
Senzu Beans
H-Here you are!
It's to thank you for the arch.
We're really, really counting on you, okay?
Then shall we hurry along?
We should get ready to open shop soon.
Ooh!
That's Hayata for you. So understanding.
All right! Away we go!
2007 Hakuou Academy Culture Fest
Oh, Nagi, what are you doing here?
Yonday
Magical Destroy
Nagi Sanzenin
Isn't it obvious? It's a solo culture fest.
I-I think her interpretation
of "culture" is a bit off...
Oh, that reminds me. Hakuou Academy's
culture fest starts today, doesn't it?
I wonder if Hayate had to
stay overnight again last night.
Yes, it appears that way.
I expect he's had a ton
of work foisted off on him,
because he's unable to say "no".
I swear! He should only be so good-natured!
Hayate's supposed to be my butler.
He shouldn't work so hard for everyone...
I see.
If it bothers you that much,
why don't you go to the culture fest?
Wha?! I-It's not really bothering me.
I hate crowds anyway.
I hear Hayate is doing
a cosplay café with the class.
I imagine he's doing
a splendid job about now.
A c-cosplay café, huh?
Customer
What? An order? I despair of this world!
Teacher! I mean, Master!
"No, no, I'm still far from it."
Well, no helping it then.
If you're that worried
about Hayate's safety...
All right, I will go myself
and do a bit of scouting.
Yes, please do.
Call the SP. I'll be leaving
as soon as I get changed.
Nagi still has such a childish side to her.
N-No, perhaps that is not so true...
Th-This is...
The Hakuou Academy culture fest:
a gigantic event held once every year
that is a specialty of Ward S
in the Metropolitan area.
After all, it's a super prestigious school,
so an endless roster of
politicians, businessmen,
and distinguished people
from all walks of life come to visit.
Surpassing the scope
of a simple school festival,
they get fabulous guests
participating as well.
Furthermore, the level of their
research presentations is so high,
even industrial spies and intelligence
agencies from various countries
supposedly quietly take note.
KA-BOOM
It's just a totally cultural
and festive three days!
Might I ask for another
cup of royal milk tea?
Certainly. Please wait a moment, Miss.
Yes, how may I help you?
Ah, you there, bring us
more tea over here as well.
On the double, in a pot.
Yes, right away.
Wait! Um, you three, why are you
playing a leisurely game of cards?!
Well, you are just so brisk
and alert, we cannot keep up.
Revolution!
We feel kind of bad
getting in the way of a pro.
Counterrevolution!
D-Don't say that! Please work!
Besides, this isn't a cosplay
café. It's a butler café.
Huh? But we are in costumes.
Um, could it be that you planned
to make me handle everything
and that's why you made it a butler café?
I cannot say I approve
of such paranoia, Hayata.
A-All right, now that we've recharged,
shall we get serious now?
Y-Yeah!
Thanks for your hard work, Hayata.
You can rest for a while.
In that case, I'm going to
make a run back to the estate.
Ayasaki, are you here?!
You're here, aren't you?!
Oh, Miss Katsura...
There you are!
If you're here...
...COME!
Right now!
Hey, wait...
Oh, Little Nagi!
Hey there, Hayate.
I'll have you know, it's not like I came
because I wanted to see you.
I'm only here because Maria asked me
to come check on things...
If it's Hayata, he's not here.
What?
He got taken away by Yukiji.
What? Hayate's not here?!
After I came all this way to see him?!
The Superintendent does not appear
to be making any unusual moves at this time.
Roger that. But don't let your guard down.
Yes, ma'am.
Given this rowdy atmosphere,
there's no way she's going to behave...
Ayasaki, what about this?
You do this with that, and this
with that! Omitting the rest!
Um, what about this?
Get it stamped at HQ, on the double!
Ayasaki, you know, you know...
I only have 500 yen right now,
but between octopus balls and a
Japanese pizza, which should I buy?
I wouldn't know.
Sis!
Huh?
What is this?!
Why is Hayate managing things
here for all he's worth?
That's your job as the
advising teacher, isn't it?
W-Well, you know...
I didn't really know how
to answer all the questions.
And it's a pain.
Sis!
I-I'm sorry!
Haruko, can I ask you to handle things here?
I do not mind.
Thank you.
Hayate, come with me for a sec.
What? But I'm still in the middle
of giving instructions...
Um, Miss Harukaze, this...
Make the judgment call yourself.
Um, what about this?
That will not be recognized as an expense!
Receipt
Here.
It's thanks for taking care of my officers.
Um, why...?
Because it's written all over
your face that you're hungry.
It's fine that you're good-natured,
but you're going to collapse
if you push yourself too hard.
Hinagiku!
H-Hayate?
H-Hayate!
What is it, Jör? Try not to
eat stuff off the ground too much.
Superintendent!
Hayate in danger!
And in the meantime, Mademoiselle Nagi was...
Sheesh! That Hayate!
Where is he? And what is he doing?
SPs, split up and look for Hayate.
I'm tired, so I'm going to stay here and...
H-Huh? Hey! Everyone?!
Where did you go?!
Hayate, you jerk...
After I took the plunge
to leave the residence, too...
I wanted to...
I wanted to walk around
and see the festival with you...
You there, the young lady
with the pigtails...
Fortune Telling
If you would like, why
don't you drop by for a bit?
Fortune Telling
I have no use for scams.
Now, now, don't say that.
My fortunes are 100 accurate, you know.
What?
Compatibility Fortunes
Super specialized in mistress-butler relations!
I-I see.
I guess I'll kill a little time
while I take a break.
It wouldn't be bad to reconfirm
the strength of my bond with Hayate.
Very well.
Then first, please look deep into my eyes.
Hm? Like this?
Ah... I can see... into your forlorn heart.
I will help myself to the opening
in your heart and take advantage of it.
I'll listen to you, just once...
Nagi Sanzenin, you
are now my just-once puppet!
Sweet potatoes! Roasted sweet potatoes!
(Ishi-yaki imo! Oimo!)
Oh, honestly, just a little, okay?
(Mou, chotto dake yo?)
Hayate, are you all right?
W-Well, somehow...
Oh, here's a souvenir.
So you were immersed in Jör's
digestive fluids and you are still fine...
What? Jör?
Jörmungandr. That is his name.
His favorite foods are the five lands,
three seas, and all living things.
He really enjoys butlers in particular.
What?
That was a joke.
Since this is a time slot
that is supposed to cater to youths.
But that didn't seem like a joke to me...
And what is up with
that suspicious-looking outfit?
Superintendent, what
are you plotting out here?
Nothing. I am simply off duty right now.
Ahem! Simply off duty!
Though, I would not object,
if someone were to entertain me.
That reminds me, boy,
I hear you spurned your prize of
100 school credits from the butler battle.
Your reason?
What? That was, well...
I didn't really have a need for it
a-and from an education stand point,
it wouldn't have been good for the Miss...
"Miss"!
"Miss"! "Miss"!
Is the "Miss" the only thing
that you have in your life?!
What?
You are a duller man than I had thought.
Enough already!
Let us forget about this guy!
Please excuse me.
Hello?
Hayate, you wouldn't happen to be
with Nagi, would you?
What? Does that mean
the Miss is here at school?
Yes, she should've
arrived quite a while ago,
but it seems she forgot her cell phone
and so I tried to get in touch
with the members of the SP, but...
I want to believe
Power of flower
Erina, you're the best.
You're the best. You're the best.
With arms wide open
Erina, you're the best. You're the best.
Like giving a tight hug...
Is something wrong, Hayate?
Y-Yes, it seems the Miss has gone missing.
Huh? What are you saying?
She's been right there for a while now.
Huh?
Whoa! There you are!
M-Miss?
Hayate, there's somewhere I want you
to come with me for a bit.
Th-There clearly seems to be
something serious going on...
Yes...
Anyway, I have something urgent
to attend to now, so excuse me.
Wait, I'll come, too.
Um, Mistress Kuzuha,
could that possibly be...?
Mm-hm, it is his doing.
He has done better than expected.
This is getting interesting!
We are going after them, Sion!
Oh, my blood sugar level is still...
M-Mistress Kuzuha!
Hayate, there's somewhere I want you
to accompany me for a bit.
No matter how you look at it,
she's in that hypnotic state
you see a lot in manga and stuff, huh?
Yes...
I don't know who did this,
but how dare they do this to the Miss?!
Oh, she stopped for some reason!
Hayate, all that aside,
Japanese Pizza
I want to try some of this food with you.
E-Excuse me, I'd like one, please!
Sure! It's tasty!
Hey, is she really hypnotized?
With the bewildered pair in tow,
Miss Nagi aimlessly paraded
all over the academy and...
This is not the place.
Nor here.
Nor is it here.
Yes, this is the place.
This is where I wanted to bring you.
Th-This is the old school building?
Then why didn't you
bring us here to begin with?!
Hey! I let you manipulate me just once!
Thank you for your hard work, Nagi Sanzenin!
You did well to follow my order
and lure Hayate Ayasaki out for me!
Uh, does this count as being "lured out"?
That outfit... Could it be that you're...?!
Indeed!
They call me the Mysterious Butler
of Darkness, Just-Once Puppeteer!
But that's just exactly what you are!
Hey, what in the world is this?
Miss, please snap out of it!
It's me! It's Hayate!
Hayate, I wanted to see
the festival together with you.
It's no fun being alone...
Miss!
That's right!
I have to catch that guy quickly
and make him undo the hypnosis!
This Week's Butler Battle
What?!
A-A robot?!
Hayate Ayasaki, I will defeat you
and restore our mistress's
faith in us, without fail!
Miss!
What the heck is this?! H-How big is this?!
S-Sis?!
Hayate, I'll handle that guy!
You look after Nagi.
Wait, uh, where did
that bamboo sword come from?
Anyone who disturbs the academy's
peace has to answer to me!
D-Don't tell me you mean to fight
the robot with a bamboo sword!
Darn! Scurrying all over the place!
Head!
Th-This girl got the camera!
Firing anchor!
H-Hinagiku!
You're mine!
Wh-What?!
Ow, that hurt...
Hinagiku, please don't be so reckless!
But I just found him unforgivable.
Now, give up the fight
and come on out quietly!
I will now expect you
to undo the Miss's hypnosis!
In your dreams. The fight is just beginning!
I will destroy Hakuou Academy!
Warning
Shoot! The sparks and firing
the jet have affected the adhesive!
What?
Um, uh...
This can't be...
But the Miss...
Nagi!
I swear, that Hayate...
It is no fun alone...
To hell with the culture fest...
I absolutely hate this culture fest!
I knew it...
Is she still hypnotized?
I am the queen of the true culture of Japan.
I will...
I will show you what true culture is!
T-True...
...culture?
It is this!
It does not just belong
in the summer and winter!
Autumn is the season
for festivals to begin with!
Autumn should have a new
Japanese culture festival as well!
That is quite interesting!
Superintendent!
Nagi Sanzenin, was it not?
You are far more promising
than that butler boy.
What?
I would love for you to show me
this true festival of yours.
Sure.
M-Miss!
Um...
Do not follow me. I do not need dinner.
And make sure you record
that late night show.
What in the world...?
Hey, is that really hypnosis?
Next time, a new culture fest will be held.
Of all people, they will be
fighting Miss Nagi!
Incidentally...
Oh, the boiled egg...
They were in the midst
of their sports fest today.
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate...
Ayumu Nishizawa's
Lettering by Mikako Takahashi
and Ayumu Nishizawa's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Spirit Transformation! I am Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I am Ayumu Nishizawa.
Then let us get right to the long-awaited
fan service shot of the hamster.
Wow, this is exciting.
Nooo!
This is a powerful photo taken
at a certain ramen shop in Suginami Ward.
Super Big Bowl
Finish the Ramen and It's Free!
Will she finish eating it in time?!
It's truly a photo about pushing the limit!
Aw, no fair. Boohoo.
Well, it's very like you,
so I think it's good in its way.
Oh, Hayate!
Then see you again!
Preview
Um, this is the Hakuou Academy, right?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Right? Don't you think
it's a weird building?
As of now, we will vend
Nagi Sanzenin's doujinshi
at a specially prepared
booth in the Academy.
Ayasaki, if your doujinshi wins
against ours by selling better...
In other words, this
is a doujinshi sales competition?
There is no way my manga
will lose against you!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Why Dead?! Academy Culture Fest – Part 2".
Next Hayate the Combat Butler
Why Dead?! Academy Culture Fest – Part 2
Did you know?
At the world's largest doujinshi fair venue,
it's hard to get through on your cell phone.