Homura-chan, I'm sorry.
I'm going to become a magical girl.
Madoka...
You can't!
I finally know what I want.
I've found the wish I want granted.
And for that wish, I'll pay with my life.
Stop it!
Then why did I...
Why did I even do all of this...
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I believe I'm standing here because you've wanted to protect me, because you cared for me this whole time.
This is the answer I've finally found.
Believe in me.
I won't squander who you've become and what you've done for me.
Madoka...
Now that you control the fate of many worlds and have become a singularity for cause and effect,
I should be able to grant you your wish, no matter how absurd it is.
You're telling the truth, correct?
Now, Kaname Madoka, with your soul as reparation, for what shall you wish?
I...
I want to eliminate all witches before their birth.
Every single witch in every universe, under my own power, past and future.
If that wish... If that wish comes true, we won't just be talking temporal manipulation anymore!
You'd be opposing the very laws of causality themselves!
Do you really plan to become a god?
I don't care what you call it.
I don't want any of the girls that have fought witches until now—all the magical girls who believed in hope—to cry.
I want them to remain smiling to the end.
I'll destroy any rule that stands in my way.
I'll change them all.
This is my wish, my desire.
Now grant me this, Incubator!
Final Episode                My best friend
Kaname-san, do you know just how daunting that wish is?
Probably.
You'll be fighting forever, past and future, for all time.
It means you'll cease to exist as an individual.
It won't be anything nice like dying.
You'll be firmly implanted in this universe as the concept of destroying witches itself.
That's fine.
That was my plan anyway.
If you told me it was wrong to harbor hope, I would tell you that it wasn't wrong. I'd say it as many times as necessary.
I'd keep saying it forever.
Why not?
If you can do it, then why not?
You've found a reason to fight, right?
You decided not to run away.
Then fine.
The only thing left is for you to do what you gotta do.
Yeah.
Thanks, Kyouko-chan.
Well, I guess that means I have to give something of yours back.
Here you go.
You're not going to make people's hopes come true;
you're going to become hope itself—the hope for all of us.
I won't let all of your wishes end in despair.
None of you will haunt people.
None of you will curse anyone.
I'll bear the fate of you all.
So please, believe in yourselves until the end.
It's okay.
It's okay now.
You don't have to hate anyone anymore.
You don't have to curse anyone anymore.
I'll assume your burden before you take that form.
Where am I...
The universe is being rearranged to fit in line with the new laws Madoka has brought forth.
Ah yes, you were a user of magic capable of transversing time, as well.
How about we watch together then? And see the final result of the person called "Kaname Madoka."
That's the Soul Gem her wish has yielded.
That's...
Do you understand just how much despair Madoka must bear as a result of her immense wish?
Almost enough hope was provided to create an entire new universe.
That means, in turn, there was enough despair generated to end an entire universe.
An obvious outcome, right?
Don't worry. It's okay.
My wish was to erase all witches.
If that really came true, then even I have no reason to feel despair any further!
Your life now has no beginning or end, Madoka.
There is no longer any proof that you have lived, nor memories of your being here.
Your existence has shifted to a higher plane and become nothing more than a concept.
No one can perceive you any longer, and likewise, you cannot interact with anyone else.
You have ceased to be a member of this universe.
What are you saying?!
Are you trying to say this is the conclusion Madoka wanted?
Are you trying to say this ending granted her wish?!
You can't be serious!
This is worse than dying...
It's worse...
No, you're wrong, Homura-chan.
I can see all of the past and future now.
All of the universes that once were and those that might come to be. All of them.
Madoka...
That's why I know.
I know just how hard you tried to help me through all that time.
I know everything.
Just how many times you cried, even while getting hurt...
And it was all for me.
I'm sorry I didn't notice until now.
I really am.
I was able to know the real you because I ended up this way.
I found out I had a great friend by my side the whole time.
So I'm really happy.
Homura-chan, thank you.
You were my best friend.
But now you can't return and you'll be separated from everyone you care about!
And now you're just going be trapped here alone for all eternity!
I'm not alone.
Everyone... Everyone will always be with me.
From now on, I'll be everywhere—any time, right there.
That's why even if you can't see me, can't hear me, I'll be right there, by your side.
Madoka... that's okay with you?
Even though I'll forget you?
Even though I won't be able to know you're there?
It's too early to give up.
You followed me here.
So even if you return to the old world,
you just might still remember me.
It'll be fine.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
We just have to believe.
Madoka...
Magical girls make hopes and dreams come true, after all.
I'm sure if it's small enough, a real miracle just might happen.
Isn't that right?
Madoka, don't go!
I'm sorry. I have to go meet up with everyone else.
I'll be able to see you again someday.
So until then, we'll be apart for a little bit.
Madoka!!
Number 25, Kamijou Kyousuke.
I'll be playing Ave Maria.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
No, I'm sorry too.
In order to save you, I wouldn't have had any choice but to make it so that nothing ever happened.
Except if I did that, this version of the future would disappear too.
But I had a feeling that's not really what you wanted to happen.
Your wish and how hard you tried because of it is really precious to me—I don't think it was pointless in the end at all. So that's why...
Yeah.
This'll be fine.
I just wanted to hear him play one more time.
I wanted more people to hear his violin.
Just remembering that feeling is enough for me.
I don't have any regrets left.
Well, I am a bit upset about how things turned out.
I can't help the way things went with Hitomi-chan.
She's way too good for him,
but she'll make him happy, won't she?
Yeah.
Let's get going, shall we?
Sayaka?
Where's Sayaka?
Hey! What happened to Sayaka?!
She's gone.
She was guided away by the "Law of the Wheel."
Miki-san used all of her power in that last attack, didn't she?
Idiot. What good is it disappearing for some dude you fell in love with?
Dummy... We finally became friends.
That's the fate of a magical girl.
Before the result of having sought out a wish brings despair upon this world,
we have to disappear like that.
Madoka...
Akemi-san?
Madoka? Who's that?
Who?
Madoka
Madoka!
Yep. That looks just like her.
Hey, Tatsuya. You can't do that.
You can't pull a woman's hair.
Madoka! Madoka!
I'm sorry, are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm sorry for stopping you two.
Madoka, right?
Yeah!
Here I go!
Bring it on!
That invisible friend of his when he plays by himself?
Pretty common for children, I guess.
Yeah, I remember her, too.
You know Madoka, too?
Is she a character from some anime or something?
I'm not sure.
I think I kind of remember hearing about her.
I see.
I wonder if I saw her somewhere with Tatsuya at some point.
Sometimes the name really sounds familiar.
Madoka...
I see.
Those ribbons are really cute!
Something I'd really like.
I'm kind of surprised.
Would you like them?
They wouldn't look good on an old lady like me.
Though if I had a daughter or something, I might have let her wear them.
I see.
What you're saying would make a decent hypothesis for everything.
It's not a hypothesis. It's what happened.
Even if it were, there'd be no way to prove it.
If the rules of the universe were rewritten like you've said, we'd have no means of verifying it.
If you're the only one who has memories of that, then it'd be no different from a dream that only you had.
Well, it is true that even we haven't been able to figure out why Soul Gems that can no longer be purified disappear.
If you think about it that way, the concept of witches you mentioned in your story is pretty interesting.
It is quite an appealing way to collect human emotional energy.
If something that good existed, the Incubators' tactics may have been pretty different.
True. You guys are like that.
In the world you mentioned, the magical beasts we're fighting didn't exist, right?
Isn't this a much quicker way of gathering up curses?
It wasn't that simple.
We weren't exactly on the greatest of terms with you all, either.
I really don't get human values at all.
Even though we're living in a world where witches are no longer born,
that alone wouldn't put an end to the curses which humans harbor towards the world.
The distortions created by cause and effect have changed forms and still attack people from the shadows.
The "bad air" sure is thick tonight.
Those magical beasts are popping up one after another.
There's no end to them, no matter how many we kill.
Complaining won't get us anywhere.
Let's go.
This may be a world with no salvation, where nothing but sadness and hate repeats itself,
but even so, this was a place that she once tried to protect.
I remember,
and I'll never forget.
That's why I'll keep fighting.
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll walk upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Keep it up.
Yeah.