Mizuki Himeji is diligent
in everything she does.
Like today, when she is
researching on an unfamiliar topic.
"How to deliver a love letter.
As expected, it's best to give it in person.
It'll convey your feelings better
--and will increase the possibility
of getting a good response."
--Himeji! Are you studying?
--and will increase the possibility of getting a good response."
"Throb Counter"
Huh? Yoshii!
Ah, yes. I was just researching something.
Oh yeah! If I boldly give it to him now...
Y... Yoshii...
To tell you the truth... This... is for you!
Uhm...
P... Please don't laugh.
Ahh! That wasn't it!
How is this funny?
Hottoite sodatsu mono nanda nandarou
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
Deai mashite wa kantan sugiruyo
Saisho ni kimeta kotae wa hitotsu
Tokimeki mashita goukaku shimasuka?
Koi mo shoubu mo awatenai
Kotsu kotsu kotsu to tetsuya ni tameiki
Watashi no naka ni tensai dreamer
Omou koto mina kanaeba iina
Hito no sekai wa kinishinai
Perfect-area complete!
Zettai koko de matterunda
Perfect-area nozomu koe ga kikoeruyo
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? Tomaranai surechigai
Watashi ga soudan aite nara
"Tomodachi kai?" "Tomodachi desu."
Kanashiki rei ten dane
No! Yarinaoshi kakinaoshi
Honki de one more chance please
Ima yori suteki na mirai ga arunoni
Ima yori suteki ni my life, my life, my life!
"Episode 10" "Prep Tests, Mysterious Thieves, and Love Letters"
Akihisa Yoshii. Year 2, Class F.
It's another typical morning for him.
Wake up please, Aki! It's morning already!
--I'm still sleepy.
--It can't be helped, then.
I'll give you a "good
morning" kiss to wake you up.
I'm up!
I'm up! I'm up, so...
I see... Then...
I'll give you a "have a
good day" kiss in advance.
I don't want it in advance or on time!
Oh well... Then I'll stop
with the family bonding.
Hurry up and change. Breakfast is ready.
Breakfast? But you can't cook...
"CalorieMaido"
Yeah, I knew it'd be something like this.
This is a nutritiously-balanced supplement food.
Since there isn't much time to spare in
the morning, I prepared the drink type.
It doesn't really feel
like I'm having breakfast,
but it's nutritious so that's okay, right?
Taking in enough calories in the
morning, when your day is just starting,
and having a light meal at night,
when you become less active, is...
...good for your health, they say, right?
Assuming that you take in
about 2500 calories a day.
I thought it'd be appropriate to allocate
1000 calories to breakfast and
lunch, and 500 calories to dinner.
Uh-huh.
This one can is 200 calories.
So please drink 5 cans, 1 liter, for breakfast!
No, I can't drink that much.
If you drink 13 cans, which is 2.6 liters,
the numbers match up well.
Like I said, I can't drink that much.
Don't worry. Just so you won't get
tired of them, I prepared different kinds.
The main is "normal" flavor,
the side dish is "corn soup" flavor.
The drink is "coffee" flavor, and for dessert,
please choose the one you'd like,
either "café au lait" flavor or "cocoa" flavor.
That's not really the point.
Yeah, you're right. I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Since you're at a growing
stage, this isn't enough, is it?
No! Don't add more!
Akihisa's happy morning
is still far in the distance.
"Ugh"
I wish she had at least
combined them with the solid kind.
Uh-huh, uh-huh...
Oh?
What're you doing, Muttsulini?
Taking routine measurements.
Measurements?
I'm recording the stats on
bust sizes in this academy.
A 10 cm difference between full-
and under-bust measurements is A cup.
After that, each 2.5 cm
increase becomes B, C, D cups...
B, C, A... A, B, D, B, B, C...
B, A... Ah! That's over G! D, A, B, A...
Wasn't that a D?
That was a fake.
I see... I'm impressed that you could tell that.
Oh? This is quite small. Is this A cup?
No. After A cup, each 2.5 cm decrease
in the full- and under-bust difference
becomes AA, AAA...
I see. Then if it's flat like the one
we just saw, that'd be five As, so...
just like a shachihoko, my
spine is bent! Broken! Curved!
Even those with flat chests have human rights!
I give! I give up!
--Ahh! My eyes! My eyes!
--You can't watch that, Yuuji.
A little more... A little more...!
I give up...
Not the Rolling!
You guys are lively, as usual...
H-Hideyoshi? Why are you dressed like that?
Oh, I get it! You're gonna comfort me, right?
"Male Nurse"
"Comfort"
This is a costume for the drama club.
It's supposed to be a costume
for a male nurse, but when I wear it,
it looks like it was made for a woman.
That should be "nurse," not "male nurse."
What?! Then I misread the script?
No wonder the front of
the underwear doesn't open.
What?!
"Rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble"
The top was the type
that opens in front, though.
Geez, what're you guys doing?
Yeah, how embarrassing.
Big Sister!
Give me a break, Hideyoshi.
If you act stupid, people
will look at me the same way.
I'm not acting stupid, though.
Not realizing it yourself
proves that you're stupid!
You being in Class F alone is bad enough,
but on top of that, it's a parade of idiots!
I'm embarrassed just to be a
student in the same academy.
You don't have to go that far!
What can I say? It's the truth.
Or, has your class's academic
performance gotten better since then?
This is a school.
If you have time to fool around,
I want you to study. Let's go, Rep.
"Humiliation"
Around that time, Mizuki Himeji
was reading a specialized book.
"How to deliver a love letter.
When you don't have
courage to give it in person,
you can ask a close friend as well."
A close... friend... huh?
Minami...
What is it, Mizuki?
About Yoshii... To tell you the truth...
Is that... Could it be that you, too?!
What? Is it possible that... you, too?!
Do you have ones that I'm missing?
I should've asked Yoshii's
close friend, not mine.
Sakamoto...
What is it, Himeji?
I have a big favor to ask.
Yeah?
To tell you the truth... it's a love letter...
W-Wait, Shouko! I didn't do anything wrong!
You're already taken.
A marriage registration form?! Hey, stop it!
I'll never sign i--
How mortifying...
"If it's hard to give just the love letter,
you can also give a present along with it."
Uhm... Yoshii...
What is it, Himeji?
To tell you the truth... there's
something I'd like to give to you.
I baked cookies this mornin--
Oh...? Yoshii?
Yoshii! Where are you?! Yoshii!
--Please have the cookies that I baked!
--I was here first!
--Shh! Quiet!
If she finds us, both of our lives will be...
What're you fooling around for, Yoshii?!
Ugh! Iron Man!
Good timing! Help me carry some stuff!
What?!
"You can also secretly put
it in their bag or shoe locker.
That seems modest and sometimes
it helps increase your likeability."
I should've done this from the start.
"Throb Counter"
What're you doing, Mizuki?
Huh? Ah... U-Uhm...
Hm? This is...
Th--
This is...
"Busty Pudding" "Get off with Pudding" "Loads of sexy photos of
the busty, ponytailed Pudding!" "Expanded Issue" "Afro Publishing"
Yuuji... where are you?
If Shouko gets her hands on this...
my life will be over!
It's finally completed...
The Complete Statistics on
Bust Sizes! No copying is allowed!
In the end... I couldn't even
put it in his shoe locker, either.
What should I do?
Huh?! This envelope is...!
This is rare in its own way.
Ah, no, no! Where's my love letter?
Did I drop it somewhere earlier?
Man... Why am I the only one who...
Feedback!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hm? What's this?
C... Could it be... the
questions for the next exam?
Which means if I see these...
If I know the questions in advance...
even I could get a 100% score!
Just kidding. That would be cheating!
If I suddenly get a 100% score,
people will suspect me right away!
Oh?
The box is torn.
What should I do?
Maybe I'll use the cardboard boxes
from my classroom or something instead.
"Enough with the stupidity --Principal"
Humph.
I'm done.
You'll see them again when you take
the prep test. Start preparing for it now.
Okay.
Ah! There it is! Good! I found i--
Ah... Delivery... slip?
What...? Whaaaaaat?!
Idiot Test
What's the matter, Himeji?
You look bummed out.
Yoshii!
Well... Uhm...
What is it? If there's something
I can do to help, just say the word.
Yoshii?
Hm?
To tell you the truth...
It's gone!
Where'd it go? My marriage registration form!
The bust size list that
I worked my ass off to complete...
My treasured pictures that
I went out of my way to buy...!
Where did my costume go?!
What's going on?! I put it in
the safe and securely locked it!
If you're talking about the cardboard
boxes, Iron Man took some earlier.
--Wh...
--What?!
--And...
--Whaaaaat?!
An important envelope was...?!
So don't you have some idea?
Well... at the place I dropped it, I found this.
The delivery slip for the
prep test exam papers...
Then... when I dropped the exam
papers... it got mixed into them!
That safe is locked and students are not
supposed to open it without permission.
What should we do?
We'll help you.
Hm?
We'll assist you!
Don't be such a stranger! Just ask us.
We can depend on each
other when we have problems.
Yuuji! Guys!
That safe has things that
are important to us as well!
They may not be worth anything to others, but...
They have our feelings in them!
They're important to us!
We'll take them back no matter what!
Guys...
Everyone... Thank you very much!
Let's join hands and
work together!
Their feelings were not together.
So they're in this safe, huh?
It's a double lock that requires the
key and the secret code number to open.
So it won't open with just the
key or just the code number, huh?
What tight security.
Why don't we just have
Aki's Avatar break the door?
I'll be the one who gets scolded, you know.
Oh yeah! I've got an idea!
What do we do?
Our drama club once performed
a story about a mysterious thief,
and the thief used some technique
to steal a treasure from a safe.
Whoa!
How did he do it?
First, he prepared a fake treasure.
Then he showed the fake treasure to
the owner and told them that he stole it.
The owner panicked and
opened the safe to check it.
And then, there, he stole the treasure for real.
Amazing!
That's smart!
That's an explanation
even idiots can understand.
Okay then! Let's use that strategy!
Yeah!
Iron Man... Look at this!
It's the prep test exam paper!
Then, give that to me.
What?
Uhm... don't you have to
open the safe and check?
Do I need to do that when you
have it in your hand right now, Yoshii?!
But... Uhm...
Oh?
Hey, it didn't work.
It went well on stage, though.
I wonder what's different.
The scenario.
We have to open it on our own after all!
But how?!
We need both the key and the secret code number.
What're we supposed to do?!
Do you want me to help you?
What?!
You are...
Kyouji Nemoto. He is
the rep for Year 2, Class B.
All we have to do is open that safe,
right? Do you want me to help you?
You can do it?!
I can't do it by myself...
but if you obtain the key,
I'll handle the secret code number.
Really?!
Yeah, I promise.
We can depend on each other
when we have problems, right?
Thank you, Nemoto!
Where is it?!
That's the one.
So that's the key to the safe...
No way! It's right behind Mr. Nishimura?!
What do we do?
This is hopeless.
Okay then! Let's go with a decoy strategy!
A-A decoy strategy?
Someone will use their
female charm to get his attention,
and we'll take the key in the meantime.
Then, Hideyoshi is perfect for that job, right?!
Why me?
Because we can't let Himeji do such a thing,
and since Minami doesn't have
any sexual charm, she'd mess up--
My spine! My spine!
"Argentine Backbreaker"
"Japanese Name: Argentine-Style Back Bend"
--Who'd you say doesn't have any sexual charm?!
--I give! I give up! I give up!
What're you doing?!
Ah, well... There're many reasons for this
and we're doing nothing ba-- Ahh!
First my backbone, and now my skull!
Man... That was terrible.
That went deep, didn't it?
But in that opening, I got the key to the safe.
--Yaay! Yaay!
--Good job, Muttsulini. Just as we planned!
So I was the decoy?!
Okay! It's unlocked!
The next is the secret code number, huh?
Don't touch it carelessly. If we
make a mistake, the alarm will go off.
I'm surprised that you know it well.
Then what're you gonna do?
Look at this.
Whoa! This is...
a nice digital camera.
This is from earlier when
Iron Man opened the safe.
It's got pictures of him pressing the buttons!
That's right. This is the
secret code number for today.
Whoa!
I found it...
I'm glad... that I was able to find it.
I found mine, too!
I'd better keep it more secure.
I found it!
I'm happy for you, Himeji.
Yes! Thank you!
Really... thank you very much!
Oh! I found it! My costume!
A... A bra, too?!
On top of that, it's a front-hook bra!
So that's what it's like, huh?
Hm? Mizuki, you don't
know about front-hook bras?
They don't have it for my size. They
said that the cups are too big for the clasp.
That's not true! The clasps are well made!
Who decided that front-hook
bras are for flat chests?!
--Too big...
--Was it the country? Mountains? Rivers?!
Hmm, so this is it?
What're you doing, Nemoto?
Well, just a little preparation.
No, Nemoto!
That's cheating!
What're you saying now?
You guys are the same, right?
You entered the safe where the exam
papers were kept without permission.
If they find that out,
you guys are cheaters, too!
What?! We just came to get what we lost!
You think such an excuse would work, Himeji?
Has your time in Class F caused
you to get infected by their stupidity?
Results are all that matters
in this world. In other words,
the means doesn't matter!
What?! But you can't...
As long as I'm able to solve
these questions on the test day,
then it's my real ability, right?
The questions given on that day
happen to be the same questions. That's all!
That logic is wrong!
Are you trying to ruin this rare chance?
That's why you guys are idiots.
"Idiots"
Even if my scores improve a bit,
there'll be no harm to anyone.
Even if I live honestly,
there'll be no benefit to anyone.
You don't even understand that,
and that's why you guys are in Class F.
It's not just your academic performance
that's bad, it's your brains themselves!
That's why it's the lowest class,
home to all the academy's scum.
You're wrong!
Himeji...
It's true that Class F's academic
performance may not be good.
But... But everyone's kind... considerate...
fun and warm... It's a very nice class!
Himeji...
Class F is neither the
lowest nor scum by any means!
Humph! Either way...
if they find out about this,
you'll be suspended...
or expelled in the worst case.
You and I share the same fate. Listen.
I don't know what you were doing here.
And you didn't see me
here, either. That's fine, right?
Try and wise up, you dummies!
Yuuji...
Are we...
idiots after all?
You're just realizing it now?
We are genuine idiots.
Yeah, I guess.
Are you upset that you were made a fool of?
I don't care if someone makes a fool of me.
But... when Himeji, Minami
and the others are bad-mouthed...
Himeji could've actually studied
in Class A's better environment.
She just happened to have bad
luck and became a Class F student.
When that's all it was, why does she
have to be made a fool of like that?!
Hmph! If you're that upset, do you wanna try it?
What?
Three months have almost passed.
The period in which the losing class
cannot declare war is almost over.
Ah!
I led the class to a loss because
I took it lightly last time. Sorry about that.
Yuuji...
But it's also true that we got close.
I won't make the same clumsy mistake ever again!
How about it, do you wanna try one more time?
What're you saying?! Of course, Yuuji!
We'll win this time and show
everyone we're no ordinary idiots!
Let's do it, the Summoner Test War!
Yeah! Well then, let's
go settle things, shall we?!
Before that...
Hm?
I'll go ask Himeji to give me her cookies.
Good idea!
It's not fair that we're the only ones
who get the short end of the stick.
Awaken!
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
vs. "Combined Subjects"
Yaay!
What's this?
It's the prep test exam paper... isn't it?
Which means that if I memorize this,
I'll get a 100% score in the next test!
Geez, they're real idiots.
Questions that were made
public won't be on the test.
Oh no...!
Did Aki and Yuuji do this by any chance?
Yoshii...
Yoshii! Sakamoto! What the hell are you doing?!
We're sorry!
Huh?!
What's the meaning... of doing such a thing?!
We were just trying to play a prank!
We got too carried away!
Don't lie! What're you up t--
We're really... sorry!
Is there a reason you can't tell me the truth?
No. This was a prank.
Have you two... ever meekly apologized before?
Okay... Then you're both
getting the demon's remedial class!
Whaaaat?!
Be prepared! I'll teach
you even better than usual!
This is a punishment for your prank!
Yes sir!
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
Jugyou owari shifuku no jikan
Tatoeru no nara “Maji de Angel!”
Fui no kokuchi heiwa kowashita
Tsuishi no shirase “Jigoku da!”
Tomodachi tono warai banashi ni
“Iru wake naiyo sonna baka”
Demo hontou wa mune no oku dewa
Sakendetanda “Jibun ga! Sou deshita!”
Chuusha jou de miru “Tsukigime” no koto
Kaisha no namae dato omotteta...
Zutto...
Baka mo tooseba otoko date
Bokura no joushiki hijoushiki?
Ruuru wa muyou sa kono sekai
Yakiniku teishoku gekokujou
Miroyo!
Nishi kara nobotta ohisama ga shizunde iku
Hashire! Mou gohan da
Ouchi ni kaerou! Ouchi ni kaerou!
"Nemoto"
Oh? What's this? A present from a girl?!
I'm quite the guy, aren't I?
I think I'll eat them before Yuuka finds out.
That's the sound of his soul being taken away.
Question 11.
What was the tactic often used by
the German military during World War II
that used a combination of
bombing and armored divisions?
Let's go full blast!
Please value your life.
Next Episode! "Rivals,
Love Letters, and Blitz Tactics."
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!"
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"