Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Now, it's time to begin.
Let's go!
Ngaah~
Hurry up and start already!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Let's have someone solve this problem...
Shiraishi!
Eh?
You just picked on me last time.
Is that so?
Then, Izumi.
Izumi?
E-eh?
I wasn't sleeping.
I didn't even say anything.
Urk...
A Matter
of Motivation
Ah!
I forgot my English textbook.
Why don't you go borrow it from Kagami?
Her class already had English today.
Geez.
You're so careless.
Thanks.
You should check it the night before.
Tsukasa, you forget a lot of things, don't you?
Speaking of which...
Konata, you never forget your textbooks.
Surprisingly, I'm pretty good with those kinds of things.
I leave all my textbooks at school!
Oh yeah, that's right...
You're not good with them at all!
But you can't review anything if your textbooks are at school.
I don't study at home.
Since you don't even bring them home until the day before a test...
But Kona-chan, you're good at cramming the night before.
Oh!
Maybe that's why I forget my homework.
In your case, we don't call that 'forgetting.'
You just don't have the motivation.
So, can I see your Japanese homework from last night?
Already!?
I always wonder...
Since you're in the same class with her, why don't you just look at Miyuki's?
How do I say this...
Miyuki-san is such a good person that it's actually hard to ask her.
Know what I mean?
I kind of do, but I'm still not convinced.
Izumi.
Izumi?
What's this...
Is she tardy?
No, I'm not late!
Oh?
I was helping someone out, and it caused me to be late.
Is that so?
We usually do things together...
So I just couldn't leave him alone today.
I see.
He was nice enough to say, 'Don't worry about me... we can disband.'
But with five people in the group, having only one parting leaves a bad aftertaste.
Not to mention we've been partying together for a long time.
So we all help each other out in times like this.
It's nice to have good friends...
I see.
So, you stayed up late last night playing an internet game?
You've been playing after I dropped, huh?
Izumi.
Izumi?
What's this... late again?
Wait!
I'm not late!
A girl bumped into me in front of the shopping mall.
Then, that girl suddenly grabbed my hand and started running.
And when I listened to what she had to say...
She had apparently stolen a Taiyaki and was running away.
So I thought to myself, 'Why do I have to be involved in this?'
But I didn't have much of a choice at that point, so...
In an attempt to hide, we ran into the nearest café and...
Uguu!
I can think of so many things to say right now...
But I probably shouldn't say them...
As a teacher...
As a human...
Uuu~
I caught a summer cold.
Oh, Izumi, what's the matter?
Sensei, I'm really sorry but I feel sick today.
What, been playing too many games again?
How many times are you going to use the same excuse?
Uh, I would like to be absent today because I'm sick.
Hahaha!
What, are you going to tell me you caught a summer cold?
The rainy season is over and the weather's good right now!
So, stop saying you're tired and get your butt over here!
Eh?
So yesterday, I totally got treated like the boy who cried wolf.
You had it coming.
Kona-chan, do you feel better now?
My fever's gone, but my throat still hurts a little.
Kona-chan, you breathe through your mouth, don't you?
Eh!?
Huh?
Well, I'm sure sometimes people breathe through their mouth...
But isn't it usually through the nose?
B-but, perhaps Kona-chan breathes through her throat more than her nose.
Huh?
Because...
If the cold virus enters through your mouth, you'll get a sore throat.
If it enters through your nose, you'll get a runny nose, right?
That's why...
When you get a sore throat...
Isn't that because the chances of the virus entering your mouth are really high?
Ahh...
At times like this, it's better to just call for Miyuki-san...
Yeah...
Eh...?
So hot...
I don't feel like doing anything.
Ah, Kagami.
About today's birthday party, do you want to do it at my house?
It's so hot I can't even take a step.
Eh?
But I'm baking cookies at my place right now.
I'm on my way.
Okay, hurry up.
Welcome.
Happy birthday!
Tsukasa and company.
Don't downplay me!
Happy birthday.
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san...
Oh, thank you!
Thanks.
And well, this is something boring...
But it's a present for you.
I wonder what it is...
Please open it.
Wow~
It's a pair of earrings.
I gave it a lot of through, but I still had a hard time deciding.
Then I shall offer my presents too!
I wonder what it is...
Open it up.
Chief
What's this?
It's the Brigade Leader arm-band.
Try it on.
Chief
Why do I have to put this thing on?
I thought it would fit you perfectly, Kagami...
Chief
It would probably look better on you.
W-what's this?
To Heart!?
That was really expensive you know.
Take good care of it when you wear it.
Don't make the both of us cosplay!
It's not that much different from our uniforms anyway.
Yeah, it'd be troubling if it were too big.
Yeah, it sure would... and when it stinks, too.
You!
It's someone else's birthday, so why don't you hold back a little?
These cookies that Tsukasa made sure taste good.
Ah...
I made it with her this time around.
I was learning as I went along.
What's the matter?
Now that you mention it...
I thought I tasted some 'good' ones and some 'not so good' ones...
Strange, isn't it?
What was that!?
I wonder if this one is Kagami's...?
Since you're all here already, why don't you guys have some cake?
And so Kagami worked very hard for one day of the year...
Her birthday.
Shut up.
By the way, do you ever get into debates about how to cut a cake?
Huh?
Why?
Like, if you're cutting it into many pieces, what would you do with the strawberry on top...
Or who gets to eat the chocolate on the plate...
Onee-chan, you like the chocolate, don't you?
Ehehe...
Darn it.
I didn't cut it straight.
I don't feel the moe when Kagami makes mistakes.
What's that!?
Itadakima~su.
Itadakimasu!
What now?
My strawberry is so small...
Hehe.
What's up with you?
Is there cake on my face or something?
I just discovered another one of your attractions...
You really look like him now so stop it!
It's almost summer vacation again...
You're right.
The ocean, pools and summer festivals...
Did I miss anything else that's important?
*Pause*
Speaking of summer...
It's that twice-a-year event...
The grand opening of a battlefield...
None other than...
Comiket!
No no no no no... that's just you.
What ke?
Well, I guess there are events for all sorts of people.
Like Go competitions...
Good morning.
Miyuki, do you have anything you do every summer?
Let's see...
I have plans to go travel abroad again this year.
'Again this year...'
Did she just say 'again?'
You damn bourgeoisie!
Is that a type of yogurt?
I heard that you started working at a cosplay cafe.
But don't you have to have good style to work in places like those?
Well...
I was pretty worried since I didn't exactly have big breasts...
But a certain game once said that...
'Small breasts are a status!'
'A rare quality!'
So it said.
A rare
quality!
Small breasts
are a status!
Yep.
Now that I think about it, you can look at it that way too.
So I'm pretty valuable.
I would like to know how she can have so much confidence because of games...
Then, I'm okay too?
Geez.
Finals are coming up soon, so are you going to be okay playing games all day?
Uh...
If only you would redirect some of that passion to studying...
I'm sure your grades would go up a lot.
Oh!
If she's that easily influenced...
A game that promotes studying may have a huge effect on her.
Since they do have Moe Drill for the DS and stuff like that.
What's the matter?
There have been a lot of crimes committed by juveniles recently.
And when you interview the neighbors, they all seem to say...
'He was always a quiet kid, so I never could imagine him doing something like that.'
Well, that just means you can't judge someone on the surface.
If you commit some sort of crime...
'I was certain she would some something sooner or later.'
I'll say that about you.
It's so hot that I don't feel like doing anything.
Hmm...
I understand how you feel...
But you come up with all sorts of reasons year-round to say, 'I don't feel like doing anything.'
Hiiragi
Hello Kagami.
Yo!
How's studying for finals coming along?
I'm cleaning up my room right now.
Huh?
Don't you really feel like cleaning when you know tests are coming up?
I know how you're feeling, but just do your best...
All right!
I should do a little today.
I'll take a 30-minute break.
I can't concentrate.
Oh, it's time already.
Just 30 more minutes...
30 more minutes...
Uwa!
It's almost time for Haruhi.
Giving Nagato such long screen times... are they slacking off?
****kan hasn't been too impressive lately.
Uwa!
Look, it's getting bashed already.
Geez, it's already 2 o'clock?
I just can't get into the mood today.
I'll go to sleep early and do it tomorrow morning.
If I wake up at 5 AM...
I can sleep for a whole three hours.
In the end, I wasted time reading manga and watching anime...
That's so like you, Kona-chan.
Speaking of which...
Konata, your game and manga preferences are quite esoteric.
You read shounen manga and mainly play bishoujo games, right?
I used to see my dad read manga and play games a lot.
So, I was probably influenced by that.
I've been watching him since I was little.
I can understand the shounen manga...
But playing gal-games and bishoujo-games in front of your little daughter...
What kind of dad would do that?
With both of you like that, doesn't your mom say anything?
Ah...
I don't have a mom, so...
Eh?
She died when I was really small.
Is that so...
That's why I'm always the one doing the chores around the house.
I bet I'm a lot better than you at doing them, Kagami.
Don't say something unnecessary at a time when it's inappropriate to joke.
Tsukasa, you're good at cooking, right?
I don't know if I'm good or not, but I like to!
I wonder how Miyuki-san is?
She looks really rich, so maybe she's not good at those sorts or things.
Eh?
Cooking?
Actually, I only help now and then.
So I'm not too good at chores like those.
It's quite embarrassing.
Oh! Just as I thought.
But Miyuki-san, you're too good at everything else, so your standards are different.
You can't take this girl's 'not good' literally.
Hmm, I see.
No, that's not true.
I wonder how sensei is?
She lives alone, but I have a pretty sloppy image of her.
Hahaha!
Nowadays, even if you can't cook, you can still manage to survive.
There are convenience stores and stuff...
Just kidding!
I can cook.
Just as well as an average person.
Please don't joke with such a straight face!
Ah!
I loaned my dictionary to Tsukasa.
Tsukasa, I'm sorry but...
Can I have my dictionary back?
I-I was cleaning my room for a change-of-mood...
You too?
Yo!
What's the matter?
Everyone at my part-time job is deciding on a new summer menu right now, but...
Eh?
You have something like that?
Wait, did you give up on your tests?
When it's hot, people think of spicy things...
So how about we have super-spicy ramen?
Why don't you make a menu that's more cafe like?
Then, a super-spicy parfait!
Just stop with the off-the-top-of-your-head ideas.
I can't stand...
Why doesn't our school have any swimming classes?
Even though we have a pool.
I'm kind of saved by that though.
Eh?
Why?
Since I can't open my eyes under water...
I can't swim much either.
Though it's embarrassing...
Oh how I wish I had your 'weaknesses.'
Oh!
Finally, the summer Comp-Matsuri is opening!
I see...
Now that I think about it, this was the reason I started working.
A festival huh...
Everything seems so nostalgic.
What's with you bringing up old thoughts?
Oh, it's really exhilarating to get caught up in the moment with the other customers...
Doesn't it make you feel that together you're making the festival livelier?
Just use a little of that enthusiasm for school, please.
I can't seem to fall asleep just yet.
Maybe I'll read a book or something.
I just bought one too.
Sigh...
Not only did I not fall asleep, it's already morning...
And now I'm starting to fall asleep...
Silent
Mode
I understand why you have to turn the power off in the priority seats...
Because of pacemakers and stuff, but...
Why can't you talk on your cell phone while on the train?
Isn't that because it's rude to talk when there are other passengers around you?
Hmm...
But aren't there still some loud people...
Not taking into account people who are talking on the phone?
Well, I guess that's true.
During the summer festival, are you going to work at the shrine like you did for the New Year's first shrine visit?
No, I decided not to do that this summer.
But it's almost that season again, isn't it?
Huh?
Weren't you on a diet?
Maybe it was because I was studying for tests...
But when I weighed myself yesterday, I was lighter.
So I thought that maybe it was okay after all.
That was fast...
Or rather, weak!
Good morning.
Ah!
Kona-chan, good morning.
Huh?
What's the matter with Kagami?
Konata!
My weight's returned, but it's not something for which I've yearned.
It's because you let your guard down and kept snacking.
Wait, was that a poem?
My weight has returned
But it is not something
For which I have yearned
But I only ate a bit here and there...
A couple of kilos won't even affect your appearance.
Why are you so worried about it?
This is why women are so...
I thought you were supposed to be a woman too.
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
It's started again this week: Lucky Channel.
Have you all been taking care of yourselves?
Always at 120% cheerful...
Kogami Akira here!
This time-
Nyoro~n!
Just kidding!
I'm the assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
Hey!
W-what is it?
Don't just cut me off!
A-ahh...
I'm sorry!
This isn't 'Not an Errand Boy,' so try to do better at your job.
Do you want to get fired that much?
I-I'm so sorry!
I'll try harder... I'll try harder... I promise!
Now then, this time...
Tada!
We have a very important announcement for you all!
The 'Make Akira Look Better' plan from November's Comptiq.
We have this many postcards from everyone!
U-um, wasn't there another person included in that plan besides you, Akira-sama?
Thank you for sending in so many!
Akira's mammothly happy-pii.
I don't think they'll understand 80's jokes.
Now, we'll present an idea that was selected after rigorous screening.
Any of these will do.
Let's see...
From Saitama-ken, this is Sappishi-Cherry-san's 'Akira look better plan!'
Kagami-san's twintails look really good on her.
How about you try out twintails too, Akira-san?
Twintails, huh?
That sounds really-
Uuu~n lovely!
You're right.
Long hair is a woman's life.
If you split that in two...
How graceful would it be?
Whether you do it or not...
I don't think it's possible with your short hair, Akira-sama--!
But you know, it's not all about letting your hair grow out.
A-Akira-sama?
It's visible.
You know, it's really heavy.
It's almost visible, therefore...
Akira-sama, it's just barely...
It's a pain to shampoo.
And it's not that popular nowadays.
Guys say they like girls with long hair, but...
Um, that's something someone in the series would say.
Do they have any idea...
How much time and money we put into maintaining this hair?
On top of that...
Not you, Akira-san.
We worked so hard and no one seems to notice...
Are you listening?
Oy?
Uwaa~
It's time to say goodbye already.
Well then, if you want to find out what would happen if Akira had twintails...
Please go to the homepage, or we can talk about it again on the radio.
Thank you!
I'll be waiting!
Bye-pii!
See you next time.
Please look forward to it.
What was with your attitude back there?
Eh?
Attitude?
You interrupted me so many times.
What was that about?
You were pissed that I didn't mention you in the beginning?
O-oh, that's not it at all.
I was just worried that they might not know who Nori-P was, so...
What?
U-um..
What!?
T-then let's go with a different feel next time, okay?
By the way, I heard they're doing a Shiraishi Minoru audition.
Yes?
Eh?
Are you serious?
I hadn't heard of this.
It's okay for you to audition, too.
What do you mean by that?
Aren't you glad?
But, I'm the real thing!
Huh?
What is?
Eh?
Kona-chan, you're amazing!
You can sing anything, can't you?
I'm limited to anime songs, though.
You sing so well with so many different voices.
It's the iron rule of anime songs to follow the originals.
Really~
All right.
I guess I'll sing now!
Onee-chan, what are you going to sing?
I saw the title earlier, but...
I didn't recognize it.
Eh?
Miyuki, you don't know this one?
Yes...
Kagami, you shouldn't be talking about others.
Ah!
I've heard of this!
We were just watching this drama together.
Eh?
Is that so?
I prefer the movie...
Are you some sort of old geezer?
Sayonara wa wakare no kotoba janakute
さよならは　別れの言葉じゃなくて
Goodbyes are not the words of separation,
Oh!
Pretty good.
Onee-chan is the best at
singing out of the whole family.
Futatabi au made no tooi yakusoku
再び違うまでの遠い約束
Just a promise to see each other again.
Yume no ita basho ni
夢のいた場所に
That place I saw in my dreams,
Miren nokoshite mo
未練残しても
If I leave anything behind...
Kokoro samui dake sa
心寒いだけさ
It will just leave a cold feeling in my heart.
Kono mama nanjikan demo daiteitai kedo
このまま　何時間でも　抱いていたいけど
I wish I could embrace you like this for hours.
Preview
Next week's Lucky Star is...
Miyuki here.
I heard that 'Golden Week' comes from all the extra money that the movie theaters make during this season.
Next week: A Famous Shooter.
「A Famous Shooter」
Look forward to it!