Please...
take my hand in marriage!
I guess I have no choice.
If you insist, I'll marry you.
Takasu Ryuuji's Pen
Ryuu-chan, look, look!
Taiga-chan gave birth to so many puppies!
They're your kids.
A dream, huh...
~I gave birth to puppies!~
True Story of Fear
from the Islands of Japan:
Even though it's finally summer break...
I'm having these dreams because of the stupid DVDs we rented.
Even for a dream, that's one awful future.
Oh, Taiga!
I had a bad dream.
You were a dog, and my husband was the dog.
Anyway...
it was a horrible dream.
You, who are going to the sea?
A premonition?
Yes.
It was a warning, telling me that if I don't work out a counter-plan, that future awaits me.
That dream was...
So, in order to change the future,
one side should fully support the other starting with the trip tomorrow.
I understand that, but...
Why badminton?
Like I said...
we're going to decide!
Decide who's doing what!
Listen, be careful when using the stove.
Stir the rice bran once a day.
Make sure to change Inko-chan's water in the morning.
Read the rest in the note I left behind.
Well, I'll be going then.
Going? Where?
I told you, didn't I? On a trip.
See you, Yacchan.
Looks like the weather's going to be great!
So I'm counting on you... for that plan.
Hey, you sure it's okay?
Yeah! It's your win, okay?
Get this thing off of me!
If it weren't for that dumb dog getting involved, I would have won!
It was punishment for setting up a match in something you're good at.
Sheesh. Nothing good ever comes out of anything involving dogs.
Still... will it really go smoothly?
Just leave it to me.
When this trip is over, your relationship with Minorin will be—
What?
Something wrong?
Good morning!
You're right on time!
Great! Simply great!
What's wrong?! Where's the energy?! Make some noise!
What's that?
Y-Yeah...
Whoa!
My, the weather has become perfect for an outing!
Don't look!
Y-Yeah...
Come to think of it, A-min's not here yet.
There's still some time left.
Okay! I've got an idea!
Huh?
Where are those guys? There's nobody here.
H-Hey...
You're two minutes late, Ami!
Good morning, A-min!
You're late, stupid chihuahua.
Wh-Where is everyone?
Hey! Don't run away, stupid chihuahua!
Ami, we're right here!
Whoa, this is great!
There's a plum in this that makes it super plum!
As expected of Takasu.
Want to marry into my family?
No, I won't.
Jeez, you're mean.
Huh?
Come to think of it...
it seems Aisaka-san didn't come. Is she late?
Takasu-kun, go get in touch with—
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh? The stupid chi' is awake?
I thought you were sleeping with your eyes open.
Wha—
Don't fight when we're on a trip.
That aside, what have you been doing during summer break so far, Kawashima?
Me?
I've been working the whole time.
Oh, you started working again?
What about Minorin?
Club activities, work, club activities, work, club activities, club activities, work,
club activities, work, club activities, work, club...
Wh-What about you, Taiga?
I was...
Huh? What, Taiga?
I was making this.
J-Just now, I heard "senpai" in a strange voice! Is this...?
Yeah.
Sampled from CD's with more to them than just what they advertised — a collection of spirit voices.
I knew it!
No~! I've been called out!
Aisaka likes those kinds of horror things?
Huh? I might like them...
Oh, that's surprising.
It's also rather surprising that Kushieda's scared of eerie things.
I'm scared of it, I'm scared of it!
I'm super scared of it, you know!
Rather than super scared, you could say I'm incredibly scared—
Minorin, you see, is really scared of horror movies, spirits, and occult things in general.
I see...
That's why we're going to scare Minorin to death.
Then you're going to save her when she's at the peak of her fear.
With a, "I will protect Kushieda!"
This is called the "Scare Minorin, Enter the White Knight!" plan!
Either way!
Scary things are absolutely forbidden!
It's the sea!
Sheesh... how far do we have to walk?
You can see it already, can't you?
Huh?
Let's go around the back.
Keep going that way and I think we'll be on the balcony.
This is A-min's vacation home?!
We're going to be staying here?!
That's right, Minori-chan.
Awesome! I'm so moved!
But... we've got to clean the place up first...
Nobody's been here since last year.
S-Since last year?!
Y-Yeah.
This looks like it'll be one hell of a fight.
What?! We've got this pretty sea right in front of us!
Let's leave cleaning up for last!
Yeah! We can clean later!
What?!
M-Me too!
I'm going too... What about you, Takasu-kun?
Why am I cleaning all by myself?
This feels great!
Hey, hey.
Huh? What's up?
That...
kinda looks like someone's head, doesn't it?
Wah, it's a floating corpse!
What should I do?! I've been soaked in corpse water!
Looks like they're having fun.
Sorry, Minorin! That might be seaweed!
Wah, then it's a seaweed corpse!
You really came, Yuusaku.
What should I do?! I've been soaked in seaweed corpse water!
Of course I came.
You can't have Takasu come without his good friend coming along as well.
You sure about this? What about the student council?
What are you saying?
Nothing...
Takasu!
Ami said to go out shopping.
Apparently there's a bike in the shed.
Bike?
If that's the case, take Taiga with you.
Take Aisaka?
I-I'm not going.
I'm scared of bikes.
What?!
Be careful, now.
Yeah, got it.
See you!
You finally had a chance to be alone together.
I had an idea, you see.
Before they come back, we've got to find somewhere suitable to play out that plan.
You're just embarrassed, just admi—
There was a mosquito there, a mosquito!
Sheesh...
Even if you say "somewhere suitable"...
This is...
a bathroom, huh?
Gotta clean here too—
Wha—?!
Wh-Who's there?!
Sorry! I didn't notice!
Takasu-kun...?
I-I'll get out now.
Eh—
You're really bold, aren't you?
Coming in while a girl's showering...
I-It's not like I did it on purpose!
It's okay. We can keep it a secret from everyone else...
What are you say—
Hey, don't you want to do it?
D-Do what?!
Clean the bath!
Gosh! What were you expecting?
What's with that face?! It's a masterpiece!
Taiga~!
Huh? Stupid chi' did?
Making it sound like she was taking a shower?
Playing with a man's pure heart?
And? Did you finish investigating the second floor?
Useless!
That's why you got tricked by the likes of the stupid chi'!
Fine. I'll go check!
And while I'm at it, I'm going to tell her off as well!
Hey, stupid chi'!
The stupid chi' was actually in the bath.
The stupid chi' was...
BOOM!
And BOOM!
And here, it was EXPLODING!
Don't say unnecessary things!
We're back!
You sure bought a lot.
Where's Kitamura?
He's putting the bike away.
I-I see.
Ah! I'll carry them!
I-It's fine!
Kushieda did the shopping, after all.
Really?
Wh-What's wrong?
R-Right now, something... on my — on my neck...
It's your imagination.
Y-You're right...
That's right...
Something definitely touched me just now!
Something slippery... like seaweed!
I-It really does smell like seaweed! It's seaweed!
Like an animal spirit entwined in seaweed!
A sea otter? When it comes to being entwined in seaweed, it has to be the corpse of a sea otter!
A sea otter with its stomach pocket filled with scallops?!
It's the curse of the sea otter and seaweed!
No way!
I don't want it spicy!
I prefer it spicy!
I can't eat it if it's not sweet!
Hey, Ryuuji!
I know.
I'll make sure your portion is sweet.
You're giving special treatment to Aisaka-san again...
That will get you hated by girls, you know.
By Minori-chan too.
Wha—
You called for me?
Almost done? You're skilled, aren't you!
Y-Yeah...
I just have to add the roux.
Come on, you guys have to prepare for dinner—
Oh, already preparing for supper?
Even I can help out with putting out plates.
Y-You...
H-Hey, Taiga!
Yuusaku, are you insane?!
Oh, sorry. I heard Takasu's voice, so...
The girls were here too.
Are you stupid?!
Taiga, get yourself together!
Sorry, sorry!
Hey!
You narcissistic heaven-sent child! Give me a nude shot!
Quit it! Quit it, you!
What are you saying while looking like that, pretending to be modest!
Come on, stop it!
Right now...
something black and...
rather lively...
It was probably a seaweed spirit!
Sea...
weed?
Kushieda?!
Yuusaku, you're the worst!
S-Sorry...
Enough, just go!
Y-Yeah...
Be careful, everyone...
There's an evil spirit lurking in this house.
Is there anything I can do?
Make the curry...
really spicy...
Got it!
Whoa, it looks so tasty!
I made it with what I had available, but...
as per Kushieda's request, I've made it as spicy as possible.
Yeah! Let's eat!
Thanks for the food.
Oh, good! It's good!
It's weally dewishus.
It's not as spicy as I thought it would be.
Really?
You want to try it too, Taiga?
Really, it's—
Minorin?
SPICY!
It's gotten spicy—
—in my throat! Rather, it's hot! It hurts!
Here it is!
I have received this meal with impact!
There it is again!
A-Are you all right?
Takasu-kun!
You're the best!
It's super-spicy! It's super-delicious!
It does indeed have a strange quality to it that makes you keep eating it...
I'm... starting to feel strange...
Oh, there's seconds too.
Seconds!
I thought it was going to die...
All right.
I'm gonna do the dishes.
Ah, me too—
What?
I think it's because I ate spicy food.
I want some stomach medicine.
Your stomach's hurting? But I didn't bring med—
Aisaka, are you feeling ill?
I brought some stomach medicine with me.
Since it's in my room, wanna come along?
Eh? Th... That's...
Then I'm counting on you.
Wha — eh — wai —
It's a chance to be alone together.
What's wrong?
No! Nothing.
Well, take care of her!
Yeah.
Hey, hey.
Ami-chan's stomach hurts too.
Eh?
Or something like that.
What now?
Nothing.
You were spacing out, see.
Observing you never gets boring.
Is that a compliment?
You're just really complicated.
What's up with that?
More importantly, if you'd like, we could go to the beach toge—
Hey, Takasu-kun, could you get that glass for me?
Ah, I'll wash it.
Sorry. What was that?
Nothing.
Was it enough water?
How is it? Is it working?
Prob... ably...
I see. That's good.
Seeing Aisaka in pain makes me hurt too.
Oh, right. If it hurts, would you like to lie down?
You... have amazing cleaning techniques, don't you?
Well, I'm doing it all the time at work, after all.
Takasu-kun's curry was prepared with splendor as well.
No. Not at all.
Oh, yeah!
I'll give you something great as thanks for helping out!
Keep it a secret from everyone else.
Takasu-kun... is the green tea flavor good?
Eh? Oh, yeah, it's good.
Not so much with the azuki one.
It's packed with stars here.
I-It's beautiful.
It's just the two of us.
Is this what you'd call a chance?
Ku-Kushieda, d-do you have boyfriend?
The seaweed spirit from earlier... you think it's still around?
Eh?
Takasu-kun, have you...
ever seen a ghost?
Huh? No. I haven't...
I believe that ghosts exist.
But I have never seen one,
and I don't believe the stories from people who have.
I see...
And then, you see, I think of something else the same way.
I believe that one day I'll be in love, get married, and be happy.
But there's nobody who has had it spelled out like that, is there?
I think that the existence of people in the world who are meant to love one another is a bit farfetched.
I mean, I can't see them.
"There really isn't anything like ghosts, so I'll never see one in my life" — is how I have resigned myself.
And because of that, there is no answer to your question.
What about Takasu-kun?
Are you someone who can see ghosts?
I think... I want to see them.
Because of that, I go to places with spirits and I watch scary DVDs.
You see, I think that...
people who are sensitive to spirits would be shocked the first time they saw one, wouldn't they?
I think there are people who have seen them, but then they tried to deny their existence,
and on the other hand, there are those who put in an effort to finally be able to see them.
Because of that, I think that you don't have to resign yourself to never seeing one in your life.
Huh? What's that?!
A UFO?
That's a satellite.
A satellite...
What? I thought it was a UFO.
I think it'd be great if you could see ghosts sometime, Kushieda.
Huh?
Because I think that there's a ghost out there that wants you to see it.
So that's why there were lots of strange things that happened today, right?
Huh?
It's appealing to me! The seaweed spirit!
What's with that, all of a sudden?
Maybe I'll see them one day?
Huh?
No! Nothing!
What a weirdo.
Hey, Ryuuji. I think my stomach's all better.
Yeah, and?
I'm full! So full!
Somehow, even I...
Hey.
What should we do tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'm talking about that plan, obviously.
You're not doing your part properly at all.
What about you?
I'm the support this time around!
Jeez! Am I ever tired.
Eh?
I kept thinking about how happy I'd be after spending an entire day with Kitamura-kun...
but I was so nervous I could die an early death.
Certainly.
Though when I'm with you, I'm completely fine...
What's that supposed to mean?
How rude!
It's so dumb.
This room is so big, yet we're sitting this close to one another...
It's like the habits of being in a small apartment have stuck.
Why, you...
Ryuuji...
I was thinking, you know...
That dream was... rather...
Huh? What's up?
Nothing.
I'm gonna sleep.
Huh? Yeah...
Good night.
Huh? Did I put my bag here?
What is... this?
And it's somewhat slippery...
Ryuuji!
What do you think this is?
It was in my bag... yet when I touched it earlier, it was still warm...
as if someone had just been wearing it...
My room's weird too!
On my pillow, there was long hair...
W-What was that?
That was prob—
Th-This is a dream... right?
Yeah! It's a dream!
It's a continuation of that dream, living in a dog house, giving birth to dogs!
Then, if we close our eyes, we'll wake up sometime, right?
We'll wake up! We'll wake up!
...right?
Next Episode Preview
Fireworks
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Horror movies are scary! Ghosts are scary! Monsters are scary!
Calm down, Kushieda!
But... the scariest might be UFOs...