Once you know how, it's pretty easy.
I don't think I'll be losing any more.
I'll give it to you.
That's what you were after, right?
Hey.
I don't want to owe you anything.
This makes us even, OK?
Let's go home, Madoka.
Sayaka-chan...
Sorry...
I'm just a little tired.
Don't push yourself. Hold onto me.
That idiot.
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and make sure of it.
oshiyoseta yami furiharatte susumu yo
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I continue to move on.
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
When can I see once more the future that I lost?
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Again and again, I'll tear apart...
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
...the shadow of distress that spilled out...
nando demo saite kono sekai ayundekou
何度でも裂いて この世界歩んでこう
...and walk on in this world.
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The time that ticked away...
toki wa ima hajimari tsuge
時は今始まり告げ
...ceaselessly now announces the beginning.
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Putting my unchanging feelings into it,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door.
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走りだした未来を描くため
My heart awoke to draw the future where I'd start running.
muzukashii michi de tachidomattemo sora wa
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road,
kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru dakara kowakunai
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる だから怖くない
the sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue, so I'm not scared.
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get broken.
Episode 8     I'm really stupid
Sayaka-chan, you shouldn't be fighting like that.
You're lying when you say it doesn't hurt.
It hurt just watching you.
You can't say it's OK to hurt yourself just because you can't feel it.
If I hadn't done that, I wouldn't have been able to win.
I don't have any natural talent for this sort of thing.
Even if you fight like that and win, it's not going to help you out in the end.
And what would help me?
Now that I've been turned into this thing, how can anything help me?
Sayaka-chan...
All I can do now is kill witches.
I'm just a rock without any other purpose.
I just pretend to be alive by controlling a dead body.
Who would do something for me when I'm like this?
Thinking about it is pointless.
But I'm just wondering what could make you happier...
You should fight, then.
Huh?
Kyubey told me. You have more natural talent than anyone else, right?
You can take out the witches just like that, without having to suffer like I do, right?
I... That's not...
If you want to do something for me, how about trying to walk in my shoes first?
But you can't, can you? Of course not.
You couldn't give up your humanity just because you pity me.
It's not pity. I...
You can do anything, but instead you sit there, and I'm the one who has to go through all of this.
Don't try to act like you know what it's like when you're not even willing to do it yourself.
Sayaka-chan.
Don't follow me.
I'm so stupid.
What did I just say?!
No one can save me now...
Homura
The Walpurgis Night is predicted to appear in this area.
What are you basing that on?
Statistics.
Statistics?
I've never heard of a Walpurgis coming to this city before.
Just what did you base your statistics on?
Neither of us is exactly the trustworthy type,
but don't you think you could give me a little more insight into what's going on?
I'd like to know as well, Akemi Homura.
Why the hell are you here?
I guess I wasn't invited.
I came here tonight to deliver some information that I thought you'd be very interested in.
Huh?
Miki Sayaka is depleting herself far faster than I imagined.
Using magic isn't the only problem; she's started to carry a curse within herself.
And whose fault do you think that is?
At this rate, it might become an issue before the Walpurgis Night arrives.
I recommend you be cautious.
What does that mean? What are you talking about?
How about you try asking her instead of me?
I imagine you already know, Akemi Homura.
I thought so.
I'm very interested in where you obtained that information.
Are you...
I've heard what you had to say.
Begone.
You're just going to let him be?
Killing it won't solve anything.
Well anyway, what issue was he talking about involving Miki Sayaka?
Her Soul Gem has accrued too many impurities.
If it is not purified soon, the damage will be irreparable.
Homura
The word "must" means that someone has to do something.
An obligation of sorts. But "have to" has a different...
I should have followed her...
Huh? Shizuki-san, is your house in this direction?
I don't think I remember you ever going this way.
You're right. I'm in the complete opposite direction.
Huh?
Then why are you going this way today?
I want...
...to talk to you about something, Kamijou-kun.
Huh?
She hasn't come home? Not since last night?
OK... Um... I understand.
OK. Thank you.
I need to find Sayaka-chan.
Why don't you get it?
You're already near your breaking point.
Fight only the witches.
Shut up.
Mind your own business.
Your Soul Gem is already at its limit.
If you do not purify it now...
Use this.
What are you planning now?
I've had enough.
You don't have the time to doubt others right now.
Does it bother you that much to have somebody help you?
I'm going to become a different type of magical girl than all of you
I've decided that.
I won't associate myself with people who use and abandon others.
I don't need any reward for my work.
I'll never use magic for my own benefit.
You'll die.
If I were to die, it would be when I am no longer able to kill witches.
In other words, there'd be no need for me any more.
That's fine, then.
The world doesn't need me if I can't even beat the witches.
Why are you doing this?
I only want to save you.
Why won't you believe me?
I wonder...
I just know somehow...
...that you're a liar.
You look like you've given up on everything.
You always speak such empty words.
This is no different.
You say you're trying to help me out,
but you're really thinking about something else completely, aren't you?
You can't fool me like that.
And in turn, you keep hurting Madoka more and more.
Madoka has nothing to do with this.
No, everything is for her.
You're pretty quick.
Yes, you got it.
I don't want to save you.
I just don't want Madoka to have to see you destroy yourself.
If you refuse me here, you'll die either way.
And if you're just going to continue to make Madoka suffer further...
...then I might as well...
...kill you this instant, with my own hands,
Miki Sayaka.
Hey! Hurry up and get out of here!
Are you nuts?
Weren't you trying to save her?
Let me go.
I get it. If I hold onto you like this, you can't use that weird technique of yours.
Huh?
Damn it.
You can't let them make any excuses.
You need to take control of every penny they've made.
Women are stupid, so if you give them a little bit of their money, they'll use it on something stupid.
Yeah, you're right. You can't treat them like people.
You need to train them like they're dogs or something.
She gets off on that, too.
If you just threaten a girl and say you're going to punch them, they'll usually keep their mouths shut.
You stop paying attention for a second,
and then all of a sudden they're saying they want to get married or something.
You can't spoil them.
There's no way a cabaret girl like her could earn the same amount ten years from now.
She needs to learn her place, am I right?
They're really annoying when you get rid of them, too.
You're really good at that, Shou-san. I'm really jealous.
I need to learn how to do that-
Hey, tell me more about her.
Huh?
The woman you were just talking about. Tell me more about her.
Are you in middle school?
You shouldn't be out so late at night.
That person cared about you and wanted to make you happy, so she tried really hard, right?
You knew that, right?
And now you're comparing her to a dog.
You're not even going to thank her?
You're going to throw her away because she's not useful any more?
Who the hell is this? Someone you know?
N-No...
Is this world worth saving?
Why was I fighting? Tell me.
I'm ordering you to tell me right now.
If you don't, I'll...
Sayaka-chan, where are you...
Do you hate me, too?
If I hated you, would you return Sayaka-chan to normal?
I can't. I don't have the power to do that.
You once said I could become a really amazing magical girl... Was that true?
Amazing is an understatement.
You'd become a magical girl of unbelievable power.
Probably the strongest in the world.
If I had accepted your offer, I wonder
if Sayaka-chan would've become a magical girl.
Sayaka made her own wish come true.
That's completely unrelated to you.
Why me?
I don't know either.
To put it bluntly, the scale of your latent power is so great that it, theoretically, isn't even possible.
I'd like someone to explain it to me, too.
I see.
If you released your power, we wouldn't just be talking about miracles any more.
It might even be possible to warp the laws of the universe itself.
I still don't even know why you alone have so much potential resting within you.
I thought I had nothing good going for me.
I thought I would continue on living until I died, never helping anyone, never being useful.
That made me frustrated, and it made me feel alone. But I thought I couldn't do anything about it.
Looks like reality turned out to be quite different.
Madoka, you can even become an omnipotent god if you wish for it.
I wonder if I could do what you can't.
For example?
If I contracted with you, could I return Sayaka-chan to normal?
I'm sure you could do that without a problem.
Would you offer your soul for that wish?
If I could help Sayaka-chan, I'd do it.
I'd become a-
T-That was terrible! You didn't have to kill him!
Why... Why do you always sacrifice yourself?
Don't demean yourself by saying that you're of no use to anyone or that you're worthless.
Think about the people who care about you! Stop doing that!
How come you don't realise there are people who would be sad if they lost you?!
What about the people who were trying to protect you?!
Homura-chan...
Have we...
Have we met before?
I...
I'm sorry...
I need to look for Sayaka-chan.
Wait.
It's too late for Miki Sayaka...
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Madoka!
You know, it's pointless trying.
You don't learn either, do you?
There are plenty of replacements, but someone taking one out for no reason is still a pain.
It's a waste.
This marks the second time you've killed me.
But now I know what type of technique you're using.
That was time-manipulation magic, wasn't it?
Thought so.
I had a feeling that was the case...
You're not from this timeline, are you?
I know who you are and what you're really planning.
I see.
That's why you're trying so hard to stop me.
You want to change Kaname Madoka's fate that much?
That's right.
I'm going to stop you, Kyubey.
No, I should say, Incubator.
I finally found you.
Just how stubborn do you plan to be?
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Huh? You're not acting like yourself.
Yeah.
That's because I don't really care any more.
I don't know any more... what exactly I was trying to protect, or what was so important to me.
Hey...
The balance between hope and despair, it keeps itself at zero. When was it you told me that?
I understand what you mean now.
I did save quite a few people, but in exchange, hatred and jealousy filled my heart.
I even hurt my best friend.
Sayaka, are you...
Someone has to be cursed to balance out a wish for someone else's happiness.
That's how we magical girls work.
I'm really stupid.
Sayaka!
This country calls growing women "girls", right?
Then it only makes sense to call those who will eventually become witches "magical girls".
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
The light of love you lit in your eyes one day...
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki o koete
...transcends time,
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume o
and surely destroy one dream...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
...of this world and hurries to its ruin.
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai o nomihoshite
Swallow down your hesitation.
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani
What is it that you wish for?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no
will there be a good future?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
Like ancient magic...
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no you ni
...that I dreamed of when I was young,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
with the power to slash the darkness,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
I want to meet the smiling you.
微笑む君に会いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In these frightened hands of mine,
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
I have the courage of hand-picked flowers.
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari o yobisamasu
a wish that awaken...
光を呼び覚ます
negai
...the light.
願い
Illustrator Takuya Fujima
Cooperation Tanaka Kentaro
You might think I'm stupid,
but I don't want to give up...
...until we know for sure that she can't be saved.
Episode 9     I won't let that happen
I won't let that happen.