On March 1st, 18 years ago,
Hinazuki was standing alone at this park as always.
It was a little before 6 PM.
Back then, I was on my way to the hideout.
I think I went to get my gloves.
I don't remember whether I actually found them there.
When I left the hideout and glanced toward the river bank,
I saw Mr. Yuuki sitting there, facing the water.
And by the time I passed by the park, taking the shortest route back,
Hinazuki was gone.
February 24th
Look at the blackboard, class.
Hinazuki Kayo becomes the first victim in a serial kidnapping and murder case one week from now.
X-Day.
If I can make sure nothing happens on March 1st and have a birthday party with Hinazuki the next day,
that will definitely change the future.
I'll erase that incident from the history books.
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
I came to a halt, and I came to reflect
On an endless today I had to lament
Made to realize that memories of days past
Are not eternal, they will not last
I've spent my days tearing myself apart
Crying alone in a corner of my heart
The times told me not to let go of what I'd got
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
But like water under a bridge, they were lost
I wanted to say it's a phase I regret most
But on that day I missed my shot
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
Today's another day I tear myself apart
Engraving a scar I'll always recollect
Saying it's you I want
ERASED
February 25th, 1988
Mornin', Satoru.
Morning.
Breakfast'll be ready in a bit.
'Kay.
Thanks for the food.
Hey, Mom.
I want to go out on Saturday.
On a date?
N-No! I thought I could visit the science center with my friends.
Aw. And here I woulda given you
some extra pocket money if it was.
For real?
It is actually a date, ain't it?
Yep.
Why don't you bring her home?
We could have some hot pot or somethin'.
Hinazuki's coming to the birthday party.
Oh, you mean the Hinazukis over on 5th?
Damn. I'm giving her all the answers she wants.
You can go, as long as you promise to be careful.
Thanks.
Now hurry up and eat.
'Kay!
Rise.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Bow.
Goodbye!
Liveman's starting soon. Doesn't it look amazing?!
It does!
What's a falcon?
They're like eagles but cooler!
Wow, you're so smart.
This Saturday, I'm going to get Hinazuki out of her house—
no, away from her mother's abuse.
Mr. Yashiro!
What is it?
I don't get this part. Could you explain it to me?
Let me see.
Tch.
Love is in the air, eh? It's pissin' me off.
Weren't you the same until just recently?
Quit being stubborn and join them, yo.
"Yo"? Are you tryin' to act cool?
Oh, crap.
Mr. Yashiro thinks I'm a thief.
And so do you.
Forget it.
Guys, I've got an idea.
What is it?
Uh, what say we visit the science center on Saturday?
Hinazuki's coming too.
Sounds good!
Sorry, Satoru.
There's something I gotta do that day.
O-Oh...
I can't go either, Satoru.
I got something important to do too.
Y-Yeah. I'd love to go, but I'm busy as well.
S-Same here.
I see...
If you're going with Hinazuki,
we'd just drag you down, anyway.
Ta-ta!
Somethin' happen, Fujinuma?
Oh, nothing.
I told them I couldn't hang out on
Saturday 'cuz I have a date with you.
"I told them I couldn't hang out on
Saturday 'cuz I have a date with you."
Imagine if I said that out loud.
Which I did...
But...
My mother told me to come straight home on Saturdays.
There's somewhere I wanna take you.
I'll talk to her.
Kenya.
Could you drop by the staff room for a bit?
Absolutely not.
I won't have two children going out on their own.
We're not just going to play.
We'll be learning things, too!
You can do that at home.
Kayo helps me here on Saturdays.
Helps you? With what?
Releasing your pent-up stress?
That's none of your business.
Why are you so against her going out?
Why wouldn't I be?
You're kids.
Who d'you think'll have to take
responsibility if you get into trouble?
The nerve of this bitch...
What's with you, anyway?
What would you stand to gain from takin' this gloomy girl anywhere?
Who cares about that? I just want to save my friend!
Save?
Save Kayo from what?
You think you're some knight in shining armor?
Crap.
I really shouldn't have hinted at her abuse!
How do you feel, Kayo?
D'you want to go with him?
Get your minds out of the gutter, you perverted brats!
Mom!
Stop it, Ms. Hinazuki.
You shouldn't go around callin' kids "perverted brats."
Ms. Fujinuma...
This has nothing to do with you.
It does, partly.
Our kids are motivated about somethin',
so as their parents, shouldn't we help them out?
I think our families have plenty in common.
Drop by for a chat sometime.
Get inside, Kayo.
Okay.
S-See you on Saturday. It's a promise.
Did I stick my nose where it don't belong?
Nah. Thank you.
I got off work early and just happened to see you kids.
Good thing I followed you.
You were following us?!
I-I was obviously kiddin'.
Anyway, things should be okay for today.
She was wearing surprisingly nice clothes.
It shows that the mother cares about appearances.
Do you know about the Hinazuki family situation?
Hinazuki
Nah.
But between that conversation and her mother,
I can pretty much guess.
That's a former TV news reporter for you.
Kayo's pretty cute, eh?
You're 29 years old! What are you blushing for?!
Don't abandon her now.
Of course not.
Saturday, February 27th
Saturday, February 27th.
It was a clear day.
Looks like Hinazuki's mother has thought better of hitting her these past few days.
This guy's my friend.
What are you, stupid?
Man, I love this place!
There's almost no one here.
It's like we snuck in. Exciting, right?
Whenever I see someone else, I hide.
Hey, she didn't ask me if I was stupid.
Take a peek into this thing.
Wanna see the planetarium?
Planetarium
It's just about to start.
I got my fill of stars the other night.
I guess...
Planetarium
I gotta run to the bathroom.
Okay. I'll be around.
What is this feeling?
Déjà vu?
I did come here often,
but never before with Hinazuki.
Hinazuki.
Fujinuma.
Thanks for inviting me today.
Did you know I liked this place too?
Did I?
Is that why I chose this place?
Do aspiring manga artists
tend to come to places like this?
I remember having this same conversation 18 years ago.
I came here by myself and ran into Hinazuki.
What?
N-Nothing.
M-Maybe they do.
Am I just repeating everything from that time?
I thought I was trying to change the future,
but have I been unwittingly going down the same path again?
Hinazuki!
Let me hold your coat.
Now?
I've changed a bunch of things with my actions.
I should believe.
Believe that I can change the future.
Fujinuma.
I'm glad I mustered up the courage to come.
Me too.
Satoru.
Hinazuki.
Hey there!
I got done early, so here I am.
Sorry we're late.
See? It changed.
Are we interrupting?
Of course not.
Right, Hinazuki?
Right.
Wow, Satoru's such a gentleman!
Episode 4
Success
Class 5-4
Good morning!
Morning, Fujinuma.
Oh, morning, Hinazuki.
Thank goodness.
It's Monday, but she's here on time.
A pretty, unblemished face.
I said that out loud.
D-Did you hear that?!
February 29th
Whoa!
Satoru's got guts!
Are you gonna get married?!
Don't be stupid! They gotta get engaged first!
February 29th
Get what?
Congrats!
Take your seats. We're starting morning homeroom.
Hope
Hinazuki is due to be murdered tomorrow,
February 29th
on March 1st.
The real battle starts here.
Ta-ta, Hiromi!
See you tomorrow!
Hey, Hinazuki.
I'll come pick you up tomorrow.
Let's walk to school together.
Sure.
Oh, Mom...
Good evening.
See you tomorrow, then. I'll come by in the morning.
I'm off!
Okay!
I left home a tad early.
March 1st, 1988.
The day Hinazuki disappeared 18 years ago.
Good morning.
But today will be different.
Morning, Fujinuma.
Morning.
Hinazuki won't be going anywhere.
We're off.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Things are different than they were the first time around.
Satoru's got guts!
Hinazuki was targeted because she was always by herself in that park.
Well, you guys better come tomorrow!
Yeah.
Of course.
Yep.
As of a few days ago, that's no longer the case.
Hey, let's go to the children's center.
And I'm with her today.
I want to go home early today.
Come on, hang out with me.
Okay.
Everything will be all right.
I win again.
Jeez, you're good!
Okay, maybe not everything.
Hey, Fujinuma. I should get home.
Yeah, I guess.
It's snowing...
Use the word 'pole' in a sentence.
Teach ate a polar bear from the North Pole.
I'll come by tomorrow, too!
See you then!
'Kay.
I said it as loud as I could.
So that Hinazuki, her mother inside,
and anybody else who might've been listening nearby got the message.
That I'm right here.
X-Day is almost over.
Is this really it?
I'm such an idiot.
What's the point of coming here?
I did it!
I definitely changed history today.
Morning, Mom.
Huh? It's not even 6 AM yet!
I'm off.
What about breakfast?
In the end, I couldn't sleep a wink.
I just wanted to see Hinazuki as soon as possible.
Morning, Hinazuki.
What are you, stupid?
1988 National
Hockey Champions
You guys are free now, right?
Free as a bird!
We're gonna party it up at your place!
Then let's go shopping—
Hey, Satoru, Kayo!
Come help me for a bit.
Why today?
Oh, well.
It's probably cause we messed up while on duty the other day.
Probably.
Man, this is heavy.
Did they seriously not wait for us?
That's ice cold.
Your total comes to 5,000 yen.
Got it.
Come to think of it, the bill was
exactly 5,000 yen 18 years ago too.
I was so excited about my birthday that I spent all the money I had.
I think my mother and I made a ton of sandwiches and ate them by ourselves.
I'm home.
One, two...
Satoru! Hinazuki!
Satoru & Kayo
Happy Birthday!!
Happy birthday!
Y-You planned all this in secret?
They said they wanted to do this, so I gave 'em a hand.
Don't tell me...
Is that why we had to help after school?
Yeah, we asked Mr. Yashiro.
He told us it was Hinazuki's birthday too.
Well, we just wanted to surprise you a bit.
It worked!
Satoru insisted on getting two cakes.
Sorry, Fujinuma.
I couldn't finish your present in time.
You were working on something?
Yeah...
Oh, so that's why she wanted to leave so badly yesterday.
I almost had it done last night, but I fell asleep.
Don't worry.
You can give it to me later.
All right, everyone.
Let's make 5,000 yen worth of sandwiches!
What? You used up all that money?
It was a lot of fun making sandwiches with so many people.
Unlike 18 years ago, we finished them all in one day.
It's fun having friends.
Hinazuki and I got a lot of presents from everyone.
And...
Open it.
Thank you, Fujinuma.
All of you, too. Thank you so much.
We'll handle the cleaning up.
You walk Hinazuki home.
I-It's cold.
What are you, stupid?
B-Bye.
Here.
I'm glad I became friends with you and the rest.
Thanks for today.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
That's a promise.
Okay. It's a promise.
Goodnight.
Yes!
I did it!
I made it through!
I changed history!
The guys were gone by the time I got home.
With my fatigue from the past two days hitting its peak,
and my mind being freed from all the tension,
I instantly collapsed into bed and slept like a log.
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
Damn, I'm late!
Good morning!
Oh, Satoru.
You made it just in time.
S-Safe...
So Kayo is the only one who's late.
Hinazuki didn't come to school on the day after our birthday.
The promise we made at the end was never fulfilled.
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory