I had last met Sengoku Nadeko more than six years ago.
Thus, I didn't recognize her at first when we met again.
If I had only realized sooner that it was her,
perhaps the story wouldn't have ended like this.
Koyomi onii-chan
Cut 25
Cut 26
Cut 27
But those regrets don't mean anything to her or the oddity.
I let out a belated shout
at the state of
Sengoku Nadeko's skin.
All of her skin was covered with scale marks.
From the tips of her toes up to her collarbone.
Snugly.
For a moment,
I thought they were growing from her skin,
but upon closer inspection, they weren't.
They were simply pressed
on, like a woodcut--
It looked as though her skin had been pressed into a pattern.
It looked like
she was even
bleeding internally
here and there.
Those painful-looking scars
made her look like she had been bound with rope.
No--
Bondage scars?
Seriously, it was from the tips of her toes, up her legs, and along her body--
It was like something was coiling itself around her.
Something
invisible.
Scale marks, all over her body.
Coiled
around her.
Coiled... as if she were possessed.
Coil
At best, the only areas without the scale marks were both her arms,
and from her neck up.  No need to get her to show me what her
waist and lower abdomen look like underneath those bloomers.
Yellow
Unnumbered cut
Episode 9
Nadeko Snake
Part 1
Font used in video:
HGP Mincho B
That girl just now...
I didn't expect to run into anyone up here.
Especially not a girl that cute.
Whatever, let's keep climbing.
Oh, and watch your step.
Don't mind the bug bites, but this mountain is full of snakes.
By the way, Araragi-senpai...
I know I asked you about it yesterday, but just what are you doing up here?
Oshino gave me a job.
Do not enter
Danger
Look out
above
Under construction
Do not enter
Do
not
enter
It seems that there's an abandoned shrine up here.
He wanted me to stick an ofuda on its altar.
Can't he do it himself?  He's got plenty of free time.
Well, it's my job to do it.
He helped me out, so I owe him.
Don't you owe him too, Kanbaru?
Black
Unnumbered cut
He is a specialist.
He doesn't just lend a hand for free.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Oh, I see.
By the way, did Senjougahara-senpai say
anything to you about today, Araragi-senpai?
Not really.
Did she say anything to you?
Black
Unnumbered cut
She told me to try my hardest to act cute.
Cut 63-A
Oh, and she told me this:
Black
Unnumbered cut
"If Araragi-kun gives you any trouble, give me all the details."
"I'll let you pick which is worse for him: being
buried in the mountains or sunk beneath the sea."
As usual.
Cut 65
She'll let you pick the worse one?!
She's merciless...
Cut 66-B
Oh, that's right, Kanbaru.
Talking about Senjougahara reminded me that it's almost her birthday.
Yeah.  It's July 7th.
I've been thinking about the type of party to have.  It's our first time, so I figured something lively would be nice.
Perhaps we should invite all our friends and have a small birthday party.
No, I think Senjougahara-senpai
wants to spend it alone with you.
She's that fine of a woman?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Hey, Kanbaru.
What, Araragi-senpai?
How's your left arm doing?
According to Oshino-san, it'll heal by the time I become twenty.
That's great.  When you turn 20, you can play basketball again.
I guess.
Black
Unnumbered cut
What's wrong, Kanbaru?
I'm a little worn out.
Worn out?  Why don't we find somewhere to rest?
Red
Unnumbered cut
There's gotta be somewhere we can sit down.
Never mind that, Araragi-senpai.  Why don't we eat?
Eat?
When I'm feeling down, I normally
cheer right up when my tummy's full.
She's like a comic book character
Cut 109
Got it.
Okay, Kanbaru.  Find somewhere where we have room to unpack the lunch box.
Black
Unnumbered cut
While you're doing that, I'll go place this ofuda.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Sure.
Sorry for making you do all the work.
All right.
Cut 121
Reminiscence
I feel like I've met that girl somewhere before.
Black
Unnumbered cut
But where would I have met a
middle-school girl?  Through my sisters?
Little sister?
This is the altar?
That should do it.
Hey, Kanbaru!
Kanbaru!
Black
Unnumbered cut
Kanbaru?  Kanbaru!
Kanbaru?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Oh, it's you, Araragi-senpai.
Come on, what kind of reaction is that?
Sorry.
I just lost my head for a second.
You don't look that good.  Are you okay?
If you're feeling that sick, I'll clean off the
porch around the altar so you can lie down.
No, that's not it.
Look at that.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Huh?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Reminiscence
Sengoku Nadeko
Cut 164
That was... Sengoku Nadeko?
* Hanekawa, let's meet up after school.
* If you don't mind, there's something I'd like you to do.
Cut 167
These two.
This one might be useful.
If you're looking for efficiency, you should try that one.
Big     Book     store
Cut 178
Search, search
Modern Lit
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Civics
Logic
Math
Governance
Modern Lit
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Logic
Math
Governance
Modern Lit
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Logic
Math
Governance
Modern Lit
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Logic
Math
Governance
Modern Lit
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Logic
Math
Governance
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Logic
Math
Governance
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Logic
Math
Governance
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Math
Governance
New Clarified
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Math
Governance
College Exam Prep
Physics
Foreign Languages
English
Civics
Math
Governance
Reference     Books
Cut 178
Five
Books
Cut 178
I'm surprised you asked me to help you pick reference books.
Meeting People
Gateway to Truth
Dance of
Awakening
I figured it was about time to focus on my future.
Your future?
Future
Cut 183
Lately, I've been talking about it with Senjougahara.
When I found out about her first choice...
Oh...  Senjougahara-san is going to the local national
university, right?  Doesn't she already have a recommendation?
You know everything.
Black
Unnumbered cut
I don't know everything; I just happen to know this.
So you're aiming for the same university as her?
Don't tell her yet.  I don't want her to get any weird ideas.
North
South
Computer
Escalator
Information
Business/Society
Science and Technology
Medicine
Easy-to-
understand
Modern Magic
Summoning
Magic
Flashy
Story
Speaking with
the Dead
Numerology
Spiritual
Self-Defense
By the way, Araragi-kun.
What's with the sudden formality?
Weren't you talking about that ruined shrine at school yesterday?
for Exams
Mathematics
Foreign Languages
English
College Exam
Physi
I'm curious about it.
What happened after you found that chopped-up snake there?
Snake
Cut 196
Snake     Snake     Snake
SNAKE
Cut 196
Black
Unnumbered cut
Snake   corpses
Cut 196
Oh, that?
Kanbaru and I dug a hole and buried it, just in case.
Reminiscence
But when we took a walk around, we found that the whole place was full of snake corpses.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Reminiscence
Full of corpses?
Yeah.
Full of dismembered corpses.
So we left right away, and ate the lunch she made at a nearby park.
I was amazed at how tasty it was.  She said her grandma helped to make it.
Reference
Taste
minutes 01 in made be can Recipes
Well, it must have been pretty tough, Araragi-kun.
Now that I think about it, I'm sure someone was holding some kind of ritual and killing the snakes like that.
After all, it was at a shrine.
Reference
Did you know there was a shrine there, Hanekawa?
Yeah, the Kita-Shirahebi Shrine.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Snake, huh.  That means...
Yeah, it seems that it's there to worship a snake god.
I don't really know that much about it, either.
Modern Lit
College Exam Prep
Physics
Society / Logic / Civics
Mathematics
English
Killing snakes at a shrine for a snake god...
It's gotta be some kind of ritual.
I guess I'd better tell Oshino about it.
That's not what I was talking about, Araragi-kun.  I meant it was tough for Kanbaru-san.
A-b-o-u-t K-a-n-b-a-r-u-s-a-n.
I said it must have been tough for her.
Floor Information    1F
Occult/Magic
Black
Unnumbered cut
For Kanbaru?  Yeah, I guess.
After all, she did get sick all of a sudden.
I wonder why.
Oh well, I'm glad it was nothing serious.
That's not what I meant.  Should you be getting that friendly with your girlfriend's junior?
It's nice to get along, but walking hand-in-hand is pushing it.
I had to.  She's touchy-feely.
You think she'll take that for an excuse?
Well, uh...
Cut 237
Come on, Senjougahara said it herself.
Cut 238
"I won't let you be rude to my junior."
Senjougahara told me to help her out too.
I see.  Kind of like this?
Red
Unnumbered cut
Black
Here you go.
Hanekawa's scent
Cut 248
Hanekawa's breath
Cut 249
Like that, right?
Like you were just a breadth away.  Right, Araragi-kun?
What are you talking about?
You're pretty waffly, Araragi-kun.
Cut 255
You're kind to everyone, aren't you?
That has to be kind of disturbing to Senjougahara-san.
Disturbing?
She doesn't want you getting along too well with Kanbaru-san, does she?
Am I right?  Getting along is fine.  If anything, she wants the two of you to get along,
but she wants a clear line to be drawn.
It seems that she wants to be sure you'd pick her out of the two of them.
I don't get it.
It's a dilemma for her too, isn't it?
You're her dear boyfriend, but Kanbaru-san is her dear junior.
Cut 263
And Kanbaru's into yuri, too, isn't she
Oh well, she's a tsundere, so I don't think you should try to understand everything she does.
Cut 263
媒体は非直結です
You've got to figure out what she really means.
Modern Lit
College Exam Prep
Physics
Society / Logic / Civics
Mathematics
English
If she's that dear to you, you've got to resist your temptations too.
Being kind to everyone is a bit irresponsible.
I'll take those words to heart.
Book Specials
Anthologies of
Ancient Japanese Literature
Japanese
Literature
Historical
Fiction
By the way, Hanekawa.  Where are you going to college?
Tokyo, right?  Or are you studying overseas?
I'm not going to college.
You're not going to college?!
After I graduate, I'm going on a trip.
Naoe
A trip?!
I figure I'll take a couple years off and see the world.
Book Specials
I've got plenty of knowledge.
Anthologies of
Ancient Japanese Literature
Japanese
Literature
Historical
Fiction
I think I should get some real-life experience too.
Don't tell the teachers yet, okay?
If you do, they'll be shocked.
I think they'll be more than just shocked.
Ow!
Headache
Cut 285
What's wrong?
I just have a little headache.
College Exam Prep
Physics
Headache?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Lately, I've just been getting headaches suddenly.
Hey, that's not fine.
I'll walk you home.
No, I'm fine.  I'm not going home.
Red
Unnumbered cut
Oh, right.
College Exam Prep
Physics
Anyway, sorry, but I'm leaving.
Later then.
Nadeko
Cut 292
Sengoku?
Entrance
Magic
Cut 296
Occult
Cut 298
Encyclopedia of
Snake Curses
Mysterious
Philosophy
Suwa
Grand Shrine
Red
Unnumbered cut
This is...
Black
Unnumbered cut
Hey, Kanbaru?  Mind giving me a hand?
So what do you need?
Do you remember the girl we saw on these stairs yesterday?
Yeah, she was a cute little thing.
I think I recognize her from somewhere.
I figured it out when I saw her at the bookstore earlier.
I think she's an old friend of my youngest sister.
What?!
So she's at the shrine again today?
Yeah, I think.
I need you to, uh...
It's tough to go up to an old acquaintance and say hi.
She might not remember me, so it'll seem like a creepy pickup line.
The self-defense instincts of an
adolescent girl are pretty fearsome.
You sound like you know that from experience.
Can't deny that.
And you seem like you're pretty
good with younger girls, Kanbaru.
After all, you're the school's top star.
I see.  I get what you mean.
I guess I am pretty good with younger girls.
You sure are.
I'm glad I asked you.
If you put it that way, of course I'm glad to help.
But you've taken what happened
yesterday into account, haven't you?
Reminiscence
Snake
Cut 318
Well, I guess.
So that's how it is.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Well, well.
Sengoku!
Black
Unnumbered cut
Stop it, Sengoku!
Koyomi Onii-chan...
Reminiscence
Friends.
Sengoku Nadeko, class 2-1.
I don't have many friends.  But Bara-chan plays with me.
Reminiscence
When Bara-chan asked me to play, I was really happy.
Bara-chan has an older brother in sixth grade.
Her big brother's name is Koyomi.
The rest is omitted
Come right in.
Black
Unnumbered cut
This room's changed.
Yeah, it's set up for single person now.
My sisters are in the same room as before.
I think they'll be home soon.  Want to see them?
Black
Unnumbered cut
So this is Araragi-senpai's room?
This is the first time I've been in a boy's room.
All right, time to look for the porno mags.
Black
Unnumbered cut
That kind of thing only happens when a guy goes over to another guy's place!
Just sit over there, okay?!
It's useful to know your fetishes.
It's not just useless for me, it's actually harmful.
Yeah, that's what I mean.  Harmful books.
You're a live specimen of a harmful book!
Either sit there, or jump out the window.
Make a choice, Kanbaru!
I figured out your fetishes when I was stalking you before.
I know exactly what kind of porn you've been buying lately.
Black
Unnumbered cut
What?  No way?!
Cut 374
There was no one at all in the store back then!
Cut 375A
Cut 375B
Cut 376
I made sure of it!
Cut 377
Suruga
You've got pretty pervy kinks!
You've made your choice.  Out the window with you!
Dammit!
I'm gonna kill you!
Koyomi
Cut 379
Suruga
Cut 380
Most girls would rather jump out the window than do that !
But of course, I can do it easily and casually.
Do you, the viewer, have a secret fetish?
Cut 381
You're showing off!
Koyomi Onii-chan.  And Kanbaru-san.
Can you turn around for a second?
It's fine now.  You can turn back around.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Bloomers?
I gave her those.  I keep them around to wear from time to time.
Oh, you wear bloomers from time to time?
It's only natural for a lady to have this kind of interest.
No, it's just like a pervert.
A middle-school girl's underwear
Cut 400
It's not like I don't understand why Sengoku doesn't want to stand there in her panties, but bloomers ?
Embarrassment
Cut 400
A maiden's heart
Black
Unnumbered cut
What's she doing?
They look like scars from bondage.
There are scale marks.
A fish?  No, these are reptilian...  A snake!
Koyomi Onii-chan.
You're all grown up, so you won't feel dirty looking at my body, right?
Of course!
Right, Kanbaru?
You're forgetting something, Araragi-senpai.
In a situation like this, it's even ruder to tell a girl you're not interested in her body at all.
I see.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Let me correct myself.  I feel a little bit dirty looking at your body.
Come on, Kanbaru!  I did what you said, and it made her cry!
Who do you think you are, playing it straight like that?
Hey, Sengoku.
I...  I hate my body!
Sengoku...
Cut 498
I hate it!  Please save me, Koyomi Onii-chan!
Koyomi
onii
chan
Black
Unnumbered cut
Deneb, Altair, and Vega
That's the Summer Triangle you pointed at
I remember that when I look up at the sky
I finally found Vega
But where are you, Altair?
You'll be alone like this
I looked up from the pitch dark world
It's like the night sky is filled with raining stars
I wonder when I started to chase after you
Please, no matter what
Don't be surprised
Listen to
These feelings
Of mine
Now streaming an extended preview at our website!
Preview
Dialog
Nisioisin
Cartoon
Haritama Hiroki
I'm Karen!
I'm Tsukihi!
Catch her!
Avenge Koyomi!
Suruga
Modern quiz!
Modern?
Damn,
she's fast
I can't see!
We're in a once-in-a-century recession!
This is my
last resort
That was quick
How serious!
Next episode, Nadeko Snake, part 2!
Next Time
Nadeko Snake Part 2
So in every century, 99 years are boom years!
That's good
Squeeee!
She's
turned on!
How optimistic!