When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Milady.
Come on a date with me.
Golden Week makes the school really quiet.
It's great that I got my position as homeroom teacher back, but I've got to make sure to get that salary up.
God, I feel like crap.
I don't feel like correcting tests at all.
I guess a drink would perk me up.
Cheers!
Yup. Hawaii's the best place to be during Golden Week break.
Hey! I'm trying to set the mood, taking one for the team!
Calm down.
Nagi's gone to the Aegean Sea.
Why didn't you go with her?
I didn't want to disturb the two of them.
I see.
Gather all the volumes of the work Bro said he wanted to see!
Sir!
Wh-What is this about?
Are they here for the Godfather series?
Or perhaps Battle Without Morals?
If it's V Cinema shows, it'll be hard to gather everything.
Do you have all the Brave ***aiser VCR volumes?
I'm not accepting half.
Oh.
Sure we do.
Then how about Super Human Robot *****der?
Not bad.
If you want, we have the entire Fight! *****man, too.
I'll come again.
Today's episode takes place on Mykonos Island where Milady is for vacation.
Therefore, those of us who stayed to watch
the house won't get any screen time, I guess.
I don't think it's so bad to have a week off.
Strange, did I just hear someone?
Must be my imagination.
"A week off", someone says, but this is the final episode.
WHAT?! SERIOUSLY?!
I think I heard something again.
Wow! So this is the Aegean Sea?!
Milady, come and see this!
Come to think of it, this is your first time to Mykonos Island, isn't it?
Yes. I've been offshore fishing to the cold ocean, so I have been to Iturup Island before.
I'm glad you didn't get arrested.
Milady! The ocean's very beautiful!
So is the Clear Black LCD, so I'm fine.
Since when has Milady been like that?
I'm not sure. She's always been like that.
You can't do anything about some things.
Isn't there anything we can do about it?
So this is Cappadocia!
This indeed is a great view!
So people used to live in those stone homes, huh?
Look, look, Hina-san. That one looks like a camel's hump.
You're right, it really is like a camel's hump.
That is  a camel!
Stop joking around and enjoy the view from a high place a little.
No! I'm fine!
Hina-san?
Besides, you know I don't like high places, Ayumu.
But, for a person who doesn't like heights,
you were able to get on the plane just fine.
That's why I forced myself to sleep
starting just before the plane took off!
I will not get up until we land, no matter what happens!
You're right. You didn't eat food at all, either.
Not a single bite in that thirteen-hour flight.
Anyway, I like to see views from lower places!
I guess it can't be helped.
You don't seem to be very energetic despite the fact that we're here for a vacation.
There isn't a reason for me to be energetic.
Then let's go outside.
If you're under the great blue sky, you're bound to get energetic.
It's hot out.
Then you're going to stay in the entire time?
Yeah.
I see...
Don't worry. Let's go shopping later, then.
But... But... Milady is...
There's nothing I can do about that.
It's fine. I'll spend my time inside, too.
What should we do now...
Fine! I got it!
I'll go out tomorrow!
Y-You will?!
Yeah. But just for a while, okay?
Just for a while.
Yes!
Sorry for all the trouble regarding her.
It's fine.
It's already been a month since the new school year started.
Please keep watching over Nagi.
Yes.
Milady is starting to adjust to the new classes well, too.
Is she?
I hope she will go to school properly this year.
Y-Yes, I do, too.
Yay! My patent for UFO engineering technology sold!
We're back.
We're back...
Welcome back!
How was Cappadocia?
The eyebrows were long, the nose was split in two, and I got spat on all over.
That was the real camel!
So tomorrow, we go to Greece, eh?
I'm looking forward to seeing the Parthenon.
It's a flat structure.
But it stands at the top of the hill on the Acropolis.
We go to the Mykonos Island after that.
Right. Hayata-kun's there, isn't he?
Yay! So this is Athens!
It's amazing!
You can see the entire city from the Parthenon!
This view! It certainly is a World Heritage site!
But...
Hina-san! Why are you only staring at the Parthenon?
The Parthenon is the World Heritage site! The view doesn't matter!
There you go saying things like that.
It's a waste if you don't see this.
No! I don't need to!
Hina-san...
I don't need to see views from high places.
Besides, where did those three go?
If you want to tour around, take those three with you.
They all said they'd seen this enough times when they were in kindergarten.
Those damn bourgeois girls...
Also, they played all night long, so they wanted to sleep until the time to catch the ship to Mykonos Island came.
But you were playing all night long, too.
So how are you so full of energy?
It's because this is my first trip with you.
This trip is meant for us to become closer friends, right?
I wonder why...
I end up at high places with you so often.
Hayate-kun? You mean you also...
What's the matter?
So? Where can I get the best view from?
Eh, ummm... The view from here.
D-Don't let go of my hands, okay?!
I won't.
Wow, this is like some magical land, isn't it, Milady?
Yeah, in a way, seeing how nothing has changed since long ago, it's like a city where time has stopped.
So you've been here before?
In fact, I used to live here.
Both Maria and I have lived in Japan
for less time than other places combined.
No matter where she went, she would always lock herself up.
Shut up.
But really, rather than always confining yourself indoors, you should start going outside and play.
Is something wrong?
Nothing. I just remembered that there was a guy who said the exact same thing in the past.
I don't remember his face, but he was a thief, a liar, and a guy who couldn't keep promises.
My hat...
Leave it to me, Milady.
Here, Milady.
I got your hat back.
Mi...lady?
Um...
Have you shrunk, Milady?
What are you saying to a person you've just met for the first time?!
I am growing steadily every day!
I-I'm sorry. I mistook you for someone else.
Gosh, you... Give this back to me.
This is my hat.
Y-You can't.
That's Lady Nagi's hat.
So it is mine.
Like I said, this is my, Sanzenin Nagi's, hat, right?
What?! This tiny girl is Lady Nagi?
Don't call me tiny!
What? This can't be. Even if this is an "anything goes" kind of anime...
It can't be!
I jumped into a time slip?!
No, I won't accept this happening.
It can't possibly happen!
E-Excuse me!
What day of the month of the year is today?
Peperoncino?
Naporitana spaghettina carbonara.
Gah! He's a foreigner, so I can't communicate.
See you, commoner. I'm in a hurry.
Don't cause trouble to others.
Wait! Please wait!
What are you doing?! Are you a kidnapper, too?
N-No! I'm not a kidnapper.
Honestly! Let go of me.
Seriously. Because there are people like you...
Anyway... Anyway, the question is why I came to the past.
If I can figure that out...
This is why I don't like going outside.
Milady!
P-Please wait! Please wait a moment, Milady.
Let's change the way of thinking.
If this is the past, and she is the Milady when she was little...
This is...
This is the chance to cure her super-indoor lifestyle.
Then she might be able to become a girl who can be touched by the blue ocean and sky.
Hey, commoner. Why are you smiling?
I'll do this! It will work!
I can do it. I will change Milady with my power!
So, like I was saying, Milady...
Come on a date with me.
Huh?
A first-class lady has to be someone who steps out under the sun.
So will you hang out with me for a while?
W-Well, I guess I can.
Will you be fine?
Fine about what?
How should I say...
Right now, I'm being targeted by the mafia, who're trying to kidnap me.
Why are you seriously being chased by the Sicilian Mafia?!
Don't ask me. I don't want them to, either.
Barbeque! Pancake! Soft serve ice cream!
Italiano taneuma.
Seriously...
This is why I don't like to go outside!
I see.
It's because she's gone through things like this as a child...
...that she confines herself in rooms.
I know! Milady, let's go stargazing on the beach!
Idiot.
I always get in trouble like this. I don't want to go outside.
Don't worry. Past or future, I will protect you.
So, let's go.
Come see the stars with me.
Okay! Then it's a promise!
It'll be all right.
How about we get rid of them before we go see the stars?
Get rid of them? But how?
Please don't worry.
Here, call the police.
You acted gallant and all, but you actually rely on others, eh?
Today, the pacific saury is cheap!
Milady!
Ish ribidish.
Komattarube.
It'll be fine!
I will protect you!
Erika-sama!
Ebi-chan!
Yunsona!
You're pretty good.
I trust you!
Milady...
Yes!
Kyaba-kura.
I'm borrowing this.
Nabeshin! Nabeshin!
Goddamn.
It's all over, Milady.
I'm sorry. I ended up making holes in your hat.
It's fine. It's proof that you protected me.
If you hadn't protected me, I could have died here.
Wait. Could the reason I was summoned to the past be...
Now, as we promised, let's watch the stars here, shall we?
My hat...
Liar...
Hayate!
Milady?
Where did you go off to?
Both Maria and I have been worrying all this time.
You, too. What are you doing here?
Well, um...
It doesn't concern you.
I was just writing a message to the idiot who lied to me.
The time difference between Japan and Mykonos Island is -7 hours.
They must be looking up at the beautiful starry sky above the Aegean Sea.
Yet, we're here stuck watching the house.
You'll comfort me, won't you, Tama?
It is true that because of this, we are capable of spending some alone time.
It's the first time we've looked up at the sky together, isn't it?
Not like I want to look up at the foggy Nerima sky.
I see, I see. So you're lonely, too.
There, good boy. There, good boy.
They are my life...
What, you're still awake?
Yes. I was wondering if Hayate-san is looking up at these stars over at Mykonos Island or not.
I'm sure, but I bet the sky over there is filled with many more stars than this.
Yes.
That's the Torus Shepherd.
Next to it is the Big Dipper.
Beyond that is...
Hey, there's a leak over there.
Keh. I'll show you the stars over the Aegean Sea one of these days.
Yes. I'll look forward to it.
What were you thinking, Hina-san?
I was wondering if Nagi and everyone else were looking at these stars too or not.
I was, too!
Nagi... She said she was going to look for Hayate-kun and...
The stars are very beautiful, aren't they, Milady?
It's not bad to see the stars outside once in a while.
Thank you for protecting me.
Um...
I'm counting on you in the future, too!
Yes! It'll be my pleasure!