Nishimura: IN THIS INFINITELY
LARGE UNIVERSE,
THERE EXISTS A PREP SCHOOL.
FUMIZUKI ACADEMY HAS
BEEN DESIGNED TO ENSURE
ITS STUDENTS CAN SURVIVE
TAKING FIERCELY COMPETITIVE
ENTRANCE EXAMS.
IT'S A SCHOOL FOR
ACADEMIC WARRIORS.
INTELLIGENCE IS THEIR
ONLY WEAPON.
EACH STUDENT PUTS THE
PRESTIGE OF THEIR ENTIRE SCHOOL
ON THE LINE
BY MAKING MAXIMAL USE
OF HIS OR HER BEST SUBJECTS,
THEREBY OVERRUNNING
COMPETITORS' STRATEGIES.
THOSE WITH THE MOST POWER
WILL WIN EACH MATCH
AS WELL AS ACCOLADES,
AND THE RIGHT TO ENJOY
A COMFORTABLE SCHOOL LIFE.
THOSE WHO FAIL WILL NOT
BE SO PRIVILEGED.
THEIR LIVES BECOME WHAT
CAN ONLY BE DESCRIBED
AS AN INDESCRIBABLE HELL.
THIS IS A STORY OF
ACADEMIC WARRIORS
WHO STOOD UP TO
SUCH A CRUEL FATE
WITH HIGH HOPES AND
CEREBRAL STEMS BLAZING.
AND HERE IS WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN THOSE SAME WARRIORS
LOST THE SUMMONER TEST WAR
ON A DAY THAT WAS
VERY MUCH LIKE TODAY.
- WHAT? HOW MUCH IS IT BEFORE
THE STUDENT DISCOUNT?
FOR A MEDIUM SODA? COME ON!
THEY BETTER BE DRIZZLING
THIS POPCORN WITH GOLD-SAUCE.
I'M SPENDING ALL THIS SO I CAN
HANG OUT FOR A COUPLE OF HOURS?
THESE THEATERS ARE FILLED
WITH EVIL AND HATE!
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- UH, THINK ABOUT WHAT?
- THIS ONE. WANNA SEE IT?
- YEAH. THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WE'RE GONNA SEE THAT ONE, 'KAY?
- OH... I, UH...
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU TWO
SEE IT WITHOUT ME?
- Both: WHAT? BUT WHY?
- FINE, WE'LL SEE AN ANIME.
- THAT'S NOT IT!
IT'S NOT THE MOVIE!
- Yuuji: YOU'RE NOT GONNA
GET OUT OF THIS, AKIHISA.
( all exclaiming )
WE'VE LOST THE BATTLE.
JUST ACCEPT IT.
- WHAT THE...
- YOU PICK.
WE'LL SEE WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- I WANNA SEE MY WRISTS.
- APOCALYPSE NOW REDUX.
GREAT CHOICE.
- OH, HELL NO! THAT THING
RUNS OVER THREE HOURS!
- WE'LL WATCH IT TWO TIMES.
- THAT'S LONGER THAN ALL
THE DAY'S CLASSES COMBINED!
- THEN IT'S PERFECT.
THIS'LL MAKE UP FOR ALL
THE TIME I USUALLY LOSE
WITH YOU SINCE WE'RE
IN DIFFERENT CLASSES.
- THAT'S IT, I'M OUT!
- OH, YEAH? I DON'T THINK SO.
( buzzing )
- YOU DON'T THINK WHAT?
OH, CRAP WHAT'S THAT?
( screams )
- NEXT TWO SHOWINGS.
TWO PLEASE.
- 'KAY... ONE STUDENT
AND ONE PASSED OUT
TO WATCH IT TWICE
FOR NO REASON.
- AREN'T THEY JUST
PERFECT TOGETHER?
- THE PERFECT-EST!
- ( theme song playing )
- Nishimura: THIS IS
AKIHISA YOSHII.
HIS PARENTS
ARE WORKING OVERSEAS
AND HIS OLDER SISTER IS STUDYING
ABROAD WHICH MEANS HE IS, AGAIN,
ENJOYING ANOTHER MORNING
HERE AT HOME ALONE.
- HELLO BREAKFAST.
PREPARE TO DIE!
THANKS TO YOUR GREAT SACRIFICE,
DINNER WILL BE MASSIVE.
HMM. WELL, MAYBE NOT MASSIVE,
BUT AT LEAST SLIGHTLY BIGGER
THAN THE BREAKFAST HALF.
- Nishimura: ENJOYING HIMSELF
A LITTLE TOO MUCH, PERHAPS.
- OH. HEY MR. FUKUHARA.
HOW'S IT GOING TODAY?
- AH, GOOD MORNING!
( screams )
- PLEASE DON'T BE BROKEN.
PLEASE DON'T BE BR...
- YOSHII! YOSHII FROM CLASS F!
- YEAH. YOU'RE KUBO
FROM CLASS A. THAT RIGHT?
- CORRECT. TOSHIMITSU KUBO.
SECOND YEAR, RANK TWO.
AND RUNNING LATE.
IF YOU'LL PLEASE EXCUSE ME
I MUST PREPARE FOR CLASS. LATER.
- HOLD ON!
- WHAT IS IT?
- UH, ARE YOU GONNA EAT THAT?
- OF COURSE NOT.
IT'S CONTAMINATED.
- YEAH, GROSS. CAN I HAVE IT?
- PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE GONNA EAT THAT.
- WHY NOT?
IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME.
OF COURSE. IT'S BECAUSE MY LIPS
HAVE ALREADY CARESSED IT.
THIRTY-SECOND RULE.
IT'S TOTALLY FINE.
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE THAT ANT.
- ACTUALLY, I'D PREFER
THAT YOU NOT.
- WHAT? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- THAT WAS A LITTLE FORWARD,
DON'T YOU THINK?
BESIDES, THERE ARE
OTHERS WATCHING.
- OH, RIGHT.
GUESS THAT'S TOO WEIRD.
- QUITE. SEE YOU
ANOTHER TIME THEN.
- SURE. BYE.
IT'S LUNCHTIME!
( groans )
- UH-OH. I THINK I STEPPED
IN SOMETHING.
- IT'S COOL. JUST MY LUNCH
BUT WHO NEEDS FOOD THESE DAYS?
- OH, GOOD MORNING!
HIMEJI?
- YES! A GOOD MORNING, I MEAN.
- THAT LETTER.
I WONDER IF IT'S
A LOVE NOTE FOR YUUJI.
BUT HE'S WITH SHOUKO SO THEN...
- WOW. LOOK WHO DECIDED
TO BE EARLY FOR A CHANGE.
SO HOW'D IT GO YESTERDAY?
- GREAT. I WATCHED A MOVIE
AND THEN MY FOOD BUDGET
DID A DISAPPEARING ACT.
YOU?
- I WOKE UP DURING THE SCENE
WHERE A BUFFALO WAS TIED
TO A POLE AND KILLED.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
THE PERFECT TIME TO ESCAPE.
THEN AN ANGRY ELECTRIC SHOCK
KNOCKED ME UNCONSCIOUS AGAIN!
WHEN I WOKE UP, IT WAS
THE SAME BUFFALO SCENE!
- YOU REALLY WATCHED IT TWICE.
- SIX HOURS.
I GAVE UP TRYING TO RUN AWAY.
NOTHING IS WORTH
GETTING ELECTROCUTED
AND THE LAST THING I WANTED
WAS TO WAKE UP
TO THE WORST SCENE
IN CINEMATIC HISTORY.
- I'M SO SORRY. YOU NEVER
EVEN GOT TO SEE
THE FIRST HALF OF THE MOVIE.
- WHAT AM I GONNA
DO FOR FOOD
UNTIL MY PARENTS CAN
SEND MORE MONEY?
- YOU HAVE A CRAP TON
OF GAMES YOU CAN SELL.
- SACRILEGE!
THOSE ARE BRILLIANT WORKS
HATCHED FROM MINDS OF GENIUSES!
YOU CAN'T JUST TRADE THEM FOR
SOME NOODLES AND A SANDWICH!
- HAVE YOU EVER HEARD THE
SAYING, "YOU REAP WHAT YOU SOW?"
- YES! AND DON'T YOU LECTURE ME
MR. "I STILL HAVE FOOD!"
THIS IS LIFE OR DEATH HERE!
- AKIHISA, DO YOU HONESTLY
THINK YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAS ANY FEARS?
- I'M SORRY.
- IT'S OKAY.
- NO FREAKING WAY.
I DIDN'T THINK THEY
COULD FIND EQUIPMENT
THAT WAS WORSE THAN OURS.
GUESS WE HAVE YOU TO THANK!
LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE TO US!
- THROWING A TANTRUM ISN'T
GOING TO CHANGE THINGS
AND, FOR THE RECORD,
IT WASN'T JUST ME,
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW!
- BUT YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO LOST IT!
- AKI, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO POINT FINGERS AT ANYONE.
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US SCREWED
UP DURING THE WAR AT SOME POINT.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SORRY, YUUJI.
IT WASN'T JUST YOU.
LADY MINAMI ALSO HELPED
TO TRANSFORM...
- "LADY MINAMI," HUH?
ARE YOUTRYING TO MOCK ME?
- YOU TOLD ME
TO CALL YOU THAT, REMEMBER?
- NO! JUST CALL ME MINAMI.
- I TAKE IT BACK!
MINAMI DIDN'T MAKE US LOSE,
SHE WAS JUST WRONG!
OW! STOP! YOU'RE SQUEEZING
MY TEMPLES TOO TIGHT!
- I'M GONNA GO BLIND.
- ALRIGHT. I'M BORED WITH THIS.
- I'M NOT WRONG!
WE WERE ALL COUNTING ON HIM!
IT WAS AN ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL LEVEL TEST
AND HE COULDN'T SCORE A HUNDRED?
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE SO HARD
ON POOR YUUJI.
I STILL LOVE THIS ROOM.
EVEN THOUGH IT MIGHT LOOK
A LITTLE DIFFERENT RIGHT NOW.
- I KNEW IT. SHE LIKES YUUJI.
- AT LEAST IN THIS CLASS I CAN
CHOOSE TO SIT ANYWHERE I WANT.
- DING, DING, DING, DONG.
HEY! IT'S HOMEROOM TIME, KIDS!
EVERYONE HAVE A... OH!
YOU'RE ALREADY SITTING. PERFECT.
- ( giggles )
- UH, WHY ARE YOU HERE,
MR. NISHIMURA?
- WELL, WE FIGURED YOU WERE
TIRED OF BEING STUPID.
SO WE'RE GONNA HELP YOU
BRING UP YOUR POOR TEST SCORES.
SOMEONE CAME TO THE
BRILLIANT CONCLUSION
THAT SINCE I'M IN CHARGE
OF REMEDIAL CLASSES,
THAT I SHOULD ALSO BE
YOUR NEW HOMEROOM TEACHER.
- Students: OUR WHAT?
- LEAVING ME...
WELL, TO TAKE OVER THE ROLE
OF YOUR NARRATOR.
- OUR WHAT?
- IRON MAN'S OUR TEACHER NOW?
- PREPARE TO FLY VIGOROUSLY AND
MERCILESSLY THROUGH THE WRINGER.
- THEY SERIOUSLY WANT US TO BE
TAUGHT BY THE DEVIL EVERY DAY?
- Hideyoshi: IT'S ABUSIVE.
THERE HAS TO BE SOMETHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT THIS.
- THERE IS.
WE JUST HAVE TO FIGHT IN A
SUMMONER TEST WAR AND WIN.
- IT'S NOT THAT EASY.
- WHY NOT?
- THE RULES SAY THAT ONCE
A CLASS LOSES,
THEY CAN'T DECLARE WAR
FOR THREE MONTHS.
- THREE?
- YEP. BUT IT'LL GO BY FAST.
YOU'LL SEE.
PLENTY OF TIME FOR US
TO COME UP WITH A NEW STRATEGY.
- MY LIFE IS SO MUCH HARDER
THAN EVERYONE ELSE'S!
- LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE, MAN.
- HMM?
- JUST FIVE HUNDRED YEN.
- HELL YEAH!
- PLEASURE AS ALWAYS.
- THIS IS AN ORIGINAL.
I CAN TELL. THANKS.
- SO MUCH FOR YOUR FOOD BUDGET.
- ( screaming )
- ARE YOU GONNA BE ALL RIGHT
OVER THERE?
- I DON'T CARE!
I'M A MAN WITH NEEDS, DAMN IT!
- WHAT A BRAVE MAN.
- IT'S FINE.
I'LL JUST LIVE ON ONE
CUP OF NOODLES A DAY
UNTIL I HAVE MORE MONEY.
TOTALLY WORTH IT!
- GREAT PLAN, BUT...
THERE'S SOMETHING YOU'RE
PROBABLY NOT THINKING ABOUT.
- THERE YOU ARE! I'VE
BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
- YEAH, SO, WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WHERE ARE WE GOING THIS WEEKEND
AND WHAT TIME ARE WE MEETING?
- MEETING? WHAT?
- I KNOW YOU DIDN'T
FORGET ABOUT THIS.
- I BELIEVE I SCORED
SOME CREPES, DIDN'T I?
- WHAT? BUT WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT ABOUT THAT TIME I TOOK
YOU GUYS TO THE MOVIES?
- THAT WAS YESTERDAY,
I WAS PROMISED CREPES.
- OH, THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN!
WOULD YOU MIND IF I JOIN YOU?
- PAY FOR BOTH OF YOU?
- WHILE WE'RE OUT, THERE'S THIS
REALLY GREAT MOVIE
I'VE BEEN DYING TO SEE
WITH YOU, YOSHII.
- YEAH, GREAT. MY FOOD BUDGET!
- Kouta: BAKA AND TEST.
- Fukuhara: IT'S BEEN
JUST ONE WEEK
SINCE THE NEW NARRATOR STARTED.
AND OUR CUP OF NOODLE
ARTISAN IS AT WORK EARLY.
- RIGHT THERE! NOW WE'VE
GOT DINNER AND... OH SNAP.
IF I ONLY EAT ONE HALF NOW, I'LL
HAVE THE OTHER HALF FOR LATER
AND I CAN MAKE TWO
HALVES OUT OF THAT.
AND THEN I'LL JUST CUT ANOTHER
HALF IN HALF AND HAVE TWO MORE,
WHICH MEANS IF I KEEP
DOING THAT,
I COULD PROBABLY CREATE
MILLIONS OF SMALL MEALS OUT
OF ONE CUP OF NOODLES
WHICH WOULD FEED ME FOREVER AND
THAT WOULD MAKE ME... A GENIUS.
- Fukuhara: HIS ENJOYMENT
WAS MULTIPLIED.
- OKAY THERE'S GOTTA
BE A WAY TO DO THIS
AND NOT COMPLETELY WASTE
MONEY, RIGHT?
OH, WAIT! PROBLEM SOLVED!
EVEN THOUGH I'M GOING
OUT TO MOVIES
AND BUYING OVERPRICED CREPES,
I'M DOING IT WITH GIRLS,
WHICH AUTOMATICALLY MAKES
IT A DATE, DOESN'T IT?
I RULE! I DIDN'T LOSE ANYTHING.
I'M JUST GOING ON A DATE!
SO, OF COURSE I'M SPENDING
A LITTLE EXTRA!
I'M THE GUY, THAT'S WHAT WE DO
ON DATES SO IT'S TOTALLY FINE!
HEY, HIMEJI!
NO WAY! IS THAT...
I WAS WRONG. THIS ISN'T A DATE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
OVER THERE, AKI?
( giggles )
OH YA KNOW, JUST GETTING BEATEN
DOWN BY THE CRUELTY OF LIFE.
- HI, YOSHII!
- HEY MIZUKI! YOU LOOK ADORABLE
TODAY. I LOVE THAT OUTFIT.
- THANK YOU, THAT'S SO SWEET!
TOOK ME FOREVER TO DECIDE ON IT.
I WAS SO AFRAID
I WAS GONNA BE LATE!
- I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
I DIDN'T DECIDE ON THIS
'TILL I WAS OUT THE DOOR.
I'M SO GLAD THIS SHIRT
FROM LAST YEAR STILL FITS.
- YEAH. HAVING ETERNAL MOSQUITO
BITES PROBABLY HELPS THAT
AND MAKES IT OKAY FOR YOU
TO TWIST MY KNEES IN
THE WRONG DIRECT...
OW! I DIDN'T EVEN FINISH
WHAT I WAS SAYING!
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO.
I COULD SMELL YOUR
THOUGHTS AND THEY STINK!
- HAND ME THE ROPE!
- AW, PERFECT.
AND THAT'S NOT HALF BAD.
- AND WHAT THE HELL IS THIS
PERVERT DOING HERE?
- INDEPENDENT STUDY.
- WHICH ONE DO YOU
WANT TO SEE, YOSHII?
- YEAH, WE THOUGHT
WE'D LET YOU PICK TODAY.
- ME?
THEY'RE ALL
THE SAME PRICE, RIGHT?
SO SEEING THE LONGEST ONE THEY
HAVE IS PROBABLY THE BEST DEAL.
- TAKE YOUR PICK, YUUJI.
- ANY MOVIE THAT I WANT?
THERE ARE SO MANY,
I'LL HAVE TO THINK.
- Shoukao: WAR AND PEACE.
GOOD CHOICE.
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT!
IT'S A SEVEN HOUR FEATURE!
- WE'LL WATCH IT TWICE.
- NO! I CAN'T SIT STILL
FOR 14 HOURS!
- IF YOU GET BORED,
YOU CAN JUST TAKE A NAP.
- ( Yuuji screams )
- I'LL BE RIGHT HERE WITH YOU
SO IT'LL FEEL JUST AS NICE.
TWO STUDENTS,
FOR THE NEXT TWO SHOWINGS.
- 'KAY. THAT'S ONE STUDENT
AND ONE CUTE ZOMBIE TO WATCH
THE NEXT TWO SHOWINGS
FOR NO REASON AT ALL.
- IT'S SO GREAT THEY'RE ABLE
TO EXPRESS THEIR FEELINGS
TOWARD EACH OTHER.
- THEY'RE SO LUCKY!
- MAYBE THE SHORTER ONE
WOULD BE BETTER.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT
GONNA GET ANYTHING?
- THEY'RE REALLY GOOD.
- OH, NO. SEE WHAT'S WEIRD
IS I'M ACTUALLY A FOOD SNOB.
AND I'M AFRAID THAT CREPES
JUST AREN'T MY THING.
LOOK, I GOTTA SAVE SOMETHING
OR I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE
ANY MONEY TO EAT TOMORROW.
- AW. WELL THAT'S TOO BAD.
I'M ALREADY PRETTY FULL
FROM THIS BANANA CREPE.
I WAS GONNA SEE IF YOU WANTED
TO HELP ME FINISH EATING IT.
- HUH?
- I WANTED YOU TO SHARE MY
STRAWBERRY CREPE TOO BUT...
IT'S TOO BAD THAT
YOU'RE A FOOD SNOB.
I HAD NO IDEA.
- BUT I GUESS YOU CAN'T HELP IT.
- OH, WELL. I'LL JUST
THROW OUT THE REST.
- ( crying )
- WHAT THE HECK
IS WRONG WITH ME?
HOW COULD I BE SO STUPID?
I MISSED MY CHANCE TO SHARE
A CREPE KISS WITH HIMEJI!
ONE BITE OF HER CREPE
PROBABLY HAS MORE CALORIES
AND NUTRITION IN IT
THAN MY ENTIRE BREAKFAST!
- YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
ONE BITE WON'T KILL YOU.
OH COME ON. IT'S GOOD.
- WELL, I GUESS IF YOU INSIST.
- YOSHII WAIT!
I WANT YOU TO TRY MINE TOO!
- MINE FIRST!
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT HE TRIES FIRST.
- Both: SAY, AH. AH!
- DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M SEEING!
YOU WEREN'T REALLY GONNA LET
YOUR SWEET LIP-CARESSED FORK
COME IN CONTACT WITH
THAT FILTHY RAT
AND SHARE YOUR CREPE WITH HIM!
HE WAS HARASSING
YOU, WASN'T HE?
LISTEN UP, PIG! YOUR DISGUSTING
RUDE-BOY DAYS ARE OVER!
- WAIT. PIG?
- JUSTICE IS ABOUT TO BE SERVED!
- WHAT? ARE YOU TALKING TO ME?
MOVE ! MOVE! MOVE!
MOVE! MOVE! MOVE!
( crying )
OH, NO! THE CREPES!
IT'S OKAY. IT HASN'T BEEN
30 SECONDS YET.
- JUST GIVE IT UP, PIG!
- MIHARU STOP IT!
- WAIT FOR ME, YOU GUYS!
- MY DEAR YOSHII.
YOU'VE MADE A MESS OF MY FACE.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
WHAT DID I DO?
- NOTHING. SHE'S JUST CRAZY!
- YEAH, I GOT THAT.
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON, GUYS?
HOW'S EVERYONE DOING TODAY?
- MAGICAL. COME ON.
WE GOTTA GO!
- WHAT THE...
- GET BACK HERE, PIG!
IF YOU GET ONE OUNCE
OF YOUR GROSS ON MY ANGEL...
I'LL BURN YOUR FILTHY BONES
TO A CRISP!
- WHAT? OH EXCUSE ME,
FOOD SNOB! WHAT'D I DO?
- NOTHING! I JUST DON'T WANT
HER TO BURN MY BONES.
- I'M GONNA GO OUT ON A LIMB
AND GUESS THAT YOU GUYS ARE
RUNNING AWAY FROM SOMEONE?
WE'RE TRYING, BUT THERE
DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
AN EASY WAY TO DO THAT.
IF I COULD JUST USE MY
AVATAR RIGHT NOW
THAT WOULD SOLVE EVERYTHING.
- I'M SORRY. THE SUMMONING
SYSTEM WON'T WORK
OUTSIDE OF THE ACADEMY.
- LAME.
- IT'S A GOOD THING I JUST
HAPPEN TO HAVE A COSTUME
FROM DRAMA CLASS WITH ME.
YOU COULD PUT IT ON
AND USE IT AS A DISGUISE.
- THAT'S GENIUS.
I DON'T THINK THIS IS SOMETHING
I SHOULD BE WEARING.
- OH. I HADN'T LOOKED.
I JUST ASSUMED IT WOULD WORK.
BUT IT DOESN'T REALLY LOOK LIKE
IT'S MEANT FOR A GUY, DOES IT?
- OF COURSE NOT. IT'S SOMETHING
THAT WAS MEANT FOR YOU TO WEAR.
- I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT HE
LOOKS ABSOLUTELY ADORABLE!
- WHAT'S HAPPENING TO
MY BODY RIGHT NOW?
- I HATE IT! I HATE IT!
I HATE IT!
( girls giggling )
- Miharu: THERE YOU ARE!
I KNEW I'D FIND! WHAT THE
CRAP... IS THAT A DRESS?
- WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
DOES IT LOOK LIKE ONE?
- IF YOU THINK
DRESSING LIKE A GIRL
IS ALL IT'S GOING TO
TAKE TO REPLACE ME
IN MY HONEY MUFFIN'S EYES
YOU'RE NOT ONLY AN IDIOT,
YOU'RE A DEAD ONE!
- NO, WAIT,
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
- YEAH, STARTING WITH THE FACT
THAT I'M NOT INTO GIRLS.
- YOU TRIED TO COME
BETWEEN SOMETHING
THAT IS SACRED AND PURE.
AND NOW YOU'RE
GONNA PAY FOR IT!
- BUT I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
- THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT
THE WAY I THOUGHT IT WOULD.
- Kouta: BUT IN SOME WAYS
IT WAS BETTER.
- SHE'S STILL BACK THERE.
WHAT DO WE DO?
- I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE IF WE
SPLIT UP, IT'LL THROW HER OFF.
- WHAT? THAT'S JUST GONNA MAKE
IT EASIER FOR HER TO GET TO ME!
- I KNOW. WHY DON'T WE
GO TO THE ACADEMY?
WE CAN USE OUR AVATARS THERE!
- Both: GREAT IDEA, MIZUKI!
- YES!
A TEACHER!
- THAT'S MS. TAKEUCHI.
SHE TEACHES MODERN JAPANESE.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK!
- YOU'LL BE FINE.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH CHOICE!
- ( all panting )
- MS. TAKEUCHI, WE
WERE WONDERING
IF WE COULD PRACTICE AN ST WAR?
- OH, SURE! I DON'T
SEE WHY NOT!
- OKAY. TIME TO SUMMON
MY AVATAR! SUMMON!
- SUMMONING AVATAR!
SUMMON!
- AVATAR.
HOW RUDE! I'LL TEACH YOU TO
COME BETWEEN ME AND MY LOVE!
SUMMON!
- WE'VE GOT HIMEJI'S AVATAR,
IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
YOU GUYS READY
TO WIN THIS THING?
- I'M SO SORRY, SHIMIZU.
- YEAH, YOU'RE GONNA BE.
- ( screaming )
- WHAT?
- THOSE WHO DIED, MEET ME
IN THE REMEDIAL CLASSROOM!
- NOW? BUT IT'S A HOLIDAY!
- REMEDIAL CLASS WITH
THE DEVIL IS LIKE HEAVEN
WHEN I'M WITH YOU.
JUST ME AND MY SWEET MUFFIN!
- YOU KNOW, YOSHI,
SELF-DISCOVERY IS A GOOD THING.
- IT ISN'T MINE!
I'M SO EXHAUSTED.
- ME TOO. I WONDER IF MINAMI
AND MIHARU ARE OKAY.
- I'M SURE THAT WHACK
JOB'S PERFECTLY FINE
BEING ANYWHERE WITH MINAMI.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOSHII, I'M SORRY.
I MEAN, I HAD A LOT OF FUN,
BUT IF WE HADN'T DRAGGED
YOU AROUND ALL DAY,
THEN YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
HAD TO DEAL WITH MIHARU.
- ITS OKAY. I HAD A LOT
OF FUN TODAY TOO,
'CAUSE I WAS WITH YOU.
- YOU'RE SWEET, YOSHII.
I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT SO.
EVER SINCE WE WERE
IN GRADE SCHOOL.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT THAT TIME
WE TOOK THE PLACEMENT TEST
AND I GOT REALLY SICK
IN THE MIDDLE OF IT.
I HAD TO LEAVE CLASS AND
YOU TOLD THE TEACHER
IT WASN'T FAIR TO GIVE ME A ZERO
BECAUSE I COULDN'T HELP IT.
- YEAH, AND THEN
HE WAS A JERK-WAD
AND SAID THAT STAYING HEALTHY
WAS LIKE PART OF THE TEST.
MAN, TALK ABOUT FAILURE, HUH?
- WHAT ABOUT THE ST WAR
WE DID THE OTHER DAY?
YOU SUGGESTED IT
WITH ME IN MIND, DIDN'T YOU?
- WHAT?
- YUUJI TOLD ME.
- HE DID?
- THANK YOU.
IT MADE ME HAPPY.
- SURE. UH, HIMEJI?
- YES?
- UH, I WANTED TO ASK ABOUT
THE LETTER YOU WERE
HOLDING THE OTHER DAY.
WHAT WAS IT REALLY?
YOU MEAN THIS ONE?
IT MIGHT SOUND SILLY, BUT IT'S A
CHAIN LETTER JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
- ( gasps )
- I'VE BEEN CURSED,
KEPT FORGETTING ABOUT IT.
YOU HAVE THREE DAYS TO MAIL IT
OR SOMETHING BAD'S
SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
OR I GUESS, MAYBE I WAS
TOO AFRAID TO MAIL IT.
AND NOW IT'S BEEN THREE DAYS.
AND I CAN TELL THAT THIS ONE
IS EXTRA CURSED, TOO.
I MEAN LOOK HOW MUCH
HAS ALREADY HAPPENED.
IT JUST BREAKS MY HEART
TO THINK THAT I'M THE ONE
WHO CAUSED ALL OF IT.
- SORRY. THAT BLOWS.
WELL, HEY, IF YOU WANT I CAN...
- YOU KNOW...
- NO, IT'S OKAY.
BECAUSE I KNOW SOMEDAY
I WON'T BE AFRAID ANYMORE AND
CAN MAIL IT MYSELF.
- I SEE.
- YOSHII, IT WOULD HELP IF
YOU WOULD BE THERE FOR ME.
- ALWAYS. I REALLY HOPE
IT WORKS OUT FOR YOU.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH!
- ( theme song playing )
- TIME FOR BREAKFAST!
- Fukuhara: DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
IT'S GOTTEN OLD YET.
- WHAT... THE?
"DEAR YOSHII,
I'M SURE THIS LETTER MAY COME AS
A SURPRISE TO YOU.
"I KNOW YOU'RE NOT ACCUSTOMED
TO RECEIVING SUCH THINGS,
"BUT IT IS THE ONLY WAY,
AND PERHAPS BEST WAY I CAN THINK
OF TO EXPRESS MY TRUE FEELINGS."
SO WAIT.
IT'S A LOVE LETTER!
"YOU'RE ALWAYS SO
CHEERFUL, THAT'S TRUE,
"AND I FIND THAT YOUR SMILE
NOT ONLY CARESSES MY SOUL,
AND WARMS MY HEART,
"BUT JUST ONE LOOK
SENDS A TINGLE TO MY...
"SOMEDAY I MIGHT BE MAN
ENOUGH TO EXPRESS MY FEELINGS
TO YOU IN PERSON
"BUT UNTIL THEN TAKE
CARE OF YOURSELF.
"I'LL SEE YOU IN MY DREAMS,
DEAR, SWEET YOSHII."
( screams ) MAN ENOUGH?
IT'S FROM A GUY?
( sobbing )
- HEY, HOW'S IT GOIN? WHERE'D
THAT LETTER COME FROM?
- IT'S GONE! THE LETTER!
WHERE'D IT GO?
I JUST BOUGHT THAT PHOTO, TOO!
IT WAS AN ORIGINAL!
GREAT. OH WELL, GUESS IT'S
A GOOD THING I DECIDED
TO LEAVE THE
LETTER ANONYMOUS.
THIS COULD'VE BEEN BAD.
- NO WAY!
BEST OF LUCK, MAN.
- ( screaming )
HE FORGOT TO MENTION
THE ENCLOSED PHOTO.
- YOU'LL SEE.
SOMEDAY I'LL DO IT!
- Fukuhara: QUESTION FOUR.
IN A POPULAR MOTHER GOOSE RHYME,
WHAT IS DESCRIBED AS BEING
"MADE OF SUGAR, SPICE
AND EVERYTHING NICE?"
- Akihisa: CURRY AND RICE.
- LITTLE GIRLS.
BUT YES, FOOD IS NICE.
- NEXT TIME, "LOVE, SPICES,
AND BOXED LUNCHES!"
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.