Someone's here!
Hello there! You approaching
this area, can you see me?
I'm a little troubled
because I'm out of gas.
Can you take me to Ganymede?
Oh, damn it, why does everyone...?
Why won't they stop?!
This sea rat
used to be raised in the oceans
of Ganymede.
After the gates stabilized,
food was no longer scarce.
And so, now the ones in the wild get eaten
by those who have a fancy for them.
So, is it good?
It's totally disgusting.
It's just expensive because
it's a Ganymede specialty.
Then it's no good.
I'll have the lobster miso stew.
Thank you.
That doesn't look good, either.
Well, I thought I'd go for something
expensive while I'm at it.
You mean, because we'll soon
have some money?
To think that Gould was a spy...
But, Mom, don't worry.
We sunk his ship.
It's all right. One vial nowadays
doesn't mean much...
Let's continue the deal
as we initially planned.
But... who was in charge
of watching the house, then?
Mom...
It was you, Harrison?
Hey! Where's my sea-rat sauté?!
Come on, there, come on!
No doubt. It's Morgan.
Then shall we go before
we get breakfast?
Hey, kid, did you know
that the Ganymede sea rat
is a very intelligent
and kind animal?
- What's that?
- That woman... I think she was...
I don't remember ordering a circus!
I know I've seen her somewhere...
We, the Space Warriors, work night
and day to preserve the environment
and protect endangered species
all over the universe.
I remember now!
That lady's worth 25 million!
Mom, hurry!
This is the end, mademoiselle.
Mom?!
Don't move!
Do you want to see your mom in pain?
Who are you?
How's Morgan?
He's full of holes.
That's a problem.
He was gonna put food on our table.
But he's worth nothing compared
to the 25 million that you're worth...
- You!
- Let go of Mom!
Stop it. These guys are bounty hunters.
We can't do anything.
Mom!
Take care of the home.
I'll be back soon.
Come on. If you don't go now,
the cops are gonna arrive!
Mom, sit tight!
Harrison, you'll get plenty
of punishment later.
Mom?!
- Let's go!
- Mom!
Lucky you, Harrison.
Your mom won't be back for a while.
Hey, are you alive?!
Please... Take this to the ISSP...
But... don't open it...
Hey, wait a minute!
What does he want me to do?
Universal Environmental
Protection Society?
More like environmental terrorists.
They're called the Space Warriors.
They used to be a good group
working on environmental preservation
and the protection
of endangered species.
But since their leader changed two years
ago, their focus drastically changed.
There are only a few members,
but now
they're even worse than a lot
of syndicates out there.
They're especially keen on protecting
the Ganymede sea rats.
And she's the leader of this terrorist
group: Twinkle Maria Murdock.
Please, don't associate us
with terrorists!
We are warriors of peace,
fighting for the law of nature.
Yeah, yeah.
And where can we get
the 25 million in reward?
The Ganymede government.
But we can't cash in.
I'm checking on it.
The government canceled
the reward yesterday.
Why?
When you're told not to open it,
the more you want to...
I didn't open it!
This thing opened by itself!
So, as you requested,
we have canceled the bounty.
And we are debating
about prohibiting
the fishing of sea rats
on Ganymede as well.
So, where's Mom?
As I said, we haven't gotten word
of Twinkle's capture!
If we can find out
who captured them...
If Mom doesn't come back,
we'll set that plan into action immediately.
Wait! We're not going
against your wishes...
Doesn't look like it
would ease my hunger...
Wait a minute, that terrorist act
we saw isn't on the records, either!
What's going on?
See? I told you that you
couldn't do anything.
So, you can just let me go.
I don't get it...
There's something behind all this.
Hello there! You approaching
this area, can you see me?
I'm a little troubled
because I'm out of gas...
Hey, she's--!
Can you take me to Ganymede?
Please?
Even getting a little propellant
would be wonderful!
Hey! Can you hear me or what?!
Then what?
You spent all the money you took from us
at the casino?!
As they say, "Money makes
the world go round."
They also say,
"Thieves have no compassion."
How is it over there?
Yeah, I'm contacting an old friend.
Man, there isn't even
anything worth keeping...
Huh? What's this?
Yes... I still don't know
where that virus is.
Yes, Mr. President.
We will continue to do our best!
- Chief!
- What?
- The one who nabbed Twinkle...
- You found them?!
And, that guy told you
to take this to the ISSP?
Yup. Doesn't that look
like it's worth something?
So, how about we call it even?
I never trust anything thieves say.
What?
What's all this about?! Hey, Bob!!
Nothing is really up.
The bounty has been canceled.
They're saying you should
let her go immediately,
Hey, Bob...
When we worked in
the same department...
...a lot of the confiscated
eye drops disappeared, you know?
What do you wanna say?
If you wanna work
until retirement age,
isn't it a better idea for you
to go along with me?
Oh, all right.
I get what you're saying.
Hey, don't break it!
The guys are threatening
under the mask of negotiation.
They're holding the 8 million residents
of Ganymede hostage.
What do you mean by that?
They basically kidnapped
the leader in virus technology
and created a virus to their liking.
The virus is called Monkey Business.
They say that humans and monkeys
only have a 2 percent difference
in DNA structure
and apparently this virus
acts on those two percent.
So, that virus selectively,
acts only on humans.
Why don't you give up?
We lost contact with the ISSP spy
that infiltrated their group.
So, we had no other option.
So you're going to agree
to their terms?!
Man, this was a big one
that we caught, too!
It's orders from up above!
WE couldn't do anything about it!
We're releasing her.
Us... or them...
Which one of us deserves
punishment from heaven?
Soon, the time of judgment
will arrive.
Yes... Soon...
The release procedure
has been completed.
We will continue to monitor
her using our special agents.
How's the satellite?
It will be ready in about an hour.
Get the chemical tech group as well.
Don't do anything until we know
where the virus is.
Sir, a communication from Twinkle.
Long time no see, Minister.
About that promise we made...
So, about the sea rats,
we will keep a stable population
using limitations
on hunting them.
Didn't I say prohibition of hunting?
Well, we will look at the demands
in a positive light.
Looks like you need some punishment
to understand.
Hey! Wait!
Mom! I don't want to become a monkey!
Mom!
Alpha 1-0-5 to headquarters.
The target has entered
the wasteland area.
Roger. Continue pursuit.
Man, they're too easy-going.
Damn it...
All that and no reward...
Jet, can you hear me?
Turn on channel 72 and watch it!
They're broadcasting
from their own satellite!
This isn't just about the sea rats.
Humans, with their culture
have escaped from
the great system of nature
and are committing crimes
that cannot be amended.
Those that don't realize this
are what you could call "bugs"
in the nature system.
That ship was a decoy.
Where are they broadcasting from?
It's near here. They're in hyperspace!
Monkey Business, our virus,
takes such humans
and returns them to nature.
Understand?
Good news, Jet!
The Ganymede government has reestablished
the ransom on Twinkle and company.
What?!
This is our chance!
We're the only ones around here!
But just catching them won't do.
If the missile falls, there'll be
nobody here that can pay the bounty
So there's nothing to bitch about
if we get rid of the missile, right?
But they're at the exit to a gate.
I know.
- What about the defense system?!
- 4 minutes and 30 seconds to impact!
The system won't make it in time!
This is an emergency!
Get the president!
They're here.
It split?! Shit!
Jet! Get the last one!
What?! There aren't any weapons
over here!
If I wait for the next shot to fully
charge, that thing will hit Ganymede!
Oh? Are you in trouble?
- How about for 80 percent of the earnings?
- You've got to be kidding!
- Okay, bye! Have a nice day.
- All right. 40 percent. No more.
- Okay! I get the 60!
- Fine... We got no choice.
Shit, will she make it in time?
Welcome!
What is this?!
Multiple warheads?!
This ain't the military!
Now all of you, become apes!
Jet! The guys from the government
are closing down the gate!
What?!
They're going to enclose all of it
in hyperspace, missile and all!
- Wait a minute, this isn't a joke!
- Spike!
I hear you!
Spike!
Why?
Didn't you learn in high school?
Matter that gets enclosed
in hyperspace can be seen,
but will never interact with matter
in this realm again.
Mom! The gate's closed!
Hey, Mom, what can we do?!
Stop! Stop!
So... this and that and no reward.
All that work for nothing.
Oh, don't look so down,
we can make money next time.
Well, I'll go take a shower.
Next time? Make money?
Hey, Jet, what did she just say?
Don't ask me! Just don't!
And she's off to shower
without asking us.
Hey, are we gonna take all of this?
Don't tell me! Just don't!
Fine, I'll go tell her.
Hey, Spike.
Should've seen that coming.
The supposedly broken music box
starts to move
and a nostalgic tune fills the air.
I then happen to wake up
from the dream.
There is no such thing
as a music box,
yet, there is a small music box
nestled in my hand.
And I awake from the dream again.
As if I was peeling an onion,
it's a dream no matter how far I go.
I can never return to reality.
Such a nightmare, this is.
Next episode: Ballad of Fallen Angels.