Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start!
When watching Kaleido Star,
please keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I came to America all by myself
with aspirations of joining Kaleido Stage.
Everything is new to me,
but I'm doing my best in the spirit
of "try it rather than think about it."
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, I'll be super lucky.
And if I'm gonna do it, I just
gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! That's me.
Well, well, well, if you were the
only one not given anything to do,
you'd get really depressed, too, right?
It makes you sad, and you want to cry.
This time, I'm the only
one who doesn't get a role.
I wonder what it is that
I can do? I wonder? I wonder?
What is it that you want to do?
Every time I was asked that
I looked up at the blue sky
The answer is only in my heart
I don't easily say the
words that are really important
I start running towards
the place the light points to
There's so much in my heart
that I want to embrace, I could cry
I'll keep painting my way,
I promise, take it someday
Beyond the horizon,
where the white clouds drift
The future is lined up and
it'll always be there by my side
"The Amazing Distant Stage."
--Anna!
--You're wonderful!
You're so cool!
A sloth.
I missed it again!
Your spins are amazing.
Really?
Can all Asians do that?
What? Oh, it's because
I used to do rhythmic gymnastics.
What? What?
What is it?!
Oh, the show that Miss Layla and the
others were practicing was Cinderella.
That's right. Even all trainees
are supposed to appear in it.
All?
Yes. So good luck, everyone.
You just want to wish
Sora luck, don't you, Ken?
Oh, well...
Cinderella...
Wow! I need to tell my
family about this quick.
My dad, mom, and grandma
are all big fans of Kaleido Stage.
Since I'm their star of hope, they'll
be happy to hear that I'll be on stage,
even if my role is just to play the pumpkin!
In the end, I'd guess that
you're more of the prince type.
No, actually I'd rather play the pumpkin.
Oh, it's because my
father's a stand-up comedian.
Oh, so that's why. Sora,
what about your family?
My family...
They weren't very enthusiastic
about you joining Kaleido Stage, right?
Well... By the way, aren't you hungry?
Let's hurry and go to the dining hall.
Your parents?
Here he is again.
How dare you?! I am the Spirit of the Stage.
Do not talk of me as if I am a ghost.
What's the difference?
Only people who are
chosen for the stage can see me.
I hear only certain people
can see ghosts too.
Ugh! Are you saying
that you cannot trust me?
Yup.
Shocking! Sora...
What?
Do you want to know why I am here?
You're waiting for a chance
to peep at me in the bath.
Wrong!
I am searching for the one who will be able
to perform the legendary great maneuver.
The legendary great maneuver?
That is correct.
It is a maneuver that was
performed only once a long time ago.
For those who cannot see me, the
maneuver would be utterly impossible.
What kind of maneuver is it?
I cannot tell you.
Why not?
If you are truly the chosen one,
you will be possessed by the charm
of the maneuver as soon as you hear it.
Then, even though you are not skilled enough,
you will want to perform it.
You will recklessly attempt
it and die trying.
Die?
Everyone who's tried that
maneuver without the proper skills
has failed to execute the maneuver and died.
You're lying.
What?!
If what you said is true,
you should be showing
up at Miss Layla's place.
As I said, someone who cannot see me...
Just as I thought, your purpose
is to peep at me bathing, isn't it?
If that were my purpose,
I would rather go to Layla's place.
It seems we have just proven
that I have been telling the truth.
I hate it that I can't come
up with a counterargument.
Now, please gather around!
Everyone, Boss has an announcement
about the cast for Cinderella.
You may know this already,
but the upcoming Cinderella
is a masterpiece that
includes a ballroom dance scene,
so all of you will be
appearing in it as well.
I will now announce the roles.
First, castle guards.
Albert.
Here.
Emilio.
Chris.
Here.
You three, that's all.
Town girls. Clair.
Here.
Jeanne.
The Prince's attendant, Anna.
Wow! It's perfect. Perfect!
You get to perform with Mr. Yuri.
Th--
The character won't have any gags...
Nope, nope, it won't.
For the role of the fairy godmother,
I want several of you to practice the
role first before I make the selection.
Even if you are not chosen,
you'll be part of the crowd scene,
so do not let your guard down.
And here are the candidates
for the fairy godmother role:
Charlotte.
Here.
Julie.
I thought so.
Mia.
Mia!
Here!
Glad it's a role you wanted.
It's great. So great! You're amazing, Mia.
Do your best and win the role.
Yeah, I'm gonna do it!
For the crowd in the
ballroom dance scene, Kevin.
Here.
Joseph.
Mileyu.
I... I wonder which role I'll play.
Monica.
Here!
That's all.
He didn't call my name. Just my name.
There must be some kind of mistake.
Maybe he just forgot to call your name.
Oh, excuse me, Boss!
What is it?
What is my role?
You don't have a role.
I don't have... a role?
Oh, come to think of it...
There's a role you can
start playing tomorrow.
The role is to hand out toys to
the children during intermission.
Toys?
Can you call it a role if the
person isn't even on stage?
If you don't like it, you don't have to.
I'll do it. I'll play the role!
It's like just for you!
Or rather, a perfect match!
Anyway, let's practice together.
Yeah, Let's do that.
Mia, Anna...
You don't have time for practice.
Starting tomorrow, you have to
play the role of passing out toys.
Okay, everyone! Please
come get the scripts here!
Boss is such a jerk!
All right! Since it's come to this,
we should drop a frog down his back,
or shave off half of his
beard while he's sleeping.
Then let's shave off half of his
eyebrows and hair, too, while we're at it.
How about drawing eyes on his glasses?
Wouldn't it be better to draw
the glasses on his eyes instead?
Thank you for worrying about me.
I'll be fine.
I know both of you really
want to read the script, right?
Don't worry about me,
you can go back to your rooms.
Okay.
Maybe we should.
I'm a person "chosen for the stage"?
It must be some kind of mistake.
I told him I'd do it on the
spur of the moment, but...
Everyone else is practicing for Cinderella.
Oh, my!
Miss Layla!
Are you handing those out?
Boss told me to.
I see.
You don't look happy.
I was told that this was
the only role available for me.
You have a long way to go if
you're still saying things like that.
Sora! It's time.
Intermission is in three minutes.
Okay.
I'm sure Boss has something in mind.
Maybe Boss doesn't like me.
Just the other day,
I got into that situation
with Miss Layla, so...
Excuse me, everyone! Attention please!
Everyone, attention please!
I'm asking you all, please listen.
You're in my way! Move!
I'm sorry.
Mommy! My ice cream!
Sora!
Mr. Policeman.
I'm off duty today, so I came to see you.
You look like you're having trouble.
Hey! Listen to what my
friend Sora has to say!
What are those?
I couldn't hand out all
of it during intermission.
You said you would do it,
but you can't even fill a role like that?!
I never should have made
an exception to accept you!
How dare he talk to me like that?!
How does he expect me to hand
out all of it in such a short time?!
He must be having fun,
asking me to do the impossible!
Miss Layla is shining on the stage,
while I'm off the stage...
"Jump Kick"
Sora, why don't you give it a try, too?
This is the best way to relieve stress.
"Jump Kick"
I'd rather not.
Sora! Over here!
You must be tired.
It must've been tough.
Oh, yeah...
Oh, dinner's delicious today, isn't it?
Yeah! Even the fries are
more crisp than usual.
You don't have to tiptoe around me like that.
Anyway, how was the Cinderella practice?
Well, it was tough as expected.
What kind of stage is it?
In the last ballroom dance
scene, Miss Layla and Mr. Yuri
are supposed to leap on six trapezes
one after another as if they're dancing.
Wow, that's amazing.
What about everything else?
You are not in the mood to do anything.
You are not motivated.
Don't bother telling my fortune.
As you can see, it's pretty obvious.
This is also the card that governs creation.
The road is blocked. But if you
want to see what is up ahead,
you have to create your own road.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
What do you mean by "my own road"?
I know!
Is this okay?
Thanks.
Are you really going to
do it in a clown suit?
Yup. If I can't appear on stage,
I'll just turn the seating
area into my own stage.
Turn the seating area into your own stage?
That's right!
It's great that you always have
this positive attitude, you know?
Jeez. Ken, you're still here?
What? Oh, sorry!
All right, I'm all set!
Hello, everyone!
Are you enjoying Kaleido Stage?
Yeah!
Now, my friends, everyone
who wants a light, gather around!
You should hurry, or
else the show will start soon!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Here. Here. Here.
Okay, wait a second.
I did it!
I finished handing it all out today.
You have no comprehension
of how the show is run.
Oh, are you talking about this costume?
It has nothing to do with that.
Think seriously about what your role is!
What's wrong?! I don't understand at all.
Sora...
What?
The show was delayed
ten minutes because of you.
What?
You put on a pretty flashy performance,
so it took a long time
to calm down the audience.
And you asked the kids to
come out to get the lights, right?
Some of them couldn't find
their way back to their seats,
and some were in such a
hurry that they tripped and fell.
I... I...
Sora...
I was only thinking about
getting attention for myself.
I only cared about getting
people to say that I was amazing.
I wasn't thinking about the
progression of the show at all.
No wonder Boss is mad at me.
--Oh! Mr. Yuri.
--It's you.
I don't want to see a clown cry.
Even if your heart is crying, isn't it
a clown's job to make people happy?
Yes.
Sora!
Why are you looking like that, Ken?
I'll help you hand out the lights.
Thank you.
No, anything for you, Sora.
But I'll be fine,
because I finally understand what my role is.
What?
A clown's job is to make people happy.
Sora, what are you doing?
Oh, Mom.
What?
That clown's been standing
there all this time.
What is it?
It looks fun. How about this?
Is this a doll?
I can't believe she's
performing in the lobby.
She's alive.
Really?
No way!
The show has already started.
Even if I'm not on stage, I'm still
going to completely play my role.
Oh, that's the clown I saw earlier.
She wasn't a doll.
Now, I'm here to give everyone a magic wand!
Everyone, use your power to
fill the night sky with stars, okay?!
Okay!
I don't have a lead role
or anything like that,
but if I can bring even
just a little enjoyment
to everyone as a supporting character...
You did it.
No, I haven't finished yet.
I understand a little now.
All roles exist for the audience.
Bringing these smiles to their
faces. That is Kaleido Stage.
Miss Layla!
Oh, you are?
What is it?
What? Me?
You're sure you want me to do it?
An autograph... let me think,
how should I sign it?
"Sora"
Here.
Thank you.
No, not at all. I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
Tim, we're leaving!
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Sora, you did a good job.
I signed an autograph for the first time.
It would be nice if the boy
cherished your autograph forever.
Yeah.
Kalos.
I wonder what you're expecting from her.
What do you think?
Your autograph is terrible.
What? Really?
First of all, there are a lot
of things you need to practice
before you practice your autograph.
That's true, but...
But I feel like I understand a
little bit of what you said, Fool.
Creating my own road
means creating my own role.
And waiting for me ahead on
that road is the audience's smile.
Are you thanking me?
Yeah, kind of...
Then, keep that thought in your heart.
And now, go take a bath!
Hey!
Like I said, stop blindfolding me!
Hey, Sora!
You ungrateful wretch!
When you're lonely, what do you do?
Never say you don't get any of that
Sleep, play, flip through a magazine
When you're lonely, you're lonely
Like always, invisible vibes fly
around the city today, tulututu*
Anyway, the vector of my heart
is talking about so many reasons
I want to be free and fly the skies
But I don't have space to spread my wings
But I have faith
There is a future yet to be shaped
And there's a me that I want to shape
Even if I'm sad, even if it's a mistake
I'll do what I want and
fly towards the freedom
"Next Kaleido Star"
I don't want people like you
getting up on the trampoline!
And so, the three of us end up with
Mia's role as the fairy godmother,
but Marion...
She started crying, saying she didn't
want us getting up on the trampoline.
I heard that Marion's late mother
used to be part of the trampoline cast.
Maybe I can't appear on
stage yet. Maybe. Maybe. Maybe.
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Try Hard and You'll Get an Amazing Chance"
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...