So why have you gathered us all here today?
Well, since the school festival was such a success,
I thought it'd be nice if we just spent
some time together enjoying ourselves.
I see. I suppose a little rest
every now and then won't hurt.
Look, Yuri!
The cosmos have finally bloomed!
Yes, they do look rather beautiful.
Ah!
This flower's really cute too!
Those are bur-marigolds.
Shy little Tsubomi's finally managed to change herself.
Itsuki's finally being honest about the things she likes.
And the Flower of Yuri's Heart is blooming again!
Your big sis is so happy for you all!
Erika, stop looking down on people!
And you're not anyone's "big sis"!
Anyway, look!
No matter what kind of cheap tricks the Desert Apostles use,
if the four of us work together, then we'll always, always pull through!
Right!
Yes!
You really think so?
Huh?
We've got trouble!
Grandma?
Grandma!
I'm counting on you, girls!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
We'll Become Stronger!
Our Trial is Precure vs. Precure!
A Desertrian?!
No.
A Desertrian is something born of the Flower of someone's Heart, weakened enough to be usable.
Just what is that?
The flowers!
Are you trying to turn this town into a desert?!
There's no way I'll let you!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
Please, stop doing this!
Thank you so much, Marine!
How dare you do that to my best friend?!
Marine!
Are you all okay?
Yeah...
Moonlight, just how are we meant to fight that thing?!
We'll use all four of our Forte Waves in unison.
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Shiny Tambourine!
Moon Tact!
Precure Silver Forte Wave!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
What on earth is this thing?
I thought we defeated it!
My name is Dune, the Desert King.
The Desert King?
He's the bad guys' boss?!
You insolent little Precure,
no matter how much you may try to stop me,
know that your effort is futile.
Behold!
Kaoruko told me about this.
I think it was called the Planet Fortress!
That planet...
This planet was stripped of all
its greenery by a desert seed—
the "Desert Devil."
A desert seed?
The Desert Devil?
I'll send you another. Consider it a present.
It shall reach the Earth quite soon.
Then not only will your planet's greenery perish,
but so too will the Flowers in all human Hearts perish.
And the Great Heart Tree as well.
We'll never let that happen!
That's right!
We'll protect the Great Heart Tree and the Flowers of everyone's Hearts!
Well then, I look forward to seeing just whether or not you can fight off the Desert Devil.
Jeez, I don't believe this!
Why did King Dune just send the desert seed to Earth without even turning to us to help?!
It seems he intends to do more than merely turn the Earth into a desert.
His true objective is to destroy the HeartCatch Mirage.
We cannot permit it to unleash its true power, after all.
It won't be long now before
the desert seed reaches Earth.
What do we do now?
The answer's obvious!
No matter who we have to face, we just have to beat 'em up!
What if we can't?
It's not just our lives at stake in this battle, but those of everyone on Earth.
We have to be certain we can win.
We've only got one choice.
We'll use what little time we have left to build up our strength.
If it's further power that you seek,
then you'll have to return to the Precure Palace.
Once you pass the final trial that awaits you there,
you will be able to obtain even greater powers as Precure.
The final trial?
So this one will be even tougher than when we were granted the Mirage?
Yes. It'll be a tough battle for you.
But if we can pass the trial...
...we'll obtain greater powers?
Then we've gotta do it!
Right!
Where are we?
Where's everyone?
Marine!
Sunshine!
Moonlight!
I wonder where they all went.
Why have we all been separated like this?
There has to be some reason we've been isolated from each other.
Why couldn't I have shtayed with Sunshine?
The final trial is something that each Precure must face on their own.
You aren't allowed to be there with them.
So all we can do is wait here and wish them luck?
Huh?!
What?!
Isn't this final trial thing gonna start soon?
Whaaat?!
You're...
The final trial is a fight against ourselves?
I am not merely you.
I am your shadow self.
My shadow self?
Just as the Moon has a dark side, so too
does your heart have dark shadows within.
And that is I, your shadow self!
Hmph.
I want to be a popular model like Momo too!
I want to be beautiful! I want to be loved!
So this shadow self is how I used to be?
But you still want that, don't you?!
I wanted to protect my brother!
I had to continue training in the martial arts to protect him and the Myoudouin family!
I had to cast my plushies and my pretty dresses aside and put everything I had into training!
That's how I used to think.
I'm not like that anymore!
I practice not for my brother or my family, but because I love doing it!
And as for my plushies and my pretty dresses,
I've grown to be able to admit I like those too!
So even though I worked so hard to get you here, you don't need me anymore?!
Huh?!
I couldn't protect Cologne!
Because I was stupid enough to think I had to fight alone, I ended up losing Cologne!
That's right.
Cologne perished because I thought I
couldn't share my burden with anyone.
And then...
In my sadness, I ended up forgetting
the things that were most dear to me!
But thanks to the strong hearts of Blossom and the others, who would always smile for me,
I've become stronger!
So that I can protect everyone's hearts!
The cycle of sorrow...
The cycle of sorrow can only be broken if you're prepared to accept it and move forward.
You know, it's thanks to Tsubomi and the others
that I realized I've got good traits of my own too.
So I'm not jealous of Momo for being a model anymore.
I just want to become someone as amazing as she is!
Then why do I still exist?!
Why wouldn't you?
All those negative thoughts are a part of me too!
I don't hate you, though,
because I love every last thing about myself!
That's right.
My brother would always accept it all, just as he welcomed the Sun's rays.
Why did you drop your guard?!
Because you're not my enemy.
No matter what wonderful or sad things happened,
my brother would always accept that and smile down at me.
I want to be able to accept everything too.
Everything?!
The old, hardened me and the me who's grown to be honest with herself are both precious parts of who I am.
So I'll accept every facet of myself.
That way I can smile with the
same kindness my brother does.
I don't intend to fight alone any longer.
We'll get through these problems together.
You think you can?
With your heart still torn in two like this?
Oh, I'm not saying it's going to be easy.
But I made a promise to myself.
That I'd keep fighting so every heart could one day find happiness.
Then it seems you have no need for me any longer—
the sadness within you that
will only tear at your resolve.
That's not true.
I've chosen to live with this sadness.
And one day, that sadness shall be enveloped in love.
Marine!
Huh? I'm back!
Does that mean I passed the final trial?
Marine!
Coffret!
That's great!
Look at that shtatue!
It's become Cure Marine!
When you pass the final trial, the Precure
Palace is adorned with a statue in your honor.
Oh, sho that's why!
You look so cool!
Sunshine!
Potpourri!
I'm sho glad you're shafe!
Moonlight!
So you two passed the final trial as well?
Where's Blossom?
It appears she's not back yet.
I wonder what happened to Blossom.
Cure Blossom.
You won't be able to change.
You are incapable of changing.
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
I'll surpass my old withdrawn self and
grow together with my beloved friends!
Change into a new you!
HeartCatch Mirage, grant us new power!
Our shining new forms reveal the strong light within our hearts!
Their name is "HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!"
HeartCatch Precure:
Precures,
Transform into Super Silhouettes!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!