"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Hey, Konata, can I borrow your computer?
I want to type up some text for
the committee meeting next week.
Sure!
I've been a bit out of whack recently...
"I've been a head nurse recently..."
...but it looks like I
will make it in time...
"...but it looks like transfer of a mania..."
...I'd like to get a bigger head start...
"...I'd like to dress in drag more..."
...not just the enthusiasm,
but taking care of
the feelings of the committee as a whole...
"...not just the enthusiasm, but taking care
of the flleing of the committee as a whole..."
...I'd like to have the contents
of the assignment at hand
worked out in detail...
"...I'd like to see nothing here of
the assignment at hand wrkd n dtl..."
Hey, mind explaining what's up with your PC?
Other people's computers are
difficult to deal with, Kagami.
"Delicate Line"
Whoa, I didn't check my
mail for a couple days,
and my mailbox is mega full!
Konata, despite how you
seem, you get a lot of mail?
Sis... you came right out with a harsh truth.
That really got to me.
Because I'm sticking my head
into places of that nature,
over 90% of it is spam or solicitation mail.
We really don't know how to react,
so don't talk about things
like that to the police, okay?
But I'm always thinking this...
How do these types of e-mails always
come up with really funny subjects?
"This is Mi*noru" "Are you free
today?" "Are you free tomorrow?"
Yeah, I know.
"Copying..." "From 'tsun-dere' to
'images'" "Time remaining: 2 hours"
This is progressing pretty quickly.
Maybe it will be over sooner than I thought?
It's always like this,
but it's so unreliable with
it fluctuating so much!
I guess I'll have a cup of instant
noodles for a late-night snack.
I ended up getting toyed around with...
Hello!
Welcome.
I heard that Konata and Yutaka caught a cold.
Oh, man, are you all right, Yutaka?
I've done myself in for the
first time in a while...
Hey, Konata! Are you all right...
Oh, Sis, welcome.
I see... you don't have enough
energy to attend class,
but you have enough energy to play games.
Now, well, see... You'd know
how I feel, right, Sis?
Hello!
Oh, Minami and everyone! You
came by to visit! Thank you!
She ended up bedridden this time,
but Yutaka has never been as
healthy as she has been lately...
I really thank you for it, Minami-chan!
No, I haven't done anything...
She had a couple good friends
back in junior high, too,
but I guess it has to do with
overall compatibility...
Minami-chan, she talks
about you a lot as well.
It's like school is just so much
fun that she can't help herself.
You know, they say that all
diseases start with willpower.
She forgets about all her illnesses
when she's doing fun things.
Hello!
Oh, Minami and everyone! You
came by to visit! Thank you!
She ended up bedridden this time,
but Yutaka has never been as
healthy as she has been lately...
I really thank you for it, Minami-chan!
No, I haven't done anything...
She had a couple good friends
back in junior high, too,
but I guess it has to do with
overall compatibility...
Minami-chan, she talks
about you a lot as well.
It's like school is just so much
fun that she can't help herself.
Oh, Minami-chan, Tamura-san,
and Patty-chan. Welcome.
Are you all right?
Get well soon.
Yeah... But why am I always so frail?
I hate making everyone worry so much...
No, no, there are a lot of people
who want to protect you for just that reason!
Well, even if it's good from
other people's viewpoints,
it's usually tough on the
actual person, right?
I guess it's like saying how someone
who has a younger sister in real life
finds it hard to feel moe for
younger sisters in general?
Yeah, that!
That's it!
And here it comes... The pouting
attack from ordinary folk!
This must be the "I can't
keep up with this" aura!
Ain't no helping it, ma'am! We're outlaws!
Speaking of being worried
about your weak points...
Minami-chan, you're often worried
that you don't have any breasts...
Is that so?
Oh, no, it's nothing like that...
They say that massaging
breasts make them bigger.
Yeah, I've heard that too!
Is it really okay?
Minami-chan...
I can't ask anyone else for
such a thing, Yutaka...
I-I'm going to touch it, okay?
Hold myself back, hold myself back!
Oh, Tamura-san, you're from that circle...
Yes. I was a part of the
previous summer Comiket.
I have a few of your books.
Oh, I'm honored.
I see...
I'd like to read some of the
manga you've drawn, Tamura-san.
Sis, let me read a couple.
Hmm... I don't mind, but...
Anything but that...
No, no, Hiyorin. Doujin are meant to be read.
Have mercy on a fellow warrior...
At least, keep it to the ones
for general audiences...
You sure put up a futile struggle, Hiyorin.
At least... At least!
That was amazing. Now, let's
go over it one more time.
Gum containing xylitol has the effect
of destroying the germs that cause cavities.
This is due to xylitol...
Before it is absorbed by the cavity germ,
the cavity germ's ATP are used up,
and simultaneously within the cavity germ,
something that is hard to dissolve...
If it's that good for my
teeth, I should try it too.
When I was chewing gum
for the sake of my teeth,
the filling in my tooth came out,
and I ended up going to the dentist.
I feel moe for a pitiful yet
difficult-to-follow Miyuki-san.
There, there...
And that's what Miyuki-san
was crying about today.
I felt moe.
I see...
And that's what Sis said.
That's why Miyuki-san was so gloomy...
I have to apologize to the
person named Miyuki-san,
but I'll be using that idea!
Oh, I was having problems
finding a good idea...
How do you come up with ideas for your manga?
Well, I can't summarize it all at once,
but I often take real-life
experiences into consideration.
R-Real-life experiences...
You read some?
You read some?!
Well, um... Well...
After I told her not to show you so much!
I'm sorry...
Those aren't based on real-life experiences!
B-But there were a lot of good stories,
and they were fun to read, you know?
Thanks...
I guess you can call it déjà vu?
Some of them made me feel like
I'd experienced them in the past.
I'd like to read it sometime too.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
That's probably the one that
used you two as my models!
Oh, ma'am, good morning.
What, Izumi, up all night
playing games again?
Or watching late-night anime series?
Well, lately, the number of late-night
anime series has increased.
It's such a wonderful generation!
Even if it's a lie, I wish she'd
say that she was studying...
I really think that maybe I
should spend a little more money
and buy a DVD recorder or something.
No good. Stop that.
You'd just end up recording
and not watching them.
It's like all the unplayed games I pile up.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Hey! Knock it off already!
You've got to be kidding me!
I'll tell you this, I don't
have anything to do with it!
Oh, hello? You didn't hang
up on me just now, did you?
Well, I had three bars, but
for some reason it hung up...
Oh, sure.
I was being immature earlier. I'm sorry.
Oh, it's not like I'm saying
this because we got cut off.
It turns out I've come back here once more...
Then, let me see where it came out.
Oh, if it's just that, it'll be fine
just by putting the filling in again.
It'll be done really quickly.
But there's a tooth in the back
that's starting to become a cavity,
so let's start treating that one first!
Lucky Star!
Oh.
Hm? What's wrong?
I just realized that strawberries
smell like shortcakes.
Oh...
But wait, don't you mean that you can
smell strawberries in shortcakes?
I mean, they have strawberries in them.
Huh?
Well... You can get confused
like that sometimes.
Uncle, Sis, good morning.
Morning, Yu-chan.
Morning.
Today's pooch.
Oh, so many animals!
They're having a pet special today.
First, we'd like to introduce
you to Koo, a Welsh Corgi.
Oh, it's a Corgi. So cute!
This one's owner is pretty cute.
The over-knee socks score really high points.
That absolute territory of exposed
thigh is really well balanced.
I think she'd look good
in a Gothic maid outfit.
Next up, we have Silviana, a Siberian Husky.
Oh, it's a Husky.
You don't see too many of those
lately, though I like them a lot.
This one clearly looks like a tsundere!
I feel moe...
When someone has twin ponytails,
I can't help but see it as tsundere...
You play games and stuff too, Kusakabe?
Though I suck at them...
Would you like to try some?
Oh, Hiiragi, you're great. That's amazing!
What, what's that? No way!
Check it out, Hiiragi is amazing!
You're right!
That opened up! That's totally impossible!
Seeing just how much fun she's having
makes me feel bad for worrying
about winning or losing...
It's a really smelly poser.
You mean "moe for smelly stuff"!
Oh, Patricia-san.
Hey there!
You're dropping by here a lot lately.
Patty is a very enthusiastic
overseas student.
That's why I'm trying to teach the
divine core of Japanese culture...
You can only teach a very, very
small portion of Japanese culture.
Otaku are the pride of Japanese culture!
It is my grand mission to absorb
everything that's out there
and take it back to America!
I'm appalled by your
enthusiasm and all, but...
Patricia-san, what kind of songs
are you listening to lately?
Well, let's see...
Orange Ran__, Chemis___, Suneo Ha__,
Porno Graff____, L'Arc~en~C____,
__n, Nightm___... stuff like that.
I listen to all sorts of artists from Japan.
Oh... That was unexpected.
But all those groups have
sung at least one anime song.
Man, Konata is as sharp as ever!
On top of that, Patty, you only
listen to those anime songs, right?
Oh, I'd really like a maid myself.
A maid.
Oh, a maid...
Patricia-san, you live alone
and not in a dorm or anything?
Yes. I'm always busy with cooking,
laundry, manga, and anime.
It must be hard, since you're not used to it.
I can see why you'd want a housekeeper.
Non, non... Not a housekeeper, but a maid.
What? Aren't they like the same thing?
Oh, it's totally different!
What have you been learning in this country?!
No... I think you have a
mistaken notion of Japan...
I-I can't give you this... It's fried...
She knows that you're the softie, Minami,
so she's not going away.
I guess I have no choice...
Come here, I'll give you this!
Now calm down and eat.
But this, in its own way, is a little lonely.
Everyone in our class thinks
she's quiet and scary,
but she's actually really
kind, cool, and awesome!
She seems to be quite
respected by Kobayakawa-san,
who lives in Izumi-san's house.
Oh, is that so?
Minami-chan, a neighborhood announcement!
Minami-chan is cool and awesome, right?
Oh, come to think of it, Izumi-san as well...
Minami-chan's image is that she's
very cool-headed with no faults,
but watching her with Yu-chan, you
can tell that she's a great person!
...had said something of that sort.
I'm sorry, this item is on sale,
and is limited to one per customer.
My...
Minami-chan is cool-headed with no faults...
Other than that, Kagami-san
and Tsukasa-san...
Minami-chan seems like the type
that does everything perfectly
in a straightforward manner.
It looks like nothing is impossible
for Minami-chan to do.
She's so awesome that I look up to her.
Minami-san is viewed with respect by
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san as well.
Mom... The thing you wanted was
limited to one per customer.
Oh, my...
My, my?
My, my, my?
My my my my my...
Minami-chan does everything
perfectly and straightforward?
S'up.
Hey, girl!
Welcome.
What are you watching?
A mecha anime that I rented.
Hey, this is pretty cool.
You're still really into this stuff?
I'm not that interested
in the mecha themselves.
Huh? You're not interested in the mecha?
Then what are you looking at?
Lately, mecha series,
to get a wider audience,
almost always have cute girls or boys...
Can you call that a mecha show, then?
Got that? Hiiragi, do you understand?
You have to say for sure!
I'm really counting on you tomorrow!
Yeah, yeah, I'll do my best.
Now, Misa-chan, Hiiragi-chan said okay,
so it's better to not be so persistent.
But from my past experiences,
"I'll do my best"
is a line that means she
doesn't wanna do it at all.
She picks the weirdest
things to be right about.
Kagami-sama!
Let's stop by Gamers on the way home!
I have nothing to buy today,
and I've got stuff to do today, so I'll pass.
Come on, let's stop by for a short visit...
I don't want to.
Come on!
Don't play with me!
In the first place, isn't there
a bookstore in your neighborhood?
Once you go to that kind of store,
don't ordinary bookstores totally
feel like they're missing something?
Like you can't find all
the titles that you want.
That's because your tastes
are too specialized!
So, what are you going to buy?
I'm getting this today.
You sure watch a lot of stuff.
No, I haven't seen the anime.
But, from when I saw this cover,
it feels like we're connected somehow.
It's been on my mind all this time.
I don't get it.
But I've finally started to
understand the philosophy
of buying something just based on the cover.
I mean, you pick your light
novels by the cover too, right?
Well, I won't deny it.
If they're right up your alley,
it really feels like a bargain.
But on the other hand, even if it's not,
you bought it with a light heart,
so you have no regrets...
In other words, life is about
the meeting of a lifetime!
That might be a good way to sum it up,
but a part of that argument sounds fishy...
Let's take it easy...
Perhaps this is the meeting
of a lifetime as well?
Achoo!
That was a brash one. At
least cover your mouth.
Well, you can't really control
your sneezes, you know?
This is the first time I've seen anyone
sneeze "Achoo!" as if you drew her.
Choo.
You know, the personal differences
you feel in just one sneeze...
It's unfair.
Being cute is somehow really sneaky.
Lay off her.
You go all the way around, and
so it actually smells nice...
But I heard they've already quit.
The two of you get along so well.
Have you ever gotten into an argument?
Yeah, we have!
Ayano may look like this, but when
she gets mad, she's really scary.
Oh, there are people like
that out there. You're right.
Geez! Even you, Hiiragi-chan?
By the way...
Hiiragi, you're scary on an everyday basis.
So after all, I'm in that kind of a position?
Minami-chan runs the 100 meter in
about the same time as you, Sis.
I see...
But if I were to really race her,
I'd win with the difference
being my breasts, or something?
"Smooth... Flat..."
"Smooth... Flat..." "Flat-chested girls"
Before that, wouldn't Minami-chan
win from the height factor?
She brushed that one aside very gracefully...
You think so too, right, Hiiragi?
It's amusing, right, Hiiragi?
What do you think, Hiiragi?
Misa-chan, who thinks, "Don't
give me half-assed answers,"
and Hiiragi-chan, who thinks,
"Don't ask me to answer anything
when I'm reading a book,"
are getting all worked up now...
Well, Japanese anime and game characters
sure have their moe factors!
You're right.
Oh? Isn't this graphic a bug?
Oh, no, it's all right. It's
supposed to look like that.
That's kind of indecent on its own...
Ahem!
What kind of game are you playing,
little high school girls?
What are all of you doing?
No!
Yu-chan, you don't need to know!
It's done!
I've written a long diary entry
for the first time in a while.
Now, send...
"The page cannot be found"
Back! Back!
"Warning: Page has Expired"
Lucky Star!
You know...
I'm not planning on saying
one thing after another
like the mother of the groom...
Gloomy.
But no matter what led up to
this, the two of you, you know,
raised a toast to do your best
to make this segment, right?
And despite that, you ruin
everything about it in the end?
Isn't that uncalled for?
Dropping shoulders.
It's been said that I'm
sneaky and sly and stuff,
all the while doing all sorts of things,
but this is the first time I've had to
try stopping a damn boring argument.
You understand?
Besides, if you guys don't finish this up,
it's going to sling mud in
my face as well, got it?
Hey, Shiraishi!
I'm terribly sorry, Gottuza-sama...
Huh?
And what do you think about this, Akira?
I'm sorry...
What's that?!
Sorry about that, Gottuza-sama...
Well then, let's call it
a wrap with this. Okay?
There's only one episode left.
Why don't you go back to basics
and pull Lucky Channel off or something?
Well? How about it?
Understood.
I can't hear you!
Understood!
All right, then it's been decided.
I'm going to leave the rest in your hands.
Go and live on, in the future
of the anime industry.
Well, I'm going to go back for now.
I'll let the producer know.
If there's anything else, call for me.
If you need them, I'll send
in a couple of my underlings.
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
Oh, geez! Shut up! Come on, guys,
let's at least do the final episode right.
Are you listening? Hello?
Oh, fine, I'll do it all by myself!
Next episode: To Be Decided.
Wait, it hasn't been decided yet?!