These six boys started on their path to salvation in January.
They have now given each other nicknames.
Do it once more!
Rokuto Sakuragi
Nick: Anchan
Keep your guard up!
Don't lose your range!
Mario Minakami
Nick: Mario
Do it faster!
Yes, like that.
Stop screwing around, Mario.
Even if you do that much boxing, you'll never be at his level.
Tadayoshi Tooyama
Nick: Biceps
Shut up!
Hey, Biceps...
Mansaku Matsura
Nick: Cauliflower
I'm tired.
Could we stop now?
Don't be stupid.
Let's do 20 more.
Instead of complaining, you should train.
Fuck yeah!
I won again.
Noburo Maeda
Nick: Spoon
Oh? I see.
I'm sorry, Joe.
With this, you owe me a total of 200 yen.
Jo Yokosuka
Nick: Joe
Yo, Spoon.
You could use some exercise to gain some muscle.
No need to.
My teeth are the only I need.
Well, you can't tell 'cause I've only used them on Anchan.
But my jaw is three times more powerful than yours!
That's impossible.
What is it, Baremoto?
Ryuuji Nomoto
Nick: Baremoto
You are bragging so much about them,
but if you are faced with a gun or a pistol, you're done.
Thanks to my head I've survived this world.
What the hell are you insinuating?!
You don't know a fucking thing!
Stop it, Spoon!
You're always looking for an excuse to fight!
I don't get why Baremoto likes the outside world that much.
I've been all alone out there since I was 10.
I've never relied on anyone but myself to survive.
If I compare this to the outside, this is as if I were in heaven.
I prefer being locked here after all.
Right, Joe?
Eh?
You come from the same place I do.
So, you get me, right?
Yes... But..
I wasn't all alone.
I had a sister.
A sister?
At the orphanage.
We were not blood related, but we were happy together.
Thinking of Megu is what helps me to stay alive in here.
So that's why I'd like to leave this place soon
and find my sister again.
I see now.
You've got a visit,
Yokosuka.
Wha...? Me?
Who's the one that came?
Could it be Megu?
Enough, come now.
A visit, huh?
Well, getting a visit from siblings would move anyone, right?
It's not his sister.
I haven't seen a single girl all year that was allowed to visit.
Enter.
Megu!
Good afternoon.
It's been a long time, Joe.
How have you been?
Hey, Joe...
who came to visit you just now?
The orphanage director.
She found a family for Megu.
Eh, aren't you happy about that?
So what kind of rich family did they find?
Hey, enough, Baremoto.
Joe, along with his sister, was abandoned by his mother at the entrance of the orphanage.
It's like she'd abandoned them at the gates of hell.
Alone, without love, the two kids realized that they could only rely on themselves.
Sign: Safety First
Watch out!
Spoon.
What the hell you are doing? You've got to move on!
I'm sorry.
Line up, everyone!
OK.
The next 20 in line, go to the showers.
I've got the requested supplies.
Thanks a lot!
I'll just leave it here.
Megu...
I'll help you get to your sister.
Ok, the next 20, go i-
A snake!!
A snake bit me!!
A snake!
There's a snake around!
Catch it, fast!
Now's the time, Joe.
Spoon...
Go ahead.
Don't ever come back.
Good.
Anchan, are you trying to 'scape too?
I saw the snake!
The snake is over here!
What?
Over here, it entered the barracks!
It's a venomous one, a venomous snake!
No I saw it here, it's over here.
It bit me!
The two boys escaped as fast as they could.
They were aware that if they were caught,
a fate way worse than dead awaited them.
That encouraged them to try even harder.
but what motivated Joe the most was the memory of his sister
which refused to leave him.
They escaped, Ishihara!
Do you understand the gravity of the situation?
I'm really sorry, but...
I don't want to hear it!
I'll give you only 48 hours to find them!
If you're not able to bring them back within those 48 hours, I'll make sure somebody else does!
Wasn't that just great.
We should try it once more.
Fuck, those kids sure do run fast.
Listen up! Let's go that way! Let's search over there!
Mama won't come over today, either?
I'm sure that if Megu behaves like a good girl, she will come soon.
Then, Megu will be a good girl!
So please, sing me a song!
The same as always.
That's fine.
You really are a good singer, Joe.
Would you sing that song for me again tonight?
C'mon. Hurry up, Joe.
Damn it! I don't fucking get it!
Why do I have to get beaten up for those guys?!
So, Baremoto...
Tell me something.
Why did you help Joe?
Not only you, but everyone knew we won't get anything out of this.
Even while knowing that,
you attracted the attention of the guards,
to help Joe escape.
And that got you into that isolation cell.
Th-that's...
He's your friend.
That's why.
Right, Spoon?
I, also had a family.
My father was always drunk.
He did whatever he wanted and he beat us: my mother and my little sister, Tai.
When he was drunk, I always took Tai for a walk.
But on that August day,
I went out by myself while my father was drunk.
I was all alone when that happened.
That time, of all the times I took Tai out...
An astounding incandescent flash...
...illuminated for an instant, that summer day, forming a grey mushroom.
I was in shock.
Everything was gone.
The houses, the streets, the people.
My sister was no where to be found.
Despite how deeply I loved her...
She had just disappeared.
That was not fair.
I no longer have anyone with me,
but Joe has his sister out there,
so he doesn't want to leave her alone.
With that in mind,
why wouldn't I help him?
Perfect, now that's all settled...
Megu, from now on, this kind gentleman will be your father.
Pl-please take care of me.
From now one, we'll be taking care of each other.
Aren't you happy about this, Megu?
This man is your father, so you can rest assured.
Megu.
Where are you?
Oh my, Joe.
You seem quite exhausted. Are you okay?
Shut up!
Give Megu back.
Aren't you being just a bit rude?
There's someone waiting for you here.
Don't move!
Thank you for your help. We'll be leaving.
Not a problem. This is for Joe's good as well.
Don't be so rude, Joe. You should be happy that your sister got a family.
If she saw you, she wouldn't be happy at all.
OK, we are done here. Excuse us.
Thanks for your work.
Wait there you old woman!
Are you doing to Megu what you did to me?
You just used us as your pleasure toys. What's next?
Wha-what are you saying?
Hey, perv grandma!
I bet you're giving Megu to someone as sick as yourself.
Director.
He's just saying stupid things, hurry up and take him away!
Oi, quiet down.
Yo, grandma!
If you're not satisfied with us any more, give me back my sister!
You son of a bitch!
No matter what you do, no one would've taken care of you but me. Who don't you show some gratitude?!
You're fucking joking! You just used the children as you pleased, you perv grandma!
And to still say such cruel things...
I'll put an end to you!
Do it.
I want you to fucking try!
Fucking grandma!
Stop it.
Megu.
Someone's going to get here soon.
Remember to welcome Joe back.
That stupid punk escaped just to find his sister.
Trying to avoid reclusion just for that...
Stupid people are just stupid after all.
Let's just wait for him, and hope he doesn't die on his way.
Damn it.
Megu, Megu. I came for you.
Let's get out of here together.
Why are you doing this?
Please take this guy away.
Megu, don't you get it? They're just using you.
Director, I'm sorry for the intrusion.
Megu! Don't do it, Megu.
We're supposed to be together,
waiting for mama to come.
How many times have I heard that?
She didn't come no matter how long we waited.
We were left, forgotten.
Megu.
We're not blood relatives.
We don't have anyone out there.
We can only rely on ourselves.
Me-Megu.
Don't look for me any more.
I can handle things myself.
C'mon. Move your butt.
Megu. What are you doing? Hurry up.
Thank you.
You made me really happy.
Bye bye, brother.
The reason why many people escape
is to follow a dream.
A dream which reunites a brother and sister.
Will there be a place in the future where they'll see each other again?
With this rainy day, the summer was over.
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
I can even sacrifice
my life for those whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but I'll never give it up.
Our unbreakable bond
has begun to entwine with fate,
guiding us to the endless future laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
A far-off distance.