What are they doing right now?
More than fifty years ago,
there were seven men
who fought and survived
the burning depths of hell.
Three things kept them going:
courage, guts, and their bonds.
The seven of them placed their hopes on the seven-coloured rainbow...
And they swore that they would definitely survive.
Even though it is hard to make out now,
What they desired is certainly engraved here.
They were the dreams of the seven men.
June, Shōwa 30
So?
Do you like it?
Oh.
She says she does.
Excuse us!
Hey, punk.
That's some fine pretence you were putting up there.
Scum like you should never touch other people's stuff. Never!
Ten years have passed since the end of the Second World War.
Japan has not yet economically recovered.
Homeless are appearing everywhere. Almost everyone is experiencing poverty.
The catastrophe is even affecting innocent women and children.
They can only accept things as they are.
In such cruel times, these 6 boys were sent to a juvenile prison.
Like fallen leaves being carried by the flow of their surroundings, they're being forced to face their uncertain futures.
Bow!
These are the 6 new guys!
Take care of them, Dr Sasaki.
I'm Sasaki, the medic responsible for overseeing this facility.
A healthy body will ensure a good future, so please look after yourselves.
Well, then...
It will be simple and quick, so there is no need to be so tense. Please, relax.
'kay?
You don't have to worry at all.
It will be over soon.
Right then. Let's start with you over there.
Oh wow. How interesting.
So this good for nothing punk still has some shame within him.
Hey! Get out,
you stupid fatfuck!
Pleas stop that, Ishihara.
I don't think I can forgive you if you harm any of these boys.
Next!
Ah, you, the blue eyed boy.
Your turn.
These boys were treated like slaves just for the guards' perverted pleasure.
They could do nothing about it.
They're asses were examined with a glass probe purely for the doctors' enjoyment.
Regardless of the kind of person subject to it,
they would feel ashamed and violated by that treatment.
These boys still have no idea
the sort of emotions they'll experience here.
Just like that, their journey through this hellish place had begun.
Ask him for advice, he's been here longer than you.
Got it?
So...
the hell are we gonna do now?
Yo, bro.
You are being a little rude.
Why won't you greet these guys?
I don't need to greet punks and fags like you.
What the hell was that?
Punk asshole monkeys like you are stupid enough to think they can hold onto their pride while being stuck in this shithole.
Based on what I see,
you're all asshole monkeys.
Don't fuck with us!
Don't go thinking you're the fucking boss of this place.
I see what you did there.
Like the rest of us, you're a pest to society.
So, no one would give a shit if we kill you right now.
You feel me, bro?
We six are all together, so there's no way in hell we'll lose.
What the fuck is so funny!?
Certainly, even if all of you punks died,
nobody would give a shit.
Damn...
Dudes.
People don't care about whatever happens to you.
So come get some.
Bo-boxing?
Boxing?
So what?
I hate it...
I hate...
I can't stand people who underestimate me!
What's the matter?
Come if you've got the guts.
I'm gonna to kill you!
Minakami Mario. Age 17.
Attemped homicide.
Assaulted a teacher who tried to rape a female student.
The teacher took 3 months to fully recover.
Grrrrrr.
Tooyama Tadayoshi. Age 17.
Violent behaviour and disturbing the peace.
Caused serious injuries to a man in the course of protecting his mother.
It was ruled that his actions were beyond that reasonable for self-defence.
Maeda Noboru. Age 16.
Serial thief.
Has been captured numerous times for these crimes.
It's not even possible to determine the exact number of cases.
Rooooaaaaaarrrrrrrr!
Yokosuka Joe. Age 16. Nicknamed Joe.
Personal assault and engaging in illicit sexual relationships.
Seriously injured a person that attempted to rape him.
They needed 3 months of treatment.
Matsuura Mansaku. Age 17. Nicknamed Cabbage.
Personal assault and alcohol abuse among others.
Constantly getting drunk and picking fights in public.
He left a man seriously injured which resulted in his arrest.
Nomoto Ryuuji. Age 17.
Robery and fraud.
Criminal activites around the region.
He's also suspected to be involved gambling fraud.
Nobody trusted these guys but themselves.
Even if they didn't mean to, they did it.
It was impossible not to lose.
What's wrong, punk?
Where's the guy who wanted to beat me?
Kill me.
Kill me now.
I lost my pride.
I can't do nothing.
Excuse me.
Take this.
Please forgive us.
A cigarette?
Yes.
Eh? I wasn't expecting to see such a flashy scene just yet.
Killing one or two occasionally seems quite fitting for you.
But all six of you should know that such violent acts are not allowed here.
You just got here today, so
I'll show you, how we break down disruptive pigs in here.
Take this as your welcoming present.
Get down.
Hey, are you listening to me!
Get down NOW!
Got it you faggots?
Make sure you see this perfectly.
Bastard!
Now.
You'll smash him too.
Don't hold back now.
You want to, right?
Try it now.
This guy is better off dead.
Do it!
C'mon!
I'm telling you.
Do it!
Hey!
You! Do it!
I can't.
You bastaaaards...
Disobeying me?!
Stop it.
Spare...
these guys.
Please...
YOU BASTARD!!!
Please wait Mr Ishihama.
Dr Sasaki.
Haven't I told you before?
You can't treat these boys like that.
What part of that don't you understand?
I'll have to treat you again.
He finally stopped?
You wiped my scars...
Thanks.
That's right.
Yo, four eyes.
Hey, you. Go and keep watch.
Keep watch?
"Guard", OK?
Guard...
Use this.
If anyone shows up, stomp once.
Got it?
Ehm....
Could you
tell us your name?
That's why you are all just punks!
You should first give your own name,
before asking for another's, you brats!
I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Hey.
Have a quick puff.
We should not smoke alone.
Everyone, I want to hear your names.
Yes.
Take a puff.
You're the last.
I'll take over the watching, so hurry.
You want to bribe us all
with just that?
Bribing six punks? What's in for me?
I understand the kind of problems you boys went through.
Hey, its almost finished, smoke it while you can.
It's good.
I'm Sakuragi.
Sakuragi Rokurouta.
Nice to meet ya.
Hopefully, in two summers time,
everyone will regain their freedom.
This is
Sakuragi Rokurouta
standing up like an older brother.
A brother who's kind and protecting.
These boys where not familiar with the feeling,
the feeling that this kind hearted brother was expressing.
That feeling might vanish from time to time.
But here,
the feeling of a rainbow marked on their hearts will prevail.
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
I can even sacrifice
my life for those whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but I'll never give it up.
Our unbreakable bond
has begun to entwine with fate,
guiding us to the endless future laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
A far-off distance.
Escape...
It connotes hopping away, thus it is referred as "rabbit".
Joe runs...
to see his sister.