Looks like you got beat pretty badly.
Bro, don't be too hard on Mario.
Your right hand...
Is it okay?
It's already late.
Get some rest.
We'll start training tomorrow.
You can't stop with just a loss, can you, Mario?
Bro...
In preparation for the next match,
they both practiced hard every day.
Sharper!
Tuck more quickly!
Mario practiced a right feint-left punch combo again and again until it became second nature.
Bro held the sandbag with his body,
Good, just like that!
even though he had not fully recovered.
Use your hip!
Will the god of delinquents smile on these fugitive boys?
Hey, Mario! Bro!
I just set up your next match.
It'll be on January 28, a Saturday.
Bro.
Yeah.
Let's win for sure next time.
Well, I need to go to work.
Hey!
Why don't you take a break for a bit?
I can't lose if you're going to be making a fortune.
Stay out of trouble.
You bet!
Turtle made money buying western tobacco from Lily's boyfriend in the U.S. Army,
and selling it on the black market.
Meanwhile,
at Shonan Special Disciplinary School...
Tohyama Tadayoshi, your request to enlist in the Self-Defense Forces has been officially granted.
Accordingly, you will be released from this disciplinary school in ten days, on January 28.
Hey, Soldier.
I'll tell you where those three are staying later.
If I were in your shoes,
I'd want to go see them right away.
So don't worry about us.
No, I don't think I will.
If I blew their cover...
no amount of tears would be enough.
I doubt Ishihara's just going to forget about them either.
Soldier...
Hey, Setsuko, what's this?
Oh, that?
It's a picture of my family.
Your family?
It's our custom to take a family photo every New Year.
Is that your little brother?
And that's your younger sister, right?
Yeah, she's turning ten this year.
Turtle.
Why don't you check it out?
Her sister's really cute.
I'm going to work.
Turtle?
What are you, a kid?
Stop getting excited over a stupid photo!
What's wrong with him?
Was it something I said?
Sorry, Setsuko.
He doesn't mean any harm.
He lost his family in the atomic bombings,
so he doesn't have any photos of his family.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
No need to apologize.
You couldn't have known about it.
Don't worry. Knowing him...
he'll be back to normal tomorrow.
Hey, why don't we all take a picture?
We're going to make tons of happy memories from now on.
If we take one together, I'm sure it would make Maeda happy.
Nice idea.
Don't you think so, Bro?
S-Sure.
Okay, then let's do it!
Sign: Shonan Hospital
Several Days Later
Here, is this what you wanted?
Wow, thank you so much.
It's my husband's treasure,
so treat it with extreme care.
Thank you so much.
So, Secchan,
what's he like?
What are you talking about?
Oh, please, I've got you figured out.
You want to take a picture with the person you love, right?
Don't try to hide it.
I-It's nothing like that!
You want to release Sakuragi?
Are you worried?
You've been paying such close attention to him.
Could she be the one hiding them?
Hey, Mario!
Why do you get to stand in the middle?
You're so loud! Shut up!
Guys, stop moving.
Bro, you'd better smile!
You're going to look back at this later.
You're acting a little cocky.
Shut up! I'm the star today!
What was that?
Hey, stop fighting!
My goodness...
Now we'll have to do it over.
I can't believe she punched me.
Okay, now get back in line.
Okay.
Minakami and Maeda, stop fighting.
Sakuragi, you need to smile.
Okay?
Okay, I'm setting up the camera.
Big smile!
So they were with her.
Yes, you were right on the money.
But it's too soon to act now.
We should carefully observe their-
Ishihara, you...
That fucking Sakuragi...
He looked so happy.
I'll kill him.
I'll fucking kill that bastard!
Why don't you come in?
You'll catch a cold.
They're late,
don't you think?
Those idiots.
They think they're doing me a favor?
Why did I need to come with you?
Are you stupid?
Don't you want to give Bro and Setsuko some private time?
Oh, I get it.
Setsuko went to all that trouble about the family photo because of me.
A woman that good needs to get together with Bro.
What's wrong?
You haven't said anything.
I can't get comfortable,
ever since I hared out of the facility.
In reality, I should be raising my arms in joy about this kind of life,
but I'm not used to happiness.
What are you saying?
It's going to get even better, you know?
Next year, you'll see everyone under that tree.
All seven of you.
Yeah.
I'm really happy.
That you got out of there in one piece.
That I can be together with you.
Aren't you cold?
Let's go inside.
Yeah.
"Can we become as happy as a typical couple?"
Rokurouta, battered and bruised, lived at the hideout with his beloved Setsuko.
Irritated and worried about the uncertain future ahead,
love was the only thing he could rely on.
Do you like it?
It's the coat my father used to wear.
It's going to be chilly tomorrow,
so this way you won't catch a cold.
Hey, Mario.
Wouldn't you say this is discrimination?
Yeah.
I have one for each of you too.
Really?
You look fabulous.
I'm not taking back what I said.
Me neither.
It's tomorrow.
Yeah.
With you as my second, I'll be invincible.
I'll prepare a feast tomorrow.
Also, the photo we took the other day should be ready by then.
Really?
All right!
Tomorrow, they will begin climbing up the seven-colored rainbow that comes after the rain.
What sort of world waits on the other side?
January 28.
January 28
The morning was shrouded in fog.
Don't push your limits.
I know.
Mario's doing the fighting.
It's okay.
Here.
If you get hungry, share it among the three of you.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
Well, be safe.
Yeah, I'll see you later.
Indulge that happiness while you can.
I'll make sure to end it for good!
Bro!
I passed the weight check on my first try.
That's good.
Where's Turtle?
He went to the city to sell some cigarettes.
He said he'd be back before the fight.
I see.
Man, that merchant was such a cheapskate.
How am I gonna throw a party with so little money?
I'll need to make another trade.
Are you Maeda Noboru?
Maeda who?
I think you have the wrong guy.
In any case, show us what you have in your sack.
This?
This is...
He's running! After him!
Damn it!
How do the police know my face?
He's over there!
Man...
Why?
Why the fuck are there police everywhere?
Stop!
Damn.
It's starting to pour.
Hey, Bro.
It's about Setsuko.
Do you like her?
Why are you asking so suddenly?
You're thinking of getting married, right?
I don't know.
I don't think I can do anything.
Still, I do want to make her happy.
That's how I feel.
She went through a lot of trouble for someone like me.
I want her to be happy no matter what.
Bro, watch me fight.
I'll definitely win.
Sorry, Bro.
I screwed up.
Mario, I...
can't make it to your fight.
Tohyama Tadayoshi!
The Self-Defense Forces are here to pick you up!
Go to the Warden's room immediately!
Congratulations!
You're being released!
Cabbage...
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Don't forget.
On June 6 next year...
I'll be waiting under that tree.
Coffee, please.
Did you hear about Maeda?
I tipped off the police,
and he got caught just like that.
I see.
Now, about the suicide note.
I couldn't find it in their hideout.
This would mean...
I know, Dr. Sasaki.
Then that shortens our conversation.
You can leave the final cleaning up to me.
Let's finish this off.
Sign: National Police Shibuya Police Station
Sakuragi Rokurouta and Minakami Mario.
The friends who escaped with you.
Don't tell me you don't know them.
Why don't you say something?!
If you won't, the Inspector's going to feel pretty blue.
Inspector?
Yeah, the guy who was in charge of you.
He tipped us off, you know.
Give me a phone!
Let me make a phone call!
Hurry up!
It's him.
He's on the move.
Ishihara's back on the move, Bro!
Looks like you're up next.
Let's go, Mario.
Yeah.
Hey, you two!
Wait!
Lily?
The short friend of yours...
He got caught by the police.
Turtle?
We got a call from a person named Maeda.
He's being held at the Shibuya Police Station right now.
The Shibuya Station...
Are you Sakuragi Rokurouta?
Yes.
He's asked us to put you on the line.
Bro.
Please go, Bro.
He must have something important to say.
He wouldn't call here otherwise.
Mario...
Don't worry about me.
Hurry up and take the call.
All right.
You'd better win, Mario.
You bet I will.
Hey, Pops.
Sorry I asked you to be my second all of a sudden.
Nah, don't worry.
Do you think you can do it this time?
I'll win.
I have to pay you back.
Not to mention...
I've got Bro's teachings inscribed in my heart.
Bro...
I'll...
I'll definitely win!
Sign: Kobayashi's House of Photographs
Sign: Tachikawa Police Station
Is that true?
That guard Ishihara is a Philopon addict.
He's in cahoots with those fugitive kids and is selling guns from the U.S. Army.
If you don't believe me,
I suggest you stake out the base.
He should be making a deal with gangsters from the city.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You're very welcome.
What's wrong, kid?
You're letting him do anything he wants!
Listen, Mario.
You need to defend in the first round.
The real battle starts in the second round!
I know, Bro.
"I'm used to being in tough situations."
"Right now, I just need to do as Bro taught me."
Mario and Bro, his trainer, were connected by a firm bond of trust.
Bro runs to take the call from Turtle.
And Mario begins to set a trap in the boxing ring.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
Mario fights alone.
Sakuragi and Ishihara duel.
The end of the battle is near.
Hey, everyone! It's Satake Uki.
Mr. Kakizaki Masasumi is one of the original creators of RAINBOW.
His much anticipated new manga will be serialized next week in "Big Comic Spirits."
Well, the new series has a completely different atmosphere from RAINBOW.
This new one is not exactly horror,
but I thought I'd try something sort of like horror.
And I hope that I can show the dark side of human beings.
Serialization begins in the new "Spirits" issue next Monday,
so please read it.