Fionn mac Cumhaill,
hero of Ireland and leader of the Knights of Fianna,
and my daughter, Grainne,
are pleased to announce their engagement!
Everyone, this night, I want you all to celebrate!
That striking man with the mole beneath his eye,
what is his name?
He is a knight of Fianna, Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Diarmuid...
Traitor.
You will suffer for this, Diarmuid.
Take me with you.
We must run away.
Rejoice, Grainne!
Fionn has recognized our marriage.
Did you believe I'd forgotten what happened with Grainne?
A dream?
That dream I had...
It was the legend of Diarumuid.
Could those have been the memories of my servant?
Where am I?
I see that you're awake now.
Sola‐Ui!
What is a meaning of this?
Wh... what am I doing this place?
So I gather that you have no
memory at all of what happened to you?
I... I was shot.
I defended myself with the Volumen Hydragyrum, but...
...what happened to my body?
Your body's magic circuits have misfired somehow.
You're lucky you didn't die instantly.
For now, I've only been able to regenerate your organs.
But your magic circuits were utterly destroyed.
I'm afraid you'll never use magic again.
But I can't...
I can't...
Don't cry, Kayneth.
It's too soon to give up.
It will be all right.
We haven't lost yet.
Sola‐Ui.
If the Holy Grail is truly an
omnipotent wish‐granting device,
then healing you completely and making you
whole again should be more than possible for it.
We need only to win.
If we succeed and claim the Grail,
everything will return to how it was.
So, with that in mind, Kayneth,
why don't you give the Command Seals to me?
That way, I can take over as Lancer's master.
I'll win the war and bring the Grail to you.
No.
I won't.
Oh, you don't believe in me then?
Me, who will marry into Archibald family?
No, I just...
Sola‐Ui, do you think...
...Lancer would actually just
abandon me and then swear fealty to you?
I do.
He is a Heroic Spirit here by the Grail's invitation.
He desires the Holy Grail just as we do,
even if he must take on a new master.
He will accept it for the sake of his goal.
He won't!
Lancer isn't the fine man you think he is!
And why do you say that, Kayneth?
When I asked him what he would wish
for if he had the Grail, he said to me,
"I have no interest in the Holy Grail."
A servant with no desire for the Grail is impossible!
He's hiding something important from me.
But no matter. What deep, dark
secret he's trying to keep hidden,
as long as I bear these Command
Seals, he must obey me unconditionally.
Kayneth?
I won't give you the Command Seals.
Oh, Kayneth, you still don't get it.
Don't you see?
We must win this war no matter what the cost.
Listen, Kayneth.
With my limited skills as a healer,
it is quite impossible to
remove any Command Seals by force.
The bearer's willing consent is the sole
way for me to take them without resistance.
If you truly cannot accept
this, you will leave me no choice.
I will have to amputate your right arm.
What's your answer?
How is she?
She's going to be all right.
Magical healing can put a
tremendous stress on the patient.
I think it will take some time yet before she wakes up.
Watch her for a while, okay?
You're going to report to Kiritsugu now?
Yes, Saber.
I'm sure he's worried too.
Irisviel, I have a request.
I'd like you to speak to him for me.
Tell him I feel that we must pursue Caster immediately.
But, Saber.
Inaction on our part will mean the
deaths of many more innocent children.
May I come in?
How long before Maiya's back?
Not too long, but she has to
stay in bed for another day or two.
I see.
You and Saber stay here.
I'm going to go follow Kayneth.
No, Kiritsugu, wait a minute.
Did Saber tell you?
She thinks we should go after Caster right away.
Apparently so.
Are you angry at Saber for not interfering with Lancer?
Iri, saving a few children,
or even a few dozen for that matter,
is not our goal.
Saber probably never doubted
that Lancer would spare me that day,
but if Lancer had betrayed her, then what?
Our Grail War would have ended right then and there.
There's no need to tell her where I'm going.
Lancer, please show yourself.
Mistress Sola‐Ui, how fares Master Kayneth?
Not well, I'm afraid.
But I've done everything I can for him.
This isn't your fault, Lancer.
Kayneth brought it upon himself.
All it means is that the Grail War
was far too much for him to handle.
It's not that, I just...
Diarmuid, don't you see? He
isn't worthy of being your master.
Kayneth has abandoned the battle,
giving his right as your master to me.
As a knight, my loyalty is
eternally pledged to Master Kayneth.
Mistress Sola‐Ui, I'm sorry, but I cannot consent.
You what?
As a servant, do you not manifest
physically in this world using my mana?
And now I also have Kayneth's
consent, as well as the Command Seals.
Before I am a servant of the Grail War,
I am foremost a knight,
and a knight can only serve but one master.
Am I so unworthy of being your master?
I have already told you that is not the issue.
Look me in the eye when you speak!
Lancer, fight beside me.
Please, you must protect me.
Lend me your support.
Come and help me win the Holy Grail!
I cannot.
If Master Kayneth has given up his quest for the Grail,
then I no longer have any interest in it.
We require a miracle to heal
him. He has no chance otherwise!
We need the Grail for that miracle.
If you're feeling responsible for all this,
if you desire to give him back his life and his dignity,
you must win the Holy Grail for your master.
Mistress Sola‐Ui, do you speak as Master Kayneth's wife
and seek the Holy Grail only on his behalf?
Is that what you're saying?
Uh, well, yes.
Yes, of course.
That is your only desire?
You'll swear to it?
Yes, I swear.
As the wife of Lord Kayneth El‐Melloi,
I shall bring my husband the Grail.
That look in her eyes.
It is the same as Grainne had.
I don't hate them for what happened.
However, fate was simply too cruel
to allow it to happen any other way.
What I seek from this life
is the loyalty denied me in my last.
I wish to keep that sad fate from happening again.
But...
In my previous life, I threw myself into many battles...
...often times, ignoring the lives that would be lost,
and, so, I understand Kiritsugu's reasoning.
However, the Holy Grail War has very clear rules.
It is supposed to be a proxy war conducted by servants
to avoid unnecessary bloodshed.
Isn't that true, Irisviel?
If Kiritsugu and Lancer's master
had not engaged in a secret battle,
we could have struck down Caster.
We would no longer have to worry about
more innocent children being killed.
Lancer and I could have finished
our duel in an honorable fashion.
Is there no chance of Kiritsugu changing his mind?
If you believe only one thing, believe this:
For Kiritsugu and me to make our ideal world a reality,
you are absolutely essential.
Uh...
You know, it does a man good to watch you drink.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
You should have told us you had a guest coming
over. I'd have cooked something special for you.
No, no, don't trouble yourself.
The simple pleasures of home and hearth
are what are truly best in this world.
Oh, my, you are such a flatterer, aren't you?
We couldn't help but worry over how
Waver was doing at his school in England,
but if he's managed to make friends with a strapping
man like you, well, I guess we were worried over nothing.
Hm, not at all.
It is I who am in his debt.
See, he even picked out these fine pants.
Look at the craftsmanship.
They're fit for a king.
So, how long will you be in Japan, Alexei?
Oh, I should have all my work here
wrapped up in about a week or so.
Well, I was just thinking that, if you
like, you could stay right here with us.
I'm pretty sure that there's space
enough to put another futon in Waver's room.
Right, Waver?
Futon?
Oh, yes, the bedding that they sleep on in this land.
Sleeping on a futon does take some getting used to.
It's strange to sleep on the floor instead of a bed.
I think that is what is best about
traveling to distant foreign lands.
My favorite thing in life is the surprise of the unknown.
Surely, Asia gives me the most enjoyment in any age.
I couldn't agree with you more.
I've told you!
Take the spiritual form when you come and go!
Yes, well, had I done so, I would
not have been able to retrieve this.
I even managed to procure this fine pair of pants.
And anyway, boy, it was you who ordered me to do it.
Why must I, the King of Conquerors, go
forth to draw water from some country river?
Because it's a lot more productive than
eating junk food and watching all those videos.
Hmm.
What is this, are you playing at being an alchemist?
I'm not playing.
I am an alchemist, idiot.
How interesting, what is that?
Spell casting residue,
remnants of magic left in the water.
And that means someone was
recently using magic near the river.
If we follow the trail,
it may be able to show us where to look for Caster.
Hey, boy, did you know ahead of time
that you were gonna find something like that
lurking out there in the water?
Of course not, but this town is unique in
that water flows straight through its center,
so water was the obvious place to look.
Rider, was there anything between here and here?
A sewage pipe, or maybe an irrigation channel?
Oh, yes, there was one of considerable size down there.
That's it.
If we follow it, it will probably
lead us right to Caster's hideout.
Hmm.
Boy, are you certain you aren't a
mage of not inconsiderable skill?
Look, a truly skilled mage
wouldn't have to do it this way.
As a skill, it's pretty basic.
Wait a minute, you're making fun of me, aren't you?
No, boy, quite the opposite.
To accomplish something so impressive
using a simple method outshines
those who use a more complex technique.
As your servant, I am proud.
Right.
Now that we have his location, he's as good as ours.
Shall we go give him a good beating right away, boy?
Wait a second.
We're talking about engaging Caster here.
I know.
No, you don't.
When it comes to defending his lair,
he has a tremendous advantage over any attacker.
What kind of moron would just
go bursting in the front door?
Listen here, in a combat situation, enemy and
ally positions can practically change by the second.
If you fail to attack the
enemy when you know his location,
it will be too late for regrets
once you've missed your chance.
Really, and what's made you so eager today?
Shouldn't I be?
My master has finally contributed
something of worth to our great endeavor.
As your loyal servant, I must also do my sacred duty.
Seek out and defeat the enemy
and bring back his head to you.
Ha‐ha, do not be so quick to
give up before we have even begun.
Let us go and see what we can find.
It may well work out better than you imagine.
Ah!
You see, I was right, wasn't I?
Everything has worked out splendidly!
Hmm, unfortunately, Caster appears to be away.
Is this some kind of water storage system?
Hey, boy, I think it would be best if you didn't see this.
What are you talking about?
If Caster isn't here, we should at
least search for clues to his whereabouts.
It'd be dumb not to.
That may be so, but don't do it.
Boy, this is far too much for you.
Oh, shut up.
I warned you, didn't I?
I told you not to look.
Shut up!
Damn it, stop making fun of me.
Damn it.
This is no time for pride, foolish boy.
Your reaction is natural.
If I saw someone who could look on all of this
and still remain unmoved, I would punch them hard.
What do you mean you'd punch them, you idiot.
What about you?
You look fine, just like you always do.
That's because now is not the time for emotion.
Huh?
Because my young master is in mortal peril!
Assassin?
But that's impossible.
Assassin's dead.
I saw him die.
We can't afford to be surprised, boy.
But how?
The how of it is totally irrelevant to us now.
However, one thing here is for certain.
Anyone in this war who believed in Assassin's
untimely demise, as we did, has been thoroughly deceived.
They ran.
Didn't they?
Do not let your guard down.
We killed two,
but there appeared to be an additional two.
At this rate, who can say how many
assassins there truly are out there?
This is Assassin's preferred terrain.
We should withdraw from here at once.
Should we really leave it like this?
Perhaps you'd find something if you were to look,
but let it go.
For now, we'll just have to break what we can.
If nothing else, it will serve to slow Caster down.
With his hideout destroyed and completely in ruins,
Caster will no longer be able to hide.
He'll be forced to come out of the
shadows, into the open, and show himself.
Then after that, it won't be too long
before we put an end to him and his master.
All right.
I get it!
Quit doing that!
Let us be off, boy.
Do not let it trouble you, Kirei.
Indeed, it is unfortunate that
Assassin was exposed to them
before we could discern the
nature of Rider's ultimate weapon.
But from this encounter,
we found out that Rider's
master is a mere third‐rate mage.
Yes, but had they not been discovered...
You think that other options
would have become available to you?
Yes.
Hm.
While your plans are certainly important,
you must see to it that you remain
refined and relaxed in all matters.
Dignity is required even during battle.
But I never expected that he'd
be such a dull and boring person.
We will certainly have another
chance to see Rider's ultimate attack.
Have Assassin to continue to monitor Rider,
but remind them to take great care as they do.
Yes, my teacher, it will be done.
You used too much mana all at once.
But I'm certain there's something I can do to help!
I just can't believe she went to Fuyuki.
Behold, the family magic of the Matous.
We were just about to get the party started.
I can't accomplish anything this way.