Hi, everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star, please
keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can, okay?
Well, well, well. Doesn't
it make you really anxious
when you go somewhere you don't know?
Everything I bump into
is something new for me.
Applying something I've already learned
or memorized is not good enough.
I know it happens all the time,
but I wonder why they still keep getting
mad at me?! I wonder. I wonder!
The dream everyone is looking
for must be someplace
It has to be somewhere
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Remember how I used to say
I could make it to the end?
I must have been pretending to be tough
Everything I did was reckless
and it never got me anywhere
But you alone were always beside me
The dream everyone is looking
for must be somewhere
You can start going forward
From this moment, something will start
I want to believe that
The light I haven't seen yet is
beaming toward the promised place
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Great work!
We're off starting tomorrow.
Since we have a week, we can really relax.
Once in a while, it would be nice
if we could travel or something.
You're full of energy, Sora.
I'm going to take a break and relax.
Me too.
Really?
I feel like visiting a town
I've never visited before.
You know, just let loose!
Sora.
What?
This...
What? This is an airline ticket.
Could you possibly be rewarding me
for my hard work with a trip somewhere?
Possibly? Possibly?
Congratulations.
Your dream came true.
It's work.
Well...
For now, at least your dream came true...
I want you to make a guest appearance
Work, work, work... I have to work...
in my old friend Mr. Pack's circus.
An ordeal...
The card signifies sacrifice.
It's ominous.
"Mysterious Amazing Circus."
Over there, I will be your manager.
So, please expect me to act accordingly.
Yes.
But I'm glad you're coming with me.
I guess life is good sometimes.
We're going to a place
called Theatrical Camp.
Theatrical Camp?
It's a mobile circus.
Their highlights are fire
breathing, knife throwing,
whip tricks, and keg juggling.
I see...
I wonder if I also need to do fire breathing.
I doubt it.
Strangers!
Ken.
Oh... Don't worry.
It's supposed to be around here.
Oh, that way!
I have been waiting for
you, Miss Sora Naegino.
Welcome to Theatrical Camp.
She really is breathing flame.
Here it goes!
Sorry.
Amazing...
Even the audience is participating.
Hey, Milo!
I know nothing.
You ate it!
That's enough, Tank!
Leave the place quick once
you finish your juggling!
But it makes the kids happy...
Don't come up with an excuse!
Okay, okay.
Excuse me...
Don't make me repeat the
same thing over and over!
Wait!
I didn't eat it!
Then who ate it?
I don't know.
Excuse me!
I'm introducing a guest to you.
This is Miss Sora Naegino.
I came from Kaleido Stage!
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Sora's manager, Ken Robbins.
Kaleido Stage...
Here!
This evening's beef stew has the best meat.
Meat, meat!
For tomorrow's show, since we have a guest,
why don't we do the one we
haven't done in a while?
Miss Sora Naegino...
I want you to play the
leading part, the Princess.
The leading part?
Yes.
And it's the role of a princess?
I don't know if I'm capable
of playing that role.
Maybe it's impossible...
What?
Impossible, impossible, impossible...
Well... I will do my best.
The story itself is very simple.
The role we want you to play
is a heroine who rescues
her younger twin sisters,
who are taken by a witch.
All right.
Mila and Milo are throwing
away carrots again, Dominique.
If you do it again, you'll have no dinner!
Yes...
Pamela, you're going to
play the villain, a witch.
Yes.
Tank, you're going to play a glutton
with supernatural strength.
All right.
And...
You will fight against a
knife-throwing monster man.
And then you will head for the witch's nest.
Pack, don't forget about me.
Of course, Mr. Dio.
He is the heroine's only ally.
The two of them cooperate
to rescue the twins,
and they fall in love and...
Lov--
It comes to a happy ending.
It's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too.
I don't think they need to fall in love.
Okay, okay.
Can you feed him milk?
All right.
Chocolate.
Tiger.
A lion handler.
Dog.
Stuffed animals.
This script talks about the story,
but it doesn't say anything
about how we perform.
I wonder what I'm supposed to do.
Lake!
Well, never mind.
We already said that one.
I'll ask during rehearsal tomorrow.
No, we didn't!
I think I should rest well today.
It already came up!
No, it did not!
Yes, it did!
You're annoying!
It came up, it came up!
It came up, it came up, it came up!
I can't sleep...
Ken...
Sora,
the stars are beautiful.
Yes, they are.
Ken...
What?
Thank you for everything.
Huh? What? All of a sudden...
Because you always help me
whenever I'm in trouble.
And you encourage me.
Without your help,
I doubt I would've had the chance
to play the Little Mermaid.
Or the chance to co-star
with Miss Layla, either.
I don't think that's true.
You got those things because you worked hard.
I wonder.
No, really.
You're a hard worker.
You work too hard.
I sometimes feel that you
may end up out of my league.
Huh?
Oh... It's nothing.
I think you should get some sleep tonight.
Well... It's noisy and...
Oh... Really?
But I'll do my best and try to sleep.
I think that would be better.
Okay, I will do my best and sleep!
That baby cried all night long.
Yeah. Tank's snoring was pretty bad too.
Nobody's here.
The male cast isn't here either.
What? Then what about the rehearsal?
They're probably not going to have one.
What? They're not?
Well...
They almost never rehearse.
What?!
Then what's everyone doing now?
Who knows?
Until the evening performance,
it's their free time.
What?
That's coming from the stage.
Mr. Dio!
I'm glad.
I was wondering what to
do, since nobody was here.
I bet everyone went out to have some fun.
People in town give us a warm reception,
and we get free food and drink.
Oh, wait a moment!
You really don't rehearse at all?
I can't perform without a rehearsal.
Well... What shall I do?
Well then, I will teach
you one important thing.
Yes.
Since you saw the show yesterday,
I think you already know this,
but each member has something
that they're good at.
The story itself is there just so
each of us can show off our forte.
So always pay attention to the
audience's reaction, and proceed.
Proceed while paying attention
to the audience's reaction...
That's right.
What you want to show the
audience is up to you.
Relax.
Thank you very much.
It's up to me...
Pamela!
You're great!
Princess!
If you wish to rescue your sisters,
you should come to my castle!
Help!
I wonder, can I show up already?
I wonder... I wonder...
What should I do?!
Hurry and get out!
I'm a heroine.
So I have to act like one.
Mila, Milo where did you go?
I hope the witch didn't...
Oh, wait!
I still haven't finished my lines yet...
Sora...
It looks like everything is going smoothly.
Going smoothly?
She's terrible.
Wait! Excuse me!
Oh! Beer kegs!
Now is indeed the time to
test the Princess's courage!
Please... Please...
Please don't move.
I'm here, Princess!
I can't finish the show like this.
Not like this!
What?
You're nothing!
What are you people thinking?
If this is how she's going to be treated,
I'll refuse to let her
appear on stage tomorrow.
If Miss Sora Naegino insists on that,
there's nothing I can do.
It seems showing a new member in
trouble is all part of the show.
If you want to leave,
I can explain the situation to Kalos.
I don't mind them making fun of my mistakes.
But, it's not like that.
They were all laughing at
me because I was a stranger.
Yesterday's show...
I thought it was amazing. The
audience and cast became one.
It was so exciting.
But today, from the beginning to the end,
they treated me like a stranger.
They didn't even allow me to perform.
Are you talking about Pamela?
Mr. Dio!
It's terrible what Pamela did to you.
But did you notice Pamela
before you grabbed the swing?
What?
You stole Pamela's thunder.
Oh...
So that's why...
I...
Thank you, Mr. Dio.
Go to sleep already!
What?
I'm sorry for what I did to you back then.
I bet you feel like going back already.
It's not so easy that you'll get applause
just for following the script
like you do at Kaleido Stage.
Kaleido Stage isn't that easy either!
I'm not leaving yet.
Really...
While I perform here,
I will appear on stage as
one of the members here.
So, tomorrow, please make sure to catch me.
If I feel like it.
Is this a foolish person's upright position?
Fool!
Just as I feared.
You look upset after being tossed
about in the storms of life.
Did you come because you
were worried about me?
That's right.
I endured staying inside that tight suitcase.
Still,
I never expected you to get so upset.
I'm glad I'm here.
Thank you, Fool.
I'm glad I'm here, too!
No!
Oh... A roach...
First, let's start with
learning more about the stage.
Okay.
As I expected, the stage as a whole is small.
It means there's not much distance
between you and the audience.
To tell you the truth, at Kaleido Stage,
the audience can't see the
performers' subtle expressions.
But here, the audience can see your
expressions even when you're in trouble.
Okay.
Doing the same show I do at Kaleido
Stage doesn't attract the audience here.
I have to perform while observing
the cast members and the audience.
Unless I can do that, I can't be one of them.
Princess!
If you wish to rescue your sisters,
you should come to my castle!
Help!
Okay!
Yes!
Mila, Milo, where did you go?
Were they kidnapped by the witch?
I will make sure to rescue them.
I will!
What?
Did I miss something?
Oh...
Well, then...
How about this?
Oh, here I go!
Here, here, here, here!
Oh, beer kegs!
Thank you, thank you!
Princess, you're the best!
Sora Naegino!
Bravo!
Good, I think I can do this.
Ready!
Are you saying to hit the
bull's-eye right in that circle?
Yeah!
Not bad...
I'm here, Princess!
I will show you the leading role's maneuver.
What?
What! Straight up?
Amazing.
You're amazing, Miss Pamela!
I've never seen anything like that before!
I can manage that maneuver
only one time in five.
But I didn't want to be outdone by you, so...
There is no way I can...
A great maneuver which may
hurt you isn't required here.
The thing which is required here
is the ability to appear on stage every day.
Kaleido Stage isn't everything.
I understand very well that
each troupe has a show
it's best suited for.
I used to be in Kaleido Stage.
What?
But it wasn't my kind of place, you know...
I wasn't allowed to do what I wanted.
Oh... Really?
You seem like the kind who
does whatever you want to do.
Well...
I don't mean to act that way, but...
I bet you're just what Kaleido
Stage needs right now.
Sadly though, it's the time to say goodbye.
What?
It seems Milo's twisted an ankle
during today's performance.
It's earlier than the date we had in mind,
but we decided to cut the performance short.
What are these?
Olives.
Mr. Pack plants olives like
these at each place we camp.
It's his hobby.
They say that the olive, the symbol of peace,
can sprout the next season even if
the place where it was burns down.
I wish to be as strong as this olive.
And, more importantly,
the olive is a must-have for a good salad.
She is charming.
That princess role was played by
many people, including Pamela,
but I thought she had such invaluable talent.
Unless someone nurtures her,
the flower of her talents will never bloom.
I understand.
I will make sure to nurture her talents.
Pamela, please come to see our show too.
If I feel like it.
What? That's not nice.
"Next Kaleido Star"
I'm afraid he no longer needs me.
And so...
What? Miss Sarah was approached
by another company?
Not only that... It's a man
and a woman's ten year love!
An entangled love triangle...
I don't understand the complicated stuff.
But we can't just let things go
like this, right? Right? Right?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Diva's Amazing Love."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
I'm here between the sky and the
roads, and facing against the wind
And I'm facing forward so the sorrow
doesn't rain down ever again
I came all the way here after
I jumped over that wall
There are many times when
I just want to run away
But I'm still here, so,
I'm not daunted that much
The poem I scribbled down, I can just
start writing over from the beginning
Unable to write it well, I'm laughing