The festival was wonderful!
Say, Nishimi-san, I'd love to hear you play the piano again!
Let me hear it too!
Would you like a persimmon?
No...
I'm with the photography club!
Let me get a shot!
Stand next to each other, you two!
This is the birth of the legendary duo of East High!
Could you stand closer to each other?
Like this?
Yes!
Hey, when did you two become friends?
Where do you practice?
How do you play in such perfect unison?
Sen, let's get out of here.
You don't have to hide anything from us!
When I count to five, run left.
Tell us!
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
They're escaping again!
Ricchan!
Aw, come on! Where are you going?!
Shit. The girls were supposed to be chasing after us.
Right now, those guys are just like the Beatles!
I've learned from them.
Forget about next year's festival.
I'm looking even further ahead.
I'll go so far
that they'll never be able to catch up.
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
Pops!
Sorry I haven't been coming recently.
Huh? He's not here.
Maybe in the basement?
Sen, what's wrong?
Bon, would you
check to see if Jun-nii's down there?
What are you talking about?
It's not summer vacation, so why would Jun nii-san—
Oh, a lot's happened while you boys weren't around.
But he's not here now. He left last week.
Anyway, I haven't seen you in a long time.
I'm sorry.
I've been waiting for you, Prince Bon.
My piano trio is finally together again!
Junichi was disowned by his father right after he came back this summer.
Disowned?
Well, first he went against his parents' wishes by going to college in Tokyo.
Then he stopped going to school
and got caught up in political activism instead.
When the prodigal son wandered back home,
it's no wonder his dad was furious.
Junichi wasn't allowed to set foot in his family's house.
I ran into him at the bar not long after that, three sheets to the wind,
so I let him take refuge here.
Pops.
Is it my fault Jun-nii left?
No, no.
He happened to find a cheap room to rent.
It's not your fault.
But I...
Sentaro!
Do not mope your life away!
Playing one good session will drive away those blues, right?
Never mind!
Forget I did that!
I get it, Bill Evans-dono, I get it!
Alright!
What do you say we play a session so I can work off this gloominess?!
Junichi-san?
What are you doing here?
Wait!
Don't ignore me!
What made him change this much?
That one winter day in the basement...
What was that?
Did he just do it on a whim?
Even if I knock, he may not open the door.
Or would he look at me again with those vacant eyes?
Sorry, but that doesn't suit you.
You win.
I got a soft spot for that angry face of yours.
You had that same expression when we first met.
I remember it well.
What are you gonna do?
Just go home?
Or...
Mukae-senpai!
Excuse me.
Would you give this to Nishimi-senpai?
Um, wouldn't it be better if you gave it to him yourself?
Oh, I couldn't!
I'd be too nervous!
So please!
You did it!
For me?
It's been a while since the festival, but your popularity hasn't waned, Kaoru-san.
Thanks.
What am I staring at?
Am I jealous?
It has nothing to do with me.
Ricchan!
Hey, which scarf design do you think is better?
Actually, lately there's this guy I kind of like,
and I'm thinking about making one for him.
Who is it?
I can't say yet.
But what about you, Ricchan?
Isn't there someone that you wanna knit for?
Come on, let's knit together!
But I don't have anyone to give it to.
Oh, be honest with yourself, Ricchan.
Just now, you were staring at a certain someone.
It's not what you think.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Yeah, yeah.
Nishimi-san is just a friend, right?
Sorry, I'll be back!
What a beautiful color.
I bet Kaoru-san would look good in this.
Huh? Wait a second.
What's wrong with me?
Why is my heart beating so fast?
That day?
Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot about that.
You wanna know why I did it?
Was it a little too stimulating for you, Princess?
Sorry.
I was just feeling kind of mischievous at the time.
N-No!
What's wrong?
Didn't you come in here because you wanted me to do this?
What were you hoping for?
A declaration of love?
Sorry to disappoint you, Princess.
But this is the kind of guy I am.
You've stopped fighting back.
Have you resigned to it already?
Yes.
"If I act like this, she'll probably run off."
Is that what you're thinking?
I'm not afraid of you.
You can do what you want with me.
Dammit!
Go home and don't ever come back here.
I'm not the same person I was before.
I dropped out of college
and got disowned from my family.
Society gave me the boot, and there's no way for me to get back.
Get close to me, and your life will be ruined too.
If you understand what I'm sayin', get the hell out of here.
What are you doing?
I'm sick of you saying "Princess, Princess,"
so I thought I'd get rid of the
"princess" image you have of me.
If you're not the same person you once were,
then I can become a new person too.
Katsuragi, I'm gonna become a new me.
Don't!
Don't go throwing away
something precious for someone like me.
So you're the Katsuragi-kun I've heard so much about.
How about saying something to mark the occasion?
Me?
I'm just passing through,
but I'd like to share my opinion on what a college should be like.
Katsuragi, you inspired me.
Muroi, you...
Listening to your speech
made me feel ashamed for doing nothing but study for exams and play music.
The Decline of a False
System
Strike
Against
Rising
Tuition
All Students on Strike
Hey, Katsuragi,
in the next battle, if something were to happen to me,
would you take over, even just for a little while?
Arita-san, I...
Hey, Muroi.
Come over once in a while to play the sax.
Katsuragi!
Arita-san's been arrested!
The bones are shattered,
so the doc told me my fingers won't be able to move like they used to.
Wh-What about the sax?
I can't play anymore.
Don't look so glum, Katsuragi.
Now I can dump everything I don't need and just focus on the movement.
I'm gonna become a new me.
What am I doing?
Katsuragi?
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?!
I don't wanna...
...see any more people get hurt because of me.
I don't know what happened to you,
and I don't intend to ask about it.
But I can see that you're deeply hurt.
Can't I support you?
Am I being too pushy?
Yeah.
You're a pushy woman.
Maybe I better stop takin' naps on the roof.
Hey, that was Yurika, wasn't it?
Was she called in by the teacher again?
Yeah. Yurika's been acting weird these days.
She's totally changed.
What happened to that innocence she used to have?
Maybe something happened to her?
I asked her that, but she wouldn't answer.
Well, since she cut her hair like that, could it mean...
...a broken heart?
What the hell happened?
What did he do to her?
So, you're Sentaro, huh?
Do you like jazz?
Ever since I first met Jun-nii, he's been like a big brother to me.
I wanted to get good at jazz like him.
Be strong like him.
Become cool like him.
I always trailed after Jun-nii,
thinking I'd catch up someday.
Hey, Sen-bou...
Your woman forgot something.
If Jun-nii would just talk to me, maybe I'd understand.
But if he did something to her,
I'll...
J-Jun-nii!
I need to talk to...
Son of a...
...bitch!
Shit.
He's the one person I didn't want to find out about this.
But what else could you do?
He was bound to find out sooner or later.
I knew it.
I knew she was beyond my reach from the start.
I knew it. Or I thought I did, but...
I don't understand myself.
Definitely, when I'm with Kaoru-san,
I can really feel at ease and have a good time.
No. I decided long ago on the person that I like...
Hi, Ricchan.
Is Sen here?
Yeah, I think so.
Knitting?
Why would she bother hiding that?
Hey! Sen!
Sen! What happened?!
What do you mean?
You're obviously acting strangely today.
Tell me about it.
I saw 'em.
Saw who?
When I went to Jun-nii's apartment,
she was there.
Y-You're sure you saw...
Yeah.
And of all people, it had to be Jun-nii.
That's what hurts the most.
Anyway, it's over.
There's nothin' I can do.
You've still got it good.
Even though you were jilted, you've still got someone who cares for you.
It's like they say. You can't see the forest for the trees.
And those trees are so tall, you must not be able to see a damn thing.
Why don't you try looking more carefully?
Isn't it high time you realized it?
Wh-What are you talkin' about?
Figure it out for yourself.
I told him.
Kaoru-san?
You just got here, and you're leaving already?
Yeah. I've got something to do.
Are you done knitting for today?
Sorry. I couldn't help seeing it before.
I'm sure he'll like it.
Ricchan, you're blushing!
Was I right?
Well, see you tomorrow.
Wait a min...
I'm sure this is for the best.
Don't have a relapse!
This doesn't hurt at all!
I won't have it!
You and this man from who knows where...
Yurika, you're being tricked.
What do you know, Father?
Shut your mouth!
I'll bring home a suitable partner for you before long.
So don't meet with this man again, Yurika.
Do you understand?
Yurika, your father is just talking to you like that
because he's worried about you!
You're a girl, so you have to take better care of yourself.
Just in case, keep next Saturday open, okay?
I made an appointment for you with the gynecologist.
Are you eating properly?
A letter came for you,
so I'm forwarding it on.
Love, Mom
To:My Comrade
From:Isao Arita
Bon, that rat...
He throws out hints and then goes home.
Someone who cares for me?
Like my family?
Is that what he meant?
So you're gonna be the Virgin Mary
in the Christmas Nativity play, huh, Sa-chan?
Yeah.
But I'm nervous about it.
Hashiguchi-kun will be there to see you too,
so you have to do your best, right?
D-Don't mention him!
I don't care if he...
Nee-chan, you're the one who said you're gonna marry him when you grow up!
What?! That was a long time ago!
Hey...
Sentaro, I...
When I grow up, I wanna be your...
Isn't it high time you realized it?
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.