It's summer...
I wanna die.
Don't be so depressed, Tooru.
Since it's summer already, let's go to the beach! Right?
I don't want people to see my underdeveloped body.
Honestly! You worry too much.
Everyone is different,
so just emphasise what you have.
Run-chan...
It's popular amongst certain types of people.
That part was unnecessary.
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Ta-daa!
I went and bought a swimsuit for you, Tooru!
I chose the smallest size available,
so let's go to the beach!
Here you go!
I'm totally sure it'll look great on you.
Hey, why don't you try it on?
All right.
Isn't it great?
But this is a bit...
...loose...
Sorry for the intrusion!
I bought some ice-cream...
What?
Tooru! It's ice-cream!
I'm not gonna join in right now.
Hey Tooru, what's up?
Well, it's because...
Hey, this ice-cream just came out this year, right?
I've been wanting to try it!
Me too. That's why I bought it.
What a coincidence.
Let's split it in half.
Yep!
Actually, I'll join in!
Why-
Why are you naked?
Beach
It's the pool!
You got changed real fast!
Honestly...
Getting so excited over the pool, even at this age.
You're so carefree, Yutaka.
What are you talking about?
Summer is meant for going to the pool!
Have you forgotten this is a class?
The pool is the pool!
Eh? Toorun, the colour of your swimming costume is a little faded except for right here.
Is it a hand-me-down?
This is...
...what I used to wear when I was in elementary school.
Honestly! That's dangerous!
It feels great to float along like this.
You've got big boobs, Yutaka...
Is that right?
It must be easy to swim with all that fat helping you float, huh?
Those are harsh words. Are you jealous or something?
No way-
Absolutely no fat!
So hot!
P.E. class is really tough during the summer!
The first years are having lessons by the pool.
Ah, it's Tooru!
So it is!
The pool would be really refreshing, wouldn't it?
All right! Meet here!
That looks nice.
I'm jealous.
What's up, Nagi?
Don't you hate the pool?
I hate the pool.
Actually, I hate wearing a swimsuit.
However...
Tooru!
Splash water over me! Get a bucket and soak me!
The heat's gone to Nagi's head!
Stop it, Nagi!
Let me go! Let me go! Tooru!
Oh well.
Eh? The beach?
Yep.
Summer vacation starts next week, so let's all go!
I approve!
I don't have a swimsuit that I can wear at the beach.
I don't want to wear a swimsuit.
What are the two of you saying?
You don't need to worry about that!
W-What?
Did you hear that?
Just because she's got a nice body...
And she's so fair-skinned!
Honestly... What are you talking about?
That's not true!
Aww... How modest!
Honestly...
I want to go to the beach with all of you!
Thank you for your business!
It's hot walking all over like this.
Sorry for making you come with me.
No... I bought some things too.
Why don't we have a rest somewhere?
Eh?
Nagi?
What's the matter?
Are you not feeling well?
There's a pocket of cool air here... It's refreshing!
I'm gonna rest here.
Hey, Nagi! Stand up! Come on!
That girl was huge!
Doesn't she look taller than 170cm?
So I'm thought of as a tall girl, after all.
They're just jealous.
You're so slender, tall, large-breasted.
You didn't need to mention my breasts.
They're actually a bit troublesome.
Really?
These bras are nice!
They're so cheap... Let's buy some!
They really are!
I want some too.
What's the problem?
On This Display
Only sizes B~D
Lingerie
They only have sizes up to D.
On This Display
Only sizes B~D
Sometimes it really is more convenient to have a smaller chest.
Let's go home already.
Hey, can I check that out?
Why? I already told you I'm not going to the beach.
Don't worry. It's cute.
I'm not gonna buy anything.
Nagi.
What do you think of this?
It's nice, isn't it?
Really?
All right, I'm going to try it on, so take a look!
Sure.
How is it?
It looks amazing.
Really? Then...
How about this one?
It looks great.
All right...
How about this one?
It looks awesome.
I can't decide...
I'm gonna look at a few others.
Just wait there for a sec.
Sure.
All right!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Nagi!
Eh?
Don't get the wrong idea!
This is... um...
I was just having a look...
I'll try it on.
All right!
I ended up buying it...
Yeah, it looks great on you!
Thanks.
Oh yeah...
Sending a message?
Yep.
I'm gonna invite Run and Tooru to the beach!
Eh?
It'll be fun!
Just 2 more kilos...
There's no way.
Ah, Run said they'll go!
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Run-chan came here earlier.
She already left?
Yep.
She was just dropping something off for you.
This is a swimsuit that I used to use.
I think it'll be perfect for you, Tooru!
I'll race you to that island, Tooru!
Play lots, study lots, and I look forward to seeing all of your energetic faces in the new semester.
Wait!
The ocean! The ocean! The ocean! The ocean! The ocean!
Is she a child?
The ocean!
Isn't it pretty?
We're going down a road.
It's turned into a streetcar.
It really has.
Amazing, we're going down the street.
I wonder when they put them on?
Eh? Put what on?
The tires, of course.
There aren't tires.
We're here! The beach!
I'm gonna swim!
Coming to the beach sure is exciting!
Me too!
Run-chan.
Thanks for lending me a swimsuit.
I'm glad it fits you. Sorry it looks kind of childish.
It's fine.
I mean, it's from when I was in elementary school.
Hey! What are you doing? Hurry up!
All right!
Elementary school.
Take that!
Now you've done it!
Hey, that tickles!
You're so high!
What are you doing?!
That looks fun, Tooru!
Let me go!
Tooru?! Nagi?!
What's on your head?!
What?
Seaweed.
It looks good on you, Nagi!
Looks good on you!
Seaweed.
I need a break.
What's wrong, Nagi? You're already worn out?
I got up at 5am this morning.
I don't have any energy left.
I'm still doing fine.
Well, I'm weak.
Then let's rest a bit. I'll go buy some juice.
All right, I'd like some melon soda.
Sure.
Get me a sports drink.
OK.
She's really worn out.
Welcome!
There are a lot of them, huh?
Which should we get?
Run-chan, look at that.
Super
Sweet
Candy
Juice
Super
Sweet
Candy
Juice
Ooh!
I can't believe we'd find the mythical candy juice at a place like this!
Yeah.
I got it for you, Nagi.
Thanks.
Hm?
Yuuko is asleep.
She really is.
Honestly, she was just going on about how she was doing fine, but look what happened once she sat down.
That looks like it feels good.
That's it!
Hm?
Ah, this feels really nice.
There's nobody around, and it's so quiet.
Tropical islands are wonderful!
Hm?
Eh? Wh-What?
Leaves?
Hey, what are you doing, Tooru, that tickl-
You're heavy!
Huh? A... A dream?
Was I asleep?
A... A castle!?
Noo!
Don't move. We're almost finished.
Hurry and get this off me!
There!
Attack!
Got it!
Sorry!
Don't worry!
What's up?
It feels like I'm being pulled! It's fun!
Is that fun?
Eh? Nagi?
Me, too!
Lunchtime!
You've gotta have ramen at the beach!
Yakisoba.
Tropical octopus rice.
I brought my own lunch.
That's the same as always.
Really?
Don't worry! Leave it to me!
Eh? What are you gonna do?
I mean, it's the beach! The beach!
Fish!
donna keshiki kiitai shiteru?
どんな景色　期待してる？
What kind of scenery are you expecting?
hora mietekita suiheisen
ほら見えてきた水平線
Look, you can see the horizon on the ocean.
atsui suna ni kokoro haneru
熱い砂にココロ跳ねる
Leap onto the hot sand with all your heart.
mabataki no tabi utsuru taiyou
まばたきの度　写る太陽
The sun is in your eyes every time you blink.
hashagi kirenai kimochi kakureteta mitai
はしゃぎきれない気持ち　隠れてたみたい
Feelings of not having enough fun were hidden.
miseta koto no nai jibun hashiridasu yo
見せたことのない自分　走り出すよ
A never before seen version of you will start running.
mune ni Blue Sky nami wo kakete
胸に Blue Sky 波を駆けて
The blue sky in your chest, racing along the waves.
hajikeru feeling
はじけるフィーリング
It's a feeling that can't be contained.
yukou Sisters mizugi no ato
Let's go, sisters, after the swimsuits.
There's not many people left, huh?
Well, it's already sunset.
kokoro tsunagu
Connect our hearts.
It feels like we played a ton.
takusan no kirameki de
Let's use a lot of sparkles
I'm glad we got up early this morning.
Right?
Wasn't it fun coming to the beach?
niji wo egakou
To create a rainbow.
Yeah.
Well, it was fun.
Let's all come again some time, all right?
Yeah.
Hurry, Yuuko.
W-Wait up!
Hurry, hurry!
We made it.
It's completely empty, huh?
Yuuko, aren't you gonna sit down?
Ah, no, I'm fine here.
It'll be a while before we get there.
Well, I've still got lots of energy left.
Are you all right, Yuuko?
Yeah, it seems so.
Cuticles!
Eh?
Are your cuticles all right, Yuuko?
You can't see them.
I bet they're fine.
Your hair is so long and pretty, so you have to take care.
And your skin is so fair.
Uh, thanks.
Oh yeah, I wonder if I got sunburned.
No, don't worry about it. You put on sunblock.
I see. What about you, Run?
Not burned at all.
Run, what did you use for sunblock?
I didn't.
How is your skin like this if you didn't use sunblock?
Unbelievable.
That tickles!
My skin just doesn't burn.
Really?
Are you an alien?
Eh?! No!
Run-chan is an Earthling.
Really?
Really!
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
Why do you get so tired after swimming?
Especially in the afternoon after a swimming class.
That's the start of something terrifying.
What do you mean?
If you sleep in the afternoon, then you can't sleep that night.
But then if you don't sleep at night, you get tired again in the afternoon!
Ah, that's true.
Next time, on A-Channel:
Next Time!
A midsummer
night's...
A midsummer night's...
At times like that, if you just sleep from the afternoon until the next morning, it's solved!
How many hours do you sleep?