This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki.
She's twelve and dreams of becoming a singer.
But unfortunately, she only has
one year left to live.
We, the Shinigami, were sent to make sure that her destiny did not change, but...
Today, she became an adult...
...and she performed incredibly at the audition.
Doesn't this mean we're  changing her destiny!?
Well, then...
I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
Be sure to watch TV in a well-lit room
and a safe distance away.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Full Moon wo Sagashite
Original Subtitles by a.f.k.
Searching for a Full Moon
Toosugiru koi no michishirube
To
The road to love is far too long for me.
Mou suki wo fuyasenai Non Non
Mo
There's no way for me to love you any more. Nope! Nope!
Yume no naka wa maru de betsu sekai
Yu
It's as if the world inside my dream is a completely different one
Sutoreeto ni omoi mo ieru no ni
Su
where I can even tell you how I really feel.
Okiniiri no fuku wo mainichi kichau no
I wear my favorite clothes every day
Ano hito no mesen ga kocchi ni chiratsuitekimasu you ni
so that person will turn his gaze towards me.
I LIKE YOU no kotoba nara ieru
"I like you!" If I could bring myself to say it out loud
Renai soudan suru koto mo dekiru
I would even be able to talk about love with you.
Anata no haato ni tsutsumaretai no ni
I want to be tucked into your heart
Doushitara tsutsunde kureru no
and I will do anything to be there.
I bU wo anata kara kikitai
"I love you!" Those are the words I want to hear from you
Kisu suru shunkan no chikai kokyuu wo
and my breath will quicken when we kiss.
Anata wo mane suru atashi wa ichiban kawaiku naru hazu
A
The me who is performing for you is the cutest of them all!
Transcribed by Steve
Editing, TLC: Zalis (ReDone-Subs)
Retiming, Encoding: E_B (Soldado)
Typesetting, KFX: shani-san and E_B (Soldado)
QC: Yogicat, E_B
THE PROMISE WITH EICHI-KUN
This is your  fault, Takuto!
Didn't that girl pass the audition!?
Man... I was surprised, too.
I never thought she'd get chosen.
Don't act like it's someone else's problem!
Stop being so shrill, Meroko.
Don't tell me you've forgotten what our purpose here is?
To make sure that nothing changes
the fact that she has one year left to live, right?
Exactly!
Then why should it matter...
...if she passed the audition or not?
Ah! I see...
...not!
She was willing to return to the house with us.
Now that she's become a singer,
it'll be a pain if we have to follow her around.
Plus, you used the Dead Arts on a human like her...
...and even turned her into a 16-year-old!
I won't forgive you for a stunt like this!
What's so funny?
I was just thinking that you Shinigami seem to be so close.
Huh?
I-Is that how it looks?
Well, after all...
We are the Shinigami Duo
who silence the tears of children.
...Negi Ramen!
I'm really grateful for everything.
Huh? Oh... it was nothing.
What is this!? Why am I the only one doing it!?
By the way, what was that song you sang...
Full Moon wo sagashite
...and find the full moon.
...at your audition?
Let's sing a song!
My father was a musician,
and that was one of his songs.
itsu demo issho kimi no tame-
Together, forever! I'm doin-
Really...
Hmm...
Is something wrong?
I feel like I might have heard it before...
Hold it!
Don't think that you've become an adult just because you passed the audition!
W-When I'm in this body, I'm all grown up!
Hmm... so then...
Meroko! Stop harassing her!
Oh, but I can't go home like this.
Can you turn me back to normal?
Huh? Oh yeah. Of course.
Amazing! I turned back to normal.
Yep. Your chest returned to normal, too.
P-Please don't stare at me like that.
Geez... you're so stingy.
Hey...
Do you really plan on becoming a singer?
Yeah.
I promised, after all.
Promised?
My promise with... Eichi-kun...
Eichi-kun? Wait, who is that!?
Your sweetheart?
What!?
H-He's not my sweetheart...
...yet.
So that means he's somebody you admire?
Until two years ago,
I was living at an orphanage.
I was with Eichi-kun the whole time, until Grandma took me in.
He told me his feelings,
but before I could answer...
...he left for America because of
circumstances beyond our control.
No, no! Don't go, Eichi-kun!
Don't cry, Mitsuki. America isn't that far away.
But...
Let's make a promise.
Until we meet again,
we'll work hard to reach our dreams.
I'll become an astronomer.
And you'll become a singer.
Mitsuki...
...I love you.
Even though we'll be apart,
I'll look for the moon in the sky.
That's why you have to shine even brighter...
...so that I can find you sooner.
More... and more...
And since then?
Since then?
Haven't you had any contact with him since then?
Like a letter, or a phone call?
Well, that's the problem. I have no idea
how to get in touch with him.
I see...
But if I accomplish my dream
of becoming a singer...
...my name might even reach
somewhere as far as America.
Then I'm sure...
...that Eichi-kun will notice me... maybe.
You've put your whole heart into this, huh?
Somewhat, I guess.
What is it, Takuto?
You're making such a frightening face.
Scary...
What are you?
I thought you honestly wanted to become a singer...
...but it was all for a guy!
That's just impure!
If you don't have pure intentions of becoming a singer, you can't become a good one!
You'd better quit singing immediately!
W-Why are you saying something like that?
That's right.
What's so wrong with doing it because of a guy?
Everything!
Huh?
I'll... work really hard at singing, so...
No matter how hard you work, you'll always be irresponsible about it on some level.
That can't be...
I would never be irresponsible about singing.
That's right! What part of this is impure!?
What part of doing it for a guy is  pure!?
Besides, doesn't it seem strange
that he's neglected you for two years?
You've been dumped.
He's probably living it up
with another girl over there already.
E-Eichi-kun wouldn't ever do something like that!
Why can't you understand that?
That's because... it's Eichi-kun, after all!
Hmph. That's foolish.
Hey! Cut it out, Takuto!
Anyway, I won't ever cooperate with someone like you again.
Because you don't respect singing!
W-Wait... Takuto. Takuto!
Come on, Takuto!
Geez... why's he so mad?
More importantly...
...what kind of person would interfere with fate?
The one most likely to interfere
with someone's fate...
...is the person that human loves.
I'll have to pay special attention to this "Eichi" character.
Just what were you thinking?
When I told you that you shouldn't audition,
I wasn't trying to be mean.
It's impossible because of
your body's current condition.
Are you finished now?
Sorry...
But now you understand, don't you?
That you'll be unable to sing for the time being.
Ah... no, I made it.
Made it?
What should I do?
I can't tell him what really happened.
But I wonder if he would believe that I transformed...
...or about the Shinigami.
What do you mean by "made it"?
It couldn't be that... you passed the audition?
Um, well...
It's no good. There's no way he'd ever believe it!
Um... I meant modeling.
Oh... modeling, huh?
Well, modeling is all well and good, but don't do anything irrational.
O-Okay!
By the way, what'd you do for the application?
Did you write your grandma's name
under "Guardian"?
Um, actually...
Did you put my  name down?
F-Forgive me!
It's fine, it's fine.
We'll keep it a secret from your grandma, okay?
I-Is that all right?
Sure. I understand your feelings, after all.
It's for Eichi-kun, right?
Y-Yep!
Kouyama
Sneaking out of the house without saying a word is simply improper.
What's more, you had your doctor
take you to the amusement park.
Your disobedience knows no bounds!
An amusement park? So that's where we were?
Thank you, Doctor.
Do you understand?
I'm very sorry.
Next time, a simple apology will not suffice.
Yes.
That's enough.
Please excuse yourself.
Yes.
Wait a minute. What is that?
What is  that?
T-This is...
From... um... the crane game.
Is that so?
E-Excuse me.
What a shrill old hag. I was worried she'd tell you to throw me away.
But this means that you're one step closer to your dream, right?
Yeah.
So, what kind of guy is Eichi-kun?
If you've got a picture, you've gotta show me!
O-Okay.
Wow! He's a pretty good-looking guy.
How old is he?
We're six years apart, so he'd be eighteen now.
So this picture was taken
when Eichi-kun was sixteen?
Sooo cute.
Besides, doesn't it seem strange
that he's neglected you for two years?
You've been dumped.
Eichi-kun's...
Eichi-kun's the only one who wouldn't...
So this is where you were?
Leave me alone.
Well, that means I have nowhere left to go.
That girl looks like she wants to be alone, too.
You upset her...
Eichi-kun...
It's all your fault, you know.
Huh?
She's down because you told her
that she'd been dumped.
Well, it's a perfectly natural assumption. Isn't it?
Besides, in this day and age, it's weird to carry a torch for a guy who's already dumped you!
It's weird, indeed.
Right?
Just like randomly busting out the Dead Arts.
The old Takuto never would've done that.
Do you like her?
S-Stupid. It's nothing like that!
I-Isn't this our duty?
Sure, I may have "assumed" she was dumped.
It's just that in general, long-distance relationships tend not to work...
Just as I thought... something's amiss.
Usually, in situations like this...
Takuto is mine!
Here you go!
Fortune telling?
Yep. I'll read your fortune for today. Pick a card.
Okay. Um, how about...
Which one is it?
Wow! That's great! Today's your lucky day.
That's lucky?
Yep. Super lucky.
The lucky word is... shopping!
Something good will definitely happen.
Come on, let's go out.
Sure!
Grandma's out today, too.
Ah, but I have to ask Tanaka-san.
Do you need something, Mitsuki-chan?
Um, I'd like to go out shopping...
But Madam said that...
I wonder what Grandma would say
if she learned that you...
...were secretly listening to music?
You might be scolded.
Shall we go?
Where are they going?
If Meroko's going along,
then I'll just let her handle things.
Wow...
Mitsuki-chan, this might take awhile.
Can you wait at the usual place?
Sure. I understand.
Then... then... just wait a little while, please!
Hey, hey.
There's somewhere I want to go, too.
Um, this might take awhile,
so can you wait outside?
I got it.
Shinigami use the restroom too, huh?
She left, right?
She should've known I'd have a reason for suggesting this little excursion.
Mero-Mero Change!
It's mine! It's mine, I say!
I wonder what that "good thing" is.
That guy is...
It's been a while, Mitsuki-chan.
E...
Eichi-kun?
Yep.
It's him!?
T-This can't be real.
Oh, it's real.
A real lie, that is.
Once your wish to see Eichi-kun is granted,
you won't need to become a singer anymore.
Plus, once your true love is on the scene,
Takuto will give up on you, too.
I-I'm dreaming, aren't I?
This is no dream.
Even though I went to America,
I never forgot about you, Mitsuki-chan.
That's why I hurried back to Japan
once I heard you'd become a singer.
But who told you that I'd become a singer?
Who told me, you ask? It was
s-someone I know in the record business.
That's an amazing coincidence.
It was more than a coincidence; it was fate.
Fate...
By the way, Eichi-kun... what's with that voice?
I guess living in America must've changed my voice.
Since America's so vast, right?
You're so funny.
R-Really?
W-What is it this time?
There's something I have to apologize to you for, Eichi-kun.
Eichi-kun, I... doubted you.
I thought you might have forgotten about me.
What? That's all?
I'm very sorry.
Mitsuki-chan...
Will you still... like me?
O-Of course.
I'm so glad.
Back then, I couldn't give you a proper answer, so...
Now...
I'm also... in...
I-
I'm... I'm... I'm sorry!
Eichi-kun? Where are you going?
Shinigami-san.
That isn't Eichi. It's Meroko.
You're kidding.
No, I'm not.
We Shinigami are able to transform.
Is... that so?
That's right.
There's no way Eichi-kun... would be here, right?
Sorry for the wait!
Is something wrong, Mitsuki-chan?
No. There's nothing wrong.
Your face looks pale. Come on, let's go home.
That was horrible! You've really done it now!
It seemed like a good idea at the time...
What was so "good" about it!?
You were just toying with
a person's sincere ambitions...
...and their pure feelings!
I'm sorry...
You think an apology will solve this?
Wait.
Huh?
"Pure"... didn't you just say that they were impure?
Huh? I said that?
You did!
"What part of doing it for a guy is  pure?"
...or something like that.
That... was about becoming a singer.
Those issues have nothing to do with each other!
Really?
I guess what I did was  pretty cruel...
But you don't even know  Eichi,
and yet you said he dumped her.
What about you, Takuto?
Don't you think that your words hurt her?
Um...
That stuff I said about you being dumped was just my own opinion. Or rather...
It's just a possibility. No... that's...
[ Children's Illustrated Guide to Space ]
I'm sorry.
No. I was also at fault.
If I really believed in Eichi-kun...
...I wouldn't be worried,
no matter what anybody told me.
That's why I won't be confused anymore.
I... love Eichi-kun!
But I love singing just as much!
If I love him, then I have to believe in him!
I have to believe in him with all my heart,
or else my dream will never come true!
These feelings will never be impure!
Well, that settles it.
Accomplish as much as you can.
I'll work to fulfill your dream over the next year.
Will you?
As long as I'm around,
my blood will always be inside you, so...
...I'll always be able to transform you.
When I'm not with you,
use this whistle to call me. I'll fly to you.
Thank you, Shinigami-san!
Enough with the "Shinigami-san". Call me Takuto.
Okay. Thank you, Takuto.
For what?
Could it be that my trick has backfired on me?
Ah, Bunny!
I wanted to thank you.
T-Thank me?
Yep.
Because today was really my lucky day!
You changed into Eichi-kun...
...to give me courage, right?
I'm really sorry!
Why did the bunny apologize?
Who knows?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'll never do it again!
Eichi-kun, I made it through the audition.
I'll definitely go see you, okay?
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's just one thing that's never gonna change:
Zutto egaiteta yume
Zu
The dream that I have always been drawing.
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
I
How would I, as I am right now
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
A
look to those small eyes I used to have?
no
ko
ro
no
chii
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, won't you look up? The night sky stretches so far.
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
So
Yes... very soon... you will understand...
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
Se
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up...
Full Moon wo sagashite
Full
...and find the full moon.
Moon
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
I
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now.
tsu
de
mo
i
ssho
Day by Day
Day
by
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
Kyo
I hold the fate dealt by the past and the hopes of tomorrow in my heart.
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
I
Together, forever! As long as I'm with you, I can overcome any pain.
tsu
de
mo
i
ssho
More and more
More
and
more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
Mo
More and more and more... to be closer to you, I stand here now and give...
Many Thanks for You!
Many
Thanks
for
You!
PREVIEW FOR NEXT TIME
Takuto! There's an emergency... an emergency!
Her manager is coming to meet her!
You can't mean that...
That's right!
Mitsuki's established Dr. Wakaouji as her guardian.
Wait... that physician only knows her as a 12-year-old.
But the manager's expecting to meet her
as a 16-year-old, isn't she?
What are we going to do, Takuto!?
Ahhhhh... I don't know anymore!
Whatever happens, happens!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
THE MANAGER ARRIVES
The Manager Arrives.
Look forward to it!