Elen...
What is it?
Well...
I wanted to see the reaction on your face when I called you by that name.
You found him, didn't you...
Where's Scythe?
Finale
Yes. Thank you for having someone come pick us up, Colonel Roshnenko.
No problem. I feel honored that you remembered my name, Dr. Giuseppe.
Being called by that name reminds me of my time in Moscow.
At any rate, to think that a sharp man like yourself
was driven into a difficult situation and is on the run...
So you found fieldwork different from lab work?
"There is a tide in the affairs of men."
What?
A quote from Shakespeare.
Their tide is also my tide.
What I had to create here...
I've already created it.
There's something suspicious going on
around a puny arms dealer named Roshnenko.
Looks like he's Scythe's acquaintance.
The Bay Area here in San Francisco is his current turf.
Scythe was seen headed this way as well.
In short, that snake is trying to make his escape
from somewhere in San Francisco harbor.
Clo?
You...!
Don't you get it, Clo?!
He helped Phantom, who pointed her gun at us, escape!
Even so, you're still telling me to take him with me?!
Yes, that's right.
Geez... You really are a tough bird.
Same goes for you.
But I'll be the commander at the site, okay?
The place Scythe is headed is...
the Woodland Wharf in the East Bay.
I heard that several of Roshnenko's henchmen were seen there.
Got it.
Come!
Kill him without fail.
If you do that...
I, too, regret that we couldn't secure Zwei.
But considering the current situation, we can't help it.
I'll give him to that vixen.
Master... Why are you...
Since when did you start asking questions?
I'm... sorry.
What's the matter, comrade Roshnenko?
I see...
So they figured it out.
Yes, please don't worry.
I'll have my own staff entertain those who are coming to see me off.
You'll assist me? Thank you very much.
Well then, I'll see you later.
Sounds like he's trying to make me owe him with just a few men.
Ein...
Can you still live up to my expectations... Ein?
Use this.
This is a suitable prop to grace tonight's stage.
There's two spare magazines.
As you know, it requires delicate handling.
Avoid firing repeatedly as much as possible.
Okay.
Do it with discretion. This will be your last job.
Ms. Garland will be arriving at the dock shortly.
I'm sure she will do fine.
I heard that you sent Zwei in as well.
Yes.
He betrayed Inferno once.
If the result turns out to be harmful to the organization,
I'll accept full responsibility.
You trust Zwei that much?
If I am to trust something,
it would be his newfound urge to kill someone of his own free will
after he's been killing on missions.
To be honest, I'm still not sure...
if it's really okay to let you run free with a gun in your hand.
That's understandable.
I've got one bullet in the chamber and 15 in the magazine.
Even after killing everyone here, I'll still have some left.
What?!
What's the meaning of this?
I can't take on all you guys with just one bullet.
But that'll be enough to kill Scythe.
You sure talk tough, kid.
It's better than being shot in the back by you.
Up there!
That damn snake!
Hey! Wait!
Scythe... Where are you?!
I won't let you get away, you traitor!
I don't know if you're No. 1 or No. 2...
but how dare you use us like pawns.
Because of you, my older brother was...!
Even if those big shots forgive you, I'll never...
forgive you!
Elen...
Let's go back. It's not too late yet.
Please... Come with me.
Scythe!
Ein...
I see... Good job, Zwei.
I had the feeling that you could eventually surpass Ein, but...
No wonder that vixen wants you.
Not only did you attain perfection in a short time,
but I never thought that you would also use Ein as a steppingstone.
A stepping stone?
I think you know what I mean the best.
Please... don't... do it.
You don't have to worry.
If I kill him, Inferno will let you off the hook.
So, come with me.
Elen...
Ein. Kill Zwei.
Once you are able to do that, you'll be my Ein.
Let's go, Ein.
You moron!
You acted all heroic and this is how you end up?
How did you guys do?
We took care of most of them.
We took a lot of hits too, but as you can see I'm fine.
Get up.
You are going to kill Scythe, right?
They called me and said that they'd bring the boat to pier 5.
That's on the northeastern edge.
Yes.
Scythe!
Hey, you damn snake! Go ahead and shoot!
Hold her back. I'm going on ahead.
Understood.
Roshnenko's...!
Master...
Scythe!
An interesting outcome.
Suitable for the finale.
Elen...
What is it?
I wanted to see the reaction on your face when I called you by that name.
I wonder if people normally smile in this kind of situation.
Sorry...
I'll make you smile someday.
I'm sure you can go back.
You smile when you're happy and you cry when you're sad.
You can go back to being an ordinary girl like that.
An ordinary...
So... please stay alive until that happens, Elen.
I'll definitely protect you, so...
Elen...
The promise... I made...
Your... smile...
Succession
Next episode
I lost everything.
What's left to me...
is the title of a killer...
Phantom.