"Early summer, 1958"
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga, Chandy10
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10, Kanra
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
That's the stuff!
You really got busted up again.
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
You get beat up by gorilla-like
wrestlers every time you go out there.
Isn't that tough on you?
It was, at first.
But things have changed recently.
The ring, and all those bright lights...
The energy I get
from the crowd's cheers...
I don't like fighting or
feeling pain, of course.
But, for whatever reason
if feels great to be inside the ring!
I'm gonna get even better at
it and become a main-eventer!
I see.
In that case,
you should thank Mr. Arito
for introducing you to pro wrestling!
Yeah! That's for sure!
Welcome!
Jeffrey...
"The next day"
Hey!
You came back as you promised!
Hey, Jimmy!
This is the guy! Mario Minakami!
What's going on?
Why'd you call me here!?
Hey!
Does anyone here speak Japanese!?
I'm Jimmy Brown.
You speak Japanese?
Glove up and get into the ring.
Good! Now your right!
I said right!
I've raised many champions in my time.
I can tell a lot about boxers.
I can tell that you've
been training non-stop
and that you have
great potential as a boxer.
--However...
--I know.
Even I know I can't box
with this busted right of mine...
I guess it's time I throw in the towel.
You've gone through
a lot of trouble for me.
Thank you, Jeffrey.
"I want to stand inside a heavily-lit
ring and fight one more time..."
Holding on to this wish,
Mario had continued his futile training.
His heart was like dynamite
that hadn't fully combusted.
Anchan...
What should I start running towards?
--See you around.
--If...
If your right hand could be fixed,
what would you do, Mario Minakami?
My hand can be fixed..?
I can't guarantee it,
but I do know a good doctor.
If you really want to continue boxing,
I can introduce you to him.
"Closed"
What!? Surgery!?
Yeah. It'll give me another shot at boxing.
But can we really trust this doctor of his?
He's a top-notch doctor
back from America.
He's helped a lot of boxers with
busted hands get back in the ring.
That's great. You, a boxer...
So it all depends on this doctor...
"Several days later"
"Right hand was broken three
years ago and left unchecked.
Grip in the hand has
remained weak ever since..."
--Is this correct?
--Yes.
In any case, let's take a look.
"Examination Room"
I'll get right to the point.
Unfortunately, I can't
recommend this operation.
The risk is too great.
To be frank, I've never repaired a
hand in such a terrible condition before.
I'm honestly amazed you've
even been able to use it at all.
--C'mon, old man! Do something!
--Can you or can't you operate on him!?
The chance of a full recovery is only 30%.
No, maybe even lower than that...
If the operation fails, it could
hinder your daily life as well.
Don't think about chance!
A small chance is more than enough.
We have nothing to lose, after all.
Even 1% would be enough for me.
Huh?
Please give me the operation!
Hey! What are you doing!?
Just go. We'll handle the rest.
What are you guys thinking!?
Don't you have somewhere to be, anyway?
--Yeah! You need to go tell him!
--Yeah!
Well, all right...
This is all there is for now. We'll take
the responsibility of paying the rest.
But we won't pay a
single yen if you mess up!
That's right! You better succeed!
We won't sit by quietly if you fail...
I'll have to eat all your lunches..!
Tell me...
Does he really love boxing that much?
Umm... That's a good question...
--I'm not sure...
--Does he like it that much?
I can't remember...
You gotta be kidding me...
Still, Doctor..!
We don't really know, but
there's one thing we can say...
He's serious.
Serious about making
"his" dream come true!
Man, I don't know if he's
simpleminded or just good-natured,
but once he gets fixated on an idea,
there's no stopping him!
Yeah! He even carved "that everyone's
dreams come true" in that tree!
He's definitely got a one-track mind!
So we can't let his
operation be a failure!
I can tell you're just as
serious about this as he is.
All right! I promise that
I will do my utmost for him!
All right!
Anchan... I'm going to give it another shot...
I will make your dream come true...
Are you..?
Tell me, are you...
Time certainly flies.
It's already been two and a half
years since he passed away.
Yes.
I had always wanted to meet you.
Huh?
You're that one who came to visit
his grave once every month
on the date of his death, right?
Thank you so very much.
Anchan-- Rokurouta-- did a lot for us.
I came today to tell Anchan something.
--Oh, you're a boxer too?
--Yes.
In fact, Anchan taught me how to box!
He certainly loved boxing.
I don't know if he was joking or serious
but he always said his dream
was to become the world champion
and make things easier for me...
Oh, yes!
Just a moment, okay?
Okay...
Use these.
Huh?
They're a memento of his.
In the end, he never got the chance
to put these on and step into a ring...
--I can't accept this...
--No.
I'm sure Rokurouta would be
happy if you used them too.
--I think Anchan was serious.
--Huh?
He told us too that he was
going to be the world champion
and make life easier for his mother.
So... I think he felt that way
from the bottom of his heart.
I would be glad to use these shoes.
"Hospital"
It might take a while,
but just you wait, Anchan!
"Operation underway"
I will step into a professional ring!
In the red corner, Masahiro Doi wins!
Mario's bout is up next...
This is it...
He can throw right punches now, right!?
The operation was a success.
The question now is if he
can use it in a real fight or not...
Let's go, Mario.
And now for the
fourth lightweight bout!
In the blue corner, from the
Kaneda Boxing Association,
Mario Minakami!
Huh? That's Mario, right?
Y-Yeah...
I almost thought it was Anchan...
He looks even more like him now...
Listen, Mario. No matter how
hard he hits or how tired you get,
always keep your eyes on your
opponent, never on the canvas.
I know, Jimmy.
Seconds, out!
Anchan... I've finally made it this far.
This is the ring you wanted to stand in...
The ring you would've stood in...
A professional ring!
Here I go, Anchan!
What are you doing, Mario!?
Don't tell me he's nervous!
That's not like him!
Fight back, Mario!
Oh no!
Mario! A right! Throw a right!
Ol' Mario looks like he's having fun.
See for yourself.
He's smiling...
Go, Mario!
You little--!
--He stopped him in his tracks!
--All right!
--And now's his chance to...
--Throw a right!
--He did it...
--He threw a right punch...
Way to go, Mario!
It looks he's going to be all right.
Huh?
Even after a complete recovery,
most people can't shake their fear
enough to hit with all their might.
But it looks like there was
no need to worry in his case.
Of course there wasn't!
Mario worked really hard, after all!
He quit drinking and smoking
and endured day after day of tough training!
Right, Mario!?
--All right, Mario!
--Turn him into mincemeat!
Did you watch, Anchan?
"World champ"
Were you happy for me?
A lot's happened since you died
but everyone's trying their hardest.
"Famous Singer"
Joe managed to find his sister!
Her name's Meg, and
she's really nice and pretty!
Joe hasn't given up on
being a singer, either.
He only plays small gigs at
American bases right now,
but he'll get his chance
to stand on a big stage someday.
"Eat lots of good food"
And Cabbage! Talk about a surprise!
Guess what he is now! A pro wrestler!
He hates fighting so much, but now
he's a wrestler! Hilarious, isn't it?
"Millionaire"
Scam went through some tough
times after falling for his first woman,
but now's he's studying hard to become a lawyer.
"Be surrounded by girls"
And Turtle...
That idiot worried us after
he got sick, but he's fine now!
'Cafe"
He got out of the black market
and is a moneylender now.
He's making a lot, too.
He's a natural-born businessman.
"Self-Defense Force soldier"
And Soldier...
He was always focused on joining the SDF,
and that unwavering
determination and strong will
have truly made him into a great soldier!
Anyway, everyone's doing well,
so there's nothing to worry about.
What about you?
What have you been doing, Mario?
"That everyone's dreams come true"
Me? Isn't it obvious what my dream is?
I'm going to make your dream come true!
Carrying great and profound friendship,
the survivors of Block 2,
Cell 6 followed down their own paths.
Muddy roads, steep paths,
roundabout ways...
They weren't afraid of any of these.
What kept them going on
the long paths to their goals
was their strong will and
the words Anchan left them...
What is life, without happiness?
End
same ta manazashi
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it; its now
a far off distance