Under Construction
We appreciate your cooperation
Do Not
Snake Constrictor
Cut 3
Snake Constrictor.
It has to be a Snake Constrictor, Araragi-kun.
Adder Shackle, Serpent Braid, Snake Constrictor.
Some even call it the Viper.
Viper? So it's a snake.
Viper
Cut 6
Oshino, what kind of oddity is a Snake Constrictor?
An oddity born from a person's spite.
Well... it's not limited to spite.
But since it's a Snake Constrictor, it has to be spite.
Sengoku told me about it.
Unnumbered cut
Black
She was cursed by a friend from her class.
Well, it was something like a hocus pocus spell.
Red
Unnumbered cut
Snake Constrictors aren't something an amateur could handle.
Black
First of all, why did her friend curse her?
It was caused by some kind of love affair.
The guy her friend liked confessed to Sengoku,
but she unknowingly rejected him.
Then her friend ended up resenting her for it... Something like that.
Cut 16
Resentment
After Sengoku found out she was cursed, she went on to read "The Encyclopedia of Snake Curses".
Cut 17
Sengoku knew
Cut 16
she was
caught in
Cut 16
a curse
Then she figured out how to lift the curse, and performed the ritual.
Killing snakes to lift a snake curse sounds pretty dumb.
Actually, it got worse after she started killing the snakes.
No, Araragi-kun.
Cut 21
Araragi-kun
Chopping up snakes to repel the Snake Constrictor isn't wrong.
Actually, you can call it the correct method.
Then why...
The procedure wasn't carried out correctly.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Lifting a curse is harder than placing a curse.
Of course it's going to get worse if done by someone with half-assed knowledge.
Unnumbered cut
Silence  / Thought
And it seems that she was pretty unlucky.
One, two...
But that's no good.
Look, it won't work.
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
GHO      ST   ORY
bakemono
gatari
N A D E K O  S N A K E
If words will ruin our relationship,
then we won't need them.
Don't you think so? Are you scared?
But wait. Something's not right.
A journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step.
So I'll go on with a resolution as firm as stone.
If I do my best I'll be your ideal girl.
Going to try my best. I'll give it all I've got!
Fluffy and fluttering, fluttery and fluffy.
I can fly to the moon if you call my name.
Fluttery and fluffy, fluffy and fluttering.
When you smile, I'll be affected by it.
Thank you, God.
Even if our fateful encounter was just a prank by fate,
I feel blessed by it.
But that's no good.
Look, it won't work.
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
Yup, I don't want it like that.
Hey, that's not enough.
I just want you to look at me forever and ever.
Snake.
The general name for reptiles of class
Reptilia, order Squamata, suborder Serpentes.
They are distinguished by their long, thin, cylindrical body and coat of scales.
Having hundreds of vertebrae, they can curve their body at will.
Demons,
cats,
crabs,
snails,
monkeys--
and now snakes?
Leaving out demons, snakes have the worst image of them all.
They feel so unlucky.
The creepiness of cats,
crabs, snails, and monkeys
doesn't begin to compare to them.
"No--
That image of them is correct, Araragi-kun."
"Since long ago, snakes have
often been considered as such."
"On the other hand, there have been more than a few instances when
they've been considered the opposite, and snake cults have been founded
--These have occurred all over the world.
Something with an image of both holiness and wickedness--That's snakes."
"Say what you will, I don't have
anything but bad images of snakes."
"Even if you mention snake cults, I don't really get it."
"How about the tsuchinoko as an image that's not negative?"
"Well, for me, the fear of snakes is instinctual rather than logical."
"Just looking at them
makes me twitch."
"Well, there aren't many land animals that look like that."
Struggle
"They look almost like fish swimming on land, so it's impossible to not find them odd."
"And they're unusually good survivors.  They don't die easily, even if you try hard at killing them."
Yellow
Unnumbered cut
Episode 10
Nadeko Snake
Part 2
Font used in video:
HGP Mincho B
Black
Unnumbered cut
I'm home.
Welcome home, Koyomi onii-chan.
How did it go, Araragi-senpai?
It seems her curse will be lifted if we use this.
Really?
Yeah, those scale marks will be gone too.
But to lift the curse, we have to carry out the ritual at that shrine.
It'd be best if we carry it out tonight...
Sengoku, is it okay for you to go home late tonight?
Yeah, it's okay.
I'll call my mom and tell her I'll be
staying over at my friend's tonight.
Cut 39
Ritual
We need to prepare a few things for the ritual.
I'll go gather those.
Meanwhile, go call your mom.
Oh, the stuff we need might be a little heavy...
Kanbaru, I want you to come and help me.
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
All right.
Sengoku is in danger.
Her life will be in danger if we don't do something by tonight.
The Snake Constrictor is an invisible snake, which is constricting Sengoku's body.
The scale marks prove that.
According to Oshino, it'll be too late to do
anything once the scale marks reach her face.
Shouldn't being constricted feel painful?
Oshino said it should be painful.
But she's probably just holding it in.
But Sengoku's classmate didn't have to go this far just because Sengoku rejected the guy she likes...
Well, curses themselves aren't a big deal.
Well, it shouldn't have activated
since it was placed by an amateur.
Then why...
The procedure to lift the curse wasn't carried out correctly.
And also, she was unlucky.
Black
Unnumbered cut
The shrine where the young lady
chopped up snakes isn't a special place.
But you see, Shinobu-chan came to this city.
A legendary vampire with royal blood flowing inside her.
Not to mention, vampires are the king of all oddities.
Because of her, a lot of unwelcome
guests began gathering at that shrine.
That's also the reason why you didn't feel well.
Then...
Black
Unnumbered cut
Yeah, the curse was activated because she was killing snakes in that shrine.
Nothing would've happened if she did it somewhere else.
That's like putting salt on your own wound...
Then Araragi-senpai...
Wouldn't it be dangerous to carry out the ritual at the shrine?
Not really.  If we follow the procedure carefully,
that place should make its existence stand out.
So it's actually to our advantage.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Hey, Sengoku...
Black
Unnumbered cut
What is it, Koyomi onii-chan?
Those scale marks actually hurt, right?
Are you okay?
Road Closed
W-Well... Please don't be mad at me, Koyomi onii-chan.
No, I'm not blaming you.
I'm just wondering if you're okay.
No bikes
It feels like I'm being constricted, but I can hold in the pain.
It's weird that you have to hold it in.
A bright future
4km ahead
Model house
Lot houses
It's okay to say it hurts when it hurts.
Yup, he's right.
A bright future
4km ahead
Model house
Restraining yourself for a little while is fine,
but restraining yourself for a long time isn't
because it'll put a lot of stress on your body.
I don't understand why you thought restraining yourself is fine
and why you ignored the psychological effects of it, Kanbaru.
Let's go.
Red
Unnumbered cut
By the way, Sengoku...
Yes?
I was wondering why you rejected the guy who confessed to you.
Well...
I like someone else.
Hey, how much do you remember about our childhood, Koyomi onii-chan?
To be honest, not too much.
My memory isn't really that good.
Oh, I see...
I'm surprised that you remembered me at all.
I didn't really play with others back then.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Rara-chan was the only friend who I could play with after school.
You mean Tsukihi-chan?
But then, Rara-chan went to a different middle school.
I still cherish those memories of us playing together.
I see.
Not to mention, I'm an only child.
I really wanted an older brother.
Cut 139
Commercial Next
(Not really. The encoder didn't leave one in this week.)
Kanbaru, do you feel okay?
Episode 10 Password: Shrine
I came prepared.
I'm feeling better than I expected.
Then let's start the preparations.
Kanbaru, I did ask you to get her clothes that would leave enough skin exposed
so we could see the scale marks go away...
But why a school swimsuit of all things?!
I was trying to go along with your fetishes.
Don't do that!
So you admit it's a fetish of yours?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Sit right in the middle of the sheet.
Then grip this charm with all your might,
close your eyes, regulate your breathing and start praying.
Pray to what?
Whatever you want.
But in this kind of situation, you should...
All right.
I'll try my best.
Koyomi onii-chan, look at me.
All right.
Please look at me.
Yeah, no problem.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Look at me, Koyomi onii-chan!
Reminiscence
Araragi household, Koyomi's room
Koyomi * Elementary Student
Um, you're Sengoku, right?
Reminiscence Part
Koyomi * Elementary Student
Sorry
Reminiscence Part
It's tough to do with an upperclassman around, isn't it?
Tsukihi's so pushy.
T-That's...
That's not true.
Even though you're a sixth grader, you're not scary at all.
And you're not mean... Besides...
Koyomi * Elementary Student
Reminiscence Part
Besides?
You're really kind...
And you fixed my bike!
Koyomi * Elementary Student
Reminiscence Part
Oh, the chain just came off, don't worry...
That's...
Not true...
Rara-chan, I'm so envious that you have such a nice older brother.
U-Umm...
Hm?
Koyomi * Elementary Student
Reminiscence Part
C-Can I call you... "Koyomi onii-chan"?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
Huh?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
Seems like it's turning out okay.
But think about it, Araragi-senpai.
You owe Oshino-san another favor.
It's gonna be a big one too, since the oddity this time was so strong.
Nah, I don't owe him for this.
Kanbaru, I told you this was a gathering place for unwelcome guests, right?
Well, it might've turned into a full-scale war between monsters, so it's very dangerous.
We've prevented it by placing an ofuda on this shrine.
Was it really that big of a deal?
Yeah.
He said that charm was a thank you gift.
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
Black
Unnumbered cut
The ritual sure takes a long time.
Yeah, but we can only wait.
Araragi-senpai, Sengoku-chan must be really tired.
Can't we just pull off that Snake Constrictor in one go?
Oshino said I could touch the Snake Constrictor and pull it off.
Black
Unnumbered cut
You better not do that.
If you do that, the Snake Constrictor will obviously try to bind to you.
And...
Red
Unnumbered cut
Even if I can avoid that,
the Snake Constrictor will go back to the classmate who placed the curse.
"Curses, like chickens, come home to roost," huh?
Yeah.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Cut 217
Curses, like chickens, come home to roost
"Curses, like chickens, come home to roost."
Araragi-kun, I'm repeating myself, but remember this phrase and think about its meaning.
I don't know what goes on in your mind.
But one day, I'll leave this city.
When that happens, I won't be able to help you anymore.
You know, oddities aren't things you should get involved with on purpose.
But you have a tendency to stick your nose into the business of others.
But I can't just ignore them!
I just can't.
Red
Unnumbered cut
Then why don't you just forget everything like Class Rep-chan.
Forget about everything...
Black
Unnumbered cut
I guess that's a bit too hard for you.
Danger
Do not
enter
Well, just relax.
We're like brothers now, so I won't just disappear without telling you.
I'm an adult, so I at least know to do that.
Emergency Call
Cut 231
But
But give some thought to that when you think about your future.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Are you saying I'm an irresponsible person for helping whoever I can?
Black
Unnumbered cut
But you know, I can't become someone like you.
I'm a tenth of a vampire, thus I'm an oddity myself.
Red
Unnumbered cut
I can't become someone who exorcises oddities.
Araragi-kun.
Araragi-kun, you just have to abandon Shinobu-chan and you'll revert back to being entirely human.
I don't want you to forget about that.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Araragi-senpai!
Black
Unnumbered cut
Red
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
Black
Unnumbered cut
Wh-What happened?
I-I don't know, but she suddenly...
Did it fail?
Is that what happened, Araragi-senpai?
Black
Unnumbered cut
No, that can't be...
Cut 259
scale
snake
I see!
Kanbaru, I made a mistake.
If we could actually see the Snake Constrictors, we would've understood right away.
What do you mean?
There isn't just one...
Cut 266
One snake
There are two!
Cut 266
Two snakes
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
Dammit!
Cut 268
One by one,
the Snake Constrictors wrapped around her.
Cut 268
Like they were going to constrict Sengoku,
two snakes
Kanbaru, stay back!
Sengoku's friend wasn't the only one who resented her...
Sengoku!
The guy who Sengoku rejected also began to hate her.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Even though I can't see it...
I should be able to touch it!
Cut 294
Don't flinch.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Red
Cut 306
Danger
White
Unnumbered cut
Red
White
Unnumbered cut
Red
Black
Unnumbered cut
Red
This might work.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Even though I can't see the Snake Constrictor,
I can see its movement path clearly.
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
Using the traces on the ground and the movement of the grass,
Red
Unnumbered cut
I can predict where it is.
Huh?
Red
Unnumbered cut
Araragi-senpai, forgive me!
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
Black
Unnumbered cut
K-Kanbaru...
Stay calm! Don't get excited!
The poison will spread if you become excited!
Snakes are violent creatures, but they're also cowards!
If we stay calm and wait, it'll run away.
But Kanbaru!
Then the snake will go back to the guy whom Sengoku rejected!
Araragi-senpai, I'm begging you!
Black
Unnumbered cut
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
Don't be mistaken with whom you're supposed to save...
Red
Unnumbered cut
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
It's too late.
Even if I wanted to go after it,
chasing an invisible snake is impossible.
Araragi-senpai...
I'm sorry for making you play such a harsh role.
Sorry.
Don't apologize, it'll embarrass me.
I'm sorry.
Voice  / Line
Cut due to circumstances
I'm sorry, Kanbaru...
I'm really sorry.
Black
Unnumbered cut
The snake went back to the one who placed the curse.
In order to take the curse back.
Koyomi onii-chan...
Kanbaru's conclusion was correct.
As a mock oddity myself, I couldn't handle real oddities.
But I couldn't give up.
Cut 384
Koyomi onii-chan, thanks for saving me.
Please don't say that, Sengoku.
Don't thank me.
I don't have the right to be thanked.
Because I tried to save the person who cursed you.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Ghostory
Snake
Nadeko Snake Part 2
Continued
Next Episode
Deneb, Altair, and Vega
That's the Summer Triangle you pointed at
I remember that when I look up at the sky
I finally found Vega
But where are you, Altair?
You'll be alone like this
I looked up from the pitch dark world
It's like the night sky is filled with raining stars
I wonder when I started to chase after you
Please, no matter what
Don't be surprised
Listen to
These feelings
Of mine
Now streaming an extended preview at our website!
Preview
Dialog
Nisioisin
Cartoon
Haritama Hiroki
I'm Karen!
I'm Tsukihi!
Just kidding, I'm actually Tsukihi!
Is that okay?
Sen-chan
She says she's coming over
Just kidding, I'm actually Karen!
Hey, wuzzat?
Delivery!
Note
We switched just in case!
Just the hat?
Did you fall for it?
Next episode, Tsubasa Cat Part 1!
Next Time
Tsubasa Cat Part 1
So, who am I?
Preview quiz!