Run! Get a move on!
Toru-chan's waiting for you.
Okaaaaaay.
You haven't forgotten anything?
I'm fine.
Be careful, okay?
Yeah. See you later.
Sorry for the wait.
Good morning, Run-chan.
Fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
Kirameku tooku no sora to hitotsu ni naru
Kazeyomi kimama na watashi no yukue wa kanata
Issho ni ikou
Shinkokyuu hazundeku, sekai no spring breath
Taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
Ohayou to sayounara no aida wa watashitachi dake
Nandemo dekiru ne
Sukitooru hizashi, umaretate no sora
Machiawaseta yakusoku no morning arch
Te o furu kimi e to totte oki no kyou o watasou
Oshaberi ga hajimaru
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
RAINY DAYS
CALL FOR BATHS
Oh, really?
Huh? I e-mailed you about it
after dinner last night.
Really? I didn't see that mail!
Run-chan?
Your sock.
I forgot to put the other one on!
How embarrassing!
I'm better off just going barefoot.
R-R-R-Run... P-P-P...
Your panties?
I can't believe I didn't notice! I didn't notice!
No squatting! You can see from the front!
Because I was sleepy? That's my only reason?
It's all right. Everyone forgets things.
Things like this can happen? I'm so...
But not panties, normally.
Toru. Just now...
Just now... you thought
"Not panties," didn't you?!
Run-chan! You mustn't run!
Again? That's tough for you too, Toru.
Sorry, Toru.
I really can't do mornings.
I'm tired and I just space out...
So that's the problem?
She already put some on.
Ah! Yeah, naturally, right?
But I thought, just maybe...
Oh, say, Run.
What?
Can I make copies of your notes
from yesterday's afternoon classes?
Oh, you left early yesterday, didn't you? Sure.
Here.
Thank you.
You're a big help.
What language is this?
Oh, c'mon, it's Japanese.
But the sleep demon came after me during class.
So it's NOT just mornings!
It might be a little messy...
N-No, not at all.
Thank you.
Tell me if you can't read something, okay?
Huh?!
Here.
Thank you!
Say, Yuko-chan, show me
that when you're done.
Sure. Give that to Run once you've made copies.
Okay.
Now then...
Hey.
Are you nearsighted? What's your eyesight?
I have 20/10 vision. These are cosmetic glasses.
Huh? Why d'ya wear cosmetic glasses?
Because if I don't, I see things
that I shouldn't see.
Don't tell me you mean...
Yes. Behind you right now, Yuko.
No, that's a lie.
It was only a joke.
You sure make fooling you worthwhile.
I'm just nearsighted.
Cut that out! I ain't good with scary stories!
I was surprised, too!
Nagi-chan, you're a good actress.
You could be in the drama club.
I am.
Even though I'm a ghost.
Well done!
Not!
Note: an excerpt from Kokoro written by Natsume Soseki,
from the official 1957 translation
"I received two or three letters from you this summer."
"If I remember rightly, it was in your second letter
that you asked me to help you find a suitable post."
I wanna go to the bathroom...
"If I remember rightly, it was in your second letter
that you asked me to help you find a suitable post."
Um, sir!
What's the matter?
Uh, well...
Oh, no! I can't say I gotta go to the bathroom!
That's way embarrassing!
Um, my head hurts...
Yuko... That's your STOMACH.
I mean, um...
Sir, excuse me!
I'd like to go to the restroom, so may I take
Yuko-chan by the nurse's office on my way?
Yeah. Do it.
Run...
Let's go, Yuko-chan!
Yeah!
I-I'm sorry. You really helped me out, Run.
It's fine. I needed to go, too.
Huh? To the bathroom?
No...
The nurse's office.
Run!
Run, what's the matter?
Is somethin' wrong?
I don't know, but I feel sick somehow.
I think something's the matter with...
I'm gonna puke!
You need a toilet? Or the nurse's office?
No, a toilet!
A toil... To... To... To?
Oh! TORU!
Yuko-chan!
No, that's not...
Nurse's
Office
Run! Hey!
Run! Hang in there.
Yuko.
You in there?
Toru! Run suddenly fainted!
And the nurse ain't in today! What do we do?!
Just calm down. We can
get hold of one of the teachers.
Both of you, stay quiet.
It's all right.
She just hasn't gotten enough sleep.
Calmly
and
Quietly
Rain...
I have no umbrella.
Me neither. It was sunny this morning!
But it's only drizzling. Will we be fine if we run?
Wait, Toru. Watch this!
Aoigaoka
High School
I discovered this recently: I'm a rain woman!
Note: Rain woman is a Japanese spirit/monster who is a bringer of rain.
In modern Japanese, it refers to someone who is seemingly jinxed
as a rain-bringer that ruins events, etc.
I discovered this recently: I'm a rain woman!
Note: Rain woman is a Japanese spirit/monster who is a bringer of rain.
In modern Japanese, it refers to someone who is seemingly jinxed
as a rain-bringer that ruins events, etc.
Note: Rain woman is a Japanese spirit/monster who is a bringer of rain.
In modern Japanese, it refers to someone who is seemingly jinxed
as a rain-bringer that ruins events, etc.
Quit risking your health and hurry back!
Note: Rain woman is a Japanese spirit/monster who is a bringer of rain.
In modern Japanese, it refers to someone who is seemingly jinxed
as a rain-bringer that ruins events, etc.
I'm all wet!
Jeez, don't be so reckless.
Who's that? He's staring over here.
Even though Run-chan
looks like THAT right now.
Run-chan.
Let's go over there.
Yeah.
Good.
How nice... And at this school.
SUBMIT PERMISSION SLIPS FOR THE SCHOOL
RETREAT TO YOUR TEACHER OR YAMADA.
WHAT A
PAIN...
Run, you have to hurry and dry off.
Okay, finished!
Toru, wear this.
GAB HSART
Ta-daa!
With this, we don't need an umbrella!
At our age, this is a bit much. If we were
in elementary school, maybe, but...
Ah, true enough, the "pair look" is a bit much.
So maybe just one of us should...
No, that's not the issue.
The heck is that?
Fine, then I'll strip. I'm gonna get wet anyway.
Wh-What?
I'LL strip.
Wanna go?
Nagi-chan! Yuko-chan!
Stay back!
Jeez. I wondered what you guys were up to...
Run, you're soaking wet!
My house is close by.
Why not come dry your clothes?
Really? Thank you.
But it's still...
Whoa.
I wonder if we've got a rain jinx at our school.
So, what do we do?
It's really coming down,
but we'll be fine if we run.
No one's afraid of getting wet, right?
Well, if it's as far as Nagi's house...
What a pain.
I don't want to get wet, so let's call a taxi.
How un-high school student-like!
I wonder if it'll stop if wait...
Doesn't look good.
So we should call a taxi-
Go!
Nagi-chan, your house is this way, right?
Hey, what the!
Wait, me too!
Wait up, idiot!
C'mon, c'mon!
Wait up! Don't leave me!
Rain makes me a little depressed,
yet they're having such fun...
Aah, youth!
K's POEMS
Miss Kito
I've got it... I've got it!
Hobby: Poetry
Miss Kito
In the
Poem
In
Reality
I'm home.
Pardon the intrusion!
Yeah, go on in. Let's hurry and take a bath.
Huh? Big Bro is home.
Nagi, you've got a big brother?
Brother! I brought some friends over!
So don't use the washroom, okay?
Nagi-chan, do you call your big brother "Bro"?
Or do you call him "Brother"?
Note: Nagi tries to cultivate a tough-girl image; aniki (Bro) sounds
kinda tough, while oniichan (Big Brother) sounds cutesy.
Nagi-chan, do you call your big brother "Bro"?
Or do you call him "Brother"?
Note: Nagi tries to cultivate a tough-girl image; aniki (Bro) sounds
kinda tough, while oniichan (Big Brother) sounds cutesy.
B-Bro, of course!
Note: Nagi tries to cultivate a tough-girl image; aniki (Bro) sounds
kinda tough, while oniichan (Big Brother) sounds cutesy.
Now then...
Only two people can fit in the tub at once.
So we're making pairs.
Here goes. One, two...
Okay, Run and I go first.
See you! Well, let's change.
There we go.
That's right!
Come to think of it, Toru and me
ain't never talked one on one!
What should I do?!
Silence at a time like this is kinda... kinda!
Yuko.
Yes?!
Should I put something on?
She has lots of DVDs.
O-oh, yeah.
SCARY URBAN LEGENDS
That Really Happened
"Scary Urban Legends That Really Happened"
or SILENCE. Which do you prefer?
That's an extreme choice!
Put your clothes down over there.
Okay. Here, right?
Well, let's hurry and get in.
Whoa! Who're you?!
It's me, Run.
Yeah, I know that.
Still, something very simple can...
Really change things.
Who're you?!
I'm bored of that reaction.
It sure feels good, right?
Refreshing, isn't it?
Yeah. Still, we should get out soon, huh?
That's right. We have to hurry
and let Toru and Yuko-chan go.
It's just the two of them alone in my room.
I wonder if they're okay.
They're okay! The two of them get along.
Well...
Yeah, but...
Game over! Game over!
At this rate, it's game over!
Oh! It's not scary if I close my eyes.
I wanna scream!
Sorry for the wait.
Okay, the bath is...
Hey, Yuko? The bathtub is free.
Yuko-chan.
Yuko-chan?
Yuko-chan!
Yuko-chan? Yuko-chan! Oh no, Yuko-chan!
What the heck happened?
Wow... That was REALLY scary.
Finally we can take a bath. Right, Toru?
Yeah.
Well, wanna go in?
Hey...
You ever gotten scared when you're washing
your bangs and you can't see?
Me, I really couldn't stand shampoo
when I was a kid.
I got shampoo in my eyes!
What're you doin', Toru?!
Where's the shower head?
My eyes... My eyes!
Dammit, Yuko!
Shut up already!
Look, stop it!
Jeez...
I thought I was gonna stop breathing.
Aah. Consciousness is growing dim...
Run, look: You can see an oasis.
Nagi! Run!
What're you two doin'?!
Yuko...
H-how was the bathwater?
Don't worry about that!
Um, just turn off the heater.
I thought we'd... dry our clothes...
It's delicious!
Ah, I'm back to life!
Jeez, don't scare us like that.
They've gotten pretty dry.
I wonder if it'll stop raining soon...
Doesn't look like it yet.
It sure is raining.
Rainy days always do your hair in, huh?
Mine always gets kinda limp.
Mine fans out, and I can't tame it at all.
Maybe we have different hair types...
Let me touch your hair, Yuko-chan.
Sure. No problem.
Yuko-chan, your hair's so pretty!
Toru.
You don't have any split ends at all.
Wanna play?
Oh, that's not true!
These clothes are cute, huh?
Don't move! This is the important part!
Okay.
Yes, yes.
Wh-what gives?
Don't move!
I lost!
Gonna play again?
I'll make Nagi a new high score.
That's nice of you.
Hup!
Yuko, your fingers are surprisingly pretty.
Th-that's not true.
Do you take care of them somehow?
No, I don't really do anything.
All right. In that case...
Ta-daa!
That feels good, but...
I-I feel embarrassed somehow.
T-Toru! Hey!
Don't you move!
Don't move!
Jeez! What should I do?!
Houkago yotei mo nanmo nai shi
Got no plans for after class
Looks like it still won't stop.
Houkago yotei mo nanmo nai shi
Got no plans for after class
Looks like it still won't stop.
Ame ga futteru kara uchi ni shuugou
It's raining, so let's get together at my place
It sure is coming down...
Ame ga futteru kara uchi ni shuugou
It's raining, so let's get together at my place
Yeah.
Ame ga futteru kara uchi ni shuugou
It's raining, so let's get together at my place
But you know, I really like the sound of the rain.
Ame ga futteru kara uchi ni shuugou
It's raining, so let's get together at my place
Huh?
Ame ga futteru kara uchi ni shuugou
It's raining, so let's get together at my place
Huh?
Kimi wa fudan kara sunao ja nai keredo
Normally you're not so open to that
Ah. But I can see that, somehow.
Kimi wa fudan kara sunao ja nai keredo
Normally you're not so open to that
Right?
Kimi wa fudan kara sunao ja nai keredo
Normally you're not so open to that
C'mon, Nagi-chan.
Kimi wa fudan kara sunao ja nai keredo
Normally you're not so open to that
Close your eyes and see for yourself.
Kimi wa fudan kara sunao ja nai keredo
Normally you're not so open to that
Close your eyes and see for yourself.
Kyou wa kitto wakaru hazu
But today you're sure to understand
What? No, I...
Kyou wa kitto wakaru hazu
But today you're sure to understand
What? No, I...
Egao ga mitai dake dayo
I just want to see your smiling face
Sonna tokoro ni kakurenaide ii kara
You don't have to hide in a place like that
Motto, hora, chikazuite
C'mon, come closer
Kimi mo tomodachi nanda
You're a friend, too
Kore kara nandomo sugite yuku kisetsu mo
Going forward, no matter how many seasons pass
Zutto, hora, chikaku ni ite
C'mon, always stay close by
Kimi to issho ni itai yo
I want to be with you
Kimi to waratte'tai nda
I want to laugh with you
Well, true, it's not so bad.
Still, it sounds like somethin' frying, right?
It kinda makes you hungry, huh?
Run-chan.
Ah. It was me, huh?
Again?
All right, then.
Be careful goin' home.
Okay! Thanks for the umbrella, too!
Well, see you tomorrow!
Sorry for the bother.
See you.
Say, that umbrella's cute, huh?
Yeah. Ah, it's still rainin' hard.
What time is the next train?
Brother! You can use the washroom now.
10 Minutes Later
I told you to be careful...
Didn't I?
Sorry.
Akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
Tanoshii ichinichi no owari
Tsukinai oshaberi mada mada aru keredo
Sorosoro o-uchi ni kaeranakucha
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Mail suru kara
Kyou no page ni minna osoroi no egao
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Itsumo arigato
Kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
Ru-ru-run, kaze to kokoro humming suru
Tsugi no kado de furimukinagara bye-bye
yup!
Everyone, the wait is over!
Next time, I, Yutaka and Miporin
will finally make their appearance!
Note: Word-final "n" is a way of making a cutesy nickname.
"Miporin" is also a nickname; this character's real name is Miho.
Next time, I, Yutaka and Miporin
will finally make their appearance!
Note: Word-final "n" is a way of making a cutesy nickname.
"Miporin" is also a nickname; this character's real name is Miho.
Sorry for the wait.
Note: Word-final "n" is a way of making a cutesy nickname.
"Miporin" is also a nickname; this character's real name is Miho.
TORUN
Sorry for the wait.
Note: Word-final "n" is a way of making a cutesy nickname.
"Miporin" is also a nickname; this character's real name is Miho.
Sorry for the wait.
Note: Word-final "n" is a way of making a cutesy nickname.
"Miporin" is also a nickname; this character's real name is Miho.
Fifteen long, trying years...
Okay, that's enough reflecting on your life.
Wait, so that talk of us being in Episode 1
was all for nothing?
Well, we ARE in the opening animation.
True, but still...
Next time on A-Channel: "Classmates"
Next
Episode!
Next time on A-Channel: "Classmates"
Next
Episode!
And not just classmates: the upperclassmen
will of course also be appearing.