Hey, Yoshii!
Got it!
Summon!
As a Probate, Yoshii Akihisa's Summoned Being has a special ability.
Not only can it touch real objects; with its exponentially increased power,
Be sure to bring the world map.
Got it...
he is forced to help with odd jobs.
Yoshii! Be sure to carry the desks to the AV room.
Eh...
Yoshii! Be sure to take down the soccer goals.
Seriously... why am I the only one working?
That's how Probates are treated.
I'm upset already!
The Probate's Summoned Being even sends sensory feedbacks, such as pain.
We'll have a quiz next, so be sure to review what you've learned up until now.
I'm going to strike back.
Stupid!
Today is Sunday, however.
This is it for today
Be sure to review when you get home.
Sign: Supplementary Class
Okay.
Although it's an off-day, 2-F had supplementary lessons.
By the way, what happened to you, Yoshii-kun?
Just a little payback...
You were taken out instead, huh?
Ah, I'm hungry.
I worked hard today, so I'm hungrier than usual.
Your Summoned Being isn't as convenient as it seems.
Yuuji, lunch.
Shouko, why?
Class A doesn't have supplementary lessons, does it?
I was studying on my own.
I'll even come on a Sunday if Yuuji's here.
You don't have to come.
I won't come on a weekday if Yuuji isn't here.
That's wrong!
You brought a bento today?
What's that?
One sixty-seventh of a cup noodle.
One sixty-seventh?
Half of half of half of half of half of half.
Akihisa, that's one sixty-fourth.
Your mastery of division is doubtful.
Thanks for the meal.
How miserable.
This meal brings tears to me.
I-I guess it can't be helped. Want me to share my bento with you?
Really?
I made too much, so I have an extra.
I don't want to waste food, so do you want it?
I do!
Hold on for a bit.
What, what?
Sorry, I think I left them at home.
Why?
I went through the trouble of making them, too.
It's fine!
For me to believe that Minami can do girlish things like making a bento—
I'm getting crushed!
I'm telling you; I just forgot to bring it!
I can see, I can see...
Sign: Finger -> Eye
Yuuji can't look.
It's as lively as usual.
Excuse me, is this the idiot Class F?
Hazuki! What're you doing here?
Ah, onee-chan!
Hazuki...
Ah, the stupid onii-chan!
That's amazing, Akihisa. To think, your stupidity is known throughout the nation.
Only the neighborhood, at most!
It is the stupid onii-chan!
Hey Hazuki, why do you know Aki?
Because he's my husband!
I'm going steady with the stupid onii-chan!
Akihisa has met Hazuki before.
How that came about will be discussed later.
Hey Aki, what'd you do to my sister?
We shall hold the Inquisition tribunal now.
What're you all doing?!
Charge: defendant Yoshii Akihisa has disobeyed the blood-bound oath of the Inquisition members
and has committed the serious crime of going out with a girl.
This is true, correct?
Yes it is!
Defendant, do you have anything left to say?
Why is my testament before my defense?
Guilty! Death penalty!
What grade are you in?
I'm in fifth grade.
You're more capable than Akihisa.
Ah, the pretty onee-chan!
Hello, Hazuki-chan.
So why'd you come here today?
That's right!
Onee-chan, you forgot these!
My bento! Thank you, Hazuki!
I'm glad you brought both.
See, I wasn't lying.
Even I can make bento.
So that was it!
I was wondering what was going on, since it's rare for onee-chan to wake up early and make a bento so enthusiastically.
So it was to feed the stupid onii-chan.
What is she saying?
Such a weird child.
Oh, that bento was made for Akihisa?
You're wrong.
Why would I do that for Aki?
Then what were you making enthusiastically?
Not the bento, but that...
A model vehicle!
Model vehicle!
A 1/35 scale King Tiger!
A German tank?
Aren't you glad, Akihisa?
It's larger than a one sixty-fourth cup noodle.
It's about size?!
It may taste better than you think.
It's not organic! I can't eat it!
Anyways, these are left overs.
I didn't make them for Aki.
Oh? what's wrong, Himeji?
No, it's nothing!
That's a bento?
So Himeji made one, too.
Y-Yes. Although it isn't too good.
Um...
I actually made this for Yoshii-kun!
Yoshii-kun, if you'd like, please eat this!
We shall hold the Inquisition tribunal now.
Wait!
Guilty! Death penalty!
So I don't get to speak at all this time?!
Please, wait! You've got it wrong!
This is...
Um, well...
It's not that.
This bento is, um...
Burn the heretic.
It's really hot!
Fire, fire!
Onee-chan?
Moron.
Are you okay, Yoshii-kun?
I'm fine. This is nothing if I get to eat Himeji-san's bento.
That's embarrassing.
We can eat without anyone disturbing us here.
You're right.
Wow, that looks delicious!
I'm embarrassed.
Oh, I forgot to bring drinks. I'll go and get some.
Ah, not only is Himeji-san cute and intelligent, but she can cook on top of that.
This is wasted on you.
Yuuji! What're you doing?
Let me have some as well.
Hideyoshi, too!
It's just a bite! Don't be so stingy.
Yuuji?
Hideyoshi?
What's wrong with you two?
Something's wrong, Ninja Pervert!
Take them to the infirmary!
Ninja Pervert!
C-Could it be that the bento...
That's impossible; it looks so good!
That was dangerous! I was about to be dragged into the afterlife.
There's no doubt.
Everyone is sick because of this bento.
The smell alone was that dangerous.
Akihisa...
Hideyoshi!
Plate... Get me a plate.
Plate?
Well, if you're in for a penny, you're in for a pound.
That means I'll be fine if I eat all of it.
This isn't good. He isn't thinking straight.
I brought the drink.
Himeji-san...
Hm, what's wrong with everyone?
Well, they got sleepy after eating and are taking a siesta.
You'll get fat if you sleep right after eating.
I'd rather get fat if it means staying alive.
Have some.
T-Thank you, Himeji-san.
This is bad, what should I do?
Oh, you're not eating?
N-No, it feels like a waste to eat it.
Was this bothersome for you?
No way, not at all!
I'm really happy.
I'm glad.
A-Are you the type that tastes while cooking?
They say that you get fat when you eat while cooking
Besides...
Besides?
I wanted Yoshii-kun to be the first to eat it.
All escape routes have been cut off.
Why are the angel and the devil telling me the same thing?!
Akihisa...
Yuuji!
Sakamoto-kun.
Sorry, Himeji, bring me something to drink too.
Can you buy me oolong tea?
Yes, I will.
Yuuji.
Akihisa, I'll teach you something useful.
Listen well.
There are several spices that have been used as antidotes since the ancient times.
Before refrigerators, they were used to keep food from rotting.
And they say that "love" is the ultimate spice in a girl's cooking.
You don't say!
That's right, Akihisa. Cure poison with the spice called "love."
I see. I got it, Yuuji.
This is a trial.
It'll be fine.
I'll overcome any hardship for the sake of love.
With the ultimate spice called "love," no matter what kind of poison it may be...
So love isn't an antidote.
Akihisa is brave.
Amen.
Hm, what's wrong with Yoshii-kun?
He got sleepy after eating.
You'll get fat if you sleep right after eating.
Now that I think about it, where's Shimada?
I went through the trouble of making it...
I should've been honest and told him to eat it.
I didn't expect Himeji-san to be bad at something.
Now I'm even hungrier.
Aki!
Stupid onii-chan!
Hazuki-chan.
Do you know where my sister went?
Now that you've mention it, I haven't seen her.
What happened to lunch?
Stuff happened, and I didn't get anything out of it.
Then you must be hungry!
Yeah, if I could've had Minami's bento...
Onee-chan's?
Yeah, I was wondering what kind of bento it was.
I wanted to eat it.
All right!
Aki, I have—
Let's eat our bento, onee-sama!
Miharu!
I've been searching for you!
Please eat Miharu's special bento, which has her heart and soul in it!
Why're you here?! Class D doesn't have supplementary lessons, does it?
I'll even come on a Sunday if onee-sama's here.
I won't come on a weekday if onee-sama isn't here!
Why are there so many screwed-up students in this school?!
Onee-sama, let's spend an afternoon filled with bliss together.
Should we look over there to start?
Don't bother me!
I won't let you get away!
Let's feed each other!
No!
Gosh, onee-sama doesn't have to be that shy.
Onee-sama! Onee-sama!
Geez, that Miharu.
Anyway, I have to find Aki.
Go, Seabiscuit!
Faster!
You can't run in the hallway.
Aki...
I'm glad.
I'll give this bento to him this time.
As we thought.
That Yoshii had two girls make him a bento.
This is an unforgivable crime!
Death for the traitor.
Death for the traitor!
You've got it wrong! This isn't that, but...
It's not that, but...
Well...
What, what?
Wait, everyone's common sense is warped!
Why am I avoiding it?
Go, Secretariat!
Full speed!
You can't run in the hallway.
This isn't the hallway.
I'm out of fuel for today.
This time for sure.
Aki!
Minami.
Onee-chan.
Stupid onii-chan is playing with me!
Isn't that nice? Don't cause too much trouble.
Yep.
Hey, Aki.
Um, have you eaten lunch yet?
Technically I did, but not really.
I see.
Um...
Well, If you're still hungry...
I...
I?
I wonder what the specialty at Oshamambe is!
Huh?
I did it!
The hair crab is Hokkaido, Oshamambe's specialty.
Kubo-kun.
You're at school on a Sunday? Are you doing self-study, too?
Class F has supplementary lessons.
Oh, you still haven't had lunch?
Eh? W-Well...
How about we go grab lunch together, if you'd like?
But I don't have any money.
I guess it can't be helped. It'll be my treat.
I'll go! I'll definitely go!
Then please excuse us, Shimada-san!
Let's come up with a plan for the midterms after lunch.
Eh, tests?
Ah, okay.
Hazuki, what about lunch?
I forgot about lunch since I was playing with onii-chan.
Geez, you have to eat properly, or else you won't grow.
Isn't this onii-chan's?
No way. Why would it be?
I made this for Hazuki.
Then I'll eat with you!
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Hazuki. I forgot that we had more lessons.
Can you go home without me?
Okay, I got it!
Should I choose lunch A? Or should I hold back and choose lunch B?
Oh, Yoshii-kun.
Fukuhara-sensei.
What nice timing. The lid wouldn't budge, so I was in a bind.
Can your Summoned Being open it for me?
No problem.
Summoned Being, summon!
Open!
Review for those who got a zero score!
Stop! I haven't had anything to eat yet!
That's because you...
Yoshii-kun is cute.
What am I saying?
Bon appétit.
Stupid! Stupid Aki! What an idiot! Completely brainless!
Who'd make a bento for a guy like him!
Stupid.
Wait!
Aki.
Are you throwing that away?
What if I am?
So what? Well...
I-I look down at you for wasting food.
Huh?
For the sake of global warming, you shouldn't waste food.
If you just throw stuff away, waste builds up.
So, in order to be environmentally friendly, we must conserve.
In other words, they must be used efficiently or something like that.
Here.
Eh?
Want to eat it?
Or not?
I-I guess I'll take it then, since resources must be—
Minami!
Stupid!
Question 5: What is the name of the sport in which you use a map and compass to find checkpoints?
Role playing game!
I knew you would answer, so—
Next week: Map, Treasure, and Striker Sigma V.
This will be on the test.