Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
Kanaetai yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora hikari ga mieru docchi? Acchi!
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Docchi ni ikou? Nayande kimaranai
Yume no michi wa itsumo kyodai meiro
Migi ka? Hidari ka?
Seikai wa docchi? (Docchi?)
Docchi o erandemo
Nakama to ireba tanoshii kara
Daiseikai!
Kanaeta yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora mirai ga mieru issho ni arukidasou
Hora egao ga mieru docchi? (Kocchi!)
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Oh, Chiya...
Wherefore art thou, Chiya?
Huh? I dunno...
Hey, Nono, why are you Nono?
Huh? I-I dunno, uh...
What are you reading? A philosophy book?
No! Love stories!
MONTHLY
LONDON
This month's issue is Romeo and Juliet themed!
Romeo and
Juliet Collection
They're so lucky!
I wish I could have a romance with my soulmate!
Hey, Kon, what's your perfect prince like?
Huh?! H-how am I supposed to know?!
C'mon, you don't have to hide it.
What're you talking about? I want in, too!
You're a bit young for this conversation, Chiya.
We're talking about an adult romance.
Oh, about making babies!
THAT'S ADULT!
But the season of love for animals is the mating se-
You blockhead virgin! Stop talking!
We're talking about humans, not animals!
Do you know what your ideal prince would be like?
N-no, I don't have anything specific in mind!
I-I have an even harder time talking to boys...
It's just really embarrassing...
Men must never...
...touch her sister!
So my big sister and Saku-chan
always protected me from them.
That's some intense "protection."
Hey, Koume!
We're supposed to be studying by ourselves today!
Getting distracted by love stories
should disqualify you from becoming an Urara!
I wonder what Nina-sensei does
when we're studying by ourselves?
It's time for Nina's Exciting Tea Fortune-Telling!
What's in the future for my romance today?
It's floating upright!
I might meet a special someone!
Maybe I'll meet my soulmate!
Today's lucky charm is meat and potatoes!
The lucky direction is east-northeast.
I'll wear something mustard-colored to boost my sex appeal!
She's doing her daily routine...
BAD
LUCK!
My sister always does those things,
like she's waiting for her soulmate.
Which means he hasn't come around yet.
I got a great idea!
An idea?
We can use our divining powers
to find Nina-sensei's soulmate,
then give him to her as a present!
Nina-sensei's always looking out for us,
so it'd be thanks for all she does...
And it'll be good practice for our fortune-telling!
AND it'll be fun!
That last point's the only reason you're going, right?
And that's a crazy idea to begin with!
Nina-sensei taught us that not even the number one
Urara can find something without any clues!
But that's why we should!
Are you the kind of person who won't even try
if they think something's hard, Kon?
Nono, you want Nina-sensei to be happy, right?!
And it could be good practice
for looking for Chiya's mom!
My mom?!
L-let's give it a try!
Yay!
That was easy.
But what kind of guy would Nina-sensei like?
Oh, I asked her that once!
Let's see, there's a lot of things,
but the most important one would be someone
who treasures the things that are important to me.
The things that are important to you?
My family and my work as an Urara,
and my cute students, too!
Nina-sensei...
What good is it if Nina-sensei
gets our hearts throbbing like this?
Uhh, so if we look for someone
who really cares about us...
...that's who it would be.
So, how are you going to look for this person, Koume?
I'm glad you asked!
I'll use something we learned about in class...
This!
Pendulum divining!
Isn't it cute?
Just so you know, my little pendulum
is a loveable but clumsy half-European girl!
I'm Cadence. I'm six.
Note: Cadence (Yureru) is derived from "Yureiru," or
"to swing in cadence/to swing back and forth."
Cadence
(Age 6):
A Pendulum
Did you have to give us all that information?!
Note: Cadence (Yureru) is derived from "Yureiru," or
"to swing in cadence/to swing back and forth."
Since it's afternoon, there should be lots of
male customers in Meirocho,
so if we just go where Cadence is pointing,
we might run into Nina-sensei's soulmate!
Will it really go that well?
It's okay! If we all work together, we can do anything!
That's right. We won't know if we don't try!
Alright! All together as one, now!
Natsumeya, go!
Everyone's really living out their youth.
Okay, let's start!
We humbly, humbly, request of you!
Search for that one person,
one tied to the red thread of fate!
Pendulum, swing in cadence, swing for love!
We humbly, humbly, request of you!
Search for that one person,
one tied to the red thread of fate!
Pendulum...
You really need to memorize the chant!
C'mon, lemme look cool the whole way through!
There goes Cadence!
I-I think it's that way!
The eastern corner, huh?
Let's go!
It's really showing us where to go!
Wow!
Pendulums react to the diviner's strong wishes.
I'm sure Koume's wishes
are being read by the pendulum.
It's getting stronger and stronger!
Over here, over here! This way!
Sweets Cafe
ARINSU
Koume, what are you feeling right now?
I was thinking about wanting to eat anmitsu.
Oh, Koume!
Get serious already!
I can't help it!
What are those girls doing?
Training? It looks like they're just playing around.
I'll tail them for a bit, but...
Right!
Left!
Left! Left! Left!
Left! Left! Straight!
This is really suspicious.
I feel like they're about to cause trouble again!
DISGUISED
Uhhh, I'm not really sure!
Don't worry about it, Cadence.
Calm down, take a deep breath.
Left! Right! Right!
They're going back and forth...
(SUPPOSEDLY)
DISGUISED
This is getting more and more suspicious.
Oh! I think it's over here!
Wait, it's just a dead end.
That's okay!
Hup!
Chiya, no! Over that wall is Bloque 9!
You'll get thrown out of Meirocho!
BLOQUE
Oh, okay!
Get down right this minute!
You can't do that, Chiya-chan!
Sorry!
That was dangerous, jeez.
Now it says to go this way!
Shoot! I've got to trick them somehow!
Ow...
Are you unharmed, Young Lady?
Y-yeah.
DEEP
VOICE
Thank goodness. Excuse me, then.
That was a close one!
That guy just now was kinda handsome...
What? He was super shady.
Is this what it feels like to meet your soulmate?
Uh...
But running into someone when you
turn the corner is, like, the staple of love stories!
Oh!
That's just like what happened
when we met for the first time, Kon!
You're right.
So does that mean Kon's my soulmate?
Huh?
Hold on, I didn't know you two were like that!
W-we're not, jeez!
What do you mean, "like that"?
Uh, umm, like special friends?
Oh! Then we are like that!
I touched her belly, too!
What kind of a standard is that?!
But the truth is, I wanna touch more and more of you!
I-I can't believe they're having
such a lewd conversation out in public!
But the truth is, I wanna touch more and more of you!
I-I can't believe they're having
such a lewd conversation out in public!
Jeez, Chiya, don't say weird stuff like that!
I shouldn't be watching from the shadows.
I need to go straight up to them and warn them to...
Excuse me, Sir?
We've received reports that a strange man
has been following a group of girls. Is that you?
Sh-shoot!
Y-you've got me all wrong, Miss.
I'm just a traveler passing through...
DEEP
VOICE
He's being super suspicious,
but I'm really attracted to him for some reason!
He's the kind of cool guy
who'd look cooler in black than a crow!
But I have the captain!
I can't let someone else stir my heart!
But...
Wait, we let him get away!
I'm so tired.
Sorry to push you so hard.
Maybe it's too hard for us to find someone at our level.
Hey, where are you?
Come out, Nina-sensei's soulmate!
Someone who really cares about us!
Where are you?!
I won't let you go, you cool suspicious man!
Huh?
A cool suspicious person?! What was he like?!
Hey, Koume!
That sounds fun!
Chiya!
This way! He's this way!
Look!
Hold up, you two!
To the right!
I'm in a real bind now...
How did things turn out like this?
How could I be the one causing so much trouble?
Y-you're the guy from before!
H-have we met somewhere before?
FAINT
VOICE
He must be my soulmate if I'm running into him again!
Koume, calm down!
That guy's really shady!
What's wrong, Chiya-chan?
What're you doing, Chiya?!
There's the shady guy!
Huh? This guy?!
This smell's gotta be Captain Saku!
Huh?
You were following us?!
W-well, I had my reasons.
I can't believe an active-duty patrolman
would be following us around.
I-i-it wasn't like that!
I was just worried about you four!
I was making sure you didn't cause a scene.
It'd be horrible if something happened
to Nina's beloved students.
...someone who treasures the things
that are important to me.
Wait, does Saku actually care about us?
She really does!
We found her!
Nina-sensei's soulmate!
Jeez, to think she was so close, too.
Huh? Wh-what?
Captain Saku, please come have dinner with us tonight.
We'll be waiting for you with Nina-sensei.
Uh-huh...
We're probably having meat and potatoes tonight.
You like that, right, Saku-chan?
Seriously?! I'm there!
Yay!
Thanks, Cadence.
I'm so tired...
This afternoon, we'll be learning
about kokkuri fortune-telling.
Oh, that's what Kon's good at!
We did it once out in a field.
As the name implies, this method calls forth a kokkuri,
a fox or tanuki spirit, to answer your questions.
Some people say that kokkuri is not technically
fortune-telling, but rather a paranormal phenomenon...
No, Sensei, I think we should draw a line
between a fox spirit and ghosts.
Oh, Kon, you're scared of ghosts?
N-no, I'm not!
Setting aside that debate, kokkuri is
actually a technique that's a bit dangerous.
Dangerous?
There are more than a few cases where a kokkuri spirit
has entranced groups of people and caused accidents.
So let's all be careful when we try it out!
Jeez, Kon, for being such a scaredy cat,
you sure have been courageous doing it all this time.
W-well, I was always studying by myself.
I didn't have any friends to do it with.
That's why sometimes...
Kokkuri-sama, Kokkuri-sama,
will you be friends with me?
KON
(AGE 8)
NO
DEPRESSED
It was so depressing...
But it's alright.
Even if they won't be your friends,
fox spirits aren't scary at all!
As long as you follow proper procedure
and address them politely,
they'll answer any question you have!
Huh...
Fox spirits were your go-to for good advice, huh?
Kinda like Nono and Matsuko-san!
Really? We're the same, Kon-chan.
Except that Nono and Matsuko are actually friends!
F-friends...
Don't cry, Kon!
You have us now!
Is everyone ready?
I'm going to start the kokkuri demonstration.
Close your eyes, take a deep breath.
Focus your will in the finger atop the paper.
I'm going to call out the fox spirit.
Chiya, tell them to go home.
Huh?
Let's begin again.
O mysterious, O fantastic, we beseech you.
Kokkuri, kokkuri, please come forth.
Please, we ask of you to come forth
and answer our questions.
I-it's actually here!
Shh! Be quiet!
You have to ask a question!
What kind of question should we ask?
Which do you like getting rubbed more,
your tummy or back?
I like my tummy!
What kind of question is that?!
"Pet...
"Pet my...
"Pet my belly," it says!
It actually answered it.
Do you want to ask anything?
Huh? Me? Um, well...
Um, uh, well, I...
INTERPRETER
"Forgive me, I'm shy and not very good
at talking to strangers..." she said.
Okay, next up is me!
Hey, Koume, don't!
If you take your hand off the coin during the ritual,
you could get possessed by the spirit you...
K-Koume?
You have some nerve to lecture the likes of me, girl.
Stop messing around!
We're in the middle of a holy ritual!
Shtop this at onshe, girl!
After calling me out here,
this is the rude treatment I get?
K-Koume?
Don't tell me...
Is this actually the fox spirit?
Indeed! I'm borrowing this girl's body.
This is punishment for your unskilled divination...
Sniff, sniff, sniff...
Wh-what?!
Wow, she really does smell like a fox.
You're kinda smelly!
H-how rude! I am not smelly!
Koume, Koume, smelly like a fox!
Th-th-th-there's no way Koume
is really possessed by a fox spirit,
this has to be one of her usual
incomprehensible fantasies, right?
HORRIBLE
THING
SAID
AS IF IT
WERE
NOTHING
Well then, will this make you believe?
Now she possessed Nono!
Huh? What was I doing just now?
I feel like I was having a weird dream.
I must still be dreaming.
S-stop!
Nono!
Huh? I...
Oh, this is nice.
This girl's body feels quite comfortable.
It's as if I'm in my own body again.
K..Kon-chan was actually a fox spirit?!
Do something, Chiya!
You're good with animals, right?!
Don't make me laugh.
I'll not be moved by the kindness of the likes of y-
Good girl, good girl!
S-s-s-s-stop...
Maybe Chiya's the one with all the power,
and the fox spirit's weak...
Enough! You foolish, fearless girls,
you'll not get away with this!
I will show you how terrifying kokkuri divining truly is!
I-I can't move!
We're paralyzed!
Your arms and legs are no longer your own!
See now what happens when you anger m-
Bad!
Why doesn't it work on you?!
Th-that's not all that I can do!
There!
T-telekinesis?!
A fox spirit can do this kinda stuff, too?!
This is mere child's play!
If I used all my power,
you lot would be nothing more than-
Wh-why?! Why does one pet make-
Good girl, good girl!
You're no ordinary human!
You're a bad fox spirit.
If you don't leave Kon's body,
I'm gonna punish you more!
P-punish?!
If I don't leave her body, you'll do more?
Jeez, okay, fine.
Good girl, good girl, good girl.
She's completely fallen under her control.
More!!
Well? Are you satisfied?
You. Tell me your name.
Me? I'm Chiya.
Chiya. You've got fascinating eyes.
So deep and red.
I'm sure you can see quite well with them.
Chiya, I like you!
We'll be together forever!
Be my bride!
What?!
No, Fox Spirit! Give back Kon!
Why, after you toyed with my feelings this much?
I was just playing around!
Chiya sounds like a horrible woman here!
Her body hasn't changed,
and it's no different with someone else inside.
It's totally different!
Kon is much more serious and smart,
and gets embarrassed,
but she's a good girl who always tries hard!
What should we do, Koume-chan?
If Kon were here, we could ask her
for the answer, but by ourselves...
If Kon were here?
Fox spirits aren't scary at all!
As long as you follow proper procedure
and address them politely...
Kokkuri
Chiya-chan?!
Do you know how to make it leave?!
I dunno, but I have to try!
'Cause Kon is our really good friend!
O strange and mysterious one,
return to whence you came.
Kokkuri, kokkuri, your debt is repaid.
Your coming is well, and your going is frightening.
Swiftly, swiftly, return to whence you came!
I'm begging you, please go back!
She's bowing to the ground?!
Hey, Chiya, what are you doing?!
Stop that!
What's wrong, Chiya-chan?!
I was wondering what you were doing!
You truly are a fascinating Urara, Chiya.
Very well. Your show of friendship
and manners has compelled me to return.
I will return to you this body.
Really?!
It's been a while since I had such fun at a summoning.
Kokkuri divining is a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
Thank you, Chiya.
Huh?
Wh-wh-wh-what am I doing?!
In front of everyone, in public, to Chiya?!
It's Kon!
Hey, Kon, do you remember anything
from when you were possessed?
No, I don't remember most of it...
Oh, but I remember one little thing.
Well, when you said that I was your really good friend...
You don't remember a lot of things
that would make your face even redder!
Huh?! Wh-what did you do to me?!
That fox spirit was really funny. I wanna see her again!
I think I could do without that.
We're back, Nina-sensei!
Welcome back.
What happened? You look so tired.
Oh, well...
I blacked out when I was making dinner...
and when I came to, this is what I saw.
Note: All the dishes have fried tofu in them, which,
according to folklore, is a fox's favorite food
D-don't tell me...
The fox spirit even possessed my sister?!
Beware kokkuri divining, huh...
It looks so good!
Magari kado turn shitara yume ni tadori tsukeru kana
Mayoi mayotte mawari mawatte
Fuwari deaetara suteki
Ichi kara juu made nattenai hi mo aru
Nee dochira e susumeba happy end?
Migi kara hidari e suki kara daisuki e
Otto koi ni koishite atafuta
Akogareru no nukedasenai
Watashi wa sagashiteimasu
Anata o sagashiteimasu
Mada minu sugata ni tokimeku kuusou Kiss me
Deai gashira de shoutotsu
Chotto kojirete unmei
Moshika moshikashite anata mo mayotteru no
Goal wa mienai
Romance de hajimaru meiro
Mitsukete kuremasu ka?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Invocations and Witches Sometimes Have to Be Ready"!
Divine what the episode will be about, Nina.
Before I do, there's something
I want to talk to you about, Saku.
Huh?
"Invocations and Witches
Sometimes Have to Be Ready"
Well, Nono went and...