Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
Onee-chan, wake up!
Onee-chan, where's that hair ornament you bought?
Let me borrow it!
Sheesh!
Onee-chan, you're sleeping with your glasses on again!
I've told you the frame will bend-
Ow...
The President is Onee-chan
Unbelievable!
Those glasses are a part of my body!
I'm sorry, Onee-chan.
Haruka said that she knows an optician,
so I'll ask if she can get them fixed.
Haruka-san again?
All you talk about is Haruka-san, each and every day,
even more than you did when you were in middle school.
It's not like you're lovers or anything.
F
i
z
Human-powered pot.
That's nice.
Warm mine up, too.
I wonder what she's hiding.
That's suspicious.
Don't drop your crumbs everywhere!
I know that she used to come over and play when Yuu was in middle school, but...
Recollection?
Since you're sick, I'll come back some other time.
Y-Yeah.
Since I always had a cold...
A cold
High school field trip
...or was on a high school field trip,
Imagination
I've never actually seen her face.
I've only ever seen her shoes.
I wonder what Takayama Haruka looks like!
What are you doing?!
The staff ate the food afterwards
Sakura
Ah, Class Rep-san is back!
What did the teacher want?
We're going to choose the members of the ball game tournament committee.
Ball game tournament?
There are only three first-year classes,
so we're not having an athletic festival for financial reasons.
No way!
We're really not going to have an athletic festival?!
Bad luck
for friends
before noon,
good luck after
Very unlucky
Very Lucky
Lucky
11am-1pm
Very Lucky
Lucky
11am-1pm
Good luck
before noon,
bad luck after
What an unlucky day!
I broke my sister's glasses, too!
I'm sorry for rubbing salt into the wound,
but you've got supplementary lessons after school, Yuu.
Yuu-chan!
Athletic...
Athletic festival...
Yuu-chan, you wanted an athletic festival?
Yeah.
Wouldn't a ball game tournament be nice too?
But...
In a ball game tournament, I can't be...
...a cheerleader.
Yeah, that's right!
You're right!
Come to think of it,
is the student council president your sister, Yuu?
We met a little while ago and she told me that her little sister is in my class.
Really?
Yep.
I've never seen your sister before, have I?
You know, she gave the welcome speech for new students at the entrance ceremony.
What?
I slept through that.
Huh?
Geez, Haruka-san...
You guys saw, didn't you?
Sorry, we were sleeping.
Hey, now.
There you are, Sonoda!
Get to your supplementary lessons!
Yes!
Ah, she was called away.
Yuu-chan...
So one got away, huh?
From what?
I have something to ask all of you.
Would anyone like to join the committee?
What?
No way!
That's it, Harupoppo.
Huh?
Join the committee and tell them what
Yuu-chan said about cheerleaders this morning.
Ah
I see!
That's a good idea!
The teachers said that if you join, your PE grades may improve.
I'll do it!
I want to do it too!
If Kotone does it...
Hey!
After school
Student Council Conference Room
It was nice that Yuzu-chan used her common sense and gave in, wasn't it?
Yeah.
I'll have to do my best for Yuu-chan!
Yuzu-chan used...
Class 1-A...
Takayama Haruka?
Ball Game Tournament          Committee Member List by Class
(1-A)
Class Representative     Ikeno Kaede
Committee Member       Takayama Haruka
' '                        Noda Kotone
Class Representative     Altazure Roset
Committee Member       Orillion Conk
(1-B)
Haruka?!
Could it be...?!
Hey, Rina?
Yes?
Which of them is Takayama Haruka-san?
Takayama-san?
I think that's her.
The one with semi-long hair.
I don't have my glasses, so...
Which one?
Which one is she?
Ball Game Tournament Committee Meeting
President
Vice President
Secretary
I'm the student council president, Sonoda Mitsuki, from class 3-C.
I'm the vice president, Sakai Rina, also from class 3-C.
I'm the secretary, Otokawa Sumi, from class 2-B.
Ball Game Tournament Committee Meeting
President
Vice President
Secretary
Thank you for taking on the responsibility of being committee members.
As you all know, we are no longer having an athletic festival.
She is Yuu-chan's sister.
She's so different from Yuu-chan!
I'm getting nervous.
Kotone-chan, are you going to cheer me up?
Shake
Oh, they're shaking!
She's just playing with me!
Shake
Softball
Dodgeball
Volleyball
Basketball
Football
President
Vice President
Secretary
This is the final list of events.
Are there any other suggestions?
How about having cheerleaders in addition to the ball games?
Okay! I can do it!
That is, umm...
Class 1-A.
Yes.
President Mitsuki looks really angry!
I can't see...
What should I do?
How dare you defile my precious little sister?
Uh, well...
Harupoppo, let me help you.
Say it after me.
President
President Mitsuki.
President Mitsuki!
Yes?
Your little sister...
...is who...
...I want!
No!
Little sister?
We're talking about the ball game tournament right now.
We can discuss other things after the meeting.
T-That's not it!
She's really pissed!
But I can't give up!
Harupoppo, fight!
I need to do something with impact to break the ice!
Pop
P-President Mitsuki, wouldn't you like cute girls to cheer you on?
How about having cheerleaders at the ball game tournament?
President
Secretary
Softball
Dodgeball
Volleyball
Basketball
Football
Cheerleaders?
That's an interesting suggestion, but we can't do that.
Since the school will be closing in three years,
we won't be getting any money from the city.
That's why we have to keep our expenditures for the ball game tournament low.
It's a shame that you first-years won't even get to have an athletic festival,
but that's how it is and there is nothing we can do.
B-But President Mitsuki has been visiting the staff room all of the last month trying to arrange an athletic festival.
She really has been trying!
And with that, the meeting is dismissed.
There.
Kotone-chan...
Why did I join the committee?
And I even did something that embarrassing...
Harupoppo.
We won't have an athletic festival next year or the year after that.
And it'll be the same when we graduate.
If we miss this chance, Yuu-chan will never get to be a cheerleader.
But there's nothing we can do.
You know, people were against me living at Shizuku-chan's house.
But...
I overcame it.
We only have these three years,
and you don't want to have any regrets, do you?
Hey, President Mitsuki!
Stick
H-Hey, what's this?
U-Um...
I want to have cheerleaders, no matter what!
My friend said that she'll be sad if she can't be a cheerleader!
I want to make sure she can be one, no matter what!
Hey, you...
That friend has been helping me out since the 2nd year of middle school.
It's my turn to return the favour!
Please let her be a cheerleader!
I won't let go until you agree!
What a strange girl.
She's going this far for her friend.
Got it.
I'll talk to the school about having cheerleaders.
Thank you so much!
What is your name?
I'm Takayama Haruka, from class 1-A.
Ah, T-Taka...
W-What should we do?
She isn't moving!
P-President Mitsuki!
Sakura
Another day
Is President Mitsuki home?
She is, but she's studying for entrance exams.
She'll totally flip out if you disturb her.
But I brought her green tea cream puffs...
Green tea cream puffs?!
I'll cool them!
Haruka-san?
The strawberry ones look delicious too!
Give me half of yours!
Give me, give me!
Please!
I suppose.
I don't want it after all.
You don't want it?
Well, I'll eat it then.
So good!
These were only on sale today, you know.
Yuu-chan, you won't be able to eat one until next year.
Though there's no guarantee they'll have them again next year.
Too bad!
That hurt, Yuu-chan!
Haruka.
Hm?
Kaede-chan told me that you're the
reason why we'll have cheerleaders.
Normally you wouldn't join a committee by yourself.
Actually you're rather bad at that kind of stuff.
That makes me happy.
Show me what the strawberry one tastes like.
Give me... a little bit.
I'm melting...
I'm turning into cream...
So sweet.
I want to...
...melt more...
...with Yuu-chan.
This is more delicious.
I want to see Haruka-san again.
This is the best chance I'll get!
Sister
After all, she got my glasses fixed.
I have to thank her!
Calm down!
Keep your cool!
I wonder what they're talking about.
What's this sound?
What?
This is my heartbeat?!
Sheesh, I just want to get a look at her.
I'm overthinking this!
Yuu, Haruka-san, how about a drink?
I'm coming in-
Throb
The President is Onee-chan                          The End
Pool Cleaning Promise
Haruka, I forgot my swimsuit.
Huh?
I was sure I grabbed it this morning...
Ta-da!
I thought you might forget yours,
Haruka
so I brought another one!
Thank you, Haruka!
Yuu-chan
Haruka
What's this?!
I worked really hard making it yesterday!
I'm fine, you can have it back.
What, why?
What are we going to do if I wear this and people ask questions?
It'll be fine!
Yuu-chan
Haruka
It's cute, isn't it?
Yuu-chan
Haruka
That's not the problem!
Are you okay with it, Haruka?
Sheesh, Yuu-chan, you're such a spoiled child.
Want to switch with me?
I wonder if it'll fit.
If I rip this off, I can wear it!
Stop that!
What are you doing?!
I'll rip yours off too!
Give it to me!
No one will figure it out with just this!
If the secret leaks out, our relationship will be over!
This isn't enough to end it!
This is beyond their usual flirting.
And anyway,
why are we the only ones who have to clean the pool?
But as reward, our class gets to use the pool first.
What, when?
Tomorrow.
Really?
Really.
There's no helping it then.
Okay, everyone, let's clean every bit!
Yeah!
Hey you!
Sakura
Hey, aren't you all just fooling around?
Well, isn't that okay?
We rarely get opportunities like this.
You can play volleyball.
Do it on the beach.
You can bury people!
Do it on the beach!
You can enjoy your vacation!
Just go do that on the beach!
Yuu-chan!
Look! Look!
See?
That's beautiful!
If you spray it higher, won't it make an even bigger rainbow?
Want to try?
Yuzu-chan, sorry!
How dare they do that...
There!
I'll put them through it as well!
Finishing blow!
Geez...
Haruka, hide!
It's showing through!
Yuu, what's wrong?
What's going on?
N-Nothing at all!
Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan.
Look at this!
Why are you stripping?
Huge!
N-No, not that...
Look closely!
This part right here.
What is it?
T-That's enough!
Yuzu-chan and Kaede-chan don't have to see it!
Ah,
Haruka has a D-cup?
She's a C-cup!
H-Hey, look!
Wow, some princesses are on vacation!
When did they...
When Kotone-chan and Shizuku-chan are alone, they look so mature.
They're just talking about dinner, though.
If Yuu-chan and I can end up like that....
Haruka!
There's a water strider over there!
Yuu-chan doesn't get it!
We'll never finish at this rate.
Hey, Yuzu.
Huh?
Your thighs are a bit fat, aren't they?
With summer approaching, shouldn't you try to work on that?
From here
Maybe going from one side to the other will help.
To here
Try it out!
From here
Rock, paper, scissors!
With five papers, the loser is obvious.
Yuu-chan, we'll leave the storage room cleaning to you.
What?
I wanted to keep playing in the pool.
Wait, everyone.
I actually had scissors which you all mistook for paper.
So let's play another round, okay?
So if Haruka and Yuu are the only two objecting...
We'll leave the storage room cleaning to you!
That's how this turned out?!
Pool Equipment Storage
Wow.
The storage room for a school that's
about to close really is something, huh?
This seems endless.
Here, Haruka.
Broom and dustpan.
Thank you!
You're so well prepared!
Wait, I'm going to do the sweeping?
What are you going to do?
I'm in charge of water.
It's time to face reality!
Wow, there's so much dust.
We should open a window.
Window, window...
So high!
Yuu-chan?
Hey-
Y-Yuu-chan!
Come now, onwards!
S-She's heavy!
I can't do this!
Her swimsuit is wet...
Haruka, get a bit closer!
I can't!
Got it!
Cherry blossoms?
Why are there cherry blossoms at this time of year?
No, look closer.
These are artificial.
Artificial?
It seems that the members of the
swimming club did a lot of different things.
Even though it'll be summer soon,
there are still cherry blossoms in the air.
It feels miraculous.
Just like back then.
Yuu-chan, your nose.
Yeah, I know there are flowers.
I didn't mean that.
Your nose!
I know?
Geez, I'm saying nose!
Knows?
She still hasn't figured it out!
Okay, I'll have to...
Yuu-chan.
No, not that!
Sorry.
It came off!
You had a petal on your nose.
You didn't seem to notice.
Yuu-chan?
Yuu-chan!
It seems she got angry.
There's still one more.
Turn this way.
Where?
I'll take it off myself, so just tell me.
Here.
You princesses, get to work!
We are!
Spray some water over there.
Where are you spraying?
I heard they were cleaning the pool after school...
Take that!
I won't!
We won't finish like this!
I can't see Yuu.
Huh?
I feel like giving up already!
Haruka-san isn't there either.
Sister
Could they be skipping out to do something like that again?!
Swish
There's no way!
Sister
What's come over me?
Yuu's probably at her supplementary lessons.
I'm worrying too much.
I should go home.
Huh, there's some trash...
Yuu-chan
Haruka
Pool Cleaning Promise                             The End
Yay
Won't you kiss
Kiss and love
futari dake no jikan ga
二人だけの時間が
Time for just the two of us
futari dake no himitsu ga
二人だけの秘密が
A secret for just the two of us
futari dake no yakusoku
二人だけの約束
A promise between just the two of us
aru kara ne
あるからね
We have all of them
yorokobi wakachiaete kanashimi wakeaetara
喜び分かち合えて 悲しみ分け合えたら
If we share our joys and split our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
一人より幸せに なれるように
We may be able to become happier than if we were alone
ashita mo omoide wo saa fuyasou
明日も思い出をさあ増やそう
Let's make more memories tomorrow as well
ippai ni shichaou ne
一杯にしちゃおうね
Let's make a lot of them!
Love you
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
この広い世界で 逢えた奇跡
I came across a miracle in this wide world
tokubetsu na no anata janai to dame dakara
特別なの あなたじゃないとだめだから
But it's no good if you're not special to me
futari janai to dekinai koto da yo
二人じゃないとできないことだよ
It's something we can't do if we're not together
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
いますぐに 大好き kiss and love
I love you now, kiss and love
Love
Preview
Iizuka Yuzu here!
I'm Ikeno Kaede.
Hey, I wonder if I really have fat thighs.
Well, some people like that.
I don't want them to only like my thighs!
You're perfect! Every part of you is perfect!
Uh, well, it's just that Kotone and Haruka were being weird.
I don't want to be consoled!
Next time: Trick 4.
A Sour Plan
Perhaps A Test of Courage?
"A Sour Plan" and "Perhaps a Test of Courage?"
Look forward to it!
So your tears were fake after all!