Yakisoba
The Culture Festival is
just around the corner.
Bzz-bzz. Bzz-bzz. Bzz-bzz.
Bzz-bzz. Bzz-bzz.
Squat lower!
Brainwashing beam!
Bzz-bzz.
Bzz-bzz. Bzz-bzz. Bzz-bzz.
Everybody has managed
to band together.
Vice President, we're running
low on posters.
Got it. I'll ask for more copies—
Vice President, about the assignments
for the schoolyard...
Oh, those should be complete.
And now they're working like mad.
What do you think?
I'm trying the costume on.
Whoa!
That's adorable!
You're brilliant!
So dazzling, it's blinding!
Not bad at all.
Watch me shine too!
Kushieda, about your costume...
I have to say...
This isn't...too bad.
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Ohashi High School Culture Festival
(Part Two)
- Another exhausting day...
- Got that right.
Hey, do I smell sweaty?
Think I'll be okay without a shower?
Oh, you're having dinner with your old man.
Answer the question, mongrel!
Th-That hurt...
But no, you don't stink.
How should I put this...?
Your old man's trying really hard.
Despite his busy work schedule, he's making
time to pick you up every night,
and takes you out for dinner.
It's not nearly enough to make
me forget what he's done.
But I guess...
he knows some good places, so I might
as well humor him for a bit.
What is it?
I didn't say anything!
That's...
Jeez...
He's early. I won't have time to change.
That's your dad's car?
You better not be thinking
that I'm getting excited!
I'm not! I swear!
Go on, he's waiting for you.
Her old man's really been trying hard.
Desperate, I'm sure, to make up
for lost time and regain her trust.
But he's not the only one making an effort.
Taiga's also...
trying her best to respond to his feelings.
Brainwashing beam.
Bzz-bzz.
Out late again tonight?
I guess...
So...
About the Culture Festival...
The Pro Wrestling Show!
People! The Culture Festival is tomorrow!
Let's get psyched!
Yeah!
Hey, where's all the makeup?
Oh, it's...
Go on.
But asking Dumb-chi for a favor
makes me feel so dirty!
Now, now...
Just suck it up.
What're you grinning about, creep?
Be nice...
Your old man said he's
coming to watch, right?
Just get it over with!
Stay right here for ten minutes!
Don't come in until I'm done
talking with Dumb-chi!
Yeah, yeah.
H-Hey there, Takasu-kun.
Could you step aside?
S-Sure...
Thanks!
Yuck, what is this?
You're giving me a present?
There's gotta be a catch.
Yuck, Dumb-chi.
Why would you assume that?
Please enjoy!
What are you doing!?
No way!
Are these from that famous restaurant!?
I went there with my dad last night.
Thought I'd get you a souvenir.
My modeling friends said these
are impossible to get...
Go on, try one.
Right now?
Yeah, eat one.
No way.
I wanna savor them at home with some tea—
Try one right now, this minute, this second!
Fine!
I'll try one, okay?
You ate one.
Yummy, yummy.
There. Satisfied?
Now get away from me.
But you ate one, right?
So listen up.
Excuse me?
So there was a catch!
For the Culture Festival wrestling show,
trade roles with me once.
I want to try a bigger part!
Wow...
Taiga wants to play the lead?
Yeah, her dad's coming to the festival,
so she wants to look good.
Kushieda, you basically know
her family situation, right?
They've been trying to patch up
their relationship as of late—
What the hell?
Kushieda?
What the hell do you mean?
That's crap.
W-Wait!
What brought this on?
I have to wake Taiga up.
What?
I have to tell her she can't trust
that lousy father of hers.
Why would you say such a terrible thing?
Shouldn't you be happy
for Taiga, as her friend?
Happy?
Me?
Why would I?
Because...
Why would I be happy about my friend's
dad slinking back to trick her?
I could never smile and watch
while my friend's being hurt.
Trade! Trade!
Stop it! I hear you!
That's a bit much!
Don't label him a lost cause when
you don't know the facts!
Taiga's old man is a loving father who—
You met him.
So how can you say that?
Takasu-kun!
Were you even paying attention
when you met him!?
Did you take a good look at him!?
What's that supposed to mean?
Ha—
Hang on!
Ry-Ryuji...
Minorin...
C-C'mon, shake hands!
R-Ryuji...
I want to die...
You're in my favorite spot.
Move it.
H-Hey!
There, a perfect fit.
See? This spot is mine.
Hey...
What did Kushieda do?
Went home.
Seriously? Oh, man...
Pretty gutsy of you to scream
at the girl you like.
She started it.
Unbelievable...
I never thought I'd hear her talk like that.
Wow, that's obnoxious.
Badmouthing her behind her back isn't
going to earn you any sympathy.
Don't want any.
Well, let's go back and
run a dress rehearsal.
But I just ruined the festive atmosphere...
It's all good.
I covered for you.
Come on.
You can go back if I'm with you, right?
You've really changed.
Is that how it seems?
I want to change, too.
What should I do?
Don't depend on others.
Figure it out yourself.
Ah, Kawashima...
I won't cling to you the way the tiger does.
And I won't become your shining
sun, the way Minori-chan is.
Yeah, so you said.
That we're on equal ground.
I take that back.
I, Kawashima Ami, will walk
the same path as you.
It's just that I'll always be one step ahead.
Ryu-chan, hurry up!
I'm starving to death here.
You come home so late these days.
Don't blame me. I've gotta help
prepare for the Culture Festival.
It'll be done soon.
Okay...
So...I heard Taiga-chan's moving.
Who told you that?
Well...
- I was taking a nap, but it got noisy outside...
- Let's patch it before we sell the place.
The furniture can be thrown away.
Oh, hello there.
Sorry about the noise.
This man claimed to be Taiga-chan's father,
and he said the apartment's too small
for the two of them to live in.
O-Oh...
Really...?
Y'know...
That's pretty selfish of him.
Don't you agree?
He waltzes back into her life...
And out of the blue...
Not you, too!
Uh, well...
Isn't this a good thing?
Two family members starting
over in a new home...
It's terrible!
I don't want Taiga-chan to leave!
She's part of our family!
Oh, come on...
This is awful!
Why didn't Taiga-chan tell me?
That's so hot!
You mean, "That's so cold."
She isn't back yet?
Tomorrow's the big day.
Her old man could have been
more considerate...
No...
If that's what Taiga wants, it's fine.
Everything's going well...
Hey, welcome back.
Thanks.
What do you need help with tonight?
Is it—
This isn't about me. It's about Minorin.
You need to apologize.
I...
don't feel that I said anything wrong.
That's not the point.
It's not about who was right or wrong.
There are more important issues at hand.
That's why you two need
to kiss and make up.
Anyway, go say you're sorry.
Got it?
"The Pro Wrestling Show!"
Author: Haruta Koji
And just like that...
it was the morning
of the Culture Festival.
Ohashi High Festival
Want some yakisoba?
The Pro Wrestling Show!
Dang, that's one long line!
Holy moly! What do we do?
Chill out, Haruta.
How can you say that to me, Taka—
Hey, stop fooling around.
What?
What're you trying to do!?
Stupid dog with your deadly face!
I was just...
After that scene I made yesterday,
I figured I'd try harder
to act like a villain.
You're trying too hard!
You're just fine at the half-assed level!
- What does that even mean?
- Anyway, did you apologize?
Uh, not yet...
What's wrong with you?
If you don't hurry, you won't get
to enjoy the festival with her...
Am I? Really?
Yes! Absolutely!
- Only you could pull off this look!
- Man, you look pathetic.
Take that!
- Take that, and that, and that!
- Hey! What're you—!?
Keep it down, guys.
The time has come!
The front desk reports that we've
already filled 80 percent of the seats.
At this rate, we might reach
standing-room-only!
- Are you for real!?
- That's more than last year!
We slacked last year and nobody showed!
I figured we'd have no chance
with a wrestling show.
Man, I'm starting to get nervous!
Okay! Now then...
Best of luck to the first performance
of 2-C's wrestling show!
Fight!
On!
The Pro Wrestling Show!
New Message
2-C's wrestling show...
2-C's wrestling show is insane?
Yeah?
You mean, it's good?
I heard Kawashima Ami wears
an ultra-short miniskirt!
I heard the Palm-top Tiger and
Takasu the Delinquent are a riot!
I-Is that...
the legendary treasure of our class!?
That's right!
The super-valuable, top-secret treasure—
Our homeroom teacher's
soulmate-finding red string!
Stop!
Anything but that!
Weren't you fellow members of class 2-C!?
Man, I'm starting to get butterflies.
We're on soon.
Taiga?
U-Uh-huh, got it!
Now, Lady Palm-top Tiger!
Come forth!
Bzz-bzz. Bzz-bzz. Bzz-bzz.
Lady Tiger! Your command!
How will we dispose of this red thread!?
Huh?
Um...
C-Cuts it!
Did she just slip up?
Yep.
She sure did.
Repeat your line.
C-Cut it!
Roger!
No, don't! Tha—
Stop!
Don't cut that!
Whoo! Yuri-chan's crashing the stage!
- This is a new twist!
- Hey!
This isn't in the script!
We don't have a choice...
Noto!
Right!
Shadow Army!
Take our homeroom teacher to the morgue!
My soulmate-finding red striiiiing!
What's a morgue?
A place for storing corpses.
No!
Ami-chan!
Keep it going!
Oh! How cruel!
My friends have all been brainwashed!
Whatever shall I do!?
God sees all!
Warrior Ami!
If you can truly touch their hearts,
you will be able to free their minds.
Now, let us begin.
Please attempt to answer this question.
It may provide a critical opportunity
to turn the tide.
- Is that...?
- I knew it...
What is the name of the most
beautiful person on Earth?
It's...
Kawashima Ami!
Excellent.
Wh-What were we doing!?
Ami-chan!
Saved!
Us!
Ooh!
Doo wa!
Curse you!
What a cheap trick!
U-Unfor...
Unforgiba...
Unforgivable, Kawashima Ami!
Off you go!
Whoa! I can't see!
What is this!?
Now, it's time for today's main event!
The Palm-top Tiger vs. Kawashima Ami!
Fight!
Heave-ho!
Bam!
Upsy-daisy!
Amazing!
Awesome!
Ami-chan!
Look behind you!
Y-You're mine!
Whoosh!
Y-You bastards!
You've been getting too lucky!
You even went to Ami-chan's beach house!
Here we go, tiger shrimp!
What? Wait...
Ready and...
Ow, ow, ow...
Ack, my back just cramped up!
Hang on a little longer.
I'll be in that position once we trade!
The Pro Wrestling Show!
Oh, yeah!
It was a huge success!
Yay!
Man...
It gets stuffy under this bald cap...
So, about the next performance.
Could you point the spotlight
a little higher, and...
No new messages.
Welcome home, Master.
I-It's not like I care if you
drink my tea or anything!
Welcome, my princess!
Your prince has come for you!
Is it just me, or are there cosplay
cafes everywhere?
Kinda cheapens it.
Ooh, what a festive atmosphere.
And we've attracted a big crowd.
Yes!
The vice president went to nearby
schools and promoted our festival.
Man...
The first performance was quite a success.
Yeah.
If we can keep this up, the next one will be...
Yo, Earth to Taiga.
You're eating your ribbon.
That crepe must be really good.
Mind if I try a corner?
Not bad at all.
H-Have as much as you w-want...
Oh, how generous of you.
Kitamura...
You're such a...
Ta-Taiga?
Ry-Ryuji, you have some too!
Oh, it's my turn to be on
student council patrol.
Sorry.
You guys can head back without me.
You trying to choke me!?
Kitamura-kun's...
Kitamura-kun's saliva...
Well, it's almost time for the next show.
I know.
Cheer up.
You're the one who shoved it into my mouth.
I know that!
Oh yeah, did you get a message
from your old man?
What!?
You've been staring at
your cell phone all day.
I was playing a game.
While waiting to go on stage?
Well, there are a few more shows left.
You can get Kawashima to trade
with you once he comes...
Quit worrying about me!
You need to focus on Minorin!
Woo-hoo! A complete success!
Yo, semi-lead characters!
You rocked!
Th-Thanks.
In the end...
Taiga never got to play the lead.
All performances have concluded!
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
Was I just blind, like Kushieda said?
That can't be...
Because...
That means I'm a total...
A total buffoon!