When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Hey, Nagi!
I came to play with ya!
Jump! Jump, Tama!
Meow...
What're ya doin'?
Ah, Saku. As you can see,
I'm giving Tama exercise.
Exercise?
The truth is, she watched ferocious
beasts leaping through flaming rings
Zaendo Nagi Sanzenin
just earlier on a circus show on TV
and she decided it was
the perfect exercise for Tama.
That about sums it up.
Now, jump! If a circus cat can do it,
there's no way you can't!
Meow.
Ya moron!
Why did you suddenly do that?!
There's no way he can jump
through a tiny ring like that!
Or rather, animal abuse is even more risky
than mentionin' copyrighted works!
Don't ya know they've gone over 'n
over it in the writers' meetings?!
Hah! Even if a scriptwriter
or two get fired,
it's not as if they'll drop
the main heroine from the show.
The Devouring of Dirt Nagi Sanzenin
Um, both of you, such borderline
conversations are a bit...
Meow.
There, there. Nothin' to be scared of now.
Hey, don't get attached to Saku!
You're my pet, remember?!
Wow, I didn't know you were so good
with animals, Sakuya.
Well, it's not just animals, though.
Right, Nagi?
Wh-Why are you saying that to me?!
How true. Nagi used to
adore Sakuya like a big sister...
Don't, Maria!
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Is it one of those so-called
youthful indiscretions
that you don't want to admit to?
Shut up!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Do You Like Pretty Rich Big Sisters?
Wow!
So, Miss, you used to call
Sakuya "Big Sister Saku"?
Humph! A thing of the unpleasant past!
I've got tons of younger siblings,
so I often looked after Nagi along
with the rest of 'em.
She was so cute.
When she was little, she used to
want Sakuya's attention all the time...
I told you to stop talking about it!
You've never looked after li'l kids,
and that's why ya still haven't
grown outta bein' a kiddy.
Don't mock me! If I had younger siblings,
I could look after them
way better than you, Saku!
For real? Then prove it.
Very well!
Hey, Hayate!
Yes?
A-And why do I have to
dress up like this again?
So cute!
Rejoice! You look really
good in that, Hayate!
That does not make me happy!
Wait, why do I have to dress like a girl?!
Well, don't sweat the details.
I will look after you now!
Seek my attention all you like!
I see...
But what in the world should I do
to seek your attention?
Oh, you're so dense!
You know, call me "Dear Sister Nagi"
and you just have to cry and cling to me.
I-I see...
Dear Sister Nagi!
Ah, what's the matter?
Dear Sister!
You...
*Conceptual Footage
...insolent bastard!
Taking advantage of the confusion
to do something perverted?!
I don't recall raising you
to be such a naughty child!
Please forgive me, Miss.
I mean, Dear Sister Nagi...
Well, butler-in-debt?
Takin' care of Nagi's not easy, right?
This is nothing unusual, though.
I just can't get in the mood
because you're not a real child!
A real child?
That's right!
This estate has lots of
out-of-the-way places and jungles
where two or three children
could have easily strayed into!
Hayate, go find children this instant!
That is easy for you to say, but...
I have things like this
prepared for you, too...
U-Understood!
She really is such a willful child.
But I wonder what Hayate plans to do...
She asked for real children, but...
Well, if it comes down to it,
he'll just hafta kidnap 'em from somewhere.
I have brought them!
WHAT?!
What's goin' on?! Don't tell me
ya really kidnapped 'em!
Y-You have the wrong idea!
Please calm down, Sakuya!
Lost?
Yes, they were wandering around the
gate, so I took them in for their safety.
They're apparently on vacation
and became separated from their parents.
It's not like they're Isumi.
Why'd they stray into a place like this?
At any rate, we should call the police.
Nooo!
Oh, dear. They may not like it, but...
There is nothing to be scared of.
It's not as if he police will
suddenly attack you with an Ingram.
Take that!
They won't mobilize Special
Vehicles Section 2 for lost kids!
What does it matter?
Miss?
We just happened to be
in need of children anyway.
We will look after them for a while.
Ya moron! They're not pets, ya know!
There's no way ya can just...
Thank you, very rich big sister!
Rich big sister!
Ah, you guys are cute. What are your names?
I'm Itsuki!
I'm Shunji!
Nice to meet you, very rich big sister!
Hayate, it seems I have a knack
for it that makes children like me!
Uh-huh...
But their parents are sure
to be worried by now.
Oh, that's not a problem.
Summon the SP Unit!
Yes, ma'am!
Listen up!
On the honor of the Sanzenin family SP Unit,
find the parents of these
two brothers, no matter what!
Yes, ma'am!
Just you wait.
I'll get you back
to your parents in no time.
Th-Thank you, but you can take your time.
We're not in a big hurry.
Starting now, you two
are my little brothers!
I'll look after you with plenty of care!
Really?!
What are you going to do
for us, rich big sister?
Now, now, you are to address me
as Dear Sister Nagi.
Yes, Dear Sister Nagi!
What is the matter, Sakuya?
Ow!
Oh, I just had somethin' on my mind.
Y-You didn't have to hit me...
Now, then...
While I said I would look after them,
what in the world am I supposed to do?
Dear Sister Nagi, how much is this vase?
Huh? That's at best about 10 million.
Hey, what about this painting?
That's probably no more
than 30 million, too.
Awesome!
Hey, Nagi.
What is it, Saku?
I'm gonna leave somethin'
of mine here for a bit.
I don't mind.
It's a treasure of mine that's worth
way more than yer ordinary junk,
so don't ya dare touch it.
I don't really have any
interest in your belongings.
Well, I'll leave it in yer care.
All right!
Now, I'll show you guys
even more amazing treasures!
Treasures?
We wanna see!
There, read whatever book you like!
This is treasure?
What's wrong?
They're all über-rare doujinshis.
I feel like she isn't
doing anything different
from what she usually does alone...
Indeed.
It seems you guys still don't understand.
Can't show it, even on DVD
Look! This book is said to be
one of only 200 copies in the world
and it contains the mythical
final chapter of YuYu Hakusho...
Ya moron!
What did you do that for, Saku?!
How is this lookin' after 'em?!
Yer dealin' with little kids here!
There're better things to do!
For example, read a picture book to them.
What? What a pain...
Don't make the sort of face
that kids'll wanna copy.
Besides, this room
is dedicated to doujinshis!
Of course, there aren't any books
for young children!
Ya got it all wrong!
If ya don't give 'em things
that kids are more likely to enjoy,
what's the point?!
Things kids are likely to enjoy?
I know! Do you guys like animals?
Animals?
We like them!
Rarr...
What's wrong? You said you liked
animals, so I brought him here.
Go on, play with him.
Um, there's the danger that they
might get eaten before they can play...
Indeed.
Ya moron!
Why do you keep doing that, Saku?!
Ya guys wanna hurry up
and get outta this room, right?
We do, we do!
Sheesh, you guys are so spoiled.
Then, next, we'll go to the game room...
Hold it!
Rather than stayin' inside,
it's better for li'l kids to play outside!
Don't just decide that!
I said I would look after these guys...
Outside is good!
We'll play outside!
Wha?!
Majority rule. It's settled.
Too rich for my blood.
(Takou te kanawanwa.)
Wahoo! Wahoo!
(Wahooi! Wahooi!)
Oh, hey!
I'm a proudly independent
online game warrior.
Why must I play a Showa era game like this?
Sheesh, ya really have no stamina, do ya?
Shut up! And you're
the one who suggested this!
Why are you taking it so easy?!
Hey!
Haha! Nagi, you slowpoke!
We dare you to come get us!
Damn them... Returning my
kindness with ingratitude...
Call me Dear Sister!
Miss, shall I take your place?
Mind your own business!
I'll catch you guys for sure!
Yay!
One! Two...
She really is competitive, isn't she?
Well, it's very like her, though.
She hasn't changed one bit.
She used to be extremely
shy 'round strangers.
She didn't even talk
to me much to begin with.
Well, she was surrounded
by adults who were after her fortune,
so it's no surprise.
Yo!
Hey, wanna go play explorers?
What?
Th-That's okay...
Well, just c'mon.
It was slow goin', but she eventually
started playin' with everyone...
I had no idea.
Ninety-nine! One hundred!
All right!
Sanzenin Roadblock
Wh-What could this be?
Hello.
Might you be one of their parents?
Parents...?
Oh, please! I don't have any children!
I mean, forget about even going
that far with the guy I like,
about all we've done is hold hands.
Oh, and resting his head in my lap.
Wait...
Look what you made me say!
I-In front of Ogikubo Station.
Still have not identified
anyone fitting the description...
Over.
Not here in front of Mitaka Station.
Not here are Oizumigakuen!
Not here in Anime Town, Kami-igusa!
Darn it! Find them! Find them!
Go over every train station
with a fine tooth comb!
Whew! I'm tired!
That was fun!
How 'bout it? Feels good
to play outside, too, doesn't it?
Humph! I was not playing.
I was only looking after these guys.
But...
It really must be nice to have siblings...
Nagi...
All right!
I'm going to do this!
I feel like I can do good this time!
What?! Don't tell me...
Dear Sister Nagi will now
cook a fantastic feast!
Ooh!
Miss, are you going to be okay?
Perhaps we should help you, too...
Ah-ah! No need to worry!
I won't mess up again like last time.
You guys be good and wait, all right?
Okay!
All right, it's done.
Itsuki, Shunji, thanks for waiting.
Ooh!
Uh, hold on a second.
Here, say, "Ah."
Oh, I was afraid of that...
Miss, are you all right?
I am fine, Hayate!
I cannot allow something
like this to defeat me.
On my honor as the next
head of the Sanzenin family!
Hey, let's go.
Fighting spirit alone will
not improve your cooking.
What? Okay...
I'll help you, too.
Okay... Thanks.
Good grief.
Oh? Where did those kids go?
She said this contained
really valuable treasure.
Hey, Bro, let's not do this.
What we're doing is bad.
What are you saying, now that we're here?!
We finally snuck into a filthy rich house!
B-But...
I figured it was somethin' like this.
I got a big whiff of somethin' shady
goin' on right from the get go.
Well, it's nothin' to me
if ya steal that cheap stuff from me.
But ya know...
...if ya make my partner cry,
I'll never forgive ya!
Sh-She's scary!
Hey!
What in the world...?
Hold it right there!
What's going on, Sakuya?
We can talk later. Let's go after 'em!
A-All right!
By Nagi Sanzenin
What do you think?
Maria!
You did very well.
Hey! It's done for real this time!
Huh? Where are Itsuki and Shunji?
Come to think of it, Hayate's gone, too.
I never imagined those kids would...
They probably got their reasons,
but they got away before
I could press 'em for answers.
Maria!
What's going on, you two? In such a hurry...
The thing is...
Did something happen, Saku?
N-Nagi?!
Um, it turns out that those kids...
Moron! Don't say that!
Those kids? Has something
happened to Itsuki and Shunji?!
Y-Ya see, those guys...
A robber got into the residence just earlier
and kidnapped those two!
What?!
Maria, Itsuki and Shunji
are all right, aren't they?
They'll come back for sure, right?
Don't worry. The security robots
will be sure to find the robber.
We gotta find 'em before
the security robots spot 'em!
Sakuya, why did you do that earlier?
Nagi'd be hurt if she learned the truth.
Sakuya...
And besides, I'm worried 'bout them, too.
What should we do? Things have
gotten really crazy somehow.
They'll probably turn us over to the police.
Intruders detected! Intruders detected!
Bro!
Are we done for?!
Stop!
Makita! Kunieda!
Are you two both all right?
Y-Yeah...
Good grief.
Ya guys, not a word 'bout this to anyone.
We're sorry. We'll give this back.
So please don't turn us over to the police.
Don't worry. I won't hand ya
guys over to the police.
Really?!
Yeah, and ya guys can have that, too.
Keep it as a souvenir.
What? But...
This is an incredible treasure, right?
Try openin' it up.
Saku, what happened?! Did you find them?!
Man, I had it all wrong.
They weren't kidnapped.
What?
Then...
Itsuki and Shunji's
parents came to get them.
What?!
Seems they had some business they
suddenly had to rush home for.
They said they wanted to say good-bye to ya,
but they apparently didn't
even have time for that.
Oh, my, how sudden.
I see.
But they found their parents then.
I'm glad.
Miss...
Cheer up, Nagi.
Saku...
You've got us, remember?
Right!
It's doubtful the Sanzenin Miss
will ever battle loneliness again
or so it seemed on this long autumn night.
Next time, they will fight a super butler,
who looks somewhat familiar.
National Kiddy Comedy Competition
Why the heck?!
Give it a rest already!
Go for it! Become popular entertainers!
Why the heck?!
Rake it in and escape from poverty!
Give it a rest already!
Mistress Kuzuha, the autumn is deepening.
This Week's Butler Battle
Yes, indeed. My appetite
refuses to be quieted.
I agree, Mistress Kuzuha.
Come forth, Mysterious
Butler of Darkness No. 3!
Make Hayate Ayasaki...
...one of us!
It's a dead heat! This is getting exciting!
Speed! Energy!
The motor passionately
drives the four wheels!
National Mini 4WD Grand Prix
That's the fastest hobby
there is, the Mini 4WD!
Don't lose! Tear it up! My Emperor!
This is nothing! The next corner
will be the true battle!
I have to get to the bottom
of this ridiculous situation today!
Uh, um, who in the world...
Hmph! Time to dash!
I'm Mysterious Butler of Darkness Mini 4WD!
I have come to defeat you
at the request of a certain person!
"M-Mysterious"?
O-Oh, so that's the premise...
Uh, um, so who is this "certain person"?
Do you want to know? It's...
Uh-oh! This is a bad situation for them!
There's a storm raging across the course!
At this rate, both vehicles
will be thrown off the course!
At this rate...
Go!
Goal!
Hayate Ayasaki's machine,
the Hayate Magnum, is in first place!
I did it!
Damn it!
I'll win the next race for sure!
You Are Today's Champion!!
Congratulations, Hayate Ayasaki!
Thank you very much!
Huh?
I ended up dancing to their tune again.
But there's one thing I've figured out.
Someone...
Someone is out to get me!
What the heck are you saying
after all this time?
This Week's Butler Battle
The End
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
Ayumu Nishizawa's
Lettering by Mikako Takahashi
Ayumu Nishizawa's Butler Report!
Butler Report
Hey, there, it's Ayumu Nishizawa.
I hope you've all been well.
I've been put in charge of this
segment for a while to come.
Don't you think this song is a great song?
It's totally like "wavering maiden", right?
I'd love it if you all memorized it
and sang it at karaoke!
I don't know if it'll
get distributed, though.
You're the thieving hamster!
Oh, right, you're our guest today.
I heard that I'd get to see
Hayate if I came here...
He said he was going to
be late today. Too bad.
Crushed!
Bye-bye!
Preview
It seems Isumi is headed for this estate.
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
And she's coming alone!
Alone?
Please, help us!
Crap! This is bad!
Hallucinatin' in the middle of town is bad!
Calm down, Sakuya.
This fish is not a hallucination.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Devil Hunter Welcome
Yoko Isumi, and Nabeshin".
Next Hayate the Combat Butler
Devil Hunter Welcome Yoko Isumi, and Nabeshin
Wait, who in the world is
that afro-ish person?
Did you know?
I hear Nabeshin can't eat
things that are too hot.