Well then, shall we call it a day?
Yeah.
Huh?
What's the matter, Akihisa?
It's been acting strange since
the midterm we took the other day.
It disappeared.
Maybe you don't know how to use it that well?
Did you read the manual?
Let's see... "Do not touch it with wet hands.
Do not step on it.
Do not use it as a hand strap.
Do not give it to your girlfriend.
Do not pawn it.
Keep out of the reach of children."
I don't see anything out of
the ordinary written in here.
This is...
"For ages 13 and above."
That's it!
I'm over 13!
Everything but your mind is.
Th-That's not true! I've got many
books that are for 18 and over, too!
We'd like to hear all about them.
Depending on your answer...
Haven't you heard "the bird that
keeps quiet does not get shot"?
Hottoite sodatsu mono nanda nandarou
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
Deai mashite wa kantan sugiruyo
Saisho ni kimeta kotae wa hitotsu
Tokimeki mashita goukaku shimasuka?
Koi mo shoubu mo awatenai
Kotsu kotsu kotsu to tetsuya ni tameiki
Watashi no naka ni tensai dreamer
Omou koto mina kanaeba iina
Hito no sekai wa kinishinai
Perfect-area complete!
Zettai koko de matterunda
Perfect-area nozomu koe ga kikoeruyo
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? Tomaranai surechigai
Watashi ga soudan aite nara
"Tomodachi kai?" "Tomodachi desu."
Kanashiki rei ten dane
No! Yarinaoshi kakinaoshi
Honki de one more chance please
Ima yori suteki na mirai ga arunoni
Ima yori suteki ni my life, my life, my life!
Good morning, Aki. It's time to get up.
Hmm... Good morning, Sis.
Your breakfast is ready.
Since you're fighting Class A
in the Summoner Test War today,
for breakfast, I did something to help
give you luck so that you'll fight well.
You want to beat the enemy.
So I put steak and breaded pork cutlet...
--Really?!
--...pictures under your pillow.
What... Just pictures?
What do you think? You think you can win?
Your actions are so complicated that
I don't feel like you're supporting me.
You're right. You are at that age
where boys have a big appetite,
so I imagine pictures alone can't satisfy you.
I anticipated that might be the
case, so I got the actual food...
Really?!
...and made a video of me eating it.
Why a video?
More importantly, you
ate the steak by yourself?!
It was really tough. I worked
hard to eat it all when I was full.
Then you should've let me eat that!
Oh, you're so bold, Aki.
No!
What I want to eat is not this!
It's this!
Forget that, Aki.
Why aren't you telling me what
you think of me in a swimsuit?
There're so many things I wanna comment on
that I won't even have
time to get to your swimsuit!
Wait. Hey! Why are you eating in a swimsuit?
The director of photography told
me that you'd like it better that way.
Director of photography?
"Director of Photography: Muttsulini
Editor: Muttsulini Produced by: SILVER LINK."
Ah...
Fumizuki Academy follows
an action-oriented ideology.
Even if a student has high
academic ability, unless they can
exhibit that ability in actual tests,
their ability won't be acknowledged at all!
That was why you became a
Class F student, wasn't it, Mizuki?
I was told that staying healthy to get
ready for the test is also part of the test.
So we'll follow an
action-oriented ideology, too!
"Action-Oriented"
What do you mean?
It means that the battle has
started even before the bell rings.
Hideyoshi!
These're my big sister's personal belongings.
Her school uniform and her favorite books.
I don't know if we can use
anything in here against her.
This is enough. We'll figure something out.
Wow... Just what you'd expect from Class A.
I wonder how you solve this math problem.
Can I see it?
I'm good at math problems!
"Shinji"
"Yuuichi"
What?! Th... Th... This is...!
"I'll wait for you under the legendary tree"
There's no answer to this one, right?
This multiplication is too much for me.
To think that this is a formula that
even Himeji and Minami can't solve...
She really is incredible.
There's more stuff, too. Why are
they so expensive when they're so thin?
These have to be confiscated! Confiscated!
It's too early for Akihisa to see it!
Akihisa! Take that and
go declare war on Class A!
What? I don't wanna get beat up again.
You'll be fine this time.
Pretend that you found this favorite
book of hers and kindly deliver it to her.
I get it. Then she'll appreciate it
and listen to me gently, won't she?
Kinoshita! I found your book!
Nooo!
I won't believe anyone anymore.
Are you all heartless?!
Big Sister?!
I can't believe you did that!
I'll never forgive you!
So you've come to check out your new desk?
You must be kidding!
There's no way Class A will be
defeated by Class F, is there?!
Why don't you idiots give it a rest?!
Idi... ot.
I don't think she means that kind of "rest."
Idiots should just stay where they
belong, with the scum in Class F!
Quit bothering us!
You're wrong!
It's true that Class F's
academic performance isn't good.
But they're not scum!
But they're Class F, right?
Himeji. If things had gone normally,
you wouldn't have been in Class F, right?
Or are you someone who belongs in Class F?
Haven't you become a real
idiot during your time in Class F?
What a terrible thing to say! There's
no way she belongs in Class F, right?!
Akihisa... By saying that, you're
admitting that Class F is the worst.
Once the ST War is over, I'll give you
my cardboard box. Take good care of it.
You'll regret this after
school! Prepare yourself!
The first step of the plan is complete!
But how are we gonna fight Class A?
We can't win if we fight head-on.
We've already used Kirishima's
weakness before so that's no use.
Yeah, I don't think she'll
make the same mistake twice.
Why do you think we didn't exchange
equipment in the past when we won?
What?
The seeds I sowed have grown.
Now is the time to harvest!
A mock ST War?
Under normal circumstances, we
would've liked to officially declare war,
but we're unable to for three
months after our loss in the war.
Would you fight us for training?
We have a war with Class F starting
this afternoon. So we don't have time.
You guys attacked Class F when
they were weakened from their war.
Is that what you'd call Class A's dignity?
Well, I guess it would be
unseemly if you had to say you lost
because you were exhausted
from your fight with us, huh?
Are you saying that we'll lose to them?
Fine. We'll fight you as a
warm-up. Is that okay, Rep?
I don't mind.
A warm-up? You sure take us lightly, don't you?
Geez... Why would we lose to an
idiot who likes to dress like a woman?
Wha--
Ah...
We'll start a mock ST War
between Classes A and B now!
Start!
Let's take care of them quickly!
Summon!
Looks like it's started.
Hideyoshi! It's your turn!
Got it!
"Whoa...!!"
How's this? Do I look like a girl?
"Whoooaaaa!!"
Too fast...
I thought the enemy of a
woman was a woman all this time!
What are these...
complicated feelings I'm having?
Incredible, Hideyoshi!
You're a true, pretty girl after all!
Like I keep saying, I'm a guy!
He's already finished changing.
I practiced changing clothes
quickly in the drama club.
Something like this takes no time.
What're you doing, Muttsulini?!
I wish you had told me sooner
that it was that kind of plan!
He must've been quite disappointed
that he couldn't take pictures.
Well then, I'll work on the finishing touches.
I'm Kinoshita... I'm Kino...
I'm Kinoshita... Kinoshita
by me. My Kinoshita...
I'm Yuuko Kinoshita!
You filthy pigs!
What?! Wh-What're you bursting in here for?!
Shut your trap! You smell like a pig!
What?!
I'm Yuuko Kinoshita from Class A!
I came to make clear our beef with
the garbage dump that is Class C!
Garbage... dump?
I can't stand such a smelly, filthy
classroom being in the same school!
A pigsty is the perfect
place for you domestic animals!
Of all things, you're saying
that we should be in Class F?!
We're not that low!
What'd you say?!
In any case, we'll be
busy fighting Class F today,
so we can't fight an ST War with you,
but we'll take care of you
soon. So prepare yourselves!
Wh... What the hell was that?!
That's it!
It's finally over. How tiresome. Let's go back!
You're the one who started it!
I'm Class C Rep Yuuka Koyama!
I'm requesting Class A
to fight us in a mock ST War!
Huh?
You...! I'll never forgive you!
Y-Yuuka! Why are you here?!
W-Were you hiding that hobby from me?
N-No, Yuuka. This is... Yuuka!
Because of this incident,
their relationship fell apart.
Everyone! Charge! Beat them up!
What's with them?! Aren't they afraid of dying?
Everyone! Let's go!
Let's go!
Honey! Please watch my brave figure!
We'll return the favor to Class F!
Yeah!
Class A is exhausted right
now due to successive wars!
Even we, Class E, can give
them damage if we attack now!
We don't want to stay in debt with Class F!
We'll reduce their scores as much as possible!
Yeah!
Don't take Class A... lightly!
I'm Class E Rep, Hiromi Nakabayashi!
I'm requesting a mock ST War!
You're not gonna turn us down, are you?
This is incredible! Class E's
fighting a good fight with Class A!
In ST Wars, you use your
physical strength as well.
Class E has many jocks, but in Class A,
there're many students who only
study and don't build their muscles.
Once they are exhausted, their
attacks won't hit the target any more.
On top of that,
it's a mock war, so there's no time
for a recovery test nor any obligation.
So this is the reason we didn't
exchange classroom equipment!
You got the other classes to owe us!
The accumulation of small
things is important in everything.
It's not about coming up with a
sure method for winning out of thin air,
but about augmenting our fighting
power by accumulating a set of advantages.
That's what you call real strategy.
You guys really play dirty!
Oh? I don't know what you're talking about.
You might think that you reduced our
scores by instigating the other classes,
but it makes no difference
to us! Don't underestimate us!
To see that you can still
fight after all those wars...
Just as you'd expect from Class A.
Talk nonchalantly while you can. Prepare yourself!
There's something else...
you should be prepared for, too.
Brace yourselves! Let's do it!
Yeah!
Idiot test.
We'll cut those Class F idiots down to size!
Everyone... The real fight starts now.
Rep?
We'll defeat Class F with all our
might! Everyone... do your best!
Yeah!
Summon!
What's our strategy?
There's a stairway behind Class F.
We'll attack them from both sides with
the main force attacking from the front
and the squads attacking
from the upper and lower floors.
Charge!
They're not here!
Where'd they go?!
Did they run away?!
Hey! We're over here!
They're over there!
You should go outside once in
a while or mold will grow on you.
Dammit! Those damn jerks!
When did they...?
Everyone! Charge into the schoolyard!
They're coming, Akihisa!
Okay!
Okay, let's go outside!
What the heck is this?!
Dammit!
Everyone, follow me!
I won't let you run... aw...
...ay...
Welcome!
Ah... Ahhhh!
Get him!
Remedial class! Those who
died will be given a remedial class!
That's Class A for you. They sure
are serious. They changed their shoes.
Though our enemy was scattered about,
now they're gathered in one place.
If all of us make a
concentrated attack on one person,
even if they're a Class A
student, we can win, huh?
Okay! The next plan! Akihisa!
Okay! Whoa!
Everyone, retreat!
You jerks! We won't let you get away!
What did you pull your pants down for?
Oh no!
"Oh no!"
Now! Bring them down while
they're preoccupied with their pants!
Yeah!
vs.
"Combined Subjects"
Just as you'd expect from Akihisa's Avatar!
He's unrivaled when it comes to speed!
Oh yeah...!
I have a favor to ask.
What's the matter, Muttsulini?
This time...
Huh?
This time, do it with bras...
I knew you'd say that.
How dare you damage us.
I'll be your opponent this time!
Okay, Muttsulini! Leave it to me!
Oh? Oh? Oh?
You're wasting your time...
because I'm not wearing a bra today.
I-I'm still...
The time has finally come for us to
battle it out, hasn't it, Muttsulini?!
Battle it out... The kanji for
it has female and male in it...
Muttsulini!
I-I'm okay. I'll bring her
down with my own two hands!
Yoshii! I'll be your opponent!
Kubo! Okay! Let's fight!
You're too optimistic, Yoshii.
If you wish...
Huh?!
...no matter what my appearance...
I won't feel embarrassed!
Now! Take my passionate blows,
which are bursting with all my feelings!
I'll also lovingly take your blows!
Hey! Yoshii! Let's battle it out,
too, by putting our lives on the line!
--Now is our chance!
--Yeah!
vs.
"Combined Subjects"
What're you doing?!
--Enough with playing around. Where's their Rep, Sakamoto?
--Yoshii...! Yoshii...! Ah...! Yoshii!
Your opponent is... us!
The enemy's numbers are getting a lot smaller.
Everyone!
Akihisa!
Aki!
Looks like things are going well.
Unexpected commotions are
an effective way of fighting serious opponents.
I knew... you'd be here.
You sure come up with a
bunch of elaborate ideas.
Aren't you impressed?
But... this is it for you.
Yuuji... I'll defeat you.
That's my line! Let's fight!
I approve!
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
Summon!
Our attacks aren't hitting them?!
We've spent lots of time practicing!
With my iron bracelet, we can summon
our Avatars without a teacher attending.
Because of that, we were able
to practice controlling our Avatars.
You're not used to using
your Avatars in everyday life.
In addition, you're tired from the
mock ST Wars and you lack concentration!
It's a piece of cake... dodging your attacks!
You sure talk big... when it takes
only one blow for you to go down!
No matter how powerful an attack is,
it won't have any effect if it doesn't hit!
In addition...
even if the offensive power is small,
when it hits you, it causes damage!
Why?! You're Class F!
We've been studying, too!
Though we're nowhere near Class A.
Can't be...
There they are! This way! Rep!
Class A students are here!
They got here quicker
than I expected... Akihisa!
Okay! Awaken!
We won't let you go through
here until the fight is over.
Dammit! Push it!
Now your help won't get here.
That's okay. I can take
care of all of you by myself.
How rude!
I'll fight you!
Yuuji...
--...prepare yourself!
--Bring it on!
--They're only lowly students and yet...!
--Why?
It's not the logic! It's the practice!
All right!
This is it!
What?
What's the matter?
Th-The bracelet is...
Dammit! Is it at its limit? It was still
okay when the system went out of control.
What's going on?
It surpassed its breaking
point because you studied!
Does that mean...?!
As I thought, only an idiot can use it!
Kinoshita!
--Shouko!
--Himeji!
Y... Yuuji...
Shouko...!
A... Akihisa...
Hime...ji...
Aki!
Rep!
What's going on?!
Akihisa!
Are you okay, Yoshii?!
That was close...
--Goodness... I had no idea what was going to happen.
--It was scary!
Akihisa! It was really, really scary!
Shocked!
--I-I was scared, too, you know!
--I was really scared, too!
Thank goodness...
That scared me!
W-Well... Th-The reason I saved you was just...
Take this!
Wha...
Wha... Wha...
I-I did it!
Huh? What?
The winner... Class A.
Huh?!
Whaaaaaaaaaaaat?!
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
Jugyou owari shifuku no jikan
Tatoeru no nara “Maji de Angel!”
Fui no kokuchi heiwa kowashita
Tsuishi no shirase “Jigoku da!”
Tomodachi tono warai banashi ni
“Iru wake naiyo sonna baka”
Demo hontou wa mune no oku dewa
Sakendetanda “Jibun ga! Sou deshita!”
Chuusha jou de miru “Tsukigime” no koto
Kaisha no namae dato omotteta...
Zutto...
Baka mo tooseba otoko date
Bokura no joushiki hijoushiki?
Ruuru wa muyou sa kono sekai
Yakiniku teishoku gekokujou
Miroyo!
Nishi kara nobotta ohisama ga shizunde iku
Hashire! Mou gohan da
Ouchi ni kaerou! Ouchi ni kaerou!
Question 13.
Fumizuki Academy adopted a
battle system in which tests are used.
What is this battle called?
Entrance Exam War.
Please don't mistake the
fundamentals of this show.
Next Episode! "BAKA and
TEST -- Summon the Beast!"
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!"
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"