Haruka's Room
Number 3
Haruka's Room!
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Our guest for today
is known as the "ESP researcher,"
and is the president of the ESP Research Society at Midorigaoka High School.
Please welcome, Mifune Yuriko-san!
I'm a second-year student at Midorigaoka High School.
I'm Mifune Yuriko, the president of the ESP Research Society.
Thank you for having me here, Kotoura-chan.
I heard you're the founder of the ESP Research Society, President Mifune.
What was the reason behind creating the ESP Research Society?
I did it because I wanted to study ESP.
I'm glad I got to meet a person who really has ESP.
I'm glad I get to take part in the club activities as well.
There are other people in this world who have ESP, just like you, Kotoura-chan.
I'm sure there are a few fakers among the bunch,
but it's not right to label all ESPs as fakes because of that.
Right. Um... By the way—
If you do possess ESP, it's dangerous to display that ability in front of the media.
Since it's not a trick, there's no guarantee that the result will be what people expect.
If you fail, you'll be shunned and treated like a monster!
That is precisely why we need proper facilities for
researching ESP and protecting those who have it.
Such government-run facilities exist in other countries!
I am forced to say that Japan is seriously lagging behind in the ESP research department!
There are a few unofficial agencies,
Let's go to commercials.
but people with ESP—
The End