There’s a memory sealed within me.
They were memories of fun times when we were younger.
Konoka.
You have a new friend now!
Friend?
This is Sakurazaki Setsuna-chan.
We’ll be taking care of her for a while.
Get along and be friends, okay?
It’s a pleasure to meet you!
My name is Setsuna!
Setsuna…
Secchan!
Eh?
I’m Konoka!
Nice to meet ya!
Konoka?
Kono-chan!
I first met Ojousama as a Folk music school friend
Here it goes, Secchan!
Ow…
You okay, Secchan?
Ah! Your forehead’s gettin’ red!
This ain’t good!
Pain, pain, fly away!
Kono-chan…
Hmm? Does it still hurt?
Should I do it again?
No, I’m fine now.
It stopped hurting!
Really? Thank goodness!
Thanks, Kono-chan!
After some time that I spent as a Folk music school friend, I was separated from the Konoe family.
And then...
I have returned from my training.
Protect the Konoe Family from the shadows. That is the mission assigned to the Sakurazaki Family.
At that point, I’ve sealed in all those memories of the past.
All the fun times, even. I sealed in every moment.
Aw dang, I fell asleep!
It’s an Indian summer, that’s why.
I know! Feels great!
Kono-chan!
That was a close one.
Secchan, you just said…!
D-dang it, it just-!
Please forgive me, Ojousama!
No, it’s fine if you call me Kono-chan!
It makes me happy when you call me that!
No. I mustn’t.
Eh?
I cannot do that.
Secchan, you don’t have to think so hard-headedly.
It’s because I’m stupid.
You’re such a bad girl.
Please… forgive me.
Hey.
Will you kiss me?
EEEEEEEEEEEH!?
Just kidding!
That scared me!
Konoka-ojousama, I, Sakurazaki Setsuna, will risk my life to protect you.
A Sunday afternoon, where sun rays of Spring gently touch.
by Yue
There’s no way I’d kiss him!
Hello, Ojou-san.
Won’t you kiss me?
What did you say!?
Just kidding.
“Just kidding”!?
I bet from this, my mystery only gets deeper, huh?
Well, then, good day to you!
So as long as it is mysterious, everything's okay?
Hello there, Ojou-san!
Another mysterious gentleman!
Nope, I’m a mysterious frog.
I was thinking to myself, “Isn’t this what makes me mysterious”?
In a good way.
Oh, but thinking about it more, maybe this is also the mystery!
Or maybe here?
Ah, well, I like that spot, though.
What’s this? Where ya goin’?
I’m busy.
Oh my, is it because you’re a witness to Negi-san’s secret?
No…
I mean…
Stop saying things that don’t make sense!
Yue-Yue…
Yue-san, um…!
Yue!
Run after her!
Are you okay, mya?
I’m back to normal…
No, you're still flat, mya.
Putting that aside…
It doesn’t matter if you put that aside.
Did you see Yue-san’s reaction?
How suspicious, mya~
Isn’t it fishy?
In a good way.
Maybe she saw Negi-chan’s magic.
I’m going after her, mya!
Ah, I'm flat!
Sometimes, I have the urge to kill you.
Eh? Yue did what?
Yeah…
We gotta hurry and find her and have her exchange a contract!
And if Motsu and Shichimi find out…!
Negi-bouzu will be in big trouble, de gozaru!
Let’s split up and look for her!
Okay!
But speaking of which, Haruna…
Does this mean you exchanged a contract with Negi?
Yeah, I did.
I’m sure you and the other girls did it, too, huh?
The kissing, I mean.
Eh? Oh, uh…
Yeah…
For the time being.
Hey, hey! You’re STILL embarrassed by this?
You guys are so childish.
What did you say!?
OW! ANIMAL ABUSE!
But more important than that is Yue-dono, de gozaru!
Like hell you’re going to catch me!
Here ya go, Iinchou! A Negi-sensei towel!
Oh my, thank you, Yuuna-san!
Looks like you can swim pretty well, Iinchou.
Oh, how rude.
Back in elementary, I, Yukihiro Ayaka, was called “The Beautiful Mermaid,” you know.
“Beautiful,” eh…?
This feels great! Many thanks to Iinchou for it!
You said it!
Thanks to Iinchou, we got permission to use the pool!
Well, the word “impossible” isn’t in my dictionary, so…
Really? Then, Iinchou, can you get your hands on Kyuu Tamiya’s 1/21 big shot?
Pardon?
Iinchou!
Ah, it’s Paru!
My, Negi-sensei!
Oh dear, looks like you caught me!
W-why is my face on…?
Seen Yue around?
Yuecchi?
Haven’t seen her. Why?
So she didn’t come by here?
Did something happen?
Ah, no, nothing really…
Yeah, it’s nothing! Yuecchi just found out about-
Again? Geez, Chamo-kun!
Alright! Let’s search somewhere else!
Okay! Guys, I’m sorry for intruding...
Now if you’ll excuse me!
Aw, Negi-sensei felt awkward~
I wonder if my figure was that stimulating~
No, I think it’s from the picture.
But in any case…
…I wonder what happened.
Let’s… exterminate ‘em.
Excuse me?
Just kidding.
Saying so is somehow popular, it seems…
Um…
I don’t think you should take him seriously, myu.
You can go back to work now.
How very kind of you…
Well then, Motsu, she doesn’t seem to be here, so let’s go, myu!
Okay. Well then, excuse us.
Are they looking for someone?
That makes three today.
Hey you, Takamichi.
Evangeline!
Didn’t I tell you to observe carefully for the time being?
Yeah… but in the end I couldn’t just leave it alone.
You’re too serious.
Here, Master.
You seem to love doing that. What’s the soup base this time?
Soup base?
Eh? Aren’t you having ramen right now?
It is tea.
Where would you find someone having ramen in the open-air tea ceremony?
You idiot.
I guess you’re right…
Elegant, isn’t it, Chachamaru?
Yes. It is the heart of Japan.
Perhaps I’m a bit too serious of a man.
Okay, I’ll go to the right!
I’ll go to the left!
Please!
Oneechan… What should I do?
If my secret is exposed… I won’t be a mage anymore…
Yes? Hello, Negi speaking.
You found Yue!?
Negi-bouzu, hurry and come here!
Wait up!
I refuse to!
Yue-dono, just accept it and kiss Negi-bouzu, de gozaru!
If you don’t, Negi-bouzu will-!
What do you mean “just accept it”!?
Do you honestly think I can kiss him so easily!?
Yue-Yue’s in a pinch!
Just a minute.
EH!?
She got away!?
Geez, what the heck were you doing?
I’m ashamed, de gozaru.
But you know, is she THAT opposed to kissing him?
She’s such a little girl, that Yue-kichi!
Goodness gracious.
If I knew it was gonna be like this, I could’ve just chosen to miss out on watching it.
When it comes to a kiss, is that really all there is to it?
Hmm… I guess I’ll go to Akiba today, since it’s been a while.
Alright.
Hi! Hello, hello! Kyuu!
Today, I went to Akiba after a long time!
I wonder if I should meet the love-love-lovely maids?
Tee-hee!
Okay. Perfect.
Hasegawa-san!
What’s wrong?
You should at least KNOCK before entering someone else’s room!
Sorry ‘bout that.
Seen Yue around?
No I haven’t!
That’s not something to get fussy over!
Were you doing something on the computer?
It’s nothing!
Whoa! Are you doing something BAD on there!?
Hell no!
How suspicious.
No it’s not! Just hurry and get the hell out of here!
Let~ me~ see~
Don’t get any closer, dammit!
Asuna-san!
It seems like Yue-Yue’s hiding in the school!
Eh? Really!? Let’s go, let’s go!
Finally gone.
So they’re looking for Ayase Yue, huh?
What happened?
Eh?
Amazing!
So you’re a ‘Net Idol, Hasegawa-san!
Chiu Chiu, aru!
You guys…When the hell did you-?
“I wonder… Should meet the love-love-lovely maids? Tee hee!”
DON’T READ THAT!
There are responses on this blog, aru!
Really? Lemme see!
Check it out, aru!
Ah, you’re right! That’s so cool!
Space, the Final Frontier.
It’s the pride of the Astronomy Club: the Planetarium. Cool, huh?
Chizu-nee used a fortune-telling technique and made a teacher buy it!
Fortune-telling technique?
My, Natsumi, don’t say it in such a way that it’ll cause misunderstandings!
I only offered and made astrological readings on the teacher’s luck!
Astrology? Is that what you used to have the teacher buy the planetarium?
His face went so pale!
It was funny!
What was his fortune?
Oh yes, Yue-san!
No, if you’re talking about the astrology thing, then I’ll pass.
No, that’s not it; didn’t you have something to do?
Oh yeah, that’s right.
I have something to confide in you about…
“Confide in”?
Um… you know…
“Is kissing something that’s okay to do so easily?”
Saying it like that defeats the purpose of talking about it in secret!
Oh my, I’m sorry!
Kissing? Yue-chan, why are you talking about kissing?
No… um… you know, just stuff…
Kissing, eh?
It depends on the level of the kiss...
A light one is a greeting in the West…
But this is a lip-lock, isn’t it?
I mean… even if you say that so bluntly…
Even I’m surprised, Chizu-nee.
If it’s on the lips… then in Japan, I think it’ll get into a conversation of whether or not you like the person…
“Whether or not…”
We can’t find her…
Hmm? That voice belonged to…
For a small fry, that Jou-chan can run hella fast!
It sounds there’s somebody in the Astronomy Club. Let’s try asking them!
Don’t you guys have a back door?
Back door?
If you want, you can use this!
I guess Strawberry’s the best flavor, Secchan!
Indeed! Ice cream must be Strawberry-flavored!
But Green Tea’s a good flavor, too…
Indeed! Green Tea is also a good flavor!
Sauce is also a good flavor!
Indeed! Sauce flavor is also hard to cast aside!
How’s that gonna turn out?
Konoka!
Asuna!
Did you find Black Rose-han?
There’s no time for that!
Right now, we have to find a person even more important than the Black Rose Baron!
A more important person? Who might that be?
Oh, I know! The chupacabra!
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
You don’t have to get angry, but…
If you didn’t wanna meet a chupacabra, you shouldn’t have made the Chupa Team.
Since then, it’s with resounding certainty that the generation is moving!
So it’s more of a matter of preference, huh?
Hmm, so this is where it leads to.
She got away again!
But why is there a loop hole in the Astronomy Club?
I think it’s best that you stop thinking about the small things right now, Aniki.
Hey, Negi-kun.
Yes?
Can’t you do anything about it using your magic?
When one becomes a partner… one is able to use magic, no?
Yeah, I guess.
Oh yeah, Aniki! Haruna-nee-san’s power could be of use for us!
Let’s give it a shot, Negi-kun!
Aniki!
Alright!
Partner: Saotome Haruna. Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
Whoa! So cool!
She seems pretty happy.
Well, if she’s that happy, then that’s good, I suppose.
Well? What can I do?
Who knows… Even I don’t know that much.
Your artifact is a sketchbook, eh?
What if you tried drawing something on it, Nee-san?
I see. Well then…
Whoa! It flew!
She can give life to the things she draws, huh?
That’s so cool! I’m happy!
Ah, but this isn’t of much use, is it?
I suppose.
“Like,” huh?
Well, it’s not like I hate Negi-sensei, but…
I know how Nodoka feels about him…
No, Negi-sensei’s future depends on this; I don’t think this is the time to reject it…
I mean… it’s just a kiss…
It’s just so hard to make a decision…
I guess the only way to make sure I can keep his magic secret quiet is to…
WE HEARD YOU, MYA!
You were talking about kissing and magic, mya!
So you do know about Negi-san’s secret!
Yue-san~
Should we be blunt about it? In a good way.
Well!?
Look! Samohan Kinpou!
Eh!? Where!?
Hey! Wait, mya!
Who’s Samohan Kinpou?
I’ve decided. I’ve made up my mind!
What a pity… But you weren’t fast enough…
I see. So you couldn’t find her…
This isn’t good.
I know.
Yue!
Yue-san…
Chamo-chan!
ALRIGHT! PACTIO!
Contract, Complete!
You did it!
Thank you, Yue-san.
Nah, well, um…
I guess we can relax now, huh?
Indeed. The secret has been protected.
No.
It doesn’t look like it!
Y-y-you guys…
Why…?
Uh, well, ya see…
We were interested in why you were searching for Yue-san,
so we came to check it out, aru.
D-Doesn’t that mean…
…that all of you saw it!?
No way…
Yes, Negi-san answer, mya!
My agile self has already informed the Magic Academy about the situation!
No need to worry.
In a very good way.
Th-then that means Aniki will...
have his magic certification revoked.
And…
Negi!
He’s a chupacabra!
Ne-Negi-sensei!
Nodoka!
N-no way…
Where are we?
The castle from before!
What a scandal! Negi has had his magic certification removed and has been turned into a chupacabra!
On top of that, the whole class has been sucked into the world of illusion!
What will you do, Negi!?
What can I do…?
I CAN’T DO ANYTHING!
Once a week, I have Hakase-san perform a maintenance check on me.
Next Time, “It is a Larger Matter When it Comes to Being an Interference With Master Than it is to Be An Enemy,”
by Chachamaru.
For the record, this is a battery.
Ah, looks like we swam a lot today.
I know! I’m dead tired.
Hey, aside from that, can’t you guys do something about your swimsuits?
You’re the one to talk, you know!
Yeah, what is that?
A Mandala!
Dunno about it.
But you know; that's even more questionable.