Really, this just doesn't suit my style...
to just sit and wait like this.
We pick our spot, then wait patiently.
That is the secret behind fishing.
Did you ever consider
that maybe this was the wrong spot?
- The bait has no right to complain.
- What are you fishing for?
Starship Pirates.
A group that calls themselves pirates.
Pirates?
People who like to attack a ship
and rob anything and everything from them.
Like to rob, rob, drunken slob.
Besides, where the hell did Spike go?
He left to overhaul his ship
and still hasn't--
Thanks.
But, Spike, man...
What's he doing now,
without giving us a heads-up?
You're late, Doohan.
Yeah! Go, go, go!
Hey.
Hey!
Strike three! Batter out!
He just let that one slide by.
And that's the game.
Man, why didn't they just send in
a pinch hitter?
Come on, Eightwood is getting old.
Don't you think?
Where's Doohan?
The old man's kind of busy. I'm Miles,
his assistant. Nice to meet you.
Man, they were really great
when they won the pennant 14 years ago.
They just kept hitting the ball
and turned losing games around.
Especially when Randy,
Blanket and Hills hit consecutive homers.
I really wish you could've seen it.
And you know...
Hey, do people often say
you're the silent type?
And people often say
you talk too much, right?
Kind of.
The... Swordfish, right?
The machine back there.
Yeah.
That's the amazing MONO racer
that the old man built, right?
It's just an old machine.
I don't want it, but it's a part of me.
I hear you.
Us Blue Sox fans feel
like we fell for some wicked broad.
I can't remember how many times
I've thought about giving up on them.
Jesus, not again.
Yo, old man!
- Yo. Long time no see.
- Yeah.
Miles, where's the checklist?
It's out there.
I put it on the ship's body.
He's been fixing that ancient thing?
I think it's useless.
The computer isn't compatible
with the MONO system.
Miles! Give me the EV transmitter,
the absorber for the main gear
and the 3-8 pneumatic tube.
A 3-8?
I don't have something that special.
Order one from Reggie. His place has them.
Yeah, yeah.
You really are some slave driver.
Some hobby.
- Did we catch it?
- It wasn't me. Where is it?
- It's close. Shit, I used bad bait.
- Hey!
This is a good machine.
Attacking blessed people like them
and giving to the poor
is human equality, don't you think so?
I get it.
This is what you call social reform.
Yeah. It's only right for us,
the poor, to take from them.
- Something's coming.
- Cops?
Hi. That's enough.
Bounty hunter?
- Harman.
- Be a good girl and come here.
Faye, above you!
What the...? Is this a joke?
It's not me!
Ruth! One more behind us.
- And it's huge.
- I know.
What a tattered old ship.
Leave me alone.
Abnormality found in the MONO system.
Booting the emergency pilot program.
Hey, stop this thing!
Like I know how.
Looks like he's taken you
on quite a few spins.
Cut it.
The accelerator pump is all worn down.
I know.
And the fuel injector
doesn't have a silencer on it.
Don't need one.
But it's noisy and it trembles...
If you put one in,
I can't hear what it's telling me.
Just hurry up and connect the injector.
First of all, a 3-8 isn't popular anymore.
Why don't you switch to the new 5-0?
Miles.
If you change the navigation to auto,
you glide along without manual steering.
Do you want to use a machine,
or do you want the machine to use you?
Which is it?
- I wasn't exactly--
- Just go.
You haven't changed a bit.
At this rate,
another assistant is gonna leave you.
And you.
The Swordfish wants to run away from you.
I haven't heard that before.
If you keep being reckless with her,
she'll really throw you off someday.
Unfortunately,
I'm not one for delicate controls.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I got something you don't see often...
A 3-8 pneumatic tube.
Yes, hello?
Oh, it's you, Missing Man.
Where are you right now?
I'm still with Doohan. How's Jet?
He seems rather busy right now.
- Saying something about some bacteria.
- Bacteria?
A virus. We got a computer virus.
Same difference.
Starting with the MONO system,
orbit calculator,
flight-path selector, engine regulator,
communications circuit...
they're all shot.
I don't get it.
Give me a simple explanation.
The computer broke,
and we're just drifting along.
Well, I understood that.
How about it? It's the newest one.
You haven't seen one anywhere else, right?
A MONO computer?
How about it? 150K... No, 100K.
A bargain, huh?
When it's that cheap,
you lose money even on salvage.
So, who did it?
Where did you get this?
A truck? Any features?
- A penguin...
- ...logo on...
...the delivery truck?
Are you sure about the info?
Yeah. They apparently were dealing
at the Orbit Drive-in.
I see. Nobody would be suspicious
of a delivery truck wandering about.
And how are we going
to counter the hacks?
Don't get harpooned.
- And?
- That's it?
They laughed this ship off as "tattered."
And they made that mess
out of my Hammer Head.
Unlike someone I know,
I always pay back what I owe.
What a wonderful principle.
I'm really not up for this.
I have an invoice from Doohan here.
Because they're physically
sending the virus,
they haven't developed a vaccine for it.
That is where this secret weapon
of ours comes in.
What? That's just our normal communicator.
If you get infected by the virus,
cut off the entire MONO system.
All navigation
and communication will go down.
As I said, I will navigate you with this.
Because this is set to the frequency
for an old communications satellite,
it has nothing to do
with the MONO system.
Oh, another run scored
against the Blue Sox.
That's some secret weapon.
It was a penguin, right?
Yeah. A purple penguin.
There are two of them?
Wait a minute.
It might be a real courier service.
It's a matter of how to figure out
if they're legit.
That's easy.
We fire a shot.
The one that runs is the one we want.
This is the first time I agree with you.
You guys.
What are you gonna do
if they're both real?
They both ran?
We didn't consider that option.
- I'm trusting you with that one.
- I have to pay them back for yesterday.
Forgive us.
We'll pay the parking fee.
This way?
Spike. Draw them out.
It'll be a mess
if they let the virus go in there.
I know.
So, let's see what you got.
He's here.
Waste of time.
He's after the arm.
He's not taking us seriously. Ruth.
Ready to go anytime.
Take that!
Welcome.
Excellent.
Bingo!
He's holding up pretty well.
- Cut off the MONO system!
- I'm doing it!
That idiot cut off his MONO system.
Hey, George.
And he's in Earth's gravitational field.
Old man! Here, here!
- This is pretty bad!
- Align the D7. You did it before, right?
Like I remember.
No good. There's nothing we can do.
You idiot.
Hurry up and do something about this.
Damn it. Move! Move!
Falling! We're falling!
Spike, I'll be right there.
I'm calculating an interception course.
Until then, somehow keep control manually.
Even if everything was normal,
it'd be tough to get out of here.
I can see that.
And I just had it overhauled.
Oh, well. Whatever happens happens.
Spike, above you.
Your tattered ship looks like a goddess.
Shit, the virus.
- Spike!
- I'm still alive.
We have to start over.
No way. Old man, you gotta be kidding.
Are you really gonna move
this ancient piece of...?
Do you think I'd do this as a joke?
Don't just stand there.
Hurry up and get me some fuel.
All right.
Spike, can you hear me?
I got a calculation.
It'll take another seven hours
for us to rendezvous.
Come on, you're joking, right?
We're too close to Earth.
The orbital paths I can take are limited.
Isn't there a way for you
to just swing on by?
If I plunge in at this angle,
both The Bebop and the Swordfish
will burn to nothing.
Jet.
I have some booze hidden
behind the fridge.
Feel free to drink some.
Something wrong?
I'm out of gas. Nothing I can do now.
How about I go there and tow you back,
in exchange for that booze?
I heard the conversation.
Give me the Swordfish's coordinates.
Doohan? How the hell do you...?
Spike, I don't care how you do it,
but slow down using an air brake.
Slow down?
If you slow down
within Earth's atmosphere,
the gravitational pull
will accelerate you instead,
which will give you enough speed
to escape.
However, you have to maintain the ship
at a certain angle.
Too far either way, and you'll be thrown
to the other end of the universe.
Unfortunately,
I'm not one for delicate controls.
Spike...
I know you can do it.
I didn't give you the Swordfish
for nothing.
Don't you start crashing, either.
Maximum propulsion.
You didn't have to force yourself
to come with me.
You know how Blue Sox fans
love to party.
- Let's go.
- All right.
We're flying.
We're really flying.
Lower the nose by 0.6 degrees.
You're in too deep.
Spike, you'll burn to a crisp.
This is the last chance.
It went in. It went in! That was perfect!
Doohan, you saved me.
Not quite.
Most of the heat-resistant tiles
have peeled off.
The temperature is rising.
The landing gear isn't coming down.
Oh yeah, and the 2 nozzle won't work.
What?! Is that for real?!
What are we gonna do?!
- We can't land without them!
- Oh, well. Whatever happens happens.
I knew I shouldn't have come up here!
I'm still too young to die!
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
Next episode: "Pierrot le Fou."