Wow!
That's Hope Kingdom's castle?
Yeah.
I'll never forget the scene surrounding the Castle of Flame's rebirth.
I wanted to capture that emotion in a picture...
but I'm not sure it's coming across.
It totally is!
Yeah!
Incidentally...
the Dreamy Shore Museum
happens to be holding an art contest.
Why not enter a work yourself?
In a contest?
Sounds good to me!
It'd be wonderful to have so many people see your art.
I think it's worth a try.
You're right.
It might bring me closer to becoming a picture book author.
I'll give it a shot!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
The contest's theme is "Share a Smile."
Dreamy Shore
Smile!
Art Contest
Entrants Welcome!
Theme:
"Share a Smile!"
Hm...
So, they want a picture that can make people smile.
But they also judge technique, composition, and originality within the theme.
What's wrong?
The people who enter in contests must be pretty skilled.
I can't submit something sloppy.
It has to be absolutely perfect, right?
I-I'm not sure I can do it...
Yui's Dream!
The Heart is in the Canvas!
Not like that...
No, the composition...
No, this design's a mess from the start!
Anyway, did Prince Kanata return to Hope Kingdom?
He said he wanted to look into something...
Will Prince Kanata be okay?
Oui!
La région near le castle is perfectly safe,
and he can always use la power of la Royal Key to return at any time!
Good!
Okay, now I'm motivated!
Madame Siamour, I'd like a lesson!
Oui!
Today's lesson is la cuisine!
I'm hungry, so that might hit the spot!
Yui, good luck with your drawing!
Sure!
Let's commençons la lesson!
I've gotta keep trying!
I'm sure plenty of better artists than me are doing this...
Would this picture make someone smile?
Wait, should I even be drawing princesses for this?
I'm just getting more and more confused about what to draw...
What should I do?
I hope Yui's in the mood for a handmade cake!
I'm baaaack!
Oops!
I'm so lost...
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired, nothing beats a cake!
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
When you're tired,
nothing beats a cake!
Madame Siamour
taught me how to
make this, so dig in!
Never give up!
Haruka
Haruka...
Bon appétit.
It's delicious!
Haruka's cheering me on, so I've gotta keep it together!
But a picture that can make everyone smile?
What might you be drawing?
Mrs. Mochizuki!
Oh, well, I...
Oh my, it's blank.
For now! I'm still brainstorming!
I've been thinking about entering a contest coming up...
but it's just not coming together.
With a look like that,
you'll lose sight of what you're aiming for.
Try not to overthink it.
Okay...
She sells seashells by the seashore!
Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers!
Hooray! Hooray! Noble Academy!
Hurrah, hurrah, Noble Academy, yeah!
Everyone's leaving me behind...
Noble Academy, where students gather to chase their dreams...
Do I really have a place here?
Mornin'!
Your care package is in!
The contest deadline is soon!
Do you think you can make it?
If there's any way we can help, just say the word!
I do shoulder rubs!
Thank you...
but I'm sorry.
I gave it some thought...
and I decided not to enter the contest.
Huh?
Sorry, I've got something I need to do.
Yui?
We have no time left.
Understand?
We won't let them have their way any longer.
Stop.
Here.
Freeze.
Show them what even greater despair looks like.
Right!
Why can't I draw?
Wow, pretty!
They're blooming beautifully, aren't they?
Now, how about we draw them?
Okay!
Mrs. Mochizuki?
Oh, would you like to join our open air art class?
Open air art class?
Every now and then, I teach the children to draw.
That's nice.
It's pretty, but why is it so many colors?
Because it's cute.
It looks cuter this way.
It sure does!
Yeah.
Do you like drawing?
I love it!
Why's that?
Well...
'cause it's fun!
Yeah... you're right!
What lovely colors.
Mrs. Mochizuki!
So, how is your drawing for the contest coming along?
About that...
I decided to give up.
Once I started to focus on winning the contest...
I lost sight of what really mattered.
I suppose I just forgot...
the joy of drawing.
Did you find something to draw?
I'm still not settled,
but...
Mrs. Mochizuki, can I borrow
some pencils and a sketchbook?
Of course.
Thank you very much!
Stop!
Freeze!
Plenty of dreams...
Small children, yet big dreams...
No!
Don't take these children's dreams!
Do not interfere.
Should you interfere,
you'll go first, you hear?
What?
I won't let you have your way!
She endured.
Who is she?
My dream... won't...
It's a Dyspairvil!
Girls!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
Dyspairvil!
You girls!
It's not safe here!
Mrs. Yume!
Oh?
Please, run!
Have we met somewhere?
Gah! Uh, just your imagination!
Now, take the children somewhere safe.
Please, let us handle this!
I refuse! I won't lose any more children!
More?
It's Yui!
Now hurry and come with me!
We'll save her.
Dyspair!
Get going!
Who are you girls?
I'll get help as soon as I can.
Just be careful!
Yui must have done something reckless again...
I promise we'll save you,
Yui!
I don't need dreams...
Who cares about picture books...
Yui!
Yuiiiiii!
Who?
Dyspairvil!
Is that...
Dyspair...
Dyspair!
Are they...
Am I...
I won't let you keep Yui from her dream!
Nor will I! Yui's serious about her dream!
But you jerks keep using it!
You shall pay for this!
Girls...
They're right...
Vil!
Yui's dream is Yui's!
And we'll protect it!
I've found... what to draw...
Nobody but me can draw the strong, graceful, and beautiful Precures!
I have to get out of here!
What's that?
What's what?
Yui...
She's conscious!
Wait for us, Yui! We'll get you out of there in no time!
Dyspairvil!
I'm getting out!
I have to draw it right this instant!
Unbelievable.
She should be in despair.
The Dyspairvil's power has weakened!
Dyspair...
Yui!
Girls!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Dreaming...
Blooming...
Adieu.
Bizarre.
Bizarre indeed.
Open!
The door to your dream!
I want to draw a story only I can tell...
I want to tell of the power dreams hold
and how important they are to protect...
Thank you...
for saving me.
Yui!
I heard you all in there.
You fought against the despair.
You're tough, Yuiyui!
You know, seeing you all fight made me realize something...
I want to draw you all fighting to protect dreams...
as the Precures!
Yui...
So I'm going to try one more time to enter that contest!
I want to tell everyone about how powerful dreams are, so... I'll start drawing!
Oh?
Nobody's here.
How curious.
Perhaps it was those princesses I've heard so much about.
What have you heard?
The students have been gossiping about a group of princesses who battle to protect dreams.
Dreams?
I see...
Yeah, it's done!
Are these the Precures?!
It's really pretty!
It's splendid!
Thanks!
Dreamy Shore
Smile Contest
Oh?
Good, so she did enter.
It's quite splendid.
Rainbow of Dreams
Nanase Yui
Honorary
Mention
I hope I can convey the power of a radiant dream to others, no matter how few.
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Mermaid!
This grand blue sea is a mirror
reflecting my heart along the southern winds
I want to know the answer lying within my chest
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Kirara, you're simply amazing!
Indeed! Appearing in a global fashion show means you must be close to becoming Top Model!
Aw, cut it out, you two!
This means your dream will come true!
Yeah... I can't fail!
I gotta show them what Amanogawa Kirara is made of!
Go! Princess Precure:
Dreams or the Precures?!
The Dazzling Kirara's Decision!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Saitama Prefecture - Reno (Age 6)
Kagoshima Prefecture - Yuuhi (Age 4)