From yesterday's me to today's me...
You will lose your memories in thirteen hours.
It's the impact of the accident four years ago.
It's regrettable that your left eye was lost at the same time as well.
Please accept that it happened and that it's the truth.
I have written everything that you will need in order to live right here.
First, please read the diary every morning.
These are your memories.
Everything about you is inside it.
Second, please make sure you write something in the diary.
Please write about that day's behavior, conversations, and other records as accurately as possible.
Third, try to avoid any contact with other people.
Because with this kind of injury, it might cause trouble.
And there is the possibility of troubling the other person.
If you ever meet another person, please write about that person's character and information in the diary.
At first, I only wrote of Renji-kun as a short, school uniformed, older student who came by the station around three.
Older?
Because my time stopped four years ago.
Ah... I see.
The next day I didn't recognize you in normal clothes and coming by earlier than three.
So that's how it is.
That's as far as you can read.
Uh, sorry. It is a diary after all.
No.
This is me, myself.
Thirteen hours... so that's how long Chihiro can remember.
When I wake up at seven in the morning, I remember everything that day until eight in the evening.
But after that, I will lose my memories slowly as each hour passes.
By midnight, I will only remember from eleven in the morning of the previous day.
And the next morning after that at seven, I will only remember things from six in the evening of the previous day.
So tomorrow morning you will forget everything about meeting me?
No, I will remember.
Huh?
I will remember very important things by repeating them.
When I repeat something many times, I can remember it for more than thirteen hours.
Every night at nine, I remember important things by repeatedly reading my diary.
That way, I can still remember them the next morning.
The fact that Renji-kun met me and the fact that I have anterograde amnesia.
Right now, I am living an idle life.
I don't go to school, and I don't have anyone that I can call a friend.
I really have nothing to do.
If I just sit idly at the station, I don't have to remember anything.
It's a life without meaning, don't you think?
It's easier if you just throw everything away.
That's not tr-
I don't have anything, so my goal in life is to try not to cause trouble for anyone else.
But even that's hard to do.
Just by living, I will cause trouble for someone.
And even then, I will forget the memory of troubling someone.
Renji-san, what I'm about to say is in jest.
In jest?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Dinner is ready.
Renji, you have the future career form, right?
How do you know about that?
I heard it from other moms at the cooking class.
That's pretty early. You're still a first-year student.
Yeah...
What are you going to put on it?
No idea.
You can just write whatever you want to be, Renji.
I wouldn't be worrying about it if I had already decided.
That's right, I need you to send something to Kuze-san after this.
Kuze-san? He's back?
Yep.
Take the pot on top of the stove and let him know that's his, okay?
Kuze-san?
Oh, it's Renji.
It's been a while.
You're still small like always.
Have you been eating properly?
It's been three months and that's the first thing you say to me?
Oh, is that the usual food for me?
Yes. My mother said please take it.
Thanks a bunch.
I wonder what the side dish is today?
Umm, can I come in?
I need to talk with you.
Sure, if you don't mind a naked woman on the bed.
Sorry to intrude!
It's all right. We don't mind.
I mind so that's enough.
Well, I guess so.
Worrying about something?
No. It's not really something important...
Well, if you say so...
Next time I'll bring some souvenirs.
Just bring the pot back when it's finished.
Thanks as usual.
Good night, Renji.
Have a nice dream.
Welcome back, Kuze-san.
I'm going.
Have a good day.
It's just the usual peaceful day.
I think of that because I remember my everyday life.
I was happy that I was able to see Kuze-san yesterday.
That's because I remember Kuze-san.
But for Chihiro, she only remembers thirteen hours of the day she spent and the people that she met.
I kept meeting with Chihiro simply because I wanted to see her.
But for Chihiro to meet a stranger like me, she always has to prepare her heart.
She must have felt scared and worried.
Despite that...
See you tomorrow!
Yes, see you tomorrow.
Is it okay for me to meet with Chihiro with this casual feeling?
If you want to be beside Chihiro, then prepare yourself.
Maybe it's just that I'm infatuating myself with Chihiro.
I hope she's not there today.
What I'm about to say is in jest.
In jest?
Every day, I thought of how it would be for me to just disappear without troubling anyone.
But I never thought of how.
I'm not afraid of myself disappearing.
If I do feel afraid, then those are just my emotions.
However...
However...?
What I'm really afraid of isn't losing my own memories, but the thought that I'll disappear from everyone else's memories.
I see... That's pretty cowardly of me, isn't it?
In jest, huh?
Is there anything that I can do for Chihiro?
Something that a knight can do in order to protect the princess.
Something... that will make her happy.
I have a dream.
A dream?
I want to write a story.
About anything; just one story.
I want to make one with the current me.
Why is Himura-san here?
I'm the messenger.
The message is that Chihiro has a fever and can't come today.  She says she's sorry.
Is she all right?
Just a normal fever.
Just for precautions, she shouldn't come outside for today.
I see.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
You promised her, didn't you?
Chihiro waited here until late at night.
Chihiro will definitely keep a promise like that because she has such a memory.
For her, a promise like, "Let's meet again tomorrow" is an important promise that connects the next day's her to the previous day's her.
She must have been really happy.
I came to get her, but she said that she had a promise. Such stubbornness.
Chihiro has just been following anything around her because she can't validate her own existence.
But I guess she still has human-like emotions inside of her.
I... without knowing that...
You're not responsible.
For Chihiro, not knowing such common sense means I'm a failure as her guardian.
Right, it's only because of that.
Ah, Onii-chan!
Yo! Doing morning exercise by yourself?
Nope, it's just everyone else is slow.
Let me have some.
Anyway, what's up? You're here so early.
With guts, I turned in the manuscripts.
I sent it to the editor just now.
I thought that I would never wake up if I slept, so I went ahead and came to school.
Note: Basically, she's commenting on the fact that it's rare to see Hiro come to school.
That's weird. Maybe it'll rain tomorrow?
Though I'm not sure if I can stay awake in class.
There's no point then!
Huh? You drank it all...
Well, I'll praise you for the effort at least. Good job, Onii-chan.
What's up with that?
Guess who?
Now, who could it be?
Hey you!
Don't be so angry.
It's just some cute, normal prank.
Normal is just closing the eyes, right?!
Well, normal isn't fun.
There's no way I'm getting killed for that reason!
But I'm glad you're here, Hirono-kun.
Why?
Because if Hirono-kun isn't here, I can't come to this locked rooftop.
Ah, I see...
Hey, will you give that to me?
Nope.
This is an important inheritance left by my big sister after she graduated.
Then how about just making a spare key?
You think I would give up this valuable place to be alone just like that?
By the way Hirono-kun, how was work today?
If you don't send in your manuscript quickly, then the editor will give you a blood bath.
If that was the situation, then I wouldn't be here at school.
I see. Then, shall we go?
W-Wait a second! Where are we going?!
Not here.
Where do you think?
It looks kind of normal.
Normal? What is?
It's like following the book...
You see these scenes everywhere.
We made it look normal.
And that's because if it's not connected, your clips will leave too strong of an impression.
What's wrong with that?
A film with too much peculiarity will not be regarded as special.
If you're aiming to win, realistic things are better.
Kyousuke...
As expected, it's fun just to walk around Otowa.
I've been living here, so I'm sick of it.
Since we're walking together, don't you feel it's different than the usual?
Nope, not at all.
This Otowa place used to have normal Japanese scenery before, right?
Well, most of them were destroyed after the earthquake.
They got burned down during the war too.
What an unlucky town.
Maybe that's why until then, they were making a completely different town.
You don't have to hold back since I did bring my money.
I really can't eat much after staying up that late.
What nice weather.
With a day like this, you won't feel like going to class.
Weren't you planning to skip class anyway?
Yup.
Do you hate school?
Nope.
Then why?
Because the town is more fun than class.
Huh?
It's not that I hate school; I just don't like being bored.
It's better if it's fun.
I'm probably not the one who should be saying this, but won't it be bad if you don't go to school?
Life wouldn't be fun if we only learned about politics and common sense.
You have to do whatever is fun for you too, Hirono-kun.
Ah, Hiro-senpai!
Hayama?
What are you doing here, Hiro-senpai?
How about you?
I was buying something.
I was buying the shoujo manga, Pokkyu.
You really like manga, don't you?
Hirono-kun, who is she?
Ah, this is my younger classman, Hayama Mizuki.
Nice to meet you.
This is my classmate, Miyamura...
Miyamura... Umm...
Hirono-kun, from now on you will call me Miyako.
What do you mean?
You forgot my name so easily, and now my heart is wounded.
I don't know what I'm going to do now.
Hey, Hayama, don't you think this is coercion?
It's your fault, Hiro-senpai.
It's strange that you're calling her by her last name in the first place.
Anyway, Hiro-senpai sure is popular.
She's not my girlfriend!
Really?
I was hoping that if Hiro-senpai got a girlfriend then boyfriendless Kei-senpai would be mine.
Why is Kei becoming my girlfriend now?!
Huh?
Miyamura?
Hiro-senpai, looks like she dumped you.
Like I said, she is not my girlfriend!
Kyousuke, I know how you feel, but please understand.
Everyone is working hard now so we can win the next film festival.
Is that all you wanted to say?
Eh?
Everyone was just worrying about the evaluation.
Why can't everyone just do it the way we want?
So that's why you did it that way?
Who knows...
Who knows?
It's been kind of boring lately.
Even when I've been looking through the viewfinder.
What do you mean by that?
I just can't seem to see what I want to do.
Hey, Kyousuke.
What is it?
Should we break up?
I just feel kind of lost... about you.
I guess you are.
Can you get me the list, Miss President?
Kyousuke...
The remains of the earthquake, huh?
It's still here.
You shouldn't be here.
There is no need to look again on what happened to these ruins.
I always only look forward, you know.
Really? Isn't it the case that you can't see what you really want to do?
For now...
However, what I really want to do has already been decided long before.
I will take the picture that I want.
And that is of what?
What I really want to take... is my dream.
The temperature wasn't all that high, but Himura-san wouldn't let me go out...
even though I wanted to meet with Renji-kun.
You should listen to what Himura-san says.
It would be bad if it got worse.
Mizuki?
Stupid Hirono-kun.
Hey, Onii-chan, don't yawn while watching me practice.
That's rude, you know.
My awake time is different than yours.
Humans sleep at night and wake up in the morning, right?
Mangaka are really lost creatures.
That doesn't matter.
Anyway, what did you want to talk about this early in the morning?
Onii-chan, you skipped class yesterday, right?
Eh? Y-Yeah.
My body was tired from staying up late after all.
I went back and slept in the morning.
Lies!
I know. You were with Miyamura-senpai, right?
Mizuki told me. You did meet with her, right?
You know about Miyamura?
She's famous, you know.
The only person who doesn't know her is you who doesn't go to school.
Is that so?
Well, because she is pretty, the boys are all over her.
They say skipping class is one of her habits.
And sometimes when she leaves from class, she doesn't listen to anything the teacher says.
When asked to do an errand, she doesn't even answer.
Onii-chan's grades are in danger, but you just follow her without knowing anything.
What a troublesome person.
Hey, stop saying bad things about someone who you barely know.
So do you know more about Miyamura-senpai, Onii-chan?
I don't.
I only met her once during Christmas, so that's not even a month.
Christmas...?
Is that true?
Onii-chan, so you broke our promise and went to see Miyamura-senpai instead?
The memories you want to deliver...
should be left to the story.
Next  ef - a tale of memories:
Honesty.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?