Oh, no, what should I do? This is bad!
Look at you...
If you have time to talk, pick them up.
Hey, could someone pick these up too?
They're all out of order now.
We're really sorry.
This little idiot is the culprit.
Thanks...
This won't do.
What's wrong with Aisaka-san?
Apparently Taiga loves Christmas.
She's all into being a "good girl" because Santa's watching.
I see.
Girls love Christmas, don't they?
It's great to help out with the party preparations,
but are you studying for your exams?
Yes.
Lately, we've all been getting together and studying.
Well, Aisaka-san usually gets good grades,
and Takasu-kun, you have pretty good grades too...
But what about Haruta-kun, and Haruta-kun, and Haruta-kun...
You're worried about Haruta?
And Haruta-kun...
Haruta-kun's not helping out with the party, right?
It's okay.
Under Kitamura's orders, Haruta's strictly off limits.
We're having him devote himself to studying.
If so, that's fine.
Just make sure you two don't let your grades drop.
It seems like you two are focusing a lot on this party these days.
I'm a little worried.
I'm sorry.
Will you be coming to the party, Sensei?
Like heck!
I don't have any plans for Christmas Eve, but it's a matter of pride.
But...
I hope it's a success.
Everyone's working so hard for it.
Their efforts have to be rewarded.
Hey! Taiga!
Minorin! Softball?
That's right!
We were stretching in the gym just now.
Kushieda!
If you don't hurry up, Coach is going to yell at you!
Got to go, bye.
Hey.
We keep missing each other.
Yeah.
Got to go.
The Christmas Eve party will definitely be fun!
So you have to come!
Hurry up!
Sorry!
She's been acting weird lately.
Yeah.
But if she comes to the party, she'll definitely cheer up.
You're right.
We need to work hard and make it a fun one!
Yeah!
Let's go, Taiga!
You're late!
What were you two doing?
We had a little accident.
What are you doing here?
I'm in the ornament-making group.
Look, aren't they great?
That's just like you!
Clumsy, clumsy! Do it over!
You...
Is it really okay for you to say stuff like that?
Weren't you trying to be a good girl until Christmas?
What an unfortunate slip of the tongue.
Is that going to be used in the party too?
Nope.
To get permission to use the gym,
the teachers made us promise to clean up the storage room.
Alright.
I'll do that, so you go over there with Taiga and make stars.
Here, scissors.
Okay.
Want to go for it, Aisaka?
Hey, hold up.
Don't hold the scissors like that, it's dangerous.
Like this.
They're pretty close.
We're going to help out over there.
What? What's going on?
Hey, hey.
Don't stir things up.
Stir?
Don't play dumb.
The fact that Taiga...
L-Likes Kitamura.
I don't know why...
But lately, everyone's been all about, "Let's get them together!"
You're worried after all.
Could it be jealousy?
Why the hell would I be jealous?
I just...
I don't like outsiders interfering in people's love lives...
Or something like that.
It's like a father giving his daughter away.
I wouldn’t know.
I've never had a daughter nor have I seen my father.
So she doesn't fall down and gets hurt.
Ever so gently, the woman that you've been protecting so tenderly
gets snatched by some guy.
You don't even know if he'll treat her as well as you did.
I'm not thinking anything like that.
But it's not very interesting, is it?
Seeing Yusaku and Taiga together.
It's twisted.
You're not even her father...
But you've decided to never go after her.
That, and you cherish her.
In your heart, you've got a wife.
The three of you know your roles, just like you were playing house.
Papa's role, Mama's role, and the child's role?
What the hell are you saying?
Why are you playing Papa?
Your relationship with Taiga is really unnatural.
You should quit playing house.
You probably got it wrong from the start.
You should open your eyes before you really get hurt.
Just scratch it all out, and start from the beginning.
And...
Include me...
From the beginning too.
What?
Nothing.
It's okay if you didn't hear me.
What am I saying?
Forget everything I said just now.
In the end...
The person you understand the least is yourself.
Okay, that's it.
Please put your pencils down.
Haruta, you're too loud.
Quiet down.
You still have class tomorrow and the day after.
So don't let Christmas get to your head.
Minorin.
Want to eat lunch with Ryuji and me on the way home?
Sorry, I've got practice now.
Too bad.
Minorin says she's got softball.
I got it, I heard her.
Sorry, I'm really sorry.
Even though you took the time to invite me.
Don't worry about it.
It just seems like you don't have much time to talk lately...
You and Taiga.
Yeah, Coach has completely fallen to the Dark Side.
Practice is really tough.
Bye!
Minorin!
She ran away again.
Yeah...
I was thinking I'd give you two some time alone.
When we arrive at the restaurant...
I'd say, "Oh! I forgot I have something to do!"
You even came up with that lie?
Angel Taiga-sama is really into it.
But, what can you do?
There'll be other chances.
Let's get something to eat on the way home.
I can't.
It wasn't a lie.
I really have something to do.
What sort of something?
I need go to the post office.
I've got to go home first to pick up the stuff.
I'll help.
You don't have to come!
There he is!
Takasu-kun!
Hey, hey, are you free?
You are, right?
I've got something to ask you.
How about lunch with us?
Hey, hey!
Sorry.
I've got plans.
I have to go with her to the post office.
Hey! Ryuji!
I said you don't have to come!
Nevermind that, let's go.
Hey, wait, Takasu-kun!
What's with you? Lying like that.
Besides, why are you so friendly with a girl who's been hanging all over Kitamura-kun?
Scratch that. Rephrase...
The very nice Kiharu-san.
Nevermind, let's go to the post office.
If I go, then it won't be a lie.
And, the stuff is...
You...
Were you going to take all of this by yourself?
Don't touch them!
It's fine, you go over there and bring the cart.
Wai—
What's all this?
If it weren't Christmas, I would have punched you for looking without asking.
But good girl me will forgive you.
These are Christmas presents I'm sending to my parents.
Why are you doing this?
You're not thinking about starting over or something like that?
It's not that.
Because it's Christmas.
Because they're my parents.
What's that mean?
I was trying to keep it a secret...
But I have presents for you and Yacchan.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I know what you're trying to say.
But right now, I don't want to hear it.
I'll go get the cart.
What's this?
Santa Claus?
I went to an all-girls Catholic school ever since elementary school.
I couldn't get into the high school...
Because I was pretty bad in middle school.
At that school, one of the things they did was volunteer work.
With the sisters, well, basically...
I hate saying it like this...
We taught games to disadvantaged children...
And helped them with various things.
The boxes from Santa are for them.
First it's your parents, now it's disadvantaged kids?
Sorry, but I don't get what you're thinking.
I want to tell them, "Someone is watching."
Christmas is a chance.
Even if you don't have parents to raise you...
Even if you can't believe in God...
Even so, someone is watching you...
That's what I want to tell them.
Somewhere, there is really someone out there who notices them.
That sort of thing...
I know.
That's right.
It's just self-satisfaction.
But that's what I want to believe.
Somewhere, someone is watching me.
In my case, Santa.
Santa, Santa...
You really believe in him?
I really love Christmas.
Everywhere you look...
The town, the stores, everywhere is sparkling.
Bright, beautiful.
Everyone looks like they're having fun.
It feels like happiness is just flowing from every corner.
I think to myself, "If I could become part of that..."
By being a good girl...
I want to become part of that happy scene.
To be one of the happy faces in a Christmas town.
And...
I've really met Santa.
When I was little...
Papa and Mama were still at home.
On the night before Christmas...
I was sleeping under the tree in the living room.
I woke up when I got cold.
Then I looked outside the window...
Santa was there.
Santa gave me a present and said,
"Taiga, if you're a good girl, I'll come and see you again."
Well...
Maybe it was all just a dream.
But...
It was a really happy dream.
That's why I want to be a good girl.
Am I being dumb for believing a dream like that?
No, not at all.
It's a dream.
That's okay, right?
It's not reality.
It's not like I'm clinging to someone who really exists.
Keep going, okay, okay, okay.
Stop!
Alright!
The Christmas tree has arrived!
Wow!
When we put it together, it'll definitely be amazing!
It looks like it'll be a great party.
Yuri-chan, why don't you come too?
As I said, like heck!
It's a matter of pride.
Ah, that reminds me. I should buy myself a treat.
Like a watch or a bag or some accessories...
A treat for working hard for thirty years.
What?
I bet you just think it's a waste a money.
I bet you think, "a treat for yourself," is just a marketing trick for single women, right?
Aisaka...
They say that you need 70 million yen to retire, but this is no time to panic.
But you know, if you hold back on everything you want, and at the end you think...
"I did it! I've saved up!"
What are you going to do with that high powered hybrid car you bought if the world turns to a place where you can't use it?
I've got it!
Maybe I should buy a condo?
It's here, it's here.
Are all the parts here?
How did you get something this great?
It was the decoration at this modeling event I did.
I got them to give it to me.
What do you think?
Do you get my awesomeness?
Yeah! Despite being a Stupid Chihuahua, this is amazing!
This is a great tree, I've got to give you that!
It'll be even greater after it's done.
Alright, everyone!
Full power into assembly!
Are these the right parts for the legs?
Wow, I'm so excited.
What's next?
What's this?
Isn't that for the top?
Aisaka-san.
You seem pretty light, could you get on my back and attach this?
With the shoes I wore to the bathroom?
To each their own, I guess.
No, please take them off.
Hey, Ryuji!
What are you doing?
You help out too!
This is probably next.
Hey! What are you doing? That was dangerous!
What are you doing, Taiga?
You're really athletic!
Just what you'd expect from Tenori Taiga!
But that's what I want to believe...
Somewhere, someone is watching me.
Taiga...
You're not alone.
Maybe there wasn't someone who was watching you these past seventeen years.
But now it's different.
You have new friends.
Kitamura's here.
Yasuko-chan and myself... Even Inko-chan's here.
When tomorrow comes, I'm sure Kushieda too...
Their efforts have to be rewarded.
That's right.
They have to be rewarded.
Everyone is going to be happy.
Everyone is going to be rewarded.
It's huge!
Wow!
Kitamura-kun!
I brought this from home.
Put this on the top.
Are you sure? Something this pretty?
It looks kinda expensive.
It's okay.
It's my favorite ornament.
But it's too big, so I can't put it on the tree in my apartment.
Alright!
Then I'll put it on carefully!
Curtains closed!
It's plugged in!
Alright!
I'm going to turn off the lights.
We did it!
It's amazing.
It's really beautiful.
We did it.
I'm sorry!
Was anyone hurt?
Minorin, it's alright.
It was an accident.
You couldn't do anything about it.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It's not your fault.
This was just an unlucky accident...
No.
It's my fault.
I think it was because I was spacing out.
Hitting the ball like that...
On top of that...
Breaking something so important to you.
Please...
It probably won't be like it was.
But please let me do what I can.
Then, Ryuji will help...
No!
No, please stop! Not that!
Minorin...
Takasu-kun, please, go.
Please let me work on this by myself.
Please stop.
Let me take responsibility.
This kind of thing...
Having you help me like this...
I...
We don't have time.
You do what you have to do for yourself.
I won't be helping you.
I'll be doing it for myself.
Takasu-kun.
Yeah.
Takasu-kun...
Takasu-kun.
I'm listening.
I'm here.
Look.
It's pretty, isn't it?
What was broken can be fixed.
So cheer up.
It won't be like it was before.
But, it's still sparkling.
I don't know whether it can be fixed or not.
It will!
It's okay.
It'll be fixed.
However many times it breaks.
Everyone!
We are truly sorry!
Thanks, Minorin.
It's even cuter than before.
Kushieda!
Come tomorrow, to the party.
It'll definitely be fun!
I want to spend it with you!
I can't.
I can't go.
I caused all this trouble.
But I'll be waiting!
Don't wait!
I won't go.
I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting!
Christmas Eve, Christmas Eve, Christmas Eve, Christmas Eve!
It's Christmas Eve party time!
I want another cup of fruit punch.
Huh? Where did Taiga go?