Now, we're going to start Kaleido Star.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
keep your room brightly lit
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Yes, Miss Layla!
Well, well, well.
Everyone, have you ever been told,
"Don't push yourself too hard"?
"You should try it next time," or
"Why don't you try harder next
time?" or something like that?
But there is something I can't
accomplish unless I do it right now.
I have to fight now.
I don't want to feel regret
because I didn't try.
I don't want that! I don't want that!
Dare mo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Dokoka ni aru
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja nai
Saigo made yareru to ittetane
Kitto tsuyogatte itanda
Itsudatte muchabakka de zutto karamawari de
Dakedo anata dake ga soba ni ita
Daremo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Arukidaseru
Koko kara nanika ga hajimaru
Shinjite itai
Mada minu hikari yakusoku
no basho e to tsuzuite yuku
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja naisa
Let's eat.
You have an amazing appetite.
I have to eat a lot first if
I want to gain muscle mass.
But, still...
Miss Layla said she would eat her
meal in her room again today.
What?
She stopped trying to
lose weight, didn't she?
She said that she wanted
to keep her concentration.
Oh, I'll take her meal to her.
"An Amazing Bond."
Here it is.
You seem a little tired, Miss Layla.
Maybe...
If that's the case,
in Japan, we have something
we call "Ume-boshi."
It's very sour, but it
works when you're tired.
I have some specially pickled by my mother.
I'll go get some for you right now.
Don't worry.
I'll be okay if I sleep well tonight.
Oh... Are you sure?
Thanks for your concern, though.
I understand.
Then please get some rest.
Good night!
It will be all right by tomorrow.
By tomorrow...
You're making me dizzy! Let me go!
You're so violent!
Say whatever you want.
But I'm in a good mood because Miss Layla
and I are finally partners for real!
Even I think it's weird.
But I think no matter what the
legendary great maneuver is like,
I think I can definitely pull it off.
I don't think I'm going to fail.
So don't you think it's about time?
Tell me about the legendary great maneuver.
No, not yet.
What?
The reversed Empress.
A suffering queen.
A suffering queen? It means...
Miss Layla!
What's wrong?
Didn't you just hit your shoulder?
I just lost my balance and
scratched it a little.
You don't need to worry.
Could it be...?
She really hit her shoulder after all?
No, it can't be.
It can't be. It can't be.
Because she made a promise
not to keep any secrets.
'Cause I'm Miss Layla's partner.
Using the swing, jump across
to the log over there.
Then push off that log with your hand
and come back to the original swing.
This will be the final stage of practice.
Sora, you're late!
Sorry.
I'm late because I was putting this on!
This way, I weigh the same as Miss Layla.
What is that?
Weights used for scuba diving.
Will you be all right?
I can't let you bear all the burden.
Because we're partners, aren't we?
You're right.
Sora, you still don't have enough
skill. But we don't have time.
Work yourself to death and master it.
We're going back to Kaleido Stage tomorrow.
Yes.
Match each other's timing.
Sora's lagging.
I wonder if it's because of those weights.
Go for it!
You can, like, do it!
Let me worry about the timing.
Just put everything you have into it.
Okay.
Good. Your timing is getting synchronized.
Please let me try one more time.
I did it.
Miss Layla!
Are you all right, Miss Layla?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's because you're matching
your timing to me...
It's not your fault.
Let's continue. We shouldn't waste time.
Okay.
Please...
A little longer...
Please last a little longer.
Miss Layla!
Miss Layla, is something wrong?!
No. It's nothing.
But...
I said it's nothing!
Really, it's nothing.
Miss Layla...
I'm positive she was holding
her right shoulder back then.
Could she be hiding an injury?
But, why?
She promised to tell me
everything from now on.
Oh, yes.
She laughed.
Good.
Why in the world are you
wearing something like that?
Ken said that you looked down.
So we wondered if you were worrying
about the show the day after tomorrow.
You don't need to worry.
Young woman!
Believe in your future!
Do you think maybe this was a bad idea?
Do you think?
Thank you, Mia, Anna!
You're right.
The only thing I can do is believe. Right?
That's right, Sora.
Fight!
Yes!
I already made up my mind
to believe in Miss Layla.
Once I've made up my mind like this,
I have to believe in Miss
Layla no matter what.
The upright Moon.
Lingering doubts and hidden anxieties.
Can you really believe in
her no matter what, Sora?
We've returned to Kaleido Stage.
Miss Layla and I both
did everything we could.
Tomorrow, we're going to
perform before the audience.
And yet...
And yet you still say we're not qualified?
Welcome back. Welcome back.
Oh... Well...
All of you...
Welcome back, Layla, Sora.
Jean...
Everyone here realized that the
current Kaleido Stage is a fake.
Tomorrow's show...
Until it's your time to appear,
we're going to do our best
to heighten the atmosphere.
Let us be part of a true show.
Let's work together again!
Everyone...
What are you doing?
Has that so-called spirit
of the stage qualified you?
That's what I thought.
It just means that you're
not capable after all.
You should just admit it.
If you do that, I can cancel the
performance with just one phone call,
and finish everything for you.
Don't worry them unnecessarily.
How dare you say something like that?!
You don't give a damn about the cast's life!
It's about time to wake up, Layla.
There's no way that you'll be able
to do the legendary great maneuver.
It's impossible.
You know that, don't you?
Yuri, stop.
You're just going to waste your life.
Yuri!
Don't you see that Kalos is deceiving you?!
He's using you!
It doesn't matter!
I believe that I'm able to perfect
the legendary great maneuver.
Everyone here wants tomorrow's
performance to succeed...
All except you.
Not Kalos.
He's trying to profit from your death,
and take over as owner again.
Just like he did to my father.
Am I right?!
But, unfortunately,
whether you perfect the maneuver or not,
Kaleido Stage is finished!
What?!
What do you mean?
Kaleido Stage will be sold
after tomorrow's show.
That is the investors' idea.
So no matter what you do, it's useless!
That's why perfecting the legendary
great maneuver means nothing!
I was proud to be partnered with you.
So don't make an unsightly
scene in front of me.
Sora...
Yes.
No matter what happens, we
will do our best tomorrow.
Yes.
We will never cancel the show.
This is not good.
It seems what I did a second ago
made my condition much worse.
Familiar smell,
familiar atmosphere...
I'm at Kaleido Stage again.
Everyone was waiting for us,
for Miss Layla and me.
But, we're not qualified to perform
the legendary great maneuver yet.
Sora!
Do you know where Miss Layla is?
I want to start rehearsal, but...
I don't know where she is...
Really?
I wonder where she went.
Here I thought I hadn't
seen you in a long time...
How could you do this to yourself
and let it get this bad?
The pain must be excruciating.
Since you forced yourself to keep
training after you pulled your muscle,
you're suffering from a stress fracture.
We need to get you hospitalized immediately.
No, I can't.
Tomorrow is the date of the performance.
Layla, you can't do that.
If you put unnecessary stress on it now,
your right shoulder will never be...
I don't care.
Layla!
Just do something about this pain.
And please don't say anything
about this to anybody.
Are you serious?
I am.
Layla! Layla!
So don't make an unsightly
scene in front of me.
Unsightly scene?
Yes.
What?!
Miss Layla?
How is Miss Layla?
She's sleeping right now.
Is her shoulder hurting?
You knew that?
I thought so... That time...
Miss Layla!
You don't need to worry.
So she did hit her shoulder.
How is her condition?
Oh... well...
Then tomorrow's performance will be...
I... I think I have to wait and
observe her condition a little more.
It's my fault.
I noticed it at the time.
But, I...
You!
Are you going to kill Layla too?!
Please stop it, Mr. Yuri!
Sora!
Stop it! This is a hospital!
If Sora noticed her condition,
there is no way that Kalos
missed it as a coach.
This guy knew what was going on,
and he still let Layla do it!
I don't think...
Kalos would never do something like that!
No. He's right.
What?
I noticed Layla's shoulder was hurting.
What? Then why?
It's obvious!
In order to get Kaleido Stage back!
No.
You're wrong, Yuri.
Layla...
Miss Layla...
I'm sorry, but I contacted them.
I know.
Kalos didn't say anything
because this is a matter I should
decide entirely for myself.
Isn't that right, Kalos?
I should have done the same for Arlon.
After I saw his practice,
I knew how difficult that maneuver was.
And of course, I knew how
dangerous it was too.
Arlon said that he would make sure to
perfect the legendary great maneuver
in order to make Kaleido
Stage more successful.
I thought I had faith in those words.
But on the final day of rehearsal,
I asked him,
"Are you sure you can do it?"
I am the one who caused him to worry.
I should have believed in him
to the last, but I didn't.
That's why, this time,
I'm going to believe in both
Layla and Sora to the last.
You finally broke free from the past, Kalos.
Hah, this is stupid!
You can't fool me with pretty words!
Anyway, tomorrow's show is cancelled!
If you do that, I'll never forgive you.
Layla, don't you understand that
I'm saying it's impossible?
First of all, you're injured.
Miss Layla...
Well...
I think it would be better
if we cancel this time.
What did you say?
Anyhow, let's get your shoulder
completely healed first!
Then we can try it.
We'll have another chance at it!
When?!
Oh... well, um...
A month later?
A year later?
Ten years later?
Well...
And even then, will there
still be a Kaleido Stage?
Can you tell me that you won't
be injured at that time?
And what will have happened to me by then?
Well, that...
I don't know, but...
What about those people who have been
looking forward to seeing the show?
The show already has started.
I can't bear the thought
of disappointing someone.
After my mother passed away, and I
watched my father drown in grief,
I pledged to myself that I
would never make my father sad.
In spite of that...
Anyway, make sure to finish the movie shoot.
After that, do whatever you want.
...I disappointed him.
I don't want to disappoint anybody anymore.
Why?
Why do you insist on it that much,
even betting on your own life?
Yuri, you've changed, to not
know something like that.
I do it because I'll receive the
best applause when I perfect it.
The best applause...
This is a duel between me and my fate.
I'm going to win,
and I'll make sure I'll
receive the best applause.
If I back out now,
I don't know if I'll ever
feel the same again.
That's why this is the only chance.
This is how I feel right now, Sora.
Miss Layla,
I understand how you feel.
In order to receive the best applause,
I'll also challenge fate with you!
Why? For Kaleido Stage?
To tell you the truth,
I just want to attempt
this maneuver. That's all.
When I've done it right,
please give me a big hand.
Okay.
Father...
Do whatever you like.
Yuri...
So you're not afraid of dying?
We're not going to die.
We'll make sure to succeed.
The time is ripe.
"Next Kaleido Star"
Miss Layla.
Sora...
Layla...
Sora!
Sora...
Layla...
Yume... Everyone...
We're...
Let's start, Sora.
Yes!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"An Amazing Comeback."
My wings are my dream and on towards the sky!
Boku wa koko ni iru sora to
michi no aida de mukai kaze
Soshite mae o muiteiru mou nido
to kanashimi ga furanai youni to
Ano kabe o koete kokomade kitanda
Nigedashitaku naru koto wa nando mo aru
Dakedo kokoni irunara taishite bibitte inai
Kakinaguri no uta "hajimekara yareba iisa"
Umaku kakenakute boku wa waratte iru