Yuu, are you done over there?
Sure am!
Gotcha!
Mitsuki and Rina’s
Graduation Celebrat
Graduation Celebration
Boy were you guys fast now.
And, sent.
You can head over now!
Send
Cancel
You can head over now!
Now we just gotta spruce up this area…
Wait, you guys weren’t  done yet?!
I already called on them now…
Where’re the party crackers?!
kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
I find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
while at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
I just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
We may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings run deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
If things stay like this
dou ka shichau
I might go crazy
gaman de wa
Nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
by just holding back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
Won’t you kiss me? It’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
Can I kiss you? It’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
With our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
Glad we made it through those exams, Rina.
I sure hope we pass.
I’m sure we did fine.
By the way, I wonder what’s up with Sumi.
I can’t think of what she’d need from us.
Good question…
Maybe she wants to ask more about her new role.
Wait, where are we headed again?
But isn’t this… why would Sumi be at your place?
I kinda know the answer already.
I’m hom—
Mitsuki, Rina. Congrats on your graduation!
Mitsuki?!
shake
Pudding and Mitsuki’s Resolve
Thank you, guys!
Congrats!!
So this  is what was up.
Though you’re a day early.
But are you sure I should be part of this too?
You two are exactly who we’re celebrating.
I know it’s a bit sudden, but we’ve prepared some dessert for you!
Mitsuki and Rina’s
Graduation Celebration
A bucket…?
Mitsuki and Rina’s
Graduation Celebration
It’s a bucket of matcha pudding now!
Matcha?!
Mitsuki and Rina’s
Graduation Celebration
How cool! I’ve never seen this sort of bucket pudding before!
Congrats!!
I never get to have this much matcha!
What’s wrong, Rina?
Oh, nothing… I was just taken aback as well…
You’ll find that pudding really helps your studying!
Oh, really?
I ate so much of this before exams, that I’m already sick of it…
I can't really say that though...
Did you all make this from scratch?!
That’s right now!
I’ll dig right in then.
H-How do you find it?!
My! You have azuki mixed in here too!
Each bean packs so much flavor!
touched
I see someone’s tearing up here.
Congrats!!
I’m so glad you’re enjoying it!
I don’t want you to graduate yet now!
There there, SumiSumi.
Now you’ve even got me tearing up here!
Oh, and thank you too, Mikan!
Huh? The tears all dried up…
Presentation of presents
Sakura Trick
I’ve got some letters and presents for you two now!
Sumi
Mitsuki
Congrats!!
Thanks so much!
Is it fine if we read them now?
It’ll be too embarrassing! Please read them later…
Mind if we open the presents then?
They’re my handmade mustaches!
Cute now, right?
They’re handmade?!
How strange…
Speaking of strange… that thing hanging up there couldn’t be…
It’s a chandelier.
I knew it!
I brought it along!
fragile
heave-ho
I thought it’d help liven things up!
fragile
heave-ho
That seems just like you somehow…
fragile
heave-ho
But it’s a rental, right?
Of course not, it’s a present!
Really now?!
Ta-da
Me and Kaede will now perform impersonations!
I’m your President, Sonoda.
What was it you stuffed in there?!
smile
I’m just all smiles?
Big Sis
You must carry yourself in a respectful manner.
Congrats!!
slide
Huh? Why’re you hiding behind me?
Mind speaking Japanese—
We’ll just be out for a minute.
Congrats!!
I think Kaedekko was crying.
That’s pretty rare.
She spent a lot more time with them after all.
Big Sis
Little Sis
Sis! Haruka said she’ll get us some brown sugar syrup!
Syrup?!
azuki and brown sugar...
Matcha pudding with
Syrup drizzled on a fine azuki matcha pudding…
Haruka.
Yes?
craving
Would you happen to have anything with garlic in it?
Something with garlic?
Okay, then I’ll make something for you!
rush
Yay!
Pasta’s one of her specialties! Lucky for you!
I can hardly wait!
Haruka’s homemade cooking… I’m kind of jealous…
Is it good to be having garlic the night before graduation?
I couldn’t care less! I’m in a garlic mood right now!
R-Really?
rattle
Sorry for that, you guys.
Kaedekko’s back to normal!
What’s that  supposed to mean?
I bet that was a jab at Kaede…
Now we’ll resume our imitations of—
You don’t have to force it.
Don’t force it.
Yuu, I think we need another spoon.
They’re in the kitchen cupboard.
You can’t have our guests doing all the work.
Mitsuki and Rina’s
Graduation Celebration
That girl…
Hold on one sec!
Haruka’s in there already! Add Yuu, and they might try something!
Excuse me for a bit.
Hey! What are you two up to?!
Oh…
I’ve prepared some clam pasta.
Oh, how nice…
I could’ve sworn you two would be kissing again.
Although you actually seem to be listening to me.
Why might you two be silent right now?
Will you say something already?!
It’s got nothing to do with you!
Of course it does!
And why’s that?!
Well that’s because…
My sweet…
I’m worried about my sweet little sister, and I also like Haruka myself…
Big Sis
My sweet…
sweet…
Sweet… potato, you mean?
Sis!
You’re always too protective of me!
That’s my duty as a big sister!
Little Sis
What’s with all this “big sis” talk, when you can’t even get up yourself?!
Big Sis
That’s no big deal, right?! At least I help you study in return!
Matcha Baum
You even ate my matcha baumkuchen yesterday!
Don’t think I didn’t know that you wore my culottes the other day!
Matcha Baum
They  sure do get along…
yell
Don’t worry, Haruka.
Let’s do it in front of her!
Can I ask what “it” is?
Kiss!
What’s that?! Hold it, Yuu!
You can’t do that!
Why can’t you just get lost?!
As if I would!
What bliss…
What’s that serene look for?!
S-Sorry…
Wait, Yuu…
No, no! Cut it out, Yuu!
We really shouldn’t do this!
ooh
aah
Why’s that? Aren’t you always doing this?
Hold on! Yuu…
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
Haruka
Little Sis
Big Sis
I mean, you haven’t even told Haruka you love her yet.
And what does that matter, huh?!
This is something Haruka and I have decided on!
It’s okay since we’re special!
We do this 'cause we’re special!
I see. So you two kiss each other just because you’re special to each other…
Then don’t I have a chance too?
What do you mean by that?
What I mean is…
I love you, Haruka.
Please go out with me.
Big Sis
Little Sis
Pudding and Mitsuki’s Resolve
End
West Misato High School
60th
Graduation
Ceremony
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Congratulations
on
graduating
Sonoda Mitsuki.
Here.
Congratulations
onh
graduating
Congratulations,
Graduates
Sakura Trick
There she is.
Congratulations, Mitsuki!
Hey Mitsuki.
Oh, Sakai!
Please give me your second button!
Well, I can’t really…
Please stop crying…
I’ve lost her again…
That was one touching ceremony!
Especially my singing, right?
What a braggart.
I’d say Shizuku had you beat...
I-I don’t know…
But she’s not denying it.
Yuu, any clue where Harupoppo is?
She was right…
She’s not here!
Where’d she run off to?!
Now, now…
I’ll go find her!
And off she goes…
Is this the place she mentioned?
Maybe I should’ve told the others I’d be going off somewhere.
I’ll bet Yuu’s already looking for me.
Can I ask you to wait for me behind the tennis court after the ceremony?
O-Okay…
I’d prefer if you kept this from the others…
That includes Yuu of course…
It’s okay… I doubt anyone’ll see me here.
There she is!
But what’s she up to?
Haru—
Forgive me for being so sudden.
Oh, don’t worry.
I just wanted to hear your decision.
My decision…?
I love you too, Mitsuki.
What did you just…?
You really mean that?!
But you’ve already got Yuu, and…
I see! It’s not like you two have confessed or anything, right?
Then that means that w-w-w-we’re going out now, right?!
Poking each other?
Pokey pokey!
I meant dating!
So what would that entail?
Well it would be things like…
walking while holding hands…
or going out places…
or staying over at each other’s places.
Going on dates in general…
As well as kissing I guess…
That’s all stuff I do with Yuu already!
Oh gosh! It’s almost like I’m listing out my desires…
So that’d mean Yuu and I are…
You know… you really aren’t getting me here…
I-I do get you!
No you don’t!
I guess you’re right...
I’ll try to find it out together with Yuu…
the kind of love you’re feeling.
But I really appreciate you telling me your true feelings.
So please…
W-Was it something I said?!
I think I know how you truly feel.
You’ll bring in Yuu, even at a time like this.
The way you put my sister above anyone else…
That’s partly what I came to love about you.
Though that sounds a bit weird, huh?
But let me be selfish… just this once, okay?
There’s a petal on my—
This one was on purpose.
Mitsuki! Where could you be?
Rina.
I’ve been looking all over for you!
Sorry about that. I’m coming right over!
Yuu?!
Oh, maybe I’m seeing things…
Or not!
Yuu?! What’re you doing here?!
I came here searching for you.
So you saw all that?!
No clue what you mean.
Out with the truth already!
What are you talking about?!
Then what were  you doing back here?
ant
Little Sis
I got distracted by some ants.
ant
Oh, okay.
Went along
with it
Hey Mitsuki?
Oh, right.
Haruka. Come with me.
S-She’s so fast!
Mitsuki, you’ve got a pretty refreshing look for a change.
Who, me?!
Ever since the party ended yesterday, you had this worried look about you.
Big Sis
How could you even notice that?!
It’s the same for me too.
Whenever I’m troubled, you’re the first to notice.
You weren’t able to tell Haruka, huh?
…the fact that you’re going to a far-off university.
So you even knew about that…
Of course I did.
Since I’ve always been watching over you…
Or something like that!
Let’s keep taking things on together, at the same uni!
You’re right. I’ll keep counting on you then.
I guess we’ll also be saying goodbye to this room in a few days, huh?
Yuu… you really did hear everything, right?
Everything we talked about…
Yup.
I see…
Hey, Yuu.
Do you  get it?
…the kind of love Mitsuki felt?
She’s just got some screws loose from over-studying!
I doubt that…
I still wonder what it is I feel for you…
I do think it’s the kind of love that Mitsuki mentioned…
…but I’ve been told otherwise.
We walk while holding hands, we go out together, and sleepover at each other’s places.
pound
We’ve sure kissed a lot too, huh?
Right?
pound
Haruka…
I love you.
I just thought we might come up with something if we kissed right after saying that.
Yuu! Did you figure something out just now?
Let’s try it again.
I’ll go for it this time.
Yuu…
I love you.
I love you, Haruka.
Yuu… I love you.
…I love you.
I love you.
This is way too embarrassing, Haruka!
You got that right!
Haruka…
Did you figure anything out?
I’m not really sure I have…
I see…
Maybe we’ll figure out what she meant someday…
Of course we will! It’s just my sister we’re talking about here!
Fire Extinguisher
The chill’s finally out of the air!
lt’s about time we get to change uniforms, huh?
Yup!
Wanna go see the cherry blossoms with me sometime?
Morning!
G’mornin’!
Good morning.
Morning.
What’s that?
My first gag of the new term.
Forget new term, it’s a whole new year, right?
Somehow it all feels the same…
Especially 'cause there aren’t any new students.
And it’s all the same people in our class.
I don’t really have a problem with that.
Right?
That’s true.
If some of us were  split up, it would cause an uproar.
Mornin’!
Good morning, guys!
Wouldn’t it?
Right about that.
Yup.
It sure would.
What’re you all smiling about?
Who knows?
C’mon! Tell us!
West Misato High School
Let’s step in together!
Haruka.
Yuu.
Here we go!
Sakura Trick
End
show
Sakura Trick
won’t you kiss?
Won’t you kiss?
kiss and love!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
The time we share alone
futari dake no himitsu ga
the secret we keep
futari dake no yakusoku
the promise we both hold
aru kara ne
we have it all
yorokobi wakachi aete
If we share in our joy
kanashimi wake aetara
and split our sorrow
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
we’ll be happier than we’d be alone
ashita no omoide wo, saa fuyasou
Memories to come… let’s make them now
ippai ni shichaou ne
We’ll make lots and lots
love you!
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki, tokubetsu na no
The miracle that we met in this huge world… it’s special
anata ja nai to dame dakara
It had to be you all along
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
It’s something we can’t do unless we’re together
ima sugu ni, daisuki kiss and love
Right now, let’s share a kiss and love
Thank you for watching our fansub version of Sakura Trick! —Lazy Lily Fansubs
Please support the anime by buying the DVD/Blu-ray whenever or wherever they are available!
Remember: More support = Possible new anime season!