Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
教室\k21}のドアくぐるとほんの少し
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
胸を張って歩き出せる
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す今この胸で
Now, with these hands that tremble
Mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
見送った手を振った
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne, to
よかったね、と
So happy for them
Hey, Senpai!
Let me try out my new move on you!
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
I call it "Toughen up in 120 hours"!
One, two, here we go, let's dance!
One, two, whoops, let's dance.
Come on, it'll be fine!
Come on.  My new move!  My new mooove!
It's like "BAM"!
Aren't they cute, Shiina-san?
How foolish.
Are you even listening?
Seriously?
Seriously, is this an elementary school?
Aww, fine!  I'll go ask Ooyama-senpai!
We keep getting more and more brats.
Hey.  Are you talking to me?
I'm God.
Huh?  You're still saying that?
After bawling in Otonashi's arms?
Who'd you say was crying?
You're the one who's gonna cry.
Now, realize the greatness of clothespins.
Realize how worthless you are in comparison to clothespins...
and despair.
C-Clothespins.
They can hold stuff...
They can hold it and it won't fall!
Your clean clothes won't get dirty!
Amazing!
Ahh!  They can even be used as replacements for paperclips!
In comparison to that, what am I ?!
I'm not good for anything at all!
Hey.
Don't use hypnotism for revenge.
Otonashi-san!  Good morning!
What's with all that?
He's the one who started it.
I prefer to conduct myself peacefully as much as possible.
What's peaceful about that?
A grown man's kneeling and crying his eyes out.
Otonashi-kun, Naoi-kun?
I've got some business to discuss with you.
Come in here please.
Staff Building, 3rd Floor - Empty Room
What's going on?
Calling us into a place like this...
Naoi-kun, I want you to try and recover Otonashi-kun's lost memories.
Are you giving me an order?
Just who do you think you are?!
She's your leader.
Your superior.
Just do what she says.
Wait...
My memories?!
That's right.  Your memories.
Naoi-kun's hypnotism is the real deal.
He should be able to get back your lost memories.
Hmm, I see.
I'd certainly like to try.
Wait just a minute!
Don't go deciding that on your own.
What's wrong?
You're not telling me you'd rather stay like this?
Ah... well, that's...
I want to remember again
But... what's this anxious feeling?
Is it... because if I get them back...
this daily life might not be able to continue?
Wait, I...
Have I really...
grown to love living with these guys that much?
But, if I remember my past...
will I still be able to continue like normal?
Still... even so-
Otonashi-kun?
I understand.
No matter what your past is...
please don't lose sight of yourself.
No matter what happens to you...
I'll always be your ally.
Please say something.
I'm your ally too, so don't worry.
Thanks, it helps to hear that.
What?  What's with that difference?!
Oh, fine.
Just sit down, please.
Now then, let's begin.
Onii-chan, is school fun?
It's not fun at all.
Because I'm not even attending.
If you go, it might be fun.
It might be fun if my head worked better.
I'm pretty dumb...
There's no place for people with bad grades.
Isn't studying fun?
Of course it's not.
It's studying.
What about your friends?  Do you play with friends?
Watching TV or playing games alone is more fun.
Playing along with your friends hobbies...
laughing at their jokes even when they're not funny...
all that does is tire me out.
Really?  I'm looking forward to studying.
I'm looking forward to making friends, too!
Oh, that's right...
Here.
Thank you, Onii-chan!
You idiot!
I... don't know why I'm alive.
I have no reason to live.
I have no interest in others.
Living without concern for others...
That's the way to live.
Working a job that earns me just enough to eat...
A life like that was enough...
But even so...
I always continued to visit my younger sister.
With my meager income...
I'd buy her manga magazines.
I'd always just go into the bookstore...
and arbitrarily grab something off the counter.
So, I didn't even know if it was the same magazine.
It's possible it was a different magazine...
and she wasn't able to follow the stories properly.
But...
Thank you, Onii-chan!
My sister always loved it and said the same thing.
In the end, it seemed she'd be happy with anything.
My sister was different than me..
She had hope in her life.
Surely, she'd be able to find a reason to live as well.
And yet...
for two straight years...
her life was spent confined to a hospital bed.
It was pitiable...
I wished I could trade places with her.
I, with no hope...
no reason to live... if we could only switch...
Those feelings of compassion...
kept bringing me back.
Winter came.
Summer was bad enough...
but my job in Winter was that much worse.
My fingertips would grow numb...
and feel like they were ready to fall off.
Even so...
I continued on in order to live.
To live...?
For what?
I shouldn't think about it.
If I think about it, I'll probably just quit.
I have to at least keep doing this...
In order to eat...
and to buy presents for my younger sister.
That's right.
For Christmas, I'll talk to the doctor...
and maybe she can go outside for a little while.
I wonder if you can still use a wheelchair when the snow is packed up.
Well, if not, I'll just carry her.
I should be able to handle carrying her with no problem.
Then, we'll go to her favorite shop and buy her whatever she wants.
If I can manage it, I'd like to take her to a nice shop to have some cake.
I'd better start saving.
If you can get out for Christmas, where would you like to go?
To Main Street!
Are you sure?
Well cause, all the trees, they have lights on them!
Did you know that?
No... I don't really go there on Christmas...
I hear it's really pretty!
It was last year, I heard.
That's what the doctor said.
Well then shall we go there?
Can I?
I'll try to negotiate so you can.
Even if they say no... I'll take you out in secret.
Really?
Really, really.
Yay!  Thank you, Onii-chan!
That's the biggest thank you I've ever gotten.
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry!
I started working multiple jobs.
All I did at home was sleep.
Now that I've got a goal, I feel like I can really work.
My only worry...
was that her condition seemed to be worsening.
Not surprisingly, I didn't get permission to let her leave.
So, I...
waited until after visiting hours were over...
snuck into her room...
and took her out into the night.
Wow!  Hey, can you see?
It's incredible.
Wow.  It's so pretty.
Isn't it?
It's so pretty.
I'm glad I saw it, too.
It's all thanks to you.
Now then, let's have even more fun, okay?
First up is your present!
I'll get you whatever you want.
As a matter of fact, your dear brother saved up a ton of cash for tonight.
So even if it's expensive, I'll get you whatever you want.
Anything you want?
Let's go into a shop.
Even a jewelry store would be fine.
Should we just go to a department store?
Onii-chan...
Hmm?
Thank you.
Yeah!
After shopping, there's plenty more waiting for you!
Next is dinner!
I don't really know about this stuff, but I got a reservation for a good-looking place from a magazine.
They serve you in courses.
A full-course dinner!  Amazing, right?
It'll be my first time trying it, too.
After that, I kept talking alone, and walked on...
I'll be going now.
Can you really live there all by yourself?
Won't you be lonely?
I'll be alright.
I'm used to it.
Really?  Will you really be alright?
If you run into any trouble, let me know right away.
You can come to eat over here any time you want, too.
Yes.  Thank you very much.
Thank you for everything you've done for me.
I...
had a reason to live the whole time...
That reason was... right next to me all along.
I just didn't realize it.
To hear her say, "thank you"...
Just by hearing that...
I was able to live.
Just by feeling needed by her...
I was able to feel alive.
I was happy.
I'm such a fool.
To only realize that now.
She was such a precious existence...
and I didn't do anything for her.
She was always...
in the hospital...
with nothing to do but read the manga magazines I brought her.
With only that...
With a life like that...
Was she truly happy?
And then...
My life after losing her...
Is it over as well?
The days I spent satisfied with a happiness I never noticed...
those times had passed away.
For me...
There's nothing left at all.
Thank you for all you've done.
Congratulations on your discharge.
Thank you very much!
Take care of yourself.
Maybe I can find a reason to live again.
A reason to live... I think I can find it.
If I can devote my life...
For the sake of someone else...
Otonashi Yuzuru-dono
Have you remembered?
Yeah...
It doesn't look like you're about to say it was a great life.
Please, I need to be alone for a while.
I had a shallow and colorless existence.
Until you taught me that there was a reason to live...
I found it...
And then...
I died halfway through my dream?
Died without finishing anything?
That can't be it!
It can't...
I can't even die!
Hatsune!
Have you calmed down?
Yeah.
It's natural to feel a little upset after your memories return.
It's not just you.
I'm pretty weak, huh?
I think I've realized how strong you are all over again.
That's not true.
Anyway, has anything changed?
Hm?
Like your feelings... are you going to continue to fight in the Warfront?
I'll keep going.
I can't die like this.
I see.
It looks like you've found a reason.
Yeah.
Once again, I'm in your care.
UTW Presents:
Principal's Office
So, you said you had a report?
We don't have enough meal tickets for tonight.
What are we gonna do?  Should we go with Tornado?
No.
Today's operation is... Monster Stream!
Monster Stream
It's finally here!
A carnival of despair!
What is this operation?
You mean monsters exist?
In this world?
Yes.  The King of the River.
King of the River?
A little ways from here, there's a river, right?
Monster Stream
We're gonna go top off our food provisions there.
W-Wait... is this just simple river-fishing?
Yeah... why, what's wrong?
Uh... nothing.
I got taken in by the name and imagined something ridiculous again.
I wonder who'll win?
Botanical Garden
I'm looking forward to this~
Hmm?
What're you doing here?
I'm weeding, among other things.
I-I see...
Oh... hey!
You should come too!
We're all gonna go river-fishing.
River?
It's against the rules to go there.
Because it's dangerous.
It's fine.
You're not the Student Council President anymore.
Forget the rules for a while.
But I'm still a student...
Why'd you bring her with you?
What's the problem?
Let's let her join us.
She's an enemy!
The enemy of the Warfront!
You're an idiot, huh?
How foolish.
Listen to me.  She's not our enemy anymore!
Yeah but she's still kinda the Student Council President!
Incidentally, we also have the current replacement President.
That's right.
But more importantly, I'm God.
You're not God!
What do we do, Yurippe?
She's not the Student Council President anymore.  It's fine.
A-Are you feeling alright?
Looks like we're getting an incredible member...
Oh yeah... how come you guys don't have any gear?
We already contacted the Guild, so we'll be fine.
We've got an appropriate maniac in there.
Below Contact Bridge 2 - Riverside
Maniac?
Who is he?
His name's Saitou.
He's knowledgeable about guns...
but in the Guild, he's known as Fish Saitou.  He's a fishing maniac.
He brought all those fishing supplies in a cart for this operation.
All that?!
How much does this guy love fishing?
Another idiot, huh?
Alright.  Let's get started!
What an idiot.
I might have been your ally in this world.
There was never a person like that.
But wouldn't it be alright if there was?
There's nobody.
Even if there were, they'd just disappear.
Tachibana...
We're not gonna disappear.
So it's okay to make friends with us.
Come on, let's all fish together.
Now what do I do?
That's wrong.  That's wrong.
First you pick a lure, and hook some bait or a worm onto it.
You don't have any problems with bugs, huh?
What's next?
Aim for the river and cast with all your might.
T-Takeyamaaaaaa~
Call me Chriiiiiiiist!
You've got some superhuman strength, don't you?
Overdrive is passive.
Passive?
Maybe...
Maybe... with you, it could be possible.
What could?
Catching the King.
Just like the name of the operation, that thing's a monster.
Something's pulling.
M-Monster Stream!
What is this?
We usually see Monster Stream as a sign of the King's anger.
When that happens, we evacuate.
But...
That girl just might be able to do it!
Are you serious?
How big is this thing?!  The rod will break!
Don't underestimate my craftsmanship!
It was made to handle even the King of the River!
Even so, it's impossible at this rate!
What's going on, you guys are going for the King?
No way that'll work.
Matsushita-godan!
I'll give you some meat udon.  Come and help out!
You got it!
Oho, Hinata-senpai.  You're looking awfully unguarded.
Okay!  How about I kick you as hard as I can and send you flying?
Stop thinking up stupid stuff and help out!
We need reinforcements!
It's Otonashi!
What a weakling.
Hey, you lot!  Pull harder!
Heave-ho!  Heave-ho!  Heave-ho!  Heave-ho!  Heave-ho!  Heave-ho!
Now!
She pulled it in!
And us, too!
Which one's the monster?!
This situation...
Looks bad.
If we fall, we'll get eaten!
Crazy for you!
God never falls.
How foolish.
We're gonna get eaten!
I have to save them.
Hey... with all this, we won't need to use Tornado for a while, huh?
You mean we'll eat this every day?
Before we worry about that, worry about how we'll even preserve it?
Yeah, but it seems a waste to throw it out.
I guess we've no other choice.
Let's make it into one big meal, and treat the regular students.
Ahh, good idea.
Let's do that.
This is just like charity work.
This isn't a Warfront... we're acting more like a ministry.
Well, we don't really have an enemy to fight anymore.
Aren't we going to stop being a Warfront anyway?
Well then, what in the world will we be?
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつもひとりで歩いてた
I've always walked alone
The "Slacking So We Don't Vanish Team"?
What's that?
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返るとみんなは遠く
When I turned around, everyone was far away
Chop, chop, chop, chop.
I never thought a time like this would come.
soredemo atashi wa aruita
それでもあたしは歩いた
Even so, I walked on
Hey, Tachibana.  May I call you by your first name?
Why?
Because we're closer now.
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That's what it was to be strong
Are we?
Aren't we?
Fishing together... cooking together...
and besides... when I first heard it, I thought...
mou nanimo kowaku nai
もう何も恐くない
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
What a beautiful name.
I like it.
I like your name.
sou tsubuyaite miseru
そう呟いてみせる
That's what I try to tell myself
Kanade means, "to play a song", right?
If that's how you'd like to interpret it, I'm okay with that.
My name is Yuzuru.
It's written like "to tie a string".
TL Note: This can mean bowstring or a string on an instrument.
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Eventually, everyone will be alone
I'd like it if you call me that.
Alright, Kanade.
I've got something I'd like to ask you.
What?
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They'll continue to live only through their memories
Could you please stay with us from now on?
Why?
I don't want to fight anybody anymore.
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru youni
孤独さえ愛し笑ってられるように
So I can love and laugh even in this loneliness
I want you to stay with us and have fun.
And... because...
I just like being with you.
atashi wa tatakau n da
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
I see.
If that's what you want, it's what I'll do.
namida nante misenai n da
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will never show you my tears
It's a promise, right?
Yeah.
By the way, where's Yurippe?
Now that you mention it, I haven't seen her.
She's probably off observing somewhere.
She's not really the kind to participate in charity like this.
Hey, you help out, too!
Yurippe!
Yurippe!  Who did this to you?!
Tenshi.
Tenshi?!
Wait a second!  Kanade was with me the whole time!
Tenshi?
UTW Staff
Translator:
Ershin
Timer/Editor:
Nikon
TS/Karaoke:
ar
TLC/QC:
Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c 201] Matsushita-godan!
[c 186] So we're trapped.
[c 73] I pray we'll meet again.
[c 183] Trap.
[c 110] I can't just distract someone that scary!
[c 145] What's going on here?!
[c 52] Let me tell you one possibility.
[c 36] Is Kanade alright?
[c 82] Angel Player...
[c 283] I'll let you catch your breath and then persuade you.
[c 233] How fooliiiiiiish!
[c 228] It seems the time has come to show it to you!
[c 161] If you don't make it you'll be left behind!
[c 151] You all seem pretty busy.
[c 326] Please be okay!
[c 327] Kanade!