"I'm sorry. There's
nothing more to it, though."
"I'll apologize to everyone. I don't
think there's anything else I can do."
"You don't have to apologize."
"It's true, you weren't exactly
the right person for the job."
"It's remarkable that
you've done this much."
"I'll think of some way
to deal with it now."
"But even if it does go well, it probably
won't go in the direction you wanted."
"Send"
"Sent"
"Please insert name here:
Sorry to bring this up out of the blue."
"M-e-♪: Sorry, there's no getting
around the time and distance."
"Not at all. Given the situation,
there's nothing you can do about it."
"M-e-♪: It's a request from my
dear kohai. I wish I could do something."
"Do you have any other ideas?
About anyone who would be able to?"
"M-e-♪: Hmm."
"M-e-♪:"
"Please insert name here: Senpai?"
"Senpai"
"M-e-♪: I'm kidding."
"M-e-♪: They may not be much help,
but depending on how you use them"
"I know someone who could dance for you."
"Then, do you think you
can come on that day?"
"L: I'll definitely be!"
"L: I made a mistake. I'll be there."
"Please insert name here:
I will be very pleased if you would."
I'll send you the time and place later."
"L: I very munich look forward to it."
"L: That's munch."
"L: much"
"Please insert name here:
You might already know this,"
but you don't have to convert to kanji."
"Please insert name here:
Just go ahead and hit 'Enter'"
"L: Are you surge?"
"L: Are you sure?"
"L: Ah, you are right."
"Please insert name here:
Okay, if you please."
Oh, and as long as you're at it,"
"L: Yes"
"you can invite your friends, too."
"Yeah, all three of them."
"L: Are you sure?"
"They're the Classic Lit Club, right?"
"I would be delighted if you brought
all the club members with you."
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
Congratulations on reaching the finals!
Mizutani Sho, 100m breaststroke
Let's Go To the Screening!
Audiovisual Classroom
Yamanishi Midori
Sugimura Jiro
Senoue Mamiko
Konosu Yuri
Katsuta Takeo
Kaito Takeo
Sitting Room
No unauthorized personnel
Shosho ('Heat's End')
For the sunshine easeth,
and blue skies begin their withdrawl
Hyouka
For the sunshine easeth,
and blue skies begin their withdrawl
General Hospital
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
"The Case of the Furuoka Deserted Village Murder"