I'm sorry. There's nothing
more to it, though.
I'll apologize to everyone. I don't
think there's anything else I can do.
You don't have to apologize.
It's true, you weren't exactly
the right person for the job.
It's remarkable that
you've done this much.
I'll think of some way
to deal with it now.
But even if it does go well, it probably
won't go in the direction you wanted.
Send
Sent
Please insert name here:
Sorry to bring this up out of the blue.
M-e-♪: Sorry, there's no getting
around the time and distance.
Not at all. Given the situation,
there's nothing you can do about it.
M-e-♪: It's a request from my
dear kohai. I wish I could do something.
Do you have any other ideas?
About anyone who would be able to?
M-e-♪: Hmm.
M-e-♪:
Please insert name here: Senpai?
Senpai
M-e-♪: I'm kidding.
M-e-♪: They may not be much help,
but depending on how you use them
I know someone who could dance for you.
Then, do you think you
can come on that day?
L: I'll definitely be!
L: I made a mistake. I'll be there.
Please insert name here:
I will be very pleased if you would.
I'll send you the time and place later.
L: I very munich look forward to it.
L: That's munch.
L: much
Please insert name here:
You might already know this,
but you don't have to convert to kanji.
Please insert name here:
Just go ahead and hit 'Enter'
L: Are you surge?
L: Are you sure?
L: Ah, you are right.
Please insert name here:
Okay, if you please.
Oh, and as long as you're at it,
L: Yes
you can invite your friends, too.
Yeah, all three of them.
L: Are you sure?
They're the Classic Lit Club, right?
I would be delighted if you brought
all the club members with you.
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
Wow. Looks like he made the finals.
Congratulations on reaching the finals!
Mizutani Sho, 100m breaststroke
Looks like.
It's amazing, huh?
When I see something like that,
Let's Go To the Screening!
I wonder if I have any kind of talent,
but it looks like Fukube Satoshi
doesn't have any natural gifts.
I'd like to think that I'm a late bloomer,
but those chances are slim.
What are you talking about, "database"?
Well, I do take pride in that,
when it comes to intellectual matters,
but even if I polish that up,
I'll never be a quiz show king.
Oh, no?
Nope. And I couldn't be
more envious, really.
Then again, there's more than
just being envious, right?
Such as?
Geniuses don't get to choose to live normal
lives like we do, even if they wanted to.
You see some appeal
in living a normal life, Hotaro?
Knowing you, that's probably true.
But I wonder if you're going to be able to.
What do you mean by that?
I know that Fukube Satoshi
doesn't have any special talent.
But I'd like to hold off on whether
that's true for Oreki Hotaro, too.
If you think I don't lead a normal life,
then you don't observe
people closely enough.
I'm saying I'd like to hold
off on evaluating you.
Anyhow, shouldn't we be hurrying along?
Mayaka will be all over us if we're
late to the editorial meeting.
That's for sure.
For Pete's sake, it's summer vacation.
You're late!
There you go again,
trying to laugh it off!
Where's Chitanda?
Oh, she's not here yet. I'm worried.
The disparity here is
pretty awful, Mayaka.
It's the difference in your behaviors.
I'm sorry I'm late!
There's a screening!
Everyone, let's go to a screening!
A video movie that was produced
by Class 2-F is being shown.
Hm?
I know someone who is in that class,
and she wants to hear what we think.
We were talking about that,
which is why I am late.
What kind of movie is it?
Um, she said it was a mystery movie.
Oh, yeah?
Sounds interesting.
Audiovisual Classroom
This must be it.
We decided to take you up on your offer.
Yeah, I appreciate you coming.
Welcome. Thank you for
accepting my invitation today.
Ibara Mayaka-san, Fukube Satoshi-san,
and Oreki Hotaro-san...
These are the other members of
the Classic Lit Club that I am in.
It's a pleasure. I am Irisu Fuyumi.
Oh, then it is you, Irisu-senpai!
I thought that I'd seen you before.
Sorry, but I don't remember you.
Oh, the culture festival planning
committee at the end of June.
Mediating that dispute between
Light Music Club and the Drama Club?
That was truly something else!
Imagine, Satoshi complimenting
someone so openly.
I'm afraid I still don't remember.
Oh, I see.
Chi-chan, how do you know her?
My family and the Irisu family
are on close terms.
Ever since we were little,
she has been there for me.
Being an old and established
family sounds like a lot of work.
Now then, this is the movie
that our class produced.
I would like you to watch it,
and give me your candid opinion of it.
We can't wait.
We just have to watch it and
give you our opinions?
Is there something unusual about that?
Even if we don't like it, you're not
going to re-shoot anything, are you?
You just want us to publicize it?
No.
Then I don't understand why
you're showing it to us.
That's a legitimate question.
You're right that there's no meaning
in having you just watch it.
But I think it would be more
efficient if you watched it first.
Well?
More efficient?
Our video movie doesn't have a title yet.
The working title is "Mystery."
Once the movie is over, there is something
I would like to ask you, so be prepared.
All right, let's get started.
Good hunting.
Good hunting?
The volunteers of Class 2-F,
having decided to participate
in the Kanyasai,
and requiring material from the
Narakubo area for their display,
are now heading to the site.
Aren't we there yet?
Yamanishi Midori
Sugimura Jiro
A-Almost there.
Less than five more minutes.
But we heard you say that before!
Senoue Mamiko
Konosu Yuri
Katsuta Takeo
This is pretty tough going.
I'm hot, and I'm getting tired.
You're not the only one who's hot!
Kaito Takeo
Come on! Let's get going!
Seems about right, for an
independent production.
I can see it.
That's Narakubo over there.
Incredible.
I see. Looks like it was worth it
to come here for material.
At any rate, let's secure
a place to sleep tonight!
Then we'll gather our material!
In that case, over there is
a good place, isn't it?
Let's go see!
I'm getting kind of a
bad feeling about this.
A mansion mystery!
A mansion mystery?
It's dusty.
The roof seems secure enough.
It's too dangerous to sleep here!
There's glass scattered about!
Let's find a place to stay
before it gets dark.
There's a floorplan over here.
Oh! A floorplan!
Let's split up and look around inside!
Eh?! Isn't that dangerous?!
And it's probably locked, too!
It's okay. I'm sure there are keys.
Eh?!
Is that an office?
What are these keys?
I think those are the master keys.
We can't have them getting lost.
We should leave them here.
Yeah, you're right.
Here they are. We should be able to
look everywhere with all of these.
Okay, let's go around looking
for rooms we can use.
Mm-hm!
Mm-hm.
If this were real, don't you
think they'd all stick together?
What are you getting at?
Something's about to happen. I'd bet on it.
He's the one who talked to me.
The incident happened soon after.
Yeah, I knew it!
How did you fare?
There were pieces of a broken
mirror scattered about!
We can't use it unless we clean it up!
I see. We found the same sort of thing.
Hey, Sugimura! How about you?!
I-It's fairly clean in here. We might
be able to use it. I'm coming down.
Where's Kaito-kun?
Is he still looking around?
Well, okay. Let's all go get him.
A sitting room?
Sitting Room
He's not here.
Hm? That's strange.
Down the wing, maybe?
No unauthorized personnel
It won't open. It's locked.
What do we do?!
I'll go get the master keys.
Ah, me too!
Kaito!
I-I-It's blood!
H-Hey, what's that?
I'm surprised she can get so
emotionally attached to this.
Damn it! Who did this?!
Oh, no...
Is it over...?
Huh? Huh? It isn't over yet.
That's all the video there is.
What's going on here?
Who do you think is
the culprit behind this?
Shosho ('Heat's End')
For the sunshine easeth,
and blue skies begin their withdrawl
Hyouka
I will explain everything in turn,
but first, I want you to tell me one thing.
Technically speaking, what do
you think of this video?
If I can be honest,
I think it's pretty clumsy.
I think so, as well. No matter how much
passion someone puts into it,
without any technical skill,
the outcome will be obvious.
But isn't that okay, for what it is?
Yes. I think it is good enough, too.
I think it's okay to indulge
a world of self-satisfaction.
Mm-hm.
I'm not saying that its quality
is intrinsically important.
Now, what is the vital issue
concerning this project?
The fact that it isn't finished.
Yes. Not even we can
be satisfied with that.
The video is shot on a unique location,
so we can only shoot it during summer
vacation, but it still isn't finished.
Did the shooting not go well?
The shooting went as scheduled,
and was supposed to finish next Sunday.
Then, what is the problem?
The script.
Hongo Mayu, the only girl in the class
who has ever drawn any manga,
was delegated to provide the
script for a one-hour movie.
That's crazy!
Hongo did a good job.
But when she had written as far
as you saw here, she took ill.
You're not saying you want us to take over.
I couldn't ask anything like that.
So, getting back to my first question,
who do you think the culprit is?
Hongo took ill just as we were
getting to the resolution.
Someone watching this should be able
to deduce who the culprit is.
But are there really going
to be enough clues included
in a script written by an amateur?
That should be okay. She has
studied a lot of mysteries.
She followed the Ten Commandments,
the Nine Propositions, and the 20 Rules.
Oh, yeah?
Moses's Ten Commandments?
No, Knox's Ten Commandments.
The Nine Propositions and 20 Rules
are all rules stipulating what
must happen in a detective novel.
Yes. In other words, the key to solving
the crime must be presented fairly.
With that in mind, who do you
think the culprit is?
This is what she meant by "Good hunting"?
I'm not good at providing the "who."
A database doesn't give those answers.
Yeah, I'm not so sure I
could do it, myself.
There is someone that I suspect, though.
Hm?
What?!
Oh, I was just thinking that
this is your territory...
Being the detective. Wow,
what a disgusted-looking face.
I wasn't watching that seriously.
In that case, let's have
her show it to us again.
Give me a break!
I wouldn't mind just your opinion.
Feel free to keep it casual.
Oh, yeah? Then I think
it was Yamanishi-senpai.
Why is that?
Because she had a bad attitude.
Oreki! Come on!
Irisu-senpai, why don't
you consider who it is?
I know very little about mysteries.
In that case, why didn't you stop them from
using a mystery as your subject matter?
I wasn't a part of the
project at the beginning.
I got back from Hokkaido,
and jumped into sort this all
out the day before yesterday.
If I had been involved from the start,
I doubt the project would
have moved forward.
Okay, lastly,
why did you call on us,
the Classic Lit Club?
First, there's my
acquaintance with Chitanda.
Beyond that, I heard all about
that Hyouka business.
Huh?
You knew about that?
Did she hear about it from Itoigawa-sensei?
When I agreed to straighten
this out, I remembered you.
I thought that maybe you could
serve as my detectives.
We don't need you
expecting anything of us.
You're right. I thought this
might be an unwelcome request.
I apologize.
Thus concludes this screening.
Thank you. I appreciate you coming.
Huh?
P-Please wait!
What will become of the ending, then?
I don't know. I'll give it my effort,
but I'm also prepared if it
ends up being unfinished.
We can't have that!
It would be a tragedy to
leave this video unfinished!
I couldn't bear that!
You can't bear it? It's Irisu
that can't bear it, right?
Well, having it unfinished would
leave a bad aftertaste.
Yeah. And all of you got
together to make it, too.
What's more... What's more,
what would make Hongo-san
go so far as to diminish
both her trust and health
to give up writing the
script halfway through?
I am curious about that!
Let's help her out, Hotaro.
You're not doing anything anyway, are you?
Oreki-san, let's do this.
Let's avenge Hongo-san's death!
Hongo isn't dead.
Oh, right.
Be that as it may, Oreki-san...!
If we accept, and can't figure out
who the culprit is, then what?
Bow down and beg forgiveness
from everyone in Class 2-F?
I can't take on that
kind of responsibility.
In that case...
What if you were to take on
roles as observers?
Observers?
You'd listen to our class's
prospective detectives,
and then offer your viewpoints.
How about that?
If that's all, then, okay.
Very well. Thanks.
Irisu-senpai is well-known.
See over there?
General Hospital
Her family runs the general hospital.
Oh, yeah? An heiress to
a big-time hospital, huh?
But that's not the only thing
Irisu-senpai is known for.
She has a nickname.
What would you guess it is?
Beats me.
"The Empress."
What is she, sadistic?
No, that would be a "Queen."
I salute you for knocking
down what I set up.
What are you doing?
It goes without saying that she is pretty,
but I hear she's also good at
pushing people to work hard.
They say that everyone around
her ends up being her pawns.
Ho? Isn't that something?
I have to say, the Empress went to
the trouble to give us an audience,
so I'd like it if we all adopted
our own symbols, as well.
Symbols?
First off, Mayaka's could
be "Justice," maybe.
It's a toss-up between that and "Judgment."
What do you mean?
Tarot cards.
Hm...
Well, Fuku-chan, what would you be?
I was thinking "The Fool."
Nah, maybe "The Magician."
I'll let you be the Fool, Chitanda-san.
Yes, you're right. Now that you
mention it, maybe I am the Fool.
That may be one of my shortcomings.
I don't get it.
Me, neither.
What about Oreki-san?
That one is obvious. "Strength."
Huh? Is that right? I
would think "The Star."
Nah, definitely Strength.
It's perfect for him.
Hmph. That doesn't sound like a compliment.
I wouldn't say that.
You're such a jerk.
No way.
Yes?
Good morning. I came to pick you up.
What a little lady.
Good morning.
Morning.
Today, we are going to see someone
who will show us to the detectives
so we can listen to what they say.
When did you manage to arrange this?
Via chat. There is a chatroom on
the Kamiyama High School homepage
where only students are allowed.
Wow, they have that? Show me sometime.
Sure.
Yes, come in.
Is this the Classic Lit Club room?
Yes. Are you from Class 2-F?
The name is Eba Kurako.
It is nice to meet you all.
I believe that Irisu has
told you about this,
but today, I will be introducing
you to our detectives.
All right, let's go.
Chi-chan, are those snacks?
Yes. Today I have some
chocolates that we received.
I thought that we could all
share them as we talked.
How nice!
Your brain doesn't work as well
when you're hungry, after all.
I wonder what kind of deductions
we're going to hear.
Aren't you looking forward to this, Hotaro?
You all sure are enjoying yourselves, huh?
Senpai, can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
Who are we going to hear from?
The assistant director,
the prop man, and the publicist.
Oh, yeah? By the way, Eba-senpai,
what are you in charge of?
I am not involved in the project.
I wasn't interested.
Truly an answer after my own heart.
Eba-san, were you close with Hongo-san?
Why do you ask?
Oh, I am just curious as to what
kind of person wrote the script.
Hongo is...
no-nonsense and meticulous,
with a strong sense of responsibility,
kind to a fault, and delicate.
She's my good friend.
I see.
Here we are.
Currently, movie production
has been shut down,
so there will probably be
no one else coming.
These three are our detectives.
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "The Case of the
Furuoka Deserted Village Murder."
The Case of the Furuoka Deserted Village Murder