Oh shit!
Riko! You're gonna be late!
I know!
Ow!
It's the same story each and every morning. Good grief.
And here I thought she'd become a bit
more graceful once she joined Fuji Girls'.
Give up on that already, Mom.
She's at that rebellious stage of her life now.
I actually think of her as a brother now.
You what, Ren?!
Screw you, Ms. Violence!
That's why you keep getting rejected!
You—
If you don't like it, show me you can get asked out.
For your information, I have been before.
What?!
Enough! You're both gonna be late!
Rentarou, stop rubbing salt into her old wounds and get ready!
'Kay.
Another one just opened.
Hang in there, Riko!
And again!
I-I think you've got the potential, okay?
Okay?
Oh, right.
Remember Satoshi, our old neighbor?
I ran into him the other day.
He was so girly back then, but he's a real man now.
He's pretty popular, according to his mother.
So I think you'll be fine if you just acted a bit more girly.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I'm just...
I'm just "one of the guys,"
and I keep getting my heart broken.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not popular!
Kurahashi Riko is as wild and dreamy as ever!
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
After school
Legend of the Worst Girl, Riko
Did something happen, Riko?
Oh, don't mind me.
Come on, let's do the usual.
O-Okay.
I'm sure I'd be popular if I was as pretty and girly as Maki.
Today,
let's try to acquire an aura that'll make boys on the street wanna talk to you!
She's dumb as hell on the inside, though.
What? You wanna be picked up on the street?
Huh? N-No.
Not something that direct.
I'm talking about casual greetings or idle chatter.
You know, as a first step.
Let's start off as friends!
Love and peace for all mankind!
A free heart is a world heritage, and my heart is Guinness-tier!
How are those related?
You know how people tend to keep at a distance...
Or well, that I don't have many friends, right?
I thought boys would treat me the same way.
Yeah, she's too perfect.
On the outside.
What if I hid in the shadows, trembling in solitude,
and stared at them from there?
People would probably talk to you, yeah.
To ask if you were okay.
Must be nice to have so many friends, Riko.
You know the techniques to attract people like the back of your own hand, right?
Truly an expert on love!
Hot stuff!
My lies are coming back to bite me really hard today.
What's keeping the others, by the way?
Suzu's absent with a cold, apparently.
Eno said she was going home because something came up.
And I'm gonna skip out.
Oh, that so?
I just can't deal with this girl.
Too bad I won't be able to take part in love practice with the master.
Especially when she acts like this.
What now, Riko?
I don't care! Screw this!
Huh?
Let's ditch this and go out somewhere, yeah?
You said you wanted some hair accessories, remember?
I wanna go!
You sure got some cute ones there.
Yeah.
Oh, can we drop by the bookstore?
Sure!
This is a nice change of pace.
Huh?
Why is she here?
Are you here to apply love practice to the real world?
Huh?
Break a leg.
I'll be watching you.
D-Did we come here so we could have boys talk to us?
H-Hey!
Let's do this, Riko.
You heard her, Kurahashi.
Kurahashi?
Wh-Wh-What now?
Is there any way I can make someone talk to me?
Riko?
Huh?
Someone did talk to me, but...
Who on earth?
Wow, it really is you, Riko!
Super long time no see!
H-Huh?
I'd heard you'd got into Fuji Girls'.
That was for real, huh?
Who is he?
Who the hell is this guy?
I wanna ask him!
Long time no see!
Ah, I'm such a dumbass.
An ex?
Huh?! No!
Did he ask you out and get rejected, then?
Listen to me!
N-No, that was...
Huh?
That was a long time ago!
Wh-Why bring that...
Damn it!
Wait—
Riko, you heartbreaker!
What?!
I had no idea it was really like that.
I'm totally shocked.
N-Nah, uh...
W-Well, yeah.
It's a frequent occurrence.
I wanna ask. I wanna ask him.
I wanna ask him who he is!
I can't remember him for the life of me.
But this means he used to like me, doesn't it?
Sis!
Big trouble, Mom!
Sis suddenly blew up in the middle of the road!
What in the world?!
The next morning
Let's go to school together, Ren!
Sorry, I'll go alone.
What?
Why don't you just go with them?
Don't wanna. Sounds like a pain.
At times like these, I envy Sis.
This guy!
Riko, you heartbreaker!
Oh, stop it!
I love that it's not a lie!
How'd you get to know him?
At school?
Sorry, but I don't remember.
You little devil, you!
I love that it's technically not a lie!
He was calling you by your first name,
so I figured you shared a special relationship.
Yeah...
The only guys who call me Riko are my cousins or childhood friends.
I want to be like that.
I want to be called Natsuo someday.
I've already bought a digital voice recorder to capture that shining moment!
Go return it!
And while you're at it,
see if you can exchange that brain of yours!
I'm sure you're special to him, though.
So if you can, try to recall who he is.
O-Okay.
Who could it have been?
Someone I rejected?
A long time ago?
Doesn't ring any bells at all.
But...
Oh yeah, Riko.
How do you know Ikezawa?
Who's that supposed to be?
You heartbreaker, you!
Come on, recall him.
Ow!
What're you talking about?
You know how I'm going to the
cram school you went to, right?
Someone called out to me the other day.
He asked me a bunch of questions about you.
And when I told him you were in the student council,
it hit him like a ton of bricks.
Hang on...
When are you going next?
Huh? Today, why?
I'll come with you.
Don't you think you're a bit too gung-ho about this?
J-Just your imagination.
Oh, Ikezawa spotted!
Huh?
Which one is he?
That one.
With the glasses.
Hey, that's Jan!
Jan?
Ack! Kurahashi...
'Sup, Jan! Long time no see!
Stop calling me Jan!
That weird nickname actually became a thing!
My name's Ikezawa Masaomi.
This thing has nothing at all to do with my name.
But it does.
Look!
Ikezawa
Ikebukuro
Tokyo
Japan
Jan
What the hell is with those random changes?!
I'll see you later.
And you're a student council member?
How the mighty Fuji Girls' has fallen.
Say what?!
You haven't changed a bit, have you?
So it wasn't that guy.
I guess that's not unexpected.
No way I could meet him that easily—
Jan!
Don't call me that.
Sorry for running late.
Hold it!
Hey!
I haven't changed a bit? Look who's talking.
Hey, wait up!
Freeze!
You there, the guy who asked me out in the past!
The one who I rejected!
H-How dare you?!
First you laugh about it with your friends, and now this?!
You're the worst girl I've ever known!
Y-You've got the wrong idea!
Wrong idea, my foot!
I mean, I don't remember any of that.
I have zero recollection of you asking me out,
or me turning you down.
So I can't laugh about it!
That's even worse!
Did you really forget?
I'm sorry.
Uh...
Could you give me a hint?
I got the wrong person.
Hey, wai—
Shut up. Let me go.
But I can't stop thinking about it.
What difference does it make if you don't remember it?
Stupid Riko.
I don't care if you go crazy thinking about it!
Actually, I want you to go crazy!
Was that...
For a second there, I...
I was one step away from remembering.
Riko.
Hey, Riko!
What do you want?!
I had her send me a picture.
I said I ran into him, remember?
Satoshi, I mean.
I wanted to show you, so I had his mom take a picture.
I have to say, though.
Satoshi's like a different person now.
He was so cute back when he was on the soccer team with you.
This is a scam!
How was I supposed to recognize him when he changed that much?
Also, he transferred away in third grade and I hadn't met him since.
Of course I'd forget about him.
Teammates are nice, aren't they?
When I asked him if he remembered you,
he said there was no way he'd forget a friend he'd shed blood, sweat, and tears with.
My.
You'd better be careful I don't step on you if you wanna keep lying there.
Actually, I want you to step on me.
No, that's gross.
A childhood friend who lived close by and was your teammate?
And yet, you...
I know. You don't have to tell me.
And I still can't recall him asking me out.
Looks like he's going to that cram school, so I'll go apologize to him next time.
Um, can I come along?
Huh?
My grades have been slipping recently,
so I've been looking for a nice cram school to go to.
Pull the other one, top ranker.
I want to get in touch with boys!
Our real-world application the other day ended partway too!
Well...
I won't interrupt you, I promise.
Please!
But...
By the way, I know where the cram school is.
I've gotten my hands on its schedule too.
You're just threatening me here!
Hey.
Did something happen between you and Kurahashi?
Nah, nothing.
Says the guy who sprinted away from her.
Th-That was only because nature called!
Looking at faces like those
makes me sick to my stomach.
Oh?
Guess you're out of luck today as well, then.
Try not to wet yourself.
I need to talk to you!
Jan, talk to Maki while we're gone!
What?!
Thanks!
Listen to me, dammit!
My bad.
I remembered who you were after you left.
That so?
Whatever.
Later.
U-Um...
I'm really sorry!
You'd become so manly that I didn't recognize you at all.
I'm sure that's no excuse, but...
I'd become what, again?
What?
Y-Yeah!
You were so totally manly that I didn't recognize you!
Unlike what you were back then, you're super cool now.
And no matter how I look at you, you're a real man!
W-Well, I guess there was nothing you could've done about that.
All right!
By the way, uh...
When did you ask me out?
You haven't changed a bit, though.
Different age, same personality.
Huh?
But I hear you're a student council member now?
Jan told me about it.
I can't picture you in that role at all.
You look just like you used to when you smile.
So cute!
Yet again
fails to
find out
what she
wants
to know
Wh-What do I do?
I have to start by greeting him, right?
H-Hello, Jan.
Jan? Um...
Who're you calling Jan?
Hello!
It's a beautiful evening glow!
What are you playing at?
You speak Japanese well!
More like I am Japanese.
Are you mocking me?
Not at all!
I thought you were an exchange student since you weren't responding to me.
As if.
You think you can get away with mocking people just because you're a little cute?
What's with that reaction?! That's all kinds of weird!
What else can I do?
Th-That's the first time a boy's ever called me cute!
What?!
Are you an idiot?!
What the?
Mocking people? Cute?
Stupid? What in the world is going on?
Are you hot 'n' cold?!
What're you even on about?!
B-Boys are incomprehensible!
Hey!
That's what I want to say.
What an incomprehensible broad.
Riko!
Sorry about that, Maki.
J-Jan said I was cute!
What?!
You're so cute.
R-Really?
Jan did?
But immediately after that he asked me if I was stupid!
You took that seriously?
Are you stupid?
What?
What an asshole!
I'll make him pay for this next time!
Wh-What the?
Hey, Nagi. How'd it go with Kurahashi?
I don't get it.
I don't get any of these guys.
The next day
Whatcha reading?
It seems not all boys in the world are gentlemen like Huggy.
The Life of an Amorous Man
I'm looking over research material in order to cure my ignorance.
Marquis
de Sade
You're gonna end up with a different misunderstanding, so stop.
Marquis
de Sade
M-Men are such...
I'd feel sorry for them if you put them all in the same boat as these guys.
I wasn't ready for a real-world application yet.
I need more practice.
Oh, right!
Today, let's perfect the method to meet only the kinda guys we like!
There's no such thing.
I'm jealous of our client from the other day.
She met someone she loves so much she can't
give up on him even though it must be so painful.
That one, huh?
She'd better tell us if she makes any progress.
Th-This is huge!
What's up?
We got another request for love advice in the suggestion box.
Huh?
"I started dating him."
That's some progress!
"How should I tell him I want us
to go back to being just friends?"
What?
What a massive plot twist.
Big trouble!
There's big trouble here too!
We got another request for love advice, and the contents are big trouble!
Huh?
Hang on a second!
I found this in the south school building's suggestion box.
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
Love Advice
I'm thinking of changing
my hairdo. What kind of
hairstyles do boys like?
This is our client from earlier,
this is what Suzu found in the north building,
and this is what Enomoto found in the south building.
The handwriting and the matters they're asking for advice on are all different.
The one who wants to break up
isn't the same client from before.
Let's calm down and get a grasp of the situation.
We should split up and check the other suggestion boxes as well.
And after that...
practice breaking up so we can give solid advice!
Calm down.
What should I do to catch
boys' eyes or make their
hearts skip a beat?
What should I do to catch
boys' eyes or make their
hearts skip a beat?
What should I do to catch
boys' eyes or make their
hearts skip a beat?
What should I do to catch
boys' eyes or make their
hearts skip a beat?
What should I do to catch
boys' eyes or make their
hearts skip a beat?
Found the third one in front of the gym.
What should I do to catch
boys' eyes or make their
hearts skip a beat?
And the fourth in the clubroom wing.
The rest are all normal letters.
So we've got four requests for love advice in total, huh?
The lab got exposed during that meeting.
Maybe the girls who attended it...
...heard the other day's broadcast and thought we welcome love advice at any time.
The teachers will find out about
this if the rumors get any bigger.
We haven't heard these rumors ourselves, so we should be fine for a while yet.
And even if the teachers found about it,
my data management is flawless.
There's no proof!
I've been learning from a certain someone.
What are we gonna do about these requests?
We can't take over the broadcasting room again.
Ignore them?
I don't want to.
Also, if we only respond to one student, people might think we're playing favorites and lose trust in us.
Things have gotten quite troublesome.
Yeah.
Really.
What's the most troublesome thing, according to you?
Conducting our love research, obviously.
And not having the means to convey the results.
Huh?
So love research does have something to do with the retrieval of the suggestion boxes.
What?
Wh-Who?
Way to go, Momo!
You managed to elicit a major testimony!
Keep going and get this scoop—
Nana.
Sorry about causing that fuss.
Let's go back.
You shouldn't run your mouth like that, Nana.
I couldn't help it. I was too happy.
I mean, if we get our hands on this scoop...
Last Boss
we can make Mizushima Sayori, our sworn enemy, cry uncle!
Too loud, Nana.
Who the heck are those guys?
I remember now.
Huh?
They're Minami and Ichikawa
from the newspaper association.
The newspaper?!
Looks like things are gonna get...
...really, really troublesome.
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
You're the worst, Riko!
I kinda agree too.
But Riko's really popular!
It's not her fault she can't remember each guy that asks her out.
Yeah, that! She's right!
Yeah.
I can't remember my boyfriend's name either.
I kept deleting his texts because I thought they were spam. The guy ended up crying.
Yeah, I'm the worst!
I'm so very sorry I forgot!
To the Kurahashi Residence!