I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
In this Holy Grail War, I am of the Rider class.
Wh-What are you thinking, you idiot?
Fate has brought us together to do battle for the Holy Grail.
But first, I wish to make a proposition.
What think you of yielding the Holy Grail to me, and joining my army?
You would be treated as honored allies.
Together, we shall share the joy of conquering the world!
I am afraid I must decline.
I may give the Grail to but one man- my new avowed lord.
Not to you, Rider!
Did you interfere with our duel merely to proffer that ridiculous plan?
You tarnish my honor as a knight.
I'd be willing to discuss terms.
Enough!
Furthermore, I am the rightful King of Britain.
I could never lower myself to a mere retainer, even in service to a mighty king.
King of Britain, say you... What a surprise!
I'd hardly have expected the King of Knights to be a little girl.
Then would you like to taste this little girl's blade,
King of Conquerors?
I suppose negotiations have failed.
Such a waste. What a shame...
Rider!
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
That moron nearly conquered the entire known world?
What is wrong with you?
So you were the one, eh?
I'd wondered what madness had compelled you to steal my relic.
I never imagined that you yourself planned to enter the Holy Grail War...
Waver Velvet.
How would you like me to tutor you privately?
How magi really kill one another...
I'll teach you all about the fear and pain involved.
Feel honored.
Magus!
So you were to be my Master, rather than the boy.
Absurd...
Only one brave enough to ride the battlefield at my side could ever be my Master.
Not a coward, lacking sufficient courage to even show himself!
And there are others, as well...
Skulking in the darkness!
What do you speak of, Rider?
Saber. And Lancer.
Your duel was magnificent.
Surely, the sound of your blades clashing
summoned other Heroic Spirits than myself to this place.
Heroic Spirits, born again through the Holy Grail, gather here and now!
Those too craven to show themselves
will draw the scorn of Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
This is...
Yes.
Quite unfortunate.
Quite unfortunate indeed.
That's...
The Servant that defeated Assassin?
So, two lesser beings dare to name themselves kings in my presence.
I do not see where any problem lies...
I am Iskandar, the legendary King of Conquerors.
What nonsense. I am the one true king.
All others are mere pretenders.
If you're that insistent, then why not name yourself?
No true king should be troubled by giving his name.
So you would question me,
mongrel?
Me, the king?
If, basking in my glory, you still cannot discern my identity,
then your ignorance is deserving of a swift death.
I see. So that is how he killed Assassin.
That is his Noble Phantasm.
Kill.
Berserker?
Hey, King of Conquerors. Did you invite him, too?
He doesn't seem terribly interested in negotiations.
Boy... How powerful a Servant is he?
I don't know. I can't tell!
What? Are you not a Master?
You can sense their strengths and weaknesses, right?
I can't tell. That black thing is definitely a Servant,
but I can't read its status or anything else!
It appears it will be another troublesome enemy.
That spirit has some curse or other special ability
that entirely conceals everything about him.
But that isn't all.
With four others present, we cannot afford any missteps.
Why did he materialize here?
No sane Master would choose to send out their Servant here...
Not amidst all this chaos.
Maiya, keep watching Assassin.
I'll look for Berserker's Master.
Who gave you permission to gaze upon me? You rabid dog...
May your death provide me some modicum of entertainment, mongrel!
Is that truly Berserker?
For a madman, he's surprisingly capable.
What, you couldn't tell?
That black thing caught the first blade that flew toward him,
using it to destroy the second spear as it approached.
You'd dare lay your filthy hands on my treasures...
You must long for a quick death, cur!
That's impossible!
Let us see just how long your lowly tricks
can keep you alive!
Fool...
I belong among the heavens,
yet you would have me share this Earth?
Your impudence has guaranteed your death!
Mutt, nothing will even remain of your corpse!
Gilgamesh is serious.
He plans to open the Gate of Babylon even further.
Repeatedly exposing his Noble Phantasm to the others...
How rash.
Your decision, my Master?
By the power of my Command Seal,
King of Heroes, quell thine anger and withdraw.
You think to order a king's withdrawal?
You have nerve, Tokiomi.
You were fortunate, mad dog.
Mongrels!
By our next meeting, see that you've culled your numbers.
Only a true hero is worthy to look upon me.
It would seem the Master was less stubborn than Archer.
Irisviel, get back!
What?
So that's it...
Whatever he grabs becomes his Noble Phantasm.
Saber?
Well, Maiya?
Can you make out Berserker's Master?
No, I cannot.
This looks bad.
Damn.
What are you?
That's enough messing around, Berserker.
Saber has a previous engagement with me.
If you insist on interfering, you'll have to face me.
Lancer...
What are you doing, Lancer?
This is your chance to defeat Saber.
I will defeat Saber...
I swear it on my honor!
If you insist I kill her here, then I will first defeat that rabid dog.
Please, my Master!
With my Command Seal, I order you...
My lord!
Help Berserker and kill Saber.
Lancer!
Saber, I'm sorry...
Irisviel, I shall stop them.
While I do, you must run...
Run as far away as you can get.
Irisviel, please!
It's all right, Saber.
Believe in your Master!
Kiritsugu is here?
Kiritsugu, I know that you can still turn this into a victory.
I'll kill Lancer's Master now.
It's the only way out of this.
Maiya, attack Assassin on my mark.
Suppressive fire.
Roger.
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
Ah...
A tough one.
As you can see, our black friend will be retiring for the evening.
Master of Lancer. I know not whence you're watching,
but do not spoil a battle between knights with your petty tricks.
Have Lancer withdraw.
If you insist on humiliating him further, then I shall join Saber.
Together, the two of us will annihilate your Servant.
What will it be?
Withdraw, Lancer.
That's enough for tonight.
My thanks, King of Conquerors.
It was nothing. A ray of kindness amidst the shadow of the battlefield.
When you first arrived, what was your intent, King of Conquerors?
I really don't think about these things...
Saber... First, settle matters with Lancer.
And then, I shall face the victor, be that you or Lancer.
King of Knights, goodbye for now!
I hope to enjoy our next meeting as much as I did this one.
Boy, you got any clever parting words?
I do wish he'd man up a little...
Farewell!
Saber, your left arm!
Yes, it was a painful blow.
It is as Rider says.
If I fail to deal with Lancer first and undo the curse on this wound,
it will damage my chances against the other Servants.
Thank you, Saber.
I survived thanks to you...
The reason I could focus on the battle before me
was that I had you to guard my back
Saber...
The battle is only beginning, Irisviel.
Tonight, we merely saw the opening gambits of a battle that is only just unfolding.
That's right.
They were all powerful adversaries.
Not one of them was a conventional enemy.
So this is the Holy Grail War.
They all turned and ran from my Berserker...
And I embarrassed that arrogant prick!
Tokiomi, how I wish I could have seen your face.
Stupid Berserker went out of my control and started fighting Saber...
If this goes on, I won't last.
But if I'm able to control it, I can win.
Just hold on, Sakura.
Excuse me, Master Kirei.
What is it?
Right, I've come to report that I found something of interest, outside the church.
A familiar?
Yes. It was outside the barrier,
but it was clearly sent to monitor this church.
Awesome! So awesome!
Hey, Bluebeard... That was all real, right?
It was for real, and not some kind of special effects?
So awesome...
So, the Holy Grail War, right?
You're gonna participate. Right, mister?
Mister?
My wish has come true...
Come true...
Um...
Look at her! She is the answer!
Her beautiful face, her noble bearing...
She is none other than the maiden of my dreams!
Someone you know?
Indeed!
She was abandoned by God, died in shame, and now...
At last, she has revived!
Such... Such a miracle.
What could it be but the fulfillment of my dreams...
Oh, chaste maiden...
My holy virigin...
Soon, I will come for you.
Episode 5
Scream of a Mad Beast
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
I promise to bring you Saber's head.
The next strike will be real!
Aren't you the one who's mistaken?
Behold the magic of Kayneth El-Melloi...
You mean to lecture me?
I've come for you, my holy virgin.
Next Time:
Night of Stratagems