You're a parasite.
What an easy way to live.
I want to become stronger.
...Strong enough to keep my own anger in check.
Takashi! Takashi! Takashi!
Saika's purpose is to love people.
Let's all love each other!
I guess it's okay to use all of it now.
I live by feeding off Saika, who loves people for me.
Oh, Anri.
You're up so high!
That's a lie...
And that's the truth...
Heiwajima Shizuo...
I love you...
He's so strong...
No...
He's scary...
He's so cool!
I...
...knew he was incredibly strong, but...
I didn't know he was THIS strong...
Something happened, didn't it?
How about you go see what it is?
You're not doing anything anyway, right?
Those are made of the same stuff as my scythe.
They'll stop something as weak as a blade.
Thanks.
Well then...
That katana...is Saika?!
Then, before...the one who attacked me was...?
You even did that to your own parents?!
It looks like you didn't teach the children
spawned from your Saika how to fight.
I have a favor to ask.
Please tell the other Saikas to stop.
They should stop if you, the parent, tell them to.
I could also order them to stop by possessing you with my parent Saika...
That's impossible!
I've suppressed Saika!
With the power of love!
To have someone like you who doesn't even know how to love...!
I'll let you listen to something for a bit.
It's what's perpetually echoing inside of me:
Saika's...
Words of love...
I love you.
I love people very much.
No!
That was a lie...
Stop it!
And that was the truth...
Her dad, who ran an antique shop...
...would blow off steam by...
...beating his family.
And, little by little, she closed herself off.
That was when...
the Slasher appeared.
I love you.
I love...you.
Her mother was the Slasher.
I like you.
I love you.
Our love should have cut into him.
Once we injure someone, our thoughts
should flow into his body via fear and pain...
...but he doesn't feel fear...
Heiwajima Shizuo doesn't...
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Don't misunderstand;
No one loves me because they're afraid of me...
Don't make me laugh.
I'm the one who's scared!
I can't control this power...
...and I'm constantly afraid of failing.
That's right, I'm the biggest coward in the world.
But so what if I am?
The fact that I'm a coward has nothing
to do with beating the crap out of you.
Besides, I can't go down...
...in front of the people who love me.
How...
...can you stand that voice?
I have many deficiencies.
That's why I leech off things—to make up for what I lack.
I don't have the heart to love people, so I can bear this voice forever.
Forever and ever, objectively—
I did it!
That's right, I'd never lose to you...
Why are you afraid?
Being slashed is an outcome of love, isn't it?
You let me slash you?!
Why?!
I'm going to do something terrible to you.
So now I won't owe you anything.
I'm going to have my Saika possess you.
I won't apologize.
If I do, that would mean I'd have to contradict my way of life.
I don't think I'm being fair...
Since I'm trying to protect my peaceful
life by doing something terrible to you.
But, I can't help it...
...because I'm a parasite.
I love you.
Saika gets lonely easily.
From our point of view, it may seem wrong...
But it truly does love people.
So, please love Saika, Niekawa.
Because—unlike me—you have the ability to love people.
Stop!
Just frigging stop!
Huh?
How'd we get like this?!
So, no one died, huh?
Where am I?
Finally...
It finally listened to me.
Anri! Is that you, Anri?!
She came after me and tried to slash me before.
I had her transferred so she wouldn't become a problem.
I guess she hasn't given—
Anri, let's get out of here!
Sonohara, I helped you out, didn't I?
Yeah, with the Harima thing!
Who do you think put you and Harima in the same class?
I've already paid you back for that.
P-Paid me back...?
You mean with what you just did?
I thought that the black biker was the Slasher.
So I figured he'd attack you...
I got lost in that thought...I wanted to help you...
Eh?
It's not because I like you.
I just wanted to pay off my debt to you at all costs.
What're you talking about?
Why was the black biker chasing you?
What in the world did you do?
Oh...
He's...from back then...
What are you...
Anri!
What are you doing with that?
Y-You too? Are you like that, too?!
Will you also...
No, I'm different from Niekawa...
Because...I loathe you.
We've got a prepubescent, flat-chested girl now!
Come to think of it, what new pocket
editions did Dengeki release this month?
You can't use this car for evil, huh?
Yeah, that's it.
Oh, that's right.
Have they started making new chapters of "Kino's Journey?"
Maybe they'll release a "Shizu's Journey!"
That Samoyed Mask would...
Even though you knew how it'd turn out if
you asked Yumasaki to take care of it...psh.
Oh, Togusa, your face is red.
Maybe you have a fever?
I'll never forgive you!
Are you sure you're okay, Sonohara?
Yeah.
It's nothing serious.
I was surprised when I heard the news from Masaomi.
Are you really okay?
And, where exactly is Masaomi...?
He went home earlier.
He said he had something to take care of.
Honestly, what could he have to do at a time like this?
There's really nothing wrong with me.
Have you talked with the police yet?
I heard a lot of other people besides you got hurt—
It's fine.
No, it's not!
I have a feeling...that nothing else will happen.
Why?
Oh, sorry.
Actually, I was attacked by the Slasher a few hours before I got hurt.
At the time, a lot of people helped me out...
And one of them was really cool...
One of them was cool?
What the hell is this development?
Yes, a sunglasses-wearing bartender and...
Eh, that couldn't be Shizuo, could it?!
And there was another extremely cool person...
Please don't be surprised when I tell you.
Umm...
It was the headless rider!
Err, uh, umm...
Wait a second!
We talked a little bit, but he was very proactive, and I could tell he has a love of others...
You don't believe me, do you?
I wouldn't say "don't believe..."
"He" is a girl!
And when I was attacked again, it
was the headless rider who saved me!
So, I think I'll be okay now.
But, he's...
I can't say it.
I mean, if I do...
Well, but, they're in a completely
different world from us normal people...
So you probably shouldn't get too involved...
Ryugamine, what do you think real
abnormality is in this world of ours?
Huh?
It's having nothing happen. It's when nothing happens over and over, day in and day out.
It's having nothing change.
That's the real...
I'll have a doctor I know take a look at her.
Don't worry.
Celty, umm...I...
Don't apologize!
You only did what you thought was right, didn't you?
Actually, I think you did the right thing, too.
Well, I do think that knocking my head off was going
a bit too far, but I'll have to take that up with Saika.
This doesn't mean I sympathize with you, though.
I just don't think I could beat you if we fought.
If you're still not satisfied, use that power you obtained to help others.
She had obtained a power;
a power that enabled her to manipulate over 100 Saikas at will.
That power weighed heavily on her.
However, that's partly what she wished for.
For someone like her who was always floating on the breeze,
the pressure of holding people's fate in her hands finally made her feel firmly grounded in reality.
I may not be...
Then, she heard a voice.
It said, "I may not be able to love you, but I don't hate you."
Or she may have just felt that she heard it.
Even when she called out to it, it didn't respond.
However, that was fine with her.
She became just a little bit happier.
She had finally returned to a normal life.
Yet, she couldn't tell them the truth;
the truth about Saika, or about who pulls the strings.
Now that she'd come to control every Saika, she was able to search through Niekawa Haruna's memory, and thus found out about him.
She didn't know his target...
...but, if it happened to be either Mikado or Masaomi...
if he was trying to destroy their peaceful lives...
Bathed in anxiety and resolve, she remembered his name.
And that name is...
Orihara Izaya certainly is an odd name.
It may be a coincidence that I was raised this way, but I think it suits me perfectly.
How much do you believe in coincidence, Namie?
What are you talking about?
They probably think all these happenings are mere coincidences...
...even though I'm the one who lead Nasujima there during that timespan.
Except, he was a complete idiot.
He could've found out Sonohara Anri's
address by just taking a look at the class list.
Well, there are lots of things that exist if you
look for them with the idea that you'll find them.
Like ethereal swords or faeries...
Yeah, what actually was an accident was when he took my money and ran.
You idiot!
Once he'd fallen into debt, Nasujima blackmailed the parents...
How much do you think you borrowed?!
When are you actually going to pay it back?!
And we want it all in cash!
...of his former stalker—Niekawa Haruna—to make some cash.
He came to me by word of those loan sharks called the Awakusu Association and wanted me to look into Haruna's family...
Oh, thanks.
He took the bait hook, line, and sinker.
I'd found out that Niekawa Haruna was Saika.
I thought I'd use Haruna to scare him by cornering him and having
her say something like, "You bastard, how dare you steal my money!"
However...
The real Saika—not just some copy—appeared.
Hm? "What happened to Nasujima," you ask?
G-Give me your money!
It'd be the best thing in the world for me if Shizu-chan were to die.
Well, whatever.
Everything went just as planned.
Just as you planned?
There are so many more police around.
The mass media are up in arms, too.
Something happened in Southern Ikebukuro Park as well, right?
That was just a clash of wills.
It wasn't the Slasher?
What ended up being the cause?
Even that old guy didn't seem like he knew much.
He didn't remember a thing—just like he'd been hypnotized.
It seems like the police are bracing for a gang war.
It's not just the police.
Would you like to try dying once?
Master, you have mail.
Huh?
What's this?
This...is from the Dollars' leader, isn't it?
Calm down, Mikado.
So...what are you after?
Now, this city's been broken into three factions: the Dollars, the Yellow Scarves, and the ethereal sword followers.
And the ethereal sword followers have spies
in both the Dollars and the Yellow Scarves.
To be honest, I would've been fine with Niekawa Haruna leading the ethereal sword group.
But Sonohara Anri's pretty interesting.
And?
I'm fine with just causing some sparks for now.
If we leave things alone, those sparks will smolder and smoke...
Oh, I can't wait any longer!
But the Yellow Scarves were formed by some middle school brat, right?
Are they really that formidable?
The fact that he was able to gather that many people,
despite being a kid...shows that they're already a threat.
Well, it's not like I don't know the Yellow Scarves' shogun...
Don't...drag me back into this.
This is definitely the Dollars' doing!
They do whatever they want!
We can't do anything without you after all, our superior!
He's not just your superior, he's the shogun!
Uh, I'm sorry!
Whatever, it's fine.
I can't call myself a shogun in this state.
I'm just a simple commoner.
Or, a simple...
A simple...high schooler.
Right, I just wanted to be a simple high schooler.
I was able to obtain some peace.
I was surrounded by good friends and was leading a modestly dangerous life...
And you've destroyed it.
I can't forgive you.
I absolutely can't forgive you for laying a hand on Anri.
We will crush the Slasher, no matter how many of them there are.
And if the Dollars are behind this, then...we'll crush the Dollars.
You dragged me back into this...
Damn it.
Damn it!
I've returned...
...even though I had no intentions of doing so...
I've come back here.
So that Saki and I...
...can settle things with that guy's past.
Next Time: Life and Death are in the Hands of Fate.