I am announcing it here.
Once I, Aisaka Taiga, am elected as student council president...
I am going to take over this school...
And turn your high school memories into a sea of blood.
And send you all to the mo-mo-morgue!
Tenori Taiga, as student council president?!
No way, please stop!
I'm the head of her supporting team!
If you got something to say, tell it to me!
It's Kitamura.
I heard that he said he was going to quit the student council and not run in the election.
So that's why Tenori Taiga nominated herself.
I won't go easy on anyone who gets in my way, no matter who it is!
Dammit!
At this rate, Tenori Taiga's gonna be the student council president!
Our school lives are gonna be ruined!
Someone!
Is there anyone who will nominate himself?
That's right, if Kitamura nominates himself...
Why isn't he running?
I'm beggin' you, please!
At this rate, our school life is going to be a complete waste!
Hey, what are you do-
Kitamura Baiting Plan?
Yes.
We thought if we could turn it into a situation where everyone would be unhappy...
He would have no choice but to run himself.
So, basically...
You thought he'd straighten out if he just became the student council president?
We weren't the only ones who thought that way.
Yesterday, when I was calling around and explaining the plan...
Everyone in class decided to help out.
So that's why you performed that little farce earlier.
But...
What are you going to do if Kitamura never nominates himself?
If there aren't any other candidates by the deadline on Friday...
Aisaka-san will really become the student council president.
Kitamura-kun is...
Not the kind of person to leave things as is.
I got it.
Come by the teacher's room later.
I'll teach you how to use the printer.
You need to make posters and manifest flyers, right?
I didn't realize Kitamura was this stubborn.
I thought that would have been enough for it to work out.
There's only one day left.
Is there anything left we can do?
I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
Yes?
Is this Takasu-kun's cell phone?
Yes, it is...
Sorry.
You don't know me, but I'm Murase, from the student council.
The student council?
Really?
Thanks for telling me.
Ryuji, what was that about?
Ryuji...
Where are you going?
I'm going to go...
Punch Kitamura's lights out!
Wai...
President Kanou is going to leave school next week and study abroad in America.
But, Kitamura, about the president...
That idiot!
Takasu-kun?
I'm sorry...
I just couldn't tell you.
We're friends, aren't we?
It was just so pathetic...
There was no way I could even begin to tell you.
Just because I like the student council president...
I heard she's going to America next week.
Yeah.
She said she's going to be an astronaut.
There's an astronautic professor over there who personally invited her to come to his university.
Wow.
I didn't know anything about it.
Actually...
I was planning to become the student council president.
If she had acknowledged me, I was going to confess to her.
But by the time I become president, that person won't be here anymore.
"Then what's the point of me becoming president?"
When I thought that...
I just...
Wanted to quit everything...
Wanted to break everything.
So then you dyed your hair?
Today, my dad finally got really angry at me.
As you can see, he hit me pretty hard.
I really am an idiot.
It's not like by doing this she's going to cancel her study abroad.
Things never go the way you want them to.
What are you thinking?
Well...
Taiga and I were talking about the very same thing before.
We were saying that things just aren't going right.
At the end, Taiga just blew up and knocked a light pole down.
That's just like Aisaka.
She's on a completely different level from me.
I wonder...
If I'd feel better if Aisaka knocked me down?
Ryuji!
Hey!
You stupid dog!
Taiga.
I actually know why you guys did it.
I know Aisaka decided to run for my sake.
And that everyone's worried about me.
I can't go on like this.
I'm going home.
Thanks for listening.
Kitamura!
I'm okay.
I'll make my own decision.
See you tomorrow at school!
There you are, Ryuji!
What were you doing in a place like this?
You didn't really hit Kitamura...
No.
Then, what was that phone call about?
Not telling.
Finally, tomorrow's election day!
Anyone who doesn't vote for me, I'm going to chase you to the ends of hell!
Got it?
This school is...
T-Taiga!
Kitamura.
Kitamura-kun.
Sorry about that, you two.
It's okay now.
No!
I won't stand for any more violence!
I, Kitamura Yusaku, will lead this school on the right path!
Kitamura-kun.
You made your decision,
Kitamura.
Isn't it just some mistake?
It's true.
Kitamura-kun hasn't turned in his nomination form.
The rules say if he doesn't turn it in by four, he can't become a candidate.
Excuse me, I need to go!
Wait, Takasu-kun!
What's wrong, Takasu?
If you're looking for Aisaka and the others, they already left.
Apparently, there's a new cafe near the station...
You have until four to turn in your nomination form.
What are you going to do?
Are you really going to...
Let's go home, Takasu.
Are you serious?
You still have some time to think it over.
I thought about it for a whole day, but I still came to the same conclusion.
It's...
Fine.
Kitamura.
It's been a while since we went home together with just the two of us.
Not since we were first years, I think.
You were pretty busy with the student council.
Now that I think of it...
I never told you why I got into the student council.
Yeah...
When I just got into high school...
I was really excited.
I wanted to go all out, start over with my high school debut.
And of course, the first step to having a great time in high school...
Is getting a girlfriend, right?
Then I heard that there was an incredible beauty in another class.
And I went and confessed to her, but...
I told you this before.
After getting totally turned down by Aisaka...
When I was pretty down...
She appeared.
I saw everything, newbie!
It's alright!
Your high school life has only just begun!
Come to the student council!
She said she was going to give me tons of boring paperwork to make me forget and stand up again.
She dragged me straight to the student council room.
After that, every day became really fun.
I even became friends with Aisaka.
My dream of a fun high school life became reality.
That day...
When she reached out to me...
That shaky first step wasn't wasted.
But...
Right now...
I can't take the next step.
And?
You're just going to run away?
What are you going to do about the brats who believe in you and are waiting for you to become student council president?
Are you going to abandon them?
Were you the kind of guy that could do that?
Your foot is lifted, right?
You did it so you could move forward, right?
Then what else is there...
But to use that foot to take that step?
Don't slack off.
I'll be watching you...
To see what kind of student council president you become.
What was that?
Takasu.
What time is it?
3:58.
A superstar shows up...
At the most exciting moment.
Sorry.
I've got something urgent I have to do.
Yeah.
And now we will start the student council speeches.
Since the other candidate withdrew, the only candidate is 2-C's Kitamura Yusaku-san.
Your speech, please.
Thank you for your introduction.
I'm Kitamura Yusaku.
I...
No, I...
About the student council president...
About you...
I love you!
The reason I can stand here today...
Is because I fell in love with you.
Before you leave, I want to ask you about your feelings.
Do I have no hope?
Is there nothing special between you and I?
Please tell me!
That's a... Love confession, right?
Kanou, answer, answer!
That's right! Answer him.
Just say it!
How about it?
And apparently, that's how it is.
That is the Kitamura Yusaku, vice president, that you all know.
He's interesting, right?
If guy that interesting becomes the president...
I'm sure this school will be more interesting too.
Please cast your vote for that interesting guy over there!
Kanou-senpai!
Why...
Didn't you answer him properly?
Yesterday...
You told Kitamura to move forward.
So why?!
I only meant for him to nominate himself.
I didn't tell him to confess.
Are you running away?!
Stupid guys who can't move anywhere but in a straight line are called awkward.
Kitamura had better learn how to live more intelligently.
You're a good friend.
Please continue to be friends with Kitamura.
Hey! I'm still...
Taiga?
Kitamura-kun... Was crying.
Please, Ryuji.
Go to his side.
It's no good if it's me.
I can't be by his side.
You...
What are you going to do?
I'm okay.
I'm okay...
So please, go to Kitamura.
But...
Go!
You can never get the things you want.
When I realized that...
And was standing in shock, still in confusion...
Kitamura-kun took this hand and smiled at me.
What a kind person.
No matter how many times I say thank you, it's not enough.
I know the one he wants isn't me.
But...
I want to do what I can.
Kanou!
Sumire!
Tenori Taiga!
Why's she here?
This may be wrong.
This is a raid!
There was still one complete idiot left.
Alright.
I'll be your opponent.
I was already irritated anyway.
Kendou club people...
I don't know if this...
Is wrong...
All I know is...
These feet won't stop.
Is there a guy named Takasu here?
Please come!
Tenori Taiga is...!
You idiot!
Stop saying idiot!
You're just a coward!
You're afraid of being hurt and hurting someone.
That cowardice, that fear... Hurt Kitamura-kun!
I can't forgive you!
Never!
Stop it, Taiga!
Let me go!
Oh my god, what is this?
Taiga!
Coward!
Chicken!
You're a weakling who can't even face your own feelings!
So what if I'm weak?
You're just a simple-minded violent idiot!
That's better than you!
Say it!
If you can't accept Kitamura-kun's feelings...
Just say, "I hate you!"
Say it!
What the hell do you know about me?!
If I could become a simple-minded idiot like you, I would!
I wish I could become an idiot that just moved straight forward!
If I said I liked him, that idiot would try and follow me!
If he knew I wanted him to do that, he'd try to do it for me.
He'd have to sacrifice a lot of things.
He's that kind of guy.
That's why...
That's why I can't become an idiot!
You're a really kind person.
I really loved you from the bottom of my heart.
I'm glad I fell in love with you.
Thank you very much!
After that, we couldn't do anything until the teachers rushed in and cleared things up.
I'm sorry for the trouble we caused.
What's wrong?
When I was cleaning up, I picked up a student notebook.
It looks like it's Taiga's.
In that case, give it to Takasu-kun...
But he went with the teacher.
She really likes him.
Below that-
This...
I'll return it.
C'mon, let's go back to our classroom.
Have you stopped feeling guilty?
Kanou-senpai spent her remaining time at school with her face all bruised.
After two days, she left for America.
Kitamura became the "Number One Sorriest Guy in School."
And the next student council president.
And...
Taiga got suspended for two weeks.
It's Christmas!
The angel Taiga is going to do something for your love!
Even if I have to run around, even if I have to strip naked!
No, it'll be a pain if you catch a cold.
So please, wear clothes.