Student Cultural Society
Ta-Taichi!
H-Hey...
You didn't need to rush here.
Student Cultural Society
But...
You sent me a text saying
that you wanted to talk.
Well, Nagase...
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
Dumb wrestling nut
Quit beating
around the bush!
How about laughing more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Loves his little sister
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
That comic was pretty cool.
Time for some curry.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi Academy
Let's go to the
sale tomorrow
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
Inabaaaan
Sorry I was even born
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Curry hot pot
Inaba Himeko
but I still like her
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
me yui
We should get married
I love youuuuu
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to have
curry hot pot.
What do you say?
The whole world
Let's go
to Disneyland
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry, I can't
go out with you.
Seriously.
Done tomorrow's
homework?
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
Time is multifaceted
Did you hear that?
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
I did some thinking,
and I realized that I'm a selfish, egotistical jerk.
Once my mind is made up,
I forget about everything else and do my own thing.
And if I think I'm right about something,
I'll never admit that I'm wrong.
That's why I ended up hurting
Inaba and arguing with Aoki.
And I hurt you, too.
I'm a selfish jerk,
so I thought it'd be best if I kept my distance to avoid hurting anyone.
But when I actually tried to
distance myself, I realized
that I want to be with you guys.
Instead of staying away
to avoid hurting everyone,
I'd rather stay together and risk it.
So, if you don't mind,
can I stay by your side?
That's not fair, Taichi.
Er, uh...
I've been working hard
to keep everyone together.
But everyone was getting hurt,
so I figured it was inevitable
that we'd all break down.
I was convinced of that.
But now you say it doesn't matter
if we all hurt each other?
Well, it makes some sense.
But I never thought you'd flat-out say that it doesn't matter if we hurt each other.
Yeah, I've been doing a lot of thinking.
Are you going to tell everyone else what you told me and bring back the whole club?
That's the plan.
This doesn't feel right.
I was trying hard, but then you
just took it all upon yourself.
Uh, well...
You really are a selfish jerk.
But your heart's usually in the right place.
Even if your methods aren't the best.
My sister said something similar.
That's why I ended up hurting you.
I thought you said it was inevitable
that we'd hurt each other?
I didn't mean physically.
It's okay. I forgive you.
Okay.
First, I'll talk to Inaban.
I'll call Aoki.
All right, let's do this!
Yeah!
Can't Stop, Can't Stop, Can't Stop
It's been a while.
Yeah.
So, Aoki...
I said some terrible things to you the other day.
I was too arrogant and full of myself.
I was convinced that I could do everything myself.
But that was wrong!
I can't undo the wrong I've done,
but I want to apologize!
Sorry!
Aoki?
Ah, you bastard!
You beat me to the punch!
Yeah, so...
I was about to apologize too.
Huh?
When you called me, though,
I already figured you beat me to it.
It really hurt when Iori said
I was getting too jealous.
I died a little on the inside.
Oh, I'm not saying that Iori
was being mean or anything.
It hurt because she was right.
I was jealous of you because you saved Yui and everyone else while I did nothing.
I started avoiding you guys
because I couldn't accept that.
Honestly, I only saved them by chance.
Besides, it was for my own reasons
that I kept saying I wanted to help Kiriyama.
Taichi, I'm sorry!
Aoki...
Can I come in?
Oh. No luck, huh?
She sent me packing before
I had a chance to talk to her.
But I'm going to drop by her house again.
It's probably too soon for us to tag along, right?
Do you think Iori got through to Inaba this time?
She said she'd call if all went well...
But since she hasn't...
Taichi...
Let's sit down.
Doesn't it scream adolescence when you see two guys having a talk out here?
Let's enjoy our youth!
I don't think it's possible to do
something completely altruistic.
Yeah. In the end, everything we do is for ourselves.
But I still...
...want to help Yui, right?
Yeah.
But I don't think we can do it ourselves.
Kiriyama has to let us help her.
Sure, but we have no idea how long these episodes will continue,
and she can't hide in her room forever.
If Kiriyama has another episode,
we should be able to stop her if we're there.
You think we can stop Yui?
If we're really careful and try our best...
That's an old-fashioned way of thinking.
I have no idea how you and Yui were able to work out her problems before.
I took your advice.
Huh?
You mentioned that swapping personalities presented us with new opportunities.
That's how I got the idea.
So maybe there's a solution that's unique to our current situation.
I-I think I have an idea.
Really?
Kiriyama
Yui? Yui!
Your friends are here again.
Open the door, Yui!
Don't worry, "Mom"!
We'll talk to Yui!
Thank you for dropping by so often.
Please, I would do anything for Yui!
Yui, it's me and Taichi.
We want to talk.
Can you open the door?
Come in.
It's been a while.
Uh-huh...
Yui, let's go outside.
Let's go to school.
You'll be fine.
How many times do I have to repeat myself?
I don't know when I might
suddenly beat someone up.
I can't go outside.
But if you just hide in here forever,
this whole mess might never get fixed.
You'll be fine, Yui!
You can stop yourself from beating someone up!
Don't be stupid!
I can try to stop myself,
but if I have an episode, I'll lose control!
That's not true!
Even when your desire is unleashed,
if you try really, really hard
to stop yourself, it'll work!
It won't work when your desire is unleashed.
You can't stop yourself.
That's how it works.
That's how it's supposed to work, but it's not impossible to control!
Huh?
I'm saying that you can stop yourself!
If I can prove that it's possible,
you'll be able to come outside,
come to school,
and come to the clubroom, right?
Well, if I can stop myself...
Okay, that's perfect!
I can't say I'm proud of it,
but I love you, Yui!
I really love you!
I love you a lot! A whole lot!
I'm also not proud to admit
that I have a dirty mind.
Honestly, my mind is always in the gutter!
I'm thinking dirty thoughts!
Really dirty thoughts!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
And honestly, if I had an episode right now,
I would be seconds away
from throwing myself at you!
Wh-What are you saying?!
That's gross!
Wait! You've got it all wrong!
Sicko!
I'm saying that my ironclad determination will stop me from doing that!
It proves that if you're determined enough,
you can fight back when
your desire is unleashed!
H-How stupid can you be?!
I have no idea what you're trying to say!
Well, I guess I understand what you mean.
Okay?
So, Yui...
Let's spend a night in a love hotel.
No way!
Why would I put myself in danger?!
Because nothing will happen.
How can you be so sure?!
Because the last thing
I want to do is hurt you.
Because I truly love you.
I'm confident that my desire to not hurt you will always be stronger.
Besides, on the off chance that I do give in,
you'd have no trouble
beating the crap outta me.
I don't want to hurt you.
In fact, you should wear
something sexy to tempt me.
Strip down to your underwear,
dress up like a bunny girl,
or wear nothing but an apron...
Stop fantasizing!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Come on, Taichi.
Seal the deal with your usual spiel!
Don't call it that before I even say anything!
You guys are so stupid.
Okay, I'm ready for that thing you do.
It's really not like that!
Anyway, I've been thinking.
Had you ever injured someone or gotten violent before what happened at the train station?
I practice karate, so it's happened before.
But it didn't feel like I was
using violence to hurt someone
since it was during a match or practice.
That's what I thought.
That's why you didn't understand what it meant to hurt someone.
Right?
Uh-huh.
But now you understand how hard it is.
And you don't want to hurt anyone else.
Which means if you ever want to beat someone up,
your desire to not hurt anyone will probably triumph.
I guess you could consider not wanting to do something a desire.
Actually, I hurt Nagase the other
day when I had an episode.
Huh?
So I think I kinda understand how you feel.
But I still want to be with you guys.
I'm guessing that you feel the same way.
You should believe in yourself more.
Good job, Taichi.
But you just made a bunch of
assumptions with no concrete proof.
So let's go to a love hotel!
Stop talking about that!
My mom's downstairs!
Kiriyama, you're yelling.
Oh, fine.
I'll go then.
What?!
No way!
To school!
But I'm still worried.
So...
If it looks like I'm losing control,
please stop me.
That's not the way to say it.
Huh?
Say this instead.
"Please protect me"?
It would be my honor!
Nagase Iori
Cellphone
Begin Use
Talk
Decline
Away Message
Nagase Iori
Missed Call
Locked
Nagase Iori
Missed Call
Locked
Nagase Iori
Missed Call
Locked
File                  Messages             Browser                  Map
File                  Messages             Browser                 Map
File                   Messages             Browser                 Map
File                   Messages             Browser                  Map
Himeko?
Did your phone just ring?
Hey, are you okay?
You've been acting strange again.
You're imagining things.
Yui!
W-Wait, Iori.
Yui?
You came to school, Yui!
That's great.
Sorry. Were you worried?
Of course we were. Silly girl.
We spent every day agonizing over whether we should visit you or not.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, Kiriyama. You're back at school?
You look well.
Yeah, sorry about making everyone worry.
Did you put on some weight?
You're imagining things!
I think he's right.
Hey! Watch your mouth!
I hope Inaban also comes to the clubroom.
So much!
Isn't this a little excessive?
I was only going to buy enough for this week,
but I had an episode at the store.
I used up my allowance for the month.
It's too late to return them now.
Aoki?
Hey, Aoki?
Give me some of those dumplings!
Desire unleashed?!
What?!
No way! Don't take mine!
Give them to me!
I wondered where this would lead...
There's more over there!
No! I absolutely must have yours!
Why do you want mine?!
That's mine!
Hold on, Nagase!
I already took a bite!
Grab another one!
I want the sandwich in your hand!
These are all mine!
You too, Kiriyama?!
Count me in!
Three at the same time?
Well, if it's just their hunger that's being released,
that's not bad—
Eat!
Give me some!
Morning, Inaba.
Um, if you're worried about what you said to me the other day, I've gotten over it.
Come back to the clubroom.
We're all waiting for you.
Bye.
Himeko, you have a visitor.
It's Mr. Goto, your teacher.
Goto?
You're not here to tell me
that everything's over, are you?
Not everything. Not yet.
Were you surfing the web?
Why do you care?
Back in middle school, that's all you ever did.
You spent all your time outside class alone.
You couldn't trust anyone else.
You always put up barriers.
You were socially active enough that you'd have no problems at school,
but you had no friends—
Enough!
I'm not interested in any of that.
If you need something, spit it out.
Have you forgotten, Inaba?
I told you that I would make it
entertaining if necessary.
Are you gonna toss me in the river this time?
I thought that only applied if we hid in our rooms.
Inaba, you're essentially hiding in your room now.
That's not true.
I'm going to school.
To prevent me from interfering?
You're a fascinating person, Inaba.
Can you get to the point?!
You didn't come here to make small talk.
Small talk...
Yeah, you're right about that.
I'm here to shake things up.
Shake things up?
Yes...
You're always so uptight, Inaba.
Why so serious?
Because you decided to mess with
us by unleashing our desires.
No, that's not what I meant.
Why do you care so much about preserving that atmosphere you share with your friends?
If it's wearing you out,
you should tear it down.
Judging from your current state of mind,
if your little group falls apart,
you'll try to destroy the world.
At least that's what I was hoping.
Who are you?
Is the atmosphere you shared
what you care about the most?
What?
Isn't there something else
you care about just as much?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, there most certainly is.
But you're trying desperately
to pretend you don't know.
Because you'll destroy your little group
if you let those feelings out.
Isn't there someone you care for deeply?
Shut up!
You've become fully aware of your own feelings.
There's no turning back now.
Once you know, it's too late to run away.
Oh?
I didn't expect this to work so well.
I'm getting excited.
Can I sock you real hard?
I'll return control to this body's owner the moment before you hit.
Are you going to visit anyone else?
You don't need to worry.
I made this trip just to see you.
Don't you find these little twists entertaining?
Hell no.
And if you're able to take control of anyone,
why did you use Goto instead of a family member?
There are very few people who wouldn't start asking questions when they have blanks in their memory.
Stop trying to hide in your room.
Yo.
Inaba...
Morning!
We were wondering why you were late.
I wasn't gonna skip out.
I'm in charge of bringing the vegetables, after all.
Let's get going.
If we're late, Fujishima will start griping.
Yamaboshi Academy
Members of Class 1-3
Next Time
Putting Into Words
It feels like it's been ages since
we just chatted about nothing.
Are the three of them doing okay?
That's the only way the
five of us can stay together!
What's that mean?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
She knows!
She knows! She knows!
I see you're busy shakin' out that thin red velvet cloth
But before you take your leave, might I ask where you're off to?
Me, I'm headed for the morning, travelin' to the west
Then may God be with you
Your eyes, reflecting up to me from the teacup
look just like a rabbit's in a cage
Must be because we forgot to add the sugar
But who cares about that
Your love is sweet enough
I cry out, again and again to the dawning sky
Are there really things in this world that I truly cherish?
This aching in my heart, and the place where I belong
Maybe even those are things that I hold dear all the same
Cry out
Nagase Iori
Tune in next time!
Laugh more
Rice? Bread?
me yui
I want to have
curry hot pot.
What do you say?
Let's go out
Screw that
Let's go to the
sale tomorrow