South Planeptune
Maidakai Village
Excursions are so much fun!
Onward ho!
Halt, citizens of Eden.
If you advance any further,
we'll open fire!
Hey!
It's the bad goddess!
Peashy...
I hate bad goddesses,
but Papa said I could play with them.
So,
let's play!
Only 1 hour of games per day!
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
#10 The Battlefront (Conflict)
of Oblivion
Sis!
Is it true that Eden
attacked Planeptune?
Yes.
It seems Nepgear's fighting by herself right now.
I'll go help!
Take a look at this, Uni.
Lift the restrictions!
Give us freedom of expression!
I want to see more extreme content!
Lift the restrictions on adult content!
Give us freedom of expression!
We don't need no age limits!
Lift the restrictions!
Lift the restrictions on adult content!
Riots involving radical factions that endorse
Eden's beliefs have simultaneously broken out
at Lastation,
Leanbox,
and Lowee.
So this is no time to be worrying about Planeptune, I take it?
This is clearly a diversionary tactic used by Eden,
but we have no choice but to address the problem in front of us.
No way! What about Planeptune?
What about Nepgear?
Our foremost duty is to protect our own citizens.
We're CPUs, after all.
Lift the restrictions!
Perfect!
We're on the right track.
Take that, and that, and that!
The entire world fell into chaos in an instant.
Please, don't talk like this has nothing to do with you.
You're the commander-in-chief of our army, you know.
"Our army"?
The people only wage war and riot because you're controlling their minds!
What the hell is that black substance?
Like I said, I don't know either.
These items were all provided by our client,
and we're forbidden to pry any further.
I'm scared.
I feel like we're going to turn the world upside down.
I wonder about that.
None shall pass! Not even you, Peashy!
'Kay!
Let's play right here, then!
It seems that goddess is exactly who we've been looking for.
I knew it.
So the reason Peashy recognized me and Iffy right from the start...
...was probably because she knew the two of you in the other dimension.
This is making my head spin!
Right now, a part of my world is totally on the way to destruction!
Are you saying Peashy was originally supposed to govern that place?
I think so.
So I need Plutia to bring her back immediately, even if she has to use force to do it.
I don't want to force her.
If we don't do anything, our nation will be in big trouble too!
I know, but...
Hello?
Oh, yes.
Hey, Neptune!
Jeepers!
N-Noire?!
What are you still doing there?
Why don't you go keep your citizens safe?
But I...
It's P-ko, you know?
Oh, please. Aren't you a CPU?
If you're gonna call yourself one,
put your nation before your feelings!
Are you telling me to get rid of P-ko?
That's what I'd do.
That's all I wanted to say.
Later.
Was I too harsh?
No, I'm sure she'll bounce back.
Maybe Noire could do it, but I sure can't.
If you can't do it, then that's fine.
Let's stay here,
play some games and relax.
This isn't the time for games, even for me...
Why?
If you're not gonna go, what difference does it make either way?
No!
Games are a means of entertainment,
not an escape from reality.
Escape from reality?
I...
This is fun!
I knew it!
I can't deal any damage after all!
Here I come!
Wh-Why?
I'm no match for her!
Sis...
Sorry I'm late, Nepgear.
Don't be.
But, Sis...
Come on, let's play some more!
Nepgear, take care of the soldiers and monsters for me.
Hey!
Are you listening to me?
They might break through the barricade.
But...
Go.
Okay, got it.
P-ko!
I'll play with you now.
I'll do things my way.
Come at me, P-ko!
Here comes a big one!
Huh?
Done already?
It'll take more than that to bring ol' Neptuna down.
You know that well, don't you, P-ko?
"Neptuna"?
I dunno!
Nah, I'm sure you remember.
I mean,
I'm your Neptuna!
I dunno!
You do know!
I dunno.
I don't need you!
Weak!
Boring!
I won't play with you anymore.
It takes one to know one!
I hate you!
Eden has almost no believers yet,
but I sensed massive amounts of Share Energy in Yellow Heart.
Something's off here.
Noire.
Plutia! Why are you here?
Because Neppy refused to play games with me.
Excuse me?
What about you?
Should you be here?
It's all right.
I've got a sister I can rely on.
If you want to keep rioting, you'd best be prepared!
I see.
CPUs!
Shh!
They heard us!
I guess I've no choice but to
take you head on!
I thought everyone here had been turned into soldiers,
but I see you managed to stick it out.
S-Spare me!
What should I do, I wonder? Lickity lick.
That tickles!
I knew you'd come!
Accept my torrent of love, Noire!
I hate you!
Got you now, P-ko.
Lemme go!
I'm never gonna let you go!
Never again!
I'd expect nothing less from you, Noire.
But my love is unlimited!
This is good.
This is great!
Rei, quit goofing off and go look for the other goddess.
I'm right here.
Oh dear.
How?
My friend just happened to know where the entrance was.
By giving her information,
I kept my chastity safe!
You're not really my type,
but you still need to be punished.
Oh, do you think you could arrange for Noire to punish me instead?
Oh?
Speak of the goddess!
There is nothing my sword can't cut!
My!
You're good.
Then it's time I...
took the extreme offensive!
What the hell?
A machine that provides Share Energy?
How violent.
You could've just asked to see it
instead of breaking the wall down.
Is this the secret behind
Yellow Heart's strength?
Ever heard of this thing called client confidentiality?
So if someone happened to smash this thing to bits...
What would happen to Peashy and the nation of Eden?
Since you won't tell us,
I guess we'll have to find out for ourselves.
Fighting Viper!
Lace Ribbon Dance!
Nooo!
Lemme go!
I won't!
I won't let go!
No!
Remember me!
Please remember me, P-ko!
Dunno, dunno, dunno!
I don't know anything about you!
Give us freedom of expression!
Huh?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
No! Lemme go!
P-ko...
P-ko!
I hate you!
But I like you.
I love you, P-ko!
I love you.
I love you!
I hate you...
I hate you!
It's okay.
I don't mind if you hate me.
So long as you're here.
I hate you...
And thus, the curtain fell on Eden's short-lived history.
The riots in each nation died down without any major casualties.
Everything went back to the way it was... or so it was supposed to.
But Peashy's memories didn't return.
Nep... tune?
Take care, everyone.
This is goodbye?
Things will get lonely without you here.
It feels like we've been friends forever.
I won't forget any of you.
Me neither.
Oh, Gear.
Here you go.
Is this me?
Thank you very much!
Take good care of it, okay?
Take care of yourself, Peashy.
It doesn't matter if you don't remember us.
We'll always be friends!
'Kay.
I hope our counterparts in the other dimension make friends with Peashy as well..
I'm sure they'll do fine.
It's you and me we're talking about.
Okay then, everyone.
It saddens me to no end that we have to part, but it's time.
The portal can't stay open forever!
Wait!
Sis isn't here yet.
It's time.
Opening the portal!
Hey!
You're late, Neptune!
Sorry!
Thank you so much for coming here, Plutia.
We'll definitely see each other again, right?
Yup.
Definitely.
Take these with you, P-ko.
Delish Pudding
Nep's
Neptune, what's this?
Delish Pudding
Nep's
The most delicious thing in the whole wide world!
U-Um...
It's time to get into the portal.
Okay.
Bye bye, everyone.
Let's go, Peashy.
Neptuna?
We don't know
why we will meet
when we will meet
The things you saw
The things you did
We both have our separate stories to tell
I am one string
You are the other string
When we are woven into fabric,
perhaps it will make life better for others
We sometimes wonder
why we are alive, and doubt ourselves
We sometimes chase our dreams
only to stumble and fall
How can we be anything of note?
Full of uncertainty, the wind envelops us
I am one string
You are the other string
Meeting the one you are destined to meet is true happiness
That is what all say
Neptuna
Peashy
P-ko...
Neptuna
Peashy
I won't forget any of you.
Me neither.
Oh, Gear.
Here you go.
Huh? This isn't like the others—
Take good care of it, okay?
The Messenger (Aggressor) From the Ancient Past
I will!