Main entrance, all clear!
He'll arrive momentarily.
Who are those people?
Minamin, somethin' wrong?
It must be him.
Who?
Of course...
Kimimaro...
I've missed you dearly, ma petite chérie!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
I see your security's as tight as ever.
Really?
I only brought half as many guards as usual.
Who is that boy?
I'm kinda curious now!
His name is Ijuuin Kimimaro.
He's from a prominent aristocratic family and an old friend of the president's.
I've heard that he's her fiancé.
Whaaaaa?!
Fiancé?
So they promised to marry each other?
M-Marry?!
How Minami feels about that is another matter, though.
He's a Noble Academy student too,
but he's studying in England at the moment.
He's on vacation and came back to see the president again.
On his private jet!
Wow, sounds like a movie!
But Minamin didn't look too starstruck to me.
Minami's Fiancé?
The Nobleman Makes His Return!
Have a seat,
ma petite chérie.
Thank you.
What a gentleman...
That's kinda overboard, isn't it?
Hey, good morning.
Professeur!
I elected to garnish your desk with roses so that Minami's gaze may grace them.
Isn't it a little... big?
It's but a petal compared to the garden that is my love for Minami!
L-Love?
Dear me...
Now I gotta know!
I appreciate the thought, but such a large bouquet doesn't suit this classroom.
Oh, my apologies!
It appears my love is simply too grand.
They're like butlers...
I can see this causing problems...
But it looks like he really does love Minami!
Shoot, we've got class!
How beautiful!
The flower bed I've been tending to is blooming nicely,
so let's have a garden lunch!
A lunch au grand air sounds like a wonderful idée!
Kimimaro...
Allow me to set the stage proper!
Kimimaro, could you take those away?
But why?
There's a certain wonder to eating lunch while at eye level with the flowers.
As Haruka here showed me. Right?
Yes!
Haruka?
I'm Haruno Haruka!
Sorry to make you take down what you just set up...
It's fine, but...
how could Minami be expected to dine there?!
You're free to join us if you'd like.
Goodness, you're injured!
Oh, I supposed I got a cut from tending the garden.
This shall not do!
Medical team, at once!
Yes, sir!
Oh, It's nothing.
You licked it?!
Sir Kimimaro!
Stay with us!
Get the limo!
Right!
Is... he okay?
He seems sensitive...
Has that boy... always been like that?
He has his dramatic side...
but that's what pushes him to work so hard.
He has a soft side, too.
I see...
Doesn't seem too streetwise, though.
Well, let's have lunch.
You've changed...
Why, O Minami?
Could it be the influence of those ruffians?
Particularly that Haruka girl...
Un, deux, trois!
Un, deux, troi—
Ouch...
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm sorry!
I'm fine, don't worry.
Now, from the top!
Right!
Ballet has always meant the world to my Minami!
Yet now she falls on her rear and giggles it off!
That first year is undoubtedly a bad influence on Minami!
I must know everything about Haruno Haruka!
Investigate her posthaste!
Right!
Un deux trois, un deux tro—
As I thought, she does not deserve my Minami!
Sir Kimimaro!
What can I do?
At this point...
you must separate her from Minami, no?
Separate her?
Hey, those flowers are coming along.
Oh, Kimimaro!
Are you all better now?
Oh, no problems here.
If there were one...
it would be with you, not me.
Huh?
Flowers are quite beautiful.
Since the day I first met Minami, she's been my noble goddess, more beautiful than a bouquet!
Pardon!
Yes?
Bonjour.
How may I help you?
Ever since, I spent every annual party nurturing our bond...
until finally, we entered Noble Academy together!
Bonjour, ma princesse.
Bonjour.
Minami's been close to your heart for a long time, huh?
But Minami has changed...
Huh?
Her once dignified demeanor has begun to decay.
B-But I think Minami's splendid just the way she is!
But she used to be even more so!
Yes...
She was the epitome of a lady,
blooming with majesty above all others!
Huh...
Haruka, was it?
Um, yes!
We all have places we deserve to be.
In your case, that place is not here.
Huh?
Let me be frank.
I'd like you to stay away from Minami from now on.
Wh-What's so bad about me being with Minami?
This is for Minami's sake.
You do not deserve her!
I'll leave it at that.
Excuse me.
Minami!
What makes you think you can say such horrible things to Haruka?
If you have a problem with me, then say it to my face!
Th-That's not it at all!
I just don't think you need commoners like her bringing you down!
You have no consideration for others.
Haruka is no "commoner."
She's my friend!
I suggest you never say such things again.
Adieu.
Sir Kimimaro!
Get the medical team!
Right!
I'm fine...
Just leave me alone for a bit...
Stop.
Here!
Freeze.
Go.
Right!
Let's go.
Yes, let's.
Am I just being self-centered?
You have no consideration for others.
Consideration...
She's my friend!
Haruka here showed me. Right?
I think Minami's splendid just the way she is!
The way she is...
Stop!
Freeze!
Who are you?!
You have a dream?
Show it to us.
I want to live my life with Minami!
We'll seal your dream in the cage of despair!
Stop!
Freeze!
Your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
What was that all about?
You do not deserve her!
Dyspairvil!
It's a Dyspairvil!
Huh?
Haruka!
Right!
There!
Dyspair.
Haruka!
Minami!
Kimimaro!
Haruka!
On it!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Girls, let's go!
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Dyspair!
Wait!
Flora!
Dyspairvil!
Girls!
Well done, Dyspairvil.
Excellent, Dyspairvil.
I'm sorry! This is all because I rushed in...
Are you concerned about what Kimimaro told you?
Huh?
Sorry.
I... happened to overhear.
I am...
I just wanted to work harder
so I'd deserve to be your friend!
Can you two focus?!
Fireworks!
Precure!
Scarlet Illusion!
Are you unharmed?
Thanks...
What were you even yapping about?
Sorry...
Who has the right to decide
whether someone "deserves" me?
Ice!
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
Dyspair!
Haruka, you're fine as you are.
I choose to be with you.
Dyspair...
Viiiiiil!
I dunno what this is about, but you're fine as is.
Indeed!
You two are always together, no?
How could that be a problem?
Dyspair... vil!
Precure!
Rose Tourbillon!
Are you okay?
Yes!
Um...
Dyspairvil!
Flora!
Got it!
Bubble!
Rage, O bubbles!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Lily!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Dyspairviiiil!
Flora...
Yes?
It's true...
As Kimimaro said, I may indeed have changed.
But... I like the new me.
And it's thanks to you that there's a new me to begin with.
So don't concern yourself with what others say.
And please... let's stay friends.
Sure!
I want to be with you too!
Dys!
Dyspairvil!
Don't butt in!
Have you finished your chat?
Huh?
Yes...
Then it's time!
Finish it off!
Right!
Mode Elegant!
Cherry Blossom!
Coral!
Galaxy!
Sun!
Dress Up Premium!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
The dream did not end.
We failed to end it.
Regardless...
you despaired.
Open!
The door to your dream!
Thank goodness he's safe.
Sure you're fine with that dream of his, though?
O-Oh yeah!
Wh-When are you two getting married?!
What?
Are you not betrothed?
Kimimaro's the only one who says that.
I-Is he really?!
Yes, all him.
Oh, great!
Why are you the one happy about it?
Haruka, I'm sorry for what I said before.
Huh?
For all my worrying about Minami, I failed to consider your feelings.
As such, I ended up hurting Minami as well.
Kimimaro!
Minami, you have changed.
But I now realize that it hasn't been for the worse.
Kimimaro...
Thank you!
Y-You truly are, now and forever, ma petite chérie, Minami!
I'll return one day as a gentleman
who is deserving to be by your side!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Mermaid!
This grand blue sea is a mirror
reflecting my heart along the southern winds
I want to know the answer lying within my chest
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Madame Siamour, I'd like a Princess Lesson!
How curious, she's not around.
What's over there?
A cat meetup?
And Madame Siamour's with them!
What the heck?!
Then let's have a Princess Lesson with the cats!
Go! Princess Precure:
Teach Me, Siamour!
Making Dreams Come True 101!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Osaka Prefecture - Sanami (Age 5)
Hyougo Prefecture - Maho (Age 6)