It's been a week since then.
It was just a coincidence that I saved your dog.
I'd probably still be alone even if the accident never happened.
If you're being kind because you're worried,
then stop it.
How did things end up this way?
Idiot...
H-Hey, Sabure!
In this room filled with light,
I'll be waiting for you
If you'd realize you're floating and gazing upon a box,
You'd notice it doesn't return your gaze
The reflected heart is pure white
Just like the light from the falling snow
This shivering rain that blankets me
Isn't going to dispel until the spring breeze returns
So let's search for some azalea
Bring me with you to a comforting garden
Is not something I can ask
That fairy tale-like happiness isn't real
I know that much already
But still
I want to go there
So hot...
Sup.
H-Hi.
Okay. Smooth. Things are completely reset.
My heart is at ease once again because our relationship has been reset.
Yuigahama has been freed from her guilt.
She has returned to her normal life.
Considering my options, it wasn't the wrong decision.
No, it was the correct choice.
That's why it ended with this.
It's fine if we just return to our normal daily routines again.
While you can't reset your life, you can reset your relationships.
The source is me.
Not a single one of my middle school classmates has contacted—
That wasn't a reset. It was deletion.
Did something happen between you and Yuigahama?
Nope. Nothing.
If nothing happened, I doubt she would stop coming here.
Did you have a fight?
No, I don't think so.
Moreover, fights only happen between people close to one another, right?
So rather than a fight—
A dispute?
Did you think that was closer?
Then war?
Wrong. You're getting colder.
An extermination.
Were you listening?
Colder.
A disagreement, I suppose?
Something like that.
I see.
Nothing to be done then.
What, no Yuigahama today either?
Please knock, Ms. Hiratsuka.
Darn, and here I had some expectations for her.
Um, did you need something?
Oh, that's right.
Let's change the match from before into a battle royale.
A battle royale with just two people?
You can recruit new members if you want to.
Since it seems like Yuigahama won't be showing up anymore.
It's not like Yuigahama has quit—
If she doesn't come, it's the same thing.
Worrying about people with no motivation beyond compulsory education is moot.
Those without the will can leave if they want to.
U-Um...
I have no motivation or will, so can I leave?
Figured.
Well, thanks to Yuigahama, we know that club growth is tied to club activity.
This is a good opportunity.
Find at least one new member who is motivated and has the will by Monday.
If you'd like, you can start now.
Tyrant.
No, I'm not.
I'm trying to be nice here.
Ms. Hiratsuka, I'd like to confirm something.
We're supposed to look for new members, right?
Exactly, Yukinoshita.
I wish you luck.
New members, huh? What're we gonna do?
I already know someone who may join.
Who? Totsuka?
Totsuka, huh?
It's gotta be Totsuka.
It's Yuigahama.
What?
I mean, she quit, right?
Then she can just join again.
Ms. Hiratsuka only said to find new members.
You think she'll rejoin that easily?
It's pretty normal for people who leave to not come back.
June 18th. Do you know what that day is?
I don't.
It's Yuigahama's birthday.
Probably.
Her email address had 0618 in it, after all.
So you haven't asked her directly, have you?
That's quite the power of communication you've got there.
Anyway, I want to celebrate her birthday with her.
So even if Yuigahama doesn't come back to the Volunteers Club,
I want her to know that I'm thankful for all she's done.
I see.
Say, Hikigaya.
W-Well, u-um...
Would you like to go out, I wonder?
Sorry for making you tag along on your day off.
No probs! I wanna buy Yui a birthday present too.
And I'm looking forward to spending the day with you.
All right, let's do this as efficiently as possible.
I'll head this way.
I'll take the other way.
Then Komachi can take this dir—
Stop right there!
What the...? My finger really hurts.
Since we're all here, let's just stick together.
This way we can ask each other for advice. Better for everyone.
But if we do that, we won't be able to check all the stores.
No worries.
According to my professional opinion about Yui's interests...
We'll be fine as long as we check out this area!
Komachi, it should be around here, right?
Huh? Did you see where Komachi went?
Heya.
Hey, where are you right now?
There's a bunch of stuff I wanna buy. I sort of forgot.
You were the one who suggested we stay together.
I can't believe my sister's mind has turned to mush.
Your big brother's in shock.
I guess it's impossible for you to understand why, huh?
What are you talking about?
Uh, nothing.
I'll probably be another five hours or so.
I'll go home myself, so you two can fight on together.
Wha? Hey!
There's no "fighting on" when we're just shopping.
Yukinoshita...
What did Komachi say?
There was some stuff she wanted to buy, I guess.
She pushed the rest onto us.
She did come with us on her day off,
so I guess we can't really complain.
We'll figure something out.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Am I really that suspicious?
It appears that in this area, people are cautious of male customers that are alone.
I guess even if I'm here, there's not much I can do to help.
I'll head over in that direc—
Wait.
Do you intend to leave this to my discretion?
I'm not bragging, but my standards are different than normal high school girls.
At least you understand that about yourself.
That's why...
I'd like it if you helped.
While I've experienced a crushing failure giving a presentation to a girl before,
I've never bought a present or anything.
Well, I don't think I can really go into any stores.
There's no helping it this time.
Try not to wander too far away from me then.
Too far away?
You can't understand without me spelling it out?
If all you can do is breathe in and out, then even an AC unit is more useful than you.
True. It would be so much easier if I had a feature that could read the atmosphere.
In other words, until the end of today,
I'm saying it's okay if we act like lovers.
Quite the high horse you're on there.
Displeased with something?
No, not really.
I-I see.
It's nothing to be surprised about.
The last thing I'd want is to be her boyfriend, but she doesn't lie.
She said act, so it'll definitely be acting.
So there's no misunderstandings here.
You definitely have a problem with this.
Not really. There's no real reason for me to refuse either.
Actually, shouldn't you be the one refusing?
I don't really mind.
If there are only strangers around,
there's no need to worry about financial damage due to a misunderstanding.
Trimming shop
Things can't go on like this.
I guess we really do need to talk.
I haven't even given him the cookies either.
We aren't getting her office supplies.
And if we're picking clothes for their durability, we'll never decide on what to get.
I doubt she wears clothes for their defensive capabilities.
What other choice was there?
I can only make a decision based on the material and stitching.
I don't know what sort of things she likes, or what her hobbies are.
Does it matter if you do?
Actually, it annoys me when someone says they "know" something with inadequate information.
It's like sending peas from somewhere else to someone from Chiba.
That example was so specific to Chiba. I don't get it.
It's like sending wine to a sommelier with only basic knowledge about it.
I see now.
If that's the case...
How does it look?
Even if you ask me how it looks, all I can say is that it really suits you.
Oh? Thank you.
But we aren't talking about me.
I was asking what you thought about it for Yuigahama.
Wouldn't she be happier with something fluffier and more colorful for someone lacking in the brain department?
That was pretty harsh, but it's hard to respond because it's so accurate.
I'll go with this one.
That's fine. Whatever you pick works.
You're buying that one too, huh?
Huh? Is that you, Yukino?
It is Yukino.
Sister...
Sister?
I'm Yukino's older sister, Haruno.
What's your name?
Hikigaya.
Hikigaya...?
Hikigaya, huh?
Well, nice to meet you.
When did you two start going out?
Come on, out with it.
We're just classmates.
I'm not her boyfriend.
No reason to get flustered about it.
I won't forgive you if you make her cry.
H-Hold—
That hurts.
So close! Too close! Close!
But she does smell good.
Could you please give it a rest?
Sorry. I guess I got a bit carried away.
She's a bit delicate, so look out for her.
Did I do something you don't like just now?
Ah, well...
I have sensitive ears.
Hikigaya, stop exposing your fetishes to a woman you just met.
You won't have any recourse even if you get sued.
You're so interesting, Hikigaya!
Is that enough?
If you don't have any more business with us, we'll be on our way.
Hikigaya, let's have tea after you become her boyfriend.
Your sister sure is something.
Everyone who meets her says the same thing.
There isn't anyone else as perfect as her, I suppose.
Everyone praises her.
You aren't all that different.
Roundabout boasting, huh?
When I said "something," I meant... uh, how should I put it?
How she puts up that thick facade.
She's sociable, and is always smiling.
She's even nice when talking to you.
Certainly, she's every man's ideal woman.
But that's just an ideal. It's not real.
That's why something seems fishy.
Despite your rotten eyes—
No, because of them you're able to see through some things.
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
It is a compliment. I'm praising you.
A-A dog...
H-Hikigaya...
Come here.
Hey, where's your owner?
No leash?
What's with this dog?
Isn't it a little too friendly?
This dog...
Sorry!
Sorry about my dog bothering—
Oh, Yuigahama.
Huh?
Hikki and Yukinon?
Why are you together?
Why? No reason.
Oh, it's fine!
Don't worry. Forget about it.
It's obvious what it means when you're out together on your day off, isn't it?
I get it.
How did I not notice?
And I'm supposed to be good at reading the mood.
Is she misunderstanding something weird here?
W-Well, I'm gonna leave.
Yuigahama, we need to have a talk about us.
Could you come to the club room on Monday?
I don't think I'll want to hear it though...
There's no point in telling me now either.
There's nothing I can really do about it.
I couldn't really tell you properly because of how I am,
but I want to talk this through with you properly.
Sure.
What're you doing?
Hi-Hikki?
What is it again?
The air sure is nice out here.
C'mon. Let's go in.
Yuigahama.
Ya-Yahello, Yukinon.
S-So you wanted to talk about you and Hikki, right?
Yes.
I want to talk to you about our future—
You don't have to trouble yourself with me anymore.
I mean, sure, I was surprised.
But I actually feel like I should celebrate now instead.
I'm surprised you figured it out.
I want to properly celebrate.
And besides, I'm really grateful to you.
I dunno about that.
I didn't do anything for you to be grateful about.
Nothing at all.
Nevertheless, I'm grateful.
Moreover, celebrating isn't something you do just because the person did something, right?
I just genuinely want to do this.
O-Okay...
It seems like they're having two different conversations here.
S-So...
I don't think I want to hear any more...
Yuigahama, aren't you misunderstanding something here?
W-Wait a sec!
Then you two aren't going out or anything?
Of course not.
Yuigahama, even I have things that make me angry.
There's no way that guy could be in a relationship.
He can't even maintain normal relationships.
Shove off.
Like I'd bother with something as annoying as relationships.
If I got a phone call in the dead of the night with someone crying on the other end,
I'm confident I'd break up with them on the spot.
Sorry, sorry. Huh?
I guess we don't have any time for the celebration.
And I even baked a cake.
A cake? Why a cake?
What do you mean why?
I called you here today to celebrate your birthday.
Huh?
You haven't been coming to the club lately, so I wanted to show my appreciation for what you've done.
I suppose this is what you'd call a "token of gratitude."
You got me a present?
Yukinon!
I wasn't the only one who got you something though.
I never would've expected Hikki to give me a present.
Things have been a little awkward because of what happened before and all.
Sorry, this isn't just for your birthday.
How do I put it?
Let's just say this makes us even.
The fact that I saved your dog, and that you looked out for me... is all behind us.
It's not like I helped you out of obligation,
so there's no need for you to repay me.
Well, it's like...
I want to repay you for looking out for me at least.
And with this, it's back to zero. We're even.
You don't have to worry about me anymore.
So that's why it ends with this, okay?
Why do you think of it like that?
I've never once thought of it like I'm pitying you or watching out for you.
I just...
It's so complicated, I don't really understand anymore.
I thought it was simpler.
It's not so complicated, is it?
Hikigaya doesn't believe he helped you.
And you don't believe it was because of pity.
Things were already wrong from the start.
So I think Hikigaya's decision was right when he said, "It ends with this."
But I don't want it to end like this.
Silly.
If it's the end, you just need to start again.
Neither of you are to blame.
Even if who did the helping and who was being helped varied,
you both suffered equally, right?
Then you should blame the source of all of this.
If neither of you are to blame, there's no reason to disagree.
So you two should be able to properly start over.
Ah, I have to go report to Ms. Hiratsuka that we've managed to find a new member.
Hey, can I open that?
As you wish.
Hey, does it look good?
Hold up.
That's...
a dog collar.
Tell me that sooner, dummy!
Honestly! I'm going to see Ms. Hiratsuka!
Thanks, dummy.
At last, his and her beginning will come to an end.
Shining in the bright blue sky I hate so
An airplane soars toward the horizon
Something is stirring from within my heart
I keep all the things I want to say pent up
And turn them into things I can no longer say
I can't even be honest until the end
Just forget that I wanted to be with you,
And that I set you free
If I had told you I wanted to see you
Before the faint trail you left behind vanished,
I would be freed from this
Heartbreak that never ends
I could be here with you again
Hello! Hello! Alone!
Hikigaya, I have an urgent message for you about the Volunteers Club's summer activities.
Please respond as soon as possible.
Are you still sleeping?
I've sent you several messages and have been calling for a while.
You've actually seen them, haven't you?
Hey, you have, right?
Pick up the phone
Scary. Super frightening.
Scary.
Super frightening
Pick up the phone
Scary.
Super frightening
Pick up the phone
Next time:
In any case, it's strange not to
take a break during summer vacation.
In any case, it's strange not to take a break during summer vacation.