Man, you run a greedy business...
600 yen a carton!
I can't go any lower than that!
If you don't like it, ask someone else!
All right, all right! I'll buy it for that!
Thanks, as always!
Well, I guess this is enough for today.
Lad...
Do you happen to sell those
Western cigarettes individually?
Huh?
I'd like to buy only one off of you...
Can't do that.
It's twenty cigarettes to a box,
ten boxes to a carton,
and one carton costs 600 yen!
That's the only way they're sold!
I see...
Sorry, old man.
That's a shame. I was hoping
I could get at least one cigarette...
Fine, here!
You'll sell me one?
I told you, I only sell 'em
by the carton for 600 yen!
These ones are mine.
Have one if you want.
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga, Chandy10
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10, Ryuga
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
That's nice. Truly nice...
Later, old man.
Buy a full carton next time, all right?
Tell me, where do you live?
I'll want to have one more before I die.
Could you give me your address?
So you really went and told
the old man where you lived?
Yeah...
I thought about lying to him
and making something up...
But, I dunno why, it felt like he'd
be able to see right through my lies...
Wow...
That's one impressive old man,
getting you to tell the truth like that...
What's that supposed to mean?!
Come to think of it,
I don't know where you live either...
Don't worry about it! Someday
I'll invite you to my huge mansion!
"Marutaka Rice Shop"
I can't even invite
girls to a two-mat room...
Starting to run low...
All right! Guess I'll go see
Lilly tomorrow and stock up--!
N-Not again...
America?!
Yes. He was given orders to return home...
So he asked me if I would live with him.
Wow! That's great!
Good for you, Lilly! That's so great!
Oh...!
It's just, if we go, then your business...
It'll be a lot harder to stock up on items...
Don't worry about it!
A guy like me can survive
doing any kind of business!
Besides, I can't stay in
the black market forever!
So, when do you leave for America?
Next month.
He's going to leave first
and get everything in order
so I can move to America.
Then you'll be here alone until then?
Yes.
In that case,
I'll come visit you once in a while!
I'll bring Mario and the other, too!
We can even live here as
your bodyguards if you want!
Mario and Soldier might be
able to, but you, a bodyguard?
You just don't know how strong I really am!
I don't care to find out, either.
What?!
It's gonna be lonely without you.
If you ever miss me,
you can come over too.
--To America...
--America?
Even he was talking about how
you'd be great at your
business wherever you go!
Please... look after Lilly...
I will!
In America, drums are beat while
trumpets and saxophones blare.
In America, jumbo-sized refrigerators
are filled with meat and ice cream,
and streamlined cars speed down the streets.
Turtle hadn't forgotten his grudge from
losing his family to an atomic blast,
but in his eyes,
the land across the ocean
was a completely different
world, a world of dreams...
I gotta earn as much as I can now!
What move will he unleash next?
Oh, there it is!
Oh, he's at it again!
What's going on...?
What's happening to my body?
Dad!
Mom!
Tae!
Where did... Where did everyone go?
I don't want to be all alone...
Isn't there... Isn't there anyone here?!
I guess... I better get... to work..
Is that... the reason why...?
Yeah, right. It couldn't be.
I'm just tired, that's all...
A flash of light and a loud boom
and suddenly it was all gone--
his mom, his dad, his sister,
his house, his school...
However hard he tries to fight it,
each time he feels ill
he remembers that
hell from thirteen years ago...
You need something?
Are you Noboru Maeda?
Yeah, why?
Mr. Sugi is asking for you.
Mr. Sugi? Who's that?
Oh, what a surprise! You've never
heard of Mr. Sugi, the 1% lender?
--1% lender?
--Well, never mind.
It's up to you to come or not.
I was only asked to find you.
Though, to be honest, I've never
seen anyone foolish enough
to turn down an invitation of his...
"Milonga"
I'll be going now.
What in the...?
That old man...!
I'm sorry, Mr. Sugi. I can only
pay you the interest today.
Oh, that's perfectly fine with me.
I'm glad to see you every day.
Umm, I'd like to borrow about 1,000 yen...
Yes, of course.
What a let-down. You're actually
just a cheap moneylender...
Bartender! Some coffee
for me and this old man!
Right, coffee.
It's 50 yen for a cup of coffee, you know.
Treating someone to 50 yen
is the same as lending
5,000 yen to someone else.
Tell me, are you that rich?
I have something I want to show you.
Come with me.
I became a 1% lender
right after the war ended
and had this house built two years ago.
You can't be serious, old man...
In only ten years of being
a cheap moneylender?!
I'll pay 3,000 yen a month.
What do you say?
Won't you help me with my work?
Huh?! For only 3,000 yen?!
Normally, I would actually
ask you to pay a teaching fee...
That stern-faced military officer
has a good side to him too!
Yeah, that's for sure.
Hey! We're out of beer!
Yes, yes, we're coming!
Sorry, for the wait.
Tell me, Noboru...
Have you figured out what you'll do next?
Yep! I've already decided!
I'm gonna be a moneylender!
Huh?! A moneylender?!
Yeah! A moneylender helps
people who're having problems!
Wait, does this have to do with
that old man from the other day?
You could say that.
That old guy is a 1% moneylender.
But he's not like a regular moneylender;
he'll only lend up to
3,000 yen per customer
and he charges 1% interest per day.
1%? So if someone borrows
1,000 yen, it's 10 yen per day?
Yep. It makes it easy for people
to borrow money and pay it back.
It makes it easier to handle
emergencies that come up!
On top of that, he doesn't
make you sign any IOUs!
Really?!
He only makes you promise one thing.
Are you sure you don't need an IOU?
Yes. It doesn't matter to me
what sort of background you have.
I only ask that you
promise me one thing.
I want you to come every day,
without fail, with that day's interest!
I want to see your face every day.
...Is what he says.
Wow! What a strange old man...!
So, you decided
to help with his business?
Yep.
Working under other
people isn't really my thing
but somehow I felt like
it'd be no problem with him.
Money-lending might actually
be a pretty good match for you...
Yeah!
You'll make money by the thimble-load!
Why, you...!
What do you mean by that?!
"I can't ridicule a 1% profit.
If it took that old man
ten years to build that mansion,
then I'll build a hotel in twenty!"
Turtle was the smallest of them all,
but answered with twice
as much pride as the others.
We should start cleaning up.
Could you wake them up, Meg?
Okay.
Who are you people?
No, what are you people doing here?!
This house is supposed to be vacant!
Don't be silly! This is the officer's house!
His contract ended last week.
Huh?!
This is this lieutenant’s
residence as of today.
You will leave immediately!
Hold on...
There must be some sort of mistake...
--Sir, is she...?
--Yeah, it seems so.
You still don't get it?
You've been had by
this officer friend of yours.
Quit lying, you asshole! He'd never--!
You got close to him after he said
he'd take you to America, didn't he?
It happens all the times at these bases.
There's no alimony to pay
so once they leave, that's it.
Stop it... Stop laughing, damn it!
But it's just so funny!
A lousy whore, seriously
thinking she could be a wife!
Talk about not knowing your place!
That's enough. There are some
things you should and shouldn't say.
You put your life at risk talking like that!
Cause any more trouble and
I'll pull the trigger...
So that's how it is after all...
That son of a bitch...
Pulling a fast one on me...
That's one hell of an old geezer...
Lilly...
I'm sorry. Mister.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble,
but as you can see, I have guests today.
I promise to leave tomorrow.
Here's for the trouble.
Take it.
Tomorrow, my ass! Leave this instant!
You're Japanese, too, aren't you?
You shouldn't harass a poor girl
who's been tricked by the Americans...
If I find you here tomorrow,
I'm turning you in to the police!
I'm sorry, everyone...
I hate to ask, but could
you help me clean up?
Come on! What's the matter, guys?
It's just...
What are you going to do now?!
I'm not an idiot.
I thought this might happen,
so I swiped enough money from him
to go into business for myself!
You mean...
you have a secret stash?
Are you serious?
I never trusted that
old fart from the very start!
What’s the matter, Lilly?
He even took the money
I worked so hard to save...
Shit...!
Damn you, you asshole...!
You can use my apartment.
We start a road tour tomorrow,
so I'll be gone anyway.
Good idea...
--I'll figure something out!
--Huh?
I'll figure out some way
for Lilly to get her life back!
Turtle...
See you later...
I'm gonna drop by
there tomorrow morning.
Look after Lilly.
--Yeah...
--Yeah!
"I don't care if she's a whore or
a personal prostitute or whatever;
Lilly is part of our family!
I refuse to let her work out on a street
corner, tugging on men's sleeves!"
Turtle vowed from the bottom of his heart.
same ta manazashi
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it; its now
a far off distance
Family.
They each show outward sympathy
and put their lives on the line.