Haruka...
Haruka!
Good morning.
Breakfast is ready.
Breakfast? What is it?
What could it be?
I know! Omelets!
Huh?
You got it!
Yay!
Would you like more coffee, dear?
Uh, sure, sounds good.
Mama, Papa said he'd rather have tea.
Is that true, dear?
Well...
But still, it's amazing you knew that, Haruka.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
I win!
Okay, Yuu, you're it!
It's always us! No fair, Haruka!
Sure it's fair. It's rock-paper-scissors!
Oh, so you're a rock-paper-scissors champion!
Why don't you challenge me,
the Queen of Rock-Paper-Scissors?
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
That was lame.
It's easy.
I mean, you're all saying what you're going to throw.
Huh?
Papa! Mama! Look, look!
Grandpa bought it for me!
It's very cute, Haruka.
Yeah, you're a big girl now.
Hey! Don't call me "shorty!"
Huh?
Hey, do any of you have a boy you like?
N-No way!
Boys are so immature.
Right, Haruka?
Why are you all lying?
Huh?
Aya, don't you like Kousuke?
What?!
And Mai, you like Hajime.
And Kaoru...
Oh, Kaoru likes Kousuke, too!
Aya, you like Kousuke?!
N-No!
I don't like any boys!
Kaoru has liked him since kindergarten. Right?
I-I never said that!
I-I don't like Hajime...
He helped you up when you fell,
so that's why you like him, right?
What are you talking about?
Hey, that's great!
Hajime likes you too, Mai!
I do not!
I don't like Mai at all!
Stupid Haruka! I hate you!
Get lost, Haruka!
We're not friends anymore!
Haruka is vicious?
Yes. You see,
everything she says is untrue.
Surely not...
Some of her classmates have been hurt,
and we've received numerous parental complaints.
I'll let you take care of that.
But, dear—
Isn't raising a child the mother's job?
I've got an early start tomorrow. I'm going to bed.
Hmm, what could this be...
Your daughter is perfectly normal.
There's nothing more I can do.
What's that?! How rude!
Wait a minute!
Please, just leave!
Mama, am I sick?
No one will play with me.
Everyone's afraid of me.
They all say I'm creepy!
Dear, when are you coming home?
We need to talk about Haruka!
I told you that Haruka is your responsibility.
At any rate, I don't think I'm going to make it home from work tonight.
Dear? Dear!
Something evil has possessed my daughter!
Please, can't you exorcise it?
I'm afraid not...
I am but a simple priest.
Why?
Why is it only my child?
Mama.
Papa will come home tomorrow.
Shut up! Whose fault do you think this is?!
Grandpa, lately Mama's been drinking a lot and getting mad so easily.
And Papa won't even come home.
Mama, Papa, and my friends...
Do they all hate me?
Don't be silly.
You know that's not true.
Whoa there.
You'll stay with us all day today, right?
Sorry, Haruka.
I have to go out this evening.
I've got something to do as well.
Papa, you're going to a hotel with Akiko?
Wha—
And Mama, you're going to dinner with Mister Yoshino! No fair!
I'm going too!
What is she talking about, dear?
I-I don't know any woman by that name!
And what about you? Who the hell is this man?!
Y-You have to believe me, dear!
She's just making stuff up and...
Again? You're doing it again?!
You're horrible, Haruka!
Why are you trying so hard to ruin our lives?
Papa...
Mama...
Wait, Kumiko!
You're abandoning her too?
What will we do about Haruka?
Father.
Do you really think I give a damn about that girl?
What the hell do you think you're saying?!
Mama, wait!
I swear I'll never do anything to make you mad again!
I'll even do the cooking and cleaning!
So, Mama, please don't go!
Don't go! Don't—
Haruka!
How could you?
If only you had never been born.
Wait! Kumiko!
K-Kumiko!
...rry...
I'm sorry...
Monsters aren't welcome here!
I-I'm not...
She looked this way!
She's gonna read your mind!
That's why your parents abandoned you!
Monster!
Stop it. I'm not. I'm not a—
Liar!
I knew something was off.
You pretended to be our friend
just so you could break into our minds and laugh at us!
N-No...
You're horrible!
Stay away from us!
Let's go.
Wait! We're best friends, aren't we?
Sorry. Not anymore.
You're all alone too?
I can't hear you saying anything.
So it was you feeding that cat?
What a pain.
I took it to a shelter, so don't let me see you around here again!
Oh? You're transferring?
Good luck at your new school.
Finally we're rid of this headache.
I'm Kotoura Haruka.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, Kotoura...
This one's going to be a pain.
Sorry for being a pain.
What was that? What a freak.
Poor Manabe, having to sit next to her.
It's the same no matter where I go.
If only everyone were like this boy,
and just ignored me,
I'd be content.
Huh? Who're you?
Huh?
One morning I suddenly realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
✩Ah✩
Nothing good can come from cuddling you all the time
Cuddle,
cuddle,
cuddle
The scent of my feelings might stick
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Tell me, is this "love"?
That's a secret beyond all secrets, you know?
Yeah!
That's a secret beyond all secrets, isn't it? ♡
Kotoura and Manabe
So, Kotoura, where did you move here from?
Not that I really want to know.
I should never have become the class representative.
If you don't want to know, don't ask.
So, um, which club are you going to join?
Please don't join the tennis club.
Don't worry. I'm not interested in tennis.
Huh?
What's with her? Creepy.
Hey...
Manabe!
What's up, Moritani?
Come on. You remember my invitation.
Oh, to come to your house?
Yeah, yeah!
I refuse!
Isn't your house a karate dojo?
Not interested.
Shot down again.
She looked so disappointed.
She must really want my martial arts prowess.
She's not after your "prowess," whether it exists or not.
Huh?
I heard you, so I just blurted that out.
Sorry.
You heard me?
Wait, did I say that out loud?
Oh, God! I'm so embarrassed!
One
Weeks Later
Two
Three
Let's eat together, Kotoura.
That looks so good.
I wonder if she'd give me a bite.
If you want.
What? Really?!
Wow, thanks!
Whoa, it's good!
Did Kotoura make this herself?
I did.
That's awesome!
You really know what I'm thinking?
Just like everyone in class said!
But keep the magic tricks to a minimum, okay?
If you go overboard, you'll scare people off
and it'll be hard to make new friends.
It's none of your business. And it's not magic.
And the croquette is mine!
Hey! Don't just take things without asking!
Morning, Kotoura!
Mornin'!
Mooornin'!
Morninin'!
One, two, three, four, five...
Kotoura! Be my partner!
Hey, Manabe!
Here!
You're not getting away!
Hup! Hup! Hup!
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Kotoura! We should walk home together sometimes!
I'm going this way.
I'm going this way too!
So it seems.
Are you used to the school yet?
Are you making friends?
Come on, talk to me!
Why do you hang around me so much?
What do you mean, "why"? Of course I...
Wait, why do I?
What a dummy.
Oh, yeah! Hey, so tell me,
what's the secret to that mind reading trick you do?
It's so cool!
If I could read people's minds, I could do anything I wanted!
Idiot.
There's nothing cool about it.
You idiot.
Hey!
What do you mean, "idiot"?
You're an idiot, so I called you an idiot!
You don't know anything!
Kotoura!
I've been looking for you.
I saw you weren't in the classroom.
So this is where you were.
Hey, Kotoura!
Hey, no need to rush.
It all starts with a kiss... right?
What the heck are you thinking about?!
You really can read people's minds.
Is it ESP?
Yes, it is. You get it now?
If you don't want me hearing your thoughts,
stay away from me.
But...
That means...
I can't think about anything dirty!
This is bad!
ESP's gonna be the end of me!
No man can endure the torment of controlling his lust!
You're... not scared?
I'm petrified!
You're gonna treat me like a total pervert!
I'm so tired.
What was that all about?
That Manabe.
I've never met such a weirdo.
No.
I mustn't.
Hey, if it isn't Kotoura!
Hey there!
That looks heavy.
I'll carry it.
And you want something perverted in return, right?
No way!
Honest.
Your confidence is less than overwhelming.
Come on, come on, just hand it over.
Are these ingredients for dinner?
It's great you help out at home.
I live alone.
Huh?
It's green.
Oh, yeah.
Are you all right?
Ho-Holy shit!
I read the driver's mind.
He simply didn't care about the red light.
Kotoura...
You must get it by now.
I'm just an intrusive, creepy, mind-reading mon—
Thanks.
Hey, you're hurt!
I-It's no big deal.
Yes, it is!
Is your house near here?
There. That'll do it.
Th-Thanks.
So you really do live alone.
Where do your parents live?
I can't control my power.
My whole life, I've heard thoughts
without really understanding them,
so I've hurt people.
Kotoura...
I've ruined everything.
All I can do is make sure no one gets close to me.
So that's why at school, you...
Why are you trying to get close to me?!
Stop it! Leave me alone!
You'll only end up getting hurt!
You seriously want to be isolated?
You don't want to "hurt people"?
What a load of bull! You're the one who's hurting!
I'm doing the only thing I can do!
Of course I don't like being alone!
Of course I don't want to hurt or be hurt!
But there's nothing more horrible...
more utterly horrible...
than being abandoned by the people I love!
That's why I'm better off just being alone.
Look, Kotoura.
Whether you can read minds or not,
people who want to leave are going to leave.
But not everyone is like that.
So let's try this, okay?
I'll stay with you.
No matter what happens, I won't leave.
How about it?
You... mean it?
Yup, I mean it.
Actually, as far as I'm concerned, we're already friends.
Hey! Don't cry!
I'm not crying.
No, you totally are.
What the heck are you thinking about at a time like this?!
Uh... W-Well...
Seeing a girl crying is kind of a turn-on, you know?
Y-You freak! Dirty lecher!
Who're you calling a lecher?
Damn it! Betrayed by my own insatiable manliness!
Glad to know you, Kotoura.
Likewise, Manabe.
How do you stand again when something trips you up?
Can truth be found by thinking about the days to come?
We all come into this world alone when we are born,
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us the flower of hope may bloom,
we start our days together here
We start our days together here
What's wrong, Kotoura? Why the long face?
There's a ton of people on the other side of the TV thinking dirty thoughts.
What'd you say?!
Kotoura is only allowed to be the star of my fantasies!
Episode 2
The First......
Silence, lecher.