Please excuse me from guard duty, Ms. McCunnen.
I have an important matter to attend to.
What if I said...
there's an even more important matter?
What is it?
Don't tell me...
That's right. This is your passport.
Your true self... your past is in this.
Sudden Change
Ein...
Be careful.
I didn't know...
How could I know...
the fate that was about to unfold.
What future lied ahead?
It's okay to take a look at it. Are you afraid of getting your past back?
I've been killing people as ordered by the organization.
Yes. You've been wonderfully helpful.
But I was able to do so precisely because I have no past nor memories.
You just followed orders, like a machine, feeling no guilt.
If you get back your true self, you may be tormented by guilt.
You're afraid of that, aren't you...
But that's exactly why I want you to recover your true self... your own will...
My will...
Distance: 249 yards. Intermittent gusts from the south.
Restore your true self. And then, accept yourself... as Zwei.
How self-centered...
It's also because of you that I have blood on my hands.
And now you...
It's a revolution.
Our organization will soon be reborn. When that happens...
Zwei... I want you.
But no matter how capable you are,
I don't need a puppet who just follows orders.
What I want is a comrade... a subordinate I can trust.
Someone who'd follow me of his own free will.
If I come to know my past...
I'm not sure if I can continue to be myself.
If that happens...
My job is to back up the assault.
Those people I see now are my targets.
Tsk! Who are those guys!?
The shipment is...!
A sniper!
We did it!
It's too early to celebrate, bro.
Just step on it!
Yes sir!
To trap us here... You sure got balls.
Read the name out loud.
Azuma...
Reiji...
So you remember now.
That's right... I... was traveling.
And...
I killed many... many... with my own hands.
I just... wanted to live.
I wish I hadn't remembered it.
I told you... that I don't need a mere puppet, didn't I?
Wake up from your dream. You'll become you again.
Your past, your guilt... Accept it all and face your own will.
Reiji Azuma...
Phantom!?
That damn Scythe!
What do you want from me?
Come with me, Reiji... of your own free will.
There's someone right here who needs your help.
This is where you belong.
If you're willing to have more blood on your hands
and bear mortal sins with me,
I'll promise to give you a wonderful future.
However, I'm not forcing this on you.
You can pick the other choice.
The other choice?
The other choice... That is...
Going back to Japan?
If that's what you wish,
I'll make a special case for you.
You may doubt it, but I'm serious.
I'll really let you go back to your homeland...
since what I want is a subordinate who has his own will.
You idiot! Why the hell are you shooting your own people?
I don't care if Scythe ordered you to do this. Stop being his puppet!
You can't escape! Think about it carefully!
That snake is just using you as a sacrificial pawn anyway.
Going... back to Japan...
It's a big decision for you.
I'll give you some time alone... to think about it.
This is the Azuma residence.
Hello?
There's no way I could go back.
Find her!
That damn Scythe. He's got some nerve.
Did you hear how many she killed?
We'll give him a fitting payback.
Of course... Phantom, too.
Ein... Why!?
Did you come to kill me?
What are you talking about?
You don't know anything? Then go back to the organization immediately.
If it's just you, they might still...
Ein!
Ein...
It's me.
There was a sudden change. Scythe betrayed the organization.
He used Phantom to attack Inferno's shipment.
What!?
He went into hiding immediately. Phantom is also on the run.
But she was shot by Lizzie.
The organization is putting all its resources into hunting them down.
We still haven't found either of them.
They suspect that you betrayed them as well, but I can prove where you were.
You no longer have time to think.
Make a decision quickly...
whether you'll come to me... or...
But let me tell you one thing.
Scythe and Phantom are our enemy.
If you take their side, the organization will...
It won't stop bleeding. The bullet didn't go through. I gotta take her to a doctor.
No. The organization is probably checking all the hospitals.
There's no other option.
Hang in there... Ein.
We blocked all the escape routes. They're completely caged birds.
They can't escape from the organization...
not even Phantom.
Now the question is who'll hunt down the prey.
Don't die.
Ein...
With all these people, you still can't find them!?
Freeway? Block it!
Dammit! If only I had finished her then...
Clo, where is he?
You mean Zwei?
He's also Scythe's pet dog. It's very possible that he'll take their side.
If that happens, Lizzie...
I want you to...
take care of him.
Ein...
Actually, Ein...
Ms. McCunnen gave me a passport tonight... my passport...
And that brought back all my memories.
My hometown... My family...
I had a place to go back to.
I remembered my name, too.
My name is Reiji. Reiji Azuma.
It's a lot better than the boring name Zwei, don't you think?
But I wonder why...
I'm not really happy.
I'm no longer who I used to be.
I'm someone who shouldn't go back there.
Is going back to the organization my only choice?
Ein... Let's go back together.
Scythe and Phantom are our enemy.
If you take their side, the organization will...
kill you.
No.
If Ein goes back, she'll be...
Then...
I'll leave her here...
and go back by myself?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Never mind.
Wind...
Blue, white and green.
That's all there is in that place. There's nothing else.
But it's dazzlingly bright there
and there's a wind blowing. A strong wind...
Ein...
Be careful.
You too...
We have no names. We were given only numbers.
We were just used like pawns and now we've been cast aside.
To hell with it... To hell with...
such a meaningless way of life.
Ein...
Ein... I'm the only one... who can protect you.
I won't abandon you. I'll never let the organization take you.
Let's escape together... from this town...
from Inferno!
Reiji...
Let's go, Ein... together!
Next episode
Name
I'll give you a new name.
Not Phantom or some number... It'll be your real name.