Everyone, like, Kaleido
Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star, please
keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can. 'Kay?
Let's go!
Well, well, well.
Have you ever made up your
mind about something?
Many things have happened in my 16-year life.
I've tried lots of hard things.
But this time I'm earnest. I'm serious.
I made up my mind in a super serious mode.
I'm going to take the challenge
for everyone's future!
For everyone's future! For everyone's future!
Dare mo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Dokoka ni aru
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja nai
Saigo made yareru to ittetane
Kitto tsuyogatte itanda
Itsudatte muchabakka de zutto karamawari de
Dakedo anata dake ga soba ni ita
Daremo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Arukidaseru
Koko kara nanika ga hajimaru
Shinjite itai
Mada minu hikari yakusoku
no basho e to tsuzuite yuku
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja naisa
What?
Hmm? What? What?
Can you see me?
"The Legendary Amazing Maneuver."
Wait, Sora.
What's wrong with you?
So you can see him too, right?
What?
I'm talking about Fool...
Fool?
My name is Fool.
I am the spirit of the stage.
Uh...
As I expected, Layla's so calm.
Oh, no...
So did I lose my mind, is that it?
I think he's the one who lost his mind.
What?!
But, Miss Layla,
you couldn't see him before.
Layla was chosen for the stage just now.
It is proof that you can attempt
the legendary great maneuver.
The legendary great maneuver?
It was tried once, a long time ago.
After that, no one has successfully
performed that maneuver.
One person was frightened.
Another tried it recklessly
and lost his life.
If you're going to attempt that maneuver,
you will be the second pair
to try from Kaleido Stage.
The second pair?
In order to try the legendary great maneuver,
it needs two stars.
What happened to the two who
tried before and failed?
They died.
One partner could not see me,
but the other one told me a lie and
made him pretend he could see me.
But, Miss Layla can see you.
So please tell me, Fool.
What kind of maneuver is this
"legendary great maneuver"?
I cannot tell you yet.
What?
Until both of you are
qualified for that maneuver.
Qualified?
When is that? How can we be qualified?
Even I don't know that.
It could be tomorrow,
it could be ten years from now.
Don't be so mean. Just tell us now.
If you try that maneuver now...
An avatar of Death...
I'm afraid at least one of you will die.
But I...
I think I can do it if
it's with you, Miss Layla!
Let me think about it.
What?
Ouch!
Miss Layla, I will do my best!
Miss Layla...
Am I not good enough for you?
As we thought, the masked
star was Miss Layla.
Yes.
Since we have a time difference,
if she leaves London first
thing in the morning,
she can be here by noon.
I want to try the legendary great
maneuver with Miss Layla by any means.
The legendary great maneuver?
What's that?
Even I don't know what it is,
but I think I can do any kind of
maneuver if I do it with Miss Layla.
But...
Hi, everyone, please come
close and take a look!
Like, the best show in history,
kinda, is going to start!
C'mon, c'mon!
Anyway, did you hear?
They found out that the
masked star was Miss Layla.
I'd, you know, rather work with them.
After all, I realized that I want
to appear on stage with Miss Layla.
Don't you think it's like,
too late to realize that?
Of course, I feel the same, but...
The small audience must have something to do
with the fact that we don't have Miss Layla.
It has to be.
If you don't like it here, you can leave.
Both of you are fired.
What?
Oh, well.
It's, like, probably better for us.
It's Yuri.
Kaleido Stage's...
Not only that...
What? That's...
--Layla!
I didn't think you'd come.
I heard she'll appear onscreen again.
How is the movie shoot?
Finished without a hitch.
That's good.
So what did you want to talk about?
I want you to come back, Layla.
I want to appear on stage with you again.
You're the only partner I have.
My current partner is Sora.
I may attempt the legendary
great maneuver with Sora.
You're going to attempt the legendary
great maneuver with Sora?!
There is no way you can do that.
Absolutely not!
Yuri...
And if you're going to do it,
then I'll do it with you!
You're not qualified.
Really...
When I saw the Kaleido
Stage for the first time,
it was truly like a dream.
I wished I could also appear on that stage.
After I started grade school,
and when I started learning
gymnastics, I thought it was fun.
For the first time in my life,
I learned how good applause made me feel.
I would practice very hard every day
on a maneuver that I couldn't do.
And when I was finally able to
do it, when I received applause,
I'd feel so happy, I would tremble.
When I got applause on
stage for the first time,
it really made me happy.
That's why I want to try
even more amazing maneuvers.
That's why I want to perform
even more amazing performances.
I want to show them.
I want them to see it.
And I want to perform on
that stage with Miss Layla.
The legendary great maneuver?
I'm sure Kalos knows something.
About people who took the challenge
before or something like that...
Okay...
but I don't know if he's
willing to talk about it.
He's never said anything
about it to anybody before.
Even if the challengers are Sora and myself?
Well, if it's the two of
you, it should be all right.
I'll give you Kalos's contact information.
Oh, damn! I wasn't watching!
Master, please do it again!
Can you wait for a second, Layla?
Yes.
You sure work hard every day, Sora.
Well, I have no choice but to practice.
So I will be accepted
as Miss Layla's partner.
Sora, is this true?
What?
"Layla Hamilton and Sora Naegino
return to their old home, Kaleido Stage,
to risk their lives attempting
the legendary great maneuver."
Wow...
It says next month.
You must be kidding.
Who are you?
Excuse me,
that announcement about the legendary great
maneuver being performed at Kaleido Stage...
Those tickets are already sold out.
What?
Excuse me, Miss!
I'm the one performing in that show!
What?
Good morning, Sora.
Mr. Yuri...
Those tickets are completely sold out.
If you need them, I'll prepare
reserved seats for invited guests.
So just let me know the number of people...
How do you know about the
legendary great maneuver?
I heard it from Layla.
What?
Then Miss Layla agreed to challenge the
legendary great maneuver! Is that right?
Yuri announced it without consulting us.
Do you want to make laughingstocks out of us?
I'm just paying my respects to those who
are going to try a very difficult maneuver,
and I decided to offer the stage.
If you want to back out of
this, you should do it now.
You can quit anytime.
All sold tickets are non-refundable.
The only people who lose
money are the audience.
You can't!
We're not going to cancel.
But we have a condition of our own.
A condition?
If we succeed in performing
the legendary great maneuver,
I want you to return Kaleido Stage to us!
All right.
I'm counting on you.
I expect you to perfect the
maneuver without a hitch.
Miss Layla!
I've made up my mind too.
Sora, no matter what happens,
I'm going to perfect the legendary
great maneuver with you.
And we're going to make sure to show that
maneuver to the audience on this stage.
Yes.
Oh, but if we don't know
what kind of maneuver it is,
we don't know how we should practice.
Kalos knows how we should practice.
Boss does?
He used to watch the two
previous challengers practice.
He said if we are serious about doing
this, come to the Grand Canyon.
He said he's going to give
us special training there.
You're going, right, Sora?
Of course I'm going!
Is he really going to give
us Kaleido Stage back?
Yes.
For everyone's sake, I'm going to
perfect that maneuver by all means.
And I'm going to get back our Kaleido Stage!
So Boss is coaching...
Good luck, Sora!
Here, Jonathan. You cheer for her too!
We will go see your performance.
I kept hounding them for tickets,
and I already got some.
I'm going with you!
What?
I'll also participate
as your special trainer.
Ken...
Me too.
Then I'm going too!
Why don't we all go together?
Yeah!
That's impossible!
So Boss knows what kind of maneuver
that the legendary great maneuver is.
Don't forget.
Finding out what it is without
being qualified means...
I know.
You want to say "It's dangerous."
We're going to help you.
Aren't you kinda glad?
Well...
Sora...
I'm going to do my best to support you.
But...
...if the legendary great maneuver
is really that dangerous,
I'm going to stop you.
Ken...
Because I don't want to lose you, Sora.
Welcome.
It's been awhile.
Boss...
Are you ready?
I have a hunch something bad will happen.
What?
I e-mailed everybody who used
to work for Kaleido Stage,
and asked them about the maneuver.
They told me that there were people who
tried that maneuver ten years ago, and...
And what happened?
They died.
I wonder, could that be...
Like, cook this one next.
Can you taste this?
Well?
Hmm... It, like, doesn't taste very good.
Then why don't you help me?
Because I'm not, like, really
good at stuff like this.
Once you finish that,
do 100 one-arm chin-ups.
No rest!
Sora...
Oh, my...
Jump.
What?!
So today's training is finished.
Not yet!
Sora, do 100 bicep curls
with your right hand.
Do it!
Yes, Sir.
Do you want me to cut it for you?
Thank you, but I'll be okay.
I'll keep at it, on my own.
Sora...
What?
No way...
A maneuver like that can't be possible...
In order to perfect the maneuver,
he said that he needed absolute confidence.
Who is "he"?
This doesn't just apply to those two.
It also applies to everybody around them.
If you can trust both Sora and Layla,
never show your uncertainty or
be soft on them until the end.
If you cannot trust them, you
should leave here right now.
Because you will get in their way.
And also,
don't tell Sora what the
legendary great maneuver is.
We don't have that right.
Does it hurt?
But please bear it.
I have to make sure to loosen
your muscles very well.
Tomorrow, we'll have an interval by
letting you do some light workouts,
and then the day after tomorrow...
Ken...
I wonder if I can endure this
kind of training till the end.
I wonder if I'm capable of doing
the legendary great maneuver.
Sora is growing uncertain.
Good.
We've been doing the same
training for over a week.
Don't complain.
You have no choice but to do it.
Ken...
You sound like a different person.
You too, Sora. Don't be so soft.
You're the one who told me you're going
to do the legendary great maneuver.
That's true.
Layla, you've completed the first level.
You're going to start training
using a rope starting tomorrow.
Yes!
Sora, come here.
Yes.
The iron ball hanging at the end of that wire
weighs almost the same as Layla.
Catch this using only your
right arm and push it back.
If you can't do this,
you can't be Layla's partner.
Can you do it?
Yes, I will.
If you can trust both Sora and Layla,
never show your uncertainty or
be soft on them until the end.
Please wait for a second.
What?
Please let me handle this training.
Ken...
Are you capable of doing this?
Yes.
Are you ready, Sora?
One more time!
C'mon!
Sora, stand up!
Next!
This is nothing...
By any means...
By any means, I'm going to do the legendary
great maneuver with Miss Layla.
Sora, stand up!
Unless you can do this, you can't
perfect the legendary great maneuver!
Yes...
What kind of maneuver is the
legendary great maneuver?
Without knowing what kind of maneuver it is,
I wonder if I can keep going till the end.
Fool!
Fool, aren't you here?
Fool, tell me.
No, I can't.
But...
I told you before.
When both of you are qualified
to do that maneuver,
I will tell you everything.
So I'm not good enough yet?
I'm not? I'm not?
"Next Kaleido Star"
Can you tell me with confidence
that you're Layla's partner?
And so, I'm training so hard, but...
This is ridiculous!
Sora is going to destroy herself!
I will not look away. I don't
want to give up, but...
I feel like crying. I feel like running away.
Miss Layla, please say something!
Please! Please!
Next time on Kaleido Star, "The Amazing
Intensive Training Continues."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
Boku wa koko ni iru sora to
michi no aida de mukai kaze
Soshite mae o muiteiru mou nido
to kanashimi ga furanai youni to
Ano kabe o koete kokomade kitanda
Nigedashitaku naru koto wa nando mo aru
Dakedo kokoni irunara taishite bibitte inai
Kakinaguri no uta "hajimekara yareba iisa"
Umaku kakenakute boku wa waratte iru