That evening I saw my mother in town.
She was wearing her priestess garb as always,
walking slowly in the sunset
as if she were simply wandering around.
The excitement I felt from seeing her
after such a long time rushed out
and before I could question it,
I just couldn't help talking to her.
But maybe my mother didn't hear my voice.
...mother...
She kept walking wherever she was heading
without even looking back.
I hurried after my mother and
turned the corner right behind her.
...mother...
But... there was no one there.
Did I have the wrong person?
It had to be.
There's no way my mother
would be here anyway.
...mother...
Because my mother is no longer...
Right then, as the streetlight flickered,
I saw my mother's back in the
blue white fluorescent light.
...mother...
The sound of the rod in her hand echoed
and the faint scent of medicine
and sweet herbs hung in the air.
That's the scent of my mother that I remember.
...mother...
My mother appeared and disappeared
as the light flickered.
...mother...
I followed her, trying to stop her,
but every time the light flickered,
she appeared further and further away.
...mother...
I was doing my best to catch up,
but I just couldn't.
My mother was walking slowly,
...mother...
but every time the light flickered
she appeared further and further away.
The fear that I may not see her again
drove me to scream her name.
...mother...
Right then my mother turned towards me.
At that very moment a bright light flashed.
That must've triggered the filament to break.
The streetlight went out and my mother
disappeared into the darkness.
...mother...
I couldn't understand what happened
and just stood there.
My beloved mother, whom I've so missed,
and had been dying to see again,
...mother...
was now right in front of me.
At the same time I knew it was
simply impossible,
because my mother was no longer...
Kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
Watashi no kisetsu tachi
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
Nemuri wo yusaburu uta
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
Kokoro wo enjiru niwa
Zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otonaja nai
Deatta kouya no hana
Kowakute yasashikute
Fureta shunkan ni diorama datte hontou ni naru
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta watashino miraichizu
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
Oikakete kuru ashita wo kowasu
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 6                                              Ganbaranai
"MY PARENTS ARE THE ONLY PEOPLE
THAT I'M TROUBLING"
Hey, Kagami.
Kagami!
Yawn...
What is it? It's my precious naptime right now.
Please don't interrupt.
Kagami, listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
I saw my mother yesterday.
Give me a break.
Yesterday...
...I saw my mother.
Are you stupid or what? Are you dying?
You don't have to literally give me a break.
Anyway, I don't have time to deal with nonsense like that.
Stop interrupting my sleep.
Okay then, Kagami, come shopping
with me after school.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I want a bicycle, but have no idea which one I should get.
You're not making any sense right now.
I'm not following you at all.
I can't go asking my brother
to give me a bike ride every day.
Two people are not allowed to ride together anyway.
So what?
Kagami, come to the store and pick one with me.
I'm sorry, but I need to take Meat
to her checkup today.
Meat?
Yes! She's a white, fluffy, squishy and lovable creature!
If I leave her alone, she'll die of loneliness,
so I need to be with her.
I'm the same way, too!
No means no.
It's not a bad idea to venture out
by yourself for a change.
You're so heartless, Kagami.
A rabbit and I are on the same level?
Unbelievable.
Mother...?
I saw my mother on the way home after school.
What's the matter, Sasami? Shopping?
What? Oh, yeah.
What are you buying?
Well, um, a bicycle.
I see. To ride to school...
You should get one with a basket like that.
No, that's not cute!
A proper Tsukuyomi Priestess has no need for cuteness.
The desire to seek comfort and relief in physical objects
turns into weakness and lowers your defenses.
Emotions of right and wrong also cloud one's judgment
when running the world righteously.
I don't have many memories about my mother,
but what I do have I remember vividly.
How I learned my techniques from her
and practiced with her.
...many memories about my mother,
but what I do have I remember vividly.
I was always with my mother when I was little.
What's the matter, Sasami?
Oh, it's nothing.
What is this annoying flashing object?
Oh, this? You control these buttons
and move the crane.
Then you catch stuffed dolls with it. Do you want to try it?
Puppets are evil.
It's easy to insert a soul into
those that look like a child in particular.
They're cursed items set up by the enemy.
Yes!
Hey, listen to me when I'm talking to you!
Darn! It's hard...
Let your mother handle it.
No, you can't do that!
A proper Tsukuyomi priestess prefers expedience.
But it's against the rules!
The store clerks are staring at us!
Then I'm going to enspell the doll and make it move.
Creepy!
It fell.
Is it okay to get it?
I give you permission.
A Tsukuyomi priestess' permission is that of the gods'-
Crap! The store clerks are coming this way!
Let's go, Mother!
A Tsukuyomi priestess' permission is that of the gods'-
Don't take off all of a sudden!
I'm not good in physical matters!
...mother...
My mother was born sickly, so she often stayed in bed.
I used to take care of her a lot, too.
Jeez! We almost got arrested for that!
This Tsukuyomi priestess can't be intimidated
by law enforcement so easily.
Your mother needs to take a break.
Mother, you're physically weaker than me.
That's a real problem as a human.
I see no benefit in physical ability!
Just wait here for a second.
Here.
I feel something unsettling coming from it. What is that?
Ice cream. It's a type of cold sweets.
Consuming articles of taste is evil. Any pleasure is-
Just have it. Here.
Cold!
Hey, my mother just made a cute noise!
Your mother is always cute.
This isn't bad.
LAPTOPS BY MANUFACTURER
-All styles and functionalities just for you-
Mother, do you have a computer?
It's convenient to have one.
A proper Tsukuyomi priestess
finds no value in convenience.
Mother, buy me this!
I'll not. Material desire is evil.
But my Big Brother would have
no problem buying it for me.
He's out of the question.
Don't rely on him. Your mind will rot.
I'll pick clothes for you. I bet you get tired
of wearing the priestess' uniform all the time.
I'm a priestess so wearing the
priestess' vestment is natural to me.
I have no need for worldly clothes.
That was fun!
Mother, do you have more time?
Can we eat dinner together?
You used to be a helpless little child,
but now listen to you.
Is there anything you want to eat?
No.
More importantly, Sasami,
I need to talk to you about something-
How about Italian? I bet you've never had it.
Wait, Sasami. I said wait.
I still harbor those memories of my
mother every now and then.
Tanko Animal Clinic
Look! There are so many animals!
There are so many fluffy things! Is this Heaven or what?
Come on, Meat! This is the doctor's office.
It's not going to be scary, so you can be calm.
Whoa! To think you'd treat a bunny like a baby,
you know what you're doing, huh, Kagami?
That's my sister!
You're irritating. You should go die already.
That fluffy thing is wearing clothes.
OUTFITS FOR BUNNIES
This has to be a sign from Heaven
that I should cuddle with Meat!
I don't think so.
So, Meat! What do you think about this?
She's not going anywhere for a while...
Sasami...
What?
Who feeds you here?
Usually my big brother does.
Don't worry. It's easy, so watch me. Like this...
More importantly, Sasami, I need to talk to you.
Oh?
What?
That evening I saw my mother in town.
You said earlier that you had fun, remember?
Sasami, that's what a mother would want for you.
Now that I think about it, we'd never
shared time as parent and child before;
shopping or talking about things and such.
I was a poor mother.
I'm sorry, Sasami.
Don't be...
Don't apologize, Mother.
I'm just happy that we're able to spend time together,
even if just for a little while.
Doing stuff like this has been my dream.
That evening I saw my mother in town.
She was wearing her priestess garb as always,
walking slowly in the sunset
as if she were simply wandering around.
I made you sad.
It's okay; I always knew that you were trying your best
to raise me to be a good successor
when you were always busy with your duty.
Sasami...
That must've triggered the filament to break.
The streetlight went out and my mother
disappeared into the darkness.
I couldn't understand what happened
and just stood there.
My beloved mother, whom I've so missed,
and had been dying to see again,
was now right in front of me.
At the same time...
Thank you. I really mean it.
I love you, Mother.
That must've triggered the filament to break.
The streetlight went out and my mother
disappeared into the darkness.
I couldn't understand what happened
and just stood there.
My beloved mother, whom I've so missed,
and had been dying to see again,
was now right in front of me.
At the same time I knew it was simply impossible, because...
And because of that I have something I need to tell you.
What's that?
because you're already...
Because...
you're...
because you're already...
already...
...dead.
I'm dead, you say?
Sasami...
...you thought that I didn't know that?
What?
Of course I'm dead.
Mother, so that means...
I may look decent because of the Alteration,
but my body is actually a corpse.
It's definitely decaying, but the people
around me simply can't tell.
This is my true form.
Everyone dies.
The souls of the dead slide down the slope
to the spirit realms and head to the Underworld.
There is no reincarnation. There is no resurrection, either.
That's the rule.
However, there is a way out.
Before I ate of the fruit of Yomi, the Land of the Dead,
in other words, before I joined the world of the Dead,
I negotiated with the King of Underworld.
Our interests were the same,
so he let me return to this world
until my body rots away completely.
Why did you do that?
Resurrection is such a horrid thing,
even the God of Creation failed!
Do you want to know why, Sasami?
I was ready to depart; I was satisfied.
But I saw how you were living your life of leisure,
having run away from the shrine,
abandoning your duty as a Tsukuyomi Priestess!
I didn't want to stay dead anymore.
I know I asked you to take care of this world.
You nodded and even said
"You can count on me, Mother."
But you broke your promise.
I'll not blame you for that because
you're not the only one who sinned.
It was also my sin for passing before all the effort
of your training bore fruit... before you matured...
Go back to Tsukuyomi Shrine, Sasami.
There you can train again.
The shrine's been destroyed.
I already know that.
The physical building isn't what's important.
It is sufficient that you have a place where
you can train quietly, away from this ridiculous world.
Let's go.
No!
I'm not going back!
What point is there in maintaining a world
so convenient for humans
while you struggle so much?
I'm not a priestess of the Tsukuyomi!
Don't get the wrong idea, Sasami.
No one is asking you how YOU feel here.
This is for Humanity!
Do you mean to tell me your happiness,
freedom and pleasure
are worth more than the future of Humankind?!
Your life isn't the only one borne on your shoulders!
This is not just your world. It's more enormous and noble!
So stop being so selfish!
No...
Stop being a baby, you fool!
Grow up already!
Your existence is worthless
if you're not a Tsukuyomi priestess!
Living your life aimlessly, neglecting your duty
and idling your time away is practically a crime!
Why can't you understand that?!
Pampering you so much was a grave mistake,
you good-for-nothing daughter!
Hey, don't get too excited now, Mother.
How about a parent-teacher-student meeting, Mother?
Tsurugi...
I'd heard about it, but this is my first time
actually seeing it...
...a person resurrected from the Underworld.
Stop speaking like a human.
You're nothing but an evil god.
Did you talk Sasami into this?
With your smile and sweet words?
I'm no evil god! YOU'RE the monster
who came back from death!
No human; not even a god should return from the dead!
That's a rule of this world set by the Old Man himself!
It's because life is finite that
you can live your life without regret.
I admit that I'm a lazy god who's abandoned the duty
to manage this world myself,
but I can't ignore a serious violation of the rules like this!
So I'm gonna fix that!
No one talked Sasami into it!
She chose on her own to live her life.
You died and left her alone all this time.
It's too late for you to act like her mother now!
Get your ass on the super express
back to the Underworld!
She underestimates me, does she?
I'm a Tsukuyomi priestess, the pinnacle of the
Tsukuyomi Shrine, who can exorcise any apparition!
Banishing evil gods is our specialty!
I'm no evil god!
Just as the myth says, you're no good at fighting,
are you, Sun God?
Tsurugi!
Big Sister!
Big Sister Tsurugi!
Stay away!
She's strong! You two are no match for her!
Will you stop taking it all on yourself?
Remember you're an empty shell
that can't exert your true power.
Shut up!
Not speaking out against an abusive parent
is a teacher's disgrace.
You lot are a bunch of nonchalant people.
The gods of this country are too laidback.
I can't afford to leave this country to the likes of you.
Progress and prosperity of this world
requires that it is managed by humans.
All is for the world and for Humanity.
Educating Sasami and making sure that she serves as a
Tsukuyomi priestess are the last duties I must carry out.
I have no grudge against you,
but if you attempt to interfere...
...death will come to you.
I'm not going to the Underworld!
There's someone I don't like down there!
What?
I expect nothing less from the Divine Sword
Ame no Murakumo.
Note: Ame no Murakumo, later renamed Kusanagi ("Grass Cutter"),
was given to the grandson of Amaterasu with the Yata no Kagami Mirror.
What an impressive force.
But at the end of the day,
it's nothing but a defensive sword.
A grass cutter, used solely for defense,
simply lacks the malice required to defeat others!
Don't tell me that's...!
It once defeated the serpent Yamata no Orochi
and fell broken to its curse,
but it's since been sharpened in the afterworld...
The Dark Sword, Ame no Habakiri!
Note: Ame no Habakiri ("Slash of Heavenly Wings") was wielded by the god of
the Underworld, Susanoo, against Yamata no Orochi. It shattered when it struck
the Kusanagi blade in the serpent's tail.
It's the god-slaying demon sword,
which I received from the King of the Underworld.
Ame no Habakiri and the Underworld?!
Now I get it!
I knew you were way too powerful for a human,
but now it all makes sense!
That damn mama's boy... How dare he...!
Big Sister! Why you...!
No way!
You can't even touch me with your level of divinity.
I bear the demon sword blessed by
the King of the Underworld!
Big sister Kagami!
Kagami!
YOU...!
You are too weak!
The path to the Underworld opens easily for me
since I came back from the Land of the Dead.
Once you descend the slope to the land of the dead,
it is impossible to turn back, even for a god.
Your era ended long ago, Sun Goddess.
Fall... and let the Moon have the world.
Now...
Move, little bug.
You're acting like some kind of allies of justice,
thinking you're protecting my spoiled daughter,
but it's completely meaningless! Worthless!
For the world and for Humanity,
Sasami is obligated to become a great priestess
and lead this country righteously.
Tama's dumb and doesn't get it...
But why do you do all this ugly stuff?
We were all happy before you came!
Big Sister Tsurugi seemed really happy!
Big Sister Kagami started to smile more than before!
All because of Mama-lin!
So I don't understand what you're talking about!
Tama doesn't get it!
Then let me put it simply for you.
You are in my way.
Stop it!
Stop it already! Okay, I'm going back!
I'm going back to the shrine!
I'm going to be a Tsukuyomi priestess again, so...
So...
Welcome back to the human world.
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Now, it's time for the ending theme again!
Today, at last, I promise I'll share Sasami's lovely voice
with all you out there in your living rooms!
But actually it doesn't look like that's going to happen...
Oh, what should I do now?
Do I have to sing it again for her?
What's going on?
Perfect timing, Mother!
Please come over here.
What are you doing?
Here, hold this microphone. Are you ready now?
Now sing! Come on!
Wait, wait, I have no idea what's going on here!
First of all I don't sing!
A proper Tsukuyomi priestess has no need to sing!
Don't worry!
Since this episode was pretty serious,
we just wanted to end it cheerfully with this song.
They're recording it, but I doubt
that it's going to be used again.
But please go ahead and sing, just in case.
Come on! Inhale!
Dokomade mo... hibiku... s-s-sy... symphony
That's a... s-s-sy... symphony that echoes... far away
...sasu koi ir-
...shines on the love-
You're not fooling me!
Why do I have to do stuff like this?
Kamiomi, sit still! I'll punish you!
Ouch! Don't hit me with the microphone, Mother!
We need to use that every time!
Well, I guess I'll see you next time!
"Ganbaranai Exercise"
Now it's time for Ganbaranai Exercise!
First inhale!
Pretend you're inhaling Sasami's scent
all the way into your lungs!
Now one, two!
Two, two!
Next, open your arms wide!
Pretend you're holding Sasami!
Now one, two, Sasami!
Two, two, I love you!
Now let's have a wonderful day today!
Next time, Episode 7:
"I Forgot How To Speak"
Episode 7