Good morning, Nayu.
You're up early for a Sunday.
Yeah...
I'll wash your pyjamas, so go and get changed.
Come on, this again? Nayu!
Huh?
If you're getting changed, do it in your room.
Oh... yeah.
She's not very lively today.
And Nayu's clothes didn't match.
More specifically, her bra and panties didn't match.
Did she catch a cold or something?
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Between an Adult and Child
What?
You have to go to the office today, too?
After I handed in my latest work sample,
they told me it gave the "wrong impression".
It's an emergency meeting!
Ah, I see...
You sound really busy, Keigo-san.
Did you have something you wanted to talk about?
Nope, nothing at all.
Nayu.
Spot-billed duck
Is there something you want to talk to me about?
What? Ah, um...
My hair, I'd like you to tie it up...
Sure.
Do you have enough time?
Will it be all right?
It's perfectly fine.
Before Nayu could do her own hair,
I did it in place of her mother, who had passed away.
When she keeps her hair down,
it's a sign that she wants me to be with her.
Goodness, she's still a kid.
Hmm? What is it?
Um... somehow... somehow...
Your hands make me feel calmer.
So? What happened?
Huh?
Try telling me about it.
Um...
I get it.
Thanks to a few peeping toms,
your Underwear Club event turned into a disaster.
Yeah.
I bothered the people I finally got together,
and the friends who helped me, too...
And what's more, I got scolded by a teacher and now I can't make an Underwear Club.
Well, I don't blame them!
For guys, underwear is something that ignites fantasies...
Huh?
Around your age,
boys start to be interested in girls, and likewise.
Just like how your body's growing,
your heart will turn into an adult's as well.
Youko-san often said,
"Underwear and love have an inseparable relationship."
Love?
Well, as for the Underwear Club,
you have little choice but to carefully make people understand it.
Is that the postman?
I'll get it!
Who is it?
It's Komachi.
Huh?!
Komachi-kun.
Ah... um, good job finding the house...
I asked your cram school teacher.
Oh, is that so?
No, it's not what you're thinking.
Ah, I feel a little lonely somehow...
I just said it's not like that!
Now then, I need to get ready to go to the office.
Um... why did you come to my house?
Huh? Eh? Hu-eh?
Eh?!
I'm sorry!
W-What? What's wrong?
Your Underwear Club event fell apart because of me.
I know apologising won't make up for it.
Komachi-kun, it's not your fault!
You drove off the peeping toms, didn't you?
But because of that, I made a big scene.
You didn't...
I see...
So, if there is anything I can do, tell me.
I don't want to owe a girl anything.
But you don't need to do anything like that!
Just tell me to do something!
Honestly, it's okay.
Tsukamoto-sensei already said that I can't form the Underwear Club...
And you're fine with that?!
You're going to let her get away with that?!
Do you have such little dedication to the Underwear Club?
Are you really this quick to give in when others refuse?
Honestly, that Tsukamoto is so bossy!
You can't give in this easily!
If you can't make a club, there's always the "Appreciation Society!"
If you're a man, you'll just do it!
But I couldn't do it by myself...
And I'm not a man, either.
There's nothing left for me to-
Agh, enough! Then I'll help you make one!
Err...
Um... will you, really?
Oh great.
I'm off!
Are you sure? It is underwear.
A man of honour does not go back on his word.
Probably, anyway.
That's right!
It'd be great for boys to be in it, too!
Komachi-kun, it seems like I'm always in your debt.
I don't really understand you, but if you're grateful then so be it!
Thank you, Komachi-kun!
You know, you always come too far into my personal space!
Get up quickly.
Eh? Why am I getting so embarrassed today?
Those of you who are done, go outside quickly.
Ah, Sensei!
Hayama-san.
The Underwear Club incident was unfortunate, right?
But don't give up, okay?
No, I've given up.
Instead, I shall create an Underwear Appreciation Society!
I see...
I see!
That's right! Even without recognition from the school,
you can have club activities.
Yup! There won't be a club room, and there won't be funding, though.
Since it's a society, I can stay in the Kendo Club at the same time!
Isn't that right, Mizuno-sensei?
That should be fine, but...
Yako-chan!
Maybe I should join, too.
Thank you, Haruka-chan!
With this we've got four members!
But there are only three people.
Komachi-kun said that he'd join too!
Komachi-kun said that he'd join on his own.
He advised me to make an appreciation society, too.
He was the one who stopped me from giving up.
I don't know much about that boy, though.
And it's not like a boy in an underwear society wouldn't fit...
"Wouldn't fit..."
Haruka-chan, do you mind?
W-What?
I thought that the bra looked tight.
Haruka-chan, have your breasts got bigger since our fitting?
But I just bought a bigger size...
Ah, it's almost time for that.
It could be because of that.
Eh?
Ah, that's right.
Around the time of your period, the breasts swell.
I see! It's just like how I read in a book!
Ah, sorry! I sound just like a child.
Don't worry about it.
That's what's good about you.
Such great style... She looks like a model.
What a bunch of virgins.
All right, E class.
You need to go to the nurse's office for the eye exams.
Okay!
Oh, right!
Today I was planning on having a meeting for the Underwear Appreciation Society.
Okay, sure thing.
It's fine with me too.
Do you want to join us as well, Sensei?
Eh? Me too?
You're our adviser, after all!
I guess I really am their adviser...
Ah, Sensei! Come in! Please!
Thank you.
Ah, where's your family?
I was hoping that I could greet them.
Nayu!
You said that your friends were staying over, right?
What shall I make for dinner?
Hmm?
Sensei, this is my older brother.
But aren't you...?
Aren't you... Senpai?!
...Senpai?
It's me! Mizuno from Ichiko High School!
Oh, Mizuno-san?
Yes!
Mizuno-sensei?
Ah, when I was in high school, he was an upperclassman...
To think that he's your older brother!
I'm really surprised...
Sensei, do you wear "People-in-love panties"?
That was a surprise; Nayu's brother being her Senpai and everything.
It was!
What is it, Yako-chan?
Ah! I was just wondering if string panties can really come undone!
There are those that do,
but there are also those that are sewn together!
Oh?
Which type are these?
No!
Hayama-san?
I wonder if the bath's too hot...
Sensei, please relax!
I couldn't, Senpai!
I'm shamelessly letting you make dinner for me, I'm sorry...
And instead of "Sensei",
please call me by my family name like in high school.
It's amazing how you remembered me when I'd only joined the...
...Ghost Hunting Club for the summer half of my second year.
Well, after all... um...
But, that's right, you did stop showing up at that time...
Pretty much.
Things were getting difficult at home.
Is that what happened?
Senpai?
Ah, but I do kind of remember you, Mizuno-san.
Around that time, your breasts were already huge, eh?
The only thing that people see is my chest.
Sorry, sorry!
I notice things like that because of my grandmother's training.
Ah? So your grandmother was also an underwear designer.
Yup. She was busy, and rarely at home,
but it felt good to have her as my grandmother.
And your brother's really amazing, too!
There aren't many guys out there that are as good at cooking as he is!
It really was delicious, but...
Thank you for having us!
G-Good evening.
Welcome! Erm, Yako-chan and...
Ah, right, right...
the busty Haruka-chan!
Boing
I guess that I'm not good with men.
What is it, Nayu-chan?
Ah, sorry!
What is it?
Haruka-chan, do you have someone you like?
What?!
Haruka, since when?!
There's nobody!
What are you saying all of a sudden, Nayu-chan?!
S-Sorry.
This morning, Keigo-san told me,
"Love and underwear have an inseparable relationship",
was something that my grandmother once said...
Underwear and love?
I didn't really understand what that meant...
Keigo-san also said, "Just like how your body's growing,
your heart will turn into an adult's as well."
But my body is still like that of a child...
If I come to like someone, I wonder if I would notice...
I see. Nayu-chan still hasn't found anyone she likes.
Why do I feel relieved?
I'm getting out first.
Me too... getting out...
I wonder if it's all right for such a childlike girl to make an appreciation society.
Oh yeah, that girl seemed to understand it...
That underwear is used for sex, right?
She said something pretty amazing...
Maybe that girl's already an adult...
They still haven't come out yet.
I'd better get going, soon.
Eh? You aren't staying over?
What?! I couldn't, it's too fas- I mean,
I don't want to bother you!
Nah, you wouldn't.
And if you want to change, there's a mountain of samples here!
Ah... really?
Yup, you have a beautiful bust line.
Ah, the other day after Hayama-san scolded me,
I went out and bought new ones.
It looks like I wasn't wearing the proper bra size...
"Underwear is supposed to protect the body", but mine was having "the opposite effect..."
"Protect", eh?
Nayu's definitely protected by her underwear.
Eh? What do you mean?
Mm...
When my father and stepmother died,
she suddenly began to wet the bed.
It happened while they were travelling.
It's only been six months...
And they have such a small child...
In the end, Nayu's grandmother took us in.
And that's why you couldn't come to club activities.
I didn't know anything about it...
Around that time, I think Nayu was also pushing herself too hard.
Thank you, Nayu-chan.
I'll be useful!
However...
Hmm?
Nayu-chan?
What's wrong? You're up early.
You can leave the laundry to me-
It's fine!
But you're...
This is fine!
This occurred two or three more times.
I'm sorry.
Nayu-chan, I'm not really angry or anything.
Here, give me your panties. I'll wash them.
It's fine! I can wash them myself.
It's fine!
Oh dear, a sibling fight in the morning?
Youko-san.
What's wrong with them?
Aren't they the briefs I made?
Grandma, I'm sorry!
I made the panties dirty.
I'm happy that you're wearing the panties your grandma made, Nayu.
Listen now, Nayu. Underwear exists to protect girls.
Protect?
That's right.
Underwear will gently wrap up your body and protect it.
Smoothly, and softly, see?
Because of work, I can't always be with you,
but I'll always protect you with the underwear that I've made.
So calm down.
It's fine if you soil it.
Sensei.
Ah, yes?
Please, look after Nayu.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Sensei, are you going home now?
But I wanted to hear your stories about high school...
I'll see you at school.
Thank you for dinner!
Sensei, be careful on the way back.
Ah, my heart was pounding...
Something that protects us, hmm?
Mind if I join you?
Something like this seems like an elementary school camping trip.
Let's do our best for the Underwear Appreciation Society, okay?
Yup! Oh, we completely forgot to talk about that.
Tickle attack...
Wh- Yako-chan, stop it!
Nayu. Na-yu!
I'm opening the door.
Still a bunch of kids, eh?
Nayu, everyone.
It's about time you got up!
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
Hey.
So what does an Underwear Appreciation Society do?
What should we start with?
Come on, you-
For now, let's just do what we can with the four of us.
Like I said, you're always getting too close to me!
Sorry.
Nayu-chan doesn't seem to be very conscious of guys...
...you should think about what it means to be a guy or girl-
Is this where the Underwear Appreciation Society is?
A-Amahara.
Komachi-kun, do you know her?
Yeah, I know her.
I'm Kiyono. Amahara Kiyono.
Amahara Kiyono-san...?
Can I join?
Do you know your three sizes?
94, 61, 86.
Quite the hourglass figure, huh?
How about you, Haruka-chan?
Then we'll find out now!
All right then, take it all off!
How forceful.
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra.
Extreme
Adolescence