Tatsuno Toshiko is Really Odd
Street Number 5
Even if you were to gaze at the sky at the same place,
the clouds you once saw will never be seen again.
Each passing day is unavoidably engraved into the past.
Whoo! Tickets to the movie preview!
I think I just acted like Arashiyama.
Is she infecting my behavior?
Crap. I'll have to watch out.
Anyway, this will get my foot in the door!
Sanada and I will be together!
The rainbow colored twilight is falling
七色の黄昏おりてきて
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
The wind is kinda refreshing
風はなんだか涼しげ
Kaze ha nandaka suzushige
Saturday night is lively
土曜日の夜はにぎやか
Doyoubi no yoru ha nigiyaka
The only thing that'll brighten soon are your dark emotions
暗い気持さえすぐに晴れて
Kurai kimochi sae sugu ni harete
Everyone can't wait
みんなウキウキ
Minna ukiuki
Can't wait.
ウキウキ
Ukiuki
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Can't wait!
ウキウキ
Ukiuki
10 days left until the screening
Art Classroom
[Tatsuno Toshiko is Unbreakable]  From Volume 1 Story 6
What is that?
Whaa! I want to see that movie!
[Tatsuno Toshiko is Unbreakable]  From Volume 1 Story 6
Battles with evil syndicates!
Sorry, but I'm going to invite Sanada.
Oh?
But, I'm going to be so nervous when I invite him.
Whoa! Bittersweet, isn't it, Haribara!
Yup! It's adolescence, Arashiyama!
*sniff sniff* Refreshing!
Stop it.
But instead of a preview, why don't you just invite him to a normal movie.
Yeah. To a more emotional movie.
It doesn't matter what the movie is about.
If he decides to go when I invite him, I'll get my chance with him.
I get it.
When you say, "Let's go sometime," the "sometime" isn't ambiguous, is it?
So, she's saying because it's a preview, the date is already set?
Yup. That's why I picked a giveaway for an unpopular looking movie.
But I wanted to see it...
It's hard to say no to a rare event like a movie preview.
Just as I'd expect from Tatsuno.
You Girls
What are you eating during my class?
Teacher, why don't you have one too?
Ahh! That's mean!
Arashiyama, I'm going to grade your work-in-progress, so show me.
Hey, hey, ho.
Oh? It's pretty good.
Do you get it?
It's very abstract, but the lively horse cutting through the wind comes through very clearly.
It's a sketch of a stretching dog...
Dog?
A dog.
Next up, Ebisu.
Huh? You don't follow? C'mon, follow me!
7 days left until the screening
Today, I'll invite him! Today, when Sanada comes to the shop,
I'll invite him!
So hot...
What kind of getup is that?!
How are you a maid?!
You have no shame in front of others!
Why are you freaking out all of a sudden?!
Try and see what you can do, poko~
It's because these clothes are so stuffy.
Grandma, make us some summer outfits.
Summer outfits, huh?
Well, if I spend all night I might be able to sew one outfit...
Oh, then... tomorrow, the day after...
We'll have three outfits for everyone three days from now!
If you make the Head Maid work overnight for three days you'll kill her!
No way!
3 days left until the screening
Al--right
Damn, pretty good hit.
If I could just get him going with an Arashiyama-like smile...
Wait, I only have three more days! I have to do it today. Today...
If I don't invite him today...
Hey! Did you ask him on a date yet?
I'm gonna do it right now. Watch me.
A personality like yours is something special, isn't it?
You'd be like that towards someone you like too.
I'm taking you to the movies!
You'd say something like that.
Let's go! This is it!
Sanada?
A movie...
Um, movie...
Movi... mov...
Get moving and finish cleaning or you'll be sorry.
Yes! A sorry girl!
Sanada is going home... is that ok?
You can catch up if you run.
Wan-na go see a mo-vie ?
It would've been just eight characters even with a question mark, so why couldn't I say it?
Want me to ask for you?
No. I'll go.
How could I be happy that someone would go in my place, even for a moment?
I'm going to...
jump these...
six steps!
Ack! Kameda from Western History!
Luther!!!
Ruta— (Martin Luther) 1483~1546
German religious reformer
1517 AD. He wrote a disputation protesting
Ruta— (Martin Luther) 1483~1546
the church, sparking the Protestant Reformation.
1517 AD. He wrote a disputation protesting
German religious reformer
Ruta— (Martin Luther) 1483~1546
This is bad.
Tsa- (Czar)
Title of Russian monarchs
Originates from the Latin word for Caesar
Tsa- (Czar)
In the 16th century, Ivan III officially began using it.
Originates from the Latin word for Caesar
Title of Russian monarchs
Tsa- (Czar)
Once he starts lecturing,
Western History Teacher Kameda just doesn't stop.
Note: Kame = Turtle. Apparently softshell turtles can be very aggressive.
His nickname is "Softshell Kameda."
Y-You!
If it were Arashiyama in a situation where she'd pissed someone off...
she'd absentmindedly escape.
What would Arashiyama say?
What would Arashiyama do?
How would she escape this?
No! No! No!
What would "I" do?
I'd...
Apologies, Mr. Kameda.
I slipped on the stairs...
but I'll be alright.
O-Oh I see. Be careful.
I will.
Excuse me.
The day of the screening
Huh? Weren't you going to the movies with the kid from the fish market today?
Rather than doing more work,
doing less work is more effective.
That's the sort of tactic I'm using.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Ah. That's what you mean.
Well, I'll leave things to you.
Huh? What about the shop?
I'm going to play Pachinko, so I'll leave you in the care of the maid today.
In order to succeed,
one must first exert some effort towards getting the reward.
Welcome.
However, very rarely...
Whoo! Free movie ticket!
doing nothing at all
results in great success for those lucky individuals.
Sneezes show a person's true nature, poko~
You see, detectives require sharp observational and investigative skills.
In Japan, a detective's profession...
is about being hired to watch the target's movements and discreetly sleuth around for their secrets.
The ones who are truly talented can find work.
I'm going to observe and investigate you, sis!
Alright, alright, renowned detective Yukiko.
Try finding the truth about me.
Ay, ay, sir!
Huh?
No chest or narrow waist.
It's a truth about sis.
Looks like you have a pretty good eye for observations.
You can eat pill-bugs, poko~
But they taste terrible, poko~
[Really Worthless Cards] From Volume 4 Story 33
Go! Fire Daruma Blaze Attack!
Mirror shield, reflect!
[Really Worthless Cards] From Volume 4 Story 33
Four damage.
Zombie detective defeated.
However, when the zombie detective dies,
an enemy of the same or lower level goes with him.
O-Oh no! Fairy defeated!
And now, I'll make a direct attack on Maki!
I'll protect myself with a turtle knight!
Pointless.
I have a spear so it'll pass a single monster guard.
Damn.
Remaining hit points: Zero. I'm dead.
I've lost.
Takeru is good!
Super good!
Ridiculously good even though your cards are shabby.
You could win against Yamamoto in class 4.
Let's go play him at recess.
Excuse me, boys.
Is it alright for you to bring that to school?
Yeah!
Shut up, Isei Ebi.
Isei Shrimp Carpaccio!
Note: Carpaccio is an Italian dish with raw meat or fish.
I'll tell them about this at next week's student council meeting.
Let's go, Ebi.
You're getting more and more annoying, Isei Ebi.
Girls are annoying.
At this point, why did Hans suddenly escape?
Do we understand what he felt at that time?
Is there anyone who knows?
Ebi
From
To Arashiyama,
Can I come hang out at
your place on Saturday?
It'll be on the test.
Ebi
From
To Arashiyama,
Can I come hang out at
your place on Saturday?
Ebi
From
To Arashiyama,
Can I come hang out at
your place on Saturday?
Huh?
No way.
She won't actually come, right?
No way she'd come.
Oh, sorry. The bathroom is open now.
Nah, I'm not waiting for the bathroom.
Excuse me!
Ehh?
Iseisaki.
Hello.
Oh my, well, good day.
So you were waiting for your friend.
I wasn't waiting and she isn't my friend!
Note: Katsuobushi is dried, fermented, and smoked skipjack tuna.
The hardest food in the world is katsuobushi, poko~
Huh... you really came.
Iseisaki, what did you come here for?
I said to hang out, didn't I?
Oh, right.
Takeru. Takeru.
Hol... Hold on.
What?
Sis is gonna give you a little something from her war chest.
Sign: right: Cards
Sign: middle: Candy
Sign: left: To Savings
Sis is gonna give you a little something from her war chest.
Sign: middle: Candy
Sign: right: Cards
Yes!
Sign: left: To Savings
Sign: middle: Candy
Sign: right: Cards
Sign: left: To Savings
Sign: middle: Candy
Sign: right: Cards
Hey, this isn't for you to spend.
Oh, okay.
She's such a cute girl.
Good luck!
With what?
Tears aren't a decoration, poko~
Seems like I've gotten some money.
Wanna go out?
Sure.
If the guys see me hanging out with a girl, it'll be a disaster.
It'd be the end.
Sign: Imaginary Student Council
Takeru, on Sunday, you were with a girl...
You were hanging out with Iseisaki, weren't you?
Yes...
Iseisaki was the one who told us, the student council.
I plead guilty.
Takeru!
Huh?
You're boring!
Talk about something!
Uhh.
Wait,
why are you calling me by my first name?
You always call me Arashiyama-kun.
Wha?
That's my own business.
Takeru-kun, you should also call me by my first name.
Oh yeah, Iseisaki-san, what was your first name?
Huh?
What? Sorry! I just forgot.
I'll remember it right now.
Uh... hint?
Eri.
What?
ERI!
My cry isn't "Fuyan", it's "Fuun", poko~
E...
Eh?
E-Eh...
Eeeh! No, no, no!
I can't even read the first names of girls in mangas without being embarrassed.
This is impossible.
Can I call you Ebi-chan instead?
That's how I call girls.
Well, okay.
Hey, want ice cream?
Eh, I'm fine. And it's cold.
I want to eat it! Buy some!
Note: Boku and Ore both mean "I" (first person pronoun). Ore is a more masculine version.
Also, I hate the word "Boku." Say "Ore."
So arbitrary...
What flavor do you want?
Vanilla.
Uhh...
nothing.
What flavors are there?
There's everything but vanilla.
Then, strawberry.
Sorry, there wasn't any.
Also, I feel like I'm going to freeze to death.
Well, pick something you like, Takeru-kun.
You got me a chocolate melon!
Y-Yeah.
It was at the top.
Thanks.
Yo, Takeru.
What's this? A date?
Hey, hey, hey, you're doin' pretty well.
You got it wrong. Wrong.
Um...
Oh.
This is one of sis's friends.
Hello.
Ain't she a cutie?
Good luck!
Like I said, good luck with what?
Sorry for interrupting.
See ya.
She's pretty.
Y-Yeah.
I thought the guys found me.
The chances of an encounter in the shopping district are too high.
I need to find some place to hide.
Iseisaki-san,
(boku)
Ebi-chan, I...
(ore)
Want to visit the store I usually go to?
Oh? What is it? I'll go.
So I get punched if I say the forbidden words...
Isn't this oppression of free speech?
Welcome.
Hello.
My, Takeru! A date?
And I guess this is what they call a false accusation.
Wow!
This is the first time I've been in a place like this.
I've always wanted to visit a cheap sweets shop.
Ah, this.
The cards that boys gather around.
I'll have this, please.
That's 1,500,000 yen,
but you can have it for 150 yen.
Uh. Thank you.
Augh. I got the worst. Crap.
Want to buy cards?
I'll just buy one.
Worst case scenario!
I didn't know they still had something left from their monthly allowance.
No place to run. No possible excuse.
My elementary school life is over.
Oh, those guys!
Takeru, hide in the VIP room.
Can I?
Elementary schoolers usually can't enter.
A place for eating monjayaki.
The refreshing candy shop VIP room...
Mamo, did you see Takeru?
Hm?
Yikes!
We checked out his house but he wasn't there.
Takeru might have entered the adult world.
Huh? Where?
Let's check out the temple.
That close call was like something out of a movie.
If I don't give up, then I just might survive.
Takeru-kun,
have this.
Eh? Can I?
Yeah.
Open it.
Ok.
A-A little close.
Any strong ones in there?
There's nothing but worthless cards in here.
So are they strong?
Yeah, depending on how you use them.
Makki wanted this one.
If I trade this with a Kabayan...
Takeru-kun,
treasure those, okay?
Ah, sure.
Don't trade them or anything.
Sure.
She's pretty different than at school.
What?
(boku)
I, err
I won't use these cards.
(ore)
Why?! Aren't they strong?
I won't know which ones these are if I mix them with the others.
Takeru is doing pretty well.
C'mon, grab on.
Good, good!
I'm gonna let go.
No, you can't let go yet!
Kids these days, making out and missin' lunch.
Oh, but I like that girl.
She can greet people properly.
I wasn't saying anything bad about anyone...
Tell those two outside that it's lunchtime.
Okay.
By the way, what about my lunch?
Eat with the kids.
You'll fit right in with grade schoolers.
What do you mean by that?
But, Hotori is going to eat with the kids anyway.
Lunch.
The next morning
Hey, Takeru.
Morning.
Where did you go yesterday, Takeru?
Uhh, I dropped by a relative's place.
Makita, look.
At what?
Whoa, that's awesome.
Morning, Ebi-chan.
Don't call me Ebi-chan, okay?
Huh?
(ore)
(boku)
I, err, did I do something?
Cozy, cozy!
Sorry, sorry, were you watching?
Look, it's not over yet.
I wanna see the transformation!
They transform every week.
Woman are...
incomprehensible.
Wahahaha! Takeru just said something hilarious!
Memo! Memo...
Ahahaha... Takeru.
Iron Maiden
Attack
Strength
Swing
Enemies, allies, and all creatures take 2 damage.
It feels bad to put two 50 yen coins in, poko~
The Japanese detective has the occupation of uncovering illegal conduct in civil affairs.
In such cases, punishment by law is determined by the police.
Alright. Have you discovered the truth about me?
Yes. I've discovered the truth.
Right here!
Middle school edition
Arashiyama Hotori
Exchanged notes <3
W-Where did you get that?
This is full of things no one knows...
You win, you win! Excellent job, renowned detective.
ひ、
1,
Hi,
ふ、
2,
Fu,
ひ、ふ、み、よ
1, 2, 3, 4
Hi, fu, mi, yo
退屈や
Living alone is boring,
Taikutsu ya
ロック魂携えて 一人暮らしの 爆音人生
Listening to explosive music with my rock soul.
Rokku tamashii tazusaete hitori gurashi no bakuon jinsei
天然の 提灯河豚のほっぺたで
My pufferfish cheeks
Tennen no chouchin fugu no hoppeta de
町をカオスに 今日も巻き込む
Pulls the town into chaos.
Machi wo kaosu ni kyou mo makikomu
ツンデレは インテリジェンスの証しなり
As a sign of the tsundere's intelligence
Tsundere ha interijensu no akashi nari
今日も彼氏に なぜか告れず
I didn't confess to him today.
Kyou mo kare ni nazeka kokurezu
卓球に 命を捧げ足腰を
I play the drums to train
Takkyuu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
鍛える為に ドラム叩こう
My body for ping pong.
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatakou
こんなバンドでもヤラセじゃねぇ
But this band isn't a fake!
Konna bando demo yarase ja nee
こんなメンバーロックじゃねぇ
The members aren't playing rock!
Konna memba- rokku ja nee
目指してるのは音頭じゃねぇ
We're not trying to lead the song!
Mezashiteruno ha ondou ja nee
たどり着くのは涅槃じゃねぇ！
We're not looking for Nirvana!
Tadoritsuku no ha nehan ja nee!
我らはメイドっ！（イエー！）
We're maids! Yea!
Warera ha meido! (Yea!)
メイド姿で参上！参上！
Visiting in maid outfits! Visiting!
Meido sugata de sanjyou! Sanjyou!
アチョー！
acho-!
ここらはメイド！（イエー！）
They're maids! Yea!
Kokora ha meido! Yea!
事件現場は惨状！惨状！
Visiting the scene of the crime! Visiting!
Jiken genjyou ha sanjyou! Sanjyou!
アチャ～
acha~
無敵のメイド！（イエー！）
Unrivaled maids! Yea!
Muteki no meido! (Yea!)
便秘は難産 かんちょー！かんちょー！
Constipation is like a hard delivery! Enema! Enema!
Benpi ha nanzan kancho-! Kancho-!
かんちょぉぉお！
enemaaA!
kanchoooO!
清く･正しく･潔く　シーサイドは （絶賛！）
The pure, right, and open hearted seaside is (Amazing!)
Kiyoku - Tadashiku - Isagiyoku Shi-saido ha (zessan!)
営業中！（めいど！ありがとうございまーす！）
Now open! (Maid! Thank you!)
Eigyouchuu! (Meido! Arigatou gozaima-su!)
Next episode
There's an old story about Pandora's box.
I know that one. It's the box that you shouldn't open, right?
If opened, a lot of bad things come flying out.
But the very last thing that came out was hope.
But really, hope is just a trap.
If there were no hope, you'd just give up
instead of reaching for the stars and telling yourself you'll win next time.
Grandma, did you lose at Pachinko?
Street Number 6  [Pandora Maid Service]
Next time, Street Number 6 "Pandora Maid Service"
We're all over, poko~
Street Number 6  [Pandora Maid Service]