Judy...
Don't mind her, Cal.
She's probably just out of booze again.
Well, I'll be off.
I should be back by morning as always.
Be careful.
Over there!
Phantom!
It's Inferno's...
...Phantom!
Just in the past year, more than 20 important figures have fallen victim to this mysterious purge.
These murders are being called "Phantom Assassinations", and are striking terror into the hearts of the U.S. underworld.
Looks like that lady's doing this the flashy way as usual.
It's not a laughing matter, bro.
It could be us on the news tomorrow, you know.
Belacruz, who was a substantial Number Two of the Gambino household, is no longer there.
The Gambinos have nothing left.
The East Coast is ours now.
This is all thanks to Phantom.
Our previous Phantom astonished us as well, but that boy is something else, Claudia.
It's almost frightening how much he's accomplished.
It's a wonder that you were able to tame him up to now.
I didn't tame him.
His devotion to Inferno is his own will.
Oh, really now?
I've always thought that he was trying so hard because he wanted to get to those tits of yours.
By the way, Mr. McGuire...
The investigation for that group is now complete.
The Japanese organization that's going to be joining us, right?
They've reclaimed their own market in Japan, and are making quite a bit of a profit.
But their Southeast Asian dealer, who was the
source of their products, suffered a deadly blow.
The Godoh Group currently has no products in stock.
If we establish a business relationship with the Godoh Group right now,
we will control the monopolistic export of products to Japan.
This weekend I've made a deal for 5 million dollars with
Mr. Daisuke Godoh, the young head of the group.
As a means of a friendly gift, for starters.
Now wait just a second.
Why are you suddenly in charge of the negotiations, too?
What about our say in this?
That's enough.
But...!
If she's able to carry out the negotiations smoothly,
I don't see why we should find someone else for the job.
Then that's exactly what I'll do.
Good work.
Say, don't you think you've been pushing yourself too hard lately?
You think so?
I'm sure you've got something in mind,
but if you give too much support to one organization, you'll end up having to carry extra burdens.
I'll be fine. Everything is going well.
That was fast.
I've returned,
Ms. McCunnen.
Lizzie told me what happened in New York, Zwei.
Sounds like it was a success.
Thank you.
I'll prepare a ride right away.
Would you care to drive?
I'll leave it to you.
Looking good, Phantom.
How was New York?
It was cold. Nothing special.
Isaac was saying earlier that you're only playing the role of Phantom for my body.
I could see him saying something like that.
Was he right?
Who knows.
If I ever had reasons... I've forgotten them.
That's right. Who really cares?
You're here out of your own will.
Yeah right...
I don't have a will.
I don't have anything right now.
But soon, like me, you won't be able to feel anything.
There's nothing for us in the past or the future.
It was exactly as you said, Elen.
Your handling's a bit stiff.
You can't blame me when 25kg of cocaine is your customer.
Only the two of us?
The whole purpose of this deal is to get to know and trust each other.
It wouldn't quite work if we brought along a lot of people with us, would it?
I see.
And so, who are they?
They're people from your homeland.
Those yakuzas, huh?
This is where we're doing the trade?
This place has always been a territory of the Bloodies.
Isaac Wisemel's gang.
That's right.
No one would pull something stupid in this area that might get them in trouble with the Bloodies.
So it's the safest place for Inferno.
Is that them?
They're not giving us a signal.
Something's up.
Zwei?
Stay in the car.
The guy behind this was working alone.
His weapon was a silenced pistol, and...
...a large knife.
So while his opponents were disoriented in the darkness, he killed them one by one.
He's pretty good.
I told you to stay in the car.
What's going on?
Looks like there won't be a deal tonight.
Who would have done this?
Who knows.
There's no point in thinking about it here.
Head back without me.
I'll be back right away.
Where are you going?
Dealing with the aftermath.
Sounds like you brought all sorts of trouble into my territory.
What do you have to say to that?!
The patrolling brats are all charged up,
and the dealers and women are scared out of their minds which is killing my business!
You really screwed up my territory, didn't you?!
How about you say something, Claudia?!
What, are you trying to avoid your responsibility, Mr. Wisemel?
What?
It's your responsibility to protect your own territory.
My customer was robbed of 5 million dollars and four men in your territory.
I want you to rethink who should be getting cursed at right now.
You bitch, do you really think you're allowed to talk to me like-
This is painful to watch.
Claudia, how is the Godoh Group taking this?
They're certainly not happy,
but they're still under control.
Great.
I'll leave their reception to you.
Butter them up to the best of your abilities.
We have to reimburse a customer's money as quickly as possible.
Along with the heads of the thieves who stole it.
That's your job, Isaac.
Hang on a second!
You're saying that those Asians are customers?!
I haven't agreed to this yet.
This is a matter of dignity.
The people who came to Inferno for help were assaulted.
It doesn't matter whether they're customers or beggars.
You're saying that we should allow something like that in front of your doorstep?
Fine.
I'll see what I can do.
It's a battlefield in there as usual, huh?
We've identified the body.
Her name is Judy Devens. 26 years old.
Apparently she was an old-timer in that area.
No connections to anyone.
She never relied on a mediator, and worked alone.
What about her room?
I took a look.
No guns, no knives, nothing.
It seemed like she had a roommate,
but we have no idea where she might be.
Is there something on your mind?
Lizzy, I'll leave this place to you.
Geez, you sure have a lot of requests.
Whatever, go ahead.
Both the police and the media should have left by now.
Is this where Judy Devens passed away?
Who are you?
Seriously, who are you?
And what about you? A friend of Judy's?
You were Judy's friend too, huh?
I'm her younger sister.
What, is it wrong to have so many sisters?
Not at all.
Who killed Judy?
How should I know?
Not even the faintest idea?
Are you saying that she had a reason to be killed?
That was thoughtless of me.
Wait!
What are you going to do if you find the person who killed her?
I'll make him pay dearly for killing Judy.
You're saying you can do that?
I guess so.
Then...
If that's true...
Take me with you!
I can help you!
No.
I know who killed her!
I saw it all.
I was here with Judy last night when she was shot!
I went to pick her up because she was drunk,
and we were on our way home.
But then, Judy was trying to protect me, and...
Please, could you take me along?
What's your name?
Cal.
Cal Devens.
What about you?
My name is...
Azuma... Reiji.
Oh, so you're Japanese.
All right, Reiji!
From now on, we're partners.
Partners?
That's right.
We're one in mind and flesh, with a sole goal: to avenge Judy's death.
I promise I'll be useful in some way.
Sounds good.
From here on, we're partners.
It'll probably only be for a little while, though.
She was such a small girl.
And I...
...continued to sin.
Someone like me, whose life had been screwed up.
Inside that whirlpool...
...I screw up people's lives.
What... should I do?
Where should I go?
What's... going on?