Can you...
be friends with me?
Friends?
You don't want to?
See you.
Yes.
Welcome back, Chihiro.
Did you have fun?
Yes, it was a lot of fun.
Don't force yourself, okay?
And...
And I shouldn't get in too deep.
I shouldn't let myself get in too deep.
Himura-san, would it be bad if I told someone about myself?
If it's something you've decided, I won't object.
As for my personal opinion,
I don't approve.
You're right.
Even if I get into trouble,
I won't be able to regret it.
All right.
Onii-chan, it's morning.
Wake up, Onii-chan.
If you don't wake up, you're going to be late.
Well then, since I've already gone this far,
whatever happens afterwards is your own problem.
I told you to wake up!
That hurts.
Aren't your methods of waking me up getting more and more violent?
Because you're sleeping in later and later.
Since it's bad for your health, didn't I tell you to stop sleeping at your desk?
It can't be helped. Because the deadline is soon, it's a major crisis.
Don't you say it's a crisis every single month?
Work is fine, but your real occupation is being a student.
Being a manga artist is also my occupation.
Quit quibbling, and go wash your face right now.
Otherwise, everyone will find out about your job.
Hah?
Onii-chan, if you don't properly go to school regularly, your attendance record will be really bad.
You're slow, and your grades are poor.
On top of being perverse, you don't have enough days in attendance.
It's like you're saying, "Let me repeat my second year."
Then I might be in the same class as you next year.
I'm telling you to go to school on time so that it won't happen!
I wouldn't go as far as telling you to stop publishing,
but come to school more regularly.
Well, I'll think about it.
Yeah, think about it.
Say, have you been reading my manga lately?
Of course I have.
You rarely tell me about your thoughts on them.
Because it's embarrassing to tell you what I think.
Besides, even if I don't tell you, your readers write you letters, don't they?
A
"sensei" is a suffix used here as a token of respect for a professional, in this case for a manga artist.
Shindou Nagi-sensei.
A
"sensei" is a suffix used here as a token of respect for a professional, in this case for a manga artist.
Don't call me that outside.
A
"sensei" is a suffix used here as a token of respect for a professional, in this case for a manga artist.
Yes, Onii-chan.
No "Onii-chan" either.
Don't doze off.
Properly listen to what the teacher says.
And if the teacher calls on you, answer clearly in a loud voice.
Are you my guardian?
See you, Hirono-senpai.
Yeah.
You're unusually early, Hirono.
Kyosuke.
Moreover, you came to school with your girlfriend.
I guess you've grown into more of a man.
She's not my girlfriend, and it's none of your business.
Listen, Hirono.
Even if she's not your type, it's important to get along with the girl first.
Among her friends might be a girl that's your type.
And there might be even more of your type among her friends' friends.
Your lack of discrimination towards girls is due to that strategy?
Nah, I'm just a fickle person.
You think something said by someone like that would be persuasive?
So, are you going to class today?
Since I'm already here, I'll just go register my attendance.
Attendance only?
I...
always...
have a feeling of loss, as if I'm lacking something.
I always feel like a certain color is missing from the world I see.
But I have no idea what color is missing,
and the more I want to search for the answer, the further away I get.
Impatience is gnawing at my heart bit by bit.
You're quite a reckless person.
I'm an idiot, so I can only see what's in front of me.
You're strong.
That's not true.
I just think that someone whose dream comes true has a kind of responsibility.
Who would that responsibility be for?
For the dreamer, me.
Did I fall asleep?
Are you awake, Hirono-kun?
You...
Morning. I'm Miyamura Miyako.
You're a student at Otowa, eh?
My uniform looks pretty tempting too, doesn't it?
You were totally asleep.
If you sleep in a place like this, you'll catch a cold.
So, why are you here?
Isn't it obvious?
I came to see you.
A
The test is read backwards here, from right to left. It's a reference from the manga "Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei." 【さよなら絶望先生】
If only this car wasn't there, it would be a good shot.
Hey, Kyosuke.
Hmm?
The shots you took are good,
but it's tough to combine them together.
Huh?
The shots require so much attention that they interrupt the flow.
When I took the one-cuts, I put all my soul in it.
You should also give all you've got when editing.
That kind of movie won't win.
If you want to win at the Cinema Festival,
you should cater to widely held interests.
But--among our works--there are lots of fans who like the movies Kyosuke shoots.
President?
Since those are popular,
shouldn't our strategy be to make good use of Kyosuke's movies in our productions?
You're right, but...
Kyosuke?
I'm going to the bathroom.
That's not it.
It's about time for me to retire.
That girl... should be Hiro's...
It's almost time for Renji-kun to come.
I'm going to tell him the truth today.
Chihiro...
Can I go to your place after my club activities, Onii-chan?
Ah, he has his deadline.
But I was really surprised.
That you're in the same school as me.
I don't come to school often.
Ah, me too.
When it comes to school attendance, I'm known as the infamous, class-skipping devil.
That's why we don't know each other.
When I saw you, I was unsure whether I should call out to you or not.
Why?
I needed to be prepared.
I'm a girl, after all.
I don't understand at all.
This is our reunion after just the two of us spent Christmas together.
I want it to be romantic.
We just spent our time in a karaoke bar and a family restaurant till morning.
Moreover, I paid for everything.
By the way, Hirono-kun.
Sorry. To tell you the truth, I saw it.
That note.
Is it possible you have that kind of dream?
Dream?
Don't be shy. Don't be shy.
It's not something embarrassing.
It's good to have a dream. Yeah, yeah.
Rather than dreaming about it, I'm already a manga artist.
A self-proclaimed one? Or an imaginary one?
An active one.
A professional one whose series appear in magazines.
Seriously?
Seriously.
What kind of manga are you drawing?
A
Shoujo manga are intended to appeal to girls.
Generally speaking, shoujo manga.
A
Shoujo manga are intended to appeal to girls.
Eh?!
Now that you mention it, I see you have a girlish face.
A
Shoujo manga are intended to appeal to girls.
That's what you're surprised about?
Heh, that's amazing of you.
In other words, you already have a job.
Well, yeah.
You're already supporting yourself at such a young age.
A dream life living on royalties...
Well... not that far...
Amazing. A master.
Ah, shut up.
If you have the time to praise others, try to do something to be praised for.
Wah, arrogant.
Take a look at my manga.
There are plenty of lines in there that sound even more arrogant.
Seriously?
Seriously.
From yesterday's me...
To today's me...
Eh?
Chihiro isn't here yet?
Good afternoon.
Ah, good afternoon.
You're late today.
I was reading until after noon. Before I noticed...
What were you reading?
Erm, that's... how should I put it...
It was a boring book.
You were absorbed in a boring book?
Ah, nah.
Rather than absorbed...
Something that you can't tell your friend?
Erm, that...
You're my friend, but...
But?
You're mean.
Okay.
It's okay for me to tell you, but please keep it a secret.
No matter what.
I won't tell anyone, no matter what.
Erm, a-actually...
I wasn't reading a story.
Weren't reading?
Is it possible you were writing one?
You're really mean.
Can you show it to me?
I refuse, no matter what.
I see.
But that's amazing. A story, eh?
That's a really unpleasant reaction.
That's not what I meant.
Just slightly.
It's a slightly unpleasant reaction?
Nah, I was just thinking of trying to write one too.
You're writing one as well?
It was just a thought.
I received a career interest survey at school.
I'm thinking of becoming a novelist.
Really?
I think that's a really good idea.
Honestly?
Yes.
I'm interested to know what kind of story you'd write.
I'm also interested to know what you wrote...
You shouldn't worry about it.
I-I see.
You shouldn't touch it for the rest of your life.
Please keep it a secret even after you pass away or go to hell.
O-Okay.
Does that mean I'm going to hell?
But a career is hard to decide.
Really?
It's not?
I think doing what you like will be the best choice.
You're right.
I was told the same thing.
By whom?
An adult.
What do you want to become?
I have a dream.
A dream?
I don't want to become a novelist. I just want to write stories.
Even if it's just a single story, I want to complete one as my current self.
I see.
I believe you can do it.
Really?
Yeah.
Even though my guarantee is not reliable.
That's not true.
Thank you very much.
I'm happy about what you just said.
I have to start going to school again tomorrow. I don't want to go.
You don't want to go?
It's not like I hate school though.
School, eh?
Ah, sorry.
Nah, it's okay.
It's fun to hear about school.
Rather, it's fun to hear because I can't go.
I see.
My twin sister always tells me about her school.
If she sounds happy,
I'd be happy after hearing it too.
Twin?
Yes. Her personality is the complete opposite of mine.
Onee-chan is like an animal that would die if it stops moving.
She's a first-year student at Otowa.
Her name is Shindou Kei.
But I won't run into her if she's in junior high.
She's in senior high.
Eh?
You two are twins, right?
Yes.
Erm, that means you're also...
If I went to school,
I'd be a first-year student in senior high.
Ah... I-I see.
Ack, I kept thinking she was younger than me.
Erm, should I call you "Shindou-san" from now on?
"Chihiro" is fine.
Everyone calls me that.
Then can you call me "Renji?"
"Asou-san" doesn't work?
It's not the correct form of address.
Then how about "Renji-san?"
"San" is embarrassing. Use "kun."
I'll be the one who's embarrassed if I address you like that.
Nah, see... as a friend.
Okay.
I'll call you "Renji-kun" from now on.
Renji-kun. Renji-kun.
It feels weird.
Yeah.
A
The furigana next to it says "Yakusoku", which means "Promise."
I'm going this way.
Really?
See you.
Yes. Goodbye.
Renji-kun!
What is it?
I... I...
Chihiro?
Nah, it's nothing. Goodbye.
Chihiro!
Yes?
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow?
Let's have fun again tomorrow.
I'll come to the station after school.
Can you make it tomorrow?
I think so.
Okay. I'll see you at the station tomorrow.
So it's you.
The one she met.
Himura-san...
If you want to stay by Chihiro's side, you have to be prepared.
Asou-san...
Renji-kun said to me, "Let's have fun tomorrow."
It's not just a greeting like "see you".
It's a real promise this time.
"See you tomorrow."
Onee-chan,
I can't imagine "tomorrow" and "happiness."
Will I...
Will I still be here tomorrow?
A
The story he's reading is a folktale called "Kachikachi Yama." 【かちかち山】
If you want to stay by Chihiro's side, you have to be prepared.
You wouldn't say "be prepared," or something like that, under normal circumstances.
Yahoo.
Are you Renji-kun?
Yes.
Good afternoon.
What should we do today?
Should we go shopping somewhere?
If it's a place with only a few people.
I don't like going outside or to places with a lot of people.
It's really beautiful.
Yeah. As if it's burning.
Asou Renji-san.
Hmm?
Am I your friend?
Why are you asking me again?
Maybe it doesn't mean anything particularly special to you.
What am I to you, then?
I think I was interested in you from the start.
And then, before long, I couldn't leave you alone, or rather...
Yeah, I'm not worried about you.
I always want to see you.
Like a sister?
It does feel like a sister too.
I also thought that if I had an elder brother, it would be someone like you.
Really?
Yes.
And, erm...
I...
Chihiro.
Yes?
Take a deep breath.
A
This is a popular practice in Japan that is supposed to help a nervous person calm down.
Write "person" on your palm, and then pretend to eat it.
A
This is a popular practice in Japan that is supposed to help a nervous person calm down.
Yes.
I'm sorry, I was testing you a little.
I wasn't sure emotionally if you were the right one to talk to about this,
but now I know.
You didn't change before, and now.
Erm, you're not a different person, are you?
Eh?
Well, since you have a twin sister,
you're not going to tell me that you switched places with your elder sister, are you?
You're right.
I guess I can't help being regarded as a different person.
Asou-san.
I have a memory defect.
Memory... defect?
Yes.
My memory doesn't last longer than thirteen hours.
In that sense, yesterday's me and today's me are two different people.
Even if I live past today, I won't become tomorrow's me.
I've always been like this.
And I will always be like this.
My feelings and that person's feelings pass by each other.
Next episode, ef - a tale of memories: Paradox.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?