[Ed] Hello...?
Can anyone hear me?!
[Water sloshing]
Hello...?! Anybody?!
What the hell is this
place...?! Damn it.
It's Ling's fault...!
That idiot prince!
[Ling] Who do you think
you are to call me that?
[Ed] Ling?!
You can't call the future
emperor of a nation an idiot.
Are you alright?
[Ed] Hold on...
[Ling] What's wrong?
How do I know you're
not Envy in disguise?
Oh, Come on...
Do you want me to recite
the hotel room service
menu from top to bottom?
Alright... You're Ling.
And what about you? How
do I know you're not Envy...?
You little ru--
Who're you calling
a little runt, you jerk?!
Okay, it's really you.
[Ed] How did we even get here?
[Ling] Last thing I remember?
Gluttony swallowed us whole.
So you think
this cavernous void
is the inside of
Gluttony's stomach?
Most likely...
Look. There.
[Ling] That's the abandoned
house where we were hiding...
Also, check this out.
And that's the lieutenant's car.
[Ling] And I'm
guessing all the fire
is from the Colonel's attack.
[Ed] Oh, yeah.
That proves it... But how could
Gluttony's belly be this huge?
I have no idea...
but I sincerely doubt
this is a very pleasant place.
Gimme that.
[Ling] What is it?
Ling... look at this.
Is that Al's?
Why is it just his hand...?
Maybe he didn't get
swallowed... Then he's safe.
He's gotta be freaking out
wondering where we are now...
I wish there was some
way I could contact him.
[Ed cries out] Ahhhhhhhh!!!
Conveniently awaken,
telepathic powers...!
Elric brother telepathy!
[Ling] Yeah, good
luck with that.
[Ed] Come in, brother! Come in!
[Ed] This place
is like a wasteland
of buildings and
human remains...
but they're all from
different time periods.
[Ling] I'm starting to wonder
if there's even
a way out of here.
If not... then I'll make us one.
You will, will you...?
How and where?
Okay, now drop the torch.
Oh, I get it now.
Here goes.
We should have heard
it land by now, right?
[Ling] A wall...!
There has to be a wall!
[Ed] There has to be...!
No matter how
huge this place is,
if we keep heading straight
we're gonna reach the edge!
There's gotta be some
kind of exit somewhere!
I still haven't found her yet.
Where is she?
It isn't like her to just
disappear like this.
Maybe she got eaten by
a stray dog or something.
Eaten?
[May Chang cries]
I was just joking!
[May Chang] She's not a cat.
[May Change] She's actually
a panda, but she got a disease
when she was a baby and it kept
her from growing all the way...
I nursed her back to health
after her mother abandoned her.
Since then... She's been
almost like a sister to me.
[May Chang] My family,
the Chang Clan,
is one of the
lowest ranked houses
out of the fifty clans that
make up the Xing empire.
We have little
to no power at all.
Maybe that's why
I was drawn to her.
She looked so
helpless and weak,
I couldn't help but
identify with her.
[May Chang sighs]
But at the time,
I guess I just took pity
on her more than anything.
[Shao May mewls]
[Shao May growls]
[May Chang screams in pain]
[Shao May whimpers in sleep]
[May Chang] But that changed...
And she became a
part of my family...
We've been through
so much together.
She's always been with me...
It feels so wrong not
having her here now.
I don't think I could have
gone through everything I have
without Shao May by my side...
I know for a fact that
I couldn't have made it
across the desert without her.
[Yoki] Sure... but that was
a pointless endeavor anyway.
Why would you risk your life
like that for something as
preposterous as immortality?
Because it's the last
hope that my clan has...
If I don't return with a
method for attaining immortality
and present it to the emperor,
it's almost certain
my clan will perish...
That's why I risked my
life crossing the desert...
With Shao May.
[May Chang cries]
[Yoki] Ahhh!
[Yoki] C'mon, cut it out!
You're gonna drown us all!
[Yoki cries out in pain]
[Crash]
[May Chang continues to cry]
[Yoki whimpers in pain]
[Yoki] Sir?
[Scar] We've got some time
before the sun comes up.
There won't be as many guards
patrolling the streets.
You mean you're gonna
help me try to find her?
[May Chang] He's a good person.
His people were
completely wiped out
during the civil
war a few years ago.
That's right.
[Yoki] He knows a
thing or two about loss...
So I'm sure he can
identify with your worries
about the fate of your clan.
[Scar] What's the hold
up...? You coming or not?
Yeah! Let's go!
[May Chang laughs]
[Water sloshing]
This is really
starting to get old...
Blood doesn't make
for good terrain.
I noticed... And we're still
not any closer to an exit.
[Ling] I'm starving to death.
[Ed] Soon as we're out...
I'll let you order
anything from room service...
And you can eat as
much as you want...
And sleep as long as you like.
[Loud splash]
Ling?
I can't make it.
Don't tell me... you're
really givin' up so soon?
[Ed] Are you that pathetic?
It's bad enough when
you collapse in the street,
but here?! Get up...! Come on!
Quit being so weak!
Just go.
[Ed] You spineless jellyfish...!
Alright, fine then !
Give up and die if you want, but
you're not dragging me down...!
I'm seriously
leaving you here...!
I'm not messin' around, Ling!
[Ling] I thought you
were gonna leave me behind.
[Ed] There's way
too many people
I'd be letting
down by dying here...
And you've
got people waiting
for you to get back too, right?
Now shut up... If
you're strong enough--
[Ed cries out]
[Loud splash]
[Ed and Ling gasping]
[Ling] So hungry... I wish
we could find something to eat.
[Ed] Well, actually...
Y'know...
Leather goods are edible...
We've got a meal.
And that should do it.
Here ya go.
You don't have
athlete's foot, do you?
My foot is made
of metal, you idiot!
[Ed] Ohhh, man...
that shoe filled me up.
[Ling] I'm sorry, Ed.
[Ed] And why's that?
[Ling] It's all my fault
that you're here.
It is not... Besides,
this place is a joke
compared to what my
teacher's put me through...
It just sucks that we have
no idea where this place is...
But that's alright... As
long as we've got our health,
we can find an
exit out of here.
You're sure optimistic.
Not really, I'm just stubborn...
And if I even think
about giving up,
I have Al's iron fists
to look forward to.
[Ling hmms]
What's wrong?
There's something out there.
[Ling] Is that...?
I thought so-- I should've
known it would be you guys.
It's definitely Envy.
Please show me
the way outta here!
You're just gonna start begging
the enemy for help like that?!
If it means surviving,
I'll be his best friend...!
[Envy] It doesn't matter
because there is no exit.
You've really gotten
us into a fine mess...
I can't believe you got
me swallowed with you.
You just said swallowed...
So we really are inside
Gluttony's stomach?
Well, yes and no. See, It's a
lot more complicated than that.
[Envy] Just ask the pips--
I mean ask the alchemist...
he should've realized
what this place is.
I did notice something when
Gluttony swallowed us...
It was like I had
a familiar feeling.
[Envy] So you do
remember then...?
This isn't the first time
you've been through this.
The portal of Truth!
[Ed] But...
But it wasn't pitch black and
filled with a sea of blood...
It was more like...
like an entirely white void.
[Envy] Oh, yeah...?
So that's what the
real one looks like.
[Ed] The real one?
[Envy] Gluttony is a failed
experiment by our Father
to create his
own Portal of Truth.
He's... a what?
Despite how powerful our Father
is, he still couldn't
create one...
We're trapped inside a
defective Portal of Truth.
[Envy] So this place...?
It exists somewhere in
between reality and truth.
In between?
And I can assure you that
there is no way out of here...
The only option we've got
is to sit here until
our strength runs out...
And that's it.
[Envy] All we can do
is wait here to die.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
No way.
Don't think I'm falling
for any of that crap...!
I know you're
lying to us, Envy!
[Ed] You're lying...!
Aren't you?!
So There really isn't a way
out... We're gonna die here?
Wait... No... Hold on...
I can't die here!
What's Al gonna do if I die?!
We made a promise and he...
He needs me to
get back to normal!
Damn it. I wanna know
who your Father is...
Who would try to create
their own portal...?!
It's Fuhrer Bradley, isn't it?!
What, are you serious...? Ha...!
Nice try, but King Bradley is
nothing more than a Homunculus.
Told ya so.
[Ed] The Fifth Laboratory...
Human lives sacrificed to
make Philosopher's Stones...
Homunculi...
And If the Fuhrer
is on your side,
then I'm guessing you
were the ones behind Ishval.
Oh, Ishval?
[Envy laughs]
I couldn't have asked for a
more enjoyable job than that...!
You remember the incident
that started the war, right?
I had always heard it was
because a military officer
accidentally shot
an Ishvalan child.
Yep! And the one that
proudly pulled the trigger
was none other
than yours truly...
[May Chang] 'Scuse me?
I know what happened
in Ishval... Yoki told me.
[Envy] You have no idea
how good that felt...
I ravaged their entire
country with a single bullet!
I mean, talk about invigorating!
[Envy] Oh, and the best part?
The officer that
I pretended to be?
He was actually a
moderate who had always
publicly opposed the
military's occupation in Ishval.
[Envy] And listen to this!
The poor fool couldn't come
up with a plausible defense
and they court-martialed him!
You know I don't
think I'll ever get over
how easily
manipulated humans are.
[Envy cackles]
So you're responsible...
You were the one who shot and
killed that poor innocent child.
[Ed] You destroyed
my hometown...
You drove out the Ishvalans.
You're the one who turned
Scar into a murderer.
And it was you...
You're the reason
Winry's parents were killed.
You're the one to blame!
What the hell?
[Ed] He didn't budge!
Okay, then...
If that's how you want it.
[Ling] Ed! Get back!
[Chanting sounds in background]
I'm gonna show you two boys
somethin' neat before we die...
Consider it a parting gift.
Did you notice his footprints?
Back when we were all
fighting in the forest?
What...? No.
What's your point?
Just that he's freakishly heavy
for the size of his body...
He might be a bit
bigger than he looks.
[Roaring]
[Ed] Damn!
[Ling grunts] What the hell?!
[Ed] How is that
a Homunculus...?
They're supposed to be
artificial humans, right?!
[Gluttony whispers]
What should... What do I do?
[Al] I have no idea.
What do I do...? I'm scared.
[Gluttony] I don't want
Father to be mad at me!
[Al] What did you say...?
You have a father?
Uhuh!
[Al] Is he the one
who made the Homunculi?
Father made us.
[Al] Where does everything
he swallows go...?
It's gotta be some kind of
trick... C'mon... Think...!
We made a promise and
Brother might still be alive...
I can't just give up now!
[Al] Gluttony! Will
you take me with you...?
Will you take me
to meet your father?
I guess so.
He'll be happy since
you're a human sacrifice!
[Al] Oh, sure, right...
That's why he'll wanna meet me.
[Al] And I guess I'll
find out... What that means.
[Official 1]
In regards to the search
for potential sacrifices...
Our only candidates
are the Elric brothers.
[Official 2] What about Doctor
Marcoh...? Isn't he ready?
[Official 3]
We still have Kimblee.
I doubt that Kimblee
could muster up the nerve
it takes to open the portal...
That reminds me...
How have things been
progressing along with
Mustang's candidacy?
That's a question
for the Fuhrer...
[Raven] He plans on having
a nice long talk with him.
[Roy] Tell me... Why are you
bothering to let me live?
Because you
aren't going to learn
your lesson if
you're dead, soldier.
And the military...? How long
has all this been going on?
The Homunculi
have been controlling
this entire nation
since its inception.
So all this time
you've been sitting back
and laughing at our struggles?
I saw you at General
Hughes' funeral.
Your hands were trembling.
So did you fake that as well?
[Bradley] Why must
everyone make such a fuss
over the death of
a single soldier...?
The moment a soldier
dons his uniform,
he accepts the reality
that he might be buried in it.
And about my hands...
Hughes' child screeched
throughout the
entirety of his funeral.
My hands were
trembling with anger.
[Roy] How can you
even say such a thing...?
You have a child, too.
[Bradley] You're
speaking of Selim...?
He's more
well-behaved than that.
And how do you think he'd react
if he found out that his
father is a Homunculus?
Was that a threat?
You'll have to do better.
[Bradley] Selim will never work
as a point of
weakness in my life.
But you, on the other hand...
I know exactly who to
use as your weak point.
[Fuery] Lieutenant Hawkeye!
What's wrong, Sergeant?
I received a memo from
the Personnel Bureau.
And well...
I'm being transferred to
the Southern Command Center.
They transferred you?!
And I'm not the only one.
[Fuery] Breda's being sent
to the Western Command.
And Warrant Officer Falman's
been reassigned to
the Northern Command.
[Footsteps]
Lieutenant Hawkeye?
[Hawkeye] Yes, sir.
I'm Yakovlev, from Personnel.
[Haweye]
Am I being transferred?
And my name is Storch.
I'm the personal assistant
to the Fuhrer Bradley...
I need you to take this.
Am I being reassigned, sir?
That's correct.
[Haweye] I'd like
to look at them.
What is this?
This can't be right! Are you
sure that these are my orders?
[Fuery] Where are
they sending you?
First Lieutenant Riza
Hawkeye is to report for duty...
At Central Command Center...
As personal assistant
to Fuhrer Bradley.
[Bradley] It's
as simple as that.
She'll be under my
watch from now on.
[Voices] Please, make it stop!
It hurts so much!
Play with me, let's play!
[Ed] Hell no... You go
on and play by yourself.
[Ling] Ugh... This isn't good.
[Envy laughs]
[Crash
Ling screams]
Ling!
[Smack
Ed grunts]
[Envy laughs maniacally]
[Ling] Ed!
Can you make a weapon?
[Ed] You got it! With
this ocean of blood...
There's plenty of
iron to work with.
You have the
tackiest sense of taste.
Ah, c'mon... I think it looks
pretty damn sharp, myself.
[Envy laughs]
[Ed] Can we take him?
[Ling] I doubt it...
He is a giant monster.
And then on top of that,
I'm pretty sure he
broke two of my ribs.
Yeah, I'm pretty beat up myself.
But that's beside the point...
All that matters now is
filling him with some pain!
[Al] Are you sure this is
the right way, Gluttony?
Uh-huh.
[Al] But this is the
way... It can't be.
Your father is
living in Central?
[Narrator] The lost souls of the
forgotten past litter the path
leading toward
the unknown future.
The young man
knows he must fight,
but the only way for
him to discover the truth
is to fully explore the
darkness that engulfs it.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode Twenty Six... "Reunion."
I refuse to say goodbye
when I'm certain that
our paths will cross
once again in the future.