TAKUTO KIRA
W-What are you doing?!
Takuto! Do you understand
what this means?
What the heck is fate anyway?
It's stupid.
I'm not gonna let Mitsuki die.
There's no way a half-baked guy like
you could do something like that alone!
Meroko! You...
Yeah!
TAKUTO KIRA
MEROKO YUI
Me too.
Live?
That's the title that I want to use.
You're using it to mean "to live"
as well as a "live concert" huh?
Yes.
I think it's a good idea.
Actually, I just used the word that
Takuto gave me the other day.
Well...if I could possibly...
What is it? Just tell us.
I would like to have
my live concert on that day.
The day I met Meroko and Takuto
for the first time.
My...well...
My last day!
Well, that's also the day
that I have a surgery.
Well...
Can we not do that?
I guess I am
supposed to say "no."
But we can work something out.
Like, we can finish the check-ups
the day before.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Thank you very much!
See, you never know until you ask!
Yeah.
Sorry, Keichi.
No worries.
Okay, we need to get started now.
We have to reserve the site,
prepare ads, and promote to the media.
Mitsuki's concert...
We'll definitely make a hit!
- Yeah!
It'll be a pretty big stage, huh?
Okay, I'll do my best on the ads!
Thank you very much!
Thank you.
Anyways, it's hard to believe it's been
a year since you debuted. Time flies!
Thank you very much for everything.
I remember the first time we met very well.
Shrimp pilaf.
I was so surprised about that!
I'm sorry about that.
I answered like a little girl.
No, no, it was actually refreshing.
Since your comments were so interesting,
I just used them the way they were.
- What's wrong?
- But readers seemed to
- Nothing.
- like them very much.
I'm sorry, it was her first job,
so she was quite nervous.
Yes, that's right.
Huh?
M-Mr. Takeda, are you okay?
Don't worry!
I just made him fall asleep.
I-I see. But why did Full Moon
transform back into Mitsuki?
Takuto?
Sorry, sorry.
Hey! Come on!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What's wrong?
Well...
Hurry, Takuto!
I know! Go!
Oops! I'm sorry I fell asleep!
I must be exhausted.
P-Please don't worry!
Huh? Since when was
this stuffed animal here?
What are you talking about, Mr. Takeda?
It's been there since we got here!
Really?!
Y-Yes, it's my favorite
stuffed animal.
I bring it with me everywhere I go.
Oh, I see.
- Yes, that's right!
- That's right!
Oh, Mr. Takeda!
Takuto...
I hope he's okay.
Yeah.
What?
I'm not putting on a show!
I-I'm sorry!
Don't worry about what happened today!
I was just a little tired.
Really?
You don't believe me?
It's not that I don't believe you, but...
Okay, watch me!
Let this withered tree bloom!
Wow!
See, I told you!
H-Hey, Takuto.
Don't' say anything!
Takuto!
Takuto, are you okay? Takuto!
I-I'm okay.
No, you're not!
Takuto... Could it be...
It's the same as before.
I thought you had stopped turning
into a ghost, but were we wrong?
It's my fault.
It's my fault!
No, it's not!
It has nothing to do with you.
This is my problem.
No! I don't want you
to become a ghost!
Don't cry!
You too, Mitsuki.
But...
Just calm down.
Takuto!
I guess I'm okay now.
Don't worry about me
becoming a ghost.
It's not like I wanted to be
a Death Spirit either.
Plus, I don't wanna stay
a Death Spirit forever anyways.
Takuto...
More importantly, the problem is
Mitsuki's transformation.
The reason why Mitsuki can transform
is because she's got my blood in her.
So she can transform
as long as I exist.
If I became a ghost...
In other words,
if I disappear,
Mitsuki will never be able to
transform into Full Moon ever again.
Shoot! All this with the important
concert coming up!
The concert is not
the problem for you!
That's right!
We can't let you become a ghost!
Yes. Let's—
Just listen to me!
Please listen to me.
I may not be perfect as either
a human or a Death Spirit,
but I always try to
keep a promise.
Do you remember our promise?
Our promise?
I guess there's
no way around it.
Go as far as you can with it.
I'll help you with your dream for one year.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
The day of your concert will be
the last day for our promise.
I will keep our promise!
I'll be sure to let you transform!
There shouldn't be any problem!
We've always managed, right?
Am I wrong?
I guess so.
You're right.
That is right.
Okay, we'll have to do
something about it.
I'll think about something
for the worst-case scenario.
You're thinking about
the worst-case scenario already?
And my Death Spirit power
might still be okay too.
Right.
All right, I'll do my best too!
That's good! That's the spirit!
Me too!
Yeah!
Let's do it!
What's up?
Do you think we should tell
Ms. Oshige about this?
Not tonight.
If the situation with my powers
is the same tomorrow morning,
we can tell her then.
I hope your powers
will be back to normal.
Yeah.
Aoi, don't worry.
I'll complete the mission.
See, I told you that I'd be fine.
It didn't work.
Don't be disappointed like that.
It's only been a day.
Takuto, drink this.
What is it?
It's an energy drink.
Huh?
What do I have to
perk myself up for?
Well, why don't you
go ahead and have it,
since she picked it up for you.
Oh fine.
Do these really work?
H-How was it?
It seems like it's
not working for him.
Yeah.
I know!
Yes! What do you think?
You think I can become Full Moon
with some make-up?
I should call Ms. Oshige after all,
and ask her to cancel the photo shoot.
I got an idea!
Good, good! That's good!
Keep doing that!
Meroko is doing a pretty good job!
I was worried because things don't go well
when she's enthusiastic about something,
but I guess she knows you well.
Full Moon, bring your face
up right there.
Yes.
Stare into the distance.
Yeah, good.
That's right.
Who is Full Moon?
It's me, but it's not me.
Before I became Full Moon,
I was a girl who didn't have any friends
and dreamed of becoming a singer.
I made friends.
A lot of friends!
It's all thanks to Full Moon.
W-What?
What's wrong, Mitsuki?
I truly thank you, Takuto.
That you let me transform into Full Moon.
What?
You've let me experience many things
that Mitsuki Koyama could never have.
Thank you very much.
What's up with you
all of the sudden?
I don't know. I just wanted to thank you.
Thank you so much.
Are you okay, Mitsuki?
I'm...fine.
Are you sure?
But just in case...
It's not getting worse
so you should be okay.
Great!
Thank you very much.
Umm... About Takuto...
Yeah, about that.
He has to take it easy and rest.
I'm fine. I know about myself
more than anyone else.
Meroko, please take care of Takuto.
Uh-oh!
Yes!
If he tries to do something rash,
please stop him no matter what.
Sure, I will.
Meroko...
I'll take care of Takuto,
so you go to bed, Mitsuki.
But...
Don't make me
take care of you as well.
Y-Yeah.
I shouldn't be crying.
This is no time to cry.
I can't cry.
Takuto, hang in there.
Meroko and Takuto are
doing the best they can do.
Isn't there anything that I can do?
Wow, I found something good!
I will show it to Izumi.
Those two might know
how to help Takuto.
Izumi!
Hey, hey, Izumi, look at this.
Does it look good on me?
You're so annoying.
Izumi, are you still thinking about
that middle-aged woman by any chance?
It's none of your business,
Jonathan.
She probably doesn't like you anymore.
Oh, poor thing, Izumi! Poor thing!
- Shut up.
- Poor thing, poor thing, poor thing!
In English, that would be...
Oh, we have a guest!
A stranger's here,
a stranger's here.
Oh my, you came all the way here
to visit me, Mikki?
I want you to tell me if you know.
Do you know how to prevent
Takuto from turning into a ghost?
Yes, I do.
Really?
Please tell me! Please!
I can tell you, but...
Can I give you one condition?
Y-Yes.
Your soul.
Can I take your soul?
What?
So what's it gonna be, Mikki?
I don't wanna die because I finally
feel like I have to live...that I want to live.
But...
I don't wanna lose Takuto
after I lost Eichi!
Takuto... He'd get get mad at me.
But I don't ever wanna feel that way!
Okay, as long as
we can save Takuto!
Well then...
Well, to seal our contract, Mikki,
I will have you kiss me.
Mitsuki, you're being rash!
I know you want to save Takuto,
but you shouldn't have gone to Izumi!
No, it's what I needed
to do to save Takuto.
I don't care what happens to me.
Mitsuki...
Gosh, Takuto, pull yourself together!
I won't accept you disappearing!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Mitsuki's Feelings, Meroko's Feelings."
- Look forward to it!