When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Where am I?
You're finally awake!
It's past 9 already!
Hurry up and go wash your
face. Breakfast's ready.
Oh, right, I stayed the night
over at the hamster's place.
Right, right.
Don't go back to sleep!
Hey, what are you doing?!
If you don't get up already,
you're gonna get this!
Here we go!
Take that! Is that the spot?!
You meanie! Stop this!
Does that hit the spot?!
Whosoever commands the
butlers, commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Ah! Hayate! It's me.
Yes, I will be coming home now.
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
I Want to Go Back to Being an Ordinary Girl,
But Buy My Character Songs, Okay?
WHAT?!
What is the matter, Miss?!
Wait... What?
Hayate!
Yes?
What kind of girl do you prefer?!
Pardon?
Special Feature 2
Good-looking Guys
Special Feature 1
Popular Girls
I-It's not that I'm doubting
your feelings for me.
It's just... How to put this?
I'm checking, just in case.
"Romantic Fortune for Sagittarius."
What are you looking at?!
"Signs point to an impending crisis.
"Your partner may be getting
tired of your spoiled ways.
"Pay more attention to
what your partner likes."
Is that what's bothering you?
Maria!
I swear!
Darn it! Answer me, Hayate! What
kind of girl do you prefer?!
What? Um...
What do you consider to be
the ideal married life?!
What comes first? Dinner or a bath or me?!
How many kids do you want?!
Th-That's so many questions at once...
Why can't you answer me?!
I won't forgive you if
you hide things from me!
P-Please!
Fielding such spoiled demands, you
must find it so tiresome, Hayate.
What?
N-No, not at all...
Let me think... My preference...
Your preference is?
In the end, I like ordinary girls.
O-Ordinary?
Yes. I think being ordinary
is extremely precious.
No parents shackling me
with a debt of 150 million.
No being targeted by "very generous people".
To marry an ordinary person
and have an ordinary family...
I have thoughts along those lines...
Ordinary?
I think your life up to now has
been too far out of the ordinary.
Ordinary...
Well, I'm sure someone like
you wouldn't understand, Miss.
What?
What did you just say?!
Huh?
As I said, someone like you wouldn't...
You fool!
Oh, Nagi!
D-Did I say something that angered her?
Yes, though I doubt someone
like you could understand.
Make a fool of me, will he?!
Is he saying I could
never be his ideal girl?!
All right, since it's come to this...!
What?!
The Miss has run away from home again?!
Yes, I just received a call
from members of the SP unit.
This is troubling.
What could her reason be
for running away this time?
You're always the reason, you know...
Welcome!
Thanks a lot!
If I hang around places like
this, can I attain the ordinary?
But this is a bit...
Oh, pull yourself together, Nagi Sanzenin!
I have to master being ordinary,
no matter what it takes,
and become Hayate's ideal girl!
I'm absolutely not going home until I do!
Now, come and get me,
ordinary! I'm your opponent!
There it is! Ordinary!
Huh?
I found it! I-I-I found ordinary!
What are you doing here, Little Sanzenin?
Ayumu Nishizawa.
Ayumu Nishizawa
She freely wields the ordinary
under any and all circumstances.
Alignment: Ordinary
Race: Ordinary
The most ordinary life form
in "Hayate the Combat Butler"!
Ability: Ordinary
Ordinary
What's that supposed to mean?!
Excuse me for being ordinary!
Yeah, seriously!
What?!
Of all people, you being
ordinary is a problem.
What is this?! You're not making any sense!
What's a mere hamster doing here anyway?!
I'm free to go wherever I choose, aren't I?!
Or rather, quit calling me "hamster" already!
Humph!
Oh!
That's it!
If I observe her, I may be
able to master the ordinary!
Honestly! What was that all about anyway?
Stare!
Hey! Why are you following me?!
Do you have some problem with being followed?
I do! I'm about to go shopping!
That's perfect!
I wanted to see what
ordinary shopping is like!
Huh?
Wh-Why does it end up like this?
Ah! So this is a station!
I know about these! This is where
you get on and off trains, right?
I'd seen them in mangas, but I
never imagined that they were real.
Oh, man. Does she really mean to follow me?
All right!
I'm being bullied!
I am being bullied by the station!
I'm against bullying!
Just because I'm not ordinary!
I'm against discrimination!
You can go in if you pay.
Honestly! Why did I have to buy her a ticket?
Now! We will finally be
boarding a train, won't we?!
Oh, you perv!
Impossible!
I cannot get on it!
Is it ordinary to get on board
at those kinds of speeds?
Huh?!
Th-That was a super-express!
Ordinary trains will come by, too!
What?! Then that wasn't ordinary?!
What the heck...
Wow!
Look! The scenery is scrolling
sideways and it's just flying by!
Hey, where's the driver's seat?
I want to try driving it, too.
What?!
There's no way you can do that!
This isn't some video game!
Oh, you can't? I'm good at the
"Pop by Train" game, though.
H-Hey...
Huh?
What's wrong?
Everyone is sitting on my
seat without my permission.
Huh?!
Of course, they are! This
seat isn't just for us!
What?! It's not?!
No way! You don't even know stuff like that?!
Oh, please! I mean, ordinarily,
that's common sense!
D-Don't talk about everything being
ordinary, like you're proud of it!
You know, I've been wondering
about this for a while now,
but why are you so hung
up on what's ordinary?
It's none of your business!
But you're the one who
attached yourself to me!
Come on, hurry!
What? We're going to walk that far?
That's right. The store's
about 500 meters from here.
Why didn't we go all the
way there on the train?
Don't be ridiculous!
Wh-What's this?
Everyone's lined up!
I'd like 3.
Oh, excuse me!
Yes?
Is Koyuki's ultimate seafood
cake still available?
Yes, you're still fine.
All right! Talk about lucky!
Could this be what they call "the line"?!
The thing that always
appears on the release date
of new video games and
limited anime merchandise?!
Yup! It's a super popular cake
and they only make 50 every day.
Today, my parents and little
brother are gone on a trip,
so I'm going to totally enjoy
the cake all by myself!
Oh, I'm not sharing any of it with you.
I don't want any.
Being ordinary means wanting
awfully stupid things, doesn't it?
I'm absolutely not sharing it!
Hey, it's not moving at all.
Patience. Patience.
Things taste especially good when
you have to wait a long time.
Wait. Huh?
Wh-Where could she have gone?
Hey! Hamster!
Over here!
Honestly! What do you want?!
Rejoice!
I was able to buy their limited
product without getting in line.
Thank you very much for your purchase.
The 3-piece limited edition 18-karat
gold XPS360 comes to 5 million yen.
I-I do not want it!
What?!
I'll take it all!
(Zenbu kure!)
It's Mister Rerere!
(Rerere no ojisan da!)
What?
H-Hayate, how about getting a
photo booth sticker together?
What?!
Ooh, she said it!
Ayumu, hang in there!
Uh, but I have to go to work now.
It won't take long! So, come
on! You know, in commemoration!
Okay? Okay? Okay?
In commemoration? Of what?
Uh, um...
To commemorate you going to work...?
Huh?
Anyway, just one! I only want one!
Whoa, Miss Nishizawa!
The ultimate seafood cake is sold out.
The limited cake...
Now, don't be so disappointed.
Hey, whose fault do you think this is?!
In the end, I was only able to
get the leftover cream puffs.
This is what happens to you
when you try to do things
that you normally don't do.
After all the trouble I've gone
to learn the ordinary, too.
This won't serve as any
kind of reference now.
Why is it that everything you
say has to be so spiteful?
Sheesh! I'm having your
family come pick you up.
Tell me your phone number.
What is that?!
Hey, no peeking at my photo booth stickers!
You! This is unforgivable!
When in the world did you get
something like that with Hayate?!
Grin.
Hehe, are you jealous?
This photo booth sticker is
a memento for Hayate and me.
I-I have something, too!
Can't tell you!
Look!
I have Hayate's number at
the top of my address book!
Address Book
Hayate Ayasaki
Wait, you have your own cell phone!
I won't tell you his number, hamster.
How about it? Jealous much?
I think I might be a bit jealous!
Since we're here, I'm going
to make it clear to you!
Hayate belongs to me, all right?!
What?!
Even if you're super ordinary, on
the order of being a World Heritage,
that's one fact that's never going to change!
H-Hah!
I bet he'll get tired of a
spoiled rich girl like you
and he'll leave you soon enough!
I-I'm not following you anywhere anymore!
Hurry up and get lost!
J-Just who do you think you are?!
You were bothering me to begin with anyway!
Come on.
I'll walk you home.
Leave me alone!
You could listen to me a little!
Ow!
You have blisters!
That's for walking all over the
place when you're not used to it!
I told you to leave me alone!
You should call home and have
someone come pick you up.
I'm absolutely not going home
until I've mastered the ordinary!
Then, do you want to come to my place?
I live nearby.
I know I mentioned this earlier,
but no one's home today,
so you can come over for now.
No helping it then.
If you insist, then I'll keep you company.
Oh, you're so stubborn!
Wow!
Sorry for the wait. Here you are.
Th-Thank you.
Tasty, isn't it?
I-I'm sorry about earlier.
You missed buying the cake because of me...
I'm a bit surprised.
What?
I guess you do know how to properly
say "thank you" and "I'm sorry".
D-Don't mock me!
Even I know how to say such things.
This is good.
Right?! They cost 200 yen a piece!
Oh, it's that cheap?
What?!
But I don't know how you can
live in such cramped quarters.
I totally understand how figurines
must feel in their showcases now.
I-Is that what you say to a person
after you ate their cream puff?!
All right! Next, I'll
have you serve me dinner!
Keep bringing on the ordinary!
She's totally unrepentant...
Wow! So this is an ordinary dinner!
It's all frozen food, though.
What the heck?
Huh?
Everything's on a far smaller scale,
but "ordinary" is not so different
from what I normally do.
I see.
You know, if you weren't super rich,
you'd be a pretty ordinary girl, too.
Me? An ordinary girl?
I mean, you're stubborn and you hate to lose.
Wh-What was that?!
You get all worked up about the guy you like,
but the way you do it can be a bit cute, too.
You're a very ordinary girl.
That's right!
I'm an ordinary girl!
But Hayate just doesn't get it at all!
Hayate doesn't?
Huh, so that's why you were so
hung up about being ordinary.
That's exactly right.
I see! So Hayate likes ordinary girls!
I'm not going to lose!
Huh?
No matter what past you
might share with Hayate,
my bond with him will never waver
over a measly photo like that!
Huh? Photo? You mean,
the photo booth sticker?
Huh?
Oh, please. There's no way there's
anything so deep behind that thing.
Huh?!
What the heck?
Your story was almost shockingly devoid
of anything surprising or moving.
It certainly shows what a master
of the ordinary you are.
Ooh! The way you said that just bugs me!
It was a compliment, you
know. You should be happy.
This is my room.
You can use the bed. I'll
sleep in the living room.
Well, good night.
Hey!
Huh?
Uh, no, I mean...
I-I wouldn't mind sleeping with you.
I-I-I just thought you might
be scared to sleep by yourself.
I-I don't really care either way.
Then, shall we sleep together?
Yeah!
Oh, also...
Huh?
Inform Hayate that I will
be staying the night here.
What?!
Just this once! You hear me?!
O-O-Okay!
Oh, H-Hayate? It's me, Ayumu Nishizawa.
Um, uh...
Yeah, it's been a long time.
Wait!
Huh?
D-D-Don't turn that off.
All right.
Good night, Little Sanzenin.
"Nagi" is fine.
Good night, Little Nagi.
Good night, hamster.
Wha?!
And thus, the night wore
on for the dreaming girls.
Now, next time, the butler battles
will finally reach a climax!
They will fight and fight and fight
their crazy, crazy, crazy hearts out!
Incidentally...
Is that right?
Yes, I understand.
Then please take good care of
the Miss for me, Miss Nishizawa.
Hayate had almost no screen
time in this episode,
so why is he here with no
events leading up to it?
On the contrary, he actually
had his screen time.
See? Right there.
And see? There as well.
And he was even here.
Hurry it up, will you?
Oh, pardon me.
Always ready to save Miss Nagi from danger,
he made sure to stalk her.
Correction. He was making sure to
tail her, s, t, u, v, w, x, y, z.
It seems there's no longer a need for
me to help the Miss and her friend.
My dear Hayate!
Over here, my dear Hayate!
Isumi?!
What are you doing there?!
I was taking a stroll in
my yard when I got lost
and before I knew it, I
found myself in this place!
Please hold on! I am coming to help you!
Please hurry, my dear Hayate!
Please don't panic, Isumi!
Wait for me, Isumi!
W-Wataru!
Young Sir, it's dangerous to climb up there!
I am coming to help you!
I'm almost there, Isumi!
Wataru!
Isumi!
No, please get off me!
No! Butler-in-debt, ya perv!
Just what do you think a girl's body is for?!
Wait, why do I gotta come fallin' down, too?!
Wait, hurry up and make a jab, askin'
where the heck I came fallin' from?!
Are you all right, Isumi?!
Oh, my dear Hayate truly
is a dependable gentleman.
So, the punch line is that
yet again, in this episode,
it was the butler-in-debt who
was secretly the most active.
That's it for the filler segment
"save the regular fall guys"!
Why...
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
Wataru and...
Wataru & Saki's
Saki's...
Butler Report
Butler Report!
What's up?! Wataru Tachibana here.
And Saki Kijima.
Young sir, about the promotional
merchandise you mentioned...
What about an autographed candid picture
of the shop's mini-manager, Wataru Tachibana?
Saki?! When was this taken?!
This is payback for last
time! How do you like that?
Well, anyway, Rental Video Tachibana
is a shop where you can
always count on a smile!
If you find yourself in the neighborhood,
please stop by and and visit us!
Yes! Mystery!
Preview
It hasn't snowed yet, this year.
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
It's already been a year, hasn't it?
Time certainly does fly.
I'm a butler who was reborn to fight you!
Take this!
It's you...!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Hayate in Peril! All Functions Shut Down!!"
Hayate in Peril! All Functions Shut Down!!
At the moment, you've lost
your butler powers...
Because of the curse brought on by that
woman, the chairwoman of Hakuo Academy.
Did you know?
"Cyborg" is short for "cybernetic organism!"