Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
I'm in your debt again.
But you don't intend to repay it.
About the Intel they were pursuing
using the Freedom of Information Act...
I mixed in some fake items
to throw them off the scent.
The government is working on
legislation behind the scenes,
but that should be derailed soon.
Now, about that other project...
Do you want me to handle it?
No, judging from the files you sent,
it shouldn't pose any problems.
We'll stick to the scenario, then.
Good morning.
Morning...
This is how you get the day started!
Don't most people drink coffee?
Ever since old times,
Japanese people have had
white rice, miso soup,
and sake in the morning.
-That's in your case, right, Ms. Misato?
-Why the attitude?
Whose turn was it
to cook breakfast this morning?
I think I know why you're
still single at your age.
Well, excuse me for being so uncouth.
And being a slob.
Okay, you've made your point!
Thanks, I'm done.
Are you really coming to school today?
Of course I am.
It's for your future plans meeting.
But you're really busy at work.
It's fine, it's fine.
It's all part of the job.
Your job, huh?
Hello?
Hi! You didn't have to
come all the way over.
Sure, we'll be right out.
Ms. Misato, please don't come
to the door like that.
-It's embarrassing.
-Have it your way.
Good morning, Mr. Ikari!
Bye, Ms. Misato! We're off to school!
Have a nice day!
Come on, let's get going!
Snark, huh?
Well, I guess it's a good sign
that he's finally loosened up.
Ma'am?
He just left the apartment.
Maintain security on him.
Look, she's here!
She's so hot! Who is she?!
Ikari's guardian?
You mean a babe like that looks after him?
Horny idiots.
Is Ms. Misato great or what?
You think so?
All that, and she's Nerv's
Operations Director! That's amazing!
You think so?
It's a good thing for us that Shinji
is such a clueless baby, Kensuke.
Yeah, he won't get in our way.
Tohji and Kensuke don't know
how big a slob she is.
Oh, I wish I could land a woman like her!
I think you'd regret it.
You are one dense dude, big guy.
Right! We'll leave peace on Earth
in your capable hands!
So you can rest easy,
knowing that Ms. Misato is in ours!
Unit 01 has met target cooling values.
Proceed to stage two.
Peace on Earth, huh?
That's what the Evas are for...
But what are they?
It smells like blood in the entry plug.
So why do I feel so safe in here?
When it's all said and done,
I have no idea what's going on.
How are Unit Zero's
organic chest components?
Badly damaged.
We're making new ones, but it's eating up
what's left of our supplemental budget.
Maybe things will get a little easier
once Unit Two arrives from Germany.
It might be just the opposite.
Angel disposal operations up there
also cost money.
No kidding. This place is
always strapped for funds.
The fate of humanity
is riding on us, for Pete's sake.
It is what it is.
"Man does not live by Eva alone."
It takes money
to keep the survivors alive.
Speaking of budgets...
The Commander is off at another meeting?
Yes, he's en route right now.
Things are so much calmer here
when the Commander is away.
Excuse me. Do you mind if I sit here
since we're traveling together?
The revised budget earmarked for sample
collection was approved without comment.
The Council places a premium
on their own survival.
That goal loosens their purse strings.
Yes, their argument was always
that the Angels wouldn't reappear.
One other piece of good news:
All council nations, minus the US,
have approved funding for Eva-06.
Well, it's only a matter of time
before the Americans sign on, too.
They have a powerful aversion
to high unemployment rates.
What about yours?
We will take part, starting with Unit 08.
Phase Two of the Buildup Plan
is still in effect, after all.
The Angels have returned.
Our only path forward is to defeat them.
Yes, I would also rather not have
a repeat of the Second Impact.
Wait, you're saying the Second Impact,
when Antarctica was vaporized--
Yes. The textbooks say it was a tragedy
caused by a massive meteorite impact,
but the truth has a tendency
to be covered up.
Fifteen years ago in Antarctica,
humanity found a humanoid object,
the first of what we call Angels.
But while studying it, there was
a huge explosion of unknown cause.
So what we're doing here--
Is preventing the onset
of a probable Third Impact.
That is why Nerv
and the Evangelions exist.
By the way, it looks like they're
going ahead with it tomorrow.
Understood.
Good morning.
Um, good morning, ma'am.
I'm going to Old Tokyo for work.
I won't be back until late,
so go grab something for dinner.
Bye.
Um... Yes, ma'am.
DERELICT ZONE NO. 28
(CITY CENTER OF OLD TOKYO)
It's hard to believe that this
was ever called a bustling metropolis.
We're there.
Why are they doing this here,
of all places?
So, is the SSDF involved in this project?
The Strategic Self Defense Force?
No, there's no sign they're involved.
That explains why they're
getting away with all this.
The Japan Heavy
and Chemical Industries Consortium
thanks you for taking the time
out of your busy schedules today
to attend this demonstration.
You will all be invited to view
the public trials from the control room.
But if anyone has any questions,
I will be happy to answer them.
-Here!
-Ah, the renowned Dr. Ritsuko Akagi!
We're honored by your presence.
May I ask a few questions?
By all means, ask away.
According to your presentation,
the unit has an internal heat engine.
Yes, that is its major feature.
It is guaranteed to be able to
operate continuously for 150 days.
I believe installing a reactor
inside a ground combat weapon
meant for close-quarters combat
poses too great a safety risk.
It is more useful than a "decisive weapon"
that can't even run for five minutes.
Remote operation poses issues
when faced with emergencies.
We consider it much more humane
than placing undue strain on pilots
and exposing them to
psychological contamination.
Enough, already. You're causing a scene.
And deliberate operator malfeasance?
It's safer than a wildly dangerous
weapon that can go out of control
and go on a rampage
at the drop of a hat, I'd say.
A weapon that can't be controlled
is utter nonsense.
It's like hysterical women.
There's no reasoning with them.
That is why we have pilots and technology!
Come now, are you claiming
that science and the human heart
can keep those monsters under control?
Are you serious?
Yes. Completely.
Nerv's reliance on something
as nebulous as the human heart
is what let that rampage
happen on their watch.
As a result, the UN was hit
with a huge extra budget request.
Money that could have fed
20,000 starving people elsewhere.
Plus, even though it was
such a serious incident,
its cause remains a mystery?
One would hope that you would carry out
your duties as the responsible party.
Isn't it nice how Nerv
enjoys extralegal protection?
You aren't held responsible
for your failings.
Say what you like,
but only Nerv's main weapon is capable
of defeating the hostile entities!
Are you referring to the A.T. Field?
We'll have that licked eventually.
Nerv's reign won't last forever.
NERV PARTY
Stupid! Jerk!
That obnoxious son of a bitch!
They're just getting even with us
for cutting them out of the action!
I am so pissed off!
Enough, already. You're causing a scene.
He's tooting his own horn
and wants to be patted on the back.
What a pathetic little man.
But how did they even
know about A.T. Fields?!
Our secrets are leaking like a sieve.
The Intelligence Department
needs to do its damn job!
We will now begin
the activation test of the JA.
There is absolutely no danger.
Observe from that window
knowing that you are perfectly safe.
Ready for activation!
-Begin test!
-All power systems engaged!
-Pressure values normal.
-Coolant pump system shows green.
-Control rods, full withdrawal!
-Power has reached critical.
Power output, nominal!
Begin walking cycle!
Walk ahead, slow! Right foot forward!
Roger. Walk ahead, slow!
Right foot forward!
Balance stable! Power system shows green!
Roger!
Proceeding to left foot forward!
Steady as she goes!
It's actually walking. I suppose they
do have something to brag about.
What is it?
This is strange.
Pressure inside the reactor is climbing!
Primary coolant loop temperatures rising!
Open valves. Inject moderators!
It's not working!
Pump output is not rising!
Damn. Power it down. Emergency shutdown!
-Shutdown signal sent!
-Signal not received!
-Radio channel also dead!
-Control has been lost!
This can't be happening...
This robot is just as big a jerk
as its creator.
Abnormalities in pressurizer!
Control rod mechanism fail!
At this rate, there is a risk
of a core meltdown!
I can't believe it...
The JA's programming
is supposed to anticipate
and deal with any possible contingency.
This situation shouldn't be possible.
And yet we're looking at
an impending core meltdown!
The only thing we can still do
is wait for it to shut down on its own.
What are the odds of that?
They're 0.00002%. It would take a miracle.
I prefer desperate action over waiting for
a miracle. Tell me how to shut it down!
We've tried everything!
No, I bet there's still a last resort,
a command to wipe the whole thing.
Give me that password.
Total program deletion is top secret.
It's not my call to make.
I don't have the authority to tell you.
Then get the authority! Right now!
Yes, it's me. Get me Mr. Manda in Tokyo-2.
Yes, the Home Ministry Director.
Oh, you mean that.
I delegated all that to Yasugi.
Ask him.
A decision that big
can't be made over the phone!
Can you send me
a formal request in writing?
Then if I get permission from
Mr. Yoshizawa, you'll approve?
Yes, I have Mr. Witz's approval already.
-Yes. Yes, thank you.
-They're all passing the buck.
Official orders are on their way.
This has to be done properly.
That won't cut it! It won't do any good
if they come after that thing blows!
Jet Alone is currently
heading towards Atsugi.
We're out of time.
I'm taking action on my own authority.
No offense.
Hello, Hyuga?
I've worked things out with Atsugi,
so send Shinji and Unit 01
over here with Type F gear.
Right, it's an emergency.
You'll never pull it off.
Forget it, Capt. Katsuragi.
Anyway, how would you even
go about stopping it?
Up close and personal. By hand.
Are you serious?
Yes.
But the interior is already flooded
with contamination. It's too dangerous.
If this works, it will save everyone.
You'll be able to manually open the hatch
once the command signal from us stops.
You can get inside
through the backpack rig.
"Hope."
That's the password for
full program deletion.
Thanks.
Our target is the JA. There's a risk of a
reactor meltdown in the next five minutes.
So we can't let it come any closer
to a population center.
-Hyuga?
-Ma'am?
Once you cut the Eva loose,
get clear and climb to a safe altitude.
-Roger.
-Shinji?
Yes, ma'am?
Run alongside the target
and put me onto its back.
After that, try to stall the JA
any way you can.
You're going inside that thing?!
-Right.
-That's nuts!
Trust me, I know.
It's our best shot, though.
But it's too dangerous!
Don't worry. Your Eva will be fine
even if it blows up in your face.
That's not what I meant!
It's too dangerous for you!
Well, we have to do everything we can.
It wouldn't sit right otherwise, right?
I have eyes on the target!
Okay, let's go.
Eva drop zone reached!
-Release docking lock!
-Roger.
-We've caught up!
-Less than four minutes to go!
Grab onto it!
Don't worry! Just set me up there!
Ms. Misato!
Be careful.
Wow, that's hot! This doesn't look good.
Stop, damn it!
Ms. Misato, hurry!
This is it.
HOPE
"Error"? What's the deal?
There's no other explanation.
The program's been tampered with!
Reactor will hit prompt criticality
in zero point two!
Control rods aren't activating!
Here goes nothing.
Ms. Misato! Get out of there!
Damn it, move! You piece of...
Ms. Misato!
Zero point one to prompt criticality!
It's no use, it's going to blow!
-We failed...
-Ms. Misato!
She did it!
-Pressure down!
-All readings normal!
-We're saved!
-She did it!
She did it!
That fool...
Ms. Misato, are you all right?
Ms. Misato!
Yeah, but I feel like crap...
Thank goodness! You're okay, then?
Wow, that's great... What a relief.
You were amazing!
I was so wrong about you!
A miracle really did happen!
Yeah.
But this little miracle
was arranged by someone.
Unit 01 has been retrieved safely.
There's no danger of contamination.
Aside from Capt. Katsuragi's actions,
everything went according to scenario.
Well done.
Morning...
Next up, a nice morning shower!
Where did I leave my bra and panties?
Good morning, Mr. Ikari!
Yeah, good morning.
See you later!
Have a nice day!
Ms. Misato is so cool...
I thought so, too,
but she's so embarrassing at home!
She's sloppy, dresses like a bum,
and is a complete slob!
Watching her act like that
makes me cringe!
That makes me extra jealous.
How come?
-You're such a baby, Ikari.
-You said it!
And why is that?
That's the real Misato,
the one we outsiders never see.
That means you're family.
TO BE CONTINUED
NEXT EPISODE
Eva-02 and its pilot leave
Wilhelmshaven, Germany, for Japan.
The sudden attack of an Angel
forces the activated Unit 02
into Nerv's first underwater Eva battle.
Next episode! "Asuka Arrives in Japan!"
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming