Crap, I'm beat...
School's such a pain.
I've put in enough effort for a lifetime...
Aokigahara
Brother?
Top Secret
Let's see what porn he's been watching!
How dare he even look at other girls? He's being unfaithful!
Even if he's around that age now,
I still won't approve of anything else other than incest!
I'm the leader of this project, Yagami Tsurugi.
The Sasami Watch Project shall commence as of now.
Huh?
kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
It all starts at the tips of gods' fingers
watashi no kisetsu tachi
They are where my seasons begin
hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
This is a song much longer than the stars
nemuri wo yusaburu uta
A song that will wake you from your sleep
Sasami@Unmotivated
mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
When I covered my ears walking in the crowd
watashi ga kieta mitai datta
It felt as if I had disappeared
kokoro wo enjiru ni wa
Yes, I want to express my true feelings,
zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm too immature to use pretty words
deatta kouya no hana
I see flowers blooming in the wild
kowakute yasashikute
They're fearful and gentle
fureta shunkan ni jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I brush through them,
it turns dioramas into realities
kamisama no itazura de egakareta
The map of my future is drawn by the gods
watashi no miraichizu
Drawn by mere whims of the gods
ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
It rings with thousands of sounds
oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
And breaks through tomorrow, chasing after today
hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
When we tightened our bonds under the watch of the stars
nukumori ga mieta yo
I found your warmth
kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our bond forms with the blood we shed
mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
But it's the kind of bond I'm compelled to keep
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 4
Parasite at home
Mic test, mic test.
I sure hope you make me look real pretty on film, Tsukuyomi!
Yes, everything's in order.
What... the hell?
The goal of the Sasami Watch Project is to support Tsukuyomi Sasami now that she's finally returned to society.
Support... me?
While the power of Amaterasu herself resides within her, she lives on as an average girl.
If that is the way she wishes to live, then I'll stand behind her decision.
That's my raison d'etre.
Tsurugi...
I want to train her to make her grow.
The point of the Sasami Watch Project is to record her progress
and laugh our asses off every time she messes up.
And here I was even touched for a moment.
Sasami's already gotten her first mission, and my wonderful little sister is recording her.
Hey, cam 2! Give us a sitrep!
You're way too close!
This is Yagami Kagami with cam 2.
At the moment I'm tailing Sasami from 30 meters behind.
Huh? Is that me?
She shows no signs that would indicate that she noticed me.
When did she record that? Did I even go to such a place?
I don't remember anything like that... The hell?
Good job, Kagami!
Next let's see cam 3!
Yep! As you can see, I'm on the school's radio staff!
But, um, heh, I was so loud during the
broadcast that the principal's weak heart—
Oh, my phone!
Hello, Tama here!
Where are you?
Oh, well, one moment the sky just lit up, and the next moment I just found myself here!
Now there are these short, gray people with big eyes filming me now!
They keep saying they have questions for intelligent lifeforms of Earth.
But they have this weird, foreign voice!
What did I tell you about strangers?!
They might open you up while you're still conscious and embed some mysterious probe inside of you!
Anyway, get back to doing your damn job!
Um, Ms. Tsurugi, what exactly did I just see...
Shut up! You didn't see anything.
How's it going over there, cam 2?
What the hell are you doing?!
Sis, can I have this?
That can wait! Where's Sasami?
Uh... It would seem I lost her.
Are you brain dead?!
I will now detect her position using electromagnetic-
spiritual waves from a satellite in orbit.
I found her. She appears to be on the other side of the shopping mall.
H-Hey!
Why the hell are you running on the roof?! What are you, a ninja?!
Tee-hee.
Don't give me that crap!
Be like, "Aren't I cute!" or "Marry me!"
Sasami is entering a drugstore.
Great! I guess she's buying what I asked her.
Oh? She appears to have trouble finding the designated merchandise.
What exactly did you ask her to buy?
Are you looking for something?
Yeah, this, please.
A dozen jimmy hats, huh?
Why are you making an underage girl buy those?
Isn't it moe as hell to see a cute high school girl blushing while asking for jimmy hats?
I'm sorry, but we don't have that product in stock.
I see. My teacher said I could find them in drugstores.
By the way, what are "jimmy hats"?
Huh? You don't know?
Sad but true, nowadays girls don't call them jimmy hats.
I'm afraid that your elaborate form of sexual harassment will go unnoticed.
No way! Back in the day we'd giggle ourselves breathless just from saying "jimmy hats"!
Sasami appears to be heading for her next shopping destination.
Everything ￥100!
The best
products
out there!
The best
products
out there!
She entered a 100 yen shop.
What does she want there?
She's not here on your orders?
Nope.
Everything ￥100!
The best
products
out there!
The best
products
out there!
She came back out.
She appears to have bought something.
Let's x-ray the bag.
You can do that?!
Sunglasses, a knit hat, and something that looks like a sweat suit.
Who cares about that? X-ray Sasami!
What color are they?
What do you want to see so badly?
The color of Sasami's panties is highly irrelevant.
Panties are nice and all, but I wanna hear about her nipples!
Stop!
Oh?
What? She's not wearing panties?
Sasami is going in Super Bath.
Super
Bath
I wonder why.
She could just take a bath at home.
She might be fed up with Tsukuyomi peeking at her.
I never peek.
I'm unashamed to admit that I take baths with her!
What did you just say?!
Super
Bath
She entered.
I will tail her.
Super
Bath
Ticket
Change
One student ticket please.
I'm surprised they let you in with that camera.
Ladies
I altered their conscious thoughts to make them not care about it.
Nice one! Way to go, Sis!
I've found Sasami.
Stop! Don't film that!
Don't take it off!
Stop! Stop!
And now, a commercial break.
Commercial break
It was a quiet winter night with the moon shining bright and brisk.
When did he...
This is so not happening!
Oh geez.
Why did you even record that?
It's a piece from my precious collection of Sasami's sleeping faces!
In that kind of situation, shouldn't you just run at her with a red helmet and a placard?
Whatever, back to cam 2!
Kagami! Kagami, what's going on?
Keeeeeep quiiiiiiet...
What did you do to deserve a break?
What about Sasami's bath scene?
Sasami just changed her clothes and left.
I'm very sleepy. Regrettably, this is where my duty ends.
Go after her!
Did you forget how much you owe me?
I changed your diapers and gave you your pacifier!
I loved you so much that I wanted to do all that for you!
My circuits are unable to comprehend a word you're saying, you pedo.
Aw yeah, keep talkin' like that.
Guess we've got no choice but to go ourselves, Tsukuyomi.
What's up with this DVD?
I don't remember ever running these errands.
What's going on? I've got a bad feeling about this.
Bad... Bad... Really bad...
Here we are.
Sasami will come here for sure.
What's this place?
It's called Uzume-no-Ana.
It's a department store that puts all kinds of merch on sale from various contemporary subcultures.
Including but not limited to anime, video games and manga.
Oh, so it's an otaku shop?
So blatant.
And Sasami?
She'll be on the third floor. Let's go.
Professional magazines
(recently published and older novels, albums, manuals)
Mail order counter
Original amateur works
(general / adult)
Adult goods
General amateur works
(anime / manga / novels / video games / etc)
Mail order counter
Amateur adult magazines
Amateur merchandise
Professional magazines
(older comics releases / adapted to anime)
(new comics releases / magazines)
This sign says the third floor is out of bounds for customers under 18 years of age.
Where's Sasami?
Over there! She's wearing a disguise.
But she can't fool my eyes!
Uh... This is it, right?
Yamato Senki
(Taketakerun)
Nibuki
Yamato Senki
(Taketakerun)
Kumaso
Come again?
Ibuki from the
Yamato Senki
(Taketakerun)!
Buy the limited edition
with removeable armor!
The normal edition can't
be undressed...
"Ibuki from the Yamato Senki (Taketakerun)"?
"Buy the limited edition with removable armor!"
"The normal edition can't be undressed"... Oh who cares?
Yamato Senki
Yamato
Senki
(Taketakerun)
Limited
edition
Ncast-off
Ibuki
(Taketakerun)
Kumaso
Only
a few
left!
Limited edition
cast-off
This crap costs thirty thousand?
Anyway, I'll have to ask the shopkeeper...
She ran away.
Nice one, Sasami! Welcome to my world!
I'll give you half of the world.
Stop! Don't go!
Little sister moe?
Could this be more embarrassing?
Huh? But she's his little sister!
So why?
Oh, yeah, I see. Makes sense.
Wait, what are they doing?
Is that the guy's—
Kill me! Just let me die!
Um, can I have a moment?
You're a high school student, right?
Uh, well...
Are you looking for the VA show on the fourth floor?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, it's really hard to find.
The stairs are here in the back.
Uzume-no-Ana
Akihabara, Reopened!
Let's follow her, Ms. Tsurugi!
Shuddafuckup!
I'm no grade schooler, dammit!
Let me buy this already!
I'm sorry, young lady, but we can only sell these to adults.
I'm a goddamn adult, for fucks sake!
I'll go ahead then.
Event hall
Amateur adult works
(anime / manga / novels)
Amateur works for ladies
Amateur software
CV mini-gig
Thanks, guys!
What are you doing? Dance along!
Are you retarded? This song's red!
Okay...
Excuse me, please let me through...
I'm sorry, no filming!
I'm recording Sasami, not the voice actress!
Huh? Kamiomi? What are you doing here?
Oh, aren't you one of the Tsukuyomi shrine maidens?!
N-No! Never even heard of such a shrine!
Please leave, Kamiomi!
If there's someone from the Tsukuyomi shrine here,
does that mean that this suspicious event is actually—
Now!
Well done.
Father?
My daughter! Let your father carry the burden too heavy for you!
Sasami!
The time has come for the Moon to take the Sun's throne,
and mankind shall rise to a befitting position!
What are you doing, Father?!
It is all according to her schemes.
Her seal weakened and she reawakened to her senses.
She contacted us and suggested us this plan.
N-No way...
Indeed, the power of Amaterasu is right here! In my hands!
Damn, that jerk held me up.
What are you doing, Tsukuyomi?
Please do as you wish...
I felt a suspicious presence.
To disturb my peaceful sleep is to ask for death.
Out of the way!
I'm so sorry!
I'm on the run with the government at my heels!
Don't worry, I'll protect you!
I won't allow anyone to get their hands on the great mystery of space, Nthos!
Woman! Hand over that alien to the Unified Terrestrial Government!
He's going back to his home planet!
Then you leave us no choice. Commence attack!
What the hell is going on here?!
This appears to be a drug to erase memories.
Men! Get rid of the hindrances!
All units, attack!
Let's run, Qubi!
I... will... be... free!
That's how it goes.
Huh?
I dealt with the guys from the Tsukuyomi shrine.
Tsukuyomi called the ambulance and took Sasami to a hospital.
That green smoke messed up your memories though.
So we compiled a DVD to show you the course of events.
Do you remember who you are, Sarcoma?
You were originally the one and same body,
so you ended up coming home here thinking you're actually Sasami.
What are you gonna do with me?
You're a part of Sasami.
Who knows what will happen if you stay separated.
I'll revert you into a lump of flesh,
stick you onto Sasami, and merge you two back into one,
just as you were.
Gi-Give me a break!
I'll be free! I'm a separate personality from her!
Do you have any idea how it feels to be locked in someone else's body?!
We're finally going to be separate! I'm gonna live on my own!
Oh right! I've got power!
Amaterasu's power resides in this body!
I could destroy some washed up has-been like you in no time!
In the name of Amaterasu, I order you—
Give it back.
That toy's more than you can chew.
What...
Go sit in the corner and think about what you've done. And keep in mind, I'm being nice here.
Don't worry too much. I even pitied you for a moment.
I'm not a diligent god, but I work miracles every now and then.
You're awake?
What happened to me?
You're just as you were, just as you should be.
The sarcoma's gone.
I see...
She and you are the same person sharing the same body.
You want the same thing too: freedom.
You're both causing trouble to the people around you too.
But she committed a sin.
She tried to find happiness by sacrificing others.
You're aware of the trouble you cause and try to keep it to the minimum.
Not only do you refrain from abusing Amaterasu's power, but you despise and even reject it.
That's precisely why, being the big bad that I am, give you this power with high hopes.
Good luck and don't spare your efforts.
Until the day you can live without making any.
Hey Meat, I'm Kagami!
Meat?
That's what I named it.
Even though they're of the same origin, I can't call it Sasami...
But isn't meat like, what you call food?
It's so cute I want to eat it.
Even though I'm not human and am not in need of nutrition.
What about Tama?
Goodbye!
There are areas of science that mankind isn't ready for yet.
Sasami@Unmotivated
I'm everyone's favorite character, our main heroine Tsukuyomi Sasami!
And today, I'll sing you my song!
Please enjoy Tsukuyomi Sasami's Osmotic Symphony!
Hearing you say "See you tomorrow" as you leave
just makes me want to see you again right away
I want to hear you talk to me until I get on the train
What's with this mood?!
Do you have a fever or what, Sasami?
You smile and say thanks
Wait, are you really Sasami? Who are you?
Come on, I'm always like this!
I love you! Smoochy smooch!
This feels so wrong...
I can hear your voice
It's a symphony that echoes to the ends of the world
That was pretty good, right?
Did I sing very well?
Uh, yes! The song itself was perfect.
Then I'll sing next time too!
I was already written out of the story, so at least I have a place here!
I'll have my happiness, dammit!
I'll put effort into it next time too!
You're really not Sasami, are you?
Who are you?
This is Unmotivated Consulting.
We have received a letter from Mr. A who lives in Tokyo.
"I can't find the motivation to do anything lately, so I'm living like a slug."
"I could do so much better, but I just can't because the world is holding me back."
"I'm sure Sasami would understand me. Right?"
Shut up and work.
Next time, episode 5:
Next Time
Episode Five
You think I'm
taking this seriously?
You think I'm taking this seriously?