When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Hmm, somewhere along the way,
it's gotten all spring-like.
I have this weird feeling like
the season suddenly changed...
And I can't help but sense
the will of some being,
similar to the invisible hand of God...
So, how about it?
Have you gotten used to
life here at the estate?
Well?
The tiger shouldn't suddenly start
talking, right from the intro.
It'll confuse the non-productive
members of society
who just started watching the show.
Forget about them. Think about the children.
And you got a problem with me talking?
Never mind speaking,
I'm a Class 2 real estate broker
and a licensed boiler engineer.
Real estate broker?
Ah-ah!
But don't tell the Miss and
the others than I can talk.
You know, in terms of a Pokémon analogy,
which celebrated its 10th anniversary,
I'm technically the Pikachu of this show,
so it's about the image.
The image is important.
Acting like you're a respectable mascot!
You're just a lame PR character!
Don't tell me you think you can boost
the economy by tens of billions of yen.
Wha?! Wh-Why you!
How am I a lame PR character?!
I may not look it, but a certain
popular weekly boys' manga magazine
had me ranked 12th in popularity!
And even at the autograph session in Nagoya!
The last character to be requested
on an art board was me!
Oh? The Miss...
I wonder if she's going
out somewhere for once.
Listen!
Wait for me. I'll return without fail.
In truth, I do not really want to go, either.
Where could the Miss be headed?
It was a fateful parting for Hayate and Nagi.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Hey, wait, you damn butler-in-debt!
Don't ignore me, you bastard!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
My First Errand
~This Is Snake. No Response.
This is a problem...
Maria, it seems the Miss has
left on a rare outing somewhere!
"Somewhere?" She went to school.
What?!
You shouldn't be so surprised.
I mean, she's obviously a school-age child.
W-Well, but ever since
I came to this estate...
I totally thought she was receiving
a special education from tutors.
No, she is... How should I put this?
She has a touch of you-know-what...
Acute societal withdrawal?
And it's mid-April already, right?
So the school sent a notice, saying
she should attend once in a while.
I see. Incidentally, which
school does she attend?
She's technically a student
at Hakuou Academy.
Hakuou?!
Hakuou is where all the rich kids go!
It's a super famous school
that covers grades 1-12!
The one thing she is, is smart.
But this is a problem...
What's that?
Nagi's lunch. She forgot it.
I will deliver it.
What? But...
This is part of my duties as a butler.
Wow...
We're in modern day Tokyo here, right?
Or rather...
Hakuou Academy
This place just might be
bigger than Suginami Ward.
Finding the Miss in there
is going to be difficult!
I'll have to work hard...
Hold it right there.
You're not a Hakuou student, are you?
Just who are you?! Identify yourself!
Huh? Are you a teacher here?
Oh, no, I'm Miss Nagi Sanzenin's...
Don't lie to me!
There's no way that you're Nagi!
She may have no chest, but
she's still a girl! A girl!
There are limits to lies and
credit cards, you know! Limits!
N-No, that is not what I meant.
I am the Miss's butler, you see.
Don't give me that nonsense!
What incredible cosmos...
What butler has such a look
of poverty about him?!
Well, there may be some out there,
but I've never seen one.
I make a point of only believing
what I've seen myself!
Do you get it?! I mean, do you get it?!
I have a duty to protect this school
from suspicious individuals.
Why? Because I can't afford to
have my salary docked any further.
So, you're a suspicious individual! Get lost!
I cannot do that.
I also...
...have an important duty to
deliver this lunch to the Miss!
In other words, it's a clash of duties.
Yes, that's what this is.
Let me at least get your name first.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
And you are?
I'm not introducing myself!
What?!
Why? Because it's personal information!
Keeping your personal information safe
is common sense in this modern age!
Y-You're awful...
You fell for it, Hayate Ayasaki.
The battle has already begun!
Uh, I don't really understand,
but that was cheap.
What's going on?
Oh, just looks like Katsy's
in fine form again today.
Who's that hapless looking kid?
Now, give it up, Ayasaki.
You're not capable of getting past me!
The background has turned into
another dimension for some reason!
C-Could this be the legendary Drunken Fist?!
Though, I don't think that's quite it...
Still, I need to get past this person
at all costs and get into the school...
Into the school...
Oh! What do you know? I've
already gotten past you.
Shoot!
We'd switched places before I knew it!
You're pretty good.
Well, I have to be on my way.
W-Wait! That didn't count! It didn't count!
Well, no idiot would actually wait...
...when told to wait.
You three...
Friends of all ages watching this anime,
I am pleased to make your acquaintance.
I am Miki Hanabishi, a
student of this Academy.
I'm Izumi Segawa.
I am Haruo Minami.
Sorry. I'm Risa Asakaze.
Don't show up out of the blue
and start promoting yourself to
people outside the picture tube!
What about your classes anyway?
"Picture tube"?
Pardon, but surely this disturbance
is more important than any classes.
"Picture tube"?
What is this? The Showa era?
Want our help, Katsy?
Huh?
Shoot. I picked up this habit from
when debt collectors were after me
and ran away without thinking, but...
Mandarin Oranges
I'm not actually a suspicious
individual in the first place.
So I should act boldly and
fearlessly. Boldy and fearlessly!
Because I am now a butler
of the Sanzenin family!
Wait... Huh? Where am I?
Still...
That clock tower sure is impressive.
Since I've come all this way, I'd
love to climb to the top just once.
You won't be able to.
Only members of the student council
are allowed at the top of the clock tower.
Wh-Who are you? Where in the world are you?
I'm right over here.
Honestly!
I wonder what a Sanzenin family butler
is doing in a place like this.
Um... What are you doing
in a place like that?
That's a Sanzenin family butler for you.
Wasting no time getting
to the crux of the matter.
I see, climbing trees is all
the rage at Hakuou Academy.
Does this look like I'm having fun?!
But it's dangerous.
I know! You don't need to tell me that!
This is... you know, one of those situations.
Trees aren't as slippery as you might think
and with the branches, they're
pretty easy to climb,
but when you're only looking up you
neglect to look down, if you will...
To put it simply, the cat has a
great time getting up the tree,
but finds itself unable to get
down... Something like that?
Don't put it so simply! It
makes it sound like I'm a fool!
Sure, they say fools and smoke
like to get up to high places,
but I'm not a fool, all right?!
No one said you were...
Well, whatever.
If you're a Sanzenin family butler,
you have decent reflexes, right?
Huh?
Come to think of it, why does she know
that I'm the new Sanzenin butler?
At any rate...
I have a little favor to ask.
Favor?
So, well, um...
Ca...
Catch me, okay?
What?!
Here goes!
WHAT?!
Oh, sorry. Are you okay?
Y-Yes, somehow...
That was no good.
You didn't catch me properly.
That was dangerous.
If you think it's dangerous, please
don't jump in the first place!
I'm sorry.
But you don't have to yell at me like that.
I was really scared and I wanted
to get down as quick as possible.
I'm afraid of heights...
W-Well, that's fine...
But it's unseemly.
For a girl! In a skirt!
Huh? It's no problem.
I'm wearing bike shorts.
Wh-What are you thinking?!
A girl should behave more modestly!
Huh? What's with this naïve attitude?
Could it be that Sanzenin family butlers
have the emotional sophistication
of a grade schooler?
Y-You're mocking me...
Besides, you didn't have to jump so suddenly.
I would've come to your
rescue if you'd just asked!
Wow, so I just have to
ask to get rescued, huh?
Oh, that reminds me,
if you don't like high places,
what were you doing up there?
Hmm? Well, I didn't have a choice.
Because that little one had fallen
from his nest and he was crying.
In this day and age,
you climbed a tree you couldn't get
down from for a reason like that?
Wh-What?! Making fun of me again?!
No, just thinking you're a kind person.
Pardon me for all the rude things I said.
As long as you understand...
But now, that chick can rest easy...
Hey, you stupid thing!
What's up with that crow?!
You can't! You might hit the chick!
Th-Those are...
The parents!
Ah, so beautiful parental
love will save the chick!
What? They're going to abandon him?!
A mother and father abandoning
their own child...
It's never okay to do that!
Mr. Crow, would you please leave it at that?
Or else, next time...
...I'll have to hit you.
Wait, you told me not to throw
it, but you did it anyway.
I have good control, so...
Wha... What's that mean?!
You make it sound like I have no control!
You really are just...
My name is Hayate.
Huh?
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
And you are?
I'm...
Why do you get so hungry
when you're in your youth?
What might this pretty girl's name be?
Leaving the mystery and suspicions for later,
to be continued in the second half!
Dried seaweed.
(Nori)
Lymph.
(Rinpa)
What? Hayate is?
Yes, he should be over there.
Have you not seen him yet?
Well, this school is as
vast as Vana'diel, so...
But I see.
So Hayate lovingly made
a packed lunch for me...
I understand. Not to worry, I will
be sure to accept Hayate's love.
No... "lovingly"? I'm the one who made it...
But where could Hayate be?
And what could he be doing?
I see, so your name is Miss Hinagiku Katsura.
It's a great name.
You think so?
Then, as part of my thanks, want
me to take you to the top of that?
What? But I thought only members of
the student council can go there...
It's not a problem.
Because I'm the president
of the student council.
What?
Honestly! What idiot decided to put the
student council office way up there?
I see.
But Miss Katsura, you don't
like high places, right?
Don't worry about me.
I'm satisfied with just
getting to see it up close.
But you said you wanted to go up
there at least once, remember?
You'll find even greater
satisfaction if you go up there.
Well, I'm sure, but...
Then don't let this chance slip away.
This is my thanks to you, after all.
Ayasaki, if you don't try to get
what you want once in a while,
you'll miss your chance at happiness.
But really, it's so stupid!
Putting the student council
office so high up...
I feel like she might be
a bit like Miss Nagi...
Okay, let's go.
I'm the student council president,
so it's not like this is
my first time up there.
So don't worry about it.
R-Right...
A boy shouldn't give such
a noncommittal answer!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Was that... really a suspicious individual?
It's possible that he's a
real Sanzenin family butler.
So high and mighty!
What would a lame bachelor teacher who
builds Gundam models at school know?
Oh, crap! The head spike went somewhere!
You listen to me!
It doesn't matter anymore if he's
really a suspicious individual or not!
The illustrious Hakuou Academy allowed
someone to break in! That's a fact!
If we don't defeat him,
Took the words right out of my mouth...
people's confidence in the
Academy's security will plummet!
You can't let your guard down around her.
And she's supposed to be a teacher...
It'd be terrible if that happened!
It would, wouldn't it?!
Mainly, terrible for my salary,
since I allowed the intruder in!
Peace.
Peace. Peace.
Who are you people talking to?
Okay, Miss Segawa, you
take the school building!
Miss Hanabishi, the area around the gym!
And Miss Asakaze... um...
Anyway, go search wherever you can!
And take Yasu with you or something.
Yasu... Who's that?
Roger!
We're doing this?
I'll start by searching for the
suspicious individual from above.
Wow!
This view is incredible!
Like it? Wonderful, isn't it?
The view from the clock
tower is truly magnificent.
The sheer beauty of it almost makes
you forget to blink, doesn't it?
You can't see it from so far inside.
I'm fine. I'm viewing it
through my mind's eye.
But you really have a great
view of the school from here.
Right? The reason the student
council office is here
is so that we can have a
good view of the students.
Have you seen the view
from here, Miss Katsura?
I'm fine. I listen to my heart,
rather than pay heed to my eyes.
But really...
School seems so fun.
Oh? But class seems to
be in session right now.
Should you be here?
Miss Katsura?
Oh, honestly! Be quiet!
There was no helping it!
Classes started while I was helping Browny!
By the way...
Who is Browny?
The chick we saved earlier.
He's a brown sparrow, so he's "Browny".
Wow, talk about simple.
Wh-What?! It's important to
have easy names in anime!
Um, I should go deliver
the Miss's lunch soon.
Now that I know where the cafeteria is.
Thank you very much.
Because of you, I got to
see an unforgettable view.
Oh? You talk as if you'll
never be coming here again.
Well, it's unlikely that I'll ever have
another opportunity, Miss Katsura.
Call me Hinagiku.
What?
There's another Katsura,
who stands out a lot here,
so everyone calls me by my first name.
So call me Hinagiku. Got it?
Hayate Ayasaki.
Suspicious individual sighted!
Y-You are...!
Sis!
"Sis"?
Yeah, Sis Yukiji.
You damn suspicious individual,
meet your hundred-year doom!
Well, not that it's actually
been a hundred years...
What? Oh, yes, I suppose so...
So, I'm going to destroy you immediately!
Hold on! He's not a suspicious individual!
Shut up! That doesn't matter anymore!
I already explained that earlier
to everyone watching this anime!
Evil, therefore kill!
Evil
Therefore
Kill
Prepare to meet your fate!
CLANG
Hina?!
Honestly! Another one of
your nonsensical antics?!
You've improved your skill, Hina!
But that won't be enough to stop
your sis's passion and young energy!
Can't stop pay cuts, either!
You're one to talk!
I've never lost to you in a fight!
The only thing I've lost to you in is age,
which you've accumulated
with nothing to show for it!
Wha?!
You may be my little sister, but I'm
not forgiving you for that, Hina!
Um, you two...
Never mind that.
When are you paying back the 20,000
yen I loaned you last month?!
Wha?! Th-That's a cheap shot!
Taking Yukichi hostage!
I never did that.
Um, I need to get going soon to
deliver this lunch to the Miss...
Yukichi's to be respected, you know!
His "Encouragement of Learning"
sold 3.4 million copies, you know!
Like I care!
What?!
Got it!
Sis!
Hina, want me to give this back?
But can you come get it when
you're afraid of heights?
If you can't, turn over that suspicious
individual right this minute
and forget about the 20,000 yen!
Hinagiku...
Don't take me for a fool, Sis!
I am the student council president
of Hakuou Academy, Hinagiku Katsura.
Treating a guest like a
suspicious individual!
I will absolutely not permit such behavior!
That's my little sister for you. Then I'll...
Sis!
Honestly! It's dangerous
to stand there like that.
Sanzenin family butlers really are amazing.
Ah, so you finally believe me.
Yeah, I guess.
Thank you, Hayate.
For my sis...
It was nothing. You were a great help
clearing up the misunderstanding.
Now, I need to go deliver
the Miss's lunch soon, so...
Sorry, I threw it earlier without thinking.
Don't waste food!
What'll I do? I'm going to be fired.
Don't worry. I'll make sure
to apologize to Nagi, okay?
Y-Yeah, maybe I'll apologize, too! Yeah!
What are you doing?
Miss!
Nagi! Um, there are a lot
of reasons for this and...
I can imagine.
Huh?
Ms. Katsura probably stole the lunch
and when she got up on the railing,
there was a strong gust that
almost caused her to fall,
which is when Hayate saved her,
but the lunch paid the price for it.
Something like that, right?
Wh-What prodigious deductive powers...
Well, the result is... you know...
But thank you for coming all
this way for me, Hayate.
Miss!
Now, I have grown hungry,
so this is perfect.
We are going home, Hayate!
You mustn't, Miss!
You have to attend your
afternoon classes, too!
But I'm hungry.
I'll deliver another one straight away.
But then, I won't be able to play hooky...
School is important.
You were in tears just a moment ago!
No, this is part of my job as a butler.
I must have the Miss study properly...
Hayate Ayasaki, huh?
But...
His infiltration of Hakuou
Academy has come to an end.
Next time, he will fight the comedy boom!
Suspicious individual boy!
And we're searching so hard for him, too...
Bastard's quick on his feet.
Well, and that's how we've gotten
to play hooky with impunity...
We truly owe it all to the
suspicious individual.
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
Preview
We sure have great weather again today!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Considering how warm it is,
maybe it'll be midsummer by
the time Golden Week is over.
No way, right?
'Course not, ya fool!
Ya sure have found a fine entertainer, Nagi.
He's a butler, damn it!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Thoughtless Jokes and
Kindness Bring Misfortune."
My friend told me that I mustn't carry
on conversations with strangers,
Thoughtless Jokes and
Kindness Bring Misfortune
and yet, I am...
It's gonna be awesome!