I hate baths.
Wai— Shiro!
I can't wash you unless you sit still!
No!
After all that's happened today, you kinda need it, Sis.
Don't wanna.
It makes my hair all stiff.
Why don't you try this shampoo, then?
Where did you come from, Jibril?!
Spiritwater
Blend Shampoo
Give your hair an elegant finish with this high-quality shampoo.
It maintains luster without damaging your hair.
Recommended by
Flugel everywhere!
Spiritwater
Blend Shampoo
Give your hair an elegant finish with this high-quality shampoo.
It maintains luster without damaging your hair.
This is the Flugel's special
Spiritwater Blend shampoo.
It's guaranteed to give
your hair a soft, silky-smooth finish.
So, as your slave, I would be more than
happy to wash your backs for you, Masters.
Give your hair an elegant finish with this high-quality shampoo.
The bodies of beings
from another world—
Stay away from her, Shiro!
18+
Her very existence is rated 18+!
Jibril, stay.
Huh?
You just sit there and watch, Jibril.
What?!
I can't see anything
through this steam! No fair!
She already has complete
dominance over Jibril.
Your brother is very impressed!
I wanna be like you!
You're amazing, Shiro. Just amazing.
I hate that I'm starting to get used to this.
mawaritsuzukeru haguruma ni wa narisagaranai
I never wanted to become just another cog in the machine
heikin enjiru tanjou kara hajimatta jigoku
I was pretending to be average in a life that had always been hell
asobihanbun de kami ga michibiita
But then God frivolously took me to a new stage
danjou no sekai no no no game no life
To the world of no game no life
nurui heion wo bassari kirisutete
Where I can do away with my boring everyday life
eikou e no kaidan ni sonzai kizamunda
And engrave my name on the stairway to glory
me ni utsuru no wa kanzen shouri no unmei
I now see a destiny of flawless victory for myself
nani mo kamo keisan doori kaete yaru
I'll change everything precisely the way I want
somaranai kuuhaku de
As an untainted blank
we are maverick kyuusai nante iranai
We are mavericks who need no savior
donna rifujin osoou to mo kateba ii dake no hanashi darou
Whatever challenges come our way, winning is all that matters
kakehiki to sainou ga muhai izanau
We'll put our strategy and talent to work and stay undefeated
umarenaoshita inochi de tanoshimu sa
We're enjoying our new lives to the fullest
jibun dake wa jibun shinjiteru
Believing in ourselves
Wh-What is this?
Sacrifice
A kitchen I prepared for my masters.
Um... Stefan?
It's Steph!
Stephanie Dola!
I have no interest in any Imanity
other than my masters,
so I'll call you Dola!
D-Dola?
I bear a message for you from my masters.
I'm Stephanie! I'm Stephanie!
"There's plenty of sugar and butter here,
so make whatever you want", they say.
Really?
I could make all kinds
of sweets with these!
Wait, so they're basically dropping
hints that I should cook for them?
They're always taking advantage of me.
If it weren't for you, we'd have lost.
Thanks.
Please! You're making me blush!
I see. So this is how the
Imanity experience love.
Love?
N-No, it's not!
You were ordered to
"fall in love", not "stay in love".
So why do you still
seem to be affected?
Every minute I spend around my masters,
I discover new things that interest me.
I'm back, Clammy.
Would you like information? Food?
Or... me?
Clothes first, I think.
These taste better than they used to.
I heard that conditions began
to improve for the Imanity
once the late king's granddaughter began
to put the new king's policies into effect.
I see.
Stephanie Dola did that, huh?
A puppet of a puppet.
She's as shameless as
her grandfather was foolish.
But you've been regretting
how mean you were to her,
and you've been secretly
practicing how you'll apologize.
That's so cute!
How did you know that?
I mean, forget that!
Didn't you say you had information?
...Let's see...
The only other developments are
that the new king's got a Flugel now,
and that he's interested
in the Eastern Federation.
What did you say?
Okay, so I got a little carried away.
B-But this will benefit
the Imanity in the long term.
It's definitely not love or anything!
Now then, Jibril.
Tell me everything you know
about the Eastern Federation,
this animal girl paradise
I'm about to conquer.
This country is doomed already, isn't it?
As you wish.
The various Werebeast clans were
embroiled in civil war for many years,
stirred up by the physical
differences between them.
However, an individual known as the Shrine Priestess
ended the war in under half a century,
uniting the many clans into a massive naval empire
and the third biggest country in the world:
the Eastern Federation.
So basically, it's a country
of girls with cat ears, dog ears,
fox ears, rabbit ears—any kind of ears you can
think of—and they're all going to be mine!
We'll declare war and
conquer them immediately.
To do that, we'll need you to
put all that knowledge to good use!
Unfortunately,
your confidence is misplaced.
I'm afraid that even you may not be
able to defeat the Eastern Federation.
...Jibril, are you saying...
...that "Blank" might lose?...
No.
I'm saying that I may not be able
to live up to your expectations.
For I have challenged the
Eastern Federation once already,
and I was defeated.
That confirms it.
The ones backing Elkia are the
Werebeasts of the Eastern Federation.
How can you be sure?
Don't you understand, Fi?
Elven Garde has challenged the
Eastern Federation four times,
only to lose each time.
To be fair, it was those
senile elders who lost, but yes.
That explains how those two could beat a Flugel,
and how they were able to overcome your elven magic.
With the support of the Werebeasts,
they could easily have used some trick
that even you elves couldn't see through.
...Clammy...
That must be it.
The Imanity could never beat a
higher-ranked race on their own.
Don't underestimate humanity.
He mocked me.
So they beat not only the elves,
but even you, a Flugel?
What kind of game
did they make you play?
I cannot say. One of the conditions was that the
loser would retain no memories of the game itself.
Do you understand now?
I see. No way to beat that.
What do you mean?
Eyes filled with pity
Game:
Rock-Paper-Scissors
By eliminating the loser's memories,
Game:
they ensure no records of what happened
during the game will remain.
Game:
Memories
Which means you can't
strategize in advance.
Game:
On top of that, they can
supposedly read minds.
Game:
How do you beat that?
Information
Game:
We just told you that
information is important.
Game:
You're a Steph, all right.
No, wait.
That doesn't make sense.
What doesn't?
If no one ever came
close to beating them,
then people would
stop challenging them.
Wouldn't the Federation
prefer it that way?
Sis, this is why you always lose at strategy games,
even though you're smarter than me.
Grr.
They've got something up their sleeve
that lets them beat the elves and the Flugel.
So, by showing a little vulnerability and luring the
enemy into attacking, they can expand their territory.
...But...
Your play style is obnoxious.
Broshock!
But you're right. It is strange.
How could they have expanded
their country so much in just fifty years?
Right?
It doesn't make sense, right?
Oh, I think I can fill you
in on that, Masters!
Fill us in?
How do you mean?
It was in one of these books.
Only one country has challenged the
Eastern Federation in the last ten years.
And who were the fools who did that?
It would be faster to show you.
Dola will accompany us, of course.
Please hold on tight, Masters.
Now, please excuse me.
Wh-What's going on?!
It's nice and clear today.
W-Wait!
What did you just do?
I teleported us.
Oh.
That's right. We're in an
actual fantasy world, aren't we?
What kind of range do you have?
I can travel anywhere
within line of sight,
or anywhere I've been to once before.
Sounds like the Zoom spell.
How did the Imanity ever survive
the ancient war against these guys?
That's considered the greatest
mystery in human history.
Oh, I remember the ancient war!
The Dragonia, Gigants, and Old Deus
storming around the battlefield,
fifty Flugel banding together and
barely managing to kill a single dragon,
or two hundred of us
taking on a god and losing!
What wonderful memories!
But never mind that.
Take a look over there, please.
...Okay...
What's that pointy skyscraper doing,
ruining the Elkian view?
It's huge.
It's the Eastern Federation's
Elkian embassy.
That's quite a building.
The Federation remodeled our former
palace into the building you see today.
I see.
Wait a minute! You said
"former palace", didn't you?!
...Does that mean...
Do you remember, Master?
Only one country challenged the
Eastern Federation over the past ten years.
...You're not telling me...
Oh, it was Elkia.
Are you okay, Bro?
Yeah. Sorry, Shiro.
Despair
I'm just in despair, that's all.
Eastern Federation
Modern Elkia
Old Territory
The elves challenged
these guys and lost four times,
and Elkia challenged them
eight times and lost half their territory?
Maybe the old king
really was an idiot.
What?
You said before that
he was doing the right thing!
He threw away half the
country's territory for no reason!
How am I supposed to defend that?
Do you have any idea how much agriculture and
industry we could build if we had that territory?
He really is your grandpa, isn't he?
Did he believe in luck
And she bet...
and figure that he'd win
eventually if he just kept trying?
He may not have
been good at games,
but he wasn't crazy enough to gamble with
the lives of three million Imanity for no reason!
He was a good, sane man,
unlike you two!
A good, sane man?
If losing half your territory
for no reason makes you "sane",
I'd rather stay crazy.
Well, I guess he's a fitting king for a race of people
who'd rather bicker uselessly than save themselves.
Humanity's past saving, seriously.
Every last one of them.
I don't care if you insult me, but don't insult my grandfather or the things he believed in!
Hey!
Steph!
Bro, you went too far.
How was I supposed to respond
to a ridiculous story like that?
Delicious.
Damn.
It really is.
Grandfather, what's this key for?
It's the key to where I keep
something very important.
I know about that!
I heard men collect books
they can't show to other people!
...No, that's another key—
Wait, no!
This is a key of hope.
Hope?
Someday, I'll give this to you.
Really?
Yes.
One day, when you meet someone with whom
you can truly entrust Elkia's fate, give it to them.
I'm not giving it to that man!
May I have a word?
Wh-What are you doing?!
I would recommend you return
to the library immediately.
That's trespassing!
Immediately?
I decided that it would be best for my
Masters if I came and informed you of this.
You may do as you like.
Wait!
D-Don't be ridiculous!
...Why would I...
Oh, for crying out loud!
Master, no matter how hard you look, I don't think you'll find anything to justify the late king's actions.
That's not why I'm doing this.
I just feel like something's
not adding up.
So would you say you're
doing this for Dola's sake?
I just thought I'd go
over the details again
so I know what not to do when I
challenge the animal girl kingdom!
Why'd he challenge them
eight times, anyway?
A sane man responsible for three million people
wouldn't just rush into defeat that many times.
So the first time,
the king wagered this land here.
An Armatite mine.
It's a valuable metal,
but we can't even use it with the Imanity's
current level of technology, so it's worthless.
Then he wagered this second,
this third,
...this fourth...
and this eighth.
Until the last time, when he wagered the castle,
the king didn't put up a single thing of value.
There has to be
some reason for that.
Master?
Why does the Eastern Federation wipe
players' memories, when that only hurts them?
Why did Elven Garde
challenge them four times?
...Why did the previous king...
No, wait!
Did he stop after eight times
because he'd achieved his goal?
This is just conjecture,
but what if he didn't lose his memories?
...Master...
I'm sorry to say this,
but not all the Imanity act with
the same level of thought that you do.
But some of them do.
And most of the time,
they're misunderstood.
It's my duty to try
and understand them.
Just say it.
"How can you believe in a lesser
life form like humanity", right?
...No, I wasn't...
The answer is simple.
I don't believe in humanity.
Humans are lowly, stupid creatures.
Every single one of them.
Including me.
They're all crap.
Between this world and the
old one, that hasn't changed a bit.
...I knew it. I can't let that man...
But I believe in the
potential of humanity.
Humanity
She's my proof.
Some of them are the real thing.
People with the potential,
the hope, and the imagination
to reach the gods themselves,
all inside one tiny little body.
It was eight years ago
when I first met Shiro.
She was just three years old.
When she heard my name,
what do you think she said?
You really are empty.
She put together my name, Sora, meaning "sky", and the
fact that I was only smiling because everybody else was,
and used that double
meaning to insult me.
Funny, huh?
It made my heart pound.
I was so excited.
People like her actually existed!
And,
even though I knew it was
impossible, I wanted to be like her.
In our old world, humans could fly
through the sky and travel among the stars.
I can't imagine that.
Nobody could at first, not even us.
But somebody did it.
One of those real people made it there.
It's our job as normal people to ensure that the
potential of these often-misunderstood ones is realized.
So that's why I need to start
by believing in the old king too.
...Sora...
I want to give you something.
There's no doubt.
It's for his porn stash!
I knew it. My whole life was a mistake.
But where's the door it unlocks, Master?
You hide your porn in your own room.
That would be this room.
Actually, we found it a long time ago.
Victory.
Remember when I said this bed
was tilted and hard to sleep on?
That was the start of the puzzle.
Then you just fiddle
...with a few objects...
and there's your secret room!
This is a failure on so many levels.
I leave this in hope that the one who
reads it will not be Imanity's last king,
but the one who will restore them.
I am not a wise king.
In fact, I expect that I will be
remembered as one of the most foolish.
But I take up my pen for the
king who will restore our glory.
I trust and hope that my pathetic,
hopeless struggles will aid you.
I knew it.
The old king didn't
lose his memories.
Unlike the elves, lower life forms like the Imanity
were nothing but easy prey to the Werebeasts.
They didn't erase his memories
because they wanted him to keep trying.
They wanted to lure
him in and beat him?
They deliberately went easy on him to make
him believe he could beat them next time.
But the previous king knew
that and challenged them anyway,
hoping to figure out
how their game worked.
He deliberately gave them useless land,
intending to eventually take it back.
Why didn't he tell the secret
of the game to anyone, then?
He probably vowed by the commandments
not to tell anyone as long as he lived.
But then what was the point?
...However...
that doesn't apply after he's dead.
He played eight times, found
a loophole in the vow he made,
and entrusted what he knew to
...a king that would restore humanity—
to humanity's greatest gambler.
And that was why he held a gambling
tournament to determine the next king?
He made a bet
that a human, the lowest-ranked race,
would appear who could
defeat the other races.
...The probability is ever so close to zero...
but it still exists.
Steph.
Your grandfather was a great man
who pretended to be a fool, challenged and lost,
and devoted himself to
finding his opponent's secrets.
This is his trust in humanity.
Your grandfather—no,
...the previous king...
He really was your grandfather.
...Grandfather...
Grandfather!
And his legacy is weighty indeed.
It's okay.
We can do it.
See, Jibril?
There really are humans like this.
Humanity
Crazy, isn't it?
Perhaps so.
Study the Eastern Federation
dare ni mo ienai
With a loneliness
kodoku wo kakaeta mama hitori de naiteta
That I could share with no one, I was crying all alone
dare ni mo jouzu ni waraenai bokura
We could never bring ourselves to smile
futari deatte waratta
But the moment we met, we smiled
mayonaka sugi ni souzou no oku ni
In the dead of the night, deep inside our imagination
dou shiyou mo nai kimochi wo tada oshiyatte
We pushed away the feelings we didn't know what to do with
sayonara bokura wa kitto umarekawareru kara
"We'll be starting our life anew, so farewell"
kanashimi ni te wo furun deshou
We waved goodbye to sadness
soshite itsuka
And someday
karappo no mama no kokoro ni akari wo tomosu you ni
We'll light up our empty hearts
togire togire no kotoba wo sagashite tsunagitometa
By finding and piecing together the fragmented expressions
sore demo tatta futari no sekai wa tsuzuite ikun da
Our own little world will never end
sora ni inoru you ni
As we pray to the sky
douka eien ni
For this moment to last forever
Fake End
Eastern Federation, your head would look good on the end of a pole!