“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
No way! Was that one of the trash cans from a store?
Anyway, don't go near that guy; his name is Hewajima Shizuo.
You know, Shizu-chan, your violent nature will listen to neither words nor reason.
Didn't I tell you never to come back to Ikebukuro.
Shizuo. Fighting is no good, yes?
Shut up!
The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Well then, it's gotta be him.
Hewajima Shizuo!
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
My company fired me!
The employee dorm kicked me out without notice.
I didn't even get a severance payment!
Not that I had any living or food expenses...
Still, the government won't do anything for me.
That's right. The government. It's all the government's fault!
Shut up.
Because you borrowed money and blew it on the sex industry?
It's love! Mint-chan and I truly love each other!
Be quiet.
We can only see each other at the shop though,
and I don't know her cell phone number.
Still, our love is completely–
You're getting on my nerves!
You can only see her at the shop?
You don't know her cell phone number?
Hey! Shizuo!
I'll say this up front:
How... is that...
true love?!
I hate violence.
Peerless Citizen
Did you know?
There's a guy named Hewajima Shizuo who's been making a pretty big fuss lately.
Huh?
Isn't Hewajima Shizuo-san the guy who wears that bartender uniform?
Yeah.
He's a scary guy as it is, but this time he's really done it.
I hear Ikebukuro's become like a war zone!!
I've seen him before...
He really is scary... that Hewajima Shizuo-san.
Really...
I think it's best to not judge anything based on rumors.
Oh, and are you acquainted with him, Setton-san?
Or... are you the source of the rumors?
I'm scared! Help me!
I'm not!
Seriously dude,
we can't collect any money if you're always clobbering people halfway across town.
Sorry.
Stinks.
They haven't been here for at least two or three days.
There sure are a lot of them these days.
I wonder if they're those rumored "man hunters"?
Stinks.
Hey, look! Somebody's been injured!
Must've been the slasher.
You mean just now?!
I saw it! It ran off the other way!
Sheesh, 'Bukuro's gotten noisy.
Stinks.
Something really stinks. There's a bad smell coming from this town!
What smell?
Shut up.
Hey, Shizuo, Tom-san.
Yo, Simon!
Shizuo?
Sorry, man. He's in a bad mood today.
Oh, Shizuo hit puberty?
It's more like he's hit his rebellious teen years.
Rebellious?
Hey! Long time no see.
Starring in another movie, is he?
He's really been busy, that Hanejima Yuhei.
No, I mean Hewajima Kasuka-san.
You seem very proud to be his older brother, Hewajima Shizuo-san.
Excuse me. I'm actually one of these people.
It's not just looks, but also the performance that matters.
What was the name of his debut work again?
That's right. "Vampire Ninja: Carmilla Saizo."
I knew he'd turn into a big shot after that.
I mean, they did all the action scenes without filming any stunts.
I wonder if that was his brother's idea or not.
And today, I'd like to ask you some related questions.
Shizuo!
I hate violence.
That's not a lie.
It's not as if I've always been like this.
It all started when I got into a fight with my little brother Kasuka.
After losing my temper over some trifle matter, I tried to throw a refrigerator at him.
It's not like I thought I could lift it.
I just did it anyway.
And then...
Shizuo! Smack him in the butt! Stupid! Stupid!
I couldn't control myself.
When my anger got stirred up, my body moved of its own accord.
And every time it did...
People get a surge of strength during a fire, right?
I think you have that same strength, only all the time.
When the power that your brain saves up passes its limit, your bones break and your muscles tear.
However, your power explodes.
It's like one of life's mysteries!
It leaves you mesmerized and speechless!
Hey, let me take a look at your real–
T-That hurts, Shizuo-kun!
It's gonna break! It's gonna break! My hand! My right hand is gonna...
I didn't know all the details.
I just knew that I couldn't control my anger.
Also, I broke the things around me,
and as a result, my body got broken too.
That's all I knew.
Therefore... I gave up on being patient.
If I couldn't do it, then there was no use trying to in the first place.
My body got broken?
Who cares!
My body broke many times. And every time it did, I grew stronger.
According to Shinra... Ah, who gives a crap?
I grew stronger and stronger!
However...
You... you're always getting hurt, aren't you?
Are you okay?
Wait a second.
Here.
You need to drink milk and get stronger, okay?
Here, you too.
Thank you.
I really did it.
I couldn't help but think...
Morning.
How did I get this way?
I grew up in a normal household.
It's not like I had any traumatic events during my childhood, and yet...
Kasuka...
What?
Aren't you... afraid of me?
Not really.
It happened about the time I entered Raira.
Opening commemoration, yes? I make it free.
Fresh store! Fresh sushi!
Somehow, it feels like fate put us in the same school again.
Shut up.
How are you feeling, after that incident?
I know! To celebrate our reunion, I'll give you an examination.
No? At least let me take a blood sample.
Certy!
What happened yesterday?
I was worried since you never came home!
Were you out looking for your head again?
You say that, but I bet you found someone el–
Certy.
If you jab the solar plexus directly like that–
Oh, him? He's a friend. His name is Hewajima Shizuo-kun.
I had a weird feeling.
I didn't know what to call it, but I felt like "This person..."
Shizuo-kun, Certy is my roommate, or should I say, my future–
I just remembered something very unpleasant.
That was also the time that annoying bug first crossed my path.
That guy... Orihara Izaya...
From the moment I first laid eyes on that guy, I didn't like him.
He was with us in middle school. He's Orihara Izaya.
Well, he's not the nicest guy around...
Or should I say, he's a bad guy.
That's mean, Shinra!
No, no. I don't mean it in a bad way.
I don't like him.
Oh?
That's too bad. I thought I'd be able to have some fun with you.
Shut up.
Don't say that, Shizuo-kun.
Look! It's fun.
The day we met, Izaya and I had a fight to the death.
There wasn't any particular reason for it, I just didn't like him.
However...
Are you all right?
It's okay, it's okay. He's a tough guy.
Is he really all right though?
It's all right, it's all right. Thank you, sir.
I failed.
What a pleasant surprise. Izaya's here, too.
More importantly, why aren't you hurt?
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
The next day was the first of several irritating days.
One by one, a slew of people picked fights with me for no reason.
I didn't do anything. I just wanted to live my life peacefully!
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit, I can't take it.
So irritating, irritating, irritating, irritating, irritating! Irritating.
I get it.
Die!
It was Izaya.
That bastard, Izaya, had been the one pulling the strings from behind the curtains.
When I realized that, I...
Izaya!
If only I could've killed him then and there... Damn it!
After we graduated from Raira...
How is it? Does it look good on me?
That moron got to be like this...
And that little bug's been hanging out with the yakuza and getting into trouble.
Still, it was quiet for a while.
However, I...
And then, it got to be like this.
Welcome.
Hey, did you see that?
You're kidding me!
It's that actor...
Hanejima Yuhei!
Yo, Kasuka. What's up?
Bartender uniforms?
I don't think you should change jobs too much.
I've got a lot of them so you could keep doing this forever.
Thanks. Well, I'll do my best!
Just then...
Dammit!
Izaya!
I got screwed over by that little insect...
and he disappeared from 'Bukuro.
They figured out that I was innocent soon enough, and I was acquitted. However...
I'm sorry. I couldn't keep my promise.
Shizuo-chan.
Tom was a year ahead of me in middle school,
and he asked me to help him collect debt money.
Well, I was really only his bodyguard.
At first I wasn't into it, but Tom-san...
We don't even have to really threaten anyone.
When the people in 'Bukuro hear the name "Hewajima Shizuo,"
none of them would dare to refuse us.
He told me that, but just then Kasuka started getting busy,
and I stopped seeing him.
I wonder if he was mad at me.
What's that?
Yuhei!
Yuhei! He's so cool!
Yuhei-san! Over here, please!
I don't know why, but I felt better after that.
Although, I'm still working with Tom-san.
Repayment deadline?
I don't understand such hard concepts. We do as we please.
That's right. School and society, they're all wrong.
They've all got darkness in their hearts!
Hey.
I'm telling you, I don't get it.
Go away, old man.
This "old man" is doing his job.
What're you looking at?
Hey!
Why's he dressed that way?
Idiot. He's a butler, a butler.
Haven't you guys heard of Shizuo?
Who's that? Is he famous?
Are you? Butler-san?
Whoops! Can you get me another one, Butler-san?
I can't believe you're in 'Bukuro and you don't know who Shizuo is.
You must really be carefree.
These clothes... These are the clothes I got from my brother...
Even so, I still don't like violence.
I want to get stronger.
Strong enough so that I can suppress my anger.
For some reason, I feel better after talking to you.
Really? I'm glad.
This place has always bugged me, and I don't know why.
Yeah. I heard rumors about it, so I was worried about you.
Really? Sorry to worry you.
Shut up. I'll see you later.
Even though I like to keep my distance from people, I can't be alone.
Which is why I always try to stay in touch with someone.
Tom-san, Kasuka, and...
She's just like me.
She must also need someone.
Yo.
Shizuo.
Hey.
Puberty is over? Then you eat sushi, yes?
Sushi is good. Tasty!
Some other time.
Izaya? Is that so. I thought something stunk!
It was you!
What is he doing?
What is he planning to do in this town this time?!
Dammit!
Izaya!!
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time on
Durarara!!
Nanka's Dream
I have a dream.
It's always the same recurring dream.
Do I sleep when the other one is awake,
and does it close its eyes when I awaken?
Next time: Nanka's Dream.