When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Since when? You're lying, right?
Itsu kara uso desho itsu kara
Donna fuu ni dou yatte doko made shitteru no?
Since when? How did you do it and how far did you go?
Watashi ni wa nai mono motteru no?
Does she have something I don't?
Souzou bakari ga fukurami dashiteru
These constant imaginations just keep increasing...
Everyone!
Thank you for coming today!
Well, here's the last song!
I-It can't be.
E-Eichi-kun?
Your dream of being a singer...
...it came true, huh?
Y-Yeah.
And yours?
Yep.
That's great!
Mitsuki.
I... love you.
Eichi-kun...
Eichi-kun!
A dream?
Eichi-kun?
I Want To Sing
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Yes...very soon...
Sou sugu ni
I'll be fine, right?
Sure.
The night sky stretches so far
Konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Sou sugu ni
Yes... very soo-
It hurts...
Mitsuki-san.
How many times have I told you to stop doing that.
Music is such a vile thing.
It reminds me of your parents.
It makes me feel bad.
I'm very sorry.
But I...
Don't talk back!
Okay...
Has your fever gone down?
Yes.
Is that so?
That's good.
Dr. Wakaouji is here to see you.
(In this context, -sensei means Doctor)
Come out to the kitchen.
Wakaouji-sensei!
Sorry for calling you in during your vacation.
No, no.
Please don't worry about it.
So, how's her health?
She seems to be doing much better this morning.
Really?
Good morning, Mitsuki-chan.
Good morning!
It seems like your tumor's swelled up a bit.
Is it okay if I apply treatment on it?
Yes, please.
All right, all done!
Thank you very much.
Um... Wakaouji-sensei.
What is it, Mitsuki-chan?
Can you pretend that you're
taking me to the hospital today?
You need an excuse to get out of the house, huh?
So, where do you plan on going?
Ta-da!
Seed Records' Debut Artists Audition!
Notification of Passing the First Review!
Huh?
I'm keeping it a secret from Grandma, so...
No way.
Aww...
You just had a fever yesterday and
had to leave school early, right?
You have a tumor in your throat.
As your doctor, I can't allow you to do that.
But I finally managed to get past the first review...
In your current condition...
...you can't sing in a loud voice, can you?
You can think about auditioning
after your throat gets better.
Mitsuki-chan.
While the tumor is still small, let's try an operation.
I don't want any surgery.
Because...
I might lose my voice, right?
That's because of its location.
I can't guarantee that it won't happen.
If that's the case...
...I don't want to be operated on.
Sensei...
What's even more terrifying than dying...
...is not being able to sing for the rest of my life.
That's why...
I'm sorry.
Mitsuki-chan...
Um... it's about Mitsuki-chan...
About her operation...
...could you possibly convince
her to go through with it?
I've already suggested it time and time again.
But...
...she still refuses to listen.
For heaven's sake.
She's just as stubborn as my late daughter was.
She is unable to give in!
I see...
Another failure...
I wonder if I'll have to wait
until my throat gets better...
Mitsuki...
Let's make a promise.
Until we meet again...
...we'll work hard to reach our dreams.
For me, it's to become an astronomer.
And you, a singer.
Okay?
It's a promise.
But...
...just when will that happen...
...Eichi-kun?
All right.
W-Who are you?
How'd you come out of the wall?
This one, huh?
Kouyama Mitsuki, age 12.
Huh?
Why does he know my name?
Wait a minute, Takuto.
A-Another one came out!
Were you trying to lose me?
Who are these people?
Because you're too slow.
Hey there.
Is that the attitude you should
have towards your elder?
You don't have to bring up your
seniority all the time, you know?
What?!
E-Excuse me.
Who might... you be?
You... can see us?
Yup.
W-W-W-Why can she see us?!
Humans who are still living
shouldn't be able to see us, right?!
You're kidding...
But...I can see you.
What do we do in a situation like this?
If it's come to this, we have no choice.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
It's absurd to remain unknown
when our cover is blown.
(Shinigami: Gods of Death)
We are the Shinigami, the ones who silence the tears of children.
Takuto!
Meroko!
Together we are...
...Spring Onion Ramen!
You call yourselves Spring Onion Ramen!
Sounds tasty!
Takuto...
I really can't stand our duo's name.
It sounds so good!
Deal with it.
Our chief chose it after all.
Bunny ears and kitty ears.
So soft...
These are used for treating children...
Treating children?
Shinigami have kids, too?
Eh...kids?
Now that I think about it, if you're Shinigami...
Did you come to pick me up?
That's what we're here for.
You're not supposed to say that!
It's too late for that.
Am I going to die today?
Just pretend you didn't hear that.
You're not supposed to die for one more year.
One more year?
Is it because...
(Mitsuki has a cancer of the throat called Sarcoma)
...my cancer gets worse?
Well, that's probably why.
Ah... sorry.
Please, don't cry.
She's not crying.
Well, while we have the chance...
Let's see...
In times like this...
Um...
Here...
Actually...
...there are people who are
trying to prevent your death.
Then...
...I'm not going to die?
No.
That's forbidden.
Fate cannot be altered.
I see.
If I only have one year left to live...
...I can't hesitate any longer.
Hey, Takuto...
Going on and on and on and on...
...just what are you trying to do?!
I'm going to report this to the chief.
It doesn't matter, does it?
Besides, we've already been seen.
So what  if another year passes, she...
Huh?
Where'd she go?
Takuto, over there!
Wait, little kid!
Stop right there!
Hey, you!
Wait up!
Taxi!
Goddamn it!
Just when I had almost caught up to her!
Get out of the way!
I-Idiot!
Shinigami-san, thank you.
I'm going to take the audition now.
If I only have a year left...
...I'll definitely become a singer before then.
Is this the place?
This is it, Eichi-kun.
The promise we made...
... I'll keep it for sure!
Where'd she run off to?
We thought she was a good girl, so...
...we let her get away.
Oh, she's over there!
Really?
I wonder what she's doing?
Does it matter?
Hey, wait.
If you just go up to her like that,
she'll just run away again.
Heh, I know that.
Geez.
Why won't it open?
Is there a key around somewhere?
I can get in through there!
All right!
I'll have to get up there then!
Yep!
They're so cute!
What are these?
I wonder if they're decorations?
They seem a little... out of place.
We caught you.
Ah... Sh-Shinigami-san.
It's troublesome for us when
you go running off like this.
Now, be a good girl and come
back to the house with us.
Yep, yep.
P-Please wait a minute!
I want to go through the audition!
I don't want to just go home like this!
Then...
...why were you trying to go in from there?
That's right.
Why don't you just go in through the front door?
I can't...
...because I don't look like I'm sixteen.
Do I look like I'm sixteen?
Well...
...no, not really.
So I should...
...go up through here after all.
Let go, stupid! It's dangerous!
What if you get hurt?
But...
...if I don't hurry, the audition will be over.
I... have to become a singer-
Did something happen?
Talking... loudly...
I can't...
My throat...
Then, isn't it impossible for you to audition?
But...
Please...
...if I only have one year left to live...
...please, at least let me audition.
If I fail...
...I'll be a good girl and listen to you.
So...
...please!
You're serious about this, huh?
I get it.
I'll make you sixteen years old.
And then, as long as you are sixteen...
...I'll make it so that your body is healthy as well.
Take it.
On my command...
...that will begin spreading inside your body.
You'll feel weird, but...
...you'll just have to endure it.
That's a good girl.
You can't feel the difference?
Check yourself over there then?
Wow!
I'm really sixteen years old!
Thank you, Shinigami-san!
It was nothing...
Thank you so much!
Hey!
Get away from Takuto!
Are you satisfied?
Well... I want to try dying my hair, too.
What are you doing, Takuto?
What?
You're disobeying orders from above...
...by letting a human know the truth.
If they find out, you'll be in for it.
Well...
You couldn't have...
With that girl...
Huh?
No!
Takuto is mine!
I'll never let you have him!
Since when  did I belong to you?
Don't worry.
It's not like that.
Huh?
If she still has regrets in this world
...then, when she dies...
If she refuses to come with us, it'll be a problem.
I guess that's true, but...
...what are you going to do if she makes it?
That'll just leave her with even more regrets.
It'll be fine.
There's no way she can make it just like that.
After turning sixteen and going through an audition...
...only to fail and face reality...
...she won't have a shred of regret left...
Wow...
Only really cute girls are here.
I wonder if I look too plain?
Everyone's staring at me.
I wonder if I look too strange?
Maybe I'm out of fashion....
Can I... sit next to you?
Um...
...sure.
You... what agency are you from?
Agency?
You're not part of any theatrical
group or a recording agency?
Yeah.
It couldn't be that if I'm not part of an agency...
...I won't be able to make it?
It's really unfortunate, but it's
probably impossible for you.
This is just between us.
They've already decided on who they're selecting.
What?!
Then, why are we auditioning?!
I-I'm very sorry.
Sorry.
Wasn't that scary?
Why is that?
This audition gets...
...lots of coverage on the
morning news and on talk shows.
With all the attention...
...she'll receive from those watching
her get chosen on television...
...she'll become famous.
Is that so..?
You... already knew that...
Sorry.
Now, what you've all been waiting
for, the judging is about to begin.
Bye, then.
Please come in when your number is called.
To start, will Number 1 please come in...
I see...
So that's how it is.
I feel kinda... let down...
I thought this was a world based
more on talent than anything else.
Don't say that you want to be a singer...
...ever again.
Grandma's always discouraged me.
You should wait until your throat
is better before you audition.
Wakaouji-sensei tried to stop me, too.
You have one more year until you die.
One more year.
Why...why am I here for?
Eichi-kun...
Number 21.
Number 21, please come in.
I'm Number 21, Kouyama Mitsuki.
Pleased to meet you.
What genre of music do you like?
I like... Japanese pop.
If you become a singer...
...is there anything in particular you'd like to try?
Well...
Anyways, I'd just want to sing...
...since I love singing.
Why don't you sing for us then.
Cue the music.
If she's going to be nervous...
...there's no way she'll make it.
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Zutto egaiteta...
the dream that I...
Wait, stop for a second.
Your voice is too soft.
Sing with a louder voice.
Eh... louder?
Is something wrong with your throat?
Does it hurt?
I guess it's impossible for you to sing then.
Impossible...
It really was... impossible....
Please excuse me!
Are you just going to run away?
Shinigami-san!
Your throat is fine...
Sing.
You love to sing, right?
You really enjoy singing, Mitsuki.
Me, too.
I love hearing you sing.
That's right...
I'm very sorry.
Can you please let me try one more time?
Um... sure.
Cue the music, then.
It's fine if it's painful...
No matter how much it hurts inside...
...whether it's pain...
...or love...
...they're all part of my dream!
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Zutto egaiteta yume
the dream that I have always been drawing
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
How would I, as I am right now...
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
...look to those young eyes I used to have?
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Wow!
ni
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
Se
I have such a loud voice!
i
ppa
ka
ga
It doesn't hurt at all!
I can sing in a voice like this!
ya
ku
Full Moon wo sagashite
and find the full moon
Full
Moon
This is fun!
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima ni watashi ni dekiru subete
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now
Day by Day
Day
by
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
I hold the past fate dealt and the hope tomorrow brings here in my heart
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain
More and more
More
and
more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
She...
Many Thanks for You!
Many
Thanks
for
You!
Um...
I'm done...
Call Miya!
Call Ishikawa, too!
Okay...
Nishida!
Send everyone else back!
We've decided on Number 21!
Okay!
Hey, what should we do about this?!
I've been chosen!
Today's audition is over.
Although previously expected...
...there will not be a third judging...
Takuto!
W-What should I do, Eichi-kun?
I made it!
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
Zutto egaiteta yume
Zu
the dream that I have always been drawing
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
I
How would I, as I am right now...
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
A
...look to those young eyes I used to have?
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
So
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
Se
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
Full Moon wo sagashite
Full
and find the full moon
Moon
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
I
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now
Day by Day
Day
by
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
Kyo
I hold the past fate dealt and the hope tomorrow brings here in my heart
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
I
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain
More and more
More
and
more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
Mo
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
Many Thanks for You!
Many
Thanks
for
You!
Preview
What have you done, Takuto?!
That girl made it, didn't she?!
Just be quiet... I don't know what happened.
It couldn't be that...
...you've fallen in love with that girl?!
I-It's nothing like that at all!
But it's no good.
That girl has someone named
Eichi-kun, whom she likes a lot.
She's becoming a singer...
...because of a promise with Eichi-kun.
W-What did you just say?!
That's just wrong!
It was because of something like that ?!
Next time on Full Moon Wo Sagashite:
The Promise With Eichi-kun
The Promise With Eichi-kun.
Look forward to it!