Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression...asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Ready...
Set...
Whoa... Kona-chan, you're amazing.
How come you don't join any sports clubs even though you're so athletic?
Well, if I join a club...
I won't get to watch anime during prime time.
Speedy Lady
Hey, Tsukasa, from which side do you eat a Choco Cornet?
Hm... from the head, I guess.
I see.
By the way, which side is the head?
The fat side or the skinny side?
I think the skinny side is the head.
I thought the fatter side was the head.
But why's the skinny side the head?
Because it's kind of like a shell, I guess...
Why do you think the fat side is its head, Kona-chan?
I guess it's kind of like a caterpillar.
A caterpillar!?
But now that you mention it, I guess the shell fits its image better.
U-um...
You could also tear pieces off the skinny side and use them to eat the chocolate that squirts out.
I see.
You're really smart, Miyuki-san.
W-Well, everyone can eat it how they choose.
How do you eat a cream puff?
Huh? A cream puff?
Let's see... First, I'd split it in two.
And dip the top half into the cream in the bottom half.
When I'm done with the top, I'd eat the bottom.
That way, the cream won't squirt out.
And then you can eat the crème and the choux proportionally.
Oh!
You know the kind that has custard and whipped cream in it?
How do you eat those?
Do you mix them?
No, I actually wouldn't mix those.
But how would you mix them?
I dunno... I just thought I'd ask you.
When do you eat the strawberries on top of a strawberry shortcake or the chestnut on top of a Mont Blanc cake?
Let's see... It depends on the amount of strawberries that are in between the two spongy areas of the cake.
Strawberry, whipped cream, sponge cake...
I try to think of the proportions of the volumes when I eat it.
So, when it comes to eating the strawberry on top, it depends on the situation.
Hm... that sounds pretty foolproof.
I usually save it until the end.
But sometimes, I get full and I can't finish it,
or my family members eat it before I do.
You really have to eat the best first.
Now that I think of it, I've never seen my sister get her strawberry taken from her.
That's Kagami for you... Totally cautious.
Can you eat the last bite of a popsicle without dropping it?
You drop them?
Well, if you don't eat it properly...
It'll fall.
Say, Kona-chan, how do you eat it?
I lick it all.
Is that so...
How about if you spin it like this while eating it?
That's a good idea!
I actually don't like soft-cream that much.
Huh? Why not?
I don't like how I'm always stuck with the cone when I'm done.
Yeah, you'll always get stuck with the cone.
I push the soft cream down as I go.
How do you push it in?
While you eat it, you kind of just go *gui gui* and push it in.
*gui gui* ...is it?
Yuki-chan, you put a big emphasis on balance, don't you?
I guess so...
Then, what do you do with curry rice?
Do you mix the rice with the curry?
No, I don't mix them, but I try to eat them evenly.
I just mix it.
How about you, Kona-chan?
It all depends on the curry.
If I poured sauce on top or dropped a raw egg on it, I'd probably mix it.
Sauce on curry?
Yeah, it's really good.
Do you put sauce on sunny-side up eggs?
Nope, I put soy sauce on sunny-side up eggs.
Really? I put mayonnaise on it.
Not just on hard-boiled eggs, but on sunny-side up eggs, too?
Yep... Mayonnaise goes with most egg dishes.
Do you put it on curry, too?
Yeah... I put it on white rice and stuff like beef bowls, too.
It goes really well with the sweet sauce.
I put it on oyako-don, as well.
Chicken and egg are like relatives, right?
So I put mayonnaise on it since it's made from eggs and call it a "family bowl."
Hm...
And although I'm not too fond of natto, if I put mayonnaise on it, I can eat it.
Ugh... I can't imagine that.
Ah, but I think mayonnaise goes best on soft-boiled eggs.
I don't fully cook my sunny-side up eggs, either.
My dad really likes it this way.
He said he also likes to pop the yoke and let it ooze out like this.
Therefore, if you overcook it, it won't ooze properly.
How do you eat yakitori?
What do you mean?
Do you eat it while it's on the skewer?
Or do you take it off the skewer first with your chopsticks?
Let's see...
If I'm eating one by myself, I'll just eat it off the skewer.
If I'm sharing one with a group, I'll take it off with my chopsticks.
Yeah, yeah.
And isn't it awkward when there's one piece left?
Yeah, it's really hard to eat that last piece.
Time passes by as no-one touches it...
And it starts to get dry and unpleasant, so it seems like no one's going to eat it.
But when the waiter comes to take it away, you say, "Wait, I'm still working on that!"
Or something like that.
Then in the end, you leave the store without eating it.
Such a waste, isn't it...
I kind of feel sorry for it.
Oh, don't you also feel sorry for the meat that gets burnt black and stuck on the grill when you grill?
When you're eating grilled meat, you have to cook it while talking to others, so it's a pretty difficult task.
Negi-tan shio cooks really quickly, so it really keeps you busy.
Yeah... And when you flip it over once, the other side is already cooked.
Flip it over?
Huh?
Salted beef tongue with onions?
Yeah.
You can't flip negi-tan shio over.
Oh... Really?
Because if you flip it over, the onions on the top will fall off.
Ah, I see.
For those, you just let the fire go through and cook it naturally.
I see...
I'll do that from now on.
So don't ever flip it over.
So that's how it works...
Yup.
Oh...
Ah.
By the way, the fat side or the skinny side... Which is the head of a Choco Cornet?
Huh!?
"I wanted to make her my slave"
Locked up for two months
That's so radical.
Haven't there been a lot of false imprisonment cases lately?
Where girls are made to call someone "Master" and stuff?
Hm...
But rather than being an issue with morals and stuff,
it seems like the guys just played too many ero-games or bishoujo games.
It's a common situation in those games, anyway.
Speak for yourself...
Wait. How do you know the contents of adult games,
Miss high school junior!?
First Semester Midterm Grades
Takara Miyuki
You're amazing... Always in the top tier.
Miyuki-san, do you have any weaknesses?
It's rather embarrassing...
But there are times when I just space out or get lost in my thoughts.
I've cut myself while using a slicer,
rushed too much and tripped on myself,
had my bag caught in a closing door...
Uwa!!?
Miyuki-san,
Miyuki-san, those aren't weaknesses... That's what we call moé.
Huh, moé...?
The klutzy girl.
What kind of image was going through Kona-chan's head?
Miyuki-san, you're really good-looking, so why are you wearing glasses?
You can only go for a certain type of guy with that look.
"Go for..."
Putting attractiveness aside, haven't you thought about changing to contacts?
I've heard that glasses can actually make your eyes worse.
Um, it's really embarrassing since I'm already in high school, but...
I'm scared of... contact lenses.
Or rather, putting things in my eyes.
I can't open my eyes underwater, either.
Damn... This girl's cute.
She's a real natural.
Hey, isn't that Miyuki-san?
Yoshimizu
Optometry
I wonder if she's here for an eye exam to get contacts.
Maybe she's just better off that way.
That looked like it hurt.
She's a real natural...
Oh? Kagami's absent today because of a cold?
Yeah, but it doesn't seem like she has influenza.
Well, I'm stupid, so I don't have to worry about catching something like that.
I've heard of colds, but being stupid works against influenza, too?
Kasukabe Exhibition Hall
Huh? A cold and influenza are different?
I just thought it was an upgraded version of a cold.
I-I don't think so...
But now that you mention it, I'm not sure anymore.
Huh? The difference between influenza and a cold?
Yep, yep.
Let's see...
Influenza is transmitted via a virus.
High fevers, sore muscles and fatigue are common symptoms,
and there's the chance that you can have multiple symptoms at once.
On the other hand, symptoms of the common cold usually include a swollen throat or runny nose, and fevers aren't as high.
There are also some other minute differences.
Hm...
Therefore, they are two different illnesses.
I see.
B-But...
...there are some overlapping symptoms, so I guess you could call it the upgraded version of a cold...
I see!
Kona-chan, why the long face?
Well, it's nothing big, but I was just thinking about the conversation we had this morning.
Hm? The one about the cold and influenza?
Tsukasa, you didn't deny it when I said I was stupid...
N-No! That's not what I meant...
Konata-chan, welcome.
She came to visit Onee-chan.
Why, thank you for coming all the way over.
Sorry for the intrusion.
Kagami... You've got a pretty cute face when you sleep.
What are you doing here!? Go home!!
Hey... You woke up.
Visit?
You?
You came all the way over here to see me?
That's right.
But I don't want to give it to you or anything, so I'll just accept the thought.
Aw, how nice.
There's the new virus that's circulating, so she was probably worried about me.
I thought that she only cared about games and anime, but... I'm a little touched.
Well, I also wanted to see the homework that was assigned the other day...
And I got to see a pretty good sleeping face, so don't mention it.
Go home!
Kagami, Miyuki-chan came to visit you.
All right.
Sorry to intrude.
Sorry to make you come over on your holiday.
Is it okay for you to be up like that?
This is for you.
Thanks.
I'm a lot better now.
My fever's gone down after I took some medicine, too.
Here.
Wa... I'm so happy to get flowers and fruit.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
I was going to come visit you with Izumi-san and the others, but I was busy that day.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, I have some documents from the Student Council meeting.
Thanks!
If you could just take a look at them, I'd appreciate that.
Sure.
Also, here are the budget sheets for some clubs, and...
If I'm making your cold worse, I'll just go home now.
This is what a visit should be like...
D-Did something happen?
The thing is, Konata came by yesterday.
And geez...
Well, maybe that's Izumi-san's way of showing that she cares.
About the homework thing,
maybe she was just doing it to humour you and make you feel better.
And the sleeping face ordeal may have been inevitable... Her way of being considerate and not causing a ruckus.
C-Can this woman only think positively!?
I couldn't even come up with scenarios like that.
Speaking of which, Tsukasa-san isn't here today?
Mornin'...
Onee-chan, do you feel any better?
As you can see, she's a lot more laid back than a sick person.
U-Um...
I'm not usually like this, but I was up until dawn...
But welcome!
I understand.
Lately, I've been having trouble waking up myself.
Yeah, don't you feel sleepy lately?
Since today is especially warm.
Yep, yep... So true.
There's nothing we can do about it.
You know how our other holiday was really warm, too?
Yeah.
When I woke up, the sun was already setting.
I slept that whole day.
You should rest while you can.
I was in my pajamas all day that day.
I guess I'm in my pajamas right now, too.
Those things you're wearing right now; those are you pajamas?
Yep, that's right.
They're so cute.
They don't look like pajamas at all.
Really?
Truly.
Do you think I can just stay looking like this?
Sure.
You could even walk outside.
I wonder if I can go to the convenience store.
There seems to be no end to this stupid conversation.
Nurse's Office
I gained weight...
No, that's not it.
Today's bra has wires and a little extra padding, so that must be it.
Hm... I wonder how many grams it is.
If I subtract it, then...
Nurse's Office
It's over.
I totally forgot today was the physical exam,
so I wore my character printed underwear.
How embarrassing...
Nurse's Office
I haven't grown at all.
Damn you... you're the only one that looks secure!
Yo!
I'm here.
Ah, Onee-chan.
I was wondering...
Hm?
Kagami, you come here often... Don't you have any friends in your own class?
Don't compare me to yourself.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
And here, I thought you were an outcast.
Shouldn't you be worrying about yourself since you have no social skills?
You don't have to worry about that.
I may look like this, but I've got almost a hundred friends,
and my social and bartering skills are pretty high.
I even join parties every night.
Huh?
With my party members, I restored the glimmering crystals so the world wouldn't end,
And one time we saved the kidnapped princ-
Hey, you're talking about a game, aren't you!?
But I haven't seen that person lately...
Who?
Probably a friend she has in the game.
Yep, he's a warrior-class character.
He said he was going to go level up his combat skill,
so he went to an area with lots of monsters, but I haven't seen him since.
Hm?
Another person told me he's camping out in an underground cave.
Everyone's wondering if he's okay... He's locked himself up in there and hasn't come out.
He's isolating himself in a game?
I'm not too sure about the details, but based on the login info, it seems like he's been logged on the entire time.
So he has no life, physically and virtually!?
Well, it's the same person controlling his character.
Speaking of which, Tsukasa and Konata, how did you two become friends?
Tsukasa was about to get kidnapped by a huge foreigner,
but right at that moment, I appeared.
I saved her using my jabs and gracefully executed a whirlwind kick,
saving her from certain danger.
Why do you always start talking about games halfway through a conversation?
Well, in reality, I just exchanged fists with an experienced fighter.
I'm not so sure about resorting to violence right away, but you've got some good points.
The truth is, a foreigner was trying to ask me for directions, but I had no clue what he was saying,
and that's when Konata appeared.
Wha-!? And you tried to pick a fight with him?
This season has come again...
Is something wrong?
Nah, I was just thinking about how it's baseball season again.
You don't watch sports?
You're so athletic, so I could imagine you watching things like that.
Well, when they go into overtime...
The later programs get bumped down and my recording times get all screwed up.
In the worst cases, the show disappears altogether.
It doesn't feel good when something you like disappears, does it?
Kagami, when do you eat the strawberry on a strawberry short-cake?
Huh, why?
I was wondering if you were the type that saved the best for last.
It's true. I do tend to save my favorites until the end,
but eating the strawberry really depends on how I feel at the moment.
Then do you cook negi-tan shio on both sides?
Salted beef tongue with onions?
Well, it cooks pretty fast as it is,
but I guess it'll cook even faster if I flip it over.
You shouldn't do that!
The onions will fall.
Huh? You don't put the onions on top after they're done cooking?
If you do that, then the onions will be raw.
Well, the onions are just for flavor, aren't they?
You just don't get it...
Well, maybe you can do it either way?
Ah.
Do you think the head of a Choco Cornet is the fat side or the skinny side?
The fat side?
Hey, that's what I think.
Wha... Really?
Then which side do you eat it from?
I tear the skinny side and use it to scoop the extra chocolate.
Oh...
Yeah.
Have you ever made any real friends other than us?
I think I had a really close friend when I was in middle school.
Whoa... You did?
I haven't talked to her in a while, but I wonder what she's doing right now...
In middle school, she wrote that her dream was to become a mage.
So she was just like you!
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
It's begun! Lucky Channel!
We're finally on TV!
For those of you who are watching for the first time, hello!
I'm the navigator, Kogami Akira.
Ah, I'm Shiraishi.
Who...?
Just kidding!
From here on, this person is going to be my helper.
Shiraishi Minoru-san!
Panpaka pa~n!
U-Uh... I'm going to be Akira-sama's assistant.
I'm Shiraishi Minoru. Nice to meet you.
Shiraishi-san, you're so tense.
It's our chance to be on TV, so loosen up!
I-I'm sorry... I'm not used to it.
Now, let's get down to business.
We've got some postcards from our viewers.
O-Oh, right.
This one's from Beriko-Lover-san from Osaka.
"Congratulations on the TV show debut of Lucky Channel!"
Thank you~!
"I have a question for Akira-san."
"I understand you're an uber-idol, Akira-san, but how much do idols make?"
"Please tell me."
Salary?
Yes.
This seems like a very direct question.
You know...
What are you gonna do after you find out?
A-Akira-sama?
If you really wanna know, I'll tell you.
To be quite honest, it could be anything.
There are times where the pay itself is pretty cheap.
But I guess it's like a kickback from the management office.
My position's fixed, so I'm not exactly sure on the percentage they're keeping from me.
On top of that, I've been doing this since I was 3 years old,
so all of my pay is deposited into my parents' account.
All I get out of it is a puny allowance.
And I mean puny.
Now that I think about it... My mom's been sportin' some brand-name goods.
That isn't coming from my pay, is it?
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'm not Cinderella!
Just cuz dad's been holding back on his cash recently,
U-Uh, I don't think you have to tell them that much...
...doesn't mean you can start taking my money!
Oh, no!
It's time to say goodbye already.
Akira's so lonely.
So, this corner is for you guys to ask me questions or send me requests,
or let me know what you think of the show. Please~
Shiraishi-san, you say "please" for them, too!
O-Oh, well, then... Please watch us again next time.
See you again!!
By the way, is it true you're gonna be in the actual series?
Ah, where did you hear that from?
It's been a while since the four of us have gone out to karaoke.
I rarely come to places like this.
C'mon. We only got two hours, so let's sing, guys!
Don't worry. We've got plenty of time.
I'm so excited.
It's really fun!
It feels good when you sing your heart out.
Hey, where's the catalog?
Catalog?
Yeah, the catalog.
The catalog?
You know, the thing with all the songs and their numbers 'n stuff.
Oh, this?
Yes.
Well, then. I'll start it off.
Whoa. You already put three songs in?
It's such a waste if you don't sing.
Nah, ah, ah... Test, test, test.
What's this song?
"Uchuu Tetsujin Kyoudain!"
You always have to start off with this song!
Never heard of it.
Da-da da-da-da-da Dada sei no
ダッダッダダダダ　ダダ星の
Da-da-da-da-da Da-da planets,
Kona-chan, go for it.
Hey, turn down the volume!
Chikyuu goudatsu ROBOT gun
地球強奪　ロボット軍
Robot Army high-jacking the world.
Turn it down, I said!!
Tobe tobe aniki Sukaizeru
とべとべ　兄き　スカイゼル
Fly fly big brother, Skyzel!
How does she know these songs?
Hashire otouto Guranzeru
走れ　弟　グランゼル
Run little brother, Granzel!
SCRUM tetsu no ude to ude
スクラム鉄の腕と腕
Scrum, Iron arm.
Pachitto hibana no dai ginga
パチッと火花の　大銀河
Sparks fly into the great galaxy.
Go Go JET
ゴー　ゴー　ジェット
Go go jet!
Go Go CAR
ゴー　ゴー　カー
Go go car!
Uchuu Tetsujin Kyodain
宇宙鉄人　キョーダイン
Space Ironman Kyodain!
Preview
And for next week's Lucky Star...
Konata here.
Sleepy~
Why is it that when I think I get plenty of sleep the night before, I still feel really sleepy the next morning?
There's no reason for sleeping a lot.
「Effort and Results」
Next week: Effort and Results
Look forward to it!