Einzbern Castle,   Germany
— Eight Years Ago —
Kiritsugu-sama!
Your child is born.
She's so adorable...
So small, so delicate...
Look, Kiritsugu.
Her eyes are just like yours.
I'm so glad she was born.
Iri.
I will... cause your death.
I know.
It's the earnest wish of the Einzberns and the very reason I exist.
I am who I am now because I learned of
your ideals and took your prayers to heart.
You've guided me.
You've given me a life a mere puppet wouldn't have.
You need not pity me.
I'm already a part of you.
So-
I...
I have no right...
...to hold that child.
Kiritsugu, don't forget.
A world where no one needs to cry that way...
Isn't that your ideal, your dream?
Eight more years, and your fight will come to an end.
And our ideal will become reality.
I'm sure the Holy Grail will save you.
So take this child, Ilyasviel, and hold her.
And be proud.
Just like any father would.
Torino,     Italy
— Three Years Ago —
Command Spells?
Yes, the marks that appeared on your right hand.
It is proof that you have been chosen by the Holy Grail.
A stigmata, bestowing you the power to command a Servant.
Kotomine Kirei-kun.
The Holy Grail War...
The battle for a device that can perform miracles...
And I've been chosen?
Normally, the Grail chooses seven Magi as Masters to the Servants.
It's highly unusual for someone like you, with
no connection to magic, to be chosen so early.
Servants...
I still think it's strange to summon and
command Heroic Spirits to fight for you.
I know it's hard to believe.
Heroes from every age and nation are resurrected to kill each other and prove their supremacy.
That is the Holy Grail War.
Naturally, there is an unspoken agreement that battles are to be fought in secret.
To ensure this, we of the Holy Church send a regulator over.
Can a member of the Church really act as a judge in a battle between Magi?
A member of the Mage's Association
would favor one party too much to be fair.
And so, like sixty years ago, your father will watch over our battle.
My father will be going to Fuyuki City?
But isn't there a problem with the judge
and a participant being related by blood?
Tokiomi-kun.
Let's get to the point.
Kirei, everything we've spoken of so far is already known to all participants.
But there's another reason why I've asked you and Tohsaka Tokiomi to come here today.
And what would that be?
Actually, many years ago, proof was found that the Holy Grail
that appears in Fuyuki City does not belong to the Son of God.
Indeed.
Otherwise, the order to retrieve it would've been given to us of the 8th Sacrament Assembly.
However, the Holy Grail in Fuyuki is too powerful to ignore.
It's an omnipotent wish-granting device, after all.
Who knows what disaster it could cause should it fall into the wrong hands?
Thus, it is best if we ensure that the Grail
at least falls into the right hands as a plan B.
The Tohsaka family are indeed Magi, but they also have a long history of friendship with the Church.
I can also vouch for Tokiomi-kun's character.
Moreover, his intentions for the Grail are clear.
To reach the Root.
That is the sole desire of the Tohsaka family.
However, both the Einzberns and the Matous have forgotten the wish we once shared.
I don't think I need to explain the case for the other Masters.
Who knows what dark plans they may have for the Grail?
So I'll be participating in the coming Holy Grail War to ensure Tohsaka Tokiomi's victory, then.
Of course, we'll act as enemies seemingly fighting over the Grail.
But beneath the surface, we'll work together to defeat the other five Masters and attain certain victory.
And there you have it, Kirei-kun.
You will be transferred from the Church to the
Mage's Association, where you will become my student.
The official orders have already been issued.
You will go to Japan and study magic,
and become a Mage strong enough to command a Servant in the Holy Grail War in three years.
Now then...
Any questions, Kirei?
Just one.
What exactly is the Grail's will in choosing its Masters?
The Grail prefers to choose Masters that need it the most.
Does that mean all the Masters have a reason to covet the Grail?
Not necessarily.
There have been cases where Command Spells appeared on individuals you wouldn't expect to be chosen.
I see, Kirei-kun.
Are you still baffled that you've been chosen?
I didn't expect him to give his consent that quickly.
My son would leap into the burning flames if the Church willed it.
To be honest, it's almost unsettling.
From his perspective, he's been dragged into a war that has nothing to do with him.
No, this just might be salvation to him.
His wife passed away only a few days ago.
A new place and a new mission might just be what Kirei needs to recover.
Fuyuki City,   Japan
— One Year Ago —
Aoi-san.
Kariya-kun, it's been a while.
Are you back from your business trip?
It was quite a long one.
Yeah, I guess.
Uncle Kariya!
Uncle Kariya, welcome back.
Rin-chan.
Did you buy me something again?
No, Rin! That was rude!
Here.
Thank you, Uncle!
I'm happy you like it.
Where's Sakura-chan?
Sakura's gone.
Aoi-san?
Well, Sakura is no longer my daughter or Rin's little sister.
She's gone to the Matou family.
Why?!
You know exactly why the Matou family would want children with Mage blood.
The Tohsaka family head decided to give our
ancient allies, the Matous, what they requested.
It wasn't my place to voice my opinion.
And you're fine with that?
When I married into the Tohsaka family...
When I decided to become a Mage's wife...
I was ready for something like this to happen.
And you're fine with that?!
It's wrong for a family bearing Mage blood
to expect the happiness of a normal family.
That's not true!
You wanted happiness when you chose him-
This is between the Tohsakas and the Matous.
You turned your back to the Magi world.
It doesn't concern you.
If you ever see Sakura, be nice to her.
She was always fond of you, Kariya-kun...
I'm surprised a failure like you would dare to show his face here.
I believe I told you to never let me see you again.
Kariya.
I hear you've adopted Tohsaka's younger daughter.
News reaches you quickly.
Are you really that desperate to preserve magical affinity in the Matou lineage?
You, of all people, are telling me that's wrong?
Whose fault do you think it is that
the Matou family has fallen so low?
Kariya.
Had you agreed to carry on the family name and learn the Matou secrets, this wouldn't have happened.
Yet you...
Enough of this nonsense, vampire .
You just want the Grail to gain immortality.
By next year, the sixty years will have elapsed.
But the Matou family has no pawns to offer for the 4th Holy Grail War.
Unlike you, your brother Byakuya
lacks the mana to control a Servant.
But even if we let this round pass, we can win the next one sixty years from now.
The Tohsaka girl's womb will produce a talented Mage.
She has quite the potential as a vessel, she does.
So basically, you'll have no use for
Tohsaka Sakura once you obtain the Grail?
What do you have in mind?
A trade, Zouken.
I will bring back the Grail in this coming war.
In return, you will release Tohsaka Sakura.
You're a fool.
You're a failure who hasn't trained a single day of your life.
You're saying you'll become a Master in the space of a single year?
You have the ability to make that
happen, with your bug-wielding skills.
Implant Crest Worms inside me.
Kariya, you want to die?
The Matous can fulfill their own desires by themselves.
I won't let bystanders get involved.
Don't tell me you're worried for me, Father?
If you're trying to keep her out of this, Kariya...
...you're a little late.
You old bastard, you can't have...!
She was crying pretty loudly for the first three days.
She stopped screaming on the fourth day, though.
I threw her into the bug room this
morning to see how long she'd last.
She's been ravaged for half a day, and she's still breathing.
The Tohsakas really aren't bad at all.
Sakura...
Well, what will you do?
A single broken girl, violated by bugs from head to toe.
If you still wish to save her...
I'll consider it.
I'll do it.
I'll continue educating Sakura until
you show me some results, though.
I'm still expecting victory to come in the Grail War after this one.
But if you do manage to somehow retrieve the Grail,
then I'll have no further use for the little girl.
In that case, her education will end after just one year.
You won't go back on your word, will you, Matou Zouken?
Start by serving as the bugs' breeding ground for a week.
If you don't die of madness, then I'll
recognize that you're serious about this.
It's finally here.
What kind of information?
It's a report from the spies I sent to the London Clock Tower.
It says the Grail chose a Master from within the highest authority of the Mage's Association, the Clock Tower.
Who?
A troublesome man.
The eldest son of the famous Archibald family, which produced nine generations of Magi.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald.
Clock Tower,    London
— Present Day —
In the Magi world, bloodline largely determines one's ability.
This is because the secrets of magic
cannot be discovered in a single generation.
A parent passes on the result of a lifetime of training to their child.
Therefore, the older the family of Magi, the greater their authority.
If you're wondering why I'm covering something so elementary,
it's because a student submitted this paper to me a few days ago.
The paper is titled "How Wizardry Should Be in the New Century".
It completely rejects the standard model I've just talked about.
It states that a deeper understanding of
spells and more delicate control over mana
would allow one to overcome this handicap.
In other words, even someone with
thin blood could become a master Mage.
To be honest, I've learned something from reading this.
Quiet.
Let me be as plain as I can.
This paper contains nothing but juvenile fantasies.
Bloodline determines a Mage's power.
This is a hard, unchanging truth.
Waver Velvet-kun.
I'm very, very disappointed that one of my students would indulge in this nonsense.
But sir, I was only trying to address a question the Mage's Association is reluctant to-
Waver-kun.
Your family has only produced three generations of Magi, correct?
Listen to me.
Your family is but a newborn baby compared to the history of the Mage's Association.
Shouldn't a baby learn to talk before questioning his parents?
How dare he make fun of me!
How dare he!
Is that how a lecturer should act?!
He read my paper and got jealous!
He's afraid of my talent!
That's why he shamed me in front of everyone!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I-I'm fine.
Aren't you a student in the Necromancer's Circle?
Why aren't you in class?
Well...
P-Professor Archibald asked me to run an errand for him.
I was in a hurry, so...
I see.
That's great.
Can you give this to Professor Archibald?
This?
Thanks.
It's apparently something important.
Important?
It was sent from Macedonia...
This is it.
Those rumors that Kayneth would be fighting in
some kind of Far East magic tournament were true.
The Holy Grail War.
Two hundred years ago, the families known as the Founding Three,
Einzbern, Makiri, and Tohsaka,
worked together to successfully summon the
Holy Grail, said to have the power to grant any wish.
However, the Holy Grail would answer only one prayer.
And their cooperation turned into a bloody battle.
That was how the Holy Grail Wars began.
Ever since then, once every sixty years,
the Holy Grail appears in the city of Fuyuki.
It selects seven Magi with the right
to hold it and grants them the power
to summon the powerful Heroic Spirits known as Servants.
Archer.
Saber.
Lancer.
Rider.
Assassin.
Caster.
Berserker.
Divided into these seven classes, the Servants fight to the death to determine who is worthy to win the Grail.
So the Holy Grail War is a battle of pure ability, where titles and influence mean nothing.
It's the perfect stage for me.
It also says a relic of a Servant is needed, as a catalyst, to summon them.
A relic...
That device still strikes me as unseemly to this day.
I have a report from the Clock Tower.
Lord El-Melloi has acquired another relic, apparently.
His participation is certain now.
It troubles me that two spaces are still unaccounted for.
Don't worry.
The Grail will select seven individuals
when the time comes, regardless of skill.
The ones it completes the group with are nearly always weak.
There's no need to worry about them.
More importantly, Kirei.
No one saw you enter the mansion, correct?
Don't worry.
There are no familiars or magical devices, visible or invisible, that are watching this mansion.
I...
I guarantee it.
No matter what tricks they use, no one can deceive the eyes of Hassan, Heroic Spirit of strategems.
There is no trace of anyone following my Master.
Rest assured.
If a Servant is summoned, my father will know without fail.
The other Magi will not act for a while longer.
Assassin, you may go.
Continue guarding the surrounding area.
As you wish.
It's only a matter of time, however.
The grounds of this mansion will soon be rife with the familiars of the other Masters.
What's that?
Another matter.
I was gathering information on the Einzbern Master.
Nine years ago, the Einzberns, known for their pride in their pure blood,
welcomed in a Mage from outside the family out of the blue.
The Einzbern Magi specialized solely in
alchemy, making them unfit for combat.
That was why they lost in previous Holy Grail Wars.
They must have run out of patience.
The Mage they chose was perfect for the role.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
The man known as the Mage Killer.
The relic we've long been searching for in Cornwall has finally been found.
If you use it as a catalyst, you can summon a sword-wielding Heroic Spirit that is perhaps the strongest of Servants.
Kiritsugu.
This is the greatest aid the Einzberns can give you.
I am honored, Elder.
There are to be no survivors this time.
Slay the other six Servants and complete the third true magic, "Heaven's Feel".
Understood.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
I know that name.
So even the Church has heard of him?
Emiya, the Mage Killer, had quite the reputation in his time.
On the surface, he was a heretic that didn't belong to the Association.
However, the higher-ups found him quite useful for their own purposes.
Similar to us Executors of the Church?
Worse.
He's essentially a freelance assassin
who specializes in the killing of Magi.
He understands Magi very well, so he hunts them down in very non-magelike ways.
Read it.
Sniping.
Poisoning.
Bombing public places.
He brought down an entire jetliner just because his target was on it.
He is a man who will use underhanded methods without thinking twice.
The world's laws do not apply to Magi, so we
must carefully obey the laws we set for ourselves.
However, he lacks any trace of a Mage's pride.
His methods are unforgivable.
Well then, what does this Emiya Kiritsugu...
...hope to gain by killing?
Money, I would imagine.
As you can read in that report, Mage
assassinations weren't all he was involved in.
He's appeared in war zones all over the planet, offering his services as a mercenary.
May I borrow this report for a while?
Let's go over what we know, Iri.
Of the seven Masters the Grail will choose, we know four.
Tohsaka Tokiomi, the head of the Tohsaka family.
A fire Mage who uses jewel magic. A difficult opponent.
Matou Kariya.
So they took the kid who left the
family and made him a Master, huh?
That old man must be desperate.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald.
He has the double affinity of wind and water, and is
an expert in Necromancy, Summoning, and Alchemy.
And...
Emiya Kiritsugu.
Newest member of the Einzbern family and their trump card.
And the man I love.
And the fourth...
I mean, the fifth Master is Kotomine Kirei, agent of the Church.
The Church?
He's the son of the judge, Kotomine Risei the priest.
He studied under Tohsaka Tokiomi for three years,
but split with him after his Command Spells appeared.
Is something wrong?
This is his personal history...
Read it.
Kotomine Kirei.
Followed his father Risei on a pilgrimage since childhood.
Graduated from the St. Ignatius School of Divinity, in Manresa.
Skipped two years... and graduated as valedictorian?!
He's pretty impressive.
But he suddenly leaves the primrose path and volunteers for the Holy Church.
Why would someone like that work for
one of the Church's secret organizations?
Because of his father, maybe?
Look, it says he's a member of the Church's 8th Sacrament Assembly, like his father.
He would've pursued that path from the start, then.
Yet, until he arrived at the same place as his father, he changed positions three times.
He was even appointed as an Executor.
An Executor?
A heretic hunter.
Basically...
...what I used to be.
A Mage killer.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
His assassinations were always performed one after another over short periods.
During the same general time periods, he appeared in war zones,
but only when combat was at its fiercest.
It's as if he was obsessed with chasing death itself.
His actions were clearly suicidal.
What on Earth is this?
Alchemy. Necromancy. Summoning. Divination. Healing.
Look at all the types of magic he's studied.
Why does he try so hard?
He gets almost to the point of mastery, then
switches to another type without looking back.
It's as if he throws away everything he's learned like trash.
Iri.
This Kotomine Kirei frightens me.
The entire concept of self-interest is foreign to him.
His actions are completely removed
from any thought of risk versus reward.
There's no way he's just a freelancer who's in it for the money.
This man has never experienced passion in his entire life.
He doesn't believe in anything.
He doesn't have a single wish he'd want to be granted.
A man like that...
What could he be after, then?
Why would he risk his life for the Grail?
But the Grail chose Kotomine Kirei as one of the Masters.
That's right.
He must have some reason to covet the Grail.
But I have no idea what it could be.
That's what frightens me.
Kotomine Kirei.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
His endless string of battles came to a sudden halt nine years ago,
when he met the Magi of the North, the Einzberns.
So he basically found his answer then.
Then I must ask the question...
What did he seek in those battles?
And what did he find at the end?
You almost didn't make it.
The Grail's chosen you, which means it
recognizes you as a Mage to some degree.
I'll give you that much, Kariya.
But you know...
You look terrible.
Does your left leg still work?
Don't get mad.
The Crest Worms inside you will devour you if you excite them.
Either way, I'd say you'll only be living for another month at best.
That's plenty.
What?
I said that's plenty.
Kariya, I've found the perfect relic for you to reward you for lasting an entire year.
Don't let your father's kindness go to waste.
I've got Command Spells, too!
The Grail chose me!
The Grail acknowledged my ability!
I can't just sit around and be happy.
I have to prepare for the summoning of my Servant!
The sixth-grade girl who went missing in Fuyuki City two nights ago,
Fuyuki City
Serial Killings in Fuyuki City
News
Good morning, Waver.
Good morning, Waver-chan.
Miki Nishimoto, was found dead this
morning in the woods in Miyama district.
Morning, Grandpa, Grandma.
Fuyuki's pretty unsafe these days.
It really is.
Anyway, Martha, the roosters were really loud this morning.
What's going on?
There are three roosters in our yard.
In our yard?
That's right.
I wonder where they came from.
Waver-chan, would you like some coffee?
Waver-chan, what happened to your hand?
Crap!
That mark.
Mark?
That mark wasn't there yesterday.
Geez!
You notice the most unnecessary things...
Wh-What's wrong, Waver?
Waver-chan?
Nothing's wrong.
Come on, have some coffee.
I've put lots of milk in it.
Don't you both like coffee?
Must I really cast another spell to make them think I'm their grandson, back from being a foreign exchange student abroad?
I'll have to find an explanation for those roosters I stole, too.
I can't believe they actually found
the scabbard of the legendary sword.
There isn't a single scratch.
Is this excavated object really 1,500 years old?
The object itself is a type of Conceptual Weapon.
It doesn't rust or degrade like normal physical objects do.
Just like in the legends, it heals its bearer's wounds and stops them from aging.
Of course, that's only if it's supplied with the mana of its original owner.
In other words, it can be used in tandem with its summoned Heroic Spirit to protect its Master.
That's just like you.
A tool is always a tool, right?
That goes for Servants, too.
No matter how famous the Heroic Spirit, a Servant is nothing but its Master's tool once summoned.
Anyone who lets their fantasies get ahead of them will never emerge from this battle victorious.
And that's why my great grandfather decided that this scabbard was just the relic for you.
Is that so, I wonder?
Are you not satisfied with his present?
Of course not.
Acht did well.
I doubt the other Masters have a trump card this powerful.
What's wrong, then?
Given how perfectly connected the relic is to its owner,
the Heroic Spirit we're after will surely respond to the summons.
The legendary King of Knights, Arthur Pendragon.
How compatible I am with him is a secondary concern.
But as the wielder of Excalibur, surely he
must be the strongest Saber-class Servant.
Indeed.
I'll have a Servant far stronger than any other.
The question is how to use that power.
To be honest, in terms of ease of use,
Caster or Assassin would suit me a lot better.
What will you do if you're worried before even summoning him?
We don't know what the King of Knights was like.
What's more, no matter your tactics,
once he learns of your ideal, your dream...
I'm sure he'll understand.
Just like me.
What?
I figured out my strategy.
The best way...
...to use the strongest Servant.
Hello, Rin.
Hello, Kirei.
Heading out?
That's a lot of luggage you have there.
Yes, I'll be living with the Zenjou family from now on.
You're staying to fight along with my dad, right?
That's why I'm here as his student.
Kirei, can I trust you?
Will you promise me you'll protect my father until the very end?
That's impossible.
If the battle were simple enough that I could make that promise,
we wouldn't have to send you or your mom away.
I just can't like you, after all.
Rin, you shouldn't speak your thoughts like that.
People might start thinking bad of
your father, the one who raised you.
What does my dad have to do with this?!
Listen, Kirei!
I won't forgive you if my dad gets
hurt because you were slacking off!
Rin, what are you yelling for?
Um...
Uh...
She was giving me a pep talk before saying goodbye, Madam.
Let me help you.
That suitcase is too heavy for you.
It's fine.
I can carry it myself.
Kotomine-san, please take care of my husband.
Please help him achieve his wish.
I'll do my best. Don't worry.
Excuse me.
Excellent timing.
The relic I arranged for finally arrived this morning.
Look.
What's this?
The fossil of the first snake's skin ever shed in ancient times.
If we use it as a catalyst and manage to
summon what we're after, our victory is assured.
Hey, Sakura-chan.
Did I surprise you?
No, but your face...
Well, you know...
Looks like I lost a little to the worms inside me again.
I guess I'm not as tough as you are, Sakura-chan.
You're turning into a different person, aren't you?
Maybe.
I don't have to go to the bug room tonight.
Grandpa said there's going to be a more important ceremony.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I'm going to the basement tonight instead.
Uncle Kariya, are you going away?
I'll be pretty busy with an important job for a while.
I probably won't have much time to talk to you anymore.
I see.
Hey, Sakura-chan.
Once I'm done with my job, why don't
we all go somewhere and have some fun?
With your mom and sister?
I don't have anyone I can call my mom or sister...
Grandpa said I should think that they never even existed.
I see.
Uncle?
Let's take Aoi-san and Rin-chan from the Tohsakas, and go somewhere far away.
We can play together again, like we used to.
Will I really be able to see them again?
Yeah, you will.
I promise you that.
Well, I have to get going.
Okay.
Bye-bye, Uncle Kariya.
Bye-bye.
You've learned the summoning spell, right?
Yeah.
Very good, but I'll have you add two extra lines to the incantation.
What do you mean?
It's simple.
Kariya, your rank as a Mage is slightly below that of the other Masters.
This will affect your Servant's base stats.
That means we'll have to pick a class of
Servant that can raise those parameters.
Kariya, I want you to add the "Berserk" property to the Servant you summon.
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill!
Repeat five times.
But destroy each when filled.
A base of silver and steel.
A foundation of stone and the Archduke of Contracts.
An ancestor, my great master, Schweinorg.
A wall to block the falling wind.
The gates of all four directions close.
From the Crown, come forth and
follow the forked road to the Kingdom.
Is a simple ritual like this enough to summon a Heroic Spirit?
Surprisingly, yes.
Summoning a Servant doesn't require an elaborate evocation.
The Grail is what does the actual summoning.
As a Master, my job is to anchor the
Heroic Spirit to this world once it appears
and give it enough mana for it to take physical form.
This should be good.
Iri, place the relic on the altar.
Our preparations will then be complete.
I hereby propose.
Thou shalt come under my command,
and my fate shall be thy sword.
Abiding by the summons of the Holy Grail,
if thou dost accede to this will and reason, answer me!
I hereby swear.
I will be all that is good in the eternal world.
I will be the disposer of evil in the eternal world.
But let chaos cloud thine eyes.
Thou, who art trapped in a cage of madness.
And I, who doth hold thy chains!
Thou, the seven days clad in the Great Trinity,
come forth from the circle of constraint.
Guardian of the Heavenly Scales!
We've won this battle, Kirei.
Victory is ours!
Who...
I ask you.
Are you my Master?
Episode 1
Summoning of the Heroic Spirits
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
I think what you and Kiritsugu seek is right.
The world cannot serve two lords.
I promise you.
You are not worthy to gaze upon me.
You're so cool, man!
You are to promptly kill Tohsaka Tokiomi.
Next Episode
False Opening