saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
along with my food!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
gomennasai
but sorry for finding out!
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Getting lost in silly conversations
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Chatting about love and relationships
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
Say, why can't you make friends?
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You came right out and asked?!
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
iitai houdai ne
You two never quit!
mitsuba ga daibousou
The three leaves are on a rampage,
dare ni mo tomerarenai
and there's nobody who can stop them!
Why are you eating here too?
Hey, don't you have friends?
My, how direct!
She ended up crying
for some reason, though.
I wonder if something was wrong?
Huh?!
issei no mae mitekou
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
mae mae miteru
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
sannin yoreba monju no chie
Three heads are better than one!
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora going my way
Everything's going my way,
susumesou my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
Let's go full steam ahead
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
I'm living the best days of my life,
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
Futaba
Lady Youko
Teru
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
I'm sure that this is a
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
Three Leaves,
Three Colors
I'm starving!
Sorry I'm late!
Really, I swear!
Yes, that's right.
Not at all. It's my job
as class representative.
Hey, over there!
C'mon, hurry!
Coming through!
Oh, sorry!
I'm hungry! I'm so hungry!
I can't make it all the way
back to the classroom!
Shortcut time!
I'll wipe off my indoor shoes
when I'm done!
Wha—?
Hey, hey! Are those...
Th-These are... bread crusts!
These are bread crusts!
You still eat as much as ever, Futaba.
I guess. I'm going easy today, though.
Are you really?
Actually, I wonder how
you eat so little, Hayama-chan.
Is that enough?
My body is more efficient than yours.
Want to eat some of my side dishes?
Can I?! Yay!
You can have some too.
What is wrong with the two of you?
Why are you eating here too?
How bothersome!
Amazing!
You just said "bothersome"!
Wow, a real high-class girl!
All right. Go easy now.
H-Honestly, what is
the matter with you?
Oh, we haven't
introduced ourselves yet.
I'm Hayama.
I'm doing Class 3 the favor
of being their representative.
Doing them the favor...?
This Odagiri Futaba-chan
from the same class.
Nice to meetcha!
M-My name is Nishikawa Youko
from Class 2.
I know.
You're famous, you know.
What?! Famous?
F-Fine! Perhaps it was improper to tell a student not to touch me with her filthy hands.
I didn't hear about that.
And I am not hiding here while I eat
because everyone shuns me now.
Um, we weren't asking.
Hey, don't you have friends?
My, how direct!
I don't have anything
in common with people,
and I never know
what to talk about with them.
We're having
a nice chat now, aren't we?
Right?
Isn't this nice?
It's fun to eat outdoors.
U-Um...
Oh, the first bell.
Huh?
Oh, no!
I'm done!
See ya, Youko-chan.
Until next time.
Huh? U-Um...
Oh yeah, bread crusts are yummy
deep-fried and sprinkled with sugar.
Fry them and use sugar?!
I've never heard of that.
What kind of—
Hurry, let's go!
Our teacher is strict about punctuality.
We have English next, right?
Yup.
Did you do your homework?
What peculiar girls.
Still...
That may have been my first time having lunch with someone since I came to this school.
So this is their class?
I kinda got sleepy...
I so hear you!
Nishikawa-san?
What's she doing?
I made it in time for the sale again!
Bread crusts are yummy
deep-fried and sprinkled with sugar.
Um, do I have any sugar left?
All right, lunchtime!
You're getting pretty full of yourself!
Whatever could you mean, Nishiyama-san?
I know you badmouthed Kondou to the teacher yesterday!
All I did was deliver
the printouts to him.
Since Kondou-san didn't perform
her assigned duty for some reason.
What?!
A-Anyway, I've got
a bone to pick with you!
Let's step outside.
All right.
Don't go too hard on her.
I don't take orders from you!
Um, I was talking
to Hayama-chan, actually...
I wonder what they'll think!
Say, you two...
W-Well, I wasn't expecting
them to show up!
And now I can enjoy
my lunch alone, like usual.
Alone...
Aw, that sucked!
Futaba-san...?
You said you wanted
to take a shortcut.
Well, I didn't want
to keep Youko-chan waiting.
Hayama-san!
Sorry, Youko-chan.
Did you wait long?
Y-You're late!
Five whole minutes late!
I'm sorry. A troublemaker
picked a fight with me.
What?! Are you all right?
Yep!
She ended up crying
for some reason, though.
I wonder if something was wrong?
Huh?!
You don't wanna know.
What?
Who is it? A pervert?
Some kind of stalker?!
Yamaji!
Wait, you know him?
He's a former servant of my family.
I sincerely apologize!
Wha— Yamaji?!
I was laboring under a misapprehension.
I thought yesterday was just a fluke.
So he was here yesterday, too?
But I would accept a fluke!
After all, it's a miracle for Youko-sama
to make school friends!
Wh-What do you mean by that?!
As a mere shadow of the
rich young lady she once was,
who lost it all after the
family company went bankrupt,
but hasn't let go of her
upper-class attitude in spite of that,
it must be a miracle that she can
make friends with commoners at school!
O-Oh...
Th-That's not how it is!
Yamaji's exaggerating!
Please take care
of Youko-sama forever!
As her school friends!
Well, shall we eat?
Huh?
Hayama-chan...
E-Er, listen, my—
Isn't it nice to be outside?
It's so much fun to eat
surrounded by nature.
Um, my—
Oh, I knew you couldn't
really make friends!
Yamaji!
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
My, how awfully noisy they are!
I only want some peace and quiet
to enjoy a book during break time...
Those loud voices
aren't ladylike at all.
How can I even associate
with such people?
Hey, Youko-chan!
Hey!
Futaba-san!
Such a bright smile...
Wh-What is it?
Um, I kinda forgot
my math textbook.
Could I borrow yours?
My class doesn't have math today,
so I didn't bring it.
Aw, really?
Shoot...
I'm sorry!
In the old days, I would've sent a servant to fetch it at once!
Oh, no, don't worry about it.
Later!
Phew, I'm starving!
I'm sorry about before.
About the textbook?
No worries!
It's my bad for forgetting it.
And she hardly pays attention
in class anyway, book or no book.
Exactly!
Jeez, Hayama-chan, you say
the rudest things with no hestitation!
Oh? Did I not speak the truth?
Okay, lunchtime!
Down the hatch!
Wh-What is that?
Huh? It's white bread.
Never seen it before?
Of course I have, but why
are you eating a whole loaf?
It's too much work
to buy more than one thing.
That's the issue?
Are you having
bread crusts again, Youko-chan?
Yes!
Look how many you can get
for such a low price!
I was so moved
the first time I saw these!
But don't you need
more nutrients?
Not to worry!
Now they're perfectly nutritious!
Um, not really...
My poor Youko-sama!
Him again?!
Yamaji!
I'll have to call the police
if you keep trespassing.
Oh, I'm authorized to be here.
I refill the school vending machines.
It's a side job.
I see!
That's fine, then.
No, stalkers are not fine!
That's unfair!
What's stalker-like about lurking in the shadows and watching her every move?
Literally all of that!
I'm merely concerned for Youko-sama.
Shortly after I succeeded my late grandfather's position as servant, I was suddenly let go.
I'm so worried about how the young miss will handle life among the common folk,
I just have to keep an eye on her.
She has such an explosive temper,
and when she doesn't get her way,
it triggers a chemical reaction!
Yamaji!
Youko-sama, take these!
They're clearance items from my job, but they're not quite expired yet.
Wai— Yamaji...
Ah, I have to get to my next job.
Goodbye!
Huh?
If he pities you that much,
he should just give you money.
I bet he's barely
making ends meet, too.
Honestly, I can't believe him.
Does he think these will make me...
Egg
Pudding
M-Make me feel...
Youko-chan...
Drat!
Now I've embarrassed myself,
thanks to Yamaji.
I've finally made friends...
I have to make sure
I don't drive them away.
Youko-sama, here is
today's expired food.
Please, take it.
Why does he have to do this
during lunchtime?!
Th-Thank you.
I'll take my leave now.
Keep a cool head, Youko.
Don't jump for joy and
make them think you lack decorum.
How wonderful! Cheese!
Good for you, Youko-chan.
Yeah, cheese is healthy.
So, you two,
what are your favorite foods?
White rice.
Not bread?
Bread kinda feels like a snack.
I like rice better.
Then why not pack your own lunch?
No time in the morning.
What's your fave, Hayama-chan?
Me?
Why, it's mille-feuille!
Fine, I like salted fish paste! Got a problem with that?!
No, not at all...
Oh, yeah, that's good stuff!
Real good with rice.
What's yours, Youko-chan? Cheese?
I need to give an answer
they won't think is strange.
Something commoners would accept...
Right now, I like pudding!
Geh, pudding?!
But that'd be gross with rice!
With rice?!
A-Are normal people's favorite foods
things that pair well with rice?
I need a more proper answer...
H-How about pink codfish flakes?
You like them?
Mayonnaise!
At least that's the truth...
Are you sure you used to be rich?
Wh-What now?
At this rate,
they might start to hate me.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
They were so happy about
the fried bread crusts, after all.
Hayama-san!
Futaba-san!
Today...
I made rice balls!
I thought you and
bread crusts had a thing.
I can cook if I try!
Wow...
I don't know how to make them.
I wouldn't mind sharing,
if you'd like some.
She can't mean
balls of just rice, can she?
Erm...
It really is just rice.
You said you liked rice, Futaba-san.
R-Right!
Rice balls are
surprisingly complex, aren't they?
So many different possible fillings...
These don't have filling...
They don't?!
I wanted to use salted fish paste,
since Hayama-san likes it, but it was expensive...
For my sake?
But in rice balls...?
Putting the right amount
of salt in the rice is tricky too.
I forgot to add the salt!
D-Did I fail again?
I thought they'd be happy.
But now...
Let's dig in!
Thanks, Youko-chan!
I'm gonna have seconds.
L-Listen, please don't force yourself...
Rice is tasty, huh?
Hayama-san... Futaba-san...
Go on, Youko-chan, you gotta eat too!
You can have one of my sausages.
Thank you very much!
I'm having thirds!
Futaba!
Central Shopping Plaza
You really don't have to do anything for me in return...
Since we're... friends.. and all.
Don't be shy, Youko-chan.
Yeah, since we're friends!
They're free tickets anyway.
I have a family member
who always wins this stuff.
Oh, here we are!
Healing Waters
A bathhouse!
Nothing beats a bath
for us Japanese.
You said it.
And it smells so nice, too.
This is wonderful.
It's been so long since I could
stretch my legs out in the bath.
But...
To heat enough water
for such a big bath...
I shudder to imagine
their utility bills!
Just have fun!
Sorry. I lost control for a moment.
Healing Waters
To think they're even willing
to bathe with her...
I was so worried, but I think Youko-sama will survive!
Why don't you get out?
No, I can't waste
Hayama-san's kindness...
Stop worrying and have fun!
A-Another hour...
No, at least half a day!
You'll get dizzy!
You're gonna boil into Youko soup!
I can endure...
Youko-chan!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The vicious class rep,
the poor girl who lives on bread crusts,
and the walking black hole.
Their days lived in their own colors
are so entertaining!
Isn't it wonderful?
And now, please enjoy
"Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
nakami ga makkuro demo
Even if it's turned black inside
zeitaku dekinakutemo
Even if I can't be extravagant
ryou ga ookutemo
Even if there's too much to handle
sannin dakara tabechaou
Three's a crowd, so let's eat!
youryou yo ga kashikoku
I'm not wasting electricity at night
takumashiku ikitemasu wa
I'm leading a strong and healthy life
onaka ippai no mainichi nan desu
Every day, I'm eating 'til I'm full!
egao ni nareru mono
Things that make me smile?
gohan, okane, koko de wa ienai
Food! Money! And things I can't say
shiawase datte sansha sanyou
We're a happy bunch, living in our own colors
omou made tanoshimou, hachamecha na
Let's have fun and make silly memories
hora guuchoki parade, sannin atsumareba
When we're together, this Rock Scissors Parade
janken wa, aiko de, eien ni owaranai
Will continue forever in just the same way
hajimatta parade, kyousei sanka desu
This parade we've embarked on is wonderful
ichi kakeru san no kotae shiritai nara
If you want to know the answer to one times three
nee koko ni oide
Then come on over here
And so my tumultuous school life began.
This new dog-eat-dog world is full of trials,
like figuring out how to spend break time!
But from now on,
I won't eat lunch alone!
raaain
Shall we eat indoors when it rains?
Yes...
Next
Time:
Nothing Good For You Is Tasty