This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old.
The long-awaited day of Full Moon's debut has finally arrived.
But, at her first live performance...
She was nervous because she had to sing in front of so many people.
I
Full Moon's Debut Single...
I am placing an advanced
order for "Myself".
Please fulfill my request.
I heard it on the radio...
and loved it after
just one listen.
It's to be expected... she's still a grade school student, after all.
However...
Thanks to everyone's help...
It's safe to say that the debut was a success.
Next time, I'm going to be the one to debut as Full Moon.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Full Moon.
Myself.
In stores now.
It's so pretty...!
Is this... really me?
For one of Seed Records' new artists...
...they put in a little extra for the TV ad.
But... I wonder if everyone will really buy it...
Losing confidence in your first sales attempt is a problem.
There's no mistake... it's a good song.
It's going to be a smashing success!
Is It Really a Hit?
Ah... man!
Just calm down... calm down!
Until I hear about the sales from Ooshige-san...
...I can't calm down.
Man... give me a break.
Hurry up and call, Manager!
It's here!
Hello?
Yes.
Is that so?
I understand.
How...
...did it go?
Um... that's... uh...
Maybe it's a slow seller.
It only stared selling yesterday, right?
We've only begun the fight, right?
All right!
It's a smashing hit!
Ah?
They're receiving orders...
...the sales are still going!
What's that...
...you had us worried...
This means that...
...lots of people are going to
hear my song, right?
If you had my cunning...
...you'd sell even more.
A million seller... without a doubt!
I'm so happy!
Isn't it great..?
After today...
...talk about Full Moon  will be everywhere.
That's right!
You should take your CD to school today!
Eh?!
You can brag and say, "I have Full Moon's  CD!"
Maybe...
It'd be nice if I could do that...
Everyone will want it!
Ah. If that's going to happen, then I should practice my signature first.
You know...
The one who's selling isn't you, it's Full Moon...
Hey, hey, hey!
Do you think a ribbon would make me look cuter?
Hey... what do you think?
Meroko, cut it out already...
Such unladylike behavior...
Good morning!
Oh! Good Morning!
What is it?
I'm thinking about what they all might say...
My heart's pounding.
I wonder if they really heard Myself...
It's fine. After all...
...it was a smashing hit, right?
Have some faith in yourself.
That's right.
Try taking a deep breath.
It looks like... I've calmed down a bit.
Then, you're ready.
Yep!
Good morning!
Ah...
Good morning, Kouyama-san!
Good morning!
And... just earlier...
Morning!
Morning, Kumi!
Geez, Kumi.
You're in a hurry today.
Whatever...
Anyways, did you hear the new single that came out yesterday?
I heard it. I heard it!
The vocal for it was the best!
Um...
Fu...
Full Moon.
It's Full Moon.
Furuta!
From the Guitar Fighters?
That's it!
Maijima-san sure knows
what she's talking about.
Of course!
I keep up to date on all the new songs.
Really, Chia-san?
What's she doing?
She's supposed to go tell them...
Yeah.
Hey, on TV yesterday...
I was so surprised... she was so pretty...
You're talking about
the entertainment news, right?
The Mashiba "Is that an alien?" Girl!
What's wrong, Kouyama-san?
Are you feeling sick again?
I-It's nothing.
Thanks.
Really.
That's good, I guess...
Nobody's talking about me at all...
If you're that concerned about it...
Don't bother yourself with gossip.
Why don't you try asking someone yourself?
Because...
It couldn't be that...
you don't have any friends?
Of course not!
It's been two years since
she transferred here.
It's just as Takuto said.
I've been absent a lot due to my illness, after all.
My health has only been getting worse...
...and I am not allowed to watch
TV much either, so...
...I don't have anything to talk about.
That's why... I've never been able to make close friends.
I see...
Sorry...
It's okay.
As long as I'm selling...
Everyone will be listening to me...
...so I can't just dwell in the past.
I'm sorry, too, for making you worry.
Geez...
Uh... Ah...?
Ah?
Ah! This is it!
Wh-What's with you all of a sudden?
Look at this!
Lunchtime broadcast inside the school.
Taking song requests?
What's this?
During our lunch break...
We have a broadcast DJ...
A lot of songs are played, and there's a lot of talking, too.
It's pretty popular.
Like I said...
That's it!
Eh?
Geez... you're so slow...
If nobody's heard you before...
...then we'll let them hear you.
Eh?!!!
That's what we'll do.
It's okay if we broadcast your CD, right?
I guess so...
But...
Ah! Geez!
You're so frustrating!
If you don't do anything about it...
...you'll never make it in the market.
It's easy to give up, but...
...try working a little harder first!
He's right.
You finally managed to debut.
That's right...
Maybe I should try working a little harder...
It's not "maybe I should try..."
It's "I'm gonna work hard!"
Wait a minute!
I haven't even thought about whether or not to request it!
You're still saying that?!
If that's the case...
Mero Mero Magic!
Ah.
My CD...
I'm going to request this!
Meroko, wait!
You idiot!
I said wait up!
Please wait!
Look... isn't that Kouyama-san?
What's with her?
What a weird girl.
She's so strange.
Ah... th-thanks...
Ah... everyone's laughing at me...
She's done it now... that Meroko...
Meroko, geez!
Stop!
Stop already, Meroko!
Broadcast Room
That's the broadcasting room isn't it?
Don't just suddenly stop!
Huh?
Kouyama-san... why are you down there?
Ma-Maijima-san!
Okay?
For the broadcast...
Say, "I want to request this", 'kay?
Oh well...
If it's come to this... just give in.
Are you okay?
Ah... um...
That...
Um...
Well...
Ah... geez!
No!
What?
Just hush, 'kay?
Play Myself!
I mean...
Please play Myself.
'kay?
It's okay, right?
Meroko...
'kay?
Huh?
I wonder what Kouyama-san's doing...
Is she fighting with Maijima-san?
Cut it out, Meroko!
It's because you have to request it!
Will you just cut it out!
Um...
Kouyama-san... just what was that?
I'm very sorry!
Oh man...
Kouyama-san?
Are you okay?
Only strange things are happening to me...
I can't take it anymore...
Ah...
I didn't give her the CD...
Nothing's changed...
This sucks...
You said it...
Who's fault do you think it is?
Ah?
Maijima-san.
This is your chance.
This is your chance, so go
and try requesting again!
I wonder if it is...
Of course it is!
Ah......
Ah...
Um... Maijima-san...
Yes.
Hello?
You know...
Maybe she was buying Myself?
Don't just stand there
and say irresponsible things!
Because, look at that.
Ah.
Myself?
Full Moon's?
See!
Absolutely...
...hopeless.
Eh?
Yep, Yep.
By the way...
I'm going with my mother to Shibuya tomorrow.
I'm looking forward to it.
"Hopeless..."
What does she mean?
Kouyama
I'm home.
Well...
How did you get that injury?
This is...
Lately, you've...
...been joking around and acting rather flippant, you know.
You have to consider your health, so...
...be more careful from now on.
Do you understand?
Yes...
Wow!
This taiyaki...!
It's sooo  good!
Come on! Come on!
It smells good, doesn't it?
Well? Well? Well?
Look!
I don't want any.
What are you saying?!
The tail is filled with anko...
It's refreshing.
That's right!
You'll regret it if you don't have any!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Well?
Come on!
Well? Well? Well?
Well?
Geez!
I don't want any means I don't want any!
Ah?
Yes?
Ah. Mitsuki?
It's Ooshige.
There's already a huge response for Myself.
The CD shop has already sent additional orders.
It's the first time one of my talents
has been such a huge hit!
You said it's a hit, but...
...is it really?
Of course!
The radio and television stations want an interview as soon as possible.
They've all been asking for one.
Can you hear it?
All the phones here are going off.
Is that so?
But... nobody knows about it...
Eh?
Mitsuki?
Hello?
It's nothing.
Excuse me.
Your manager is going to worry about you.
Because...!
Even though nobody's heard it...
...why does she say it's a hit?!
That's because...
But... there hasn't been
much publicity for it...
Even if there was publicity,
no one would listen to it!
It's useless!
Besides...
Ah..."Myself"?
Full Moon's?
Absolutely...
...hopeless.
Sorry.
Can you leave me alone for a bit?
Don't come to school anymore either.
I'm leaving.
Good morning!
Oh! Good morning!
For some reason... I don't think I'll make it...
What are you saying after coming this far?
Ah?
Takuto!
Ah.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
It's okay.
Anyways, don't get hung up over something like that.
You can't act like before from now on.
That's because...
I thought everyone would be
talking about Full Moon!
Yet everyone... Even after
I put all I had into it...
You know...
If you want them to hear you sing, then sing for them yourself!
You want to be friends with them after all!
If you don't tell them yourself...
...they won't be your friends.
Sing together?
Like I said...
The fact that you don't have
any girls you're close to.
Before you can even start worrying about how you can't talk to anyone...
Smile and try to talk to them yourself first!
I see...
Sing together, huh?
That's right.
Anyways, give it a try.
I wonder if I can do it.
I told you yesterday, right?
In times like this...
Take a deep breath.
That's right.
I should smile myself.
Come. Come.
Check this out. Look at this.
That voice is...
Meroko!
What we have here is...
It just went on sale yesterday...
Right now...
There's a mad rush to acquire this huge hit...
It's crazy!
Which means...
It's something you can't easily get!
Over here...
Don't just sit there studying
with your buddies...
Come!
Buy it! Buy it!
Those are... my CDs...
What the hell is she doing?
Kouyama-san somehow become quite a character all of a sudden.
I never thought she was
this kind of a person.
Yeah.
It's totally different from her image.
You're horrible...
You're horrible, Meroko!
What were you thinking?
Because...
I thought I was kinda wrong yesterday...
If you're regretting it...
Why did you pretend to be her?
If they listen to Full Moon's  song...
...Mitsuki will be able to make lots of friends, won't she?
Even if that was your goal,
your methods were wrong!
I thought that was the best way
to get their attention.
You know...
It's alright.
It's okay, Takuto.
Eh?
That's enough...
Well...
Meroko was doing it for my sake, too.
Besides...
I didn't have friends to begin with, so...
It won't change the way people think about me.
Ah...
I have to go already.
I thought it was a good idea...
Hmm?
Ah... she's here! She's here!
Man... we were looking all over
for you, Kouyama-san.
Eh?
Hey, I was wondering if it's okay for me to use this CD during the lunchtime broadcast.
Eh?!
But...
You said it was absolutely hopeless yesterday.
That's right.
No matter where I went...
I couldn't get one at all.
I was even thinking that I'd have to go to Shibuya to find a copy...
It's really popular.
The lyrics are great...
The song's the best!
Especially that part.
Doushite konna ni...
No, you're wrong.
That seems kinda off.
Really?
I'm pretty sure it went like this...
Doushite konna ni...
That sounds even more off.
You think so?
I wonder how it really went.
If I recall...
Um... um...
Isn't it like this?
Why do I love you so?
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ah sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
Amazing.
Kouyama-san, you're like the real thing.
You're so cool!
Eh?
I wonder if that's so...
Yeah.
Kouyama-san, you're good at singing, aren't you?
It's not just singing...
Her performance earlier.
Ah... That was hilarious.
Ah... that was...
I didn't know you had it in you.
Hang out with us more from now on, okay?
Teach us how to sing, too.
Okay!
If I can do it, I'll sing as much as you want!
Hey, Mitsuki...
Ah! It's okay if we call you Mitsuki, right?
Do you want to come to
the broadcast with me?
I'll show you how it's done...
broadcasting, that is...
Let's go! Let's go!
Okay!
I want to try it!
You can call me Tomoe.
Well, well.
That takes care of this for now.
Ah!
Meroko.
I'm sorry for saying mean things to you.
Takuto, thank you.
Mitsuki.
What's wrong?
Oh, I'm coming right away.
Bye!
All right!
Thanks to what I did...
I don't have to leave, and Full Moon  won't be sad anymore, right, Takuto?
You're getting better.
I
Full Moon
"Myself"
Please wait
for your order
to arrive.
Sorry for the
inconvenience.
Look at this.
It's really selling.
The production can't even keep up with it.
Everyone wants to listen to Full Moon's  song!
Believe me!
Yes.
I know.
Like I said...!
Eh?
I know it very well.
Lots of people are listening to it.
From now on, I'll work harder!
Take a deep breath and smile!
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Oh well.
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Hmm...
Takuto, what's wrong?
That doctor, Wakaouji...
What's on his mind?
No matter how many times he goes around with Mitsuki...
He hasn't heard of Myself.
Eh? Why?
It's a good song...
Isn't it?
Now that you mention it... that person...
Someone said he was
a musician before, right?
Is there something else to him?
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
I Wanted You to Listen
Look forward to it!