--Hey! Just show it to me!
--Ah, hey!
Wha--
Seriously, what're you doing with this?!
Ah...
You don't have to secretly take pictures,
you know. If you want it that much...
Well, sorry, sorry! What I really
wanted was Hideyoshi's picture. Yours was--
I can't breathe!
I'm not gonna let you off the hook today!
I'm not going to just keep
taking these beatings forever!
Teacher! We'll fight a mock
ST War! Please give us approval!
Okay. I approve.
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
"Name: Minami Shimada"
"Subject: Combined Subjects" "Score: 823"
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
Oh? Summon!
Summon! Summon! Summon! Summon!
This is odd. I wonder what happened.
Summon!
I'm suspending the approval!
What's going on?! The field is out of control!
Hottoite sodatsu mono nanda nandarou
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
Deai mashite wa kantan sugiruyo
Saisho ni kimeta kotae wa hitotsu
Tokimeki mashita goukaku shimasuka?
Koi mo shoubu mo awatenai
Kotsu kotsu kotsu to tetsuya ni tameiki
Watashi no naka ni tensai dreamer
Omou koto mina kanaeba iina
Hito no sekai wa kinishinai
Perfect-area complete!
Zettai koko de matterunda
Perfect-area nozomu koe ga kikoeruyo
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? Tomaranai surechigai
Watashi ga soudan aite nara
"Tomodachi kai?" "Tomodachi desu."
Kanashiki rei ten dane
No! Yarinaoshi kakinaoshi
Honki de one more chance please
Ima yori suteki na mirai ga arunoni
Ima yori suteki ni my life, my life, my life!
Problems always occur without warning.
Who is it?
What's the password?
Makes me too frisky.
Okay.
Where's the stuff?
You'll get it when you hand over the cash.
Whoa! A real picture of Hideyoshi
as a waitress! Oh, I'm glad to be alive!
That's just the beginning.
Here's the picture of him
changing. It costs twice as much.
What?! Give me a discount, Muttsulini!
I'm living off salt water this week!
If you buy it, I'll give you this one free.
Hmmm, if that's the case...
Dammit! They sure don't make this easy, do they?
Hm? More security?! Password is...
Dammit!
Dammit. That scared me!
Seems like something happened.
Sorry to bother you!
Principal! A problem in the
Summoner Test system occurred.
Yeah, I know.
Man... They've spread this far.
I wonder what's going on.
Such a hindrance!
Ouch!
Go away!
Ahhh! Ow, ow! Stop it!
Yoshii, did you play a prank again?
Why am I the first person you suspect?
What'd you do, Akihisa?
It'd be better if you tell us now.
No one will blame you.
You guys, too?!
But your Avatar is the only one
that's behaving strangely, you know.
Oh? Why?
I wonder if the system is unstable.
I'll try summoning my Avatar.
Summon!
That's an adult version.
Ahh! Please don't look at her!
--I see...
--Ahh! My eyes...!
--You can't see it, Yuuji.
I wonder if Himeji is
going to grow up like this.
One part in particular really grew.
I-I'll summon mine, too! Summon!
I see... Just like Minami,
she didn't grow in the fr...
...ankensteiner!
Huh?! Could it be that...
--if I do this, I can see what's underneath her clothes...
--Ahhh! Don't! Please don't! No!
--That's our Muttsulini!
--Don't take a picture!
Stop it!
A skeleton...
It wasn't a bad idea, though.
If I get closer...
That looks kinda fun.
I think I'll try summoning my Avatar, too.
Summon!
Oh, no! Mr. Wolf!
--A-A pretty girl!
--Oh, I said, stop it.
Just as I thought, Hideyoshi!
I wasn't mistaken at all!
This is clearly a mistake!
The system is out of order.
Well then, I think I'll try, too.
Summon!
How handsome...
I'll try, too. Summon!
They're well-matched.
What about yours, Muttsulini?
Summon.
"Yuuji: You're so stubborn..."
"Yuuji: You want me..."
"Yuuji: don't you?"
"Kouta: Don't be so conceited..."
"Kouta: You said you wouldn't do anything."
"Kouta: .................."
I know you like me.
"Kouta: You liar!"
Stop... Stop...
Ugh!
Hey, wait! My Avatar was acting on his own!
Hey! Stop! Ahhh!
Betrayer.
What's your Avatar like, Yoshii?
Show us, Aki!
I'll try. Summon!
This is odd. Why is mine behaving
differently from everyone else's?
Ah, they're back to normal.
What happened?!
They're out of control!
Where are they going?
What's going on?
The teachers' Avatars, which
are close to the core of the system,
are completely frozen and can't be summoned.
The students' Avatars are out of control.
I'm stumped. I can't access the crime
prevention system in the server room.
As it stands, we can't open the door
so we can't even go in there to fix it.
How about turning off the power to the system?
The permanent power supply unit will
keep it functioning for at least a month.
Then... we have no choice but to
break the wall and enter there, huh?
Tomorrow, we'll introduce our
academy's system at the conference.
It'll be terribly embarrassing
if we have a hole in the wall.
Then what would you like to do?
Hmm... well...
why don't we have an idiot do the job?
You want me do fix it?!
The Avatar of a probationary student is
run from a separate area of the system.
So, unlike other students' Avatars,
yours isn't affected,
hence it's not out of control.
I see. So that's why Akihisa's Avatar
was different from all the other Avatars.
But I couldn't summon him correctly.
That's because you summoned him
inside a malfunctioning teacher's field.
But you have your own field, right?
Oh, that's right! If I use my iron bracelet...
Send your Avatar inside the
server room and connect the cable.
After that I'll shut down the crime
prevention system from the terminal
and open the door.
That's an operation that only the Avatar
of the probationary student can carry
out since he can physically touch objects.
But my Avatar can't go through the wall.
There's a vent to cool down the system.
An Avatar is small enough to go through it.
But if he can't see inside the vent,
wouldn't it be impossible to control his Avatar?
Here...
A video camera and a transmitter.
If we have his Avatar take it
with him, we can see inside.
Smart idea, Muttsulini.
I'm surprised that you
have stuff like that on you.
What do you use them for?
Don't attack Muttsulini!
He's actually a good guy!
--He's just a little... no... very naughty, and...
--I haven't said anything yet.
--Akihisa is his customer, so...
The effective field area
for the iron bracelet is small.
Go to the front of the server room
and control your Avatar from there.
We'll guide you from here.
So that's the entrance, huh?
Awaken! Summon!
Go!
His Avatar has entered the vent.
The route is clear!
Keep going straight, Akihisa.
Got it.
Is it okay? He's a probationary
student... a trouble student.
We have no other choice
but to leave it to him...
as that idiot is the only one who
can use that iron bracelet for now.
Turn right 3 meters ahead
and left at the next intersection.
This is just like a labyrinth.
Why is it so complicated?
It's a security measure.
Ah! Ow, ow, ow! I'm going numb?
My score is going down! Wh-What's going on?!
It's a poison swamp.
Why the heck is something like this in here?!
It's a security measure.
We'll have you take a detour
around the dangerous area.
Turn right at the next corner.
I see a light!
You're almost there. Keep going straight.
Oh? I wonder what that is.
Avatars?!
Out of control Avatars have appeared!
They're gonna attack!
"Blast
Tenpa Kyouran"
Make him stop, Yuuji!
I can't! He's out of control!
Oh no! I don't like this! I don't like this!
Stop it! Hey! Make them stop!
Yuuji! Hideyoshi! Minami! Himeji! Dad!
Stop it! Don't do it!
"0 points"
Hm?
Those who died will be given a remedial class!
--Why?!
--What?
"Loss of Control, Labyrinths,
and the Avatar Instrumentality Project"
Idiot Test!
Are you okay, Yoshii?
Humph... I saw Hell.
What kind of remedial class was it?
We'll continue the operation.
Please take the recovery
test and fill up your score.
But unless he gets a considerably good score,
it'll be over once he encounters the enemies.
Yoshii... If you like, I can help you study.
Yoshii...
If you like...
What?
I can help you study.
You're gonna give me a
private lesson, Himeji?! Really?!
Your mind sure is sharp when it comes
to turning things into something dirty.
The only method that will work is one
that shows effective results right away.
Then, I know a good way.
Hm?
I see. If the test is full of easy
questions that even Aki can solve,
he can get a good score, huh?
It's kinda cheating, but...
Whoa! Akihisa's achieving
a level never seen before!
You're amazing, Yoshii!
Go, Aki!
What did you make a mistake on, Akihisa?
The Taika Reform took place in 645!
You don't remember that after what happened?!
That's exactly why I got
confused as to which one was correct!
But hasn't his level gotten quite high?
With this score, won't he be
okay even if enemies appear?
Let's start the operation.
Okay then!
Summon!
I'll clear it for sure this time!
Okay, turn left at that intersection.
Got it.
Ahh!
It's a poison swamp.
So he gets numb even
after becoming stronger, huh?
Don't make me a guinea pig!
This time, go right at the end of that path.
Got it.
What?
Be careful, Akihisa. If you touch it...
Ahhh!
Yoshii!
Aki!
I-I can't breathe...
I said be careful, didn't I?!
It was out of habit.
Ah! That's...
All right! I won't lose this time!
I can win! I can win!
Be on your guard!
Tsuchiya is coming!
Don't worry, since the
subject we'll fight in is history!
Since Muttsulini can't use his Health
and Physical Education knowledge,
he's no match for me right now!
"Danger"
It was a poison swamp.
Those who died will be given a remedial class!
What?!
That's not fair!
Our Avatars fought and lost on their own!
No arguments!
This is absurd!
I made it!
There should be a
disconnected cable. Connect it.
Got it.
Ah! There it is!
Minami?!
Aki!
Please run!
But...!
Hurry!
Or... I'll be...
Himeji?
Esroh Nedoow Dimaryp!
Yoshii!
Aki!
Dammit!!
Something is coming!
Summoning field! Phase sync!
An Avatar is appearing!
Honey!
Miharu?!
Even if it's just among Avatars,
I can't let you cling to a pig!
If you're gonna hold someone, hold my Avatar!
Now!
Remedial class!
--Nooo!
--Oh no.
Sorry, Himeji!
All right! Huh?
Yoshii! You can't beat her! Please run!
But... When I've come this far... I can't...
Yoshii!
When... I'm so close...!
He can't fight any longer. We should stop him.
As educators, forcing pointless
suffering on a student is...
Not yet!
Hm?
I still have some points left!
When there's that much of a
difference in points, you have no chance.
Your ability levels are too far apart.
But... even so...
Ability levels...? That's right!
Just like my Avatar became stronger,
the points are not necessarily
a reflection of real ability!
Himeji! Take the recovery test!
What?
Please!
I get it!
Ms. Takahashi! Please let me take it!
If you raise your points any
further, he won't have a chance.
Please grade it!
Yoshii...
Mizuki Himeji...
"Class: F, No: 28, Name: Mizuki Himeji, 0 points"
...0 points!
Good job.
Hm?
The system... has been recovered!
The problem has been
resolved for the time being.
Hajimete no kisu wa yappari ichigo miruku aji
Jitensha oshinagara kaeru yuugure doki
Mousou shumireeshon yumegokochi docchi
Nana kai koronde hachi korobi wahahaha
Anna konna hibi no mainichi ga kinenbi
Tsunagete yukou ano sora made
Shourai yuubou itsuka oomono ni nareru yokan?
Ashita mo kitto hare tokidoki egao ni naru
Yoshii! Are you okay?
Yeah, this is nothing.
Those who died with their score reduced
to zero will be given a remedial class!
Well then... I'll see you later.
Yeah.
Himeji...
What's with that gloomy look?
Ow! What'd you do that for?! Ahh! My points!
Don't hang onto such a small number of points.
You go take the remedial class, too.
Whaaaaat?!
Yoshii!
Yeah!
Entrusting such an important task to
a Class F student was a big gamble...
but I'm glad that it went well.
I don't think it was a gamble or anything.
Huh?
You'll learn eventually...
how to deal with idiots.
"Japanese History"
"Class: A, No: 1, Name: Shouko Kirishima, _ points"
Teacher...
Please grade mine, too.
"Preview"
Question 9
One of the units used to indicate
a woman's breast size is "cup."
Explain the size of A cup,
which is used as a basis.
--Minami Shimada.
--No comment.
Next Episode! "Kisses, Breasts, and Ponytails!"
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!"
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"