Hideyoshi, about today's supplemen—
Huh?
Wh...
W-What is it?
A-Akihisa.
Suspicion
You...
...seem slightly different today.
Suspicion
I-Is that... so?
I-I'm... I am always like this.
My height and appearance are the same as always!
Usually you look more girly and cute though.
daimondai hitori to futari
大問題、ひとりとふたり
The big question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
karafuru mawaridasu watashi no shourai
カラフル回り出す 私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
a sou ookina sekai wa kibun ga hirogaru
あ、そう 大きな世界は 気分が広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日も大好き
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当に大好き!
I really do love you
watashi no baka
私のバカ
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
星の数よりもバカだ!
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaete kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えて 君＋謎＋私は
Answer me. What does you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Ms. Takahashi, have you had any progress?
Yes, Principal Todou.
Question 3
Me, That Girl, and the Stuffed Doll!
What do you think of Kinoshita Yuuko from Class A?
She has good grades and is quite sociable.
Hmm.
Her twin brother, Kinoshita Hideyoshi, is skilled enough to perform in an opera,
so I'd expect her to be able to sing well.
That's good to hear.
As the principal, I'm proud to have a student who excels at everything.
Yes, not only is she attractive and well-mannered,
but she also has outstanding grades and an amiable
personality. She's quite exceptional; a model student.
Pretty boys are the best!
This scene where Yuuichi assaults Shinji with a blunt weapon is especially—
Wait!
This isn't the time for that!
I'm home!
Sister!
Huh?
What's the matter? You just tossed aside your favorite novel.
Favorite Item
Why do you possess a skill that I do not?
What do you mean?
Ms. Takahashi asked me today
Please
to sing the school anthem for Fumizuki Academy's promotional video.
Fumizuki Academy
Promotion
Video
School Song
Sing
What?!
You don't have have any singing
talent; not even one iota.
Iota
Solar Plexus
Fist
Are you looking for a fight?
You could have just saved yourself the trouble and turned her down.
No way!
I've portrayed myself as a model
student, unsurpassed in all fields.
Your vanity is certainly unmatched.
Vanity
Unmatched
Clap
That's the nature of a Kinoshita.
You perform as a model actor, and I, as a model student.
We are alike in that sense.
Of course!
I hate to admit it, but you and I are...
twins...
Wh-What is it?!
What's going on, Sister?!
You're good at deceiving people, right?
It's called "acting".
Wait, you're not gonna—
Hideyoshi~
You'll help your big sister with a big favor...
won't you?
Violent negotiation
Th-That's not asking; that's coercing!
Asking for a favor
FIST
Are we really going to do this?
It's fair enough since I'm taking your
supplementary lessons for you, right?
Still, if my classmates find out about this—
What if they do?
They'll keep treating me like a girl forever.
Yeah, somehow I doubt they'll figure it out.
Oh, take this with you.
What is it?
It's a microphone.
With this, I'll be able to hear everything you say.
Where did you even get this?
A classmate of yours gave it to me.
Fresh supplies.
This classroom is as shabby as ever.
On the run
Time remaining
HP
Sugawa's making a run for it.
He has violated the pact and approached
a girl! He's our president no longer!
He's a traitor!
After him!
Yuuko (freaked out...)
Curse
Yuuko (really freaked out...)
Oh, Hideyoshi! It seems today's lesson is just printouts.
Oh, really?
Man, Sugawa really messed up.
Emergency announcement! Emergency announcement!
On the run
Time remaining
HP
We have obtained the testimony of a girl whom Sugawa approached.
She stated that she has no interest in Sugawa, but did want to know how Aki was doing.
Aki
Really disgusted
I repeat, the female wanted to know how Aki was doing!
See ya!
Alone
What idiots.
Now then, I should check on Hideyoshi's current situation.
Kinoshita, thank you.
Is that... Kubo?
You gave me courage.
You needn't worry about it.
What's going on? What are they talking about?
Kubo
No, I'm relieved to have a kindred spirit in my class.
I never knew that you too were into
same-gender love.
O-Oh, Hideyoshi, is something wrong?
Sister! Can I borrow you for a minute?
Wait, Hideyoshi?
Sister!
Hideyoshi!
Tell me what exactly you were babbling about.
It was just chit-chat.
How did me being into "same gender-
love" come up in your "chit-chat"?!
Well, you do read novels where—
Idiot! You hopeless idiot! That's
something completely different!
You made it sound like I'm into girls!
That wasn't my intention at all—
The next time you say anything ambiguous...
I understand! I understand completely!
Did he really understand?
Yuuko, um...
What is it?
Class Rep?
Shouko
Hideyoshi, you'd better not give yourself away!
Yuuko, your skirt is rolled up.
Shouko
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
That dumbass!
Thanks, Rep,
but it's fine.
But, your skirt.
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
After all...
"After all"?
I'm wearing my underwear today!
Sister!
Do you have some kind of excuse?
I meant it's all right since I'm wearing athletic shorts under my skirt.
That's NOT all right!
Crack
You made it sound like I don't usually wear panties!
But they are a kind of underwear!
Don't be such an idiot and keep an eye on your skirt!
Still, your skirt is so loose around my waist-
I-I'll be more careful!
I promise I will!
Join the eavesdropping!
Jeez.
K-Kinoshita!
Who is that?
Yokomizu
My name is Yokomizo Kouji.
Yokomizo Kouji? I've never heard of him.
I-I love you!
P-Please go out with me!
Yokomizu
A confession?! Oh no!
I don't want to flat out reject him, but...
Sorry, I'm happy, but...
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
That's a good reply!
Yokomizu
Th-Then, please tell me the kind of guys you like.
Sorry,
I...
I?
I'm...
only interested in pretty little boys!
I am...
NOT a girl-loving, panty-less, pedophile!
I tried my best to analyze your preferences.
Those are my preferences for fiction!
I hide all of that from the public!
U-Understood.
I'll act out your external character perfectly this time.
Sigh
Hey, Hideyoshi!
All right.
A-Akihisa, they're not pursuing you anymore?
Yeah.
They heard that Yokomizo confessed to your
sister, so they all went after him instead.
I-I see.
Yuuko
Yokomizo, you poor guy; you've suffered almost as much as me.
He never learns.
Yuuko
Eh?
Well he confessed to your sister
because you rejected him after all!
I take it back!
Yuuko
Poor guy
I take it back!
Yuuko
Poor guy
I take it back!
Yuuko
Poor guy
I take it back!
Yuuko
Poor guy
I take it back!
Yuuko
Poor guy
I take it back!
Yuuko
Poor guy
I take it back!
Yuuko
Oh, speaking of your big sister...
I take it back!
Poor guy
Yuuko
I take it back!
Poor guy
Yuuko
I take it back!
Poor guy
Yuuko
Huh?!
Your big sister's really awesome.
Wh-Why?
I mean...
she's cute,
has good grades,
and is good at sports.
Aren't you proud of her?
I-I guess...
Also, look!
She's always so gorgeous.
Gorgeous, huh?
That's why it's such a waste.
Eh?
I heard your sister's actually a lesbian
pedophile who doesn't wear any panties.
Octopus Hold
Erase that from your mind!
What?!
Why?!
I think I feel something soft...
...like some small bumps!
They aren't small bumps!
I do have breasts!
Recently, there's been a rumor
that my breasts have developed.
What a coincidence.
There's been a rumor that I'm into girls, love little boys, and come to the school with no panties on.
What have you done? People are treating me like a girl even more now.
It's still pretty much the same for you, though.
Look at me; I'm suddenly a pervert with three fetishes.
It's your fault for suggesting we swap!
It's because of your lousy acting!
Oh well, let's just leave it at that.
Yeah, worrying won't help.
After all, our school is full of strange rumors.
Question 3
Mark the syllable that is stressed in the
underlined English word.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
It's your imagination.
.
Teacher's Comment
Correct. In most cases, when a word ends
with "tion" the vowel preceding the "tion"
is stressed. It's good rule-of-thumb.
Tsuchiya Kouta's Answer
It's your imagination.
Teacher's Comment
You won't get it right by
taking the machine-gun
approach.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
It's your imagination!
Teacher's Comment
Sometimes I wonder if you're actually a genius.
Going back to one year ago...
Going back to
one year ago...
Everyone, freeze!
Inspection
Put your bags on the table and open them!
Futile
Resistance is futile!
Sakamoto!
Empty out your pockets.
Damn it!
I'm confiscating this.
Damn it! Why me?!
Yoshii!
Take off your uniform and change into your gym clothes!
Why?!
You're going overboard!
Trust me a little more, will ya—
Hey, Akihisa.
You dropped your game console.
Thanks, Yuuji.
Trust me a little more, will ya?
Don't bother changing.
Summoned Being: Summon!
Today is the Summoning Training
Session for the first year students.
The day has only just started and
I've already had such bad luck.
Damn it!
I bought that mp3 player just last month!
He took some costumes and props of mine.
Well, I lost...
a handheld game console, some games, DVDs, CDs, light novels, manga, trading cards, celebrity photos, a spinning top—
What do you come to school for?
It's Himeji's turn.
Huh?
Voyeur, aren't you gonna take any photos of her?
My camera was confiscated.
That's too bad.
We're in different classes, so it's pretty hard to see her in her gym clothes.
Summoned Being:
Summon!
She must be popular, being cute and smart.
Oh yeah, you guys know each other don't you?
Yeah, we were in the same class in elementary school,
but it's been awhile since we last talked.
Next: Yoshii Akihisa!
Okay.
Your opponent will be Shimada!
Shimada!
Shimada Minami!
Ah, here!
Yoshii?!
What's wrong? You were zoning out.
Are you hungry?
I'm not like you!
Oh, I know!
You were disappointed with how
weak your Summoned Being is—
I'm glad that you're going to be my opponent.
Because...
...I'm really going to enjoy beating you up!
Wai—
Our Summoned Beings are the ones fighting, not us!
You're right.
We aren't going to fight.
That's good to hear.
Since it'll just be me pounding on you!
Shimada...
See! Even he's against it!
Just for today, okay?
Thanks!
Why?!
Man, today's been one thing after another.
T-That's Himeji!
All right!
I'll use this chance to talk to her!
This is too much for me.
Time for a full retreat!
Please! This is all I want!
I have to get that doll, no matter what!
Please!
I'm sorry kid.
Umm, what's the matter?
Well, this little girl wants that
doll over there pretty badly,
but she doesn't have enough money.
Hey, why do you want it so badly?
Lately my sister's been really down.
Your sister?
Yes.
She's been wanting to get that doll.
That's why...
I see.
You wanted to cheer her up with that, right?
We only moved here recently,
so she must have lots of schoolwork!
But still...
But still she...
she does all the housework and even plays with me!
Don't cry!
I'll do something about it!
Really?!
Yeah.
Mister.
Thank you so much!
So, how much is that doll?
Tax included
Twenty five thousand yen.
I'm sorry.
I tried my best, but I couldn't help you.
Shock
I have ten thousand yen if you need it!
So to summarize,
together with my thousand yen, we have a total of eleven thousand yen.
We have half the money.
Not quite enough though.
Maybe we could...
buy half of the doll!
Are you really a high schooler?
You're an idiot.
It won't be sold just yet.
But without the money...
You're right, twenty-five thousand yen, huh...
If I sell the stuff I had confiscated this morning...
That's it!
What's wrong?
Hazuki.
Let's meet again in this park tomorrow!
Tomorrow?
Yeah!
Got it!
Great!
You're gonna get your confiscated stuff back?!
I need your help too, guys.
We have to get Iron Man's locker key for that.
The key is in the inner pocket of his coat.
In that case...
we'll drench him with water
and while he's changing we grab his key.
Give it your best, Akihisa.
Me?!
He's here!
Do it right!
Godspeed!
Aren't you guys gonna help at all?!
Since it's come to this...
Sorry! I slipped!
WHAT?!
You ain't dodging it!
Sorry about that!
I slipped—
Didn't you say something about "dodging"?
I went through hell, but I got the key.
Good.
We'll open his locker now.
Confiscated stuff
They're here!
Scram before he gets back!
Got it!
Old books?
Oh well, he's gonna dump them anyway.
Man, we got lucky.
If it weren't for those old books, I'd never have got the twenty five thousand.
Ah, Mr. Stupid.
Sorry for the wait!
No, it's all right!
What's that?
Um, a pretty girl spoke to me before you got here.
A pretty girl?
Yes!
"Take this doll and give it to your sister!"
"You can keep this doll if that
guy comes here with the doll!"
Uh...
So this is for Hazuki, then.
It's... mine?
Yes.
And this one here is for your sis!
Nui!
I hope this will cheer her up.
Umm...
Mister.
Can you bend down?
Like this?
Thank you, Mr. Stupid!
You're an idiot,
but you're really kind. I love you!
When I grow up...
I'll let you be my husband!
Yesterday,
Problem
a theft took place.
Someone took the items that had been confiscated and my old books.
Unbelievably, this person had the audacity to use their own ID when they sold the items.
What do you think of him, Yoshii?
He's got balls!
You don't say.
Yoshii!
Brace yourself!
I'm sorry!
I can explain!
Yoshii.
I'll give you a title for which your
idiocy is ideally suited. Take this.
Yoshii Akihisa.
From this day forth, you are...
Punishment Inspector
Reflect on
your actions
Punishment Inspector
Reflect on
your actions
Punishment Inspector
Reflect on
your actions
Punishment Inspector
Reflect on
your actions
Punishment Inspector
Reflect on
your actions
the Punishment Inspector.
Punishment Inspector
Reflect on
your actions
hirameite kagayaite
閃いて 輝いて
Flash and sparkle!
denkyuu pikkanko
電球ぴっかんこ
Light bulb goes off!
(hai)
(はいっ)
Yes
進展しないよ
I'm not making progress
shinten shinai yo
dareka jama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
Oh no, someone's in the way
zenzen tarinai
全然足りない
It's totally not enough
sore ga mondai no koubaisuu
それが問題の公倍数
That's the common multiple of the problem
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I kind of get it
nani ga hontou no koto Baby?
何が本当のこと Baby?
What is it really, baby
mitetara koko de
見てたらここで
If you're watching
zukai shite yo Baby!
図解してよ Baby!
Show it to me, baby
kotoba mo kazu mo kimi wo arawasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
Words and numbers can't express you
(chu chu chu chu)
(ちゅちゅちゅちゅっ)
(kiss kiss kiss kiss)
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to
心がビリビリするS と
The magnetic forces between S and N
(S to)
(S と)
(S)
N  no jiryoku de
N の磁力で
It electrifies me!
(S, S, Supaaku tsuite nanbaa)
(S, S, SuperくついてNumber)
(Super goes with number!)
(I say No. 1 boy)
(And you're the number one boy!)
omedetou ima kara
おめでとう 今から
Congratulations, from now on
kimi wa My, ma, my otakara
君はMy, ma, my"お宝"
You're my treasure
tokubetsu nanda dou natte mo
特別なんだ どうなっても
You're special
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I won't let you go, no matter what
watashi wa koi shitai
私は恋したい
I want to love
yume ni genkai wa iranai
夢に限界はいらない
Dreams need no bounds
tokubetsu dayo ne acchatta mo
特別だよね 会っちゃたもん
You must be special since we met!
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
Please forgive me as is
hirameite kagayaite
閃いた 輝いた
It sparkled and flashed
seikai pittanko
正解ぴったんこ
Now I have the answer!
(gyu)
(ぎゅっ)
Sis!
Here you go!
I-Isn't this...
Sis, are you feeling better now?
Thank you, Hazuki!
I feel so happy right now!
Japanese is hard, and all kinds of other things as well, but...
Yeah!
Let's do our best together!
Also...
Also?
Recently, I...
...found an interesting guy.
Eh?! What sort of guy?!
Well, he's in the same class as me,
and one hell of an idiot!
Question 4
Answer the following question.
What is the sum of the numbers
on a set of 52 playing cards?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
364.
Teacher's Comment
Correct as always, Himeji.
There are a few ways to go about
calculating it. For example, if you
pair up each of the 13 spades from
1 to 13 with a heart from 13 to 1 in
reverse order, the sum of each pair
is 14. You do the same for diamonds
and clubs, and this gives 14x13x2 = 364 in total.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 4: What is the sum of the numbers on a set of 52 playing cards?
One plus two plus three
One plus two plus three plus, um...
plus umm...
Good luck.
Next episode: Me, True Feelings, and the Dignity of Men!
Me, True Feelings, and the Dignity of Men!
This will be on your test.