Joe, who failed to escape, spent two weeks in solitary.
While confined alone, he patiently awaited his return to Block 2, Cell 6.
Joe!
Get in already!
Joe...
Joe!
Sorry, everyone...
Hey, did you meet your sister?
Yeah...
For us with no blood relatives
the only way to survive is through being used by others!
Don't bother with me anymore.
I can survive by myself.
I, really don't know what I was trying to do...
Joe, your face is all bruised.
What a waste of a good man.
Hey, Mario. Go get a damp towel.
Okay.
Dumbass.
In the end, all you did was cause everyone pointless suffering.
Baremoto! You-
It's true.
Am I wrong?
Hey!
Why are you calling it pointless?
It's not the results that matter.
All guys like us get are one-in-a-hundred chances.
Joe just took one of those chances.
It wasn't pointless.
"For the dregs of society like us, the moment we stop risking our lives for even the slimmest of chances, we become losers.
That's why, our guts alone are our last ray of hope."
Anchan's words were buried deep into everyone's hearts.
You know, I...
think I want to become a singer.
A singer?
Yeah.
Megu... my little sister... was always so much more mature than I was.
She'd already prepared herself.
I can't just let myself rot away in a place like this.
I need to get out of here, even a day sooner, and starting climbing to the top...
Become more famous than anyone, until Megu notices me...
I definitely won't give up.
Hey!
You two over there!
Stop slacking and pay attention!
Sorry sorry!
Okay, this time we're fielding.
Two more months huh?
You guys look like you're getting along pretty well with Sakuragi aren't ya?
No, I...
Well, I don't care if you're buddies, but...
If you didn't need anything-
Do you know why Sakuragi's in here?
He...
killed his own parents!
His own parents!
What!? Joe wants to be a singer?
Let's see, sing a little something for us.
What? Here?
It's a bad idea to sing in here.
C'mon, just a little.
How about I
sing along with you?
Your singing would lead you straight into solitary.
What'd you say!?
You sure, Anchan?
Yeah.
Thanks!
Cabbage, don't eat that.
Baremoto...
It'll be the end of you if you start eating a murderer's food.
What are you talking about all of the sudden?
What do you mean, Baremoto?
Exactly what I said.
He's the worst kind of murderer!
Let's have this explained in front of everyone
about how you ended up here because you murdered your parents!
Who got you all puffed up!?
If you wanna smack me, go right ahead.
That's your thing, isn't it.
Hey, Sakuragi, what are you doing?
Nomoto, why don't you explain what's going on.
You can tell just by looking.
Oh really.
All right. Come, Sakuragi.
Anchan!
Hey, Baremoto!
What the hell are you doing? Anchan's our pal!
What pal?
Anchan...
You've got a lot of nerve laying a hand on those brats!
Man, you're-
1 year ago
How's that, Sakuragi?
Don't get all cocky!
Satisfied yet, Ishihara?
What?
If you want to beat me, you'd better get your fill now,
but I'll definately beat you half to death someday.
Enough to make up for the others too...
What's with that look Sakuragi!
About that, even we respect Anchan...
but... killing your parents is no joke.
What are you saying? Anchan's our pal isn't he!?
We have to believe in him!
Open your eyes, Mario.
You can't believe in people like that.
Act all buddy-buddy like that, and one day they'll pull the rug right out from under you.
Baremoto...
Anchan!
Baremoto.
Pull
For
Attention
What!?
It's Nomoto. There's something I'd like to check, can I go to the library?
Very well!
Just being in the same room as you makes my skin crawl.
Anchan, what Baremoto said is a lie right?
Please explain. We just can't accept things at this rate.
Anchan!
Brats don't stick their noses in!
Anchan! It's not like that!
That's too much!
Pull
For
Attention
What is it now!?
It's Sakuragi.
I would also like to go look up something in the library.
Very well!
Anchan!
I'll believe whatever you say!
Anchan...
What's going on...
Aren't we friends?
Aren't we, Anchan!?
Bruises and broken bones may heal over time,
but hearts scarred by words will not simply mend themselves.
A miserable, hellish cell where love and trust cannot grow.
That's what lies behind these bars.
I don't need any friends.
I won't believe in anyone.
I can't believe in anyone.
Package: Sweets
After Japan lost the war, those who lived in cities cried out in hunger.
"Humans aren't creatures anyone can believe in."
A pitiful mother who fell into the clutches of disgusting old farmers
just for the sake of a few scraps of food.
The young Baremoto was thrust into the depths of loathing for his fellow man.
Hey, Nomoto.
Wh- What is it?
Come over here.
O- okay.
Wow, you did quite a good job hiding them in here.
Say, Nomoto.
This is Sakuragi's stash, right?
That's right, isn't it?
It's simple.
All you need to do is sign this testimony.
Then I'll pretend I found it and we'll have Sakuragi grilled over the fire.
Why would you go that far?
Come on, Nomoto. Would you rather it was you?
You care that much about your parricide pal?
That is... Sakuragi's... stash...
Yes, just like that.
Hey, Sakuragi!
The library's over here!
What is it?
What's all the ruckus?
There's a fire.
A fire?
It seems to have started in the library.
The library!?
It couldn't be...
Ishihara, can you take care of Block 2?
Evacuate everyone onto the field!
Guess there's no helping it.
Hey.
Sakuragi's in Cell 6 of Block 2, right?
Cell 6 Block 2
Wh- What're you-
Oh man, the key for Cell 6 is missing!
Hey, Nomoto.
You confirm it too, Cell 6's key...
It's not there, right?
So there's no way we can get Cell 6 open.
Don't panic everyone! Calm down and make your way to the field!
You just have to keep your mouth shut.
If you can do that, I'll keep quiet about your stash too.
You know what I mean, right?
Open up!
What's going on!?
C'mon!
It's dangerous! Stay back!
We're taking roll call! Line up by cell number!
Nomoto.
There's no turning back now.
Sa- Sakuragi...
What!?
Sakuragi!
Baremoto.
Sakuragi...
Why are you here!?
Ishihara, can you give us a hand?
Ishihara!
Shit, this is one hell of a surprise...
Either way, those five scum can die for all I care.
Baremoto.
Where are Mario and the others?
I- I- don't know anything.
Baremoto...
I don't know!
I don't know anything!
Shit, what the hell is going on!?
Why are we the only ones still locked up!?
I don't wanna die here...
Suppon, if you don't keep low
the smoke will get you.
No good. It won't move an inch.
Don't worry.
Anchan will come to save us for sure.
I believe-
Don't talk nonsense.
We've got to do something ourselves right now!
Mario...
You wanna croak in here!?
Mario and the others are still in there, aren't they?
Baremoto!
It's not my fault!
He did it! Ishihara did it all himself!
I don't know anything!
I- I-
Wait, you're-
you're not going in there to save them are you!?
Are you insane? Look at the flames!
No one's gonna praise you when you act all cool and die trying!
No one's waiting for you! They're not expecting you to come save them!
They don't even think of you as a friend anymore!
Maybe.
So-
But, you know.
I still think of them as my friends.
Even now...
I might be able to do something.
What's with that?
Why can you go that far?
Nothing good ever comes from believing in people...
As long as you yourself survive, that's good enough...
Isn't that good enough?
He might not make it in time.
He may not be able to save them.
But if he doesn't try now, there's no second chance.
Anchan runs,
amidst the swirling flames and black smoke of a hopeless situation,
towards his friends.
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
I can even sacrifice
my life for those whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but I'll never give it up.
Our unbreakable bond
has begun to entwine with fate,
guiding us to the endless future laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
A far-off distance.
Roaring flames. A life-and-death situation.
He can't give up, because they're there.