I thought I told you, Sam.
Melanie Square doesn't need hard drugs.
Please wait, Mr. Tony. I didn't have a choice!
Ben told me to sell them no matter what.
I don't give a shit why you did it!
This is my turf... the Stone Family's turf.
I'll show no mercy to those who can't follow my rules,
even if they're the President or the First Lady!
That's enough.
Old man Gant...
I'll take him. You don't mind, do you?
Suit yourself.
You're old fashioned as always.
You're probably the only mafia family in L.A. that doesn't allow hard drugs these days.
I just want Melanie Square to be a decent place to play.
We've got enough money. We don't have to bend our principles to make more.
Don't talk so big, you novice.
You don't even live by the sweat of your brow.
You're right about that.
Hardheaded Tony, huh?
Daddy!
Duke! I didn't know you were here.
Sorry to show up so suddenly, Tony.
Eva.
We came to the Square to see a movie, so...
Daddy, you didn't forget, did you?
We're going to the amusement park together the day after tomorrow.
Yeah, of course I remember.
How could I forget about a day where I get to hang out with you?
Yeah!
Tony, can I have a moment?
That guy again?
It's about time we settle this.
If he won't comply, teach him a lesson.
Yes sir.
Ms. McCunnen, this is Richard Harrington.
I'm hoping to get a favorable response from you tonight.
We're giving you the best deal we can offer.
I see. Well, it's not a bad deal.
But my response is the same.
Why is that?
Don't make me repeat myself.
Melanie Square is our family's turf.
Everyone who lives here... Everyone who works here...
They're all my family.
I won't betray them.
You heard the man. So go back and tell your boss.
Or do you want to take a few bullets and go back in a body bag?
It seems that you guys still don't realize Inferno's true power.
What'd you say?!
We'll give you three more days. This is your last chance.
I trust you'll change your mind, Tony Stone.
What an annoying prick!
How can he be so confident?!
Even if it was a bluff, it's creepy.
Lutz, Rob. Do a thorough investigation on who's behind Inferno.
It's hard to believe that they're just some new organization.
Yes sir.
Are you ready?
Whenever you are.
Even if you block your opponent's weapon once, it doesn't end there.
I see.
That's impressive.
You couldn't do anything at first, but you can hold your own now.
That's because I've got a good coach.
There are two missions that I'd like you to carry out.
Will you accept?
Two?
I'll explain at my place. Come with me.
Your place?
So this is where you live, Ms. McCunnen?
That's right, though it's a little too big for a single person with no family.
Lizzie's been recruited for a different case today, so...
To get to the point, please explain the details of those missions.
First, I want you to be my guard and keep me company tonight.
I told you... Lizzie is out.
Even though the security here is perfect,
I want someone around just as a formality.
Why does a high-ranking executive like you have only one bodyguard?
Do I need someone else?
And the second mission is to monitor a mother and her child.
Okay, if that's your order.
That's not good.
You're not a doll.
Why you have to monitor them...
Why it is important...
You need to ask those things, okay?
What do you mean you can't get a clear picture about Inferno!?
We've asked information brokers and others all over the place,
but each of them say something different.
One would say the Verrocchio Family is involved,
while another one would say it was the Cervantes Family.
And of course, I heard the Bloodies' name as well.
What the hell is that?!
Lutz, since when did you start letting people sell you a bill of goods?!
I apologize.
Cut it out, Anton.
They did their job.
What do you mean?
Extending their power in a short time...
Doing things in various ways...
Their executives who don't show themselves...
And the information Lutz and Rob got...
If we put them all together, we'll get the answer.
Inferno is a special organization that is connected to the mafia families on the West Coast.
What?!
That guy's confidence also comes from that.
The only way for us to survive is to kiss up to them.
He knew that from the start.
Boss, then Melanie Square will be...!
Not in my book.
No matter who we're facing,
I can't betray the people of the Square!
Anton, set up a meeting with Inferno immediately.
But give them a condition.
Tell them to bring their boss.
Tony... don't tell me you're going to...
I'll negotiate, at least...
The real boss probably won't show,
considering their organization system.
But that's okay.
It'll be enough to pick a fight with them.
But if we do that, they'll definitely retaliate against us.
He's right. Not just the Square,
but your family will be in danger too!
I'll leave them to you.
Make sure you keep them safe.
I'll teach them that we're too troublesome to swallow.
Then, depending on how they react,
the mother and her child will have to be...?
That's right. Even if that's the case...
...will you be able to do it?
Tell me... Don't just take orders...
Tell me your answer.
Come on! Hurry up!
Coming.
Thank you.
No problem.
Looks like you're getting used to it.
In order to blend in with a flock of sheep, you have to wear sheep skin.
What were the characteristics of the fifth to last person that we passed by?
A white male in his twenties.
He was wearing a Dodgers cap and a black shirt.
Based on how he was talking on his cell,
he got separated from a friend and is trying to find a place where they can meet up.
Correct.
Even when wearing sheep skin,
a wolf shouldn't forget his sense of smell.
That's also something you taught me.
Hey, hold on.
Okay, got it. Buy it for him.
Well then, Duke. See you later.
Okay, Daddy.
Tony, please be careful.
Anton said that everything is ready.
Let's go.
What're you hardheaded guys doing all dressed up tonight?
Old man Gant... I don't think it has anything to do with you.
Don't do anything that would hurt the citizens, got it?
If you do...
I know.
Your residence is thoroughly guarded by Abel and Bark.
That place is the safest place in LA tonight.
What about Inferno?
They'll be here soon.
So it's okay to have you handle it, Ms. McCunnen?
Yes. We have to think about the future too, so I'll represent Inferno at the meeting.
I appreciate your thoughtfulness.
My feelings are a bit mixed though,
being the one in charge of this district.
I'd like to make Melanie Square ours without turning it into a battlefield.
I'm counting on you, Ms. McCunnen.
You needn't worry. If one has two trump cards,
they can win most games.
Rob just called and said that the meeting is about to start.
I see...
Please don't worry.
So far, things have been quiet around here.
So long as nothing happens tonight, the game is ours.
Yes...
I didn't expect a babe like you to be an Inferno executive.
Many people get surprised.
I sure hope you aren't just a decoration.
I thought we told you to bring your boss.
I won't say that I'm the head of Inferno.
However, I've been given full authority with regards to this case.
She's right.
Please refrain from speaking rudely to her.
Back off from Melanie Square.
You think we'd just agree to that?
We'll pay the debt later on.
That's the code of conduct among mafia, is it not?
You won't have to. All we want...
...is Melanie Square.
Those at the Square are all people who were driven out from other places and live in obscurity.
They are inept and cannot live anywhere else besides the Square.
Even so, they're our family.
I can't betray our family.
That's against my principles.
Old-fashioned and hardheaded.
You're just like your nickname, Tony Stone.
Could you still say the same thing if I told you that your real family was in danger?
If you do that, you'll lose everything, too.
Is that okay with you?
I'll ask you once more.
Will you hand Melanie Square over to Inferno?
No.
You're late, Phantom.
What the hell?!
Duck! It's a sniper!
Shoot back! Kill the sniper!
We can't! He's too far!
Zwei, you're up.
What?! What about the Boss?!
Is he okay?!
The negotiations were broken off.
Boss and Anton are all right, but Rob and Lutz were...
Oh no...!
In any case, please go stay with Duke.
Okay.
They're... crazy...
Inferno!
Mommy!
Duke, haven't you gone to bed yet?
You see, the guy I saw at the amusement park is...
What?
Eva! Eva!
Fantastic.
You're... fantastic.
Being a tool... Being a device...
All we need to do is function.