When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Let us stop the chitchat now
Come, let us quietly see this through
If it's romance, look, it's already begun
Maria All the Way
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Today, we have an original
episode drafted by Mr. Hata.
Isn't that right?
That's what I hear.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
The Strangest High-Deflation Ever.
Play Your Games and Don't Build Up a Backlog
Damn it! Damn it!
What is this game?!
This game's got awfully crappy graphics.
This is a PS3 game?
No.
But I'm tired of high-deflation games,
so I felt like giving an older game a try.
Huh. So you're sayin'
modern games're lukewarm?
Then wouldn't it be better
to play outside or somethin'?
That would be tiring.
Well, yeah, but...
Rather than do something so tiring,
I want to play games from the good old days
and get a renewed perspective
on our current era of high-deflation.
New Heroic Dragon Tale
I obtained an old, rare game in
an attempt to cleanse my tainted soul
with the purity of
something old school, but...
It's more you-know-what than rare, though.
Well, to put it simply,
that's what it comes down to.
I mean, I'd heard that it was you-know-what,
but this game is even worse
than I'd been led to expect.
But isn't that the appeal of retro games?
A Black-Hearted Santa
has appeared!
Hayate LV Small Fry
Command
Run
Tools
Attack
Defend
Kowtow
I mean, yeah, the audio's fair at best,
the movement's choppy,
Hayate throws a punch!
The Black-Hearted
Santa swiftly dodges!
and the screen's so cluttered,
you can barely tell where you're at...
The Black-Hearted
Santa
attacks!
He delivers
a marvelous blow!
Hayate takes
69372 damage!
Hayate has died.
Shuddup, you Kansai person.
Shuddup,
you Kansai person.
Go have some
octopus balls
Go have some octopus balls
as your side dish with white rice.
as your side dish
with white rice.
The hell was that?!
You makin' fun of Kansai people?!
H-Hey, Sakuya, you don't have to
get so pissed at a silly game.
And you, your game play sucks,
so don't blame it on the game
And you,
your game play sucks,
so don't blame it
on the game,
you little squirt!
YOU LITTLE SQUIRT!
What did you say?!
Why you! You're nothing but a crappy game!
I'm never enterin' more than
"AAAA" for a character name!
Grab a hold of freedom
Um, dinner is ready.
What are you two both doing?
Nothing! We were just consigning
a societal evil to oblivion!
Melf me all da way
One hour of
gaming a day
Pardon?
Never mind that. What's for dinner?
Green peppers stuffed with meat,
among other things.
What? But I hate green peppers.
It's 'cause yer so picky
that you're not growin' any taller.
Nah, it's not just yer height...
Wh-What are you trying
to get at?! Don't stare at me!
I didn't say anythin' yet.
What d'you think I was referrin' to?
The next morning!
Butlers must be manly!!
Why does the sun...
...rise every morning?
What are you doing griping about
nature in your first waking moment?
The sun just doesn't get it!
It's only when you miss deadlines
and take breaks once in while
that people will appreciate it
when you actually have a chapter in print.
A-Airing such an appalling statement
on TV is a bit questionable...
Anyway, please change quickly
and prepare for school.
Sakuya and the others
are waiting, after all.
Makita! Kunieda!
All righty, I'm off to school!
Hmph! School, school! What an annoying girl!
Hmph! School, school! What an annoying...
Tell me, Maria, is this déjà vu?
When watching Hayate the Combat Butler,
please keep the room bright
and sit away from the TV
I feel like I've seen this scene before.
The thing is, it seems
this episode takes place
during the same time
period as two episodes back.
Hmm, zapping, huh?
Anime sure has become
a lot more complicated.
After all, this is the era of DTT,
EPG recording, digital coloring,
outsourcing whole episodes overseas,
the leaking of storyboards
to online auctions, and manga ministers...
Yes, it can't be helped.
I don't like it, but I'll go along
with that course of action.
Especially since it's looking like
I might not have to go to school.
Oh, dear, so that's
the tack you're taking this time.
Oh dear
"'All righty, I'm off to school!'
"Sakuya left the room in high spirits,
"but she suddenly got the urge
to watch M-1 DVDs
"and she u-turned back
to second floor of the residence.
"And click. When she opened the door
to the gaming room, there she found..."
Heh heh heh heh....
You saw me. Bastard,
you're not getting out of here alive.
You~~~ saw~~~
me~~~ Bastard...
Makita. Kunieda.
Yes, Miss!
Nooo! Wait! Oh, you're going to break me!
Eh? It's not a small fire?
Wait! What's a game console doin',
talkin' like it's totally normal?!
This is horrible... I'm all sticky, tima.
"Tima"? What's with that
artificial-soundin' sentence endin'?
Was that the cuttin' edge for yer time?
Ah-ha, I bet you're the demon king
inside that game or somethin'.
What superhuman deductive powers!
Tima! How did you know?!
It seems she was really right.
Ah, I knew it!
Yeah, lemme guess.
'Cause you're a crappy game,
you've gotten shoddy
treatment over the years
and the resentment's been
gradually buildin' up,
and with yer rage over
what happened last night,
ya finally became aware as a monster.
Yeah, that's 'bout what happened, right?
Wh-What superhuman deductive powers, tima!
I already said that.
Besides, I may not look it,
but I'm a Kansai person, who's so
capable I even turned down Hakuou.
And we don't got enough time.
Makita! Kunieda! Shut that thing down
before it gets up to no good!
Go after its reset button or the power cord!
Yes, Miss!
N-Nooo! Don't come near me, tima!
But that "tima" sentence
endin' sure gets on my nerves.
Wait... Huh?
Tima!
You will be punished!
The Demon King's castle!
On Sale
Demon King
the Great Slygian of Abe (temp)
I can't move! I'm unable to escape, tima!
You will be punished! You will be
punished! You will be punished!
Oh, shut up, shut up, shut up!
And after I finally got out
into the real world, too...
Th-The hero will come
at the end of the world...
That's right, tima! I'm the final boss.
House For Sale
And this castle is the stage
for the final battle.
If I can turn the tables on the hero here...
That will be the end of dreams...
Tima!
This time, I just might
get out of this place, tima!
Um, don't you normally get sent back
to the title screen or something?
All right! Now that's decided,
I better start by capturing the hero, tima!
Not that she's listening...
Push.
Ultimate Super Awesome
Demon King Guillotine Scythe
Th-That should do it!
Um, Mr. Hero, please fall
for the trap! Tima!
M-Maria, what do you think of this?!
Oh, my, it's fantastic!
Tima!
Where are you going?
You can't walk around the residence
dressed in a sailor uniform.
Tima-ma!
Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima!
Demon King the Great Stygian of Abe (temp)
gave herself over to lonely tears.
They're awful. No one will notice me, tima.
You will be punished!
Oh, shut up, shut up, shut up!
Huh? Has someone come, tima?
No answer.
What? After we came all this way
to see Nagi's new butler?
It can't be helped.
As much as it breaks my heart,
I guess we'll have to head out
to Ekoda or something.
Yes. And skip classes, of course.
Sanzenin
What is this?
What? Wait!
Miki?!
Miki, your panties are grownup.
They are new.
Let me see.
Can't show you!
Owowow...
Wh-What in the world?!
Heavy...
Th-Thank you for noticing me!
Uh... Ahem.
Now, heroes, hurry up and
overcome the trials and tribulations,
I hear a boinging sound.
and get to the castle, where I,
Demon King Abe, am waiting for you, tima!
What's that?
A slime has appeared!!
This is fail.
Wow! It's a moving doodle!
No, the way I see it, a crappy game
that was downtrodden for many years...
Omitting the rest of the explanation.
What?! Then we're inside
the world of a game?!
Come, heroes! After him!
After the eager monster!
Hm, it cannot be helped.
When you get down to it, it is my fault
for picking up that controller.
Since it has come to this...
Y-You can't, Miki! You can't fight it alone!
Right? Right?
Is that your final answer?
Great Demon King, she is the hero!
The slime attacks!!
The slime attacks Risa!!
Risa is hit for 42837 points!!
Oh, no!
Damnd
Sodom
Risa is dead.
Risa is dead!!
What?
I'll leave the rest to you.
N-No way!
The slime attacks!!
The slime attacks Miki!!
The slime attacks Izumi!!
N-Not good! At this rate, the heroes
I finally got will end up dead, tima!
You will be punished!
No!
Push.
Bro
Congrats to
King-Show comeback
World
Conquest
Gorangai
World
Conquest
Gorangai
Activate
Hey, are you okay?
Just barely...
Izumi Segawa
Yes! Saved by the skin of her teeth, tima!
You will be punished!
Calling me from somewhere
Somehow, I feel like on of us has it easy...
Rissy, no fair!
What?! It may not look it, but it's
cramped in here and tough for me, too!
An echoing cry on the verge of tears
Oh, I can't wait to be revived,
so I can fight with you!
I'll be right there!
Y-You do?
Because I belong to you now
Then, I'm sure it'll be rough,
but we'll revive you for sure
when we find a village or something.
I appreciate that.
By the way, could I ask you
for one more favor?
Hm? What is it?
I'm thirsty, so go buy me a Pocari.
Pushed around by the terribly selfish crowd
If you're about to fall
on to the hard asphalt
You're awful, Rissy!
Quit playing a game within a game!
Y-You're wrong! Th-This is, you know!
Here, it's okay, I'll draw you into my arms
I'm checking to see if we can make
contact with the outside world!
Lies!
While the three girls
were bickering in the game world,
there was just one person
at the residence back in the real world,
who had noticed the strange occurrence.
What shall I do?
I become lost yet again
when I woke up this morning.
Incidentally, this ghostly air...
It is likely some sort of monster.
Fruition of Love
And the monster is most likely...!
Dating Site
Not in here...
The top 3 will finally be
announced in the second half!
Sushi rice beam! (Sumeshi biimu)
Monsieur in the mood. (Musshu muramura)
Presented by Nagi Sanzenin
Today's Fortunes Countdown
Today's fortunes countdown!
Aries 4th
Sagittarius 5th
Virgo 6th
Aquarius 7th
Pisces 8th
Cancer 9th
Capricorn 10th
Leo 11th
Libra 12th
Today's 3rd Place
Coming in 3rd is Cancer.
Lucky spot is oil fields.
There may be a wonderful
encounter waiting for you.
The Much-Anticipated 2nd Place
Coming in 2nd is Taurus.
A happy day, where everything will go well.
Might be your one chance to quit being
an unproductive member of society.
1st Place
Come, let's work up that courage!
I-In first place is...!
Bright smiles! A great selection!
We, at the Rental Video
Tachibana Shinjuku Flagship store,
shall be awaiting you,
the discerning customer.
And now, please continue to enjoy
Episode 10 of Hayate the Combat Butler,
Showing Now Hayate the Combat Butler!
Episode 10. Please enjoy.
"I Saw the Tears of Snakewoman
in the Fires of Hell".
The three student council girls
trapped in the cursed game world...
...after much pain and effort,
finally arrived in
an otherworldly kind of village.
Where's the church?! We want to
revive our friend from the coffin!
Captain Cam
Nuu, nuu!
Nuu, nu-nu, nuu!
Nu-nu, nuu, nuu, nuu!
Wah! No matter who I talk to,
all they say is "nuu, nuu"!
It appears this game is too much for us.
It cannot be helped.
Since it has come to this...
I'm insanely fired up right now!
King Scascher!
Hello?
Yes, it is me. Miki.
I feel bad, but please come right away.
I'm here.
So?
That was fast!
Um, Hina, you didn't get attacked
by anything weird on your way here?
Huh? Oh, all kinds of things showed up,
but just I drove them away with this.
Oooh!
So what in the world is going on?
Would you explain it
to me so I can understand?
Do not let this shock you now.
We are actually inside a cursed game
and mumble, mumble, omitting the rest!
What are you saying?
There's no way such
an unscientific thing would happen.
What? Uh, but...
This is one of those things.
Which is to say...
Hardcore gamer Nagi must be throwing
a large surprise event for us.
Yup!
But those monsters
and things sure were well-made.
That's our student
council president for you.
A super pragmatist.
I wonder what kind of mechanism
they have that makes them move.
In a way, it's an incredible
talent that she's got.
So, you three, don't tell me you plan
to skip our afternoon classes.
N-No.
Then let's finish up here
and get back to school
before the end of lunch break.
Oh, but I wonder where the goal is.
H-How promising!
Yes! That lady is truly worthy
of being called a hero, tima!
You will be punished! You will be
punished! You will be punished!
If that lady can make it here,
maybe I can finally be
free of this annoying skull
and this meaningless "tima"
sentence ending, tima!
Push.
Over here, tima!
A full set of equipment suddenly
came falling out of the sky...
Over here, tima!
I see, so we're expected to use these
to get over to that tower.
What?
I-Is that what it means?
All right! Then let's all
go defeat the Demon King!
Hakuou, fight!
F-Fight!
Fight!
Hinagiku sure is serious.
It seems we can leave the rest
of the episode to Miss Katsura.
Yes.
Then, since this is the perfect opportunity,
I think I'll read some mail
cheering us on for once.
A postcard from penname Tama
Fangirl of N Ward, Tokyo.
"Hello to Hayate, Nagi, and Maria."
Hello!
Hello.
"I always look forward to
watching Hayate the Combat Butler."
Good. Thank you!
"By the way, I was surprised when
I saw the profiles on the official homepage.
"I had no idea that you were
just 17 years old, Maria."
Y-Yes, I'm 17 years old. What of it?
"Y-You seem rather composed
and I totally thought you were over 20.
"Wh-Why don't you try acting
more like a g-girl of 17 for once
"and say things like 'uber bad'?"
Hey, T-Tama Fangirl,
Maria is young! She's young!
After all...
I see.
So I look that old...
I don't mean to repeat myself,
but I am 17 years old.
I'm bursting with freshness!
It's not that I've aged before my time,
it's just that I face endless
hardship every day,
thanks to some people.
S-Sorry about that! We're
always grateful that we have you!
Right, Hayate?!
Hey, why haven't you said anything?!
Since the majority of the cast
is comprised of stooge characters,
I handle the straight man role
to make things interesting.
It's only natural, since I'm the one
with the most common sense here.
B-But then, a little girl sent
in this postcard to the show. Scary.
Maria seems kind of mean
It's fine. It's fine. I'm just...
Bright smiles! A great selection!
Wait! Wha?! Hayate!
Why aren't you saying?!
We, at the Rental Video
Tachibana Shinkuju Flagship store,
Um, on to the next postcard!
shall be awaiting you,
the discerning customer.
A postcard from Sergeant Naohikov
Furuitch of K Ward, Tokyo.
And now, please continue to enjoy
Episode 10 of Hayate the Combat Butler...
"I love Maria!"
Last battle!
Can't show you
Can't show
Having crossed oceans
and beat all kinds of dungeons,
with almost 100 hours
of play time behind them,
the student council party
finally made it to the Demon King!
Finally, the time has come
for the last battle
to determine the fate of this universe.
O Demon King the Great
Stygian of Abe (temp),
come fight us fair and square!
Welcome Heroes Party
Reserved
I could not have asked for more, tima.
Now, face my ultimate
super lethal technique!
Push.
The Demon King has been defeated.
What?!
Weak! The Demon King's weak!
Truly a hero. Your swordsmanship
was brilliant, tima.
Huh? But I haven't done anything yet.
I can resign myself to my fate now.
I can feel at peace crossing over
into the other world, tima.
Or so I thought, but I don't
want to go, after all, tima.
Though, I feel like it
wouldn't be so bad to go, tima.
Hmm... But then again...
Which is it?!
She is being damned indecisive.
You will be punished
for not making up your mind!
Ending 4 "Beyond Oblivion"
Hinagiku Katsura and
the three student council girls
Hinagiku Katsura
and the three student council girls
defeated the Demon King in this way
and traversed space-time,
returning safely to the real world.
With their memories of their adventures
in the game world completely lost to them...
With their memories
of their adventures in the game world
completely lost to them...
Thank you, hero. Thank you,
Hakuou Academy student council.
Kind of grateful. Kind of a happy ending.
However, your battle has only just begun.
I will fight again next time
to win the role of protagonist!
Izumi Segawa
Class: Normal
Person
Specialty:
Nothing Notable
That was kind of fun, wasn't it?
Miki Hanabishi
Class: Fox Hound
Specialty:
Intel Gathering
I suppose that's
a happily-ever-after for now.
Risa Asakaze
Class: Aspiring
Good-for-Nothing
Specialty: H*rricane M*xer
Hinagiku Katsura
Class: Student Council President
Yes.
Hey, wait! Aren't ya forgettin' somethin'?!
Pardon me. I opened the door normally.
What's up with this old
Showa-era punch line?!
Is it me or are we gettin'
shoddy treatment lately?!
It's always been like that.
Uh, next time, we will return
to our normal format
and bring you a butler episode
that will thrill you!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
Nagi's...
Sign: Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Since Hayate is out this time I will be
doing as I please with this segment!
Oh, my, this could mean trouble.
Now's your only chance
to sit back and relax, Maria.
What?
The fact that I am in charge of this segment
means that I am free to do whatever I wish!
In response to requests from Maria fans,
I could insert a fan service shot of Maria!
Nooo!
Nobody may want it, but I could
also insert a shot of Klaus bathing!
Nooo!
Keep doing this and production
will never catch up to the schedule!
Oh, that would be bad.
We won't do any more Klaus after this!
Bye-bye!
Preview
Nagi, why don't we go
to the primary family residence for once,
where your grandfather resides?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
I would like to introduce Hayate as well.
I don't want to. Besides,
I don't think there's any need
to pay our respects
to that old geezer at this point.
Man, it's been a long time
since I've seen Grandpa Mikado.
I'm gonna pester him for some pocket change.
What's this, Saku? You're going, too?
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"The Value of My Life: Priceless".
In other words, your life
is utterly meaningless.
The Value of My Life: Priceless
An armor runs within your heart!