Where'd Masaomi go?
He went on ahead. He said he had something to do.
The higher the flames rise—
We're done, finished!
You only did what you thought was right, didn't you?
This is from the Dollars' leader, isn't it?
And if the Dollars are behind this, then...we'll crush the Dollars.
This way!
You go that way! Block off the entrance!
Why...?
Why is Kida...?
The girl ran...
...to escape the shadow that was chasing her.
She just wanted to know...
...the truth.
What a pain.
Where'd that brat go?
We won't let her get away.
Why is Kida...?
She couldn't feel anything else.
Why...?
The shock from what she had just seen was
the only thing resonating throughout her body.
You must be happy that you're being released sooner than predicted.
Thank you very much.
I really appreciate what you've done for me.
Here.
Thanks.
The Slasher incidents suddenly ceased after
that night, and the city's peace was restored.
And Sonohara Anri's uneventful everyday
life should have returned to her as well.
Sonohara!
Great! I made it in time!
I got held up by class committee stuff...
Ryugamine...
I heard you're going to start attending school again tomorrow, so you're okay?
Yes, I'm all better now.
Oh, I'll take your bags.
N-No...I'm fine...
Let him take them!
Mikado ran his heart out so he could hold those bags for you.
Anri, how much do you think I had to listen to this today?
"Sonohara's getting discharged today!"
"Will she be able to come to school tomorrow?"
"Anri's so erotically cute."
I didn't say that last part!
Um...thank you for coming to visit me so often, Kida and Ryugamine.
It's no big deal...
By the way, Masaomi, you just came out from the hospital, didn't you?
Ah, yeah...
I must've just missed her on my way in.
Hmm.
Oh yeah, Sonohara.
Here are my notes for the time you've been absent.
If you're okay with using mine, I'll let you borrow them.
My handwriting's pretty bad, so they might be a bit hard to read, but...
If that's okay, feel free to use them.
Oh, just a second.
I know I brought this one today...
Kida seems...somehow different.
She felt vaguely discomforted by him...
Ever since he first visited her in the hospital.
There. That should do it.
Kida...?
Anri...
What...happened?
Um, it's nothing, really.
The Slasher kind of...
Oh, but it's really nothing at all.
Sorry, something just came up.
I guess I'll have to let Prince Mikado do the honors of escorting the princess back home.
You won't get another chance like this for a hundred years!
See you.
Oh... See you tomorrow!
And so, an unknown feeling of insecurity enveloped her.
Don't do anything until I get there!
Got it?!
A lot of people have joined the Yellow Scarves recently, huh?
That's very true.
They stand out much more than the
Dollars, since you can tell who they are.
That gang had been around for a while,
but it seems like they've changed somehow.
They've changed?
I can't really put my finger on it,
but they're different from how they used to be...
Somehow...
I feel like they've become more violent.
Saika has entered the chat room.
Oh, good evening, Saika.
Good evening.
Welcome.
Good...evening.
Um, I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You weren't familiar with the Internet before,
so you got a virus and that's how everything happened, right?
You can't help that.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You're apologizing too much.
By the way, Saika, do you know of a gang called the Yellow Scarves?
You mean the people who wear yellow cloth around the city?
Yeah, that's them.
There's also another group that's a lot like them called the Dollars.
Due to the Slasher incidents, both of those groups...
...are in pretty dire straights right now.
Um...
What do you mean by that?
Give it a rest, Kanra.
Don't bring up that stuff with someone who doesn't know anything bout it.
No,
you have to know this stuff if you live in Ikebukuro!
The perpetrator in the Slasher case has yet to be caught, right?
Anyway, both the Yellow Scarves and the Dollars have had their members fall victim to the Slasher.
Apparently, they both think that the
Slasher is in league with the other gang.
The Dollars don't seem so hung up on that idea...
They don't know much about each other,
so I'm sure that breeds misunderstandings.
Either way, if neither of them take matters into their own
hands with the Slasher, blood will rain down upon Ikebukuro.
It'll be really scary...
Now that's a real rivalry!
You don't have anything to worry about, Anri.
Those gangs are running amuck of their own accord.
You're not the real perpetrator, so it
doesn't matter if you come forward or not.
Don't be hasty.
The police are really scary now.
They truly are scary.
They really are!
Especially the traffic cops!
Thank you so much.
Huh?! Oh, right...
I'll teach you about private conversations later.
Um, excuse me, but this is it for me today.
Oh, okay.
See you around, Saika.
'Night.
See you.
Saika has left the chat room.
Alright, I guess I'll be logging off, too.
See you later.
See you around.
Setton has left the chat room.
Kanra...
About the Slasher incidents...
I'll let you know if I find anything out.
At a bargain price, that is.
The real perpetrator has to be somewhere in this city.
The sooner he's caught, the sooner the Yellow Scarves and the Dollars can clear up their misunderstandings.
I wonder if it'll really be that easy.
Neither the Yellow Scarves nor the
Dollars are completely cohesive groups.
There'll be some people who shake down members of the other group in the name of that rivalry.
It'll simply turn into a real conflict if things keep going like this.
I won't let that happen.
I wonder...
I don't think you can stop it anymore.
And there's nothing you can do about the Yellow Scarves.
Even so, I won't let it happen.
Hmm. I'm looking forward to that.
"I have to do something,"
thought the girl who houses an ethereal sword inside her body.
thought the girl who'd only seen the world through a picture frame.
However...
...the boy who'd passed through that window and had visited her world was already restrained...
...by the heavy yoke of his own past.
He could no longer escape.
Hello?
I see.
Got it.
I'll be right there.
Sorry! Something just came up with my friend!
Oh, really?
If you want to hate someone, hate my friend to your heart's content!
Hate doesn't cost anything, and it doesn't cause me any harm!
It's a perfect "two birds with one stone," it's "many wives for one man!"
"Many wives for one man?"
See you tomorrow!
I wonder if it's really that important?
Don't you think Kida's been acting strange lately?
Really?
You're sure it's not all in your head?
Um...sorry.
I have some business to attend to.
See you.
Did you hear that some of the Dollars
were shaken down by the Yellow Scarves?
Apparently, they were beaten to within an inch of their lives.
The Yellow Scarves are the ones saying that the Slasher is part of the Dollars, aren't they?
The boy who leads the Dollars knew that things couldn't go on like this.
However, he didn't yet know that he was
being used like a pawn on a chessboard.
Customers, eat sushi!
Sushi is the heart of Japan.
It's enka!
I wonder if it's true that he does a Cossack dance when you order take-out?
Come to think of it, he was on a delivery when he followed those kids last night.
If you swing that rod, I'm going to turn you into sushi.
Human sushi... Ooh, it hurts and it tastes bad.
Luck sure doesn't last very long.
Hm?
Man, those clouds look ominous...
Does anyone know anything about the Dollars or the Yellow Scarves?
Anyone...?
Our boss is Kida Masaomi.
I've seen him with you, mother.
He said he was going to get revenge on your enemy, mother.
That's...
Of course she couldn't believe it.
However, her children are unable to lie to her.
Where's Kida...?
He's going to a meeting today.
Please take me to that meeting.
And so...
...she found out everything.
Kida is...
Is it in the back there?
If she doesn't run...
It's easy.
Why is Kida...?
I'll love everyone.
I'll slash open those yellow children and love them, too.
What will happen to her?
I'll love them in your stead, since you can't.
I don't...want to hurt anyone!
The boy would find out that she's a monster.
She trembled in fear.
It's too narrow.
I'll go.
Kida?!
Help me!
Someone, please help me!
Hey! It's that thing...
And, standing there in the rain...
...was the female dullahan.
The only thing the trapped girl could do was ask for help from someone like her who wasn't supposed to exist in this world.
It scaled the wall with her bike!
I can believe that.
It's going to make a move!
...Are you serious...?
Celty!
I'll explain later.
We're getting out of here. Hop on the back.
O-Okay!
Th-Thank you very much.
Hold on tight.
I've seen you around for a while,
that suit seems a little tight for a guy.
I don't care if you're a guy, but I could
love you just for the suit if you're a girl.
They do say, "love the Buddha, love his clothes."
This is the guy who's always with Mikado and Anri...
Oh, I see...
She doesn't want him to see her face.
I don't understand the situation, but I'll do it.
What?
Damn!
You monster!
Don't!
They knew one of them had to be the legendary headless horseman.
The fragments of information they knew came together in an instant.
The intruder wielded a sword like that of the Slasher.
And the black biker had come to save her.
There were also rumors that the black biker was part of the Dollars.
They all arrived at the same conclusion:
the Slasher is part of the Dollars.
The boy didn't know whether or not that conclusion was correct.
But what he did know was that no
matter how much he thought about it,
he wouldn't be able to restrain
those who had witnessed this incident.
Hey...
Do you know about dullahans?
Huh? Umm... No, I don't.
They visit the homes of those who're about to die.
They're headless knights who ride headless horses.
Well, I guess they're like the Grim Reaper.
The boy suddenly thought:
"Someone amongst us may die..."
Why...do I want to see Saki at a time like this?
"The blue dynasty is dead."
"The sky has fallen."
That was the slogan that a certain yellow flag-toting group used in the Annals of the Three Kingdoms.
It certainly isn't very blue.
Well, it's not very yellow, either.
Tanaka Taro has entered the chat room.
Kanra has entered the chat room.
Gooood evenin'.
Are you the only one here, Taro?
Kanra has entered the chat room.
Good evening.
It looks like it.
Starting right off with a private conversation, are we?
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Um, have the Yellow Scarves always been in Ikebukuro?
They started up about three years ago.
At first, they were fairly docile.
The boy who leads the Dollars learned about the heated
rivalry between the Blue Squares and the Yellow Scarves.
He remained unaware of the fact that his best friend's former girlfriend was a casualty of that conflict...
...and that the man who was answering his
questions controlled the mind of that girl,
as well as left an incurable wound on his best friend.
...So, only the Yellow Scarves survived—
However, the Blue Squares didn't die.
What do you mean?
The leader of the Yellow Scarves got tired of fighting,
and after he left,
they joined the Yellow Scarves.
You mean they merged?
To put it simply, yes.
I'm sure neither gang—outside of their respective leaders—
cared enough to find out where people came from.
After they threw off their blue uniforms,
They'd get the OK just for saying,
"I want to be in the Yellow Scarves."
But what about the leader who quit?
He probably doesn't know...
...that the guys who sent his girlfriend to the
hospital are now hanging with his old friends.
You should be careful, too.
Apparently, there are some guys who are in
both the Dollars and the Yellow Scarves.
And if I spread the word that we had no part in this,
then they'll be likely to pass it on to the Yellow Scarves.
If it truly isn't the work of the Dollars, that is.
The Dollars don't have any rules, and it's not like you control everyone's actions.
While you weren't looking...
...some member of the Dollars...
...could have become the Slasher.
In other words, that's the Dollars' system.
As long as you're planning to come over to this side...
You'd best be prepared.
I'll take that to heart.
'Morning.
'Morning!
Good morning.
What's up? You don't sound too good.
Maybe you haven't fully recovered...?
No, that's not it.
'Morning.
Oh, 'morning.
Oh yeah, I just met Kida at the station and he said he's not coming to school today.
Eh? Why?
I don't know. He didn't tell me.
I see.
See you.
Oh... Thanks!
You can't run from the past, Masaomi.
You're worrying about something to do with that past, aren't you?
If you can't run from it, then you should just face it head on and beat it.
If I could settle everything with your past too, just by fighting it...
I'd love to.
Why can't you?
There's no way I could fight you, Saki.
He simply wanted a place where he belonged.
Every time he talked with his childhood friend about his new home,
he'd feel uneasy about his existence, which
was draped in hand-me-downs from the city.
He now understood...
...that amongst the Yellow Scarves, the place where he belonged...
...was with a single person named Mikajima Saki.
And now, his motivation springs from having found a new place with an important friend.
Man, it's raining again...
Kadota...
You went back?
Yes.
I'm here, so I have.
Some great person once said, "The world is a construct of the mind."
Some great person once said, "The world is a symbol."
A detestable past is the product of your imagination.
That reality never existed.
Isn't that good enough?
Next Time: The Yellow Dynasty Shall Rise.