Here, Bro.
Take this!
Komachi's recommended souvenir list!
Ta-da!
In third place...
Raw yatsuhashi.
As long as it's authentic or the original kind, it's fine with me!
In second...
Facial oil blotting paper.
Get some for Mom, too.
Now, what's in first?!
Komachi's Recommended
Souvenir List
1) Find out after these ads
2) Facial Oil Blotting Paper
3) Raw Yatsuhashi
1) Find out after these ads
2) Facial Oil Blotting Paper
Well, what is it?
The best souvenirs
would be your precious memories!
So cheeky. So cute!
...Chiman...
Hachiman...
You didn't call Uno!
Yay!
You're not even in our class.
Yay—
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something real
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Scariest Haunted House Of All Time
Hayato, I'm scared!
Shit!
Shit! Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit! Shiiit!
What was that creepy laughter?
I can't handle this stuff.
What's so scary about
ghosts in haunted houses?
Human beings are far scarier.
Contrarian or not, you're kinda like
a knight in shining armor right now.
I'm saying that I'm terrified of haunted houses where people do the scaring.
Or not! Some knight you are!
You seem just fine, Totsuka.
Yeah, I love this stuff.
Kawasaki?
Kawasaki!
Oww...
S-Sorry! I hope I didn't hurt you!
You totally did, but...
Uh...
Well, how do I say this...
Thanks.
Let's go.
Scariest Haunted House Of All Time
It's finally over.
That was pretty scary.
Wasn't that fun?
You guys look like you enjoyed yourself.
Shall we get going, then?
Oh, I'll go get Ebina.
Wooden sword slash!
Time to go, Ebina!
Think the haunted house helped?
Dunno.
Hup.
Fancy running into you.
Didn't know you were here.
Well, I am.
Apparently this place is also known as
"The Garden With Tiger Cubs Crossing."
I wanted to find out which part
represented the tigers.
Oh? Was her interest piqued
'cause tigers are felines too?
She does have a pesky,
frisky love of cats, after all.
Oh, Yukinon!
Let's take this elsewhere.
How are we doing with the request?
It's not as easy as we thought.
Right?
We don't want to go too far
and turn Ebina off.
Also...
A certain someone is acting weird.
Also, what?
Nothing. Never mind.
I'm sorry for leaving it all in your hands.
Nah, no biggie!
I don't know if this makes up for it,
but I came up with some ideas myself.
What kind of ideas?
Famous spots in Kyoto that girls might like.
I thought it could come in handy.
That's my Yukinon!
I'll head back, then.
'Kay. See you tomorrow!
See you tomorrow.
Well, if it ain't Hikio.
Hey, what exactly are you guys tryin' to pull?
Could you stop messin' with Ebina?
You listenin' to me?
I am.
And we're not messing with her.
You totally are.
It's clear as day.
You're being a pain, y'know.
A pain, huh?
But that's what someone wants us to do.
Why do you even care? It's not like it's affected you in any way.
'Scuse me?
It's about to.
Y'know...
Hasn't your relationship with Yui taught you anything 'bout Ebina?
W-We're not in a relationship.
Hold your horses, creep.
I know Yui'd never date you.
That ain't what I was talkin' about.
I meant talkin' to Yui, and all that stuff.
Creep.
Did you have to say it twice?
Ebina's a pretty face so long as
she keeps her trap shut,
so a lotta guys asked me to introduce them.
Then when I try an' set 'em up,
she acts like she'd rather drop dead.
I thought she was just shy, so I kept at it.
And then she smiled and went,
"Fine. Whatever."
Like she didn't know me no more.
Ebina doesn't like talking
about herself, and I don't ask,
but I'm pretty sure she hates that kinda stuff.
That's not quite right.
If you had to sacrifice a bunch to protect something,
you'd probably throw it all away.
Even the relationships you currently have.
Y'know, I'm having fun right now.
So stop stickin' your nose
where it don't belong.
You don't need to worry, then.
Hayama said he'd handle it.
Wassup with that?
Well, if Hayato says so, then we're good.
Whoa! This is amazing!
What a view! You can see
the entire city from here!
Time for a break.
You're right.
Oh, it's Tobecchi!
Yo, 'sup!
We meet again!
Hikitani, you remember my request, right?
Huh? Yeah.
How's it going among the men?
It's going good, I guess?
They played cards at night and shit.
But if I can't see it,
it's not a feast for my eyes!
I want the guys to be tight
where I can see them!
That'd be the best!
Well, we're going to Arashiyama, too.
Maybe then...
I'm counting on you.
Randen Arashiyama Station
You won't have any room left for dinner.
You eat it, Hikki.
I don't want it.
Why does this girl randomly
start biting into things?
If she'd at least offered halfsies,
I would've taken it.
What do I do with this, Yukinon?
I'll have just a bit.
You help out, too.
I guess I could eat some.
Then...
Here.
I feel like a pet getting fed.
Not bad.
Food tastes divine when
you don't have to work for it.
Wow!
This place is incredible!
Indeed.
Look at the ground, too.
Lanterns, huh?
This is it!
This is the perfect spot, I think!
For what?
T-To be asked out.
Why the passive voice?
It does seem to be the ideal location.
R-Right?
If Tobe's gonna go for it,
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
it's gotta be here.
Damn, I'm startin' to get nervous!
Shit!
It's all good.
You're getting a girlfriend, huh?
I bet you'll stop hanging out with me.
That won't happen!
This is bad!
You got this, man!
Even I'm getting kinda nervous.
Hey, Tobe.
What is it, Hayato?
I'm losin' my mind here!
Actually, never mind.
What the hell?
I thought I'd tell you to break a leg, but I lost confidence once I got a look at you.
Wow, you jerk!
Oh, but that helped me relax.
You're being awfully uncooperative.
Am I?
You are.
In fact, it even felt like
you were getting in the way.
I didn't really mean to,
but I don't want things to change.
I like Tobe, Hina,
and the time we all spend together.
So—
If this is all it takes to tear you apart,
then maybe you weren't good friends at all.
Maybe.
But...
Once you lose something, it's gone forever.
In my opinion, it's messed up to try and make such shallow relationships work.
Really?
I, for one, don't think they're shallow.
Right now, my surroundings mean everything to me.
No, they are shallow.
And where does that leave Tobe?
I told him multiple times to forget about it.
I don't think Hina's ready to open up just yet,
but you never know what
might happen in the future.
That's why I didn't want Tobe to rush things.
Talk about selfish.
That's just your perspective.
In that case,
how about you?
What would you do?
Who cares about me?
"If it were up to me"?
Thinking about that is a waste of time.
Hayama and I are different.
Likewise with Tobe.
My opinion on this matter
is completely irrelevant.
So basically, you don't want anything to change?
Yeah. That's right.
You were the last person I wanted to rely on...
The feeling's mutual, dumbass.
I don't understand what it is
Hayama's trying to protect,
but I don't need to.
Not knowing lets me do
things nobody else can.
Tobe.
Hikitani?
Dude, I can't take it.
My heart might explode at any moment.
Say, what if you get rejected?
Why are you bullying me
right before I ask her out?
Just answer me before Ebina gets here.
Well, I ain't gonna give up that easily.
You know I'm usually
whatever about stuff, right?
But this—I'm serious about this.
That so?
Then you'd better keep at it until the bitter end.
Sure thing!
You're a real bro, after all.
Hell no, dumbass!
You can be a nice guy at times, huh?
What brought this on?
It's not what you think. Seriously.
Tobe's going to get rejected.
Perhaps.
I guess.
But there is a way to make things work out.
What is it?
Well, we'll leave it to you.
Yep.
Uh...
Yeah?
First off, Tobe's gonna get shot down for sure.
He's probably prepared for the worst, but what about the others?
Tobe's not the only one who holds their group dear.
That's why she came to us with that request.
That's why he was agonizing over it.
"I don't wanna lose this."
"I don't wanna let it go."
All three of them want the same thing.
I, uh...
Er...
To keep Tobe from being rejected, their group from falling apart,
and their friendship with Ebina the same...
There really is only one thing I can do!
The thing is...
I... I...
I...
I've liked you for a long time!
Please go out with me!
I'm sorry.
I don't want to be in a relationship right now.
It doesn't matter who asks me.
I will not date them.
Is that all?
Bye.
You heard her.
Hikitani, dude, that was not fair.
Well, I'm glad I found out
before I got shot down, but...
That was not cool at all.
It just means now's not the right time.
But hey, enjoying what we have right now isn't all that bad.
I guess.
She did say "right now."
Hikitani, bro,
I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna back down.
Aww!
Come on, cheer up!
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I knew that was the only way
you could do things, and yet...
I'm sorry.
I don't want your damn apologies.
I hate your methods.
Yukinon...
I'm having trouble putting it into words,
but I really hate the way you do things.
Yukinon...
I'm heading back.
W-We should go, too.
Right.
That wasn't such a great plan, huh?
It came out of nowhere, so Hina let it get away from her...
Yeah.
Still, that was quite shocking.
For a second there, I thought you were serious.
Don't be stupid.
I know, right?
But...
But hey...
Make this the last time, okay?
It was the most effective way.
That's all there is to it.
It's not about that.
There were guys who didn't want a resolution.
People who wanted to maintain the status quo.
And you can't please everyone, right?
As the words escape my lips, I realize...
that it was a fallacious argument.
The kind of deception that I hated more than anything in the world.
Tobecchi didn't get rejected,
the guys seemed to still be on good terms,
and it was a weight off Hina's shoulders...
Now things can go back to normal tomorrow,
like nothing's changed.
But...
But, you know,
would it kill you to spare a thought for how someone feels?
How can you be so smart, and yet not understand something that simple?
I never wanted to see something like that.
HelloHello!
Did you wait long?
Nah.
I figured I should thank you.
No need.
We still haven't fulfilled your request.
On the surface, yes.
But you knew what I was implying, right?
When she said she wanted the guys to get along amongst themselves,
she meant she wanted no part of them.
In other words, she wanted us to prevent Tobe's confession.
I bet she talked to Hayama about this, too.
That's why he was beside himself and acted so wishy-washy.
Thanks for what you did.
You're a lifesaver.
Tobe may seem like trash,
but I think he's a nice guy, you know?
Not happening.
If I were to date someone right now,
there's no way it'd work out.
How can you be so sure?
Because I know.
I know I'm rotten to the core.
I guess that's that, then.
Yeah.
That's that.
You know,
maybe it could work out if I was with you.
Don't even joke about it.
I might fall for you if you whisper sweet nothings like that.
I actually do like how you're such an
open book with people who don't matter.
What a coincidence.
I like that part of me, too.
I'm no better.
I like how I'm capable of saying things I don't really mean, too.
You see...
I like my current self and the way things are.
I haven't had anything like this in ages, so I don't want to let go of it.
I like where I stand right now,
and the people who stand with me.
That's why...
I hate myself.
Everyone has something they hold dear, something they never want to lose.
That's why they pretend.
That's why they hide the truth.
And that's why they lie.
But...
The biggest liar of all
His and Her Confessions
Won't Reach Anyone.
was me.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
Silently, Yukinoshita Yukino Makes Her Decision.
Sure is quiet without Bro around,
right, Kaa?
I wonder if he's doing all right.
What do you think, Kaa?
It's so boring without him around.
Let's play, Kaa!
There, there! You're so cute!
Your fur's so silky! There, there!
Come back, Kaa!
I hope Bro comes back soon.