So Ra No Wo To
There we go!
It's fall now.
A Typhoon Passes - Illusion and Reality
So your dad was a tanker?
That's right.
He was one of the
legendary heroes
who led over a thousand
citizens and soldiers
out of the surrounded
city of Wardenburk
in just six Type-2 Millipads!
Amazing.
Isn't it?
And when he was wounded
in battle,
he met my mother, who was a medic
at the hospital he went to.
And you ended up their kid.
Yup!
Am I a potato?
My! What a wonderful potato...
You took such good care
of them, Kana-chan.
We'll be able to share some
with the townspeople.
Oh, Claus-san is coming, too.
Maybe we'll give him
some as a present.
He's coming?
You really like him, don't you?
I-It isn't that I like him...
I respect him.
Poke.
Rio-sempai...
I didn't know she could do that.
She's really good!
The wind's started to blow.
The weather's going to get bad soon.
We should go inside.
Right!
You, too, Noël-chan.
Like...
Isn't something strange
about Rio-sempai?
How so?
The way she was playing
that trumpet?
Wasn't that wonderful?
She's so cool.
She seems kind of down.
Rio-sempai never talks
more than she has to.
But... I know! Dinner!
That tempura was
good, wasn't it?
Yup! The potatoes
were so crisp...
That's not it!
Here you go, Rio.
Eat up while it's hot.
Thanks.
Is it good?
Yeah.
I see.
I'm glad.
She was scarfing down
the green peppers!
Rio-sempai, eating peppers?
That's right!
No matter how chopped-up
they are,
Rio-sempai always finds the peppers
and takes them out!
Well...
That could be bad.
Poke.
Is this Claus-san?
Yeah! It's my treasure!
The Desert Wolf, Miracle Claus!
On his left breast, a wolf's head
tattoo symbolizes the glory
and unity of the 481st platoon!
Isn't it cool?
You can't have it.
Don't worry too much, OK?
The thing with the captain was
overthinking on our parts.
'Cause it's Rio-sempai!
She's cool, awesome,
and so pretty.
Yeah!
I'm sure she conquered her hatred of green
peppers and can eat them now.
Kureha-chan, you really
like her, don't you?
She's the person I look up to!
Me, too, but...
What do you think, Noël-chan?
Poke...
Watch out!
Noël-chan's asleep.
Oh, well. She can have
half my bed, I guess.
Kanata, you grab that end.
OK!
You forgot to turn off
the fire in the bath.
Sorry. I wasn't thinking.
The way you seem so on top of things, but actually
aren't, is one of your charm points.
But lately, there's been
too much of that.
I'm sorry.
Do you regret hanging
up on your father?
It can't be helped, I guess.
I'll cover for your problems
with your job.
At least be an awesome sempai
when they're around, OK?
Is that the wind?
No.
Sorry for dropping by so late.
It's a Class-1 Priority.
Who's it for?
Master Sergeant Rio Kazumiya
of the 1121 Platoon.
Please take it.
Major, come in.
Even the Desert Wolf couldn't
go anywhere in this rain.
I told you not to call me that.
I'm sorry.
As an apology, how about
some hot tea and a bath?
Thank you for completing your
mission in this typhoon!
I'm sorry all we have is
leftovers from dinner.
Here you go.
You should've woken me
up when he got here!
These are good!
It's even good cold.
The green peppers
are quality, too.
Really?
I was the one who picked
and fried them!
You'll be quite a wife someday.
Is that a new paper?
Yes, the Major brought
it with him.
How are the peace talks?
The conference isn't going well.
Neither side's conditions
are being met...
If Princess Iliya were still alive,
things might be different.
Princess Iliya...
You don't know her?
She was the hero of Vingt!
The first princess of
Archduke Arkadia!
She's the Helvetian army's
goddess of victory!
She's a tanker goddess, right up there
with Claus the Desert Wolf!
Kureha, that's actually-
Is everyone here?
There's an emergency!
Rio!
What's going on?
One of Yumina's kids has
been missing all day.
Help us look!
What?
Yumina-san, who vanished?
Seiya-san.
The river's risen quite a bit.
The fields downstream haven't
been harvested yet.
If the dam breaks, they're all done for.
I've never been to the city.
Show me around, Kureha.
OK!
I'm really sorry.
I only took my eyes off
him for a second...
Search and rescue
is an army's job.
Leave it to us.
Let's go.
Right!
Seiya!
Seiya-san!
Wow. There's so much water...
If he fell...
Seiya!
Seiya-san!
What?
You!
You know something, don't you?
You came out here because you
have some idea where he is!
Tell me!
Where is Seiya?
The fields...
The fields?
Yumina-oneechan loves eggplants.
So everyone used their
allowances and...
Seiya must've...
Where is it?
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing, downriver
in the middle of a typhoon?
I must protect the eggplants!
What?
You idiot!
Everyone's risking their
lives for you!
No one asked you to come!
I didn't ask for help!
What?!
Stop being such a brat!
Listen...
Kids without parents have to be stronger
than those who have them.
When you cause trouble for people,
you're not the only one they get angry at.
They get mad at Yumina.
Your big sister, too.
Kureha...
OK.
I'm an orphan, too. So I know.
Now, let's get back.
But...
Are you going to keep whining?
Hold up.
When you've worked really
hard to raise something,
you value it the same
as your own life.
These are big enough
to be eaten.
They'll be great pickled.
Thanks, mister!
Major...
Seiya-kun's started going back up.
Major, go on ahead!
N-No... You go first.
Leave the rear to me.
OK!
They're both safe.
But...
Now, they have no way
to get back up.
This is really bad...
Thank you.
The situation is bad.
But you're with me!
I believe we'll be OK.
You're wrong...
Did you say something?
No...
Listen, don't be afraid.
You're with Miracle Claus now!
Right!
The ground's starting to collapse!
The flooding's making the
ground crumble...
Damn! This is why I hate kids!
Kids who don't listen should just be tied
up and locked in a room somewhere!
Rio!
What good will scaring them do?
You know they're always
watching you.
I'm sorry... That was too far.
B-But I'm sure it'll be all right.
Claus-san is supposed to
be a miracle worker.
That's not true.
He's not the Desert Wolf
or Miracle Claus.
He just happens to have the same name
and close to the same appearance.
When they first met, Kureha just decided
it on her own and got all happy...
You know how he doesn't
really talk much, right?
He just never found the
right time to tell her...
But...
Anyway, we need to think of how
to save those two down there:
the courier with years of
service but nothing else,
and the one with tons of enthusiasm,
but no experience.
Give them a rope?
There's no good spot above them.
And it's too far to send
it from here.
There is a way to get
them the rope.
There.
The first time I met you,
I thought my dad would have been
like you if he were still alive.
I tell everyone that I knew
my dad really well,
but it's all second-hand information.
I don't actually know much.
He died when I was very little.
Kureha...
Watch the upper left?
Pull! Pull! Pull!
The Takemikazuchi!
Stop!
Noël-chan, how is it?
Linear Anchoring Coil online.
Targeting System partially
online from B7 to F5.
Initiating targeting.
It can be shot.
Prepare to fire the wire anchor!
Kanata, do it!
Right!
It's coming!
I'll protect you, in your late father's place!
Right... Major...
Ready! Fire!
Come here!
Kureha!
Major!
Kureha-chan!
Pull up the anchor!
Hurry!
Hey, Kureha...
We're safe now, so I'll tell you...
I-
I knew it.
You are the person I admire!
The blue sky after a typhoon, huh?
So you kept it up the whole time?
Honestly, I'm surprised.
I didn't think you could do it.
When I saw her eyes,
her total faith in me,
I was more scared of breaking
her dreams than of dying.
That's why I was able to do it.
In the end, I guess I'm a coward.
That's not true!
You're wonderful, Claus-san!
Listen up, miss.
Most of the time, what you
think you see in a person
and what they're really
feeling are different.
Admiring someone always
makes your vision blurry.
Someday, when you're looked at
in that way, you'll understand.
Are you sure you can't stay
until she wakes up?
Can you tell her for me?
That this is the most honorable
wound I've ever received!
A Departure - The First Snow
Next time:
A Departure.
The First Snow.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.