Dropping out of middle school
seems bad though.
Can't we wait until we graduate?
Well, the guy at the live house told us
that there are countless cases
of people getting nowhere
after hesitating too long.
But what will our parents say?
How about taking a gap year?
Oh, that could be good.
We record an album then go back to school.
No.
Trust me, it's going to work out.
The people at the agency told us.
We're a revolutionary girl band,
and we'd make it big out in Tokyo.
That they'll help us debut.
I can't imagine it going that well.
Me either.
They didn't ask us
to drop out of school, right?
Then...
I told you, that's no good.
So much confidence.
If we create a contingency plan,
we'll want to run to it.
The more escape routes we have,
the less motivated we'll be.
But...
Because it's hard, it's important
to not have any escape routes!
Momokan.
Hey! Hold on!
We're gonna make it!
Does anyone need a bathroom break?
She's asking you, Momoka.
Shut up.
Then answer her.
Why you!
Don't provoke her!
Take the pit stop.
Okay.
This unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
In a world where nothing changes
We have to live through it
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
We've already started walking
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
This hopeless city of ours
But I still saw it with my own eyes
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
First, apologize.
Excuse me?
Yeah, that makes sense.
What? You're taking her side?
There are no sides here.
But you shouldn't have
said all that there.
The stage is for the audience.
The most important place.
Not the place to spill
your personal situation!
That's exactly why I wanted to say it there
to you, Momoka!
Both of you sit down. People are staring.
You're not innocent either, Subaru.
Why didn't you stop her?
Me? As if I could stop her.
This is embarrassing,
I'm going back to the car.
We should welcome internal conflict.
This is all your fault, Momoka.
My fault?
Yes!
You said you're quitting and that
it was your last without warning!
I don't want to hear it from someone
who suddenly decided we're going pro.
You're both at fault.
You're the one who made this complicated!
I'm sorry.
Anyway,
I'm not quitting.
You're free to get all worked up,
but you'll regret it later.
Do you have any idea
how popular Diamond Dust is?
That doesn't mean I want to just give up.
I don't want to say that we were wrong.
Face reality.
You're the one turning a blind eye
and running away.
Shut up.
What do you know about me?
Then tell me!
Why did you keep playing music?
If you thought your music was no good,
why didn't you move back home?
Why did you start a new band?
Whatever, you need to go back
to cram school.
No.
Then do whatever you want.
You're running away?
Don't run away!
Shut up.
Sorry for the commotion.
They're acting!
We're filming a TV drama!
They're so passionate.
They're just stupid.
You can punch me if you want.
I'm used to it.
Go ahead and do it.
Then I'll be able to hate you.
You'd just be the same as them.
Want some water?
It's over again.
It's the beginning.
Thank you all.
I'll text you tomorrow.
We're finally freed from this tension.
Hey!
What?
What's with that guitar?
It was given to me as I was leaving.
What?
Is there a problem?
Mine gave Nina
one of her guitars she wasn't using.
She said her voice wasn't
unpleasantly seeking attention.
That she was like you, Momoka,
and wished her luck.
Thanks.
I told the car owner that you would
be the one dropping it off.
Sure, no worries.
Then maybe I'll get off here too.
I can take you.
I know going downtown is a pain.
The trains are still running.
Don't forget to take
motion sickness medicine next time.
Don't talk to me.
- See you later.
- Drive safe!
Are the trains really still running?
Nope.
I figured we should talk.
I was being considerate.
This kind of house is really relaxing.
Maybe I'll move here.
Do you want to when a room opens?
Wait, if you're going to be my roommate,
I may need to reconsider.
That's cold.
Did Rupa and Tomo know
Nina would say that?
No way.
But I bet they saw it coming
from the way she's been acting.
You're the only one who didn't notice.
Why didn't you stop her?
She's free to do as she wants.
You know just how reckless
what she said was.
We haven't even made our indie debut.
We got accepted to that festival.
And a label contacted Rupa
expressing interest.
What?
You may think it's crazy,
but you're a former Diamond Dust member.
Rupa and Tomo are a mystery duo
that got a lot of attention online.
And some vocalist tweeted
how much they liked Nina's voice.
That went semi-viral.
Really?
We have this many followers now.
The survey for our next performance said
we have the most fans
that are specifically coming for us.
I see.
Nina's not talking about some pipe dream.
I mean, beating Diamond Dust is crazy,
but we can at least take the first step.
What's Rupa and Tomo saying?
They were always looking to go pro.
What about you?
I'll do whatever.
What I'm saying is that
we won't be kids forever.
The rest is up to you.
So basically,
everyone was already in agreement.
Not exactly.
But Nina is always saying
that we need to set a goal
and corner ourselves.
Because it's hard, it's important
to not have any escape routes!
Hmm... This one?
Hmm...
And this?
Hmm, I guess that should be good?
A minor.
F.
G.
How do they do this?
Let's see...
Freedom, freedom, I'm free starting today!
I'll do whatever I want
Tomorrow and the day after tomorrow!
Tada!
Dear Dad,
Thank you for raising me.
I'll try to make it on my own now.
You don't need to send me money anymore.
I'm returning your bankbook too.
From Nina.
MUNEO ISERI
Hey, welcome!
We're not a sushi place.
Was that wrong?
Just say hello.
You've been here before.
I never pay attention
to this type of thing
when I'm the customer.
Gulp.
You eat it, you're fired.
Really?
Obviously!
Why did you even apply
to work here anyway?!
It's my first job ever,
so I figured I'd do it with friends.
You're so slow!
We asked for the check ages ago.
I'm sorry.
Where are you from?
You foreigners should know your place.
Excuse me!
My apologies.
Just watch it.
Thank you very much.
Rupa.
This happens all the time.
It means that I need rock and roll too.
I'll check the inventory.
So what's up with you and Momoka?
Nothing.
We'll probably just fight again
if we talked now.
Just so you know, if things stay rocky,
we're going to quit.
I know.
Hey, welcome...
One medium bowl.
Hello!
One medium bowl!
You don't need a beer?
Nina.
Would you like to order?
You free after this?
I... am.
Girls Band Cry.
So can we agree that there was
no intention of bullying or harm?
A simple argument
got a little out of hand.
Is that the understanding here?
That's good.
We'll have both girls write an apology
and seal it with a handshake.
Ms. Iseri?
Where are we going?
Somewhere close, we'll be there soon.
I see.
Did you want to go somewhere?
No.
I don't hate driving with you
in the Kei truck.
Honestly.
The least they could do is send us
a message, especially when we're waiting.
It'll be okay.
They say the opposite of like
is indifference.
They still want to talk alone
after all that fighting.
It proves they care.
They're just stupid.
Is this the place?
Just open the door.
Diamond Dust.
This is what it means
to not set escape routes and survive.
We can't afford to just play
the songs we like.
In order to survive,
we'll have no choice but chase
what will sell, what will be liked,
and what will go viral.
Not everything will necessarily
be like that.
Only a handful can survive
doing the things they want to.
Even the current Diamond Dust
didn't want to do this from the start.
They chose this to survive,
to sell tickets.
That doesn't mean your songs
won't reach people.
You rejected your song and
quit the band before you even tried.
But they found an audience
as they are now.
What they're doing now is right.
At first, they were all
totally against being an idol band.
That they'd only play their music.
Nobody listened.
But the reality was, even if we
were praised, we didn't sell tickets.
Only the most laughable acts
would become hits.
That's how the world is.
That truth slowly begins to pressure you.
And then comes the choice.
If you choose to reject it,
you can't continue.
They chose to continue.
You can't hold that against them.
But I don't want you
to make the same choice as me.
You asked me why I never moved back home
and why I started a new band.
When I saw you sing, it reminded me of
myself when I was first starting out.
You didn't care about money
or recognition.
You just sang a song you loved.
You were the version of myself I loved.
Someone I used to be.
That's why I wanted you to continue
singing as yourself.
Bound by nothing,
I wanted to listen by your side.
Thank you very much!
We're Diamond Dust!
Stick around for the next band!
What about my feelings?
Nina.
What about my feelings?!
Nina!
Let go of me!
I'm not your memory.
Don't lock me up inside your memory!
Now, shake hands to make up.
Ms. Iseri?
Ms. Iseri!
Stop, Nina!
It's so blank
It's so long
Answers are just formalities
Whether my fingers tremble or not...
There are people who decided to live
because of your songs.
Who you need to protect
isn't yourself in your memories.
It's your desire
to have your songs reach people.
You started the band because
you wanted to express
your feelings, your joy, your anger,
your sadness.
That's why you sang at your school
and came to Tokyo!
That's why you went professional!
Why are you so scared?
Stop being scared!
There's one in front of you.
Someone who was able to fly
because you gave them the courage!
Someone who felt joy being able
to sing with you,
and is willing to bet everything on you!
Someone who believes in you
is right in front of you...
Momoka.
Don't use me to run away.
Momokan?
It's you, right?
Right?
Let's go, Nina.
- What?
- Just come on!
Hina.
- Hey!
- Coming!
I'm leaving!
- You can take the train!
- What?!
Momokan!
Momoka!
Wait, Momoka!
You idiot.
Are you crazy?!
Now we're even.
Why are you running away?
You don't need to run.
You did nothing wrong!
Shut up!
Momokan!
You don't have to say anything,
just listen!
We heard you started a band.
We look forward to it.
We don't regret anything.
We're going to make it to the top.
We'll make you admit we weren't wrong.
We're gonna survive until then.
We're not going to lose either.
You'll say that we were right.
That we weren't wrong!
What?
Who do you think you are?
You've got some nerve saying that
after that crappy performance!
Momokan.
You're an idol band, right?
If you don't have any regrets,
then try being cuter!
Act professional!
We're entering the next festival too.
If you play like crap again there,
we're stealing all your fans!
What's that?
A declaration of war.
Momokan!
We won't forget!
Nina, get in.
Do you know her?
No.
I don't know her.
Damn it.
Damn it!
What's so funny?
Momoka.
What?
I love you after all.
The hell is that?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm confessing my love.
HOW DID IT GO?
What is it, Rupa?
I told you so.
Good grief.
They're interesting for sure.
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
I laughed, thinking it a dream
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
I can't even say that I'm lonely
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
Is incapable of making anyone happy
But still, I feel a growing hope
Moving past all of the lies
I just want to hear
That I'm not wrong
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
I don't care if I'm still the same today
I just want to sing with you
My emotions stir so often
I've been hated
But I'm going to keep walking
Proud of myself
Who can never become anybody
Even if I'm alone
I believe in myself
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing
Next episode, "The Waning Moon Was Out"