These three have theories about
the murder in the unfinished film.
Please listen to each of their ideas,
and then decide for yourselves.
Okay.
You're the ones who are supposed
to know all about mysteries?
This is Nakajo Junya. He's the
assistant director, on the film crew.
This is Haba Tomohiro, prop maker.
It's a pleasure.
And this is...
Ciao!
Sawakiguchi Misaki, publicity.
Thanks for coming all the way over!
Pleased to meet you.
R-Right!
You think this group is all there?
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
All right, if you please.
Give us a holler later!
The Case of the Furuoka Deserted
Village Murder
Take your time.
Sorry for having to bring
you into this mess.
It was a blast when we started,
but without an ending,
it's not cool, you know?
So, give us a hand, here.
Yeah.
Oh, I forgot!
Everyone, please share these.
These are whiskey bonbons, right?
They said they were promotional
samples of a new product.
That's strong!
Well, shall we get started?
Nakajo-senpai, you're on
the film crew, right?
Was the shoot very hard?
We had some fun with the performances
and production, adlibbing some of it,
but the real chore was getting there.
It took an hour by bus and train.
I wonder why they chose someplace
so far away for the location.
Why do you think it was?
Someone recommended that the place
had an interesting look to it.
I've heard that the Narakubo
area had a deserted village,
but I'm surprised they
let you go inside there.
The same person put in a word for us
with the property manager there.
Does that have anything to do with this?
Thank you very much. This is
informative. Please continue.
Um, how is the screenwriter,
Hongo-san, doing?
She doesn't sound very good.
But then, you can't really blame her.
Is Hongo-san just not a very
well young woman?
Yeah. She's had to stay home
from school a number of times.
She didn't come to the shoot, either.
If she worked so hard on the script
that she couldn't make it there...
Was Hongo-san's script not well-received?
No one had any problem with it.
Nobody found any fault with it.
Are you saying that you secretly wanted to?
What are you getting at? Everyone accepted
the work that Hongo did!
That goes for me, too, of course!
Ahem...
So then, Senpai...
Hm? Yeah...
Did anyone hear from Hongo-san
who would be playing the villain?
Hm... As far as I know...
Wait, hold on.
Now that you mention it,
she mentioned something along the lines
of wishing good luck to Konosu.
Konosu Yuri
That's something she might
have said to anyone.
Then, have you asked all of the actors?
About whether she said
anything to any of them?
Nope, none of them.
Were there any kind of physical or
psychological smoke and mirrors?
What's the difference?
Are there any other questions?
Okay, do you want to know what I think?
Please, go ahead.
Ahem!
If you ask me, your typical viewer
doesn't care about the shenanigans.
It just has to be thrilling.
"The culprit is you!"
Once called out, the villain breaks
down in tears and gives it up.
As long as you have that,
nobody will complain.
The End
Coming to a head like that would be
great at paying off Kaito's death.
Our props guy did himself proud
in making him die in style.
That scene was great.
You're saying that the scene was adlibbed?
Yeah. But everyone was so fussy about it.
Going on about the rules
of a mystery and whatnot.
Forget about all the
little details, it's the drama!
Play the title straight, too...
"The Case of the Furuoka Deserted Village Murder"...
The Case of the Furuoka Deserted Village Murder
Or something like that, because you've
got to put people in the seats.
I'm sure Hongo understood that much.
So, Nakajo-senpai, what do you think?
With the way he died, you know
what it was, don't you?
A locked-room murder.
Kaito died in a room with no other exits.
So, how did the killer do it?
That's the question.
Yes, so how did he do it?
That's simple. The window.
The window?
Yeah. After the villain kills Kaito,
he obviously went out the window.
The window... My memory
is a bit fuzzy here.
Satoshi, do you have the floorplan?
Yes, sir. Just a moment.
Here. Thanks for waiting.
Kaito died right here, stage left wing.
The other appearing characters enter
here through the right hallway.
Before they do, however,
the door here was locked,
so someone went back to get the master key.
And so, when they return to
stage left wing, Kaito was dead.
The stage and the hallway backstage
were blocked with junk and obstructions.
Which means that the only access to the
murder scene were these two places.
The door through which everyone entered,
and the window at stage left wing.
So, um, did Hongo-san know these facts?
Oh, I just meant, um...
It's true, that is important.
How so?
If Hongo-san wrote the script without
seeing the condition of the place,
and only went off of the floorplan,
there's a chance that she
considered other routes.
No she didn't.
Hongo went to see the location before
she started writing the script.
When was that?
June... no, probably more
like the end of May.
Which would mean,
the killer came and went through
the window. By doing so,
they could pull off shooting Kaito's
death scene without using the door.
How 'bout that?!
How about that, he asks?
But that wouldn't make for
a very well-crafted mystery.
Hm? Tell that to Hongo.
She wasn't very up on mysteries.
She didn't have any fancy
contrivances set up, right?
Let's say you're right; who was the killer?
The killer?
I mean, supposing that was the setup,
who does that make the killer?
Moreover, once everyone
arrives at the scene,
the outside of the window
is shown, isn't it?
Yeah.
Looking at it, there is clearly no trace of
anyone having passed by outside the window.
If someone had walked through
that overgrown grass,
there would definitely have
been some indication.
But that wasn't at all what was portrayed.
It would have been impossible
for them to flee out the window.
Maybe Hongo forgot to write that in.
If you say that, all bets are off.
Besides, we heard that Hongo-senpai's
script was entirely consistent.
In that case... hm...
I've got it! It's summer grass!
Remember I said that Hongo went to
scout out the site at the end of May?
At the time, the summer grass
hadn't grown in yet!
That's why Hongo was convinced
that she could use the window!
Which means that if we cut that grass
when we go back to shoot again,
and re-shoot the dead body scene,
it will all fall into place!
There, you see?! How 'bout that?!
All right, that solves it! The killer
fled through the window!
Now we can pull this off! We're in!
Well, there you have it!
Does that count? You can't even
call that a twist, can you?
Still, from a physical
perspective, it is feasible.
Yeah, but...
Oreki-san...
Do you think that what Nakajo-san
just said is what Hongo-san intended?
Does it not sit right with you?
No, it's not that.
I'm just not entirely convinced.
So in other words, it doesn't
sit right with you.
Yes.
Well, there are definitely some
inconsistencies with what Nakajo said.
Huh?
What? There are inconsistencies?
The utterly simple physical solution
is contradicted by its utterly
simple psychological aspect.
Hm? What do you mean?
That's a pretty convoluted
way of saying it, Hotaro.
Just like someone playing "detective."
Hmph.
Um, what exactly do you mean?
If you put yourself in the killer's shoes,
you could never go in through the window.
If you were to use this window,
you run the unavoidable risk of passing
through someone else's line of sight.
You see? Both here and here.
If you walk around outside,
you're sure to be seen.
What's worse, it's in broad daylight.
Sure enough. If I were the killer,
I wouldn't choose that route.
Well, that's that.
But whether or not Hongo-senpai
realized that... we can't tell.
That's true. But if we read
the script that Hongo wrote,
I think it would help us figure that out.
Mm-hm.
By the way, guys,
how many detective novels
has everyone read?
Why?
I was just thinking while we
were listening to Nakajo-senpai.
When you use the term "crime mystery,"
it can be taken to mean
lots of different things.
Well, Nakajo's way of thinking
certainly is novel, in one sense.
Mm-hm. How about you, Hotaro?
Not a lot. A handful of paperbacks, maybe.
Mayaka?
Hm, about average. Christie, and such.
The classics, huh? Chitanda-san?
I don't read them.
Not at all? Ever?
I've read enough to decide that maybe
I just don't enjoy reading mysteries.
I haven't even touched one
over the last few years.
Huh... I wouldn't have expected.
So what about you?
Me? Hm, I...
I already know. Fuku-chan fancies
himself as a Sherlockian, huh?
What is a Sherlockian?
A passionate fan of Sherlock Holmes, right?
A very passionate fan,
am I right?
A "Sherlockian" is a little bit
different than that.
How did it go?
Well...
We rejected Nakajo-senpai's idea.
I see.
Oh, one other thing...
What is it?
Could you find us the script?
We'd like to know how attentive
Hongo-senpai was, you might say.
Very well.
I will go look for one, so until
then, please talk to him...
The prop maker, Haba Tomohiro.
Hey.
I understand you know your mystery stories.
Shosho ('Heat's End')
For the sunshine easeth,
and blue skies begin their withdrawl
Hyouka
You know, if you think of mysteries as being
a contest between the author and the reader,
an amateur like Hongo
comes up a little short.
We heard that Hongo-san doesn't have
much experience with mysteries.
Yeah.
Those are the books she used to cram with.
Up until she started this film,
I understand that she hadn't even seen any
mystery manga or movies, let alone novels.
Ah, the Nobuhara translation.
And the latest editions, at that.
She was trying to study
mysteries by reading Holmes?
That's right. Which is what
makes her such an amateur.
I suppose you could say that.
Hmph.
Oreki-san, Oreki-san!
What is it?
There are some odd marks on here. Look.
Hm?
The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes
Here, look. They're on here, too.
The Casebook of Sherlock Holmes
She probably just marked the
stories she could draw from.
Is that so?
Never mind that,
what do you say we start deducing?
What is this floorplan?
I got it from the town hall.
Oh...
So please tell us what you think.
Ahem...
To my thinking, this mystery
is not all that difficult.
In fact, I would categorize it as easy.
How so?
The murder was not premeditated.
Rather, circumstances just happened
to fall into place for the killer,
so they seized on the chance
to commit the crime.
Why is that?
If it had been planned out,
how would they have lured
Kaito to stage left wing?
The reason Kaito went to the right
corner of the first floor alone
was the result of him spontaneously
picking up that key.
Now, this is a locked-room murder.
All of the points of escape were blocked,
and the window,
which was the only route out,
had no footprints left outside it.
Meaning that the culprit who killed Kaito
could not have escaped conventionally.
So the killer used the master
key to sneak onto the scene.
Is there any chance that
they returned it afterward?
That is neither interesting,
nor reasonable.
To get to the office where the keys were,
they would have to pass
through the front lobby.
There was always the danger that they
would be spotted in the lobby
by any of the other characters.
So none of the characters could
have safely entered the office.
And it's not just the office
that they couldn't safely enter.
The first-floor hallway down the right side
that leads to the stage left wing itself
is someplace that no one could
have gotten to. That's crucial.
Why is that?
They couldn't even get near the locked room
in order to set the whole
thing in motion, right?
Well, you're right.
For the same reason,
any chance of the victim himself
creating the locked room is negated.
Other possibilities...
Murders committed by mechanical
means or sleight of hand are out.
He died after being slashed hard
enough to take off his arm.
In short, this locked-room
mystery that Hongo created
is quite difficult to tackle head-on.
How about it? You're Oreki-kun, right?
How do you think this locked-room
murder could be solved?
Golly, I don't know.
Well that isn't going to do!
Although, who could blame you?
This is the key to it.
Rope?
I am the prop master.
Hongo made a point about this.
She said to have a rope that wouldn't
break, even with a person's weight on it.
You already know how it
will be used, right?
Don't you see? If they couldn't
get in from the first floor,
they could get in from the second floor.
Konosu was there on the
right second-floor hallway.
Konosu
The truth is that while Konosu looks
slender, she's in the Mountaineering Club.
Konosu dangled the rope
down from the second floor,
Stage left wing
Kaito
climbed down
it to stage left wing, killed Kaito,
then escaped back along the same route.
If I were to give this movie a title,
it would be, let's see...
I think I might call it "Unseen Incursion."
Okay, let me hear what you guys think now.
Did Hongo-senpai ask you for
anything aside from the rope?
Hm, not especially. Hongo was
a bit capricious, though.
For example, the amount of blood she
called for was not nearly enough.
I had no choice but to play it smart
and get a whole lot of it ready.
Anything else?
If not...
Um...
What is it?
This may not be a big deal,
but have you seen the movie?
Actually, I haven't seen it yet.
You know, it really galls me!
What does?
His attitude! Fuku-chan,
didn't it get to you?
He even made fun of Holmes!
Not really.
Why not?!
The view that Holmes was intended for
beginning readers is true, in a way.
And Hongo-senpai was,
in fact, a beginner at this.
So, what do we think about Haba's theory?
Well, it's a good one, isn't it?
The conclusion isn't very thrilling,
but the fact that Hongo-senpai
called for the rope is decisive.
I don't find any problem with it, either.
I... I can't go along with it.
Just like with Nakajo-san's theory earlier,
something simply feels out of place.
I'm not sure why it is,
but I don't think it was what
Hongo-san intended.
I think you've had enough of those.
Ah!
Oh my, did I eat all of those?
They tasted so unusual,
so I was curious if they were
supposed to be like that.
Chi-chan, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
♪ I'm fine... ♪
Oreki-san! Do you think he is correct?
No, I don't.
Why not?
If this were an actual
murder, it might fly,
but it wouldn't work inside the movie.
In what way?
It's inconsistent with the movie.
Oh, right. The window.
It had been left closed for years,
and fallen into disrepair.
Katsuta gave it a good jolt, and it still didn't
want to open, so it had to have been pretty tight.
It creaked awfully loudly, too,
plus, it opened upward.
It would have been impossible for anyone
to open quietly while dangling from a rope.
What's more, would Kaito just
stand still there in the room,
while the window was being rattled open?
That would be beyond dumb.
That's why you asked Haba if
he had seen the video, right?
Hongo had gone there
to scope out the house.
If the window was such
an important plot point,
she would have checked to see
if it would open or not.
But we all saw the actual
footage they shot, right?
In other words, Hongo wasn't concerned
about the state of the window.
I shouldn't have been so eager to agree.
How did it go?
Rejected.
I see.
This is the script.
Thank you very much.
Nice! Nice! I want one, too!
You're drunk.
I'm fine.
Oreki, let me see.
Indeed, it's shipshape.
This is pretty detailed, huh?
"Make sure that there are no
footprints outside the window."
Sure enough, she thought about that.
So where is the next
person... Sawakiguchi-san?
Thanks for waiting!
Ciao!
Hello there, Sawakiguchi-san. Ciao to you!
Man, from a publicity standpoint,
I'm stuck until this thing has a title.
Making up publicity posters is on hold.
I think it's about time we settled
this matter of the script.
Did Hongo-san put herself up as
a candidate to write the script?
Nope, she was recommended.
And the decision to make a mystery?
That was also by majority vote.
What about the idea to make
a video in the first place...
We're getting off point here, aren't we?
But I am curious.
Here. I have the meeting minutes.
If they're any help, take them.
Thank you very much.
Now then, why don't you
listen to what I think?
When you hear the word "mystery,"
what do you picture?
Let's see... you!
The Orient Express, maybe?
That's a whodunit novel, right?
What a freak.
Huh?
If you look at mysteries
at the video rental shop,
you'll find Friday the 13th and A Nightmare
on Elm Street, right? Typically.
Yeah, but those are horror...
Yes, indeed you will.
Huh?
Think about it like someone who has
no interest at all in the genre.
They don't draw a distinction
between "mystery" and "horror."
So anyway,
nobody could get into the room
where Kaito died, right?
In that case, there obviously
has to be a seventh person.
Seventh person?
Hongo was looking for another actor,
in addition to the other six.
Huh?
They all stop trusting one another,
and once all of their
paranoia gets built up,
the much-anticipated
phantom killer appears!
Phantom?
I'm not sure how many
of them get killed off,
but other than one lucky couple,
they could have probably whacked
all the others, I'd guess.
Finally, the couple defeat the phantom,
and end with a kiss by dawn's light.
The title would be, let's see,
"Bloody Beast," maybe.
Or whatever. That might be a little cheesy.
But you all buy that, don't you?
B-But, Senpai, what about the locked room?
Why was the door locked?
What does it really
matter if it was locked?
A phantom killer has to at least
be able to pass through walls.
Otherwise...
That's it! A vengeful spirit! Mm-hm!
That's possible, right?
You're wrong! You're absolutely wrong!
Sawakiguchi-san, your idea is definitely
not what Hongo-san intended!
Yeah, for sure. I couldn't tell
how much of it was a joke, either.
But can you refute it?
Logically, of course.
It's just wrong!
Yes, but logically?
What's wrong is wrong!
Chi-chan?
It's like looking into a kaleidoscope...
Kaleidoscope?
Whoa, Chi-chan!
Chi-chan?
I think she's asleep.
I have to admit,
I liked how bold
Sawakiguchi-senpai's idea was.
Actually, I like it, too.
I'll bet.
Although, it does have its inconsistencies.
Like what?
You saw how detailed the script was, right?
If Hongo was planning that kind of
horror twist for the second half,
she would have at least
arranged for the prop for it...
The one most necessary.
The one most necessary?
Remember? The one that
Haba played it smart over?
Oh.
Hongo only ordered a very small
amount of fake blood.
The description in the script backs that up.
Upon helping Kaito-kun up, there is blood on Sugimura's
hand.
So Hongo's intent was not to write a body-count movie.
That makes sense.
It makes for a lean horror movie
to only have one dead person.
There's a reason for
everything, isn't there?
How did it go?
Rejected.
Chi-chan, shake it off!
I'm sorry.
It turns out we rejected them all.
Step on up! Cheap prices, cheap prices! Step on up!
I wonder what's going to become of their video.
Excuse me, mister. Could I please have...
Well, they won't be able to finish it.
It's so depressing, huh?
"Summer grass, 'tis all that remains
of ancient warriors' dreams."
Mm-hm.
Later.
Yeah.
No matter how much passion someone puts into it,
without technical skill, the outcome will be obvious.
Could you spare me time enough
for a cup of tea?
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "Blind Spot to All."
Blind Spot to All