Madam?
Please hurry.
Another intruder.
Right in the direction we're headed.
We'll run into him if we go this way.
Understood.
Let's circle around to the north side, then.
Madam?
The one who's coming is...
...Kotomine Kirei.
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kotomine Kirei?
Maiya-san, Kiritsugu ordered you to protect me, right?
Yes.
But...
But what?
We cannot let him get to Kiritsugu, no matter what.
Isn't that what you're thinking?
Madam, you...
What a coincidence.
I was thinking the exact same thing.
Kotomine Kirei.
He probably poses the biggest threat to Kiritsugu.
The two of us will stop him here.
Is that okay, Maiya-san?
I apologize for asking you this, but please prepare yourself, madam.
Yes.
Don't worry about me.
Simply fulfill your duty.
What you believe to be necessary, not what Kiritsugu told you to do.
Yes.
Is there something else?
No.
What we call the human heart...
It's such a mystery, isn't it?
You repeat an attack you know to be utterly futile.
Scalp!
Strike!
He broke through Volumen Hydrargyrum's autonomous defense?
No.
I was just careless in facing his petty attacks.
I shall assume defensive posture more quickly and efficiently.
He's a disgrace to Magi everywhere.
Low-class piece of garbage!
How dare he draw my blood...
He'll pay for it dearly.
Now that he understands how powerful
this attack is, it won't work a second time.
He'll put all of his mana into defending next time.
No.
That's what I need him to do.
An illusion?
Maiya-san, no!
Madam!
No!
Woman.
This may be a surprise, but I'm not here to defeat you.
I know that, Kotomine Kirei.
I know what you're trying to do.
But I won't allow it.
You will never reach Emiya Kiritsugu.
We will stop you.
Right here.
Madam!
He's an Executor! An expert at hunting Magi!
Normal magic won't be enough against him!
Kiritsugu taught me more than how to drive a car.
He taught me how to live.
And how to survive!
Shape ist Leben!
Shape, carry life!
Madam!
It won't work!
Maiya-san!
Please!
No...
Bastard...
I'm honestly stunned that we made so little progress.
It's that grimoire, Lancer.
As long as he holds that Noble Phantasm, the situation won't change.
I see...
So that's it.
But we need to break through the wall of minions if
we're going to knock the book off that blue freak's hands.
Lancer.
Are you up for taking an all-or-nothing bet?
It annoys me that we couldn't outlast him, but it's foolish to continue fighting these minions.
Very well.
I'm in, Saber.
I shall clear a path.
We have but one chance.
Lancer, can you run with the wind ?
I see now.
Easily done.
Have you finished saying your final prayers?
Now, tremble and fall into despair!
There is a limit to the difference in
numbers that superior skill can overcome.
Isn't it humiliating?
You will die, suffocated by these ignoble, nameless monsters!
There is no greater disgrace for a Hero.
That beautiful face...
Twist it in agony for me, Jeanne!
Strike Air!
Prepare... yourself!
Pierce it, Gae Dearg!
Damn you...
Damn you, damn you, damn you!
Damn you!
How did you like that?
Things wouldn't have been much different
if Saber had regained the use of her left arm.
Prepare to die.
Fiend.
How pathetic.
I didn't participate in the Holy Grail War for this kind of battle!
Where is he?
There you are...
...little rat.
Surely you aren't expecting the same trick to work a second time.
Low-class scum.
Your success in landing a single blow wasn't due to any tactic or clever scheme of yours.
It was a simple, improbable coincidence.
I'll see that you understand the difference.
I won't let you die easily.
I'll use healing magic to regenerate your heart
and lungs while I tear up every inch of your flesh.
You will die in regret, agony, and despair.
And as you die, you will curse.
You will curse the cowardice of those who hired you.
You will curse the Einzberns for disgracing the Grail War!
Fervor, mei sanguis!
Boil, my blood!
You're actually using the same trick again, fool?!
You're wasting your time.
Bastard...
What unbelievable cowardice.
Lancer.
Is something wrong?
My lord is in danger.
It seems he left me here and breached the castle himself.
It must be the work of my Master.
Lancer, hurry onward.
Rescue your lord.
King of Knights, you have my thanks.
It is nothing.
We swore to settle matters as knights would.
Let us see that pride through.
So everything went as Kiritsugu had planned in the end...
Your origin lies in severing and binding, kid.
To cut and tie...
It's a little different from destroying and regenerating.
If you cut a thread and tie it back together, the
thickness will be different where the knot is, right?
In that sense, it carries the meaning of irreversible change.
I've powdered two of your ribs and put some of it in this bullet.
Your origin will materialize in anything that this hits.
It'll be especially powerful against Magi.
If they use any magic against it, your origin will destroy
their Magic Circuits, which will then reconnect improperly.
The more powerful the Mage, the more
Magic Circuits will lose control and short out.
Naturally, they won't recover, as a Mage or as a human.
This is your Mystic Code: "Origin Bullet".
You have sixty-six of them in total.
Use them sparingly.
You understand how easy it would be
for me to skewer you right now, correct?
Master of Saber.
I see.
I won't allow you to kill my Master.
And I won't kill Saber's Master, either.
Neither she nor I wish for things to end like that.
Never forget this.
The only reason you are still alive is the nobility the King of Knights displayed.
Woman, I have a question for you.
It appears that both of you challenged me to protect Emiya Kiritsugu.
Whose will was that?
Since you lack the Command Spells, you are not the Einzbern Master.
You are most likely a homunculus,
charged with protecting the Grail vessel.
Someone like that could never be stupid
enough to risk fighting at the front lines.
So I ask again, woman.
On whose will did the both of you fight?
Kirei-sama.
Caster, Lancer, and Lancer's Master have all left the forest.
Saber will arrive shortly.
It is dangerous here, my lord.
I see.
It's red, after all.
These women challenged me of their own accord, and not on someone else's orders?
Impossible.
Emiya Kiritsugu is like me.
Understood and acknowledged by nobody, and empty to the core.
He has to be like that.
Irisviel...
Irisviel!
Hang in there.
Saber...
No!
You must stay awake!
I'll call Kiritsugu over right now.
Be strong until then!
Where is Kirei?
The enemy who was just here?
He escaped.
If only I'd been a little faster, then this wouldn't have happened.
What about Maiya-san?
She is badly wounded, but she will survive.
I'm more concerned about you.
You've lost so much blood...
Irisviel?
What on Earth...?
Iri, you'll be carrying Avalon.
But this Noble Phantasm heals its bearer's wounds.
I think you should carry it.
No.
Without its original owner, Saber, nearby to supply it with mana, the scabbard's effects won't manifest.
You'll be the one to accompany Saber from now on, after all.
It's better if you carry it.
Seal it within you as a Conceptual Weapon.
And tell no one else about it.
Including Saber, of course.
From the moment you touched me, I felt Avalon's power.
Thank you, Saber.
Kotomine Kirei.
That Executor is dangerous, just as I imagined.
No, even worse.
We were lucky today, but I don't know what'll happen next time.
All I know for certain is that I can't let him reach Kiritsugu.
But...
I'm not the only one who's protecting Kiritsugu.
Right, Maiya-san?
We'll win next time, for sure.
We'll both protect Kiritsugu, okay?
Episode 8
Mage Killer
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
My Master is in mortal peril!
Elegance is required, even in battle.
I cannot give you my consent.
Give me the Command Spells.
Lancer isn't as admirable as you think!
Next Episode
Lord and Vassal