oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to have it again and again
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
jounai manjou
The theater's full
nazotoki dokidoki shinan
Mysteries are fun
shikake ga ariari desu
Tricks are fun as well
joshiteki onayami wa sugoroku sai wo futte
We can solve girly problems by throwing dice
(hai hai)
(really?)
ichi de mo roku de mo nain
It's not one nor six, but nine
(sou kai)
(really?)
ichi kake bachi ka de sain
The stakes are high, but you can get a sign
(sou kai)
(really?)
hanashi no tsunagari ga miemasen ne
I don't really see how that's related
oya omoshiroku narisou na yokan wa
See, this looks like it's gonna be fun
(oya oya desu)
(see, see?)
me no sakkaku desu ka
Or am I just seeing things?
iya soredemo kamawanai
I don't even care
hai minna
Come on, everyone
mawatte
Let's spin!
omote mo ura uragaeshite
Front and back, let's just turn it around
dondengaeshi mo yoshiyoshi
You can turn the story upside down too
osaki ni ikou saa douzo
Let's go on, ladies first
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to see you around again and again
ura butai ga hare butai de
The backstage is the main stage
muda uchibanashi mo yokayoka
That's where we can chat idly
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo shiroki gokuraku da
I hope it was a good comedy
gokuraku da gokuraku da
A comedy, a comedy
arayotto gokuraku joudo ringu
A comedy from the comedy heaven
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
"Well, sir, I already know that."
"But if you know that, then why are you feeding your cats from a Kakiemon plate?"
"Oh, 'cause sometimes I can pawn a cat off for a couple gold coins."
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Glasses Girl
It's pouring outside!
Must be annoying when your glasses fog up.
They don't.
Oh? I thought rain causes glasses to fog up.
It's pouring outside!
Must be annoying when your glasses fog up.
They don't!
Oh?
It's pouring outside!
Must be annoying when your glasses fog up.
THEY DON'T!
A
This anime is
full of ordinary dialogue
so that viewers can fully
enjoy how cute the girls are.
What the hell was that for?!
Oh, shut up. I've been holding it back.
It's pouring outside...
Must be annoying when your glasses fog up.
A
This anime is
full of ordinary dialogue
so that viewers can fully
enjoy how cute the girls are.
Why did you hit me?! Kigu said it this time!
Wait.
If we're gonna talk about glasses, first we must...
Turn towards Sabae, and...
Bow!
Please watch over us!
Sabae produces the most glasses in all of Japan.
Sabae
Come, Violent Four-Eyes!
You hit me twice in a row!
You'll pay—
A
This anime is
full of ordinary dialogue
so that viewers can fully
enjoy how cute the girls are.
So strong!
Last episode, I thought you had no
openings. I guess I overestimated you.
Dammit!
You wear glasses! You shouldn't be so violent!
On the contrary, glasses are the most fitting accessory for violent people.
What?
Everyone hesitates for a moment
before hitting someone with glasses.
"She could get badly hurt if I break her glasses."
"I might hurt my hand."
"It may cost a lot to get her glasses fixed."
"Could I really live with myself as a human being?"
They start overthinking it, and their punches come moments too late!
So that's why my punch was a fraction of a second late!
A fraction? That was a whole second.
No wonder Ushijima is so strong!
Gan, do you cover people in honey and leave them in the forest?
No!
Even if they give you an advantage,
I still don't see how glasses fit violence!
What would convince you otherwise?
Glasses girls must turn into cute girls
when they take their glasses off, right?
Gankyou, take them off!
Why the Nobita face?!
Jab, jab, straight!
Finish with an uppercut!
You're even stronger without glasses!
So her glasses were actually suppressing her...
You should put them back on!
Just accept that she's a violent glasses girl!
I'm not wearing glasses so I can be a stereotypical character.
Then let's all wear glasses!
Will that even solve anything?
Which pair do you want?
She looks smart!
A real intellectual!
She looks like she's scheming something.
Like a troublemaker.
The perfect underling.
There's no way she'd be the main character!
Those are the same as mine!
Don't put glasses on for fun, dammit!
You didn't even hesitate!
Wait!
You're all labeling her as a violent glasses girl,
but she actually cares about the people
around her more than anyone else I know!
Tetora, don't say that... You're embarrassing me...
I have to say it!
She always looks around at offline meetups or other gatherings.
If more than 50% of the people wear glasses, she takes hers off for the sake of balance!
Well, a meetup with 80% glasses people just feels wrong.
You care so much about the balance of your surroundings!
Isn't that great?!
I guess, but like...
It's normal for over 80% of the people at an offline meetup to wear glasses.
It isn't weird at all.
Just consider this.
Wouldn't it be weird to have the Okiyahagi and the Tokyo 03 together on a TV show?
Yeah, that would be really weird.
Too many glasses.
At least one of the Tokyo 03 should take his off.
Seriously!
And it's stupid to have a manga where all three brothers wear glasses.
Yeah, totally stupid.
Imagine if the waiter at one of those meetups
was also wearing glasses.
It would be terrible.
You can't just ask for a hot pot.
Hot pot?
I got this!
All rig—
A
This anime...
etc.
They don't fog up!
It's really mean of you to try and fog up her glasses.
Yeah!
It's very humiliating to walk around with foggy glasses!
Oh shut up already.
Just think about it!
It would be a catastrophe if a celebrity's glasses fogged up!
Think of a star whose smile can steal a woman's heart!
A what now?
If his glasses fogged up, he'd look like that guy from the Melon Books doujin shop!
Yui
And that's not all.
There may be even more dreadful situations!
Nipple attack!
Noooo!
There!
The world as we know it would end if his glasses fogged up!
No it wouldn't.
This really is a bit much...
They finally fogged up!
They did— fog up!
They did!
So...
Time for the nipple hunter game!
Seriously?!
Fascinating.
Even with foggy glasses, I won't miss my targets!
There!
Correct!
Why are you so accurate?
I just have to find the vertex based on the faint sense of the chi's flow...
And aim for that!
I missed?!
I win!
I dodged at the very last moment.
Dammit! How could my eyes betray me?!
Here?
Not even close!
Marii...
She doesn't realize she's being made fun of...
Yup...
Why are we riding the Laughing Gull?
Officially it's called the Tokyo
Waterfront New Transit Waterfront Line.
Long.
The laughing gulls are gulls that laugh?
What gull is that?
How fitting for a comedy anime.
There really are laughing gulls.
Order: Charadriiformes. Family: Laridae. Genus: Larus. The black-hooded gull.
Hoods...
Biker gangs are on the decline these days.
They can't buy bikes because of the depression.
Modifying them costs a lot too.
A
Nausea at Sea
Look, it's the sea!
I totally want to go somewhere!
We're in the middle of going somewhere.
Somewhere even further.
Wanna be a stowaway?
No!
Taking the train reminds me of back when we were still in train ing...
Ah, before we were allowed to perform on stage?
I had to perform on trains often to test my courage.
A difficult train ing indeed.
I had to try to speak while doing situps... It was really hard.
Carrying the master's bag...
Cleaning the master's house...
Wiping the master's ass...
Those were sumo wrestlers a century ago!
It was really tough to perform while
bungee-jumping off the Rainbow Bridge...
You didn't do that!
The Rainbow Bridge...
We're about to cross the bridge of rainbows!
Whoa, this curve!
It's turning so suddenly!
What's wrong, Kukuru?
I got trainsick.
You're sick?!
Does that happen to you a lot?
Not really, it just caught me off-guard...
Want some water?
No thanks...
Or some sweets?
That'd just make her feel worse!
But sweets cheer you up when you're feeling down!
If you eat when you feel motion sick, you'll barf.
You'll barf anyway.
Kukuru, get over it!
Get over with it and barf?
No! Endure! Endure!
Just write "person" on your hand and swallow it!
Enter
Swing and a miss. That's "enter," not "person".
Sorry, my mistake.
Go back to elementary school then!
Person
..
Why did you add that?
It looks cuter this way. Persön.
Person
..
Perzon
Perzon.
That has a dangerous edge!
I guess...
P3r50n
It doesn't even look like "person".
Gestaltzerwall!
That's "fall"!
Okay, then...
Brutal         person
Why are you doing this to her?!
Just swallow it and get over it!
Even if it's just a brute, it'll still do!
Telling her to swallow a brute?!
But actually this is a way to avoid being
swallowed by nervousness in front of people.
Really?
Then what should we do?
I heard that if you train your semicircular canals you won't get motion sick!
But how do you train them?
How can you make your semicircular canals stronger?
They say backward rolls will do the trick.
Like this!
That was a Mori Mitsuko-grade backward roll!
You'd been embarrassed to perform rakugo on a train!
You've grown so much, Teto!
Now you can even do backward rolls on trains, no problem!
I guess I've grown...
It's nothing to be happy about!
In the meanwhile Kukuru's gotten even worse!
Terrible trouble is brewing in Kukuru's body now.
Trouble?
Trouble between the stomach and the gullet?
Or between the food and the gastric fluid?
To return or not to return, that is the question.
Looking at the scenery might help!
That's right!
Look, you can see the goddess of freedom!
Amazing! So big!
That's Freedom for you!
Eleven meters tall, weighing in at nine tons.
There's Fuji TV's Odaiba headquarters!
Look, the ferris wheel!
It's gotten worse! She looks even sicker now!
Now that it's come to this, I've got no choice!
You wanna throw up too?!
I can't...
Girls, I'm sorry...
I tried, but I can't do it anymore...
Let's get off! We should just get off!
You're right!
Are you okay?
I'm better now that we got off!
So quick!
I'm glad!
By the way, where are we?
Let's go home.
Yeah...
So he stole the boss's moonflakes?
That's funny. So what happened next?
They turned into moon fragments.
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Eye of the Rabbit
It's so beautiful...
Remind me again, why are we watching the moon in the dressing room?
We've got no choice...
It's too cloudy outside for us to see the moon.
Even though it's a full moon tonight.
So where are the windows?
Why?
I'm gonna break them all!
Marii, it might be a full moon night, but it's not the fifteenth.
So I just made a real stupid mistake?
I don't want to become a boring adult.
Then let's keep watching the moon.
It doesn't look like a rabbit!
That's not a rabbit!
Yeah, it doesn't look like a rabbit.
Rabbits look like this.
Eek! That's not a rabbit, that's terrifying!
Rabbits are cute like this!
We're only supposed to watch the moon and eat dumplings, right?
Not exactly a thriller of a night.
People eat other kinds of food
associated with the moon as well.
Let's eat moon-watching soba!
This isn't exciting either!
What's that? Are you tying someone up?
No.
In southern Kyushu and Okinawa,
it's traditional to play tug-of-war on full moon nights.
This isn't exciting either...
Then how about we drum for the moon?
The full moon!
Is wonderful!
The full moon is great!
Cut it out! We might as well watch the moon in silence!
It still doesn't look like a rabbit.
Yeah, you won't be able to see the rabbit until you've seen it at least once.
Actually, foreigners see many different things in the moon.
Girl with a bucket
Crab with big claws
Woman reading a book
Roaring lion
A woman reading a book?
A girl with a bucket?
By the way, to me it looks like a NEET asking his mom to buy the latest issue of Jump for him.
I... can't see that!
Now that you mention it, it does kinda look like that.
Doesn't it?
There are no NEETs on the moon!
To me it looks like a pervert sniffing
someone's ass from a highly unrealistic position.
I can totally see that!
I can... not!
It looks like something different to everyone.
What does this look to you?
Like a Rorschach test. Enough already.
Yeah, people see things so differently.
That's why there are wars.
But if we all try to understand each other's point of view,
I'm sure we can achieve world peace!
You're right.
We must even accept countries that see an ass-sniffing pervert in the moon.
That's not a country, just you!
But there are smells you just can't resist, right?
Yeah.
That part of a pair of glasses that rests on one's nose...
A freshly used hairbrush...
Between the legs of my stuffed toy...
Talk about perverts!
No!
Anyway, that must be a huge rabbit.
If it looks this big from the ground, how
many meters must it be from tail to head?
Meters? More like kilometers.
The moon's diameter is 3474 kilometers.
I can't even imagine how big that is.
As I recall the Tokyo Dome is 244 meters in diameter, so...
Yes?
Why do we always use the Tokyo
Dome to compare the sizes of things?
Because it's easy to understand.
But if you've never been there
before, it just makes it even harder.
What?
The Master's rabbit got away.
He wants us to call him if we see it.
His rabbit?
Don't tell me...
The Master's rabbit!
It's huge!
A
What do I
look like to you?
A rabbit!
Definitely a rabbit!
A rabbit it is!
You look like a rabbit!
A pervert sniffing someone's ass from a highly unrealistic position!
Holy crap!
We must... We must calm Lord Rabbit's anger!
A feast! We should prepare him a feast!
What the hell is it, anyway?
The Master's inside, obviously.
We should get him to leave somehow!
We should sing him a song that'll make him homesick!
That mountain where we chased rabbits
That river where we fish—
Why?!
Was he offended that we mentioned chasing rabbits?
As penance, we'll all do ten bunny hops!
He's even angrier!
Think... Think of something that'll make him happy!
That's right! They say rabbits die alone!
Let's all become rabbits!
Lord Rabbit, please have some.
Let me massage you.
Aren't you feeling hot?
May I scratch your back?
How was it?
Why?!
Rabbits die if you pester them too much!
Now all we can do is become its
natural enemy, the turtle, and fight!
That's no good at all!
Violent people like him are weak against authority!
Grovel at the feet of Princess Kaguya, supreme ruler of the Moon, you rabbit!
She was taken away.
She really was Princess Kaguya after all.
She belongs in the Moon.
Hey, look at the Moon now...
Doesn't it look like a rabbit sniffing Marii's ass?
A
jugemu jugemu gokou no surikire
Live long, live long and prosper
A
kaijari suigyo no suigyou matsu
May great wealth await you wherever you go
A
unrai matsu fuurai matsu
Even in different lands and under different skies
A
kuuneru tokoro ni sumu tokoro
May you always have your daily bread
A
yaburakouji no burakouji
And always be brimming full of life
A
paipo paipo paipo no shuuringan
Like the long-lived king Shuringan
A
shuuringan no guurindai
And his dear wife Gurindai
A
guurindai no ponpokopi no ponpokona no
And their children Ponpokopi and Ponpokona
A
choukyuumei chousuke
Live a long and blessed life
A
choi to jikan itadakimasu
Let me have a bit of your time
goseichou kudasai
Please listen closely
A
totonoimashita
We're ready
A
warau koto to kakemashite
You write it "laughing"
A
omatsuri yarou zo tokemasu
You read it "let's party"
A
sono kokoro wa sono kokoro wa
And the point of it is, the point of it is...
A
dochira mo happi ni naru deshou
That everyone will be happy!
A
oato ga yoroshii you de
Thank you kindly for your attention
waraou waraou sa waraimashou
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh
konna jidai koso waraimashou
Life may be hard, but let's laugh
waraou (soiya soiya)
Laugh (yeah yeah)
naitara make da
If you cry, you lose
yakekuso waraimashou
So just laugh until your sides ache
haranbanjou sui mo amai mo
Life may have its ups and downs,
norikoeta appare nipponjin
But great Japanese can get over it
waraou donna toki de mo
Laugh, whatever time may bring
nanikuso waraimashou
Laugh until you run out of breath
kuuki nante yomazu ni warattoke
Who cares where you are? Just laugh
egao (egao) egao (egao)
Smile (smile), smile (smile)
warau kado ni wa fuku kitaru
Smile and the world will smile back at you
A
Preview
I am Buratei Marii.
Ladies and gentlemen, how are you doing?
Thunderclouds?
Ah, those tall clouds.
When I look at them piling up and up on the horizon,
it totally feels like summer, and I get really excited!
I wonder if the Dragon's Nest is really in there too!
But anyway, we somehow made it to the fifth performance of Joshiraku.
Praise the Girl, Stylish Little Town and Farewell to Glasses will be on stage.
A
Praise the Girl
Stylish Little Town
Farewell to Glasses