"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Since autumn is a time for reading,
I'm getting my hands on
all sorts of books lately.
I see. But that's so unlike you.
Though I know it's for me
to gain knowledge,
the expenses keep piling up...
You don't have to buy them.
Why not borrow books from the library?
They'll have a lot of the books
you want to read.
No, libraries wouldn't go to the
extent of stocking up on manga...
Reading books, huh...
"That Feeling"
"Studying for exams"
I can't concentrate.
Well, everyone needs
to take a breather.
And a push of a button...
I'll take my mind off things
a bit by playing my game.
Oh, it's Miss Kuroi.
"Hey! Don't fool around! Study!"
"I'll yell at you if your scores suck!"
Drat... I didn't realize that the siege
had surrounded me this far.
That's asking for too much, ma'am...
When someone interrupts me
like that, the game isn't as appealing.
Sigh.
Ma'am, how did you study for exams
back when you were in school?
"When I couldn't concentrate,
I played around or I slept."
"What you're doing is no different."
So it was the same for her.
"But, considering my circumstances,
I'll have to be hard on you!"
I kinda see where she's coming from,
but somehow it seems so unfair!
This time around, I think I'll set goals
and make sure to work my way up.
Sis, can you teach me the things
that I don't understand?
Then should we study together?
That's why, in this case,
the value of x...
What is it?
I just thought about how
the drama show is on air now.
I think today's episode was where
the main character gets written up
in a weekly magazine,
and word spreads of her pregnancy...
So do you want to watch TV?
No, it's okay, I've got it
recorded on video.
Here.
Let's see...
When there's one thing I'm not
good at after another, I get sleepy!
Which means, you've been
sleepy the entire time.
Maybe I shouldn't go full-throttle
from the beginning after all.
I guess I'll call it a day
today, you know?
Okay, your ambitions are
getting lower and lower now.
I just can't concentrate, after all.
All right.
What's that?
Tips on studying for exams?
I was just wondering how you
went about it, Miyuki-san.
Let's see...
If you think about it too much,
I'm sure you will burn out
from the stress.
In my case, I just try to
behave as I usually do.
And so, I'm pretty confident
this time around.
You know, feeling like
I have a bigger heart?
Isn't your usual a bit
on the risky side?
You haven't done anything, right?
What, even with such a cute face?
Yeah. And their hooked claws
are poisonous.
I see... There was
an unusually scary side.
S'up.
Oh, Kagami, how'd you do?
Not so well this time around.
Though I managed to stay
in the top end of the class.
Even you have times
like that, Kagami?
Sis was helping me out
the whole time.
Thanks to that, I scored
better than usual.
How about you?
Mysteriously enough, it was no good.
I was pretty confident, too.
It's not mysterious at all.
Or rather, it was practically inevitable.
Well, it was a feeling much similar
to birds of a feather
flocking together...
For instance, Kagami and Miyuki-san
are both class committee members.
Kagami and I both like to play games.
But the genres we play are different.
You like gal-games and RPGs,
while I mostly play shooters.
I had thought that Tsukasa
and I were the dumb ones,
but this time around, there was
a bit of a difference between us.
Well, not doing so well doesn't
bother me at all this time.
Worry about it at least a little bit!
If you lower your guard just because
everyone else did poorly,
you'll get left behind.
Or rather...
This time, I didn't bet anything
with Dad, so I'm not upset at all.
I'm sure you will never
end up a decent adult.
If you want to be like Miyuki,
you should take notes all the time,
not just around the exams.
Miyuki-san is very neat...
She's a typical type A.
Oh, people say that often,
but actually my blood type is O.
Really, type O? You don't look it.
Yes, but...
According to this book,
"Blood Type Reader"
there are many traits of
type O blood that fit me.
For instance...
Like how type O people
are childish and simple...
I think that fits me very well.
Type O people are forceful
and greedy and stingy...
So Miyuki-san has a side like that too?
Konata, you're type A, right?
Yeah, though a lot of people
mistake me for type B.
Type As care about their surroundings
and the people they interact with.
They wish for peace
in human relations?
Does this fit you at all?
I am too caring, and I notice
all sorts of things!
Only when it concerns your hobbies.
I'm calm, and praise other people!
Only when your
homework is involved.
You say that, but what's
your blood type, Kagami?
Me?
I'm type B.
Someone that goes at her own pace,
rude, derails often, contrary,
moody, and doesn't
think things through.
Trying to say something?
Then, you're type AB, Tsukasa?
What do you mean, "Then?"
Why?
No, just a random thought.
From the image you get
from your personalities,
Tsukasa looks like a type A,
and Kagami looks like a type B.
We're both type B,
or rather, we're twins.
Oh, that's right. I overlooked that.
Aren't you the one who
does things at her own pace?
When it comes to fortune-telling,
there are many methods,
like with animals, or even with sushi.
"Sushi Fortunes" "What is your favorite sushi?
The fish you choose shows
what kind of personality you have."
Sushi?
Let's see, Miyuki-san is...
"You are a salmon roe kind of person."
Oh, so Miyuki is salmon roe.
She's posh even here.
I love salmon roe.
So, what about Tsukasa and I?
"You are a cucumber roll type of person."
Cucumber roll...
Cucumber roll, huh?
Well, it is a type of sushi after all...
That fits in pretty well.
And what about you?
Me?
"You are a ginger type of person."
Ginger?
You're ginger!
Don't make fun of the ginger!
Well, its presence is necessary
in a sushi meal,
and the fortune says
good things about it.
Yeah, she's right.
Even cucumber rolls are sushi,
when you think about it...
Hello, Konata?
I'm making sure about that
blood type talk from earlier today,
but fraternal twins can have
different blood types,
so what you were thinking
isn't completely wrong.
You might take me seriously,
so I thought I'd mention it.
Well, thanks for being so polite.
You really are honest.
Kagami, I'm starting to think
you're a type A as well.
That's right, they were doing
a psych test on TV the other day.
More like, those personality tests
get some things right
and some wrong,
so no matter who ends up where,
you feel like the test results
are close enough...
Kagami, if you keep saying
such realistic things,
your life will definitely be boring!
Why can't you act more
your age or something?
Oh, Tsukasa, you did
pretty well this time.
Kagami, you seem to be dropping
your pace a bit compared to usual.
But still, Kagami's scores were better...
Thank you for the hard work,
both of you.
How to put it... You both
did your best and studied hard--
Oh! Tsukasa, you did pretty well!
But Kagami comes out on top after all.
Hey, Matsuri, can't you think
about the atmosphere a bit...
Good morning!
Oh, good morning.
Kagami and Tsukasa, you're both
doing so well. I'm jealous!
Oh, no.
Not at all...
I hear that both of you attend
Ryouou, and furthermore,
your grades are at the top of the class!
--If I could only get my
child to be more like you!
--I feel like I'm getting
complimented as an extra to Sis...
--Oh, it's really not much...
I can't honestly be happy about this!
Lucky Star!
Since we're done with exams,
why don't we take our mind off things
by going out and having a blast?
Oh, that sounds good!
Would you like to go
see a movie for once?
What's playing in theaters now?
There's an amazing one playing now.
What kind?
In a way, it's splatter,
and on top of that,
it has hints of a psycho-suspense thriller.
A premium horror flick!
Oh, then let's go for that!
Okay, how about we go home first,
and then meet up again later?
Let's do that, let's do that!
--Splatter and psycho-horror in one!
That's a good feeling right there!
--That won't cheer me up...
That won't cheer me up at all!
--What do you mean by suspense?
We have some time left...
What do you want to do?
Konata sure is running behind.
Is she going to be late again?
Maybe so.
There's no way that she would
show up before us, either.
Geez, the movie is
going to start already!
When did you get there?
I didn't realize it was you
until I saw that thing!
Well, it's time, so let's go in.
Oh, that's right, can you say
that I'm your sister, Kagami?
Huh? Why?
Well, then I can get in on the
children's price with less suspicion.
That brat! She always makes
a fuss over her height,
but when times like this come around,
she puts it to good use!
That was so scary, Takepi!
Oh, you're just so cute!
I'm a bit hungry.
You're right.
Tsukasa, you got hungry after
screaming so much, right?
Yeah.
What should we eat?
How about a cake buffet?
Sounds good!
Buffet... The outskirts
of a woman's desires!
There are so many different
drinks and cakes.
No kidding.
I wonder if we can try
one of every kind?
For you, Kagamin, it's a piece of cake.
We offer one-hour courses.
Drinks are over there
in the drink corner,
and the cakes are in
the showcases over there.
Please feel free to take what you like.
Okay!
Then, excuse me.
Oh, and if you have an inordinate
amount of food left on the plate,
there will be a separate charge
for what you leave behind.
We'd like to warn you in advance.
I see...
Then, please relax and
have a good time.
I wonder what an inordinate
amount of leftovers is...
There are people out there that
take a ton and don't eat them all.
Come on, let's go.
Taking so much...
Can you eat them all?
What? You too, Kagami...
This is normal when it comes to cakes.
I'm perfectly fine.
Thank you for the food!
This, too!
That, too!
This is getting a bit
on the tough side...
We took too much, thinking we'd
finish it just like the first round.
--A regretful retirement from the race...
--Peek.
But they'll charge extra
if there's leftovers!
That's not good...
So painful... I can't...
Wah, our time is almost up!
Whoa, Kagamin, you've gone so far
as to eat two pieces at once!
I mean, it would be a waste!
I can't...
Don't do that!
If you just go drinking water,
you won't be able to eat more.
Now is the time to cram as much
as you can down your throat,
and wash it all down at the very,
very end with some water!
I see.
You too! Don't just sit there,
eat at least a little bit!
I can't fit anymore in.
I'm sure some pudding or
Bavarian cream will fit! Here!
Kagami, you should eat it.
I'm really on the edge too!
I tell you, I've already given up.
I'm sure you can
wash it down with pudding!
Oh, man...
Now, hurry!
--This won't cheer me up!
This won't cheer me up at all!
--I really can't eat anymore!
The exams are over, so I really
gamed my heart out for
the first time in a while!
Thanks to that, I'm pretty sleepy.
If you could study that intently,
your test scores would be different.
The cute-girl games lately
have lots of places to save,
but I just can't find
a good place to stop.
After all, I'm the type that
finishes all of it in one sitting.
I've always wondered,
but students can't buy
games like that, right?
How do you buy them?
--Dad buys them for me, you know?
--Really!
Every time, I think your family
is amazing, in all sorts of ways.
The dad goes out to buy such...
Or rather, the daughter
shouldn't be asking.
And so, I'm sleepy.
Miyuki-san, you don't look like
the type that plays games.
Oh, we don't have any game consoles,
but we do have a computer,
so I play a small bit.
Oh, what kind of games
do you play lately?
This is a surprise!
Things like Solitaire and Minesweeper.
I get excited every so often.
No... It's not a mistake,
but Miyuki-san, that's not it!
But I kinda get it.
With simple games like that,
somehow you end up
getting really into it.
Yuki-chan, how good are your scores?
Solitaire depends on luck,
but I get over 10,000
points pretty often.
As for Minesweeper, I finally beat
100 seconds on expert mode.
I see...
People like this really play
stuff like that over and over.
There were all sorts of things going on
in the world of sports this year.
Yes, that figure skater won the
gold medal in the Winter Olympics,
and the high school baseball
tournament really got rowdy
with such an amazing
extra-innings game.
Yup, yup, you mean
Prince Handkerchief, right?
Speaking of baseball, that player
went to the US as well...
Hey, is the Japan Series already over?
Way past.
You're kidding! Were there
any bargain sales this year?!
This year's Japan Series was
between there and there,
so it didn't involve any
supermarkets or department stores.
But they had sales that
took advantage of it all.
But in the end, it was just
blocks of ham on sale...
I think they did have that...
In any case, next year,
I should keep an eye on it.
Knowing you, it's all about
buying sweets and stuff, isn't it?
No, I mean stuff like
salt, sugar, soy sauce...
All the condiments we use
at home and stuff.
Well, I'm sure you wouldn't
understand what I'm talking about!
Excuse me! I know that I'm
bad at household chores!
Eye drops? Want me to help?
Oh, thank you so much.
Now, lie down face up.
Okay.
Now, relax.
Okay!
Then here goes.
Hey, don't be so tense.
Okay...
Oh, I'm sorry...
It's not on purpose, but...
Your face is scary!
The problem with giveaways and stuff
is that it takes time for
the goods to arrive.
That's where I found a way to
enjoy giveaways twice, Kagamin.
What is it?
In the beginning,
you enjoy it like a festival,
and then you get happy again
when the goods arrive,
right around when you
forgot you even entered.
See, what a deal!
One piece, twice the yummy!
I hate waiting in the first place...
but I guess when you like something,
you can be positive about it all.
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Hi! Today, we'd like to bring you
Lucky Channel in a lively manner!
Time goes by so quickly, and this
is already the ninth installment!
I'm Akira Kogami, your navigator!
And this is someone that will be
called out by our producer Itoh,
like, "Shiraishi, come over here a sec."
What, really?
Devoting 100% of my powers
to being Akira-sama's assistant,
I'm Minoru Shiraishi.
Nice to see you all!
--Now, today is the third time
we'll be introducing a character.
--Tamegoro gets all surprised with a wah!
--This time, it will be Tsukasa Hiiragi!
Are you a clumsy slow turtle?
--Hiiragi...
--Finally...
I'm sorry.
Finally, things are picking up!
Yes! I feel we need to re-cinch
our loincloths, and do our best.
Right, Akira-sama?
Loincloths?
You know, I am an idol after all,
so things like that are a little...
Think about that, okay?
Oh, that's right... Then...
How about we cinch the loincloths
so hard we get wedgies...
You know, I may be going
out of my way to say this,
but I'll tell you one thing.
Going out of your way?
When a comic can't manage anything
but potty humor, it's all over.
I was a comic?
That, and coming up
with the same topic.
You've been doing that
a lot lately, so be careful.
Sure...
And so,
what were we talking about today?
Oh, we were introducing
Miss Tsukasa Hiiragi.
Oh, oh, oh, you mean that To Hea__--
Mi-Mi-Miracle...
Kamig___--
...Minorun-run!
Right?
You'd really say that?
What is it...
The character that seems like
an idol from the previous
generation, right?
Oh, well, I guess so.
Well, Miss Tsukasa,
if you say that she's an idol,
it's not the case that she
wouldn't look like an idol.
Don't make me laugh!
Tsukasa Hiiragi is an idol?!
Where did you get that from?
You know, you've been
working with me like this,
so why don't you learn what
a true idol is all about, huh?
All right...
Tsukasa Hiiragi is only
a healing-type with a face
that looks like she has
no happiness, right?
I see... Maybe her face
lacks happiness.
--In this case, Tsukasa really
doesn't matter here.
--Not even my own father hit me before!
I'll teach you right here
the basic notions of what an idol is!
First off, how your photos are taken.
You know, this will be a learning
experience for you as well,
so put some effort into listening up!
Yes, ma'am!
You know how you get your picture
taken suddenly in the streets, right?
Now, push down on the shutter.
A face lacking in happiness?
Well, it goes something like this.
Props are necessary items too.
It's best that you have them
handy at all times.
Where?
That, and sometimes when
you're walking down the street,
it'd be bad if someone caught
a snap of you when you're off guard,
so you should be tense at all times.
And, make your teeth
shine really white!
Shinjo!
...theater.
And then, the eyes should be
as round as acorns, and wide open.
Express laughter with only this area.
Scary...
The expression should be made up
as naturally as possible.
For instance, if a camera were to be
suddenly pointed at you here...
Akira is so surprised!
Just like that.
I see... Naturally, huh...
That's right... Also, as a variation,
when you're leaving
with a guy from a hot--
Too bad! It's time for us
to say goodbye already!
And so, please send questions
and praise to me, as well as
comments about the show to
this segment, one after another!
We also accept submissions on
the radio and on our homepage!
Yes. Now, see you again. Please
look forward to the next episode!
Bye-nee!
A photo shoot! We had one!
Yes, we did one.
--How was it?
--I wore a pink cardigan and everything!
Oh, you were so cute.
Thanks so much!
Is something the matter?
Not so? Everyone commented
on the cuteness.
--That's right, you were all worked up.
--That's right... I was worked up.
You seemed to be having fun.
You know, kinda looking up
at the camera...
And folding your hands together
underneath your chin...
It was all very fun. Yeah.
--Maybe you didn't get enough of it all?
--Well, cross-dressing included,
I can't get enough of all of it.
Did you check the photos?
No, I haven't.
--The manager checked the photos,
--Yes. Yes.
And mentioned that a
couple shots were... problematic.
Well, I think I'm fine on that aspect,
because I have tons of photos
of me while I'm hard--
Sorry, sorry, I made such
an elementary mistake.
This time, I'll make sure
to sing properly.
So she says,
entering yet another song!
Lend that to me once in a while!
Here you go.
Did you guys decide
on something, Tsukasa?
Hold on for a little bit longer.
I haven't done enough studying,
so I don't know that many songs...
It's all right. I'll sing in
the meanwhile, anyway.
Hey, can you sing something
other than an anime song?
This one isn't an anime song.
I've heard this before somewhere.
What is it?
It's Kyon-Kyon.
I sang this song a lot
with Dad back when.
So if it's not an anime song,
it's an oldie?
What? Calling this an oldie
would be an insult to Kyon-Kyon!
♪ The encounter was in the wind,
from the day I fell in love ♪
Tsukasa, a simple song will do.
Like, a children's song.
I'm looking in that area too, but...
I'm terribly sorry.
You don't have to fret so much.
We still have a lot of time left.
♪ Please don't cry, my loving heart,
if my wishes were to come true ♪
♪ I want to get over the river of tears,
and forget everything ♪
♪ A painful one-way romance,
one that you aren't conscious of ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
Konata here.
In World 3-1 of Super xxxxx Bros.,
at the stairs close to
the end of the stage,
when you step on the turtle
that's coming down just right,
and keep hitting the A button
to keep hopping and jumping
and kicking the turtle
for infinite lives...
That's all good in and of itself,
but sometimes you
accidentally go too far
and end up with more than 129 men,
and when you do, it's game over
as soon as you die once.
That's not infinite lives!
But putting that snide
remark aside, you know,
maybe it's an admonition about life,
to do everything in moderation,
from that company located
near Toufukuji Station.
Next episode: Desires.
"Desires"
Please look forward to it!