Your Highness, I have your tea.
You're looking at that again?
I got it from Mother, so...
Why not look at it?
The legend of the Silver
Princess and the Blue Knight...
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
Cultural Festivals and Beetles?!
What?!
We have to write a script for the theater club?!
That's right!
The cultural fair is almost here.
My best friend, Matsudaira Kenji,
is in the theater club,
and they still don't know
what they're doing this year!
I would like to help my friend!
And for that, I need your help!
So, Sanae, where's this act coming from?
Mr. Glasses told him that he's got
no talent for this sort of thing,
so he's not expecting any help, and
I guess Koutarou didn't like that.
How idiotic.
If everyone writes one,
the chance one of ours gets
used will go up quite a bit!
Theater Club Shouharu Festival Play Script
Application Guidelines
The deadline is the end of this month?
There's not much time.
I can't do this...
I'm not asking you to do this for free.
Corona House #106 Territory Allocation
No Man's Land
If you help me write, I'll give you 5 points.
5 points
And if any of yours gets
picked, I'll give you 20 points!
20 points
So, if no one has theirs picked,
you're giving away 20 points,
and if someone has theirs
picked, you're losing 40.
That's quite the gift, Koutarou.
Big!
Yes, it is!
You're really dumb, aren't you?
Is it that important to show him up?
Theiamillis, Your Highness.
Y-Yeah?
Sometimes men must take up a fight.
I-I see.
Anyway, I, Koutarou Satomi,
would like to request your help!
Help me get back at my enemy, Makkenji!
I'll do it!
I'll participate!
If mine gets picked, I'll get 25 points,
and even if it doesn't, I'll get 5 points!
Even if it just helps me out a little...
Yeah!
Work hard so they pick yours!
Very well, Neanderthal.
If a subordinate requests help,
it's a master's job to fulfill that request.
I'll do it, too!
I'm currently in a cease-fire
with you, anyway, so
I don't think it'd be that bad to help out.
Well, then.
I guess I'll have to
participate myself, as well.
I may have the most points, but
I'm not so nice that I would allow
Theia-dono to overtake my three point lead.
A prudent course of action.
But, to be honest, I think
it'd be fun to try this out.
That sounds just like you.
Yeah.
I appreciate all of your help!
Just you wait, Makkenji!
To be honest, I'm not sure what to write.
Left! Left!
Your Highness, I have to analyze some data,
so I'll be heading back to the Blue Knight.
Sure, I'll be back soon.
I've already figured out what I'm writing.
What?!
Are you serious, Tulip?!
We're just not on the
same level, Neanderthal.
This chick...
I'll get everything ready for writing, then.
Satomi-san, I'd like to ask you something.
Hm? What is it?
Well, the vice president from
the Cosplay Society wants me
to take care of her pet while she moves.
Pet? What kind of pet?
Well...
What?! You've already brought it here?!
Here it is.
Show me!
What is it?
Are you stupid, Yurika?!
Why did you bring that thing into this room?!
Do you understand what you've done?!
I'm sorry...
Why did you decide to take this thing?!
Wasn't there something else you could do?!
No...
Hm? Is this bug really that dangerous?
Well, Theia-dono,
this is a rhinoceros beetle.
Do you really like beetles
that much more than me?!
What should we do, Neanderthal?!
If Ruth sees this, it'll be awful!
That's why I'm worried!
How long do you have to keep him?
The vice president's family
just came into a lot of money,
so they have a bunch of stuff...
I think it'll be a while.
One or two months...
One month
Two months
People go crazy when
they get a lot of money.
Yeah, but Ruth always acts on a schedule,
so I don't think it'll be hard to—
This is bad, Tulip!
Sorry, I forgot something.
Hm?
Were you all doing something?
Oh, nothing at all.
Yeah, we're not doing anything.
We definitely don't have a be—
No, it's really nothing.
Right, Tulip?
The Neanderthal is right.
You said nonfiction,
did your parents run away
and elope or something?
Yeah, my mom's family was rich,
so they wanted her to get
married for the family, you know?
She ran off to my dad's place.
I see.
Want to take a break, Koutarou?
I've been borrowing your body to write, so...
I'm fine.
I haven't even figured out
what I'm going to write yet.
It's weird to have a literal ghost writer,
but it's fun.
Well, then,
after this I'll massage your shoulders
and help you out.
Sure, thanks.
You've got pretty nice writing, Sanae.
I know, right?
Just try remembering how your hand's
moving to make those letters.
Sure, why not?
Keep telling me how awesome I am!
You're awesome.
Help me, Satomi-san!
W-What's wrong, Yurika?!
Hercules-chan keeps moving
around and I can't sleep.
Why do I care?
Yeah, but when Hercules-chan moves around,
he sounds exactly like a cockroach.
Please do something, Satomi-san...
Yeah, but...
You just can't get rid of him?
No! The vice president really
loves the little guy.
Oh, well. I have a good idea.
Really?
Yeah, you can keep Hercules in the closet.
And then you—
Can get out.
Sanae, I understand how you feel,
but you're not helping.
Just relax a little.
Right.
You put Hercules in the closet,
and Yurika, you...
can live in the room for a while.
Huh?
A-Are you sure?
Thank you.
Aren't you happy, Hercules-chan?
Now you don't have to leave.
I'll make sure you get back to your master.
Are you not tired, Your Highness?
I've got the instant writing device ready...
No, it's important that I keep myself
on the same level as this planet.
Also, I need to play on the same
field as the Neanderthal and Kiriha.
A space-time quake.
Coordinates 125, 88, 493.
Size 181.
Right next to this planet.
Could it be...?
One month later
Thank you for coming here,
savior of the Theater Club!
Congratulations on winning
the scenario competition,
Theiamillis Gre Fortorthe-dono.
No problem.
Winner!
Shouharu Festival Playwright
"The Silver Princess and The Blue Knight"
It was a wonderful script,
"The Silver Princess and The Blue Knight".
I'm just glad that this
planet understands true art.
Yeah, right.
Why did the Tulip get chosen,
while the rest of us didn't?
Right, Yurika?
I know, right?
Do you think you amateurs can
really understand what we wrote?
Yeah.
Those two get along really well.
Yeah, almost too much.
I guess they've grown closer after
writing every night together.
You losers can go console each other.
Don't get all worked up, you stupid princess.
Shouharu Festival
The play that the princess wrote, "The
Silver Princess and the Blue Knight",
is based on a legend that everyone
in the Fortorthen Empire knows.
The Fortorthen princess,
Alaia-sama, caught up in a coup,
was defended by Reios-sama, the Blue Knight,
while traveling to their old friend
in the Land of Pardomshiha.
I see.
Sounds like a story the
club president would like.
All Forthorthen girls adore the Blue Knight.
Her Highness really likes the story, as well.
So, she was really enthusiastic, then?
If she didn't have her script
chosen after working so hard,
I'm sure she would have
been extremely dejected.
I'd like it if you could do whatever you can,
considering this shows her
feelings for the Blue Knight.
I understand, Ruth-san.
That's why I'm helping out here.
I'm the one who asked her in the first place.
Thank you.
You're quite nice, Satomi-sama.
No, well...
No!
You all aren't bad, but... I don't know.
You're not the Silver Princess!
You need to be more fragile-looking—
Delicate.
But with a fire burning within her.
Oh, you understand, don't you?
Hey!
I'll be the princess!
I don't want to be the back of the horse.
At least give me a role where they can see my face!
Yeah, we do have a limit
on the people we have.
Since whoever we have be the Blue Knight
will be a far cry from the real thing,
I don't really mind if Matsudaira does it.
I don't really want to
compromise the Silver Princess.
Why are you ignoring me?
Calm yourself, Comrade Yurika!
Satomi-san!
Tulip, I've heard your concerns.
I know someone perfect for
the role of the Silver Princess.
What?
Are you serious?
Tell us!
No problem.
In exchange, though,
I want you to give my comrade,
Yurika here a role where her face is shown.
Satomi-san...
Oh, well.
Is there anything available?
Well, if she can't play the
back of the horse any longer...
There's the evil Bandit A that she can play.
I-I'll do the bandit!
I'll do my best to be evil.
evil
Hey there, leave your
money and get out of here.
You want that role?
So, Neanderth—
Koutarou.
Who's the person you mention
that's perfect for the role?
Hold on.
I'll bring them now—
Excuse me.
Oh, Satomi-kun.
Could I help with something?
Oh, Senpai!
Good timing!
Harumi Sakuraba, huh?
Reios-sama, you can't fight all on your own!
You've already fought so hard for me.
Please forget us, and run...
That was good.
I was worried that you didn't
want to actually take the role,
but I think you'll be fine.
While I think it's a wonderful story,
I don't understand
Princess Alaia's feelings...
I see.
Maybe it's hard because you don't
have a partner to practice with?
I'll help you out, if you'd like.
Y-You will, Satomi-kun?
Yeah!
Soldier A doesn't really
get much screen time.
Princess Alaia, it seems this is as
far as I'll be able to accompany you.
Reios-sama?
Your Highness,
please run away with your sister.
I see.
The princess...
Alaia's drawn to this person.
The Forthorthen Empire,
and the Knitting Club...
they're both in danger, and
could disappear any moment,
but the Blue Knight,
Satomi-kun, saved me from that.
That's right. The Silver Princess and I...
Our feelings are the same.
No, Reios-sama.
No, it was because of you, Princess.
All of your subjects adore you.
That is why for all the people, I...
I understand.
I understand how she feels.
The Silver Princess...
The reason why I didn't fold,
was because you were there...
You've already fought enough.
Please forget us and run.
You should be able to escape on your own!
I want you to live!
Bravo, bravo, Sakuraba-san!
President?
I knew it was the right
choice to make you the lead.
I'm looking forward to the play.
I'll be counting on you too, Satomi-kun.
Right!
Koutarou Satomi will back up
Princess Alaia with everything he has!
S-Satomi-kun...
So, there really aren't any clues
left after that space-time quake.
Yes, we're not even picking up a faint signal.
There's only one answer, huh?
We'll stay alert.
Hopefully it's just a warning.
A day off close to the festival
Work, work.
Excavating stuff!
I need to go help out with
the play after it's over.
What are you doing, Tulip?
Neanderthal, don't just look, help me.
You seem like you're just fine.
What are you doing?
You think a Fortorthen princess would
purposely bring shame to herself?
Talk to you later, Tulip.
Wait, Neanderthal!
Hm?
I guess it'd be better to tell
you then someone that passes by.
They're props.
Huh?
I have a bunch of props to
use for the play in here!
I tried to ask someone to help me carry them,
but I tripped.
That's all!
Just laugh already.
Neanderthal?
Didn't you want to laugh at me?
I changed my mind.
I thought you were trying
to do something crazy again,
but you actually were trying
to help everyone out.
There's nothing really to laugh about there.
Are you hurt, Princess?
N-No.
I'm sorry for my rudeness,
Princess Theiamillis.
The Blue Knight...
Hm?
What's wrong, Tulip?
Did you hit your head or something?
I'm fine!
This isn't going to work!
The Blue Knight is fine, but
what about the princess?!
Koutarou and the theater club president
both said you were the best!
That's weird...
It was so perfect before...
Sakuraba-san, are you not
feeling well, or something?
N-No, that's not it...
There's no time left!
Stop it, Tulip!
Satomi-kun...
Sakuraba-senpai is just tired
from her first full rehearsal.
I'm sure she's going to be nervous when she's
paired up with Makkenji all of a sudden.
What should we do, then?!
We do this one step at a time.
Makkenji, change with me.
Hm?
First, we'll rehearse with me,
then she should be able to
perform like she did before.
After that, we can gradually put
Makkenji in, so it works out.
Do whatever you want.
We can't make do with
her acting as it is now.
Sakuraba-senpai's got a lot more
in her than you think, Tulip.
Right.
Princess Alaia, it seems this is as
far as I'll be able to accompany you.
Reios-sama?
Your Highness,
please run with your sister.
I'll draw as many of them as I can.
Get as far away as you can in that time...
No, I can't leave you behind, Reios-sama.
I was able to come this far because of you.
If you're to thank someone,
it should be the people of this land.
If they didn't help us...
Reios-sama!
How was that, Tulip?!
That's Sakuraba-senpai's true acting ability!
Y-Yeah...
Her acting just now was completely different.
Harumi Sakuraba's pretty good,
but why do I feel more than
ever that the Neanderthal
is a lot like the real Blue Knight?
Okay, Sakuraba-san, how about we have
you do the same with Matsudaira-kun—
But, from what I've seen,
it seems that Sakuraba-senpai
can only perform like this
when she's with Satomi-kun.
Huh?
I have a suggestion, in that case.
How about having Satomi-kun
be the Blue Knight?
You want me to be the Blue Knight?
Yes, rather than having Sakuraba-senpai
try acting with Matsudaira-kun,
why not just have you do it,
Satomi-kun? It's faster.
I see.
I don't have a problem, either.
It's not that I'd like to give up the part,
but unfortunately,
I can't get Sakuraba-senpai to act like that.
Makkenji...
You're the only one who can do this role.
Oh, well.
I'm a little reluctant, but I'll
let Koutarou be the Blue Knight.
W-Wait!
Soldier A was hard enough, but
now I have to be the Blue Knight?!
There's nothing to worry about!
Huh?
I know more about the
Blue Knight than anyone.
I'll make sure you're the perfect
Blue Knight before the play.
Seriously?
Pretty silly to have a play
about the Blue Knight here...
But, this works out pretty well for me.
Theiamillis-san, your play won't be
getting a happily ever after.
The color of the flowers
have already faded away,
while in idle thoughts,
my life passes vainly by,
Hey, what game is this?
as I watch the long rains fall...
I don't understand what she's saying...
Yeah, I don't think the people here
are going to be able to do this.
Next Episode: My Knight