It's something that's very important to me.
I might not even remember my own face soon!
Umm...
No! Nooo!
Hey!
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals, huh?
Is this really where those human experiments are being conducted?
That's not Harima Mika...
You can use as much money however you want.
We'll be together forever.
I love you, Celty.
All of them are fakes.
The world is filled with them.
They say things like, "I love you," and, "I like you," just to tie others down.
"Look this way," and, "Stay by my side."
They just covet and fawn on people.
My love is different.
It's a broader, more complete thing.
I know, sis.
Thanks for the money transfer. See you.
You want me to get you something to drink?
See, from that vending machine right over there.
Wait a bit.
Whoa.
You're so cute.
They still haven't been found?!
I'm incredibly sorry...
What in the world was security doing, then?!
According to the person in charge,
they were staying in the same hotel, but Seiji suddenly
changed locations in the middle of the night—
I could still reach him on his cell phone at seven PM.
If something were to happen to him...
He promised he wouldn't leave Ikebukuro,
so I believe we'll find him soon.
Listen.
What do you think will happen to us if the police get wind of this?!
Well, that's...
That's enough.
I can't wait for you guys.
Director...!
I'll be back soon.
To me, it was just a doll.
Like one of the expensive, beautiful dolls my
uncle would buy for me on his trips overseas.
I didn't like dolls when I was young.
I assume he wasn't trying to please me,
but just kept sending me things he liked.
Hey, Seiji, look at this.
It's pretty, isn't it?
So, what do you think this one over here is?
What?
It was always utterly silent in that house, and we were always alone.
Even before my younger brother was born,
my uncle often had to look after me.
I could also enter and leave his study whenever I wanted.
That's...where it was.
My uncle would sometimes gaze at that thing he'd
smuggled in from overseas as if he were in a trance...
And sometimes he'd even talk to it.
It certainly was beautiful.
More so than any doll he'd ever given me.
It didn't seem mysterious or cruel; it seemed
like just its head was a whole creature.
But that's all it was to me.
That's why, when I secretly invited my brother into the study...
I thought we'd just have some fun.
I may have simply wanted to share my secret with him.
It's pretty, isn't it?
That was the beginning of it all...
My one and only regret, which continues to this day.
This is the first time we've met, isn't it?
Did that list of illegal immigrants
prove useful to you, Ms. Yagiri Namie?
I'm so happy.
To have the director of the sixth research
facility come all the way to a place like this...
Please, sit anywhere over there.
It's an emergency. Find out where my brother is.
I'll pay you however much you want.
I haven't been able to contact him since last night.
He should be somewhere in Ikebukuro.
Not that much time has passed, has it?
Why are you so worried?
He's with a girl; one who has a wound on her neck.
A girl?
He's at that age, you know.
Get going now!
Wait a second.
Aren't there many more important things we should investigate first?
There are rumors going around that your company is
about to be taken over by that foreign company Nebula, right?
If that's true, then your position—
Mr. Orihara Izaya, I don't have time for idle chitchat.
How unexpected.
That such a capable woman as yourself
would be in love with her younger brother, that is.
What do you know about me?
The Yagiri Namie I know is quite a distinguished woman.
I mean, even though it was a family business,
your father screwed up and had to hand it over
to your uncle, who doesn't do you any favors.
So you had to use your own abilities to get the job,
and now you've come this far, despite being so young.
And you're also very beautiful.
You certainly do know me well.
It should be easy for you to search for my brother, then.
Your brother, huh?
You shouldn't interfere with his business, you know.
I'm not interfering!
I'm the only one who can protect him.
It seems stalkers never do realize what they're doing.
They always say they're protecting their—
Don't group me together with any stalkers!
You're scary.
It was just a joke.
Alright, I'll help you.
However, we'll do things my way.
Information dealers are different from the police.
What rules do you play by...?
I have a question.
Are you jealous of that girl with the wound on her neck?
Why?
There's no way I'd be jealous of her!
A chest-burning jealousy that dyes people a rusty red...
Sis...I have...someone I like.
I knew Seiji was slowly getting stranger.
He'd go into our uncle's study for no reason at all, then stare at that thing every time he snuck in.
Seiji wasn't in love with a person.
It had no soul, or even a body.
I wanted to take Seiji's mind off of it, so I asked my uncle
if I could move it as soon as I entered the company,
and brought it to the facility as a research subject.
That's when it happened.
Nebula began contacting us,
and just when I started losing my mind, trying not to
let any information leak, my security card was stolen.
The card that only I had...
Sis, I might have killed someone.
What should I do?
And what welled-up in my chest at that moment was neither fear nor anger, but unbounded joy.
Seiji needed me.
You don't need to worry about anything.
Leave everything to your sister.
Okay?
Now, about her—not that girl over there...
So you did take her?
It's okay.
Leave everything about her to me.
It's okay. Really.
At that time, I didn't realize there was a
stupid girl named Harima Mika stalking Seiji.
After she invaded his room without permission and saw "it," Seiji just...
I'll protect you, no matter what.
Ahh, okay.
Apparently, you don't have to panic.
The police should be picking them up and contacting you shortly.
I did say "police," but you should be fine.
It's no big deal.
I assume.
Don't toy with me!
Yes?
Yes, it is.
What? What's wrong?
We're going?
But, we still...
Wait!
I'm happy you love me so much.
I love you, too.
Forever and ever.
I'm scared.
Of what?
Please, take me far away...
I want to be alone with you, too, but where would we go?
What's with them?
A lovers' quarrel?
C'mon.
No!
Stop it!
Okay, please calm down.
We're not bad people or anything.
No! Nooo!
Just listen.
Let...me...go! Let...me...
Huh?
Let her go!
I'm alright. It doesn't hurt.
Just go.
I don't really get it, but you have to chase her, don't you?
I've always wanted to say this:
Leave this to me and go on ahead!
Wait!
Uh, so-sorry...
Are you okay?
You're...
Wait!
No, you wait!
Let me go!
I said, "Let me go!"
Is she your girlfriend?
Yeah, she's my destiny!
Why does she look like that?
Like I'd know!
Whaaaaat's thaaaaat?!
Are you saying you don't know your girlfriend?
Isn't that a bit irresponsible?
Huh?!
Stuff like that's not important when you love someone!
Oh?
Then why?
Why's she your destiny?
Because I love her!
There's no other answer!
I can't use another word for it besides "love!"
That's why I...
The black bike!
...I'm going to act on it!
I'll protect her!
That's all it is!
I like you a lot more than Izaya.
So I'll leave it at this.
I'm going to bleed if I pull this out, huh?
I'll pull it out after I buy some band-aids.
No, maybe an instant adhesive would be better?
In other words, your head was walking around attached to another body...
When you caught it, a high schooler interfered...
Then another high schooler appeared when you were chasing it...
And he ran off with it?
You want me to believe all that?
I won't ask you to believe it all.
Well, I do.
But why was Shizuo there?
I'd completely forgotten about that...
I was waiting in the park while on a job from Izaya,
when Shizuo happened to pass by, so we started talking...
Anyway, I got a message afterward saying the job was canceled, so it's okay.
Orihara, huh?
Anyway, I wanted to talk to you...
So, you're still confused, huh?
I'll listen to whatever you have to say.
Why is my head on someone else's body?!
I'm in the dark, seeing as I didn't witness
the events, but if I could venture a guess...
What if...
It found a girl who looked like she had your build and attached itself to her.
That's horrifying...
It could've found a newly dead corpse.
Stop that!
But...no...
It couldn't have...
What I did wasn't wrong...
Creating that girl with the body from that incident...For Seiji's sake...
I have to go.
It's okay.
Everything's okay.
She...
It was scary, wasn't it?
But nothing went wrong, did it?
My love never faltered, even when she ran away and met up with Seiji.
Seiji's love uses my love for him as a stepping-stone.
He knows that, and I know that he knows.
Everything's twisted, but still...
Damn, that was a Raira Academy uniform.
Who was he?
I know, so just leave it to me.
Anyway, we've got to find a girl from Raira.
Then all I can do is meet my head and talk with it.
You mean the head that could only scream when it saw you?
What're you going to do about a head that's living as a complete person?
Are you telling me you'd separate it from its body for your own sake?
Celty...
I don't want to admit...
That I've lost my head and my memories...
That all my efforts these past twenty years have been in vain...
They haven't been in vain.
I'll get her back for you.
Just wait here.
Oh yeah, where's your cell phone?
Did you lose it?
I don't know.
It wasn't there, even though I put it in my bag.
Eh?
She...needs me.
We have to be alone.
Really? I guess so...
It's alright. Leave everything to your big sister.
What nerve!
Dolls should act like dolls and do as they're told.
And not interfere with my love.
I've decided...
I don't want to regret anything else...
Ever again.
Listen.
Circulate a message to all our underlings.
I don't care whether she dies or not.
Depending on the circumstances, dispose of her on the spot.
I see.
Everyone's busy.
I can't wait!
I can't wait!!
I can't wait!!!
There are so, so, so many things even I don't know in this town that continually appear and disappear!
That's why I can't leave a city where so many people gather!
People love!
I like people!
I love them!
That's why...
People should love me as well.
Thank you.
Do you feel any calmer?
Can you answer questions?
You said you didn't remember anything, right?
In other words, that means...umm...you have amnesia?
I'll say it again, but I think you should go to the police or a hospital...
I'm sorry!
No, it's okay.
Please don't apologize.
I have to go...
Before she interferes...
Forever and ever—
I have to go.
Seiji...
I love you.
Err...
The headless rider, Orihara Izaya, and the
girl with the wounded neck appeared again...
And to top it all off, a guy from the next class over is in The Dollars!
Next Time: The First and Only.
I had a dream where I was leading an abnormal life, yet...