As of now, I will be the fifth Grade team's coach for today!
Nice to meet all of you!
You just randomly appeared out of
nowhere and claimed to be our coach.
That's right, that's right!
Can we even believe you?
Of course.
Ginga is the best.
Even if you say that...
All of you want to win, right?
Oui.
I have a great strategy.
Really?
Please tell us...
Hasegawa-san?
I requested him.
I asked my dad if he could be the fifth grade team's coach for today.
What?
How could you betray us, Subarun?!
No, it's not that.
Even with him helping them, we should win without much of a fight, given our calibre.
I see.
That's true, right?
If Subaru-san's father gives them advice,
I think the ball will be passed around the five of them more.
That's true.
The fifth graders are currently unaware that basketball has to be played amongst five people.
The match will become more fun.
Oh~!
Hina wants to have more fun, too!
Let's go!
okose big halation
起こせ! big halation
Invoke the big halation
ano hi no chikai wo hatasu tame
あの日の誓いを果たすため
To fulfill that promise you swore on that day
hirake! new formation
開け! new formation
Open out, the new formation!
shisen no aizu yobiau
視線の合図呼び合う
Call out to each other with eye contact
kibou o nosete hanate arch
希望を乗せては放て arch
Bear and release the arch of hope
itsumo no toori ni ne
いつもの通りにね
Just like always
shinjiteru (makasete)
信じてる (まかせて)
I'll believe in you (Leave it to us)
mune ni te wo atete
胸に手を当てて
Bring your hand to your chest
hikiyoseta heijoushin
引き寄せた平常心
and tug at your usual attitude
kanaete dekita koto
叶えて来たこと
The things I fulfilled,
sorezorega oboeteru
それぞれが覚えてる
I can remember them all.
ano hi hisoka ni naita koto mo
あの日密かに泣いたことも
Including that day when you cried in secret.
onaji yumemiteru no wa
同じ夢見てるのは
Surely, we can't be the only ones
watashi tachi dakeja nain dayo ne
私たちだけじゃないんだよね
having the same dream.
me no mae ni arawareta
目の前に現れた
Appearing in front of our eyes,
yuru ganai hitomi hibana chirashite
揺るがない瞳火花散らして
is an unfaltering spark that's dispersing.
okose big halation
起こせ! big halation
Drop the big halation!
hiraku space e hashiriko me
開くスペースへ走り込め
Run into the open space!
wazukana sensation
僅かな sensation
The slight sensation
senobi shite ita kinou e
背伸びしていた昨日へ
when you were overstretched yesterday
wakare wo tsugetara
別れを告げたら
Announce your goodbyes,
egao wo tsunagete
笑顔を繋げて
Connect your smiles,
yume mita basho e hanate arch
夢見た場所へ放て arch
Release the arch to where you see your dreams
Ginga Paradigm
Private
Keishin
Academy
Kagetsu!
Yes!
Hii!
Okay!
What?
They are fast!
Get-tan!
Yes!
She's shooting directly?
Masami!
Oh!
Masami, amazing.
They're good.
No wonder she was so confident in saying to leave the long-range shots to her.
In normal basketball, that would have been a three-pointer.
Masami-san definitely practised hard.
Also, looking at Kagetsu-chan's movements...
They're on a level that can't be reached easily.
That's because Hinata has trained her before.
Considering Kagetsu's height, she should know post play as well.
You seem to know quite a bit.
T-That's not true.
Even though I asked for it, this team is becoming quite a handful.
The team's movements have become drastically better.
What did you do?
Who knows.
The fifth graders are pretty good.
Yeah, their movements have become quicker.
I didn't think they'd give us such a challenge.
Kage-chan was amazing!
She kept coming at me relentlessly.
Oh~!
She's not Hina's younger sister for nothing.
All right, let's keep this up!
Yeah!
Let's bring up the heat, we won't lose!
Oh!
Maho-chan!
Leave it to me!
Hey, Dad.
I think I might have figured out your strategy.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
It's not really a strategy.
I think it's more like volleyball, where there's a shooting rotation.
Exactly.
I wouldn't expect less from Coach Subaru.
How did you figure it out?
First, I thought something was off.
I was wondering why no one was shooting twice in a row.
For example, even though Kagetsu-chan could
have done a putback off the rebound, she didn't.
That's true...
If that were so, then the order of people taking the shot was also predetermined.
Tsubaki-chan, Masami-san, Hiiragi-chan, Kagetsu-chan, then Mimi-chan.
This is the order, I suppose.
Oh, you're definitely my son!
But even though you said that, wouldn't they reject it?
Of course.
So in order to give them some motivation, I raised a condition.
Condition?
If they manage to maintain the rotation throughout the game, I would treat them to ice cream.
I see.
You taught them what to do instead of the what not to do.
Shooting is not where all the fun in basketball comes from, right?
Changing their point of view, and getting them to have fun is most important.
Oh...
Unlike you, your father actually takes basketball seriously.
What's that supposed to mean?
Get-tan!
Yes!
Just now, Get-tan didn't shoot in this situation.
That time, the one who shot was...
Oh no!
I'm so awed that I'm in a daze, Masami.
I won't even give you enough time to say that.
Oh~!
Maho!
I won't lose here!
Oh no!
I'll take this!
Tsuba!
Nice, Hii!
Tomo, I'll leave Mimi-chan to you.
Airi, Get-tan can't shoot long, so guard her on the inside!
Yup!
Maho, Hina, mark TsubaHii more closely.
Close off their passing lanes!
Okay!
Oh~!
Thanks!
Saki!
I'll work hard too.
I won't lose to you, Masami.
Tomoka, let's have one more match!
Yup!
[Name] Hakamada Kagetsu
[Date of Birth] 20th February
[Blood Type] O
[Class] Grade 5 Class D
[Height] 160cm
[Bust] Biggest amongst the fifth graders
[Rival] Hakamada Hinata
(Even though she is her respected elder sister,
Hinata is also her goal as a basketball player)
It's the move that Subaru-san always practices!
I won't let you!
A scoop shot, huh?
It's a shot she only scores once or twice by luck though.
Tomoka-chan is also going for the scoop shot?
I'll stop you!
Please, Hinata!
Oh~!
Nice pass!
Oh, she didn't care about the 1-vs-1.
Their teamwork is impeccable.
I lost against Tomoka again.
We won't lose in terms of chemistry!
Thank you very much!
So frustrating!
Go practise some more, TsubaHii.
That's right.
You guys haven't practised much as a team, right?
You won't win against us like that.
Erm, if you need a goal, I think we can all practise together.
Let's practise together!
Is that OK, Masami!
Don't joke around!
We don't need your pity.
That's right, that's right!
We're lending you the court momentarily.
Nee-sama, good work.
Oh~!
The match was fun.
Kage-chan, you were really good!
Thank you very much.
Tomoka, next time.
Next time I won't lose.
Yup.
We won't lose either!
As a temporary team, you did well!
It was really amazing.
Get rid of that frustration and work harder as a team from now on.
Right?
Ginga, will you continue coaching us?
I really want to, but I have to return to Hawaii soon.
Besides, there's someone more suitable compared to an old man like me.
I bought the ice cream!
Who's that?
She is Subaru's childhood friend.
Aoi-chan will be everyone's coach.
I am Ogiyama Aoi.
Nice to meet you.
Is it really okay, since you're his childhood friend?
What a beautiful layup.
Told you so.
It'll be fine to leave it to her.
Let's defeat the sixth graders together.
OK?
Throw down Maho Dumbo!
I'm fine as long as I can win against Saki.
I'll defeat Tomoka.
Let's work hard together.
Please teach us well!
Same here, I hope to be a good coach!
Good job, Tomoka.
You were amazing as always.
No, it is because Subaru-san is always coaching us.
I could react to Mimi-chan's move because Subaru-san always practises it with me in the morning.
The scoop shot?
If you could, could you teach me that move someday?
Yeah.
Although, mine is still incomplete.
Thanks, Aoi.
It was a sudden request.
It's fine, I was interesting in coaching the kids, too.
Really, it's a great help that you accepted.
I'll repay you sometime.
That's fine, don't worry about it.
The match was fun!
If we could do it again soon, that would be great!
Oh~!
I'm looking forward to it!
It would be better if they had joined our team...
Well, it's already over.
Oh, that's right! Mokkan, did you finish it?
The thing we were going to pass to Subarun?
The invitation to her birthday party?
Y-Yeah, I finished writing it.
It is a bit embarrassing...
Even if it's embarrassing, you have to do it!
Oh~!
Will you give it to Onii-chan tomorrow?
Yup...
I'll do my best!
I'm holding a birthday party this Sunday.
To Subaru-san
Everyone is going, so if you want to, Subaru-san...
I'll gladly go if I'm not any trouble.
No, not at all!
How about you, Subaru-san.
Aren't you busy?
I don't have anything more important than your birthday.
Thank you very much.
I'll look forward to it!
I have to buy a present.
What would be good?
Subaru!
Oh, what's up?
Kazunari said that he found a member to join the interest group.
Really?
Narayama-san, who has been with us in middle school.
I managed to get a lead through our school's students.
Could that possibly be Kashima from Hashida Middle School?
The ace from Hashida Middle School?
Was his name like that?
I don't really know, but this is that person's phone number.
You could talk directly.
See you!
All right!
Suddenly, it seems like lots of new things are about to happen.
Yeah.
I'll buy a new ball and cake after school.
Hey, Aoi.
Can I go too?
If I choose on my own, I don't think I'd choose a good one.
Choose?
Since I'm always being taken care of, I want to put my heart into choosing it.
Is that...
Yeah, a present.
We always seem to be together,
and because of that, I don't know what to get.
So I thought it would be better if you choose instead of me.
Gosh, even though I said I didn't need it!
Don't worry about me!
Also, if it's something Subaru chose, I'm sure anything-
I can't do that.
I don't understand what girls like, so I don't know what to pick.
What?
Erm...
Would something related to basketball be better for Tomoka?
That's right, something related to basketball-
Eh?
It's Tomoka's birthday present.
I thought of other things, but it's still difficult.
T-Tomoka-chan?
I see, that's right.
Yeah, yeah.
I see, so basketball's still the best, right?
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Thank you very much!
Thanks to you, Aoi, I got something nice.
Thanks.
No, that's great.
Cheers!
Tomoka, happy birthday!
Thanks for inviting me over.
No, same for me.
Thank you for coming over.
This chicken is delicious!
Yes!
My, that's great.
Everyone, eat up!
Tomoka, will you become as good a cook in the future?
I don't know...
I will teach her well.
Tomoka's home-made cooking, huh?
Seems like something to look forward to.
Subarun, eat mine too!
Oh~!
Hina will cook too!
I don't know if it will go well, but I will try my best!
A repertoire apart from okonomiyaki is important too, right?
Y-Yeah, I'll look forward to it.
Thanks for the food.
I'm so full~
Oh~! Onii-chan, would you like a drink after a meal?
I'll take oolong tea.
Oh~!
Hina will pour it for you.
Thanks, Hinata-chan.
Hinata-chan?
You can use Hina's head as a table.
Hey, Hina!
That kind of delicious position has to be given to Mokkan!
That's right.
Today, Hasegawa-san is Tomo's!
Oh~!
That's right, sorry, Tomoka.
Airi, help her!
Now, get her in Hasegawa-san's lap!
And then,
"You can do whatever you want with my body", appeal time!
Erm, you don't have to do it if you don't want to.
No, it's not that, in fact-
Oh~!
Hina is all warmed up!
Isn't that great, Tomoka-chan?
Okay, let's give Tomo her presents.
Yup!
I agree!
Oh~!
So big!
Everyone chose it for Tomoka!
We hope you like it.
Can I open it?
Of course!
This...
It will help in Mokkan's training, right?
Everyone thought something you could use
through middle and high school would be good.
Tomoka is like an older sister~
Hina will grow up quickly soon!
Hinata
Watching Tomoka-chan play
basketball is so amazing! I love it!
Airi
Please continue to be good
friends with me from now on!
Let's play more basketball!
Saki
Ya~~~~~y!
With this, Tomoka is also a
grown up woman like us!
Maho
It's so cute!
Oh~!
It's Hina's special drawing!
Thank you.
I'll take good care of this!
I also have gifts for you.
First up is Aoi's present.
Wow, amazing!
I'll have to thank Aoi-san.
It's done, Tomoka-chan.
Yup, it looks great!
Oh~!
Tomoka is really cute!
As expected from Aoi-chi!
She has great taste!
And this one's mine.
Here.
It's more practical, so it's nothing good.
No, as long as it's from Subaru-san,
I'm happy no matter what it is.
Thank you very much!
Actually, there's one more present.
Amazing!
That was lucky.
I have to thank the gods for that.
I want to teach you the scoop shot technique as my next present.
Let's continue practising!
Just like you, Tomoka, I want to make this shot my own.
Yes!
All right, let's start practising!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Rolling! Rolling! hazumitsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! はずみつずけろ
Rolling! Rolling! Continue bouncing forward!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show you guts cool say what saikou daze! Yay!
Show you guts cool say what 最高だぜっ! イェイ!
Show your guts cool say what it's the best! Yay!
karada mo kokoro mo SS dakedo
カラダもココロもSSだけど
Although our bodies and hearts might be small in size,
yume wa LL datte ii jan! ii jan!
夢はLLだっていいじゃん! いいじゃん!
isn't it good enough that our dreams are large!
seishun miman no onayami ippai
青春未満のお悩みいっぱい
We are full of worries about growing up
hitori janai kara norikoerareruyo
ひとりじゃないからのりこえられるよ
We're not alone, so we can get through this!
motto umaku naritaina
もっと うまく なりたいな!
I want to become better!
(motto)
(もっと)
(Much)
(umaku)
(うまく)
(better)
anatano (oh...) odoroku (sugoi) kao ga mitai no
あなたの(おぉ...)おどろく(スゴイ) 顔が見たいの
I want to see (boo~) your surprised (Impressive!) face!
mawase mawase mawase mawase
まわせ まわせ まわせ まわせ
Spin, spin, spin, spin
chikyuu wa okki na Basket Ball
地球はおっきな Basket Ball
The Earth is just a big basketball.
ashita wo shinjite ikuyo! (hai i-ku-yo)
あしたを信じていくよ! (ハイ い・く・よ)
Believe in tomorrow and move forward! (Yes, let-us-go!)
mawase mawase mawase mawase
まわせ まわせ まわせ まわせ
Spin, spin, spin, spin
uchuu wa okkina Basket Court
宇宙はおっきなBasket Court
The universe is a big basketball court.
anata ni todoketai na... (se-no!)
あなたに届けたいな... (せーのっ)
I want it to reach you... (One, two!)
pasu! pasu! pasu!
パス! パス! パス!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
uketometekudasai!
受け止めてください!
Please receive it!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Rolling! Rolling! hazumitsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! はずみつづけろ
Rolling! Rolling! Continue bouncing forward!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show you guts cool say what saikou daze! Yay!
Show you guts cool say what 最高だぜっ! イェイ!
Show you guts cool say what is the best! Yay!
We lost...
Tomoka was really strong!
Next time, we'll have our revenge!
We can't lose to Maho Dumbo!
Until I get back at Saki!
Let's practice together so that we can catch up to the sixth graders!
Next Time:
A Foolish Man
Yup!