Full Moon's second single is finally in the works.
She's singing a cover of one of her father's old songs.
All that was left was to go ask Takasu-san to produce it for her, but...
Full Moon
Plan (Proposal)
Talent Organization Village Pro
Ooshige Masami
Full Moon
Plan (Proposal)
Talent Organization Village Pro
Ooshige Masami
Full Moon
Plan (Proposal)
Talent Organization Village Pro
Ooshige Masami
Full Moon
Plan (Proposal)
Talent Organization Village Pro
Ooshige Masami
Full Moon
Plan (Proposal)
Talent Organization Village Pro
Ooshige Masami
Full Moon
Plan (Proposal)
Talent Organization Village Pro
Full Moon
Plan (Proposal)
Talent Organization Village Pro
Full Moon
...Takasu-san had agreed to produce the same song for Wakamatsu Madoka.
Then... who should we ask to be Full Moon's Producer?
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Paging Dr. Nakamura.
Please contact the front desk immediately.
Please contact the front desk immediately...
Come on.
O-Okay...
What's wrong?
Aren't you going to knock?
Huh?
What's up, Mitsuki-chan?
Why are you here?
Ah.
Um... that's...
I just happened to be in the area...
B-Bye.
I see...
It's not an easy thing to ask for, huh...
I'll talk to him myself then.
Mitsuki, you just wait there.
Okay...
Sorry...
Hey, I'm the one who should be sighing.
Why didn't you just ask him?
That's 'cause...
What am I supposed to say...?
It's like a little kid playing make-believe...
I feel like I'm dragging Wakaouji-sensei into this...
We're not playing make-believe here!
Man, you worry way too much!
Anyways, you know...
It's not acting child-like.
Y-You think?
It's not child-like, is it...?
And what's with that Takuto...
He's the one who said that we should all go
together, and then he's like...
"It be better if I didn't".
What's he trying to do?!
Ah...
When Takuto said that he shouldn't, he wasn't lying.
What do you mean?
Wakaouji-sensei, that is...
I guess he doesn't really like him...
Why's that?
I want Wakaouji-sensei and Takuto to get along, but I guess it's impossible.
A doctor... and a Shinigami...
So... if we have a former member of Route L as the producer,
then we can use that to target old fans of Route L and draw them in as well.
It'd be something like this.
Wow...
It's like grown-ups doing business...
I refuse.
Eh?
C-Can you tell me why?
Ah...
I'll tell you the truth.
If you don't produce it, then this plan won't be possible.
For Mitsuki's sake...
...can you please do this?
I refuse.
Why?!
My reason doesn't matter.
No way...
That's right...
It's no use...
You're the only one I can ask Dr. Wakaouji!
They're really going at it now...
You should understand how hard it is!
This will be the conceptual image that we're going to use.
Q-Quite untraditional...
But, it seems like a mismatch...
You hit it right on the nose.
Is is a mismatch.
Eh?
On top of the appeal that her raw, primitive feel has,
I'll throw in something completely different to complement it.
Understand?
Y-Yeah...
Which means that I want each of you to keep this conceptual image in mind.
Any questions?
Takasu Kouhei...
He's not known as the Hit-Maker for nothing...
He'll make me...
Hey! Look here please!
Madoka-chan, over here!
Okay!
...into a top star!
Sorry...
I guess the plan was flawed.
We'll have to patch things up.
But... how do we do that...
Um...
Ooshige-san...
It might be a problem for him.
Hey. Don't say that.
It's your song.
Yeah...
Hey... Mitsuki...
Why do you have a pillow?
Wh... what?
What?!
What?
Producer's Chair
Oh, boy...
Meroko's also...
...begging you too!
Can you give that back?
If I give it back, will you listen to our request?
Now, look here...
Pretty please!
Please! Please! Please! Please! Please! Please! Please!
You're bothering me.
Man!
What's with that doctor?!
He's got that attitude despite knowing that she doesn't have much time yet.
He said last time... that he couldn't accept the fact...
Yeah...
Basically, about her lifespan...
It's not like I don't understand his views as a doctor,
but he's way too hard-headed!
Huh?
Hey, hey.
What have you been doing?
Oh, just a little...
Let's see...
Give up
Ask him
What?
Give up
Ask him
What is she doing?
[Amidakuji: Ladder lottery (used to make decisions, choose turns, or assign prizes)]
Amidakuji, I guess...
Again?
Ah!
What are you doing?
It'll be the same no matter how many times you keep doing it.
No matter which one comes up,
you'll never be satisfied, will you?
Besides, what are you thinking, using amidakuji to decide this...
You're right...
That doctor...
I'm sure he could tell...
...that you aren't sure about how you feel yet.
I get it.
So that's why he said no, huh?
Be clear about your own feelings first.
I agree!
You know, I...
...I could never give up on music...
But Wakaouji-sensei gave it up for good...
...even though he loved music.
It must have been a hard thing to do.
Much harder than what I'm going through...
Maybe.
But, just because of that...
...you're not going to say that you're giving up Eternal Snow, right?
Well...
I won't give up on it.
Is that so...
Then... everything's okay.
What do we have to do next?
We're studying the movement of the constellations and the Moon.
Eh?!
You got your own computer?!
Yep!
Must be nice...
My daddy's so kind.
He'll do anything I ask!
Kind? More like he's spoiling you...
You're so mean!
Wakaouji-sensei!
I have a favor to ask!
Please be my producer!
If Mitsuki-chan's asking me,
I can't very well refuse.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
I love you, Wakaouji-sensei!
That kind of conversation could never happen...
We want to do Eternal Snow... no matter what!
Why are you so determined on doing that?
Because... you're telling us to change the song, boss!
In reality, that won't work.
You can't do Eternal Snow.
You haven't even found anyone who's willing to produce it.
I'm currently talking it over with someone.
And you think that Seed Records will be okay with that person...?
I believe that they will be!
I didn't want to say this, but...
...if you keep this up, I'll have to transfer you.
Transfer?
You mean... change managers?
To put it bluntly, that's correct.
T-That's...
This is Cassiopeia at seven o'clock.
Here... two hours later, at nine o'clock...
It shape has stayed the same,
but its position has changed like so.
Yes.
Excellent job.'
Return to your seat.
What's wrong?
You don't look to happy.
It's nothing, I'm fine.
This is the one thing that I can't talk to Tomoe-chan about...
As Maijima explained...
...the shape of the constellation does not change as time passes...
However, the position in the sky do  change.
Then, next...
...let's look at the relationship between the Earth and the Moon.
The Moon as everyone knows...
...doesn't shine by itself.
Eh?
Do you know what makes it shine, then?
Hasegawa, do you know?
Hey Mitsuki.
The Moon...
It doesn't shine on its own.
Then...
How does it shine?
That's because...
With the Sun at the center...
...the Earth and the Moon revolve around it.
Because it reflects the light from the sun like a mirror...
Then, if there was no Sun...
...the moon wouldn't shine?
That's right.
That means...
That means?
Eichi-kun is my Sun!
But I'm not the only one...
Eh?
The teachers at the orphanage...
The teachers at school...
Your friends...
And...
Your father and mother, who have passed on...
They're all helping you sing, aren't they?
Yeah.
So... just be yourself...
Stay true to yourself.
Everyone is helping you shine.
Eichi-kun...
I...
I'll go try and ask him!
M-Mitsuki?
Can the teacher ask for something too?
Please, I'd like you to sit down.
Kouyama-san did it again!
So, what did you need?
Wakaouji-sensei, I'm begging you.
Please accept the position as my producer!
So that's what this is about.
You know, even if it's Mitsuki-chan who's asking me...
...there's some things that I can do, and some things that I just can't.
I understand what you mean, but I still have to ask you...
Wakaouji-sensei...
...I want you to help me do Eternal Snow !
That's impossible, Mitsuki-chan.
I'm happy you feel that way, though...
I see...
Doesn't he have any regrets?
Eh?
What did you just say?
I said, doesn't he have any regrets?
W-What do you mean?
Mitsuki-chan, who are you...
Could it be those two...
She won't ask you, so I'm going to do it myself.
You.
So you really don't feel anything for music now?
Nothing at all.
I'm so envious...
What do you mean?
Well, I'm a Shinigami...
I see all kinds of people in my line of work
Every one of them... dies with regrets...
If only I had done that...
If only I had done this...
S-Stop it Takuto!
This isn't something I should be saying, but...
...while you're still alive is the only time when you can do what you love.
That means that you have to give it your all!
I don't want to hear that from a Shinigami.
I suppose so.
On top of that, I look like a stuffed animal.
I'm probably not convincing at all.
But, you know...
...it's just like I said.
You can only do what you love while you're alive.
That's why she's working so hard.
While what little is left of her life...
With that tiny body of hers...
There will be suffering... there will be sadness...
But, if she can sing a song that she loves...
I-I'm sorry, Wakaouji-sensei!
Sorry to be a bother to you.
Excuse us!
Hey, you damn brat!
Back then...
...when Route L decided to split...
...I tossed music.
In a world that had nothing to do with music...
...I thought that I could live a different life.
I chose the path of a doctor.
I have never regretted it.
A doctor is a worthwhile job.
But...
...every time I heard music, it hurt inside...
Like reopening an old wound...
I wonder... if that was regret...
If it was, I...
Compared to that, Mitsuki-chan is...
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness...
Only while you're still alive, huh...
Geez!
Geez! Stupid Takuto!
Why'd you say all those things to Wakaouji-sensei!
Hey! I couldn't just stand there any longer!
Hey, hey...
Did something happen?
The hell if I know!
That blockhead...
Oh...
So you're going to let me be the odd one out?
Fine!
Late...
Yeah...
I wonder what's wrong.
Mitsuki...
Ooshige-san!
Sorry... I'm late...
What's wrong? You look awful...
I drank too much last night.
Broken heart?
No, I was just pissed off...
About what?
My boss...
Wait, that doesn't have anything to do with you!
Come on, let's go to work.
Ooshige-san...
That's dangerous...
Okay, good job!
Thank you very much.
Good work.
Hey!
It's over.
Is your headache any better?
A little, I guess...
Wa-Wakaouji-sensei!
The offer that you made a few days ago...
I spent some time thinking over it carefully.
Sensei, I'm very sorry about that!
We won't bother you...
There are some conditions, but...
...I'll accept the position as Mitsuki's producer.
C-Conditions?!
If you want something...
I don't care about money.
I'll get to make music again after all.
Then...
Then... what are the conditions?
If it's something that we can do...
My conditions are...
Mitsuki-chan...
Ah, yes...
First...
...you have to get your throat checked regularly.
Second...
...when the time comes, promise to listen to what I said before
We'll do the surgery, 'kay?
S-Surgery?
That's...
Of course, I'll be the one doing the operation.
I'll have to stop working full-time...
...and work part-time instead, though.
Eh?
A-Are you sure, Wakaouji-kun?
You've already been selected to serve as the next director...
I'd like a little more time.
This may be selfish of me to ask for, but...
...I'd like you to reconsider.
Sensei...
I have my own reasons as well.
I really can't forget about music.
To tell you the truth, I actually wanted to resign...
But there's something besides
music that I must do, after all.
That is... to heal Mitsuki-chan's throat.
Sensei...
I want to hear Mitsuki-chan sing Eternal Snow  as well.
Your father in heaven...
and your mother...
I want to let them hear it!
I...
...believe in you, Wakaouji-sensei.
With your help, I'll be able to shine even more than before.
That's what I plan to do.
I'm going to help you shine more and more...
...until Eichi-kun notices you.
Okay!
Also...
Here.
You dropped it in your room at the hospital.
I asked around, but no one knew what it was.
I figured it was probably yours.
Thank you, Wakaouji-sensei.
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
I'm counting on you!
So am I, Mitsuki-chan.
No... Full Moon.
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Okay!
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
That place you had to leave for a while...
Sukoshi hanareta basho
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
What are you fretting over, Meroko?
It's great that we asked Wakaouji-sensei to be the producer for her new song, but...
...he won't let her sing at all!
And then, he asks Mitsuki questions like "What do you want to tell people through your song?"
At this rate, we'll never get it recorded.
It's fine.
She'll definitely find an answer!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
What I Want to Say...
Look forward to it!