Tooru!
Want some ice cream?
Huh?
She's not here.
Run-chan...
What are you doing there?
I fell off in my sleep.
I can't move.
Help me.
Coochie-coochie-coo!
Sto- Stop it-
What are you doing?
Saved
I just felt the urge to.
And one more!
Stop it...
Nice shot!
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
ふわふわ　浮遊して
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
きらめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
一つになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
私の行方は彼方
Let's go together.
issho ni ikou
一緒に行こう
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
セカイのSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　集まるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
おはようと　さよならの　間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
私たちだけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
生まれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ち合わせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振る君へと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
取って置きの今日を渡そう
and we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
おしゃべりが始まる
Here you go, Tooru.
Let's dig in!
Delicious!
Tooru, your bangs have gotten longer.
It's because I've left them alone since summer vacation started.
I'll cut them for you!
Huh?
Scissors!
With those scissors?
Yep. Stay still.
Wait!
You're going to hold the scissors horizontally and cut?
Hm?
Um... you look rejuvenated!
A ransel backpack would look good on you!
Not even middle schoolers wear those...
I'm done for. I can't go to school like this.
It's summer vacation right now.
There's the mid-vacation school day.
Don't worry, it looks cute!
That's the problem.
In that case...
Bring this up here, and...
There we go!
We match!
We match...
A Midsummer Night's...
Coming!
Good morning.
Good morning, Tooru-chan!
I'm sorry, I'm afraid Run's still asleep.
Could you wake her up for me?
Certainly. I'm coming in, then.
Run-chan.
We have school today.
Run-chan!
We're going to school!
You're wearing long sleeves again, even though it's summer.
I keep telling you,
you'd look cuter in lighter clothes.
Run-chan!
Go on.
Take it off...
Fine! I'll take it off!
I'll take it off! I'll take it off!
Take it off...
So hot...
It's making my head all fuzzy...
Run-chan! School isn't that way.
Watch
out for
molesters!
It sure is creepy.
All the perverts and molesters come out during the summer, don't they?
I heard some of them call out at you from their cars.
It makes my spine tingle.
We'd better be careful.
Hey, want to get out of the heat and ride to school with me?
A molester!
Somebody! There's a pervert here!
No way...
A pervert?
Should we report him to the police?
This is a misunderstanding!
I'm a teacher at their school!
Please don't report me!
Okay then.
I'm handing out some forms, so pass them back.
Just fill out that survey by the start of next semester.
Okay.
Everyone, listen up!
Please check your planned course of action in the future.
・Higher education (college/junior college vocational school)
・Employment
・Other ( )
Those pursuing higher education, please write your first choice school
This is a survey about your future plans.
Please think it over carefully before next semester.
Don't write something silly
just because you're still first-years.
If you slack off, it'll be exam time before you know it.
Mid-break review
Summer break assignments
New semester: Sept. 1
Even during the rest of your vacation,
don't lose focus, and study hard.
Dismissed!
See you next semester!
Kitou-sensei.
Tooru-san.
Sensei, you look pale today. Are you okay?
Oh my.
What a kind girl.
She's my student, all right.
You're right.
I've had a slight headache since this morning.
There's medicine in the nurse's office.
I can beat this headache with enthusiasm!
Oh?
Dear me, what's this, Kitou-sensei?
Wearing a white coat again, I see.
That's my territory you're invading.
It's none of your business!
Besides, I've been wearing this since before you came here!
Still,
when you think of a white coat, you think of the nurse, don't you?
Speak for yourself, Satou-sensei!
Please do something about that ridiculous patterned shirt of yours!
Eh?
Are you saying I have bad taste?
I don't think you're in a position to talk.
Well then, let's have Tooru-san decide!
Fine by me.
Oh my. Tooru-san?
Uni-chan?
Tooru-san?
Kitou-sensei.
Did you step on Uni-chan?
What?!
I'll bet it was you!
No, I'm sure it was you.
No, it was you!
I'm not that tiny.
No...
That's...
Could it be... an SOS signal?
The first-years' classroom?!
Just hang in there!
This way you don't have to go downstairs
to shake off the chalk dust.
How did the chalkboard rag get so dirty?
Right?
"Right?" isn't an answer.
Where's the fire?
Um, senpai.
What's wrong?
This atmosphere...
I must have jumped to the wrong conclusion.
Um, you see...
I'm...
I'm here to clean!
I want to die.
I'm so sorry, senpai.
If it weren't for her stupid ideas...
N-No, it's fine.
I mistake situations all the time.
I've got another funny story to tell now.
Right, Tooru?
If only I'd stopped Yutaka earlier,
you wouldn't have embarrassed yourself like this, Yuuko.
I'm sorry.
Stop it! Please, don't apologize!
It's even more embarrassing when you apologize to me!
I'm sorry.
Stop it!
Easily flustered, isn't she?
Watch it.
It really looked like a distress signal.
When I saw it, all I could think of was "fire"!
If it was a fire, there would be smoke.
You lose your head too easily.
Be more calm next time.
Here, Nagi-chan!
Hoooot!
F-Fire!
... is the sort of panicked reaction you shouldn't have.
Wait, Run!
It's summer! What's with the hot drink?
I was in a rush, so I messed up!
So hot!
So basically, people shouldn't panic.
I couldn't help it!
If it was a real fire, we'd be in trouble.
Same for me!
Hot coffee in the summer is unreasonable!
Exactly!
They should take the "hot" off vending machines in the summer!
Yeah.
No, I don't think that's the problem.
Huh?
shirt: Hot-Blooded
Confident
in her
taste...
probably?
Oh no!
What do I do?
I left the survey sheet at school.
That's right!
Yuuko, huh?
"I left the survey sheet at school.
I want to go get it, but I'm scared to go alone.
Come with me."
Gosh, that's why I said you shouldn't panic...
There we go.
"Just leave it until next semester"...
I can't do that!
"I want to think it over carefully before filling it in.
I'm begging you, come with me."
Ah, geez.
Message received
Nagi
Really?
To school, at night?
New text
received
Yuuko
Re: Really?
Please!!!!
I'm too scared to
go alone!!
Yuuko
Re: Really?
Please!!!!
I'm too scared to
go alone!!
"I'm too scared," huh?
Oh no!
I'm late!
I'll bet Nagi's there already.
There she is.
Hey!
Huh?
Why's everyone here?
I called the other two.
Is the front gate not open?
We came in from the back gate.
The back gate's pretty far.
Yuuko, you'd better sprint here at full speed!
Yeah, yeah!
Here we go!
Ready, start!
You sound impatient.
Listen up!
No matter what, don't look back!
What's that supposed to mean?
Noooo!
That's your personal record.
Well, let's go pick up what you forgot.
Wait.
I can't move yet.
Ah. She died.
Looks like it's not open.
Is the faculty entrance closed, too?
I guess this won't cut it.
What were you trying to open that with?
Curses.
The school really is scary at night.
Well, you know, sometimes you find a window open.
Pretty careless of them, but it saved us.
That's for sure.
Yuuko, stop clinging to me!
But...
If I don't hold on to someone, I get nervous.
Fine, fine.
I'll go to the science room and get an anatomical model for you.
No, stop it!
Then get off me!
That's even worse!
Huh?!
That looks like fun.
I'm begging you! Don't leave me!
I dunno about that.
Gosh, Yuuko, you really are a scaredy-cat.
But the school feels different at night! It's creepy!
Oh.
What?
Hey,
seeing as we're at school at night...
Let's go exploring!
Huh?!
All right!
And off we go!
We'll be departing from the classroom now.
W-Wait!
Everyone, do you have all your belongings?
A piano rings out in the middle of the night.
Tra-li-lo-li-la-la, the enigmatic seven mysteries.
Say hi to the skeleton dancing by the window.
Come on, escort me carefully now!
Now, let's go, it'll be fun, just don't look back.
Well, it's all right, just keep moving and there's nothing to fear.
David, and the Mona Lisa too, let's all explore together!
Being at school at night really makes your heart race!
Yeah.
I'm scared.
Um...
What is it?
Bathroom.
Hey!
Huh?
We're stopping by the bathroom!
'Kay! We'll wait!
I'm not going into the stall with you, though.
I get it, I get it.
Let's see... lights...
Make it quick.
Got it.
What, what?
Well... over there.
Something came out!
Something came out something came out something came out!
Your constipation was relieved?
That's not what I meant!
Th-There's a hitodama outside the gym building over there!
Hitodama? That's when someone's soul turns into a spirit right after they die, right?
Well then, if we return it right away, maybe we can save him!
What are you saying?
Shh!
This hitodama has feet!
Don't move!
I wanna see it!
Footsteps...
It'll see you!
No it won't!
A burglar?
Huh?
Uni-chan?
Oh, it was just Satou-sensei.
How anticlimactic.
What are you doing here so late?
We're here to clean.
No, we aren't!
I see.
So you're here to get something you forgot.
Yep. That's the story.
Sensei, that candle...
Ah, I'm fond of candles.
This frail, flickering flame
reminds me of my life.
You could call it empathy.
He collapsed.
Right on cue.
He's not responding.
What? He seriously blacked out?
Must be a seizure!
Oh no!
First thing's first, we gotta get him to the nurse's office!
Not while he's face-down!
You're chafing his face!
Huh?
Damn, he's too heavy.
Can I even carry him?
A-hah!
That's right!
We'll just bring the bed here, instead!
And what's your plan after that?
Us two will carry this end,
so you take the feet.
Tooru, you spot us.
Got it?
Yeah.
Got it.
Let's go.
Ready, and...!
So heavy...
Up we go...
Huh?
He got lighter.
Run!
You left the main body behind!
Huh?
Nurse's Office
Heave-ho!
I'm exhausted.
He's not waking up.
Cut that out.
Sensei, pull yourself together!
If you keep hitting him like that...
Serves him right.
Did he come to?
Sensei!
Please pull yourself together!
Can you hear me?
What's this?
Run-chan.
Satou-sensei!
I don't want you to die!
Run-chan!
I'm not going to die!
Run-chan...
Grr.
Is he all right?
He did say he wasn't going to die.
Let's go home.
Good idea.
There aren't any more dogs, right?
Of course not!
Ah, man, I'm really exhausted.
Well, good night!
Good night!
A downtown train will shortly be arriving.
For your safety, please stand back from the white line.
Yuuko-chan!
See you later!
Yeah!
I'm glad everyone came today.
Oh.
I forgot it again!
The hats hanging from the tall rack
akane ni narabu
あかねに並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kakeboushi
背高かけ帽子
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
楽しい一日の終わり
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　おしゃべり
Our chatter goes on and on,
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigatou
いつもありがとう
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれてよかったな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
るるるん
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風と　心ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
次の角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
We ended up making the trip for nothing.
And I got the scare of my life.
I can't get to sleep at all.
At my age,
I can't exactly ask my family to sleep together.
That's right!
It's been a while since we slept together, hasn't it?
Good night.
Next time
Miporin, what do you look forward to at summer festivals?
Well, if I had to say, it's gotta be the fireworks.
Ahh...
Also, the octopus balls, savory pancakes, oh, and I love the ginger malt drink.
Ooh, that sounds nice!
Yutaka, what do you like?
Well, all things considered, Yutaka likes to eat a lot-
Hold on just a second!
Next time on A-Channel!
"Summer Festival"!
... to eat a loooot of oden at the night stalls!
Oden, in the summer?
See you next week!