What's the matter?
Fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
Kirameku tooku no sora to hitotsu ni naru
Kazeyomi kimama na watashi no yukue wa kanata
Issho ni ikou
Shinkokyuu hazundeku, sekai no spring breath
Taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
Ohayou to sayounara no aida wa watashitachi dake
Nandemo dekiru ne
Sukitooru hizashi, umaretate no sora
Machiawaseta yakusoku no morning arch
Te o furu kimi e to totte oki no kyou o watasou
Oshaberi ga hajimaru
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
CARBONATION
Run!
What?
About our conversation yesterday...
Yeah?
Run! You dropped your notebook.
It looks like the latest issue is out already.
Akira Katsura
Haruna Togawa
Yu Sasaki
Akiba Shingo
Tetsuya Suenaga Kyoko Ueno
Atsuko Higashi Hitomi Kisaragi
Yurika Numata Motoko Kubota
Akemi Nagai
Kazuki Kawashita
Mari Kobayashi
Jun Morikawa
Kyoko Ueno
Klaus A
Yoko Sato
Sonya La
Shino Hisano
Sun-Joo
Motoko Kubota
Engi T
Akemi Nagai
Nagi!
I-I-I'm sorry! I'll erase it from memory,
so please don't kill me!
I'm sorry!
What are you talking about?
This is a notebook where you write the names of
people you hate so they'll be cursed, right?
No! I'm doing a notebook exchange with Toru.
That's her page.
Then what are all these names?
A memory test!
We're competing to see who can remember the
most names of people we've come across so far.
Why would they do that?
She has a great memory, huh?
I may not have a chance.
Also, suddenly all the names are foreign.
Don't tell me Toru used to live overseas!
No, she said those are names
from manga she's read.
Oh. That's why they're so weird.
Justine, Michelle
Francoise
Justine?
Oh. Michelle Richard.
Joule August Guillaume.
Mari Francoise Victoire!
Dauvich Kechenovich.
Count Francoise Polignac.
Michelle von Parnas.
O'Brien Buchkovich.
Alessandro Garickson.
Paul Linares!
Andorius Banderas!
Gladios Andretti!
What?
Salvadore Andrea!
Hisel Poncho!
Yuko.
Velasquez!
What is it?
So, what did Toru say?
That she has something to show us,
so please come by the house.
Huh. What could it be?
This'll be my first time to Toru's house,
so I'm lookin' forward to it.
Me, too.
I wonder what kind of place she lives in...
You'll know, soon.
This is it.
Toru sure lives in a nice place!
Let's go.
Silly Toru. We said we'd help her clean
so she didn't have to leave ahead of us.
Could there be something
she didn't want us to see?
What's wrong?
STEP
This is like a foot massager, and it feels good!
Quit actin' like an old lady and let's go!
STEP
Toru! We're here!
It's open, so come in.
Okay!
Here we come.
Toru. We're coming in.
How dirty!
Is Toru the kind of girl who can't clean?
No. Usually, it's so clean,
it's almost too much. So this...
SPIHC
OTATOP
Potato
Sticks
SPIHC
OTATOP
Potato
Sticks
A room in disarray!
Its occupant missing!
A window locked from the inside!
It's a locked-room murder!
The front door was OPEN.
Huh? This room isn't really dirty.
If you look closely, the trash has been
knocked out of the trash can, that's it.
So the trash came out for a walk, eh?
There's no way it grew arms and legs!
Eek! Humans!
I get it.
Should we go ahead and clean up?
Yeah.
Run-chan, what you're thinking
is probably wrong.
I'm sorry for the mess.
This one tore the room up.
"This one"?
How cute!
What's with this cat?
I found it this morning.
It looks like it was abandoned.
A Oranges
Oh! Cats have limbs too, don't they?
I don't know what that means.
And they're personified, too.
What are you talking about?
If they did, I think they'd be Toru!
That...
I think I can see that.
Right?!
What does that mean?
See you.
See you tomorrow!
Take care of that cat, okay?
Later.
It's gotten cold, huh? Toru, you okay?
Yeah.
Oh! Wanna eat something on the way back?
Yeah. Something sweet would be good.
How about a restaurant?
Let's go by the shopping arcade.
The shopping arcade, huh?
Can we take a bit of a detour?
I thought it was around here...
Where are we going?
I want to buy a collar.
Oh, I see.
I'd like to get some cat toys while I'm at it.
Toys?
THAT I know!
TOYS
This place is sure to have them!
ADULT TOYS
I'm sure you're right.
But you're wrong!
Welcome.
It's a white cat, so what color
would suit it? Red? Blue?
She's so serious...
You think that cat's really important, don't you?
I think YOU'RE important, too.
I know.
That tickles...
Welcome to Goonies!
My apologies for the wait.
Please have a seat here.
Toru, you take the booth side.
No, Run-chan, you.
We should just sit together, right?
SPOUT
Oh, that's right. About my cat...
The drink bar makes it hard to choose, huh?
How many kinds are you putting in there?
It's a delicious mixed juice of FIVE varieties!
You hadn't thought of a name for the cat yet?
I can't come up with a good one.
What about the name of a snack or a drink?
You like those, right?
Oh, that's good.
This has cola, cider, ramune,
ginger ale and melon soda in it.
Put them together and you get Carbonation!
We're home!
You been doing well? Starting today,
your name is Carbonation!
Well-behaved, isn't it?
Sometimes it runs wild, though.
Carbonation, your collar suits you.
So cute, so cute!
You want food? I'll give you some right now.
We got some toys for you too,
so let's play with them later, okay?
Run-chan, let's talk.
I never got Run's attention back...
Good morning, Carbonation.
Tickle-tickle. Tickle. Tickle-tickle-tickle-tickle.
Tickle-tickle. Tickle.
It's this late already? I have to get changed.
No, you'll get fur on my uniform.
This is no time for rolling around.
Starting this morning, today is going
to be an extremely cold one.
There is a high probability of snowfall in the afternoon,
so please take care when leaving the house.
It can't be helped...
Okay, I'll be back.
Good morning, Toru.
It's going to get colder today, huh?
It's supposed to snow, Run-chan.
The forecast said so.
Hold on a minute!
What's the matter?
Ta-daa!
STRAWBERRY
SHAVED ICE
I got some syrup!
For the snow?
Yup!
Yuko-chan, good morning.
'Morning. It's cold right off the bat today, huh?
Yeah.
Good morning.
Good mor-
Nagi! What's with that getup?!
The forecast said snow, so I planned ahead.
You look like an assassin. So cool!
Won't you be mistaken for a pervert?
Jeez. Why do we have to come to school
when it's this cold?
Of course we do. We're students.
Don't you think that once fall is over,
we should be off till spring?!
You hate winter, don't you?
In the summer, you just kept saying,
"It's hot, it's hot."
At this rate, if snow falls,
I'm not sure I'll be able to live!
Why're you so glum?
Snow is nothing but fun!
Huh?
You can make snowmen and make igloos
and have snowball fights!
So Nagi, you need to pray that snow falls, too!
Did you not listen to what I said?!
Huh?
One
Hour
Later
Math A
Two
Hours
Later
Biology
I
Three
Hours
Later
Selected Narratives
and Biographies
Four
Hours
Later
Math II
It won't snow... It definitely won't!
You haven't given up yet, have you?
I've halfway given up.
Give up ALL the way!
Ah! It started snowing!
What?!
Awesome!
Wow!
Sure enough. Snow.
Bleh. This weather changes on a dime, huh?
Run, good th-
She's gone.
It's here! Food, food!
Eat your LUNCH, not the snow!
Looks like it's gonna start piling up.
It's really coming down!
If a lot piles up, I'd like to try this:
And get buried so deep, I can't see the bottom!
Like something from a manga, huh?
Maybe I can do it if I jump here.
Uh, I don't think...
Fine, then from the roof!
I think it's no good.
It piled up! Great, isn't it?
Okay, let's go!
Yeah.
Yaay!
R-Run-chan? You dead?
She's eating it!
Run-chan, no!
You all jump in, too!
Hey, don't do that.
What?
Yuko-chan, that's a strange pose.
Good job, Yuko.
Jeez!
Snow...
Snow is warm, isn't it?
Nagi!
Nagi, you okay?
She looks cold.
That's it!
I'll warm Nagi-chan up!
What are you doing, Run-chan?
I thought I'd make an igloo for Nagi-chan!
Ah! That IS warm, isn't it? I'll help!
Okay! Nagi-chan, it's done!
Looks cramped...
Nagi, is it warm?
Yeah. More than outside.
I'm glad.
You're wide open, Yuko-chan.
Hyaa!
Here I come! Hyaa!
Now you've done it!
Tenki yohou, yuki no mark de watashi no kokoro odoru
My heart dances at the snow mark on the weather forecast
Samusa nante kankei nai no yo
Cold has nothing to do with it
Hora, inotte
Come on, pray
Miageta sora ni
To the sky we've looked up at
Yuki fureba Lucky, kimagure ni Snow man
If snow falls we'll be lucky, a snowman on a whim
Ashiato tsukete
Leaving footprints
Omoikiri Diving katadotte
Suddenly imitating diving
I Wish I Wish Snow Day, Happy Happy Snow Day
Motto motto furitsumore
Fall and pile up, more and more
Lucky Lucky Snow Day
Zutto zutto furitsuzuke
Always, always keep falling
Happy Happy Snow
Motto furitsumore
Fall and pile up, more
Happy Happy Snow Day
I played outside that much but surprisingly,
I haven't caught a cold...
I caught a cold
- Yuko-
"I caught a cold. Yuko."
I caught a cold
- Yuko-
Why did YOU catch one?
Have a fever of 38 deg. Celsius
- Toru-
"Have a fever of 38 deg. Celsius. Toru."
"Looks like I caught a cold. Run."
I think I caught a cold, too.
Sending Text
Akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
Tanoshii ichinichi no owari
Tsukinai oshaberi mada mada aru keredo
Sorosoro o-uchi ni kaeranakucha
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Mail suru kara
Kyou no page ni minna osoroi no egao
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Itsumo arigato
Kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
Ru-ru-run, kaze to kokoro humming suru
Tsugi no kado de furimukinagara bye-bye
Come on.
So warm...
I-It's cold.
Okay, everyone! Let's give this
snow-shoveling our all!
Ma'am...
yup!
The time to say goodbye to
everyone is drawing near, huh?
What, already?! Isn't it a bit soon?
Speaking of, it's already winter?
Fast, isn't it? By the way,
what did you do last winter?
Well, I had to prepare for
high school entrance exams...
Oh, yeah. We studied for them
together, didn't we?
Rather than "study,"
I, Yutaka ended up teaching you...
Don't lie.
Next time, on A-Channel: "Birthdays"
Next
Episode!
BIRTHDAYS
Next time, on A-Channel: "Birthdays"
Next
Episode!
BIRTHDAYS
Everyone! Good luck with your entrance exams!
Just what month do you think it is?