The person you have called cannot come to the phone now.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Uh, Kushieda!
About tonight's Christmas Eve party...
Ryuji! You there?
I'll call you back later, but you have to come to the party!
Hey, open the window!
Ryuji!
It'll definitely be fun!
Too slow!
What are you doing?
What are YOU do—
Take this!
What the heck are you doing?
Throwing things at people...
Nevermind that, open it right now.
You'll understand when you open it.
I'm going to get ready too. I'll be over there in thirty minutes.
Bye.
Hey!
What, what, what's going on de-yansu?
Coming!
It looks great!
You look really cute, Taiga-chan!
Ryu-chan, come and see de-gansu.
Ryu-shi, you look good de-yansu.
I'm glad.
It fits perfectly.
Are you really sure it's okay?
B-Borrowing something like this?
I'm not lending it.
I'm giving it to you.
Giving it?!
It has R. Aisaka stitched inside!
It's your old man's, right?
It didn't fit so he never wore it.
It's okay, just take it.
Who wants a hand-me down from that guy?
If you're not going to wear it, I guess I'll just have to throw it away...
Little tasks like that really suit you.
You're the one who told me to do it.
Wait!
G-Good line.
How come you can say that but not your own name?
Alright!
Magical Girl Yacchan is going to cast some magic on you two.
Magic?
Don't touch it too much.
By the time the party starts, it should mix with your natural smell and create a faint scent.
And for Ryu-chan...
There you go.
Could this be my dad's?
It's not de-yansu.
A long time ago, when Yasuko ran away from home, she took everything of value.
You mean, this is Grandfather's?
That's right de-gansu.
Sto- Sto-
Stolen goods.
Hey, you're going to catch a cold.
That's a huge crowd.
How many people are here?
However many people there are, there's only one important thing.
You got it?
Tonight, you have something you need to do.
Wow!
Yuri-chan-sensei is all dressed up!
You said you wouldn't come to the party because you have a date.
It's not a date.
I'm going to a class on buying real estate for single women.
Real estate?
That's right.
Because I'm going to buy a condo.
But why today, of all days?
That's because the kind of women who have a date on Christmas Eve haven't really made up their mind yet.
That means if her ideal property comes up, she won't be prepared to intercept and grab it.
I'm a little concerned about tax breaks for home buyers, so I'll be going now.
Everyone, please stay out of trouble.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm glad the tree got fixed.
And your grades went up.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you, Sensei.
I'm sure all your hard work will pay off.
Yes!
I'm sure you will find a wonderful piece of property.
A fantastic single's life is waiting for you.
Yeah, thanks.
Everyone!
Thank you very much for participating in this event planned by the God of Unrequited Love.
We had a lot of trouble, but that's all behind us.
Hey, Kitamura's costume is...
It's going to be a great party.
Don't say it.
You'll be playing into his trap.
Thank you all for your help and cooperation!
I hope you all enjoy yourselves tonight!
And now...
Are you ready?
In the name of this year's Christmas Eve...
Merry Christmas!
Drumsticks!
I know this one.
This is called turkey, right?
No, it's chicken.
So she says.
Yummy.
It's definitely chicken turkey.
Yeah, you're right.
Nanoko, there's cake over there.
Really? Where, where?
Over there. Let's go.
Let's!
Kihara in short shorts and Nanoko-san in a grown-up dress, sexy.
Why is everyone all dressed up?
I'm so underdressed.
I look like a bum.
Hey, you!
Look where you're going!
If you spill the syrup, it'll make the floor sticky.
I-I'm sorry.
Scary.
Takasu.
Just when I thought you weren't here...
What are you doing?
The person doing it was just so bad, I suddenly...
Didn't know you had such a nice suit!
Wish I had one.
Hey, your fingers are covered with chicken grease!
Huh, you don't know?
This is called turkey!
It's chicken turkey.
Kaoru, you're late.
Sorry.
What, what?
Nothing.
That reminds me...
I haven't seen Ami-chan yet!
She's here, right?
Probably.
I think I saw her.
Really? Was she sexy?
What what she wearing?
But she's not here now, right?
Neither is Taiga.
Taiga?
Taiga's not bad either, but right now it's Ami-chan...
He's right.
Where'd she go?
saa christmas ippai no egao
Now that it's Christmas, a lot of smiles
kimi ni todoketa party night
will be delivered to you on this party night.
saa christmas ippai no negai
Now that it's Christmas, a lot of wishes
kimi ni chikaunda holy holy night
will I vow to you on this holy, holy night.
Ami-chan and... Taiga?
Wow!
kotoshi no CHRISTMAS chotto tokubetsu sa
This year's Christmas must be special.
ogai to CHRISTMAS janakutatte
Even if it's not a Christmas with you.
hoshikuzu no ILLUMINATION
The stardust will illuminate it,
When did they practice?
hora furitsumoru yo
Look, it's piling up
kirakira kagayaite
Shining brightly,
minna ga shiawase de
giving everyone happiness.
chika chika matataite minna ga yume wo mite
Blink, blink, close your eyes and dream...
saa christmas ippai no egao
Now that it's Christmas, a lot of smiles
kimi ni todoketa party night
will be delivered to you on this party night.
saa christmas ippai no negai
Now that it's Christmas, a lot of wishes
kimi ni chikaunda holy holy night
will I vow to you on this holy, holy night.
Uh, Kushieda!
About tonight's Christmas Eve party...
Ryuji! You there?
Hey, open the window!
I'll call you back later, but you have to come to the party!
Ryuji!
It'll definitely be fun.
Hey, Ryuji!
Bye!
That was great!
Ami-chan and Taiga were sexy-cute!
Here.
Thanks.
Takasu!
How long are you going to keep doing that?
I may have just seen my dream come true!
Isn't this completely different from the dream you saw?
What about the part where they were sexy-cute and wearing costumes?
In that case...
Am I sexy-cute too!?
Hey!
Dammit, you perverted bastard...
Hey, Maruo! What do you think you're doing?
Hey, Kihara!
Am I sexy-cute?
Isn't that sexual harassment?
Payback!
Fruit punch, please.
Y-Yes!
Kawashima.
So this is where you were.
Somehow I ended up here.
Hey, hey, how'd you like the song?
It was really great!
When did you practice?
If I didn't keep quiet, it wouldn't have been a surprise.
Surprised?
Yeah, you had me completely fooled.
Yeah?
I'm glad.
Where's Taiga?
She worked hard too, I was thinking I'd deliver her some fruit punch.
Taiga went home.
You didn't know?
N-No...
Really?
You didn't notice?
She said she was going to stop by Minori-chan's house.
She said she was going to make Minori come here, and then go home.
She even said she was going to get ready to meet Santa.
Why does it have to be like that?
Why'd she go home?
Dunno.
Maybe there's something she doesn't want to see.
That's why I warned you.
Warned?
"You should stop playing house."
"Why are you playing papa?"
Whatever.
Kawashima!
What's with him?
He doesn't listen to anything I say.
For everyone's happiness and a happy Christmas, Angel Taiga-sama is ready to do anything.
Is that okay?
Really?
By being a good girl...
I want to become part of that happy scene.
Be one of the happy faces in a Christmas town.
Takasu!
Can you give me some fruit punch?
I burned up too many calories.
Kitamura!
I'm leaving for a bit.
Hey, Takasu!
There's no way it's okay!
Is that true?
Is that really true?
That's right!
Ryuji is waiting for you to come.
He said he's not going to leave until you come.
Even if he has to stay overnight at school.
I'm sorry, Minorin.
But, you don't hate it, right?
I can tell, since I'm your best friend.
If I weren't...
Santa-san still hasn't come.
Being a good girl just for Christmas was pointless.
After all, Santa doesn't really exist.
That's why this year, I'm alone.
Next year...
I'll be alone.
Always, always...
Not relying on anyone.
Alone.
Not relying on anyone?
What's going on?
It's coming from the bedroom.
Santa-san?
H-Hold on!
Heavy!
Are you really Santa-san?
What's with that costume?
Hey!
Come here, come here.
Look!
Santa-san!
That's our tree this year!
Right, right?
Yay!
I knew it was absolutely great!
Wow, wow!
Santa-san liked my tree!
This is reality, right?
Wow.
My dream...
...became reality.
Thank you.
Truly...
Thank you, Ryuji.
Hey, don't take that off! Dummy!
Give it back!
And? Where did you find this?
I borrowed it from the guy who was wearing it.
What happened to your suit?
I traded it with the guy who was wearing this.
I'll get it back from him later, of course.
Naturally.
Taking it off now when you need it most....
You idiot.
Stupid idiot!
After I went and prepared everything for you.
Just so that you can meet Minorin.
What do you mean by idiot?
I told you to believe in Angel Taiga-sama!
Minorin should be heading to the party.
She should be arriving around this time.
Hey, you can still make it, so hurry up and go back.
But...
Tonight, I'm stuck in this.
I don't want to leave you alone.
What are you saying?
I'm fine now!
It was really fun playing Santa and the good girl.
Of course, I'm looking forward to tomorrow too.
In case it goes well with Minorin, tomorrow's Christmas is going to be a feast at Takasu's house.
Chicken bowl!
Beef bowl!
Because of Inko-chan, let's not do chicken.
Then, just beef bowl!
Hey, go on. Hurry up.
But!
If you don't go, that means I lied to Minorin!
Go on, go on!
Hey, I said wait!
Santa's already come, so I've got to be a good girl until the end of the year.
Let me be that good girl.
Making Minorin go to the party is my real present to you.
So, please...
Take it.
But...
Go on, you mangy dog.
Thanks!
He finally left, finally.
I forgot to give it back to him.
What a pain.
Huh?
Why?
Oh, I see.
I was relying on Ryuji.
On his kindness.
But that's over.
Minorin is definitely drawn to Ryuji.
Ryuji really likes Minorin.
That means...
They both like each other.
And then...
I can't be next to Ryuji anymore.
I won't be able to walk alongside Ryuji.
The one next to Ryuji...
Isn't me...
I don't...
Want that...
Ryuji...
Ryuji!
I really did it this time.
I don't have my cell phone.
I forgot the present in my suit pocket.
What am I going to do?
That's a nice bear costume.
Hey.
Kushie-
Takasu-kun.
I'm sorry, just let me say this first.
Do you remember?
During summer vacation at Ami's summer house, we talked one night.
We talked about some weird things, something about UFO's and ghosts.
Uh, yeah.
Takasu-kun...
I've decided that I don't really need to see UFOs or ghosts after all.
It seems like it'd be better if I can't.
I've been thinking a lot lately, and that's the conclusion I came to.
I wanted to tell you that.
That's why I came.
Kushieda.
Sorry for just saying everything that I wanted.
Kushieda is going home now.
Seriously?
You mean, this is... What do you call it?
A broken heart?
Kushieda rejected me, just closing my eyes like this...
Takasu-kun!
Dream!
I keep hearing her cheerful voice.
Yes, there!