Without the first issue,
we're not getting anywhere.
Yes, you're right.
It wouldn't hurt to bring
Satoshi and Ibara in on this.
No, um, I mean...
Well, even supposing we
never solve this mystery,
someday, your own statute
of limitations might expire.
Statute of limitations?
All right.
I will ask Fukube-san and
Mayaka-san, as well.
I am curious...
about what happened
to my uncle, 45 years ago.
Everyone, I'm asking for your help.
Your uncle, huh?
That really happened?
The untold story of a heroic tale,
uncovered by someone 45 years later.
We were just checking out
some things from that time period.
You're right. This picture
is intriguing, too.
If there's some reason for it,
I'd like to know, too.
This is kind of getting exciting, huh?
If things work out right, this could
be material for our anthology.
We can investigate all we want,
and call it a Classic Lit Club activity.
And so, looking into
the Classic Lit Club's past
had become the top priority
for all of its members.
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
The Classic Lit Club's
Glorious Days of Yore
Sorry! Been waiting long?!
What's with you, Hotaro?
Pipe down! Have you no sense of shame?!
So, got all your material ready?
What about you, Hotaro?
Find anything good?
Yeah, I guess.
Then we can look forward
to your hypothesis, too, right?
Aw, crap. Were we supposed to do that, too?
All right, let's get going.
Being such wealthy farmers,
the Chitanda family mansion
ranks in the top class of all of Kamiyama.
You're sure enjoying yourself, huh?
That's because I love cycling.
Slicing through the wind under
the power of your own legs like this is...
Not that, I mean your
entire high school life.
Ah, the whole "rosy" business, huh?
My basic attitude is to be rosy,
no matter what's going on around me.
More like shocking pink, don't you mean?
That's great! If we're going with that,
then you'd be gray, right?
That's what you said before, too.
I did? Still, I'm not trying to
diminish you by saying that, Hotaro.
Hmph.
My basic attitude is
shocking pink, after all.
And it won't work if someone
tries to color me rosy.
I won't accept the color.
Aren't you already unusually tinged?
No, I'm not.
What's wrong, Hotaro? Do you say that because
I'm busy with the executive committee,
Handicrafts Club, and Classic Lit Club?
Well, am I wrong?
Yes, you are. Whatever I choose
to do, I still am who I am.
That doesn't mean I'm "tinged."
When I'm trying to diminish you,
I'll say you have no color.
Hmm.
I'm not looking to endear myself to you.
No doubt about that!
By the way, Hotaro, how did you
do on your midterm tests?
Average marks on all of them.
That's our gray Hotaro for you.
Hmph.
It's coming into view now.
That's the Chitanda estate.
What do you think?
Something else, isn't it?
Let's go. Chitanda and Ibara are waiting.
Yeah, okay. Hotaro!
Seems like a servant might
greet us, doesn't it?
Welcome! I've been expecting you.
Yeah.
Pardon the intrusion.
Come on in. This way.
Please sit anywhere you like.
You sure took your time.
We aren't late.
Hmph.
It's rare to see a man so unsuited
to sit at the head of the table.
Okay, shall we get this
review meeting started?
Yes!
Mm-hm.
Yeah.
Today, I would like to consider
the incident that happened
in the Classic Lit Club 45 years ago.
If we do get to the bottom of anything,
I would like to include it
in this year's anthology.
First, we'll share and report on our data,
then we'll all ask our questions,
then comes the presenter's hypothesis,
and finally, discussion of that hypothesis,
and that's how we'll proceed.
Ho, she's quite the
accomplished meeting leader.
Okay, for the first report... Huh?
Um, who should we have go first?
Then again...
It doesn't matter, does it?
Chitanda, you go first.
Okay then, I'll start,
and we'll proceed clockwise.
The subject of my research
was Hyouka itself.
The only thing that touched on
what happened 45 years ago
was this foreword. I compiled
the facts that I gathered from it,
and listed them on the second page.
First, Item 1.
1. 'Senpai' has departed (from where?)
"Senpai" refers to my uncle, Sekitani Jun.
My uncle dropped out of
Kamiyama High School,
and his academic career ends
as a middle-school graduate.
2. 'Senpai' was a hero 45 years ago,
and a legend 44 year ago
Next is Item 2, but I think that
it shows that as time passes,
the story becomes more exaggerated.
Items 3 and 5 are connected.
3. 'Senpai' was a 'quiet warrior' and a 'kind hero.'
5. The conflict
had a casualty (casualty = 'Senpai'?)
The quiet, kind "Senpai,"
after turning warrior, became a hero,
and finally... a sacrifice.
4. 'Senpai' gave Hyouka its name
Item 4 is a curious matter,
but let's leave that aside for now.
That is my presentation.
Are there any questions?
Tell us, why did you exclude where it says
heroic tale
"It was in no way a heroic tale"?
Because that was the
writer's own mental image.
It could mean that the fighting was
down-and-dirty, not something awe-inspiring.
I suppose.
Okay, I'll present my hypothesis.
What
It's conceivable that my uncle
was contending against something,
and as a result, he left the school.
There's one other factor,
besides the other five that
I gave, that I thought of.
This part here about it
having been "a year since."
That means that it was around the time
of the Kanyasai that my uncle left.
If I may digress a little, I heard
from a friend at another high school
that there was an incident
at the culture festival last year.
A culture festival shakedown, huh?
The sellers getting extorted, and their
proceeds disappearing, or something?
I think that there are
so-called punks in any age.
What if the Kanyasai that year was
unlucky enough to be
targeted by such folks,
and so my uncle fought back
against them violently,
which is what made him a hero?
I think the underclassmen who hated to see my
uncle have to leave school to answer for doing so
wrote this piece as a result.
Hmm...
Rejected.
Yeah, rejected.
No good? Please tell me why.
Chitanda, when you first
brought up the anthology,
do you remember what
I said to counter the idea?
Let's see...
A refreshment stand, right?
That's right. But you said that refreshment
stands were traditionally prohibited.
Nobody would come rip off a Kanyasai
where no money changes hands.
I think that some might come to it,
even if money wasn't involved.
You're pathetic, Hotaro.
Oh? Then let's all hear
what you think about it.
Punks hassling the culture festival
45 years ago would,
marvel of marvels, never have
happened in the first place.
Why not?
When you think of the 1960s,
doesn't it bring to mind something?
Mmm...
Tokyo? The Diet Building?
Placards? Demonstrations?
Satoshi, what are you getting at?
Student activism.
Remember, the sort of campus violence
that Chitanda-san speaks of
was yet to be seen during the 1960s.
It was an era when we weren't
fighting teachers or schools;
instead it was the state, and the system.
Don't say it like you were there to see it.
Like I said, I checked
this time period out.
It's true, I overlooked any
sense of the era it was in.
Chi-chan, I'm sorry!
What's come over you all of a sudden?
The material I have doesn't
fit in with your explanation.
It's my turn next, so I wasn't
sure how much I should say here.
Damn it, Ibara! Why didn't you
stop me from wasting my breath?
All right, we'll withdraw
my theory for the time being,
so Mayaka-san, please tell us
what your explanation is.
Is that all right with everyone?
Yeah.
Yes!
Ah, my legs are falling asleep.
I have to say, this mansion is huge.
Do you have a pond out
in your gardens, too?
Yes, we do.
Really?! I'd sure like to see that!
Oh, I want to see it, too!
Okay, why don't we continue
in a different location?
It is very comfortable out on the veranda.
A pond, huh?
Boushu ('The Seeding')
The time to sow bearded grains
Hyouka
This is a copy of the book
Solidarity and Salutes, Issue 1,
which I found in the library.
I couldn't find issues 2 and higher.
It was published 45 years
ago, just like Chi-chan's.
Solidarity and Salutes, Issue 1
"Our valiant activism," is it?
Sounds so old-fashioned.
Okay, I'll start, then.
We
First, "we" refers to the students,
while "reactionary forces" and "authoritarians"
Reactionary forces
Authoritarians
refer to the teachers.
June
There was a conflict
during June of the previous year,
and its leader was Sekitani Jun,
president of the Classic Lit Club.
They engaged in what they called activism,
Activism
sticking it to the teachers.
Oh, the reading of this word
means "conflict," does it?
This Solidarity and Salutes
seems a little hinky somehow.
Hinky?
It's not that I'm questioning this account.
I was just thinking that someone
who was caught up in college
or other illustrious movements wrote this.
So, does that have any bearing?
No, I'm just thinking out loud.
Sorry, Chitanda-san.
All right, are there any other questions?
Well, here's my hypothesis.
First, I reject Chi-chan's theory.
According to Solidarity and Salutes,
the incident happened in June.
As for the "action" that led
to him having to leave school,
violence is what comes to mind, right?
In other words, the people who were led by
Sekitani Jun let the teachers have some of this...
and gave them what for.
I'm not sure if he actually
hit anyone, though.
But something happened to deprive the
students of their autonomy 45 years ago,
and they must have been
rallying against that.
My uncle did?
Hmm...
I kind of understand what
you're getting at, but...
What do you mean?
Mayaka, your theory is that
the students resorted to violence
to resist the oppression
of the teachers, right?
Mm-hm, I guess.
Your theory is too abstract.
And we also can't interpret
anything more from it.
Sure, if you're talking about specifics,
I might not have any,
but are there any inconsistencies?
Yes, there are.
Hyouka
Solidarity and Salutes
If you believe
both Hyouka and Solidarity and Salutes,
the incident occurred in June,
April
October
but he left school in October,
when the culture festival takes place.
If he
was being punished for acts of violence,
Apr. May June July Aug. Sept. Oct.
he would have
been expelled right after the incident, right?
I suppose.
This four-month differential
also has me curious.
It says it had already been
a year since the culture festival,
so I'm thinking he left school in October.
Hmm, you're all so nitpicky.
I think you're heading in
the right direction, though.
So do I.
Well, is it okay if I end my turn now?
Yes. Thank you very much. Okay, next...
Sorry, I guess I'm getting hungry.
Jeez, you ate all those snacks, didn't you?
Yeah, well...
I can make you some onigiri,
if you'd like that.
How about the rest of you?
Chi-chan, anything I can do to help?
No, that's all right.
Really?
Yes.
Handmade!
You sure seem pleased.
Fuku-chan, isn't this...
Mayaka, I'm sorry!
According to my data,
your theory is partially negated.
I forgot to mention it.
Is that right?
Hmm? Is this the Kami High
Monthly Newsletter?
Come to think of it, Togaito did say
they were nearing their 500th issue.
That's right.
What I checked into were
the back-number issues
of the Wall Newspaper Club's
"Kami High Monthly Newsletter."
About the only thing that mentions
any incident 45 years ago was this article.
I put a summary on the second page.
The first one and the last one are the same.
No violence occurred during the incident.
Nonviolent resistance was
maintained during the incident.
There were no incidents
of violence during the incident,
so Mayaka, your theory is off-course.
Also, if the whole school, or all of its students,
The incident affected the whole school.
During the incident, 'we'
were in solidarity.
Whole school = We
are the same as "we,"
it would mean that the incident
involved all of the students;
and if not, it would mean that someone who had won
the support of the all the students was involved.
Thank you for waiting.
Wow!
Thank you, Chi-chan.
Not at all.
There are plum, kelp,
and mustard leaf varieties.
Please, help yourselves.
Thank you for these.
Hmm? What's the matter?
Nothing!
Hmm...
This is good!
Delicious!
Chitanda-san, did your
family grow this rice?
That's right.
Oh, if you have any questions, go ahead.
Are you positive that this
"legendary movement"
is the incident that forced
Sekitani Jun to leave school?
It seems awfully thin
going by just this copy.
Who knows? There's no proof.
Who knows? Then it doesn't
count as data, does it?
Yeah, maybe not, I guess.
But still, there is some indirect evidence.
If the "Sekitani Jun Incident"and the
The Sekitani Jun Incident
The Legendary Movement
are different,
there would be something
that said that of the two,
this one is the legendary movement,
wouldn't there?
Yeah, yeah! That's what I was trying
to say! Leave it to you, Mayaka!
Hmph.
All right, your hypothesis, if you please.
Ah, my hypothesis?
What's the matter?
Chitanda-san, I hate to say it,
but I can't offer a hypothesis.
It's all I can do to correct the
Ibara theory with what little I have.
Besides, databases don't draw conclusions.
I knew he would say that.
Now then...
Thank you.
Not at all.
What do I do?
Okay, Oreki-san, if you would.
Hotaro, this wouldn't happen to be...
"Kamiyama High School's 50-Year Progress"?
I thought there might be something
written in the public record.
Showa 42 (1967)
Although, looking at it again now,
there's nothing worth mentioning.
I have no hypothesis, either.
What should I do?
Something the matter, Hotaro?
Hey, have you forgotten how
you're supposed to proceed?
You start with your summary.
Is this even something
I have to do to begin with?
Hotaro?
Oreki?
Oreki-san?
Enough!
Should I blow this off?
What's the matter?
I forgot I had shiitake
mushrooms drying.
I have to hurry and bring them in!
Can you handle it alone?
Yes, I'll be fine.
Chitanda...
Yes?
Sorry, but can I use your restroom?
Oh, yes. Go out this door,
and then head straight.
Getting nervous, or something?
Straight... Straight...
I'm lost.
She researched it this much?
I guess I can put my brain
to work for a bit.
45 years ago...
An event that happened to Sekitani Jun...
Four different references...
What is it that ties them together?
Think.
Student activism... Acts of violence...
The time interval before expulsion...
45 years ago, Sekitani Jun was...
You were in there quite a while, huh?
Well, excuse me. It was
my turn to present, right?
Forgive me, but I didn't
prepare a hypothesis.
So could we end my turn,
and move right to the wrap-up?
Hotaro, you came up with something, huh?
Yeah, maybe. It should provide
a general explanation.
You've figured something out,
haven't you, Oreki-san?!
Now, now, Chitanda-san, calm down!
Let's hear it, then.
Don't disappoint us, now.
All right. I'll explain this by steps.
First is the "when." 45 years ago.
45 years ago
The time period is the issue.
If we believe both Hyouka
and Solidarity and Salutes,
the incident happened in June,
Incident... June
and the senpai left in October.
Expulsion... October
Next is the "where."
It was at Kamiyama High School.
Kamiyama High School
As for the "who,"
according to Solidarity and Salutes,
the primary figure in the incident was
Classic Lit Club President Sekitani Jun.
Sekitani Jun
From the "Kami High Monthly Newsletter,"
we know that the entire
student body was involved.
Now the "why." The ones that all
the students were rising up against
would have to be the teachers.
To borrow Ibara's words,
the reason why they rose up is that
they were deprived of their autonomy.
Deprived of autonomy
And the cause of the incident...
was the culture festival.
Did it say somewhere that the culture
festival was the cause of the incident?
No, but as I see it,
June
in June, the students
and the teachers discussed it,
October
and they decided that the
culture festival would be held in October.
By "discuss,"
do you mean this "meeting to
consider the culture festival" part?
That's right. Take a close look at it.
There are circle and square
marks at the top of each entry.
I've got it! The squares are
customary events held every year,
while the circles are things
that only happened that year!
I looked at the other years, too,
and that much is unmistakable.
Why was there a meeting that was only held 45
years ago to consider the culture festival?
Probably because of strong
demand from the students.
It hints to that here in Hyouka.
Right here.
"In this last year, he has gone
from being a hero to a legend.
The culture festival will have another
rousing five-day run this year."
I think the point isn't
that it will have a "run,"
five-day
but that it will be a "five-day" run.
How do you mean?
The "five-day" part is the achievement
that the hero, Sekitani Jun, won.
This is just a guess,
but taken with the principal declaring
an emphasis on academic aptitude here,
I wonder if the
principal wasn't trying to shorten
Five days
the usual five-day culture festival.
That's probably why the whole
school was in such a fiery rage.
That's the cause of the
incident... the "why."
As for the actual act, the "how"...
Classic Lit Club President Sekitani Jun
The "valiant activism" supported by
Heroic leadership
"heroic leadership" was carried out.
Valiant activism
This leads to the final "what."
The students did not engage in violence.
Violence
If anything, it rose to
the level of boycotting.
The school had no choice but
to discuss it with the students,
and abandoned shortening
the culture festival.
However, the toll for that was the
expulsion of the hero, Sekitani Jun.
Incident: June
Expulsion: October
Why was there so much time between
the incident and his expulsion?
If they had expelled Sekitani Jun,
the furor would have gotten even worse.
As such, they probably waited
until after the culture festival,
when all the hoopla had died down.
That's all for my wrap-up.
45 years ago,
that's what happened to my uncle?
Impressive work, Oreki-san.
Yeah, that was pretty nicely done,
Hotaro. Mm-hm, it makes sense.
Not Oreki again! I can't believe it!
I just stumbled into it.
Does anyone have any questions?
No objections.
I hate to say it, but I think he's right.
Mm-hm. Well then,
let's center this year's anthology
around Oreki's theory.
We'll consider the content
in more detail at a later date.
Let's now adjourn the meeting.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you so much, really.
I didn't do it alone.
No, it was all because of you, Oreki-san.
Sorry to have to borrow
an umbrella. Well, bye.
But then,
if that were true, why did I start crying?
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "The Truth About the
Historic Classic Lit Club."
The Truth About the Historic Classic Lit Club