I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
The Classic Lit Club's
Glorious Days of Yore
1. 'Senpai' has departed (from where?)
2. 'Senpai' was a hero 45 years ago,
and a legend 44 year ago
3. 'Senpai' was a 'quiet warrior' and a 'kind hero.'
5. The conflict had a casualty (casualty = 'Senpai'?)
4. 'Senpai' gave Hyouka its name
"heroic tale"
"What"
Boushu ('The Seeding')
The time to sow bearded grains
Hyouka
Solidarity and Salutes, Issue 1
"We"
Reactionary forces
Authoritarians
June
Activism
Hyouka
Solidarity and Salutes
April     October
Apr. May June July Aug. Sept. Oct.
No violence occurred during the incident.
Nonviolent resistance was maintained during the incident.
The incident affected the whole school.
During the incident, 'we' were in solidarity.
Whole school = We
The Sekitani Jun Incident
The Legendary Movement
Showa 42 (1967)
45 years ago
Incident... June
Expulsion... October
Kamiyama High School
Sekitani Jun
Deprived of autonomy
June
October
Meeting to consider the culture festival
five-day
Five days
Classic Lit Club President Sekitani Jun
Heroic leadership
Valiant activism
Violence
Incident: June
Expulsion: October
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The Truth About the Historic Classic Lit Club